I am seeking information about Bob. Let us see what is on the radio.
You're listening to PR News.
No, I don't think I can accept that program.
Nor that one.
The Self Genius Power Rolls!
guitar solo
He must go the way he's expected to go.
Look, I've got a blade.
I could open up a lung.
If you look in the back there, you see I don't have a rug on the floor.
I've got linoleum.
That's for puking from people like you.
God damn it, who's going to clean up this mess?
guitar solo
linoleum
Lend an ear, voodoo child.
Who counts birdshot in a dead man's chest?
You don't want to hear about napalm, you just want to rock.
Circus Magazine says that you're writing a song that you're going to dedicate to the Panthers.
Wake up before the whole fucking world goes into the atomic sewer.
But you two have a very...
abstract thing going here.
I'll flash my cock if you'll burn your draft card.
Worn out, harsh, wrung out.
Hands reaching in the air, grabbing at everything.
A lot of guys with boners.
A lot of girls in heat.
Everybody angry, crying, hard up.
Boners against blue jeans.
I look for rainbows and all I see is pink blue.
Look for flowers.
I see crap all over the oval room rug.
I look for father figures and I get Richard Milhouse, Nixon, and Spiro.
All the half-back new.
I look for love and all I get is napalm.
The lady is a poet.
The mystics could tell us.
The gurus.
The medicine men.
They feel we're in the 15th round, the ninth inning.
In the capitals of the world, men who can no longer get their peckers up have found a new
way to get turned on.
They're the butchers of the world with their 18 pound sledgehammers.
The bacon for tomorrow's breakfast will have the peculiar color of ash.
I could stuff even my own ass.
with the pillow? No, he must go the way he's expected to go. Look, I've got a blade. I
could open up a lock. That's right, he's got a choke on it.
All right.
Thank you.
Yes, yes.
One pill makes you larger and one pill makes you small.
That song.
Oh.
But Dave can't hear it.
But it's okay because it's a...
From what we said, I can capisco it.
It's a counterpoint to the serious subject of sexual harassment,
which is all you hear about in the news this particular week.
Of course, by the time the listeners hear this pre-recorded canned live show, it won't be in the news anymore.
It'll just be back to being, you know, normal.
Not in the news or in their memories.
Right.
Yep.
I got pictures of Al Franken on the back of Mr. Moore's horse.
What's his name?
Rudy Moore, the judge from...
Uh-huh.
Yeah, and Trump was telling them they weren't doing it right.
Yeah, that's not where you grab them.
You gotta grab them right here by the...
It's so sick just to see his smug face when he reviews these cases and then tweets something on his Twitter line.
He thinks everybody's a pervert more than him, and he's the most perverted of them all.
Who's him?
I'm sorry.
Mr. You-Know-Who.
Oh.
The President of the United States, Mr. Otis POTUS.
Mr. POTUS.
The President of the United States.
The Boogeyman.
Oh, it is from The Boogeyman.
Yeah.
Otis Boogeyman.
That's the head.
Yeah, man.
Everybody's seeing Trumps under their beds.
They're afraid there's a Trump under...
Kids are afraid there's a Trump in the closet.
There's always a Trump trying to break into your apartment and do a home invasion.
Yep.
It's real.
It's real fake news, yeah.
Mommy, there's a Trump under my bed.
We can't go to bed now.
I mean, there's no such thing as a Trump.
There's a...
Oh, God, I wish.
If only.
No, it's a planet of the Trumps, man.
War for the planet of the Trumps.
Or he could just be, what's his name, the King of the Orangutans, because isn't he better
known as the avocado perpetrator?
No, as the...
Oh, yeah.
You know, the orange...
the tangerine dream?
...the tangerine smoothie?
Yeah, the tangerine smoothie.
Tangerine nightmare?
Yeah.
That was that other band .
It was really bad, Tangerine...
You remember that band?
Dream was pretty good, yeah, but Tangerine Nightmare was, God, they were awful.
Do you remember Tangerine Dream?
Um, yes, I remember Tangerine Dream.
Boy, you are mighty facile with your memory lobes.
Oh, you say that, yeah.
I used to play them on the hour of slack all the time.
The first time I ever heard that band, however, was the soundtrack of Sorcerer.
It was the first time I, or for that matter, the director, William Friedkin,
had ever heard that kind of synthesized music that was driving and weird and spooky, but really pretty.
Intriguing.
Yeah.
Cut to Sorcerer theme.
No, not really.
But I could.
Yes, you could.
Yeah.
In post.
Well, Dave, how's the weather in Cleveland, Ohio?
Because we're not there.
Or Ashtabula.
I guess tomorrow it will be in the 50s.
And sometime not too far away, perhaps maybe too soon to be far away,
it's going to go all the way up to 60.
People are just going crazy.
Dave's only going to be 50 years old.
We're going to be 70.
We'll be in our 70s.
Yeah.
And then won't that be a sad thing when the little kids come with the sprinkle pedals,
flower petals on your grave or on the water in this case,
because it's been such a huge, you know, since the dam broke in the year.
Hey, did you have a dam?
Yeah, sure.
Went and broke.
And it wasn't even, I mean, they were trying to fix it.
We saw them trying to fix the dam.
But first, before we realized that was why there was a truck in the river,
we saw a truck in the river just trundling down the river.
The river obviously wasn't very deep nor muddy.
And when we turned to wave at him, he beeped his horn at us.
Well, we were filming.
We did?
Yes.
Well, and then there was another truck.
It was like a whole, there were trucks passing each other in the riverbed.
And it turned out they were carrying in and out.
Loads of dredged silt and filth and crud and grud and scrum from the bottom of the Paluxy
and dinosaur bones from the bottom of the Paluxy River.
Paluxy River sludge.
If they use a really...
In the Mississippi and Paluxy, Mississippi, we talk about near Pascagoula.
No, Paluxy River in Texas, north central Texas.
You know, Pal.
Yeah.
Pal.
Wise up, Pal.
It's luxurious.
The Paluxy.
It's...
And our creek empties right into it.
Here goes some more.
Right into the Paluxy.
You better make sure their mascots are all teethed up because you can't find the right number.
Some of them like to just...
That's the first thing they'll do once you get them hypocritic.
They'll just pull that thing right off their chest and throw it under a chair.
It's a hell of a...
I don't know.
And then they'll be asked by the mentor or perhaps the Parma Heights, one of those gentlemen
with the long, hairy beard, you know, where the fur on their faces grows upwards towards
their eyes.
Those are werewolves, guys.
Yeah.
The Paluxy River in north Texas is actually where Noah's Ark sank.
The river was much wider then and covered what is now part of our property.
So basically, we have the wreck of Noah's Ark on our land.
The Bible historians haven't gotten wind of it.
In fact, the Creation Evidence Museum guys keep going to Turkey looking at some collapsed
old log cabin that they think was Noah's Ark packed with dinosaurs and subgeniuses.
Meanwhile, it's right here in their own backyard.
Yeah.
And then you had to pick two subgeniuses of every kind.
So they packed a merkle.
And there aren't any.
There's no such thing.
That was the problem.
There were no two subgeniuses of every kind.
Any similar ones had been put to death, according to Bob's Law.
If any two are alive, one must die.
Or was that Princess Wee's Law?
No, that wasn't mine.
That wasn't mine.
Jack.
But yeah, we're mostly moved in.
We've set the museum up, the Destruction Evidence Museum.
Actually, it's not ready for the public yet, but we're getting there.
It's a process.
Yeah.
We're going to have the insulation man is going to come and spray insulation everywhere
so that the skeletons won't get too cold during the winter and nor too hot in the summer.
Yeah, you got to blow the summer.
You got to keep the foam on them.
Well, no.
Keep them intact.
You know, that is an idea, though, I suppose, is to foam down some of the skeletons so they
don't roll around so much.
We haven't mounted them quite as well as people do in museums.
The bones are just laying there on a slab.
The prehistoric devil skeleton, the cave subgeniuses that we call Adam and Eve, even though they're
both male.
Adam and Steve was their original names.
And they both have like dinosaurs that they ride around in cars like Barney Rubble and
stuff.
I didn't mention you, Princess Wee.
The other day when I was in the post office, the small town post office, I couldn't get
over to the recycling bin and recycle all the junk mail because the creationist guy,
the creation museum guy, was standing there in the post office yakking on his phone in
this forced lurch.
I don't know if you've seen that.
He had a very fast, learned voice that was kind of wrecked by his Texas accent, kind
of like me.
And just bombastically reminded me of that bad filmmaker, Palmer Rocky, who used to do
the same thing in the Dallas post office.
Standing there, he'd talk real loudly to somebody on his phone, and then he'd look at people
walking by and say things like, I'm talking to Hollywood.
I'm talking to Hollywood producers.
And the creation evidence guy was standing there just taking up space.
Taking up air.
Taking up noise.
And blathering away so everybody would notice him.
Good thing he didn't try that in the East Cleveland post office up in Northeastern Ohio.
Boy, they'll kick you out on your butt if you even touch your cell phone inside the
post office.
Yeah, they give you the prattles instead of the rattles.
I touch my, I fondle my cell phone.
It's, you know, you wouldn't have to have a Bible then.
I don't make phone calls on it.
I just fondle it.
I'm not talking.
I'm not wandering.
I don't want to look like a crazy person.
Like everybody else on the street walking around talking to themselves through their
earbuds.
Gesturing madly.
Yeah, gesturing madly just like a street schizophrenic.
Those are what make the streets so much fun, Stan.
Just being able to drive in any direction for less than five minutes and see somebody
with gargantuan hips and purple teeth.
An R. Crumb character, we call him.
Like white with horns and stuff.
Especially in Cleveland and also in Glen Rose.
You see R. Crumb characters everywhere.
All kinds.
We do.
Fat ones, skinny ones, rich ones, poor ones.
But they all look like they were drawn by Robert Crumb.
Yes.
The celebrated underground cartoonist.
How so?
In the fat stretches or the sweeps of the lines?
They just, they look like human cartoons.
They just look like Crumb characters.
The reason for that is Crumb is a cartoonist.
Crumb draws people that, they're cartoons but they're real people that you've seen,
you know?
Yeah, of course.
You know.
I mean, that's...
Persons, persons.
I mean, types.
People whose features are naturally exaggerated.
He just draws them accurately.
Yeah, people that look like...
You still have to do a lot of cross hatching.
There's, there's, yeah.
Well, the ones that are actually have the cross hatching on them, they've really looked,
drawn.
The two dimensional ones that are just flapping in the wind.
Uh huh.
But you don't see many of those.
Most of them are real people that just happen to look sort of funny.
Look a bit cartoon.
Yeah, look a little, not like me.
Yeah, that's your rough life out there, ain't it?
This is funky.
This is music to sexually harass.
But Dave, are you, am I going to have to kick you off the show because some girl's going
to come forward, well, some old woman is going to come forward and say...
He grabbed my booty.
When?
When we were just talking.
Yes, I'm afraid, Stan, I'll have to admit that I'm one of the, one of the Barneys and
Dino Flexes riding on that dinosaur.
I think she said she was 12 years old, which as you know is the signal of consent in the
state of Ohio.
And I tried to tell her, I tried to talk her out of it.
I said, look, baby, you know, there's plenty of 13 year olders who've died on the avenue
and so forth.
And then she just looked at me.
Then she started tackling.
Then she suddenly, she looked like she was about 85 years old.
And a big green...
Yeah, go on, Senator.
Go on, Senator.
I know you're getting choked up, but the committee needs to hear this whole sordid story.
So proceed.
What did you do to the illegal 85 year old, 12 year old?
I personally, I don't recall doing anything.
I do recommend that, I highly recommend that.
We have this photograph here.
Now, no one can fake a photograph.
Well, wait, that's somebody else.
That's the fake one.
Hold on.
Let me get the one with your head pasted on there.
Okay.
Now, is this not you groping and fondling an immature Billy goat kid?
Boy.
Well, that's not you fondling a Billy goat.
I don't think so.
Sure, I don't recognize him.
That's not me there.
Oh, I'm sorry.
That's a Billy Clinton goat.
Okay.
Well, that's not you.
You've got about three more to go.
Yeah.
There, that's the one.
That's me.
And I'm proud of it, damn you.
I feel that one of my young wild oats were sown have certainly fornicated a different
dimension in my logic and my superstition.
And for that reason, I refuse to comment any further on my Fifth Amendment rights in the
way you tend to intimidate me.
Well, I got to admit, when this sexual harassment explosion happened, I was in a very bad mood.
Listen, I was in a state of this sort where even the head of the company that I knew did
not just breastfeed theiran 29 year old and I loved his role, but I was also making Buz grain
Unfortunately a number of givers from 100I still believe I am.
Could some of those people have really turned a blind eye to bi character favorites?
Could they have committed a crime for which they did not take into account that they soy
No, go ahead.
tenderloin. Who'd want to live in a district where prostitution is so readily
available? None of the senators on this committee
in any way are irresponsible or
refuse to neglect the unavoidable circumstances
involving this committee.
I say, Senator,
you're not wearing any pants.
I'm not wearing any panties either, sir.
Please stay seated. Please stay seated.
Bring some kind of jail clothes in here for the senator.
What do you think about that? Check it out.
That's horrible. That's disgusting.
It is horrible. It's offensive.
It's horrible. It's disgusting. Let's run him for president.
He's the only one of us who can beat Trump.
He's even uglier, fatter, lazier, bigger mouth braggart.
More ignorant. Didn't know it was possible.
But, yeah. Go, Senator Moore.
President Moore. President Roy Moore.
Moore, Moore, Moore. That's what we say here at Moore Science High.
Yeah.
That's right, Senator. Moore Science High.
The tiny,
the few,
the few I refuse to get.
That's my message to everybody.
As long as you're going to keep on having these sexual fabrication
between different types of women
and different age men than the average men's room.
We have a spurious and a jocular problem on our hands here in beautiful America.
I think everybody should stand up and sit down a few times to go to their window
and very carefully part their hair before saying, I'm as mad as hell
and I need some peace.
That's right.
And I'm going to pass out.
I think everybody in America should listen to this rather sobering song by the Rainmakers
that I dug out from a pretty old album from the 90s called Skin.
Strangely enough, even though this is 20 years old, the first two songs deal directly with today's news headlines.
The Rainmakers
I
Take a look at what you talk
Granddaddy at the minstrel show
Watch the darkest greatly old banjo
Grandson at the strip club
A little racism with a different rub
It's the same difference with a different rub
Granddaddy never owned no slaves
Grandson never committed rages
Quiet men in their own time
Keeping quiet is its own kind of crime
It's the same difference with a different rub
And
It's
This ain't about no books that need burning
Less about blame and more about light
The freedom of one at the cost of another
This ain't about sin, it's about civil rights
That ain't what a woman is
Down through our histories
We have been told
That women hold mysteries men cannot know
But boys learn true secrecy
How to hide lies
And cracks in their souls and behind shaded eyes
That filter all light through the sins of their fathers
Shining on down on good sons and daughters
We were true believers
Yeah, that this song would go
Oh, it was a high holy fever
That purified the soul
But bass turned to piss off
All equality of laugh
As girls danced the go-go to our golden calf
We borrowed the tune from the hymns of our fathers
We are not wrong, we are not wrong
Rebels, just good sons and daughters
Good sons, good sons and daughters
Good sons, good sons, yeah
The revolution came
Oh, the revolution went
And I'd never, oh, just that 50%
Oh, the truth that comes from penis
From porno to rape
And bought into Hollywood
Heftless like hate
Millions of Maryland's who died for their lovers
Seducing the culture of good sons and daughters
Good sons, good sons and daughters
Who travelled to the General Assembly
To school with their guys
Post th'olutionary
Post they and their sake
We have no proof to say
Like they never were
Yeah, us, you've been repeating the same thing
Until daybreak
I was reading through the paper
And I happened to see
A police officer
That looked a whole lot like me
And so I started dodging questions
And lying on top of lies
And I thought what I thought
Was a good alibi
I never knew your mother
Your sister or daughter
I ain't no killer
Hmm
Yeah this guy's old enough
That was my community founder father person
I'm the head of the local Boy Scout troop
And here took place
A service mission
178A dash slash comma slash five dash D.
Never mind.
I don't need to break up the time.
Well, we're going to weather it.
We're going to weather this whole world war and ecological disaster and zombie apocalypse
and the concentration camps.
I'm sorry, not the concentration camps.
This whole sicko story.
They don't let you concentrate in there.
You can't.
You have to play video games all day long.
Yeah, Patriot camps.
It's just call of duty, but you're the victim the whole time.
And you can't never take the knee either.
Well, and when you get killed in that game, you don't come back and do the round again.
Well, what don't you want for something better than that?
I mean, that's what life is about.
It's a slice of life is just a series of vile tasks.
I'll swear it.
Huh?
I thought you sounded briefly and nasally like William Burroughs there.
Jack Kerouac was a crazy kind of guy.
He drank more than most men can usually drink without falling asleep or falling down the steps.
I'm not sure if you can get that from him.
But William Burroughs?
Yeah, I love that famous line he does.
Repent, quit your job, slack off.
Slack off.
The world ends tomorrow and you may die.
It's the most mucilaginous, slick, slimy end of the world you can imagine.
Here.
Let me see.
Let me set this apple on top of you.
Yes.
I'm William Tell.
Now, where's my cross-eyed crossbow?
Now, it's probably unfair to bring up the guy accidentally shooting his wife in the head.
But he's dead.
Who cares?
And hey, Dick Cheney shot a guy in the face.
Nobody said anything about Dick Cheney shooting a guy in the face.
It's because he was a lawyer.
It was another lawyer that got shot in the face and nobody gave up.
He was able to expunge it from everyone's memory just magically.
Well, I'm sure he paid the lawyer a lot of money to go, oh, it's okay.
Yeah.
I don't mind looking like Phantom of the Opera, Mr. Vice President.
Anybody can get completely plastered and shoot the guy next to him thinking he's shooting at a goddamn dove.
Yeah, you ever see how they hang them upside down and keep them in a place and then when it's time to hunt,
they bring them right out in front of them.
Oh, and now that's not fair, though.
I mean, not all hunters do that.
Real hunters don't go to those places.
Real hunters lease Stang Ranch and go out there and shoot them animals fair and square.
All four of them.
Actually, there's a...
Yeah, I've heard that coming.
Especially when you rode to the defense of hunting adulterators before you even got to the scene.
I'm a good part of it.
You just...
You moralized your objective.
Furniture is very funny.
It's not like they had to go looking too far.
I don't know what he's talking about.
All I know is, you know, it's kind of sad to go deer hunting in Texas because, strangely enough,
the deer in Texas are tiny.
They're like chihuahuas.
They're little bitty deer.
They're not big springing things.
They're little tiny springings.
They can still spring over a fence.
But they're sadly small.
And they are herbivores.
And they are completely defenseless.
And they are tricked into walking up to these deer feeding machines every afternoon as the sun is going down.
Or when it's coming up.
Because the deer feeding machines suddenly go...
And a whole bunch of corn falls out.
And the deer go to eat the corn and the men go to shoot the deer.
And the deer go to shoot the deer.
But it actually, it's not that easy.
You've got to know what you're doing.
And then you've got to clean up the horrible mess of the dead carcass.
And eat it.
My problem is, I never did like venison.
Or blood.
If it's treated with the right wines and vinegar...
Oh, sure, of course.
But I'm a hypocrite.
I want to buy my dead animals.
Killed by...
Somebody else.
And wrapped in cellophane.
All the blood squeezed out.
Ready to throw on the griddle.
You know, I'm a hypocrite.
I don't want to look at the naked lunch at the end of my fork.
Who does?
You don't want to think about lines and lines of chickens being...
With their heads turned upside down.
Scribbling and scrabbling and trying to get away from having their necks...
Their necks croaked.
It's terrible.
I had a friend who went to work...
For a...
Kosher...
Chicken farm.
Which he thought, well, it's got to be more humane.
And it didn't make any difference.
Less machines, more people doing the dirty work.
Right.
Well, somebody's got...
They do their killing by hand and they pray first.
Right.
That makes a big difference.
But somebody's got to do it.
If you're going to eat chicken...
Oh, chicken, I'm so sorry.
Dave, it's okay.
If you study paleontology,
you'd know that the age of dinosaurs
was followed not by the age of mammals,
but the age of giant birds
who kept the mammals tiny for a long time
because for millions and millions of years,
chickens ate us.
Very big chickens,
and they were very weak, little versions of...
Well, primates of some kind.
But they were our ancestors, nonetheless,
and chickens ate us for so long
that that means it's okay for us to eat chickens now.
For another four and a half...
Four and a half years.
After four and a half years,
we will have eaten so many billions of chickens
that the karma will have come around
and something else will start eating us again,
probably aliens or viruses.
I think it'll just be a bigger chicken than the first time.
I think the big chickens are growing.
The small chickens are lessening
or getting smaller in our own minds
because that's the transversal areas
that we use in our matriculations.
When we get to one point or another,
the next thing you know, we're going to die.
Well, we got some other point,
but I forgot what it was.
I thought so.
I knew where that one was going.
Nowhere.
Right down a big black hole.
The hole in Dave's mind.
And mind.
I thought it had a cramp.
And the listeners.
Dave's sentences go right down the black hole
and all of those minds involved.
All the show hosts and the listeners.
He was going,
some way he just got sidetracked.
At least it's going somewhere.
But it's...
Yeah.
But it can never, ever go home.
Something derailed his thought.
Yeah, the punchline never came.
The train never left the...
Well, the train left the station,
but it never arrived.
It got derailed along the way.
Yeah, but that's only if...
If you're an over-fuehrer,
von Gruppenmeister,
von over-fuehrer,
von, you know,
non-liminal sightings,
synthetic leakage.
It was in...
The Twilight Zone.
It was?
Yeah.
That's where your sentence went.
A whole bunch of them.
Oh, yeah.
I see what you mean.
My sentence that I just uttered,
the tail end of it,
made no sense,
so it kind of just trailed off into idiocracy.
Not the movie, but...
Well, like everything.
Everything kind of trails off into idiocracy nowadays.
Yeah.
We were ahead of our time
with the Church of the Subgenius.
You'd think we'd be richer and famouser
and more presidential by now.
Oh, we didn't do enough harassing.
Not...
Although there's lots of people
who'd argue otherwise.
But, uh...
I didn't...
I've only had to kick out
about 10 or 15 people
out of Church of the Subgenius
for being sexual predators.
But I actually,
I actually have.
I have...
But here's the thing.
I did it real quietly.
Is that a crime?
I didn't make a big, big deal out of it.
I just said,
don't come back.
Don't call yourself Pope anymore.
That's a discreet and to the point,
and you're telling them,
you know, you're not saying,
or I'm going to punch you right in the eye
or anything like that.
If they don't get it,
then, you know,
they're the ones who are hopped up.
Well, the ones who don't,
get it,
the ones who don't know
about all the times
that I have policed all that stuff.
And they see a girl in a bikini
with a funny meme statement
on a Facebook page
and get mad at me
because I allowed dumb jocks
to post dumb pictures
on the internet.
And I didn't,
I didn't immediately do something
about each and every one
of those examples.
No, I waited until
one of the other people
or administrators noticed it
and went, oh, that's stupid.
Let's just cut that.
If that guy does it again,
I'll ban him.
But, you know, if you...
I've been harassed
and then fairly treated.
Yep, I can tell.
But people who feel
they've been harassed
and then fairly treated.
My snowflakes are all melting.
Yeah, you're melting.
The victim church of the...
The kid glove.
That was it.
Yeah, they splintered off.
Like iron fist in the velvet glove.
I'm sure they're enjoying
their great sense of humor
all together.
Not.
Yeah, they've got that
blacksmith commune going now.
Hey, watch it, buddy.
Hey, watch your language.
Hey, nobody needs their dog buddy
and expects you to get away with it
for longer than...
Hey, man, I'm a Smith, okay?
We prefer to be called
Stan.
Stan, okay?
It's just more polite.
Oh, wait.
No, I'm the only one who does that.
Well, I've been having to grapple
with my two names lately, Dave.
You know, I had a human street name.
It's pretty ordinary.
Except in the circumstances
under the...
In the context of
Church of the Subgenius,
the name that my parents gave me
sounds fake as hell.
Douglas St. Clair Smith.
It's even got a religious thing in it.
St. Clair.
And the family wasn't even Catholics.
They don't even believe in saints.
It sounds so stately in Irish.
It sounds like
Mrs. and Claire Smith.
Right, but I needed a name that's...
The Catholic in Dublin
claims that the werewolves
are not real werewolves.
After all,
the stigmas of the toad...
No, no.
That person wouldn't be named Smith.
He'd be named Budlington or something.
But...
Budlington.
Yeah.
But, uh...
Yeah, there's...
There...
I was about to say
there aren't many Professor Smiths,
but we did...
We did work with a...
We all worked with a Professor Smith
for years, didn't we?
Yes.
Professor Chess.
I was about to say
there would not be anything
as even a barbecue dentist
or a fallopian tube...
Well, there's never been
a king named Smith,
but there will be
a king named Stang.
King...
Oh, wait.
There's already a King Drummond.
It's going to have to be
like two kings.
Like,
when tonight...
When Ignatius D. did that.
Yes.
That worked out great, didn't it?
Oh, wait.
No, they poisoned each other
simultaneously.
Dang.
Man.
See, at City Hall,
everybody's just
rockin' sockin' robots.
That's all there is to it.
See what they do?
Everybody is
rockin' sockin' robots.
Yep.
Just think,
that's a horrible future
for us to visage,
don't you think?
To what?
It's a horrible future
for us to visage.
To visage.
All of us,
you, me,
and...
He and we
and everybody
don't you see?
To imagine ourselves
as a rockin'
rockin' robot.
Well...
It really sucks, man.
Just think of it
because it's kind of true.
You know what I mean?
Well, that was
Tenacious D.'s point
when they said that line
in that famous,
famous song
that you probably
don't know.
I obviously don't know.
I wouldn't have tried
to start...
Are you familiar
with the band
called Tenacious D.?
Of course.
Okay.
Well, I never know.
You're kind of
old, you know.
I didn't know about them
until they'd already
broken up
and been, you know,
old for ten years.
older than even you.
Princess,
we can sing
every one of their songs
by heart,
but we didn't learn them
until after they were
already old and broke up.
Figures,
like everything else,
you know.
We get on to
the new cool thing
long after everybody else
dropped it.
Oh, that's because
we already did
the new cool thing
ten years before them.
Yeah.
Twenty years before.
Yeah, we were
Tenacious D.
before Tenacious D. was.
Wait a minute.
What am I talking about?
That's right.
Yeah, and we were
South Park, too.
We just weren't
quite as good.
Or in California
or something.
None of us were
as in California.
Well, now you're
taking me to
the blessed
oblivion again
when I can't
come out right out
and say,
I don't know
what the hell
you're talking about.
Right on.
And friends,
that's why you're
listening to
The Hour of Slack
from the Church
of the Subgenius.
And we've got
a new address, folks.
Got that pencil ready?
We'll be back
to Cleveland Heights,
but we're mostly
at Post Office Box 807
Glen Rose, Texas 76043.
And we tried to get
Box 808
for reasons
that you,
you would understand
if you wrote down
those numbers
and then put quotes
on either side
of the eight.
But it was taken.
And that means
I have to find out
the name of
whoever owns 808
and arrange
a little vacation.
Perhaps he may
be convinced
to disappear.
You might just want
to make him an offer
he can't refuse.
Well, that would be hard
because we're not
going to be able
The offers I'd make
that I could afford
to make
are easily refused.
Yep.
That's it for 23 years.
And friends,
this has been
Hour of Slack
number 1,650.
1,650 shows.
Almost a fresh one
almost every single week
for 37 years
or some such craziness.
Oh, God.
Every...
And it's in 9 o'clock
at 9 o'clock.
9 o'clock on Sundays
in most...
in a lot of the stations.
Yeah.
And two of the stations
are 89.3 FM.
Strangely enough.
Almost...
In completely different cities.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yep.
Yep, friends.
We're back in Texas
but we're not in Dallas.
So,
everything's cool, baby.
Cool.
Funky.
Yeah.
We didn't get down.
Boy, that hurt my jaw.
Hey, hey.
I know what offer
we can make.
NeighborWorld.
NeighborWorld is still in print.
Woo-hoo!
Yeah, I've got 20 copies
in a box up there.
All right.
Well, 18 copies
because I sent...
I think I sent one
to the...
to...
Canada today.
Ah.
Yeah, it was Canada.
They cost about...
They cost like 11 bucks
to send them to Canada.
And they pay...
They have to pay extra.
But yeah, Dave.
Friends,
NeighborWorld is out.
It's Dave's book.
It's great.
It's amazing.
And I know how many
of you have bought it.
Only about 35 or so.
That's ridiculous.
Come on.
It really is...
I think I've given out
that many copies.
I've given out
to my friends
who aren't my friends
but decided they can get
something free
because I'm like,
I'm so, you know.
Right.
Well, I also know
how many you got.
Not that many.
So, so...
Yeah, just
subgenius.com
You'll...
Currently, right now
on subgenius.com
I still have a...
a promo
for the Subgenius movie
even though they raised
their 200,000 bucks.
Can you believe that?
I can't believe it.
And thanks, everybody.
Thank you, buddy,
who contributed to that.
But yeah, they raised
the 200,000.
But I've left
one of the fundraiser
videos of me
and mighty celebrity
Matt Groening.
So whenever any
of my enemies
goes to
subgenius.com
let me show you.
It's always the same.
It hadn't changed
in 25 years.
Just look at this.
And nobody cares
about subgenius.
And there's me
and the creator
of The Simpsons
saying,
come on,
give your money
to subgeniuses now.
Now,
hawk it up.
Hack it up.
Hawk it up.
Hawk it up this way.
Yeah, man.
And there was...
And they saw you, too.
The people who followed
the fundraiser
saw Lonesome Cowboy Dave
sitting there
telling him to
kickstart this program
with your left foot.
That was real funny.
Is that the foot I use?
Yeah.
Everybody loved...
Everybody loved everything
and they all...
And they spent...
And they got the 200,000 bucks.
Yep.
Wow.
Amazing.
That was the goal?
Yeah.
They had to have that much...
They had to raise that much
or they wouldn't get any of it.
Now, it could be that...
Right.
That they knew
they could top off
whatever was left
if they had to.
Or somebody would.
Bob would.
If nobody else did,
Bob would have topped it off.
But they actually made it
fair and square.
And I had to...
In fact, I just...
I had to sign
all these rare subgenius things
that we were mailing
to the control room.
And I had to write
to the contributors as rewards.
Like 50 first edition
subgenius pamphlet number one.
Signed
by Reverend Stang.
Even though the copyright inside
says Douglas St. Clair Smith.
That's how you know
it's a first edition.
So, there you go.
Subgenius.com.
Neighborworld.
Subgenius Movie.
Book of the Subgenius.
They're all out there.
And this is the part of the show
that won't be on the public radio...
On the radio broadcast.
Because we can't
try to raise money there.
But we can do it on the internet.
Yes.
What delights
the weight of the listener
and reader
of all such tomes
and so forth.
Right.
What delicious delight
awaits them
is they sit down
in that plunky, fatty old chair
and lift their legs up real high
and crank out a Weezer sound
and just start reading
different bibliotechs.
That's what you do.
Start reading them bibliotechs
and texts
and textees.
And you'll grow hair on your chest
and other spots.
You'll squeak out Weezer sounds.
Huh?
Right.
With joy.
You'll be squeaking Weezer sound in joy.
When you spend that $35
and procure your
Subgenius ordainment kit,
which makes you a minister
and you can perform weddings
and you can also read
the 25 or 30 things
that come with the kit
that are pretty good.
And...
I've got...
I've got to change the address
on every single one
of those sheets of paper.
That's what I said.
So, Dave,
it's the end of the show.
Again.
We have to end it,
although we'll come back...
What's he...
He's on about something again.
Well, he's not talking
into his phone.
Dave, what are you on about?
I was talking to a utensil
and you couldn't hear me,
could you?
No.
Oh, that's too bad.
I thought it was going to make
a real exciting sound.
No, Reverend Stang was telling you
that the show had come around
to the end unbelievably again.
Yeah, but we're going to
cut back to it afterwards.