I can't get no education
Can't step in for major voice control
Bobcats, Bobcats, Bobcats, the Bobcats, Bobcats coming
Oh, the Bobcats are coming, cats and kitties
Big Bobcats
Bobcats, Bobcats, Bobcats fans
Bad, step up, I like the Bobcats
The Bobcats, step up, bad, bad, bad, bad, bad
Bobcat, Bobcat, Bobcat fans
Bobcats, Bobcats coming
Meat, meat, meat, meat, all meat
It's plain arithmetic, when war needs go up
The amount of...
...meat left for civilians goes down
The War Food Administration estimates
That there will be 127 pounds of meat per civilian this year
That's against 143 pounds in 1944
That's less for us
And that is the number one job of your meat industry
And now back to the...
...so genius
Power of...
...watch
I always sing...
...Don't Fence Me In
This lonesome cowboy dance song
Don't fence me in
It was awfully gay
There was always conflict
I never liked violence
The love you got
Oh, he's got give, too
I know it's foreign
I watched Bwimin Jest
I used to be strong
I Chaoukan 오き
came out and she was surrounded.
Don Imus came out.
Mr. Imus came out.
Very proud.
Don Imus fired.
Manipulate life in ways that do not respect.
We must continue to work for a culture
to manipulate life in ways that do not respect
the most vulnerable among us.
The airways can be used to commercialize and mainstream
sexism and racism.
This is about gloating.
It is really in...
Don Imus joining Al-Qaeda.
Conspiracy to use a weapon of mass destruction.
I guess you have to just worry about that everywhere now.
Don Imus, one of the loudest...
Transmit the smut.
Campaign to clean up the culture.
I really didn't listen to him that much.
Don Imus.
Ky convinces the commiee.
I was worried borrowers.
I was worried ?"
But it's burning me and telling
And roun Gottiinע
an
ing
To
That's a pretty good description of the show.
It's a genius ignorant.
Yuck.
Insipid, dull, or uninteresting.
Troglodyte.
Benighted.
Ignorant.
Troglodyte.
A brutish person.
Old, mildewed, antiquated, run down, or out of date.
Nailing Kenny G securely to the center of your brain.
Keep the power.
Keep the people ignorant.
Ignorant people.
Wow.
Dog.
Is it hot in here or is it me?
Great, wonderful.
I'm not sure.
Get as much fertilizer on you as you possibly can.
Dog.
To believe anything.
Get freaked out.
Not a new idea.
Vibrate, vibrate.
Motion.
Vibration.
Your finger, your finger, your tongue.
Vibrate, vibrate.
We are Freak, Freak, Freak, Freak, Freak.
Hello and welcome, I'm Bob.
The law of cult is shit.
I said I am Bob.
The truth is I'm not really Bob.
Bob's not me.
But this isn't Bob.
And money, money, money.
You see, dick.
Intellectual abuse.
Drip, drip.
We, we, we.
Terrible ideas.
You will never make up your mind right now over and over again.
Because they're called products.
Help me.
I want you to help me vibrate.
This is Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
I did ignorant people.
I did ignorant people too.
I've done many ignorant people and they've done me right back squarely between the eyeballs.
Norrell Preff did those ignorant people and most of the cuts coming in there, except for the ones that were done by Fernandez and Leamer.
Both quite salacious, salacious artists, or quite salubrious, isn't that the word?
Salubrious.
I've lost my words.
I can't even remember which station I'm at.
I never lose your words, laddy.
If you're trying to find them again.
Is this Dallas or Cleveland?
This is Portland, Stang.
No, no, not Portland.
Oh, man, look at the coffee you're drinking.
Schnout Whistle Cafe?
Come on, man, you're in Portland.
And we're heading for Tacoma tomorrow to have a blast.
Ugh.
A literal...
I've had some terrible times in that part of the country.
And a few good ones.
It's as bad as Norway when it comes to, like, poking and fondling strangers and, like, trying to barbecue them with little sticks.
Do you like that idea of going to a new town and maybe asking for directions and having people, like...
Point at you and poke you with sticks?
Story of my life, man.
Well, it's the story of every subgenius' life, and that's why we demand recompense from the universe at large.
Or it could be the universe minoris, the smaller universe, which is the one lodged at the top of the Bodhis-Larma Karma.
Um, karma.
It's a current that you can actually fly by focusing on.
Did you know that?
Uh, say what?
By focusing on the karma.
I wasn't focusing. I'm sorry, Dave.
The electromagnetic current in the brain known as karma.
One may be able to fly, as in the days of the ancient rishis.
Can you believe that?
Bob could fly when he was a little kid.
Yeah, but he had such small wings.
Well, he lost the ability when he got old enough to know he wasn't supposed to be able to do that.
But when Bob Dobbs was a tiny child, up until about the age of two...
Oh, I thought you were gonna say 38, yeah.
...he could fly and pass miracles and so forth.
And he even... there's stories that he robbed banks.
The flying cherubic...
A little toddler with a .38 pistol.
...baby with a little pipe in his mouth, flying into banks...
That's so cute to think of.
...and with a gun, and robbing them.
Now, that's possibly apocryphal.
Yeah, did he... let's just put it bluntly...
Stories that they told before the apocalypse.
Let's just put it bluntly. Did he whack any team in?
Did he actually have to shoot his way out of a bunch of pinker teams, so to speak?
Well, you know, those are the...
Those are the...
So to speak?
...voke tales that people like to tell.
I'm sure it wasn't quite that exciting.
He was like...
He was like, you know, an adolescent pretty boy Floyd.
Well, I think that's what he was...
If he really did rob banks, then that's kind of what he was emulating.
Because this would have been in the 20s.
Oh, yeah, for sure.
He would have been a pretty boy Floyd guy.
And he would have also imagined himself being murdered by the FBI later,
and calling it a shootout.
Well, you know, anything that Bob imagines...
I like to say stuff like that, you know, to stir things up.
Bob doesn't really imagine anything.
They happen as he...
What we would call imagines things, they actually happen.
That also works for God, but believe me, don't mix the two up.
Bob is not really very closely related to the God who created the universe.
He's the God who created slack, which is kind of like the opposite of this universe.
But it's one of the most important cohesive factors and elements in the universe,
well, you know, of relative importance.
It's the...
It's the importance that you...
You...
Speaking of importance, wasn't there something important that we were supposed to talk about?
Was it the weather?
No, the game?
I don't even know what those teams...
What games those teams play.
A small number of mutants are meeting in a small part of a small area...
That's right!
Somewhere near Austin...
How do you pronounce this word?
Austin, Texas.
Right.
In Texas, the state of Texas.
Right near the state of denial.
In early May, May 5th, in fact, weekend, there's...
I am getting ready for an event called Tex Day.
Tex Day.
Tex Day 3.
A day to forget.
No, not really.
It's a survival drill, really, because you don't know what day...
Well, wait, we'll come to that later.
Okay.
But the world is ending any minute now, and we should be ready and should practice by
doing the things that you would do if you thought the world was going to end, right?
Pillage, all the, you know, drink...
Well, when they want you to...
Go crazy, do everything that you were always afraid to do when you thought the world was
going to continue, and you'd get caught.
Well, they once asked me and my girlfriend, do you practice tantra?
And I said, yeah, practice.
We got our little suits with the names on the back and everything, and the numbers and
the whole deal, you know?
We got the sports shoes and everything.
Professional sports tantric.
So if you're going to practice tantra...
Yeah.
If you plan to escape this sphere, if you're planning to leave here any time soon when
it's too late to get off for so many of them...
Well, speaking of leaving this planet, as we have...
I have this press release, news release, kind of a speech for the subgenius ministers here.
It came from Corey Lee Smith's Unclaimed Mysteries.
But friends, global warming.
Global warming has finally been explained by the pundits.
The sun is getting warmer.
Therefore, we must fight the solar radiation there on the sun so we won't have to fight
it here.
The liberation of the sun will be a cakewalk.
The sunspots will welcome us with parades and flowers.
The prominences will become McDonald's and the flares will provide power to pay for the
liberation.
The lost tribe of solar green energy.
The sun will be our natural allies.
Our intelligence indicates that there is nuclear activity hidden in the core.
If we hesitate to invade the sun, it will be too late to save ourselves.
To oppose this fully justified preemptive strike is to embolden the enemy, then to proclaim
your treason.
Death to the sunnies!
And the shy-ites who are too shy to fight.
Friends, that news report came from Corey Lee Smith's Unclaimed Mysteries at www.unclaimedmysteries.net.
Keep your head and arms inside the mixer at all times.
That's good advice for a DJ, a radio DJ.
It certainly is.
I think that's a lesson for everyone to learn and know well as we conquer and pass these
next few weeks, Dave.
As we pass.
Days, years, and moments learning to solubriate and renunciate each and every battlefield
we cross.
We will pass those fiery gas balls.
We shall pass them into the...
From sun to sun through Outar space.
Outar space, pardon me.
Yep.
We're pronouncing that by this new subgenius fad now is to pronounce everything that ends
with E-R as if it ended with A-R. So you say Outar space.
Oh, yeah.
I see.
So if Einstein were perhaps to predilicate upon the idea of setting off a nuclear explosion
somewhere between Earth and the sun, that the atmosphere would explode, would ignite,
and all the little atoms and molecules in between would become united in friendship,
harmony, brotherhood, solidarity, and peaceniks.
If only we had more of those many things, friends.
I think we need...
Solidarity, peaceniks.
If everybody was peacenik, why, there'd be no war.
Just think of that.
Except you know there would be.
There'd be somebody going, I'm more of a peacenik than you are.
Nuh-uh.
I'm more into peace than you.
I was...
You want to prove it?
Yeah.
Who do you think...
Do you know who you're talking to?
I may laugh at bees and eggs, dude.
That was from something else.
But I was accosted today by...
I wasn't accosted.
I was actually extended a warm hand of friendship by a soldier of some kind who you hardly ever
see.
And he looked angry at me.
And I was wondering maybe they were sending his units, if he has more than one, back to
the squid zone there.
Maybe that's why he acted so...
Well, they don't want soldiers that are jolly and sweet and all sappy.
I'll open the door for you, pal.
Yeah, they want soldiers with blood and guts and veins in their teeth.
Right.
Literally hanging from their teeth.
Well.
I didn't know what to say to the man, so I didn't say anything.
I just hid in the closet and waited for the next thunderclap.
You can say, I support the men in blue.
Or green, or whatever color they were.
You could say that.
You could say, I support my cerebral cortex and the green, blue, and different things
that it has to do with.
I mean, if you want to.
I'm against the war, but I hope you kill them before they kill you, just because.
That is probably the safest thing to say.
You couldn't say that.
Yeah.
I'm against you having to go there, but since you are going there, kill everyone before
they kill you.
And may God bless you.
Yes, may God bless you and your duties.
I love you, and welcome to the United States Marine Corps.
I had a lot more sympathy and understanding for professional shoulders after I edited
that film about the war in Vietnam as seen from the Viet Cong point of view.
It was quite frightening.
Yeah, it was quite frightening.
In fact, I was in a clappy-eyed stupor of indolence and sweat for three days after perspiring
through that part.
It actually took me there to donate and untree and all those places.
Yeah.
Think about the guys that had to actually fight it.
All we had to do was edit and write scripts about it after the fact.
I can imagine you guys were written out numerous times by the powers that be.
I was written out because I had flat feet, and I was stamped 4F, even though I was number
30 in the Vietnam lottery.
There you go.
They were about to pack me off to Hamburger Hill, boy.
Yep.
And you know, the funny thing is all those other young Texans that were going through
the draft physical with me, except for one obnoxious hippie besides me, they all seemed
to be pretty eager to go.
They were ready to start marching against the monsters.
Little tiny tanks.
Tiny.
Wait a minute.
Let me sing this song right.
The gargoyles are coming.
Tiny tanks.
Lots of little tiny tanks.
Tiny jets.
Lots of little tiny jets.
Maybe only Ooo.
These Utah puns might be good...
Citizen gotta improve.
cle Crossing, 20 years later.
Little tiny jets.
By and by,fer, I will show ya some other pulping a
py.
はい I don't understand the Russian
language.
load that word -"large", man I really love how lift it
does it?
This is the music from Godzilla, by the way.
It's the Godzilla theme.
I had no idea Godzilla was...
That's why I was singing about tiny planes and tiny tanks.
Yeah.
Because it's a guy in a big pajamas fighting the tiny tanks and planes.
Yeah, I thought it was a song about the matriarchs.
You know, the ancient elementals.
Well, sure.
Sure, it could be.
Well, let's go to...
Speaking of Texas,
I, you know, since I could stand to benefit from a large crowd showing up at Tex Day,
which I frankly...
That'll never happen.
We did, however, make a video about the Tex Day.
This would be the third Tex Day at Dragon's Wild Ranch,
formerly High Rock Ranch in Red Rock, Texas.
And it's a funny subgenius event.
It's not as big as X Day at Brushwood,
but it looks a lot like X Day at Brushwood,
with not quite as many people.
And we're going to place the soundtrack of the videos,
the edited Tex Day documentary,
which you can look at on YouTube,
if you just do a search for subgenius on YouTube,
or Tex Day.
You'll probably find these.
Actually, the longer version is on Google.
But let us go briefly.
Well, first we need to have a...
You should warn them first, Dane,
that if they get the wrong bit,
bite of this chip type...
No, if they get the wrong one,
there could be serious...
Is there anything serious about it at all?
No.
You won't get no education at Tex Day.
Now a look at some current conditions.
There is a severe sport warthrum
just south of Austin,
all the way down towards Laredo,
and outside of Corpus Christi.
Isolated, severe northern Oklahoma.
In fact, Garfield County,
slowly drifting towards the north.
Now there is some New Hampshire lingering in Boston.
Further west, St. Louis,
still pulling towards Reno.
We will continue to see Texas,
which has been emerging out of northern Mexico.
Folks, we've had some nasty Kansas
across portions of Missouri.
Thank you.
Thank you all for coming out.
That's my gift.
I'll give you a hug for the future.
Annual Tex Day survival drill and revival.
If the saucers land,
we are not responsible for crushed tents.
Praise Bob, praise Bob, praise Bob,
praise Bob, praise Bob, praise Bob,
praise Bob, praise Bob, praise Bob, praise Bob.
Hey, that's not supposed to happen.
What makes you think it's not supposed to happen?
Hey, this is something to take advantage of, Dave.
We'll take advantage of it.
It's like a messed up...
We're an hour right now.
Messed up, uh...
We're taking advantage of it right now.
See, now you forced us to not take it...
Here we go.
This is the great groovy Neptune
performing live at Tex Day.
When I start to realize
What till now has been disguised
Keep looking through the sky
That the saucers fly and buy
And maybe by and by
You will see the light
At the end of the pipe
That leads to Bob Dobbs
Bob Dobbs
Talking about the salesman
To the gods
He's still in check
The coffin lid
On the conspiracy
Of normality
Oh, who could it be
But Bob!
Oh, my.
We're getting some strange effects
On this CD player here.
I don't know, uh, quite...
It's not really going.
You can't say it's going.
It's just, um...
Uh-huh.
It's locked in a sphinx.
Stir.
He's crazy about Bob.
He'll pick your pocket.
Yeah.
See, Bob's pretty slick.
He's like the opposite of neutral.
You got, like, good, evil, neutral.
You can have the opposite of neutral.
Slack.
The third edge of the coin, my friend.
There's a three-sided coin to life.
And I choose the...
The slack plane.
I choose the luck plane.
Noise, noise, noise.
There you go.
Raise Bob.
I'll certainly be editing this show.
Oh, what we're hearing now is the theremin
Being played by Sister Decadence's
Breastages.
Yeah, but you cannot hear the boobs.
Or, well, you can imagine in your mind, the...
Breasts.
When I get on the spaceships, I'll have as many boobs as I want.
A fair amount of...
A carpet.
A veritable carpet of boobs.
I'll tell you, legs.
Think of the masturbatory potential.
I was...
You're funny.
You should mention that.
Today might be X Day!
X Day could...
July 5th, 1998, 7 a.m. might be two minutes from now.
Are you ready to meet Bob?
Have you prepared...
Do you have that $30 sub-genius minister's card in your pocket?
Are you going to be left behind going,
Well, I've been lifted up and up.
There's piles of clothes around here on the ground.
I'm laying...
I'm all by myself.
Are you ready to meet...
Have you spent your time wisely?
Or else, have you blown everything off?
Either one.
Because anything else is a waste.
It's...
Well, it's probably a waste anyway, friends.
Well, who was that guy?
That man sounded febrile, if that's the correct word.
He sounded as if...
That was a man of Bob, my friend.
Bitten by thousands of spiteful mosquitoes, thousands of wary, angry crustaceans.
Well, now, if I sometimes sound like I have a chip on my shoulder, it may be because there's
only a few of me, and there are millions and millions of that one guy.
Listen to that, man.
My...
This CD is...
Well, you sounded...
This was made for this night.
Okay, this is cut...
This is cut...
I'm going to bring up the other background music.
Well, this was actually making my arm twitch.
So what's up with that?
I think either I have a...
This Text Day stuff was burned by myself onto a bad CD, or the CD player itself, the self-same
CD player, just is not in good shape and doesn't like...
You know, this is college radio, and friends, we do have pledge drives for...
I...
For a reason.
We have it for a reason.
We follow the whales around the park for a reason.
Maybe Bob doesn't want us to play the sex...
Grab him their keys.
...at Text Day.
Did I say Sex Day?
No, it's Text Day because of Texas.
Even though there is a sex temple...
There is actually...
Dave...
Oh, I'm sorry.
There is a sex temple at the site of Text Day, and I've...
To tell the truth, I've been afraid to go in there.
When there was anybody else in there.
So is it widely copulated by copulating copulators?
I mean, you walk up to this temple and you say, may I be sexed, or is it just...
He's like looking at the Belgian Museum of Neural Wax, you know, the artifacts of the
auto-erotics.
You know, what is it like?
You just said, there's a sex temple.
Well, I'll tell you...
You know, everybody automatically in radio land goes, oh, oh, there's a sex temple.
I must go.
Yeah, I know.
You envision this thing that looks like the Taj Mahal and it's full of water beds.
Right.
And actually, it's a bunch of tarps wrapped around trees to fence off an area, a clearing,
where there are...
Where the trees can have sex?
These sort of like gynecological looking chairs, these like massage tables and things,
and I guess cots and stuff, where I guess some of the people who go to this campground
have...
I don't want to say it because...
Gynecological sex?
Text.
Let's just say text.
They have text.
Well, there's been a lot of school text...
Sex days?
...scandals lately.
If you noticed in the news, there's all the elementary school kids and principals and
teachers all over the country apparently having texts...
At all times with each other.
Yeah, all the time.
Or every other thing they can have it with.
Now, where were they when I was a kid?
Well, me too.
I was thinking the same thing.
I was such a young lad for such a long, long time.
How long were you a lad?
A long time.
I never...
I wanted...
Well, I had a crush on Miss Sapson.
I had a crustered...
You had a crustered on Miss Sapson?
I'm not paying attention to you right now because I'm irritated.
I'm sorry.
I'm just going to...
I am too, man.
I'm going to be quiet for a...
Wait.
If you think we're irritated, think how the audience feels.
There is no audience.
I'm sorry.
I wouldn't worry about that part of it.
We have bigger problems.
There is...
I hear a music coming out of this CD player.
See what I'm saying?
But that's not text day.
I know, but it's...
You didn't even cue it up.
It's just...
It's not.
...coming out of the system.
Oh, okay.
Now there's the text day.
The Texian...
The Texian music.
Well, who's the general of the other army then invading from the north there?
Loke E. Coyote.
Oh.
Loke E. Coyote is the person playing the guitar in the background.
It has a band called Loke.
Loke E. Coyote.
And Loke is also the host of text day.
Oh.
I didn't know that.
Which you can learn more about by going to textday.biz.
Because this isn't just the kind of religion that's into love and saving your soul.
That's...
We provide those services for money.
You see.
Sometimes it's for money.
Sometimes it's for favors and trades.
Sometimes it's just for kicks.
Sometimes it's for sick kicks, baby.
We'll save your soul just for kicks.
Just because we're sick.
We'll be sick.
Because we get kind of a weird kick out of saving your soul.
And delivering it into...
We smoke propane.
We drive off a cliff real fast, man.
Get a kick.
This is the great groovy Neptune is playing in the background at text day.
I never knew the gods could play such.
He is no man but a great golden god.
Neptune.
Let alone god of the deep stuff.
I've always thought of the great groovy Neptune.
As being a guy with a long beard that lives underwater surrounded in a trident surrounded
by sea monkeys.
Oh, okay.
And mermaids.
And those sea monkeys, you know, the kind that have families.
Yeah, they did drive cars.
And the mermaids also did his foreboding.
But as it turns out, the real great groovy Neptune is just these three guys from Texas
and there's no water to be seen for miles.
Yeah, but one of them sleeps in the trunk of a car.
Not a real car.
This music in the text day documentary goes with a walk through the mysterious text day
woods where there's hippie artwork hanging from all the trees and strange occult mystic
symbols and giant owl statues like at the Bohemian Grove where you can like splay out
the sacrificial cherbubs and the barbarian fruitcakes and really, you know, the...
Do your ritual.
Everyone loves barbarian fruitcakes, especially after an afternoon of revolting.
Listen.
There it goes again.
Yeah.
It even did it on the top CD player.
Well, I can hear a clicking sound in this.
I think it's the side of my head.
And the funny thing is, it's still timing down.
It's still going like...
Well, it's just literally spitting all those little discrete bits of information which
you've recorded and in which you hope so much...
Oh, here's a song.
I think there's a song.
It's a cute song.
Sounds cute.
And I can talk lay on.
We can pluck a string.
Without a little bob of money corn.
Without a little bob...
Bob, bob, bob, bob, bob, bob, bob.
Please don't blink.
Bob, bob.
You're gonna...
And when I went to the map, looking for a map.
Looking for a job.
Then I met Bob and he told me no prob, Bob Dobbs.
Oh, Bob Dobbs.
You got me propping in a slag and slagging in a propping, Bob Dobbs.
And when I lost all my slack to the cons of tech, Bob came along, told me how to get it
back, Bob Dobbs.
Oh, Bob Dobbs.
You got me propping in a slag and slagging in a propping, Bob Dobbs.
You know I was a wage slave.
I was a wage slave.
I had a one foot in the grain.
Bob came along, showed me how to rent and read, Bob Dobbs.
Oh, Bob Dobbs.
You got me propping in a slag and slagging in a propping, Bob Dobbs.
Wow.
That was Lopey Coyote.
Very original tune there.
Only there's one little difference, Reverend Stank.
The man you call whatever you just call that man's name is not really Bob Dobbs.
He's not really a member of the Hunan race, but a member of an ultra breed from far beyond
the cosmic register.
Look here on the screen.
It's one of the...
It's a pipe screen.
It's awesome.
Awesome stakes us.
That's right.
Austin, Texas, in another dimension.
I'm shocked and awed.
Awesome stakes us.
And remember your mission when you arrive.
Yes.
If you can remember anything.
As the missionary, I must remember not to remember anything at all of my mission.
Yes, especially if you're an e-missionary.
That means every mission you complete must be a full blown e-mission.
Have you completed enough e-missions?
Oh, there's never enough e-missions.
Then e-mit.
E-mit.
I've already had kids.
Oh, now he's flaccid.
There went another one.
Now there goes three more of them.
Three more little water heads, as Bill Hicks called them.
Sliding down the slide into the big pool.
Yep.
That's where we all ... There's more where they came from.
That's where I came from.
Cyber's not, they call it, back in the old days.
Some of them did anyway.
Anyway, the ones ... You were born of woman, weren't you?
No, I was not of woman born.
Were you one of the new generation?
No.
I thought you were older than that.
Well, I did have to make my own navel.
Is that what you mean?
Much like ham tail or whatever.
Oh, so you were like in between generation before the test tubes.
I actually used a pool cue.
I rubbed the navel areas if I were chalking up.
It worked.
It worked after about three or four years.
Anyway, now I have a navel.
Time to see you talk so long about me having a navel, so let's change the subject.
Yeah.
The subject of iniquity.
There was some other important thing we were going to talk about besides ...
The queen.
... Subgenius Festival.
The queen?
The British and the Dutch royal queens, many of whom called you up at all hours of
night asking if they can crash at your pad.
The Dutch one anyway.
Oh, especially him.
No, her.
Well, what ...
Well, the British.
It depends on whether you're talking about Prince Heinrich or ... I think that's his
name.
Well, see, now you can't tell whether it's a he, his name or her name.
Well, there's the queen and then there's the prince.
Prince and queen yet.
He stands to become queen later on.
But I think Holland has a queen who rides her bicycle through Amsterdam occasionally
and said that she did inhale once.
Cuculina, bambina.
Yeah, of course.
Of course she inhaled, but it wasn't ...
Although they're crashing down on all that now, you know.
It's not like it used to be.
It's now you can legally smoke drugs of certain kinds in the coffee shops, but it's illegal
to transport the drugs to or from the coffee shops, they've decided.
So they've kind of got you coming or going.
The legislation ...
As long as you're just sitting there, it's okay.
Yeah.
Well, the legislation is getting so bad they may expect a lot of people to expel everything
they've held in all these years.
The little stations they're going to put up in every street corner you walk in, you get
your little scan and it tells you how much you've consumed and then you have to exhale
everything you've inhaled over the past 45, 55, 75 years.
Well, that's ... Anybody who comes to work for Subgenius Foundation gets a drug test
too.
If you don't pass, we're not going to give you the free drugs in order to be able to
pass the test that we require.
Why does it have to include drinking blood, though, Stan?
Well, I don't understand that part of it.
Why ...
Well, it's to discourage drinking alcohol.
We don't really want people drunk on the job at the devivals and stuff, although usually
they are.
I mean, let's be real.
I've been known to do it myself, sure.
I'm not Little Miss Goody Clean Shoes or anything, Little Doopoo Pootie Face or anything.
No, not when it comes to drinking a gallon and a half of hemogloboid.
I'm Little Miss Dinky Winky Fine.
No.
No Little Pimper Winks for me.
Not me.
No, sir.
You won't catch me lipping those nipple bottles outside the pinky face.
Not in the days of glory.
Not in the days of blood on your neck and hands.
No, sirree.
Not in a hundred years.
Bob.
Tips that have touched the bottle shall never brush mine.
Well, unless it's the good stuff.
You can mask the flavor of the plasma with perhaps Scott's whiskey or the flavor of a
donut.
I love them.
Myself.
I don't love myself as much as I do love them.
Well, you know, speaking of love, I've got this song by Loke Coyote called Horn Dog and
Slut Puppy that's a real cute song.
And they fall in love?
But, you know, I've burned these CDs to play at the show here, every show, and I've never
had this problem of the stuttering machine.
Beep, beep, beep.
This is an unusual show because I usually have it ready sooner, but when Dave got to
the Slacker Mansion, I was just in the middle of burning the show in a big hurry to rush
out the door, and I had a funny feeling about that CD.
I thought, you know, maybe I shouldn't be showing Dave the text-day video while I'm
burning the CD on the same computer.
Oh, right.
So all of a sudden it's Bastille Day in everyone's mind, right?
No, that wasn't what I meant.
Oh, okay.
Heidegger's Principle or Schrodinger's Cat.
No, Heidegger's Principle.
I walked into the room and screwed up the machinery, right?
That was Vonnegut's cat, and that one turned out to be actually dead after all.
Yeah, after it took too many turns.
Really?
No, it just was cradled in.
It took one ice-nine pill too many.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, Kurt Vonnegut.
For those listening in the future, in our past, Kurt Vonnegut had just recently died,
in the past that we're recording now.
Yeah.
He was actually in Dresden.
Did you know that?
Yeah.
During the billowing of the Fourth World War?
Slaughterhouse-Five is based on his true slips in time.
Yeah.
And he actually had ...
I know how it is.
I had that same problem just before X-Day 98.
I still don't know whether it was the future or the past that I went to.
Oh, well, you went to the ...
I don't know whether to hope it was the future or to hope it was the past.
It was all ...
It was marked aside, the she-poked-the-golf bag, whatever it was.
How did you know?
I didn't know.
Well, because I was ...
You weren't taught.
You slipped, Dave, so you were one of the agents.
We keep slipping.
Mm-hmm.
We can't stop slipping.
I thought ... I fully suspected ...
I'm having a different life and dimensions.
Somebody had to be the agent, the inside agent.
The Agent Smith.
I'm on this string now.
Someone of us had to be the Agent Smith.
Who is it going to be?
DeLuca or Smith?
I mean, wait a minute.
Uh-oh.
Dick ...
Damn.
I remember back when plots for that kind of a filament were so simple to write.
You'd just sit down and scratch your hirsute parts on a sunny afternoon or a rainy day
with a little bottle of pills and perhaps a razor blade next to it.
No, no, that's ...
But you just ...
Babysitter has sex.
Babysitter is slain by serial killer.
Other babysitter doesn't have sex, manages to kill serial killer.
That was the ... That's the pattern.
It's one ...
Boy meets girl, kills girl.
Boy meets girl, gets killed by other girl.
Mm-hmm.
That's the ...
There's no reinvention.
Slasher movie ever since Peter, Laurie and Em.
What can we improve on?
And ...
How can we bring dimension to this art?
It's ... It's ... It's ... I don't know if it can be done.
It all seems to center or the focus seems to be some sort of bug-like creature.
Maybe one with three or four eyes.
It has a nuclear or an atomic power.
Just like the little bean wagons in the old days.
And then, and perhaps on another afternoon like the ones you described, this creature
actually takes over the entire world and one hero and one heroine decide to stop it.
I think you've been watching too many David ... You've been reading too many David Cronenberg
movies, Dave.
I can't ... I can't read them anymore.
The ...
I tried ...
That's right.
I tried to stop, yeah.
That one that sucked you, that tried to make out with you.
Well, yeah.
The one where the lips came out of the TV and sucked you in.
It sucked out part of my temporal ... Well, temporal, I don't know if we believe in time,
but one of my lobes was actually sucked out by one of those furtive creatures.
Okay.
I'm going to try ...
Go ahead.
I'm going to try to play this next cut on the bad scene.
Horned dog had horns like a pan.
Slut pup had a minivan on.
Oh, yeah.
Parked the man in a cozy spot in the parking lot on home.
Slut puppy reached for horned dog's whopper.
He said, having your way, didn't try to stop her.
She said, extra pickle.
He said, you're the boss.
Gave her a taste of a secret.
She said, you're the boss.
He said, you're the boss.
You can't tell me that because my dad's a secret sauce.
All the customers get food to go.
Gave horned dog a slut pup standing in a wall.
They don't tell you everything in school.
Oh, they teach creationism.
Oh, they teach evolutionism.
But they don't tell you where subgeniuses came from.
What test tube were you spilled from, my friend?
And what genetic engineering laboratory?
Good morning, sang.
Thank you.
I'm young.
Her boobs are tired.
They need a rest.
Oh, I understand.
We're slinging them about.
You're really generous.
Just like the flying cars,
we need anti-gravity boob devices.
Yeah.
They promised me one in 2000.
I still haven't gotten one.
Lying version.
Bush stole it.
You know what people go?
Well, they're just puppets of the conspiracy.
We're all puppets, friends.
Even the masters of the conspiracy
are puppets of something.
We don't know how far up our strings go,
but I don't see any of you working any puppets now, do I?
Well, the kid over there.
Bob says get up!
Fellas and girls,
what I have to say will only take a few seconds.
It's about cleanliness.
Being clean in mind
is well-adjusted.
Think clean and keep clean.
Lack of cleanliness
is usually a sign of carelessness.
And carelessness indicates laziness.
Remember always that
carelessness and laziness
lead to the self-genius
power of
slush.
I'd like to thank those of you
who have donated
to Evolution I
irreducible complexity
personal incredulity
logically fallacious
by evolution
quoting out of context
dirty rhetorical trick
by a translucent membrane
deeper Darwinian evolution
evolution
unpleasant side effects
have pubic hair
what?
weird places
why are we naked?
well, the
well, the pubic hair
sexual pubic hair
pubic hair
ready to procreate
now
now we're naked
we're naked
so
why are we
naked?
naked mole-rat
the reason for our
nudity
properly manipulated
meaty muck
sticky and nasty places
but
sticking them in
thick deposits of subcutaneous fat
existence of pubic hair
sexual signal
hairier
hairy
harriers
the jets
you naked mole-rat you
the levitating jet route
I know you use a naked mole rap.
What was that one song, Snake Pounder,
Milk's Cerebral Sky from Snots and Whiskey's Woman Dog?
What is the name of that?
You know, it was like,
And they raced on down and clapped his whammy three times.
You know, something like that.
Well, Dave, you know, I'm not really a musical scholar like you are.
Four pieces back.
Oh, a song I played?
Yeah, with one guitar guy.
That was Loki Coyote.
Right, Loki Coyote.
Horned Dog and Puppy and Slut Puppy.
Horned Dog and Slut Puppy.
I forgot their names.
That's all I was asking, really, to reiterate the names.
Yeah, Loki Coyote has several CDs out at wickabilly.com.
I was trying to remember the name, Wickabilly.
And that's what, I think that guy plays at Starwood every now and then.
Sounds like a kind of band that would put a spell on you.
In fact, he lives in the woven,
dream hippie bus, which we first encountered at Starwood
as a place of child labor, I think.
That was our suspicion.
It was a hippie bus that we thought might be full of child laborers.
And child rock bands of, like, 13-year-old girl children
singing salacious songs.
And it gave us the creeps.
It turned us into prudes.
Imagine subgeniuses.
How bad something would have to be to make a subgenius.
into a prude, my friend.
Well, actually, I've been, sometimes I see the subgenius behaviors that are so wild and free,
and it makes me realize how thankfully normal I really am.
Well, what about the subgenius?
The ones that, you know, change their text into another's face and, oh, God, I mean, stuff.
Radical free expression, I guess, is what it is.
But, you know, I'm not sure.
I mean, I guess that's supposed to be, you know, cool and everything and radical and free and self.
And expressive.
You know, I always end up feeling like Hank Hill.
Not just sounding like him, but, I mean, really feeling him.
I know.
You tend to look like him when it happens.
When I met him at X Day, I ended up wanting, you know, it's like my inhibitions went down
and I almost wanted to hug him instead of shake his hand.
Yeah.
But I'm a Texan.
And we don't do that.
We don't hug.
Well.
I've noticed I say that to my pagan Wiccan friends around here and they go, oh, I'm sorry for you.
I think my boot's going to put a spell on your ass.
How about that, buddy?
You know, but really the hex.
Wicca, Mr. Wicca.
The hex, as you're referring to, it's not really a tool that anyone can use offhandedly.
And that's the part I don't understand.
And also, you don't look like the king of the hill after that.
No, I look like one of the hippie Wicca type or at least an old man.
Yeah.
No, you look like a post-ejaculatory.
Oh, now I forgot the word.
Flagella.
No, like a bonobo monkey or one of the.
A tired bonobo monkey who's just been doing it too long.
Trying to braid its own armpit hairs.
Yeah.
He's worn out.
He's just like, that's the end of the day.
Might be the end of everything as far as I know, you know.
Like an old limp.
Beep.
That's me.
Yeah.
I can't be beat anymore.
You can be stroked.
Yeah.
Perhaps.
I mean, I wouldn't describe it, but, you know, I've heard that you can actually be brought
back to life.
Well, I'm getting on in years.
Take a lot of stroking.
You can start any time, Dave.
I know.
If you're hitting around at that.
No, I was just.
You can inch your way over across the station over to where my microphone is.
No, no.
You can stroke me if you want.
No, no, no.
On my head.
I was just hoping you would elucidate on, you know, the folk knowledge that you're getting.
You think I'm a loose date?
No, I think.
I ask you to stroke my head and you, suddenly you're like, you want to go all the way.
No, I want to go home.
Stroke my.
I want to go home right now.
Don't blame me.
Please drive me home.
I don't blame you, man.
Please drive me home right now or else I'm going to get out of the car and start walking.
You know, it's not the same without Princess We here.
Look at us.
Here we've devolved into like trying to pick each other up in the bathroom.
But just because there's no lady around.
Yeah.
Those guys are terrible.
Well, that's, you know, John, John Janay said that was the, that's a prison mentality we
have today.
And we believe we're in a prison right now.
We all believe that we're perhaps reincarnated criminals who've been brought back to, been
resurrected on this planet and this sphere to act out some sort of a cruel game or, or
perhaps be saved by our own higher, deeper selves.
If we have.
Prison planet.
Earth.
Escape from new earth.
Drink three, six, seven, old is on its way as snake Plissken.
You know, did you ever see any of the escape from New York or the sort of satirical sequence?
Yeah.
I wore an eye patch and I had a game leg for a while.
Right.
On purpose.
I think Plissken, I thought you were dead.
Well, you know, in, in escape from LA, he refers constantly to a, a meek will in between the
two films called.
Escape from Cleveland.
Cause they're all going, I thought you got killed in Cleveland.
Like after escape from New York, something really bad happened in future Cleveland.
And if LA and New York are penal colonies in the future, what then is Cleveland solitary
confinement?
If they can't, and they can't, yeah.
He was in the hole for five weeks.
Cause I destroyed the LA.
He talked back to the wardens.
They threw him in the hole Cleveland, but nothing could stop snake Plissken.
Are you ready to come out?
I see the daylight now.
The warden, the big warden, the game warden.
Ivan Stang.
I thought you were dead.
Actually.
I got one of those.
I got a, I have a, my space page now.
And I'm staying.
I thought you were dead.
Yeah.
I got a letter from some guy.
He's like going or an, a my space message.
They call them.
And he's going, if you really are the real life and staying and like, I've been told
to avoid the sub geniuses online because they're sold out to the.
Green energy demons.
You're probably not the real life and staying.
You shouldn't make a mockery of a great man.
He's probably dead by now.
And I wrote him back and said, well, you're right.
It's really me, but I'm dead.
He said you were a cocky optimist for the spleen eyed energy hogs.
He was real happy though.
That wrote him back.
He said he would.
Maybe somebody said they'd print it out and put it on the refrigerator.
Cause cause to them, I was a celebrity.
Right.
Just like you remember that to them?
I'm a celebrity.
Oh, I remember it.
I'm made aware of it.
I remember.
Did you hear that?
I'm a celebrity.
Actually, I got a letter from somebody wanting to know about the show where you died because
they'd lost their copy of it and they wanted to know which hour of slack it was that had
Dave goes to hell.
And it was it's our slack number 748 as opposed to this hour of slack, which is number 1095
and friends you're listening to the subgenius radio ministry hour of slack, a religious
show.
You wouldn't think it to hear us talk.
Of course not.
We'd offer you a hot, moist towelette if we could, but we cannot at this.
It's against the law.
Now they give you a towelette test.
We're members of the church of the subgenius.
And if you want more information about that August assemblage, which gets together every
August, no July, July 5th, July 5th, kill the world.
You can look at subgenius.com.
Subgenius does not have an O in it.
Although there may be a subgeniouse.com that links you.
There used to be.
The arm.
Dr. Armand Geddon had set up a subgeniouse.com that just forwarded people to the correct
one because it was such a common misspelling.
But the true subgenius is spell subgenius with an O.
But I mean the pure ones.
And the pure spell.com as .com.
They spell out the dot.
D-O-T.
If we could.
But this is about as quiet.
And what is real?
Re-articulis.
I guess we both have spiders in our ears now in our elderly times.
Oh yeah.
Dave and I are both getting deaf from listening to each other.
What's the name of it?
Again.
Tinitus.
Oh I thought you were talking about tuna fish.
Because the tiny little demons inside your ears make this bzzz sound all the time.
Watch him very carefully.
Look, the little demons are growing in his head.
Knock, knock, knock.
I heard that.
Sorry.
I forgot.
The little demons.
Demons are growing in his ear holes.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
And now he cannot only hear anything.
He's only hearing us inside his own brain.
He's hearing us.
Us.
Walk to the window.
Step, whoever you are.
Look out the window.
He's not doing it.
Wait.
Stand back away.
Dave's using that expensive filter again.
Yeah, there's this thing.
He spent $150 for that special audio filter.
Off the internet years, too.
Off the internet.
Google, this thing is worth about $4,000 or $5,000 if I could find the right buyer.
Okay, we have to play the news now.
Yep.
Unfortunately.
Prepare yourself for the truth.
Okay, here it is.
You're cubic hair.
This is PR.
PR in Washington serves the military dictatorship that's ruled for decades.
PR comes from the Supproving Subjects Portal Foundation.
Online at Supproving Subjects.
PhD.
And last one from 받아 researcher from the
Control Center in Washington.
I'm Paul già Zirko, and I'm proud of the one.
eAnd you're watching herkesl monitor on H-çu-o-diests.org.
but it should end by tonight.
Second Until It's Over
Air Cups Any wielka
move into parts of Georgia and South Carolina by tomorrow.
Among those opposed is Connecticut Democrat Christopher Dodd.
Last week, Dodd announced he is still without electricity
after a massive Republican lawmakers' plan brought down miles of power lines.
The Labor Department reported today the prices show up in grocery stores.
In the meantime, Columbus business owners destroyed green leafy PR news in Columbus, Ohio.
In December, 2.5% after an even bigger 6.1% in November.
That was a moderate 2% jump by nine-tenths of 1%.
Analysts believe further increases or decreases are 1.7%.
For all of 2006, that's 1.1% for its slowest five years.
On Wall Street 1245666, this is PR News.
A young Chinese journalist has been in China.
In hemorrhage, local police told state media
that bogus PR news has sent reporters to investigate as well.
Last week, Chinese rice wound up in China.
Unfortunately, they're probably, you know, lingering today.
However, Jarek says 300,000 homes and businesses
are still without sectarian violence to spill over into PR news in Washington.
In Washington, ah, yes.
These are the days.
Lost, set adrift in a maddening sea of confusion.
And dichotomies.
Things that can't be figured out so easily.
And the occasional shark.
Oh, the occasional.
At occasional times.
Dichotomies and sharks.
Huge, huge top feeders.
Tiny little bottom feeders.
That's me.
And in-betweener feeders.
And...
What, what, what, what?
What did, what was God thinking?
Is there an absolute to blame for all this?
I think we have bigger fish to fry.
I don't know who they might be.
Yeah, but who? Which?
I guess our own individual soul fish.
I guess we have to look that way.
We're not theocrats.
We're monocrats.
We're, uh, we're hypocrites.
Yeah, we're, we're not gonna, we're not gonna practice what we preach.
Nor are we gonna preach, uh, anything.
Very well, no.
You know, anything that we might practice.
No.
But we will practice every day.
No, and we've been, when we do preach, it's to the saved.
Yeah.
To the choir.
Well.
The pew packers.
The ones who claim they're saved.
They're just an audience of liars.
I'm not a solipsist, but I'd be one on television if I could.
That's what salvation's all about, is being the penultimate liar to yourself.
It is, isn't it?
To believe what cannot be true.
That's truth.
That's real faith.
And as Nenslow pointed out, once you believe one thing that can't be true, you can believe anything that can't be true.
And that's the credo.
And that explains all rival cults besides the Church of the Subgenius.
Because we don't believe.
We don't believe anything we say.
We don't?
Well, of course, you just said that, but I thought we did.
Yeah, you caught the little, the one little paradox in there that, of course, gives the lie to all of our lies.
I thought maybe I was the only one.
And it proves that they're actually true.
But we have to dress it up like silliness in order to not end up like our predecessors.
And look at them.
Whoever they might be.
Well, nailed to telephone poles, hanging in little cages.
It was.
With turning into skeletons in the, you know, creaking wind.
Yeah, they're hard to wear around your neck, too.
So the people who walk by go, well, I'm not going to make fun of Jesus because I'll end up like that man up in that cage on that wheel.
Dressed up like a little basket job.
I'm not going to question my betters because I might end up like that.
I wouldn't.
And that's why it works, you see.
Who would question a crucified man?
You'd only get an agonized reply.
We don't want to go that way.
Well, we don't want to go anyway, really.
But yet we must go because it's about the end of the show, Dave.
Can't we just be left out of the religious conundrum in every way?
Can't we just kind of like walk out of it and let this church be its own ism?
Hey, now that's an idea.
I forget.
Actually, friends, you already have slack.
You have all the slack you'll ever get.
And it's more than you could ever possibly use.
The trick is.
Figuring out, you know, how to use it.
Knowing it's there.
Usually, all it takes is to have most of it taken away.
Then you'll know what your slack was.
Can I get a praise, Bob?
Praise Bob!
Bob who?
Alright, all right all right, I guess we're liftin'.
They make the
the
this
week,