Colloids are liquids with particles suspended in them.
Yes, sir. Yes, I understand. Goodbye.
He says he's pretty sure this isn't sabotage.
But he thinks there's something far more terrible than that in back of it.
The Self-Genius Power of Swagging!
But why did they come here?
Well, they're not friendly, we're sure of that.
No matter what the cost, it must be destroyed.
Perhaps one of the most interesting words in the English language today is the word...
Trump.
Out of all of the English words that begin with the letter F...
...is the only word that is referred to...
...as the F word.
It's the one magical word.
Just by its sound can describe pain, pleasure, hate, and love.
Trump.
As most words in the English language is derived from German, the word...
...which means to strike.
In English...
Trump.
...falls into many grammatical categories.
As a transitive verb, for instance.
John...
Trumped.
...surely.
As an intransitive verb, surely...
Trump.
...is.
Its meaning's not always sexual.
It can be used as an adjective, such as...
John's doing all the...
Trumping.
...work.
As part of an adverb, surely talks to...
Trumping.
...much.
As an adverb enhancing an adjective, surely is...
Trumping.
...beautiful.
As a noun, I don't give a...
Trump.
As part of a word, abso...
Trumping.
...lutely.
Or, intrumping.
...credible.
And, as almost every word in a sentence...
Trump.
...the...
Trumping.
...Trump...
...ers.
As you must realize, there aren't too many words with the versatility of...
Trump.
...as in these examples describing situations such as...
Fraud.
I got...
Trumped.
...that they use Carlot.
Dismay.
Aw...
Trump.
...it.
Trouble.
I guess I'm really...
Trumped.
...now.
Aggression.
Don't...
Trump.
...with me, buddy.
Difficulty.
I don't understand this...
Trumping.
...question.
Inquiry.
Who the...
Trump.
...was that?
Dissatisfaction.
I don't like what the...
Trump.
...is going on here.
Incompetence.
He's a...
Trump.
...off.
Dismissal.
Why don't you go outside and play hide and go...
Trump.
...yourself?
I'm sure you can think of many more examples.
With all of these multipurpose applications, how can anyone be offended when you use the word?
We say...
Use this unique, flexible word more often in your daily speech. It will identify the quality of your character immediately. Say it loudly and proudly.
Trump.
You.
...you.
Who here can tell Bob what critical thinking means?
A time comes when silence is betrayal.
Bob, we're going to the Shite.
Bob! That's great.
That's great.
The purpose of this presentation is to show that the conspiratorial view of history, particularly of recent history, is the correct view.
And that it properly can be identified as the capitalist conspiracy.
Look around you.
Wa...
Wake up, humans.
If we are passive, we are enabling the controllers.
And therefore, we must rise up, not in violence, but in peace, but with one voice, without fear.
And we will say, enough of the secrecy, enough of oil, enough of economic slavery, enough of the wars.
It is time for a new civilization, and we will see that it will be born in our lifetime in the coming months and years.
We'll also grant you unrestricted access to all our recreational facilities, including our non-denominational modern house of worship.
A new day has dawned.
There's no force on this planet that will keep me from speaking the truth.
...speaking the truth.
They'll have to carry me out feet first in a coffin before I'll shut up about the truth here.
...shut up about the truth here.
Stop living in the future or living in the past, and always live in your now.
Bob.
But let's leave things of this world behind, and walk now down the path of Bob for this brief minute of slack from the Church of the Subgenius.
Ah, yes, dear friends, this is Reverend Ivan Stang.
Hey, you know those policemen on Motorcycle?
They won't let me preach on car hoods downtown because they think I'm a crazy man or a drunk man.
And there's no reason to arrest me, yet they would.
Because I'm free, free, free enough to rant to myself in public because I come against death, taxes, work, and premature immaculation.
For Bob, your mind, friend, your mind has to be certified okay by them.
Them!
Them, and oh, we hate them.
They and their tools of iniquity.
Not the tools of the preacher, not the tongue, nor the other parts, nay, but tools of false slack,
dangled forever in front of you like that raise right around the corner,
or like that rat swimming in poison cheese.
Let there be slack.
On two tops down.
Tops down.
Here I come.
I'm going to tops down.
Tops down.
Here I come.
They got some crazy little tops heads staring up and gonna get me one.
It's the modern age.
Excuse me a second.
Hello.
The electronics department, please.
Hey, how you doing?
You're a sound effects man always fooling around with electronic devices.
Fooling around, boy.
Tell me, do you suppose robots would enjoy listening to music?
If I can repeat it, do you think I like your job or your job isn't enough?
I do from a salesman's point of view.
You don't.
I'm a salesman at the office.
And it'd sound like you just had a good night's sleep, час but true,
and now folks are missing the prime time, damn it, now that you've suddenly got this,
behind the scenes, you're audience to the front lines.
It's the modern age.
It's the modern age of us.
It's the modern age of 我的街道 Alaska
It's the modern age of ポトランタ
Hell of a time of living
Hey let's go, hey let's go, go down now
Bob. Great.
The acclaim and applause of millions
heralds the triumphant return of
Bob!
Invited.
To me it looked like a Leprechaun
to me.
I gotta do a little British
treat.
Who else in the Leprechaun
say, yeah?!
Yeah!
Eyewitnesses say the Leprechaun
only comes out atова пожалуйста
night if you shine a light in its direction it suddenly disappears oh that was good listen to
this right here now what you're doing you're helping god in his work yeah we should totally
hit it again but i get first damn night to me come on first minute dead with love i watch the people
like electric forehead
come out of the wall please
you want to stay in the wall bob bob you know my therapist says that if i don't value my time
nobody's gonna
you
you know what
keep it together bob
where am i am i here or am i here bob i'm everywhere
bob i've got some nice ground beef for you bob
the need to feel alive was killing me
torture
torture oh that is
that's oh my god oh my god no that was bad dude do you want some coffee with me
That's a myth.
I'd fire all of you if I could.
Bob.
All of you if I could.
He may call his living.
Yes, Bob.
Your due date was today.
Are you sitting comfortably?
Then we'll begin.
O-A-C.
That young.
Tender as a cotton tan.
And we got a saver.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, you're the worst kind of autistic.
You can't even count.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, Dave?
Yes?
Oh, there you are.
Okay, I almost forgot to push the button.
Yeah, I wondered why somebody forgot to push the button.
I would have just said...
I really...
I didn't...
I pushed a button, but I didn't push your button, Dave.
Me too.
Here on the other end.
I forgot which one I did now, so it's not even worth mentioning.
If I could push your button...
This is one of the many buttons that I have sitting here.
I love to push your buttons, Dave.
You better not be pushing his buttons.
That's called lobotomizing someone in modern terminology.
I don't know about that.
Kiss my button.
That's a good bumper sticker.
Yeah, kiss my button.
Well, no, it'd make a much better pin or button.
Yes.
They call them pins.
Like elongated noses and ear balls and eye wax.
It would give it a little bit more branding flavor.
That is, if you want to consider it any kind of sauce.
Well, Dave, we would love to come and press all your little buttons
and rub your nose and your little brown belly.
But you're an ashtabula, so we can't.
Oh, how terrible.
How sad.
Can't go rub on Dave.
Well, they could rub on some sort of symbolic image of me.
Perhaps Neil Ficrap's apple mode or something like that
or wearing those huge Wagner-like horns, you know.
Well, Dave, isn't it good to do a live show for a change?
Isn't it good or is it good?
It is good.
I've been editing my little fool fingers off on all that X-Day stuff since X-Day.
You don't want to fool your fingers because they're an important part of your anatomy.
Yeah.
Because if they accuse you of lying, somehow you could never get out of that
unless you had to maybe, I don't know.
Yeah, it's not a smart practice to put your fingers on.
You need to be straight up with your fingers.
Yeah.
You need rehearsal, but don't practice too much, you know.
Right.
Can you do a radio, can you engineer a radio show without fingers?
That would be the question.
Oh, of course, with stumps.
I can actually work all the buttons in front of me with a stump and my nose.
It would be best to have at least two stumps.
Hmm.
What if you had a pencil mounted to your forehead and you could push things with that,
using your head?
You talking to me?
Say.
I think we ought to patent that, only I think it's already been done.
It's been done.
Yeah.
I copied that from someone else.
Well, people who are quadriplegic have things like that.
Well, some have five times, six, seven times more pleages than every other person.
So why shouldn't they be included in the grand octopussful mess of what we have left of our brains?
Why not?
Well.
It sounds like taxi driver music to me in the background.
That's what I have to.
It is.
I believe that it is Bernard Herrmann's score for taxi driver, but it's being done without
any orchestral instruments at all.
It's a woman named Petra Hayden.
She's the daughter of a famous jazz musician.
Charlie Hayden's gal.
Yeah.
And she does all of this music with her voice.
She does all the orchestral parts of movie themes and other things.
I think she did a brilliant.
I think she did a Who album like that.
Yes, she did.
Some of that is on here.
The Who sell out.
Yeah.
She did.
She did the Who sell out all the way through.
It's amazing.
She did Knocko Blocko Jocko and the rest of the boys.
She had quite a fan club when she was about 22 and then she got red eye syndrome.
And the worse it got, the more she thought she was Bernard Herrmann herself, which was
not true, of course, as we all know.
And that led to a series.
You know.
A lot of recovery time.
Deep, deep, deep, deep, deep, deep implants and anything else that could get her off the
wisdom gizm chart, you know?
Yes, I know.
And I also know this.
I haven't done the credits yet.
But don't worry, Dave, they won't take long.
Oh, I'll shut up.
Well, we just did.
We're listening to Petra Hayden in the background.
But the collages tonight, there was a bunch of collage stuff.
I got a new package from Reverend Chris.
Christian Blatter.
And that really is his name.
He also goes by the name Chris Hand Luke, except when I'm messed up and calling him Cool Hand
Chris, which is not correct.
Anyway, he sent us a bunch of new stuff and he did the collages, except for a couple of
things that Lee Murr did, of course.
And the music we heard about the modern age about 15 minutes ago, that was Rural War Room.
Our favorite.
Our buddies, St. Byron Werner and Donovan, the Donovan and Theramina.
They were at the devotional.
And yeah, there may be more of the modern age by Rural War Room coming up at the bitter
end.
It's a barrage for the senses indeed.
And we heard Reverend Bleepo Abernathy twice, but I'm not going to say where.
Well, he was a woman the whole time, so it's hard to tell.
I don't know.
I mean, it's not an audio perspective, I guess, but it sure makes it difficult for
me anyway.
I'm having a hard time focusing anyway.
Focus if we can't take a joke.
Yes.
Trumpets as well.
Yeah, trumpets, man.
I've already played that little bit, but you got the idea.
Everything's all trumped up around here.
Well, and I also conceded there were many people who trumpeted up the funk.
And who were trumpets and people who had stern pots.
I think he needs to go play a game of hide and go trump yourself.
Hide and go trump yourself.
Indeed.
How could he do it?
You know, that's the double entendre of that disheveled argument.
Oh, he's doing it all the time.
If baboons could make stew, what great stew they would do.
Do you think anybody lets Trump trump them?
I don't know.
Without being paid real well?
What do you think, Will?
Do you think it's possible?
No, I actually don't.
I thought you didn't.
No, I think he's a lonely, lonely man.
No, that's not necessarily true.
He probably just doesn't need anybody else, you see.
He can sit and just look in the mirror and comb over, over and over and over.
And that's all he needs for stimulation?
No.
He obviously needs a hell of a lot more than that for stimulation.
And he's getting it.
And I'm sure that the big smackdown is being built up even as we speak.
Mackie?
Yeah.
There's got to be drama, you know.
When the climax comes, it's going to be entertaining.
For so many months.
We hope.
Yeah.
But we'll see.
Who knows?
In the meantime, the WCSB Halloween masquerade box.
The next big pass ball is next Saturday for us here in Cleveland.
Woo hoo.
And that's been going on for what, five or six years now?
At least.
I think this is the seventh one, I believe.
Yeah, yeah.
I guess so.
That's why I don't remember them.
I had so much fun.
It's lucky seven.
There wasn't one 11 years ago.
Are you sure there wasn't one 11 years ago?
There was one that you, me, and Princess We weren't invited to.
And Brother Love.
By the way, Brother Love is in British Columbia now.
the studio tonight.
He just didn't go home this time.
But yeah,
for people in Cleveland,
if you didn't know,
there'll be, what, four or five
bands.
Oh, right, there they are.
Simply Saucer. Well, that's
a good subgeniously type
of thing. It's not the saucers we were
expecting, but better than nothing.
Thomas Jefferson
Slave Apartments.
Destructor and the
Shale Saitans.
And the theme
of the Masquerade Ball, not that anybody
has to pay any attention to this, is space.
I had to pay attention to it
because it's my job to
do the video projections,
don't you see?
You don't see.
You see, in reverse language,
you just said, you don't see.
Meaning you were unobtrusive, except
for the parts where you're showing, you know,
Grizzly,
except for the parts where you're showing, you know,
the great acceptances of human
anatomy.
Well, we've got Grizzly atoms in space,
we've got everything in outer space.
Four hours of space
compilations on two
screens, or maybe brick
walls, we'll see,
as usual. You only notice
these if you look up,
and the only reason anybody would look up at
that party is if they're laying down
flat on their back.
Or perhaps, once again,
they've had their third nostril removed,
or,
or been lobotomized,
or had other, you know, had their foreheads
tampered with.
So, we'll be there,
although, how would anybody know?
Because everybody's got a mask on.
Yeah, but you'll know
somebody's there. You'll be able to fill in the blanks
by yourself.
Well,
Princess We will be the one that looks like
a beautiful space princess, and I'll be
the guy with the blue
Greek fisherman's hat.
Which almost never comes off.
A couple of years ago,
I had a Mitt Romney mask
that was really pretty good, and if you stuck
a pipe in the mouth, you looked darn near
like Bob Dobbs. Sure did.
Yeah, I remember that. It was
frightening. You don't remember
it. It's really horrible. You weren't there.
But I remember it, and it was still horrible.
Can I at least make those
two points? He has a vicarious
memory. Others
can see that stuff
in that if you go to,
subconsciousofgenius.com
and click the events button, and you're looking
at this events page, which is all about
X-Day and Starwood, but if you scroll down
a long way,
you'll start coming to the Halloween
and WCSB events.
And you can, if a person
really wanted to, they could look
at every little kid that's ever
trick-or-treated at our home,
the Slacker Mansion. Quite true.
Over in Cleveland Bluffs.
Literally thousands of photos of cute little bunnies
and other perversions.
Actually, you'd be surprised. They're very creative.
They really are. Especially the kids
whose parents aren't rich.
They have to make their own costumes.
And those are pretty interesting.
But obviously, you can't photograph
every kid. You have to ask
permission. And not
every parent wants their
child's picture on
the internet. I wonder
why?
The internet's not full of
perverts or anything now,
is it? Yes, it is.
But the internet
doesn't lie to me.
Oh, no. No, no. Whatever you want
to believe, the internet will tell you
that it's true. You can think the
dumbest thing in the whole world and go to
the internet and it'll go, yep, yep, there's
10,000 of us that agree with you.
It'll confirm your inadequacy
right there on the spot. Any kind of
idiocy you want to believe or disagree with,
it's right there.
Yeah, it's there to
validate your
craziest, most
self-righteous
notions. And, you know,
that's really what the best thing about the
internet is, that glorious feeling of
self-righteousness and
moral outrage when you
push thumbs down.
Yeah, it's like argumentative
bowel syndrome. That'll show
them. I'm a slacktivist. I sit here on the
web and get things done
by expressing my disapproval
with a thumbs
down. Or,
in some cases, if you don't have that option,
I'm going to withhold
my thumbs up. That will show
that other
loser, internet
loser, nothing better to do.
My glaring silence, I'll give that
to them, yes.
I'm about to use
the internet to send out a giant
form letter to everybody
who signed up for it.
And here's what it says.
Thank you and praise
Bob to the people who not only
ordered, but
donated.
Wait, I can't talk about that.
You are the ones motivating the production
of new radio shows, books
in progress, videos,
and the continued existence of
the Subgenius Foundation
Incorporated.
Your contributions are worth
way more than just money,
for they also boost slack
across the board
and across the planet.
They feed you pretty good, too.
And for that matter, come to think of it,
WCSB Radiothon
is coming up.
Start
breaking open your piggy banks,
kids, because the station
needs HEP.
It starts in two days?
Two weeks.
Oh, two weeks.
My heart bestows.
Remember next week, remember next week,
remember next week.
Because by the time everybody remembers
next week, they'll have forgotten it.
So you have to spring it on
right in between, like,
Nary Weasel would do.
Just to...
I know, next week,
Ohioans can vote
two different
confusing marijuana initiatives.
Not that any of our listeners
would care about that kind of thing, but...
There's the
one that supposedly
legalizes recreational
marijuana, but not really exactly.
And the other one that outlaws
monopolies, which
defeats the previous.
So it's like, if you vote
for three, you're
voting against two, even if
you don't know that.
All I know is I have to read a lot
more about them to find out which one
is which.
Now I'm mixed up.
I should just
stay out of this.
You said last night to me that you believed
that three was the true
positive one.
That's right. I've got my numbers reversed.
For legalization.
Do you really want
people to be walking
around on
marijuana? Wouldn't you rather
have them just be drunk?
Horribly drunk,
smelling, puking, driving
real fast, getting in fights?
Yeah, the getting in fights thing I really think is
a lot more
better than having people just hide,
just kind of smiling and
walking around.
Right.
You don't see a lot of punch fests at a Zooter party.
Well, we'll just have to let the votars figure that one out.
I don't.
Come on.
This is Ohio.
Might as well be Texas.
Well, it's not.
Okay.
It ain't Texas.
Well, they tried for 14 years, I think.
I'm not sure of the exact number, but they've tried for many, many years.
Ohio was one of the original ones that would get slapped down by the, it's going to make
everyone take heroin and LSD.
Really?
Oh, man.
Well, in that case, I'm going to vote for them.
I'm going to vote for it.
I can't wait to try that heroin and LSD.
Everybody says-
At the same time?
Oh, hell, that's the only way to do it, man.
You're a wuss if you don't do it all at the same time.
Everything, all at once, and the whiskey.
Our friends, we're just doing a comedy show.
We're not advocating any sort of unhealthy behavior.
We never would.
Absolutely.
We're in the slack here.
We wouldn't even think of that.
Slack, love, frop.
If we thought of that, if we dreamed of it, we'd wake up and apologize.
If we dreamed of it, we'd wake up and apologize.
We were going to legalize something.
We legalized Habifrop Zipulops.
We have the money earwigs in our earrings.
Right.
When is Ohio going to vote on Habifrop Zipulops, or frop for short?
Oh, never, never, never, never, never.
That reminds me.
We forgot to bring those ... Oh, well.
Is that a Radiothon giveaway?
Yeah.
That's a good Radiothon giveaway.
Yeah, a Radiothon giveaway.
Free frop.
He forgot his premiums.
Yeah.
It makes you forget your premiums.
This is our jockstrap collection I own.
That's the problem with the frop.
It makes you forget.
You forget your premiums.
In fact, this is the saddest thing.
When the drug user gets so high, he forgets all his other drugs.
You know, that's the saddest thing.
The drug user wakes up the next morning and goes, I forgot to take my heroin and my LSD.
I smoked too much frop, and I forgot my heroin.
Oh, darn.
I was going to overdose and everything.
Got my heroin.
Yeah, just like them people on TV.
Well, you can't hide from Bob, friends.
And we know that half the people listening to the Hour of Slack and using the subgenius
Facebook pages aren't actually dues-paying subgeniuses yet, but still pink in the eyes
of Bob and everybody else who counts.
It's a serious and crippling problem, but it can be solved very easily.
But I can't tell you how.
How about that?
Talk about a conspiracy.
Mm-hmm.
Yes, sir.
I'm going to ask you a question.
Well, you know, sadder things have been said.
You're saying it is a sad thing, but just think of the sinking of the lunatic and the
few of the other small vesicles that made their way past the department.
They thought the lunatic was unsinkable, too.
What?
Just like a fat woman or something.
I don't know if that's really true or not.
It's just handed down from the foot to the cartwheel.
Unsinkable?
I don't know.
I'd like to find out in a fun way, though.
Oh, ha ha.
Oh, actually, we should be happy and say something happy.
There's two new stations, broadcast stations, carrying the Hour of Slack.
No, get out of town.
Yes, so let's ... Well, actually, we've been on our beloved other WREK in Atlanta, for instance,
WORT in Madison for months.
Many, many, many years.
But the latest new ones are WOZO, WOZO in Knoxville, Tennessee.
Praise Bob, Hour of Slack.
Praise Bob.
And it's on with the Fugue Segway show, which is an interesting original show, and WLSL
in Dade City, Florida.
Oh, yeah.
Wow.
They are also playing the Hour of Slack now.
So, hello, Dade City, Florida, and Knoxville, Tennessee.
Yes.
We'll be driving through Knoxville in about a month or two, but not stopping.
Be looking for a ... Welcome to the origami, I mean, the fold, I mean, you know.
Yeah.
That made perfectly sense to me.
Yeah, brother, love, this is before your time, but the Hour of Slack, this used to just be
another station that we mailed the show to.
And they paid me for it.
I used to get five bucks a show.
Of course, that's my ...
It's not how much it cost to mail a cassette.
Yeah.
But my phone is ringing.
I'm not going to ... It's Priestess Pisces, and she should know better.
Oh, my goodness.
She's been trying to get ahold of me all week.
I mean, I've been trying to get ahold of her.
That rascally gal.
We've been going back and forth.
Oh, Lordy.
She was a big star of last week's show.
She's quite a rapscallion.
What the hell's a rapscallion, anyway?
It's a type of vegetable, believe it or not, that is formed by a plant.
It's formed like a hand shooting the finger.
A rapscallion?
Yes.
In Monster Hunter.
I know that ...
It's a vegetable.
That was a word that was ...
Well, aren't we all ...
It bloomed large in my grandmother's lexicon.
Was rapscallion?
Rapscallion, yes.
Just add two cups of moist rapscallion and a turn of butter.
Pound the cakes down until they're solid and smooth, and wrap around in gravy and bits
quits.
Oh, my goodness.
That's saliva all over the ...
It's not an onion that rocks the microphone?
Yeah.
Yeah, man.
There's also two new subgenius music albums.
Bob's Song 7, called Bob's Prolapsed Something Something, and Bob's Songs 8, also known as
Orally Transmitted Diseases.
That's oral.
You can actually hear ...
... everything on those for free if you want to.
And all you have to do really is look at subgenius.com, and it will make itself pretty
obvious when you see the little word download and music albums and all that.
It's a delightful world unto itself.
There's a Lonesome Cowboy Dave song on there that you probably don't remember because you
only sang it once on Chaz's show.
You just made it up off the top of your head.
Why?
I just put it on there.
I love Bob, and Bob loves me.
And me, me, me, me, me, I'm on a funny little tree.
Something like that.
I can't do that.
That's why he's so lonesome.
What he bring in ... Well, to me, like the work mongers, the rest of these people that
want to build nuclear fuels across the United States even while everybody's still arguing
about the ...
the most recent accidents.
Wouldn't you say that's kind of a conflict
of interest between like
maybe Strumpet Dumpet,
what's his name, and the
Marquess of Queensberry?
No, I'm sorry.
Well, it doesn't matter.
No matter what you ask him, he's got a plan.
He won't tell you what it is,
but he's got a plan, and he knows all the right people.
Yep.
And he doesn't know
anything about the government.
That's the important thing.
He knows what's for you.
That's a matter to brag about now.
I will make the best leader
because I have never led.
I know nothing
about what I'm taking on,
and that's why I
always lie, and I'm always right.
So vote for me, Bob Dabs.
And if you don't, you're all
trumped, all of you.
Bunch of trump wads.
Dingle dags.
Trump wads.
Yeah.
I'd slap them all if I had a big enough hand
or foot or I could even think
that far, you know?
When you just like, you just go
across thousands of them.
Just like a little
lightning bug ready to spiel.
Okay.
Yeah.
Well, you know what I mean.
No.
No, but when I play the recording back online.
Maybe perhaps a lady's glove
from late 1950s.
Are you advocating
slappery?
Slapping Trump?
You want to trump slapping, don't you?
Trump slapping, yeah.
Make him your little trump.
Son of a trump.
Trump him up.
And he is a trumpet.
He can trump his own trump.
Hey, what else rhymes
with trump dump?
Pump, hump,
jump.
Pump, trump, dump, trump.
I'm going to trump you up.
We've been quoting Arnold Schwarzenegger
lately because we saw that third,
fifth, the fifth Terminator movie.
Arnold came back from retirement
to act in that.
And then went back and looked at
all of the Terminator movies.
Princess, we had not seen the original one.
She saw the most recent one,
which makes for a confusing,
confusing beginning.
But the important thing is...
Was the fourth one really terrible?
Huh?
I hear...
Well, let's see.
That was the one with Batman in it, right?
Right.
Christian Bale
was in the fourth one.
Right.
Yeah.
No, it wasn't that terrible,
but it wasn't...
I don't know.
I don't remember it well enough,
but the point about the new one is...
Okay, Arnold Schwarzenegger's
in his...
He's in his 70s now.
He's pushing 70,
if he's not over 70.
And he plays...
They show the young Arnold bot
and a 50-year-old Arnold bot,
both of which had to be done in CGI.
The only one they couldn't do,
they didn't need to do in CGI,
was the 70-year-old Arnold bot.
But the cool line from that one,
the take-home line is...
Old.
Not obsolete.
Right.
Yes.
Three times during the course of the movie,
he gets to say,
Old.
As opposed to obsolete.
Not obsolete.
At one point, his hand messes up
and it's going...
Like, you can hear the little servo motors
getting caught,
and he bangs it on the table
and looks at the hero and goes,
Old.
And then the hero goes,
But not obsolete.
And then they go and kill the bad guys.
But of course, you know,
you can't leave a Terminator robot around
in our time.
Because, Scott,
that just leads somebody
to invent Skynet all over again.
But why do they have to,
when they go out on these campaigns
across the country
to build awareness
of the most current movie stuff,
why do they always have to wear
those, like, green diaper things
and stuff like that?
Why can't they just wear
a common, ordinary Japanese business suit
or a pair of Toreador pants, perhaps?
Well, let's say you'll know
which ones are Terminators
and which ones are politicians.
Oh, yeah, of course.
Otherwise, it's kind of hard
to tell the difference.
They're all old.
They're all Trumpy.
Yeah, everything's old.
They all got back buttons, too,
so stay out of the way.
Stay a certain distance.
Oh, yes.
What's this world coming to?
I'm so glad I'll be dead
40 years from now
at the very, you know,
there's no way I could last another,
I'd be 102 in 40 years.
I don't want to see
what's going on then
because I have a sneaking sense
of suspicion
that in the words of Frank Zappa,
it won't all blow up and disappear.
It'll just look ugly
for a thousand years.
Yes.
But we won't have to worry
about that, will we, Dave?
Because we'll be dead, dead, dead,
and gone, almost certainly,
unless some idiot
invents the singularity
and turns us into Terminators.
Trumps, Terminators, same difference.
Trumpinators?
Trumpinators.
Yeah, the Trumpinator.
Trump rhymes with Trump as well.
Right, Trump.
Are you a Trump chump, my friend?
Of course, you know what they're going.
Well, you probably think
that Hillary is going to save
all your problems
and she's going to give you
everything for free
because that's all Democrats want.
It's just everything for free
because no Democrat
has ever had a job.
I want you to know that.
I've never known a Democrat
to have a job.
I tell everybody what I think
and I've never heard
a single one of them
tell me they was going to vote
for Hillary Clinton.
I read on the internet today
that Obama was the most
monstrous individual
who has ever lived
on the planet Earth.
I'm not kidding.
Wow.
A very, very butthurt
Yahoo commenter
had that to say.
Okay, Obama was so much worse
than Hitler, Stalin, Pol Pot
put together.
Oh, my goodness.
Well, look what he's done.
He's destroyed America.
We're just sitting here,
being able to say this
and nobody's killed us yet.
That proves that America
is destroyed.
If Reverend Ivan Stein
can get on there
and make fun of Trump,
then what kind of a country is this?
Obama must die!
Hillary's going to be impeached
the first day she's in office.
She's going to be impeached
and put in jail
because you know what they do
for treason?
Hang.
Hanging.
First day she's in office,
she's going to be impeached.
She's going to be impeached and hung.
It's another thing that I have read
numerous times over and over again.
The spelling is almost always the same
every time they say that.
I wonder if...
Oh, well.
They just paint it.
I'm sure it's spontaneous.
I'm sure there's nobody
coordinating these things.
That would be crazy.
Only rich people could afford that.
Only very, very rich brothers
could ever afford to pay people
to sit and post nonsense
on the internet.
And create an echo chamber.
Oh, yeah.
It's going to sell 52 million.
That's nothing.
What's that?
Yeah, that's pocket change.
That's me about a year and a half.
Right.
Or the late 40s.
Or 50s.
That was a lot, right?
I guess that would probably be
about 10 times what it sounds like now.
So, yeah, it'd be about 500 million
instead of 50 million.
That's a fair shake.
That's a good piece of change.
So, the Kochs Pappies
made money off Stalin?
Yeah.
Well, how could he make money
off communists?
Communists don't even know
what money is.
They don't know what God is.
They don't know what money is.
All they know is slavery
and they think it's slack.
They think it's slack.
And diaphanies.
I hope so.
They're really good on Twitter.
That's what they're...
Burmese Sambers.
He's a communist, socialist, Nazi.
Same thing.
All the same thing.
Muslim.
They're all the same.
That's the same exact definition.
You said Muslim.
You didn't say Muslime.
You always say Muslime.
No, actually,
I prefer to say Muslamics.
Right.
Muslamics.
Which is actually not one
that you hear people say all the time.
My son made that up
to make fun of people
who are complaining.
All the time
about something
they never actually see.
Hmm.
But they hear about it
from each other.
And that's the important thing.
I am the master
of many a fine singing.
I'm sorry.
That's my group.
Joe Joplin.
I'm sorry.
Dave, I can hear
the voices in your head.
Yeah, we just heard it.
You're not the only one
hearing them this time.
Goodness.
That was chilling.
I can barely hear it.
Yeah.
I've been spending a lot.
I kept it under fruit wire
for a long time.
Like they used,
you know,
the Norwegian days
when they used to build
those big husky vitamin C's.
And sometimes
the whole swamp
would be full of them.
Just like burbling up
like in Dante's Inferno,
you know?
That's the part I didn't like
because it's too loose a fabric.
You just kind of lose your mind.
No, lose your mind?
No, Dave.
Oh, I can't imagine
something like that happening
around here.
Well, it's free.
On the internet.
On this show.
Building enormous ascorbic acids?
Yes.
Especially if you're planning
to actually exit
on X day
and so far
as yet to materialize.
Hmm.
Wait a minute.
You're talking vitamin C,
did you say?
That's coffee, right?
Yeah.
It's copy grass,
coffee,
carnivorous wax.
Yeah, it's an important
vitamin your body needs,
coffee.
Actually, I think the C
stands for caffeine.
Ah.
Okay.
Like vitamin S, salt,
vitamin G, grease.
Grease.
Those are the important vitamins.
It makes me hungry
just thinking about it.
Well, that's the problem
with many people
who worship the devil
is they assume
their problems
with their agronomy
and growing things,
the little vegetables
that they create.
Like you, Dave.
Oh, yeah.
Like I'm one of their little vegetables.
I'm Satan's carrot or something.
Yeah, you're Monsanto's
Franken-Dave.
Monsanto grows Franken-Daves
and they get out
into the environment
and they kill off
all the natural daves.
Wow.
Uh-oh.
Because they are powerful.
That sounds dangerous.
The bees are sick and tired of it
because there's no real daves
to suckle on.
Franken-Dave is
ugly.
Our kids aren't going to know
what real daves
are like anymore.
You can still find them
in Amish country.
Okay.
But that's about it.
Yeah, the Franken-Daves
are big and strong.
They're ugly
and they're covered with scars
and they have electrodes
in their necks
but they're strong
and they'll live forever.
I like the naturally occurring daves.
Myself.
Yeah, but they rot real fast
before you even get them
to the store.
They're all bruised up.
Just look at this one.
He's covered with bruises.
He actually is, too.
Unfortunately, friends,
if you believed in prayer,
I'd ask you to pray
for Dave's shoulder
but we won't do that
because we don't know
who might be listening.
Yeah.
The devil might be listening.
On the other hand...
As a matter of fact,
if you wouldn't mind
signing your name
and giving us
every bit of financial
and information
that you might have,
we would at least like
to know who you are
and where you're from.
Where you live
and what your credit card number is.
You mean all our hippy-dippy listeners
can't send their healing energies
toward Dave's shoulder?
They can.
They must.
But the problem is
that there's other...
You know,
somebody else might go,
well, I know how to get Dave now.
I'm going to send
injury vibes.
I'll send a doubt
and hurt energy towards Dave
because I don't like
that Lone Camp boy.
Dave, he confuses me
and makes me feel stupid.
The injury reiki?
Yeah.
It confuses.
Yeah, it makes me confused.
I don't like that stuff.
It makes me...
Yeah.
It makes me feel angry.
And alienated
and brushed
and dark
and full of anger.
Yeah.
And alienated
and brushed.
Yeah.
Anger.
Oh, it feels so good.
Especially when you
type out that
cutting,
cutting put down
and push send.
Oh, you're such a
brave, anonymous man
when you do that.
Not you, Dave.
I'm not anonymous.
Poor old Dave
hardly even has
any kind of computer.
I'm hoping that he'll
get his started up
so that
so he can put his
put his hand out
like everybody else.
What are those?
They got the crowd
crowdfunding or that?
What's that?
Go fund me.
Yeah.
Yeah, right.
The new
the new
Go Trump yourself.
The new
funding program.
I've actually seen
people start
Go Fund Me
that so that they
could drink, you know,
send me money.
Yes.
Drink.
I can't afford to drink
as much as I want.
Didn't Janice Joplin
make a song about that?
Did she?
Yes.
Oh, Lord, won't you
buy me a night on the town?
Yes.
Perfect.
I'm counting on you, Lord.
Please don't let me down.
She did.
Prove that you love me
and buy the next round.
Yeah.
And Priestess Pisces
did a takeoff on it
last week at the very
end of this show.
Marvelous takeoff.
Well, they're certainly
not celibates.
We know that.
And we've witnessed
some of the strange
acrobatics.
Mom and Dad used to
report on the
History Channel,
as it were.
You've witnessed
Mom and Dad acrobatics?
Oh, of course.
At least when I was
into my late 50s
or 60s or 70s.
Wow!
Probably my late
100s or something
like that.
They'd fly by
just as rapidly
as a raven
in the Mad Men's
scrawl.
Wow.
Dave's parents
were circus people,
you know.
I did not know that.
Yeah.
They weren't actually
the main acrobats.
They did do acrobatics.
They were involved
in another...
They dressed like clowns
and did milder acrobatics.
There was the one
accident one time.
He said that they
cut a rope
or that the...
something was wrong
with the main line
and so that's why...
Cut the cheese.
Cut the something.
Princess Andrew's
Lena
actually
fell on top
of somebody
and broke
the person's
foot.
But that was
mostly happening
in the sideshow,
wasn't it?
Not the main...
tent.
No.
Well, there were
a couple big tent shows
but no,
they were mostly
in the sideshow.
That's okay, Dave.
Most of our friends
in the circus
are the sideshow
people too.
They're all bearded.
They're all...
No, just the ladies.
Andrew the Impaled
and David Apocalypse,
they're sideshow
performers
and they're not...
They're not...
They're both
clean-shaven
fellas.
Absolutely.
One thing you could say
is...
They're covered
with blood
and scars
and tattoos.
You know?
You can really
Those aren't tattoos,
Princess Wee.
Uh-oh.
Those are tumors.
They're very
artistic tumors.
I see.
Very artistic.
Designer tumors.
Yeah, the one
happens to look
kind of like a skull.
That's why you
thought it was a tattoo.
Ah, okay.
Yeah.
They grew those
themselves.
Wow.
They just injected
some Trump
under their skin.
Well, it's almost
harvest time.
That's what we should
be thinking of, comrades.
These tumors
are about to be picked
at the height
of their flavor
and delicacy
and taken
to the nearest market
to make the party,
Thomas ours,
and of course
the corporate heads
smaller than usual.
So let's all
get together right now
as quickly as we
possibly can.
Join together
in one vast movement
of silk and iron.
A movement of
depth and clarity.
And we can just
all just forget
about all the rest
too, please.
Thanks for the
hummingbirds.
You know.
Smaller heads,
did you say?
Much, much
smaller heads,
my friend.
The kind that only
the head of a pin
would compare to.
Ah.
Pin head.
So yeah,
the side right there,
we're back in the sideshow
in that remark.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's why
I started singing
Gibba Gabba,
We Accept You,
One of Us,
much in the same
vernacular as
The Church of the Subgenius.
We accept you
despite the fact
that you are
semi-functional.
You know,
I was in
Todd Browning's Freaks
when I was a teenager.
I was in that.
I was the chicken man.
He had great big glasses,
kind of a bald head
and a little bit of hair.
I was a little skittish
No, no, you didn't.
No, that was me
in high school.
You were a chicken man
in high school?
Yep.
1933, I think.
Yeah.
Did you win
the Robuster Award?
No, but I got paid.
I think it was
20 bucks a day
back then
for, you know,
sideshow people
in the movies.
Oh, that was
big money then.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
That was a real
good day's pay.
Chicken,
fried chicken
and pizza
or badly made
chicken?
Chinese food or?
Yeah, mostly
badly made
Chinese food.
Oh, that's
inexpensive.
my favorite.
That's everyone's
favorite today.
That's all I've ever
let me have
in this job.
Four walls, man.
That's the way it is.
Yeah.
We must accept
our own mutual
enslavement.
We've all helped
put each other
in these tiny
little cubicles
and now we won't
let each other out,
I believe,
perhaps.
Perhaps.
And we just have
to sit around
in this room
waiting another
week while all
the other victims
have to do their
shows.
Wait our turn
and then sit down
in the hot seat
and do our show.
There's no escape.
They don't let
Brother Love leave.
Dr. Sinister's
over there
in the other room.
Keith's asleep
underneath the
console in there.
Right.
The whole station,
everybody's,
they keep us here.
It's like a
submarine.
Yep.
Won't let you go.
You can tell
by the way these
shows sound
that we're victims.
We're prisoners.
We're kept here.
But luckily,
we'll only be here
for,
we only have to
keep talking
for another four,
no,
three and a half minutes.
Well,
he's just,
you know.
I love that last,
the last five seconds
of the show
because I know
that I'll be able
to shut up finally
and the listeners,
I know they feel
the same way.
They're crying
for the same thing.
They're going,
oh man,
I'm going to be so glad
when this show's over
and Stank can shut up
and I can,
well,
but then,
then what do they get?
Dr. Sinister
or whatever other
person is coming in
for our beloved
other sister stations.
You know.
Yes.
It's not Dr. Sinister
everywhere.
Not on every station.
Yeah.
But someday,
it will be Dr. Sinister
on every station
all day.
Hey,
it's the only hope
against Trump.
I don't think Dr. Sinister
is in on in Knoxville.
No.
No, no, no.
Now what do you mean
by he's not in on Knoxville?
Well, I was saying
we're on the air
in Knoxville
once a week now
by the miracle of
Oh yeah, of course.
That's right.
Me mailing CDs
to Knoxville actually
is how that works.
I was wearing
the sunglasses
and the pig nose.
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
I used to mail cassettes
to WCSB
from Dallas.
But the female cassettes
were the ones
that you were
most particularly
interested
at least in your career
there before
all of the problems
with the law
and a couple
of underage
elderly women.
Now, Dave,
I'm going to have
to fade you out
if you keep this up.
We've made an agreement.
No more
dirty laundry
old history now.
But it's such good talk.
You know,
it's good talk radio, man.
To hear the things
that you had to go through
to make things worse
in your life.
Didn't you?
You do represent a model
that we can all look up to
and go,
what the hell
are we looking at?
It's a contradiction
in terms.
Good talk radio.
That's like
good daytime TV.
Yeah, right.
Or good mime.
No, that's a little
No, you wouldn't see again.
You're bringing up
my sad past.
I'm sorry.
I love mimes.
You know that.
Good tofu.
You love everything.
Well, yes.
I had dressed up
like a Snoopy
as a Christmas dog
one time.
Okay, I've got to
we've got to get out of here now.
What kind of
goofy thing
can I put on
to get it?
Beethoven.
A little bit of the old
you know
Ludwig van
and that there.
No.
No, I'm just going to
put on a nice little
mysterious instrumental
by Reverend A.T.
Old history.
By Reverend A.T.?
Yeah, Reverend A.T.
sent some music.
Cool beans.
Hey, you know what we didn't
we never did?
We never read through
Charlie Worsham's thing.
Charlie in New York
or someplace far away.
He was actually a contributor
to subgenius shows
back in the 80s.
And he sent a letter here
with a note that said
open them on the air
and tell us what you have.
And it's wacky packaging.
I think you should keep that
for the next show.
Hostage filled cupcakes.
Screech tragic embalming type.
Dampers.
Sure to rust your hampers.
Irish ring leaves rings
around your tub, Agora.
And armor hot dogs.
Armor metal encased hot dogs.
Some of those are
dead on the same
as old brain rot.
For instance,
the hostage cupcakes.
Well, hostage, yeah.
Hostage filled
with mud cupcakes.
The food kidnappers
give their victims.
Oh, that's weird.
Well, we expanded it
and in a different direction.
Screech tragic embalming type.
Well, happy Halloween, everyone.
If the metal encased hot dog
was empty,
it would be a Halloweener.
Oh, stop it, you.
Okay, well, we'll see
something somewhere someday.
Perhaps.
There.
Okay, there's Reverend Castro.
He might000.
He's music.
I'm out of here.
Bye, Dave.
Bye, everyone.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Oh.
Thank you.