I see no reason for violence.
Sex.
If, however, you are confronted, you may result in...
So genius.
Bug sex.
So now we can hug our fleas and ticks, too.
Yes.
American tits.
Sex.
Don't kill flies with our nostrils.
From PR News in Washington, I'm drifting lower on Twitter.
Two of President Trump's cabinet secretaries burned more than 200,000 acres and left seven people dead today on Twitter.
The U.S. Forest Service is part of the Department of Press Conference.
The Cal Fire has the Car Fire and stressed the importance of PR News in Montana.
The president has been attacking PR's reports on federal Twitter.
He's charged with tax fraud not related to his work on Twitter.
The Dow is 5-7.
Officials say they don't know yet whether they're attacking PR News on Twitter, accidentally or on purpose, today.
Afghan officials say hundreds of people have been killed.
In four days of federal tweeting in the city of Seattle, officials say 30 civilians were also killed with the help of U.S. tweet strikes.
The Trump is getting cheated by shady lending practices.
PR reports.
The White House appears predatory and people can get PR news.
The West Virginia House of Delegates agreed to plead guilty to using state-owned PR News for personal use today.
One, two, three, four.
Four.
clumsy
Bobb.
Four, three, two, one.
región
dialogue
television
TV
Thank you.
You're a c-c-d-e-a-c-t-g-a-a-c
We're going nuts with my c-c-t-g-a-t-a-t
My airs nice like it's down today
In a sapiosexual way
I said let's get it down today
Bob?
Oh my!
I'll tell him!
Bob?
Of course!
Don't, don't, don't!
Bob?
Gosh!
Yeah, that's it!
Oh!
Bob?
Ah!
Fuck!
Bob?
Father!
He is a very fast man
I can run right through his wall
They'll laugh when I see
I can fly through his wall
Oh!
Maybe if I vibrate fast enough
Yeah
I can catch his flow
On their city
Why are you so weird?
Oh!
They say
Why are you so weird?
And they say
Why am I easy?
Yes, they say
Why are you so weird?
Oh!
And they say
Why do you talk that way?
I don't know
Why am I so weird?
This'll no longer be
The way to the hopeless
When she comes back to me
Oh!
And they say
Why are you so weird?
Oh!
They say
Why are you so weird?
They wanna know
Why do I believe that she could
Be brought back to me?
They say
Don't you know she's dead?
Yes, I know
I know it in my head
But I don't
I don't feel it in my head
Because I don't believe in it
I don't believe in loose
I don't feel it
I don't think I expressed it
I don't even know where she Cc
I'm 20 years old
No way
At that fee claim
I don't feel it
I don't know how to commit
I just, you know
Because we're friends
Thank you.
I felt that he had just a little too much pizzicato!
In the enghante...
Didn't you?
No...
Get up out of bed.
Sour on my head.
Drinking down a cup.
Trying to wake up
Driving across town
Feeling like a clown
Some guy's in my lane
Put a bullet through his window pane
Pull into the lot
Got them horses, got my favorite spot
Greeting everyone
Trying to act, trying to act dumb
I don't belong here
But then of course the question is then where?
I'm plagued by one great doubt
It's become what my life's all about
If I had done that
I wouldn't have to do this
Get up out of bed
Shower on my head
Throwing back a cup
Trying to wake up
Slapping across town
Feeling like a clown
Some guy's in my lane
Put a bullet through his window pane
I'm plagued by one great doubt
It's become what my life's all about
If I had done that
I wouldn't have to do this
To do this
If I had done that
I wouldn't have
To do this
If I had done that
I wouldn't have
To do this
If I had done that
And now the finale.
Here we go.
A 17 year old man presented with a 3 day history of double vision on upward gaze after having
been struck in the right eye with a clenched fist.
A 76 year old man fell from a 6 foot ladder incurring trauma to the right side of the
face.
A 21 year old man presented with a laceration and swelling of the dorsum of his right hand.
A 30 year old man had been bitten by a snake that he kicked up while it was crossing his
driveway.
A 22 year old man presented with fever, malaise, headache, and rash of the palms of his hands
and soles of his feet.
A 53 year old man presented with low grade fever and abdominal pain.
An unresponsive 26 year old woman had been found in a hotel room.
A 4 year old girl presented with 1.5 cm of pain.
A 28 year old woman complained of a foreign body sensation and redness of the outer lower
quadrant of her left eye of 2 days duration.
A 73 year old woman presented with fever and right arm pain and redness.
A 17 year old young man presented with pain, tingling, swelling, and oozing from tooth
puncture, wounds in his right middle and ring fingertips 30 minutes following having been
bitten by a snake.
An 80 year old woman was found lying down in her backyard.
Her rectal temperature was 80 degrees Fahrenheit.
A 52 year old man presented with a painful, pruritic, air venomous rash to his left anterior
chest wall that occurred after he dried himself off with a towel in which a pus caterpillar
was found.
Heirs to the largest fortune of its kind in the world today.
The most famous and most famous person in the history of human history.
Who are they?
You're one of them.
We were sent to crush you today
Oh, you will be crushed
You will be crushed
Don't say another word
Kneel down and hush
There's nothing you can say
And nothing you can do
Cause we are the ones
Sent to crush you
You will be crushed
Dismantled and vaporized
And when we're done with you
We'll be laughing at all of your lies
You will be crushed
And ripped to a thousand shreds
And while you're bleeding
We'll be making sure your blood is red
You will be crushed
You will be totally crushed
Don't say another word
Kneel down and hush
There's nothing you can say
And nothing you can do
Cause we are the ones
Sent to crush you
You will be crushed
Like you've never been crushed before
And when we're done with you
You'll be wishing and wanting for more
You will be crushed
And torn limb from limb
Because we don't need you
And now it's our own time to win
You will be crushed
You will be totally crushed
Don't say another word
Kneel down and hush
There's nothing you can say
And nothing you can do
Cause we are the ones
Sent to crush you
You will be crushed
Dismantled and vaporized
And when we're done with you
We'll be laughing at all of your cries
You will be crushed
And taken far away
Because we don't like you
And now it's our turn to play
You will be crushed
You will be totally crushed
Don't say another word
Kneel down and hush
There's nothing you can say
And nothing you can do
Cause we are the ones
Sent to crush you
You will be crushed
Oh, you will be crushed
Yes, you will be crushed
Yes, you will be
Oh, yes, dear friends.
You will be crushed
By one thousand leagues
Under my nutsack.
And I think now there may be...
What? What, what?
What was that?
What, what, what?
What? What?
What? Did I just drop Dave?
I think I accidentally just dropped Dave.
Now, oh, it's...
Don't drop Dave.
No, I don't want to drop him.
Hello? Test, test, Dave.
Test, test, test, test.
There, there, okay.
There you go.
Monsonaris time.
Once again, the old land of the Monsonaris diseases.
I've got this sneaking suspicion
that we're pretty soon in this decade,
we're not going to be able to make fun of religion anymore.
You're going to be out of work, Stang.
Well, I'm not making fun of religion.
Who's making fun of religion?
I'm promoting, I'm promoting a religion
that can encompass all other religions.
Do you get checked from the NRA?
Because we're a bunch of subgeniuses,
so we'll believe anything.
Yeah.
Yeah, I mean, no, wait.
Do you get checked from the NRA
or any other people like that?
Uh...
Come on now, wake up, bro.
You know it's true.
Not big enough to report, no.
No.
Well, that's what many have said
about your sexual Monsonaris,
it's not too big to report.
And that's why everybody in every small town
knew how large or enormously small I was.
And it's not right.
That is not right.
You know what I mean?
No, that's not right at all.
I mean, I don't know, it's a very small town,
but I don't know everybody I see.
People smirk at me and stuff.
I don't even know who they are.
That's not right.
Well, they probably don't know who you are either, Dave.
Oh, I don't know who I are either, Dave.
Well, you know, Dave,
we're just unlearning oppressive behaviors
and decolonizing our minds.
Because, you know, we reek of privilege.
I'm sorry.
I need to stay in my lane.
Yeah.
It's true.
If I say anything on this show,
if it's stepping out of place,
let me know so I can make apologies and erase it.
That's the problem, though, that you won't,
because you are going to be,
you will be attempted to at least stop you
from doing these things as long as they can right now,
you know, in real time.
But you see, Dave,
my ignorance has caused harm in the past.
If I don't call out my friends today, who will?
That's true.
Makes you kind of wonder.
Well, you know,
it's because realizing the extent of my own privilege
is a conscious excavation.
I'm inherently violent.
Acknowledging the harm I've caused is a painful,
it's a painful experience, Dave.
You're ultra-violent, you're purple,
or you're ultra-violent like in Clockwork Orange,
or you're what?
Well, you know,
I don't know.
I don't think we really make ourselves feel better
by putting on safety pins and announcing that we're allies.
Well, I'm afraid you're right.
I shouldn't be in charge of anything.
God, if you ever said anything,
it's definitely so much sense to me.
I'm the worst.
You are.
My parents made a moral error when they conceived me.
He has his father's eyes.
Just my identity causes violence.
You mean like if you walk into a room
and they're eating pan-fried Texas-style steaks,
they're ultra-rare on every side and everything like that,
and you announce to the world you're coming in,
you got six guns, one on each blazing hip,
for the other...
Well...
What happens then?
Then I renounce my masculinity
because it's an unhealable illness.
No.
You're supposed to renounce Satan.
Renounce Satan.
I was infected with racism at birth,
and it's gonna take me the rest of my life to get over it.
I'm sorry for my unkind.
You're not a very kind person to be...
I don't know what you're basically talking about,
but in the clouds, I do wonder and do kind of spread asunder
and do believe you're onto something real deep, man.
Well, I'm not a very kind person.
Well, you know, this is just one example
of a long history of violence and erasure
and appropriation and shaming and hatred.
I'm so sorry.
I'm a plague on society.
And even my tears are a form of emotional and psychological violence.
I'm sorry.
Well, I shouldn't do...
You...
I've learned of things I shouldn't have done,
and I just didn't realize.
It's been an amazing learning experience,
and I'm sorry.
But what kind of a political spectrum do you represent?
Because I'm getting those weird-looking, like,
flashes over the phone that, like, somebody's not listening.
I don't know what you would call it.
Can you hear me?
I self-identify as a puppy.
You self-identify as a...
...self-identify as a puppy?
Yeah.
And who cleans up your poo-poo?
A sad puppy.
Who cleans up your sad poo-poo, sad puppy?
I'm...
I'm inherently violent.
No one.
David, if any of that...
The church hierarchy...
...didn't sound exactly like Reverend Stang.
It was...
He was...
He was copping lines from social justice puppies.
I'm outing you.
Oh.
No, I forget the name of the guy that wrote this.
You're out.
Yeah.
I'm outing you.
I'm an outie.
No, man.
I'm actually an innie.
I'm in with the in crowd.
Well, keep eating those pork chops and fried chicken and you'll be...
You'll...
The in crowd at the Stumble Inn is my favorite one.
Is that a real place that we've been before?
In Dallas.
Yeah.
This is real.
It was a real place in Dallas.
But, yeah.
I'm sorry, Dave.
I don't know if any of the listeners in the Cleveland area remember the Big Egg.
The Big Egg?
You remember the Big Egg?
I remember the Big Egg, of course.
Right down the street from...
The breakfast place?
Yes.
Wasn't he a Spider-Man villain?
The Big Egg.
Yeah, the Big Egg.
Yeah, he used to hang out at the Public Theater Annex.
Right by Cleveland Public Theater.
Across from Anon.
Right by the Annex there.
Yeah.
And there were like four or five women that weighed well over 300 pounds.
which was really, really, really weird.
Yes.
Firstly, they could, like, load up plates of trays on their armpits.
Like, they were walking like they were jocular,
dancing around some kind of ancient dance, you know?
He speaks truth.
This was a topless restaurant, right?
Well, it was like a headless horse restaurant.
Oh, man, if it was topless, that would be like a really bad dream.
They don't even have heads.
Yeah, especially if somebody was in the mammalian stupor,
whatever you call it, when you're giving milk, you know?
I haven't donated my sperm species in five weeks,
so I'm clean, I'm good to go.
I meet all the criteria, all the stamps are passed up and standardized.
You listening, ladies?
Yeah.
Dave's ready to make a deposit any time.
I'm not sure of what.
What do you mean you're not sure of what?
I taste the nervous agony and the psychological disunity in your voice there.
I see what you're trying to say.
You're saying that I don't have no sperms, right?
No.
No, no, not at all.
We were advertising the fact that you had finally built up some
and were ready to let go, you know, and man up.
I'm ready to come back.
I'm ready to colonize and repopulate your computer.
I'm going to stand up and sit down and shut up again because I can't get started.
But believe you me, I'm going to...
Haven't you heard of eugenics, man?
Sure.
Yeah.
Sure, that's sort of like...
Look like me, talk like me, smell like me, and all that stuff.
So you want to make more little Daves?
Yeah.
I need protections.
Well, ladies...
Ladies, get on down to the Dunsome Lowboy Cave in Ashtabula,
and there you'll find Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
Hey, how'd you like that name for your hotel, Dunsome Lowboy Cave?
Yeah, I like that.
Oh, I like that. It's a good name, yeah.
Yeah.
It kind of describes what's going on, but it's more illusionary, A-L-L-usionary,
not I-L-L-U-A-sionary.
You know, crazy.
Creates an illusion.
It's a cave where they've done some lowboy.
Yeah, and there's chicken spread there, too, and they had a whole bunch of topical ointments.
I remember they were selling...
There were a lot of stands that cost too much money, you know what I mean?
Yeah.
A lot of people just couldn't afford to have a space this year at the fair.
Don't you understand what I'm saying?
No.
I don't either.
You got me totally lost, Dave.
Why not?
Don't ask me why we don't understand what you're saying.
I was trying so hard.
I'm sorry, man.
I'm inherently violent.
That's right.
I forgot.
A reek of privilege, man.
I'm sorry.
Hey, who's that?
The president of SIAM or somebody originally from Ashtabula?
What?
The president of SIAM.
Now, is that the one they call Thailand now?
Thailand has finally agreed to have medicinal marijuana and get away from its...
Back to its old, old, old Chinese medicine style medicine and get away from the DEA-enforced
American view of getting rid of marijuana and said now they're going to get back into
research.
All they have to do is just...
Well, what's up before the French and the British and the Americans came over there
and ruined everything?
That's my opinion.
You know, Dave, actually, it's funny.
I worked in China for six weeks in Beijing in the 80s, and these college students that
were traveling around China on a bus told me that they'd looked out the window along
the highway and saw these endless fields of...
Marijuana growing.
Now, I guess we might call that hemp, but they made the bus driver stop and they ran
over and gathered a whole bunch of it.
They were so excited.
Now, probably what they were gathering was what we might call highway dirt weed.
But when I was walking down the street, I suddenly knew somehow that there was somebody
smoking hashish right around me.
And I looked down and there was a...
There was a little man who didn't look like a Han Chinese.
He looked ethnical, like a Tibetan or something.
And he was sitting there crouched and smoking on a little pipe.
And it was full of marijuana.
Wow.
I thought, well, they were supposedly...
See, if you got caught with marijuana in China in those days, they'd shoot you in a stadium
and then charge your...
And they'd charge your family for the bullet.
But I guess it was okay if it was a Tibetan just smoking guangua or whatever he happened
to call it.
Is that why they hate Tibetans?
Well, I don't know.
So they were getting away with murder.
And I heard that they legalized hemp growing in Ohio and also Texas, which means they
have to test everything because what you're smoking or carrying in your car might just
be legal hemp.
Plain old ordinary hemp.
Plus more states now have legalized legislations.
This is Arizona.
In Arizona, there's a fly trap of...
I'm sorry, go right.
Yeah.
You wouldn't believe some of the deals that we're making for branding CBD out of...
Well, a certain subgenius who lives in the legalizing state of New York.
Nevada is planning to use a brand name that I own for one of those products.
Yeah.
And we should even get sort of paid for it.
But the important thing is, Dave, I renounced drugs a long, long, long time ago.
Yeah, like three weeks ago.
No, no.
I mean, when I was like five, six years old, I said, no, I'm just not going to do any more
than that.
I'm not going to take a big old hefty puff of that, even though I'm three and a half
years old and I got my...
It was weird, like sailor pants and everything.
Right.
And the cute little hat.
Cute little hat.
Well, yeah.
Yeah.
All the other kids were, but I...
My mama used to dress you up as a monkey because you would stop teasing the other kids and
radicalize them.
Sometimes you dress up like Lenine, the famed Russian revolutionary.
You know, they have a little goatee and everything and you give speeches.
I don't know.
They used to call me Little Lord Fropleroy.
But then when I was, like I say, when I was about five, I decided to swear off that stuff
and I quit.
But Dave, I have to confess something to you.
No, you don't.
Okay.
But I'm going to anyway.
I'm messed up on...
I'm messed up tonight.
I came in to the station.
It's against the rules, but I came into the station under the influence of...
Well, I'm messed up on apps.
Man, I'm messed up on apps.
He can't stop, man.
He's hooked.
His brain is cooked.
He can't stop.
Yeah.
I've actually...
Yeah, it is the worst thing you can do, actually, man.
I was...
I've been apped up all weekend.
I know it's an appdiction, I guess you could say.
You know, Dave, it's like in that book, Neighbor World.
Who wrote that?
Was it Kurt Vonnegut or somebody?
Oh, that's really a piece of futuristic literature.
Yeah.
Neighbor World, the novel by Kurt Vonnegut.
Is it Kurt Vonnegut?
Joseph Heller?
Thomas Pynchon?
One of those guys.
Some huge name in weirdo literature.
Won't your cowboy Dave meet?
William Burroughs?
No, Anthony Burgess wrote Neighbor World.
It's me.
Anyway, well, anyway, this one weird book...
Listen to this penguin on the back of the train.
People in it get high off of these light patterns.
They call it looming.
They get loomed in this book.
And...
I think I understand exactly what that's like because I've gotten to where I can't
stop getting these new little apps that when I push buttons on them, they make these colors
and these images and stuff.
And I just, you know, I can't stop.
I use up all the...
It's not just a dream, it's ugly reality, which have encroached in all of our synapses
together.
At one time, they just got in there and just co-opted everything to the point where there
is now a stem sublim and you can get loomed.
Why smoke a joint or drink a beer if you can just go and look, stare at a light pattern
for about five seconds and the next thing you know, you're...
Well, so far, I haven't like just put it on automatic where it just totally automatically
generates images.
I...
You don't want to do that anyway.
I still have some control over it.
I can pick the base image and, you know, but I...
It's like I use up all the tricks in hyperspective and then you have to get a new app or pay for
more hyperspective.
It is.
And then you got...
Then it was like, well, this isn't enough.
Now I need pixel loop.
And so you get really, really pixel looped.
But you use up all the images...
All the filters.
Yeah.
And the filters and things in that, the generators in it, and you have to spend money to get
new ones.
So the next thing you know, you're just, you know, you're robbing convenience stores to
pay for your new app.
Plus they also, in each of these newly released apps, they create commands for you to go out
and shoot people and stuff.
Things like that.
Oh, I didn't know about that.
Yeah.
All they ever made me want to do is...
You don't know because they haven't called you.
They haven't...
Go 645-4789.
You can call Stang anytime.
And then they do that a couple of times and they dance around and look real sissy, man.
And then you're like an Ashtabulean candidate.
You've been programmed, right?
Yeah.
So they'll tell you...
The messages in the looms tell you to go to the Walmart with a assault rifle.
And then you're like, you know, you're a real asshole.
And walk around looking like a big tough man.
Dave, Reverend Stang has been doing this app thing and becoming so hap, app happy that
he's starting to become this sort of a glowing orange color.
He's actually turning into an app-ricot.
No, that...
No, no.
Princess, wait.
That's...
It's called augmented...
I like that phrase, man.
It's called augmented reality.
Do you like apricot?
Augmented reality.
Oh, yeah.
I see.
But you can augment your reality in a customized way.
You know, I saw an app today, I don't have it yet, but that you can build little things
that you add to your reality that you see through your phone.
Oh.
So for instance, I could program it to where everybody that I looked at had Bob's face.
Or one of those skull faces.
Or one of those...
Like in They Live.
Wasn't...
Those Republican skull faces in They Live.
Remember those?
Yes.
Yeah.
I thought Puzzling Evidence was doing that quite a long time ago.
What, giving commands?
Programming things into his phone that would come into every picture he took, like spaceships
and...
No, actually, I used to do that a long time ago.
Oh.
On a video camera.
Yeah, you could take a picture of a dog's head, but it didn't automatically map onto
anything.
Oh.
Your thing...
Trademark G did that.
He used a Kinect camera, or one of those video game systems that follows your motion.
And he used that.
He set it up at X Day at the campground.
Everyone who walked in front of his camera could see a mirror, a giant image of themselves
on the screen.
But with the dog's head.
Only they all had Bob's head.
There'd be five or six people standing there dancing.
Wow.
And they'd all have Bob's head, and he was always looking at you.
So if you turned around, his head remained like an owl.
It could swivel all the way around.
It was creepy.
Yeah.
And fun.
Well, thank goodness for articles of faith like that to keep us, our minds, unencumbered
and clearly on the prize, whatever it might be, like maybe third prize, hopefully.
Yeah.
Well, you know, we send out...
We add subliminal messages to our...
Oh, there's music in the background is the Flyin' Ryan Brothers, and it's packed with
subliminals too.
But they're pretty...
They're actually not real harmful ones.
They're subliminals that make you want to do things like pick up trash on the highway
and plant trees and admit that you're inherently violent and that kind of thing.
You know?
Yeah.
And this show, of course, is constantly programming all of its listeners to...
Well, it's a dog whistle, basically.
Yeah, it is in there, and right here as well.
The believers know what we're saying.
Well, that's why I was asking if you think it's going to be a great crime or problem
to tease or poke religion at fun at.
I believe that the administration is trying to push through a...
some sort of bill or law that would make...
make it illegal to criticize conservatives or...
because that's censorship, you know?
Or repeating what they say or talking about them in any way except as gods.
That's going to be illegal on the internet.
Well, did you know that the crimes...
It's to prevent, you know, it's to prevent the liberal media from lying about it.
Well, it's to prevent them from lying about it.
Well, you know, liberals are very much into making and distorting everything.
It's like basically you won't be able to say anything that's liberal or scientific.
Well, you know, liberals give you commands to go into restaurant districts and start shooting randomly at your family and stuff.
Yeah, but with a camera.
And they just call that left wing.
Yeah, but no, they teach...
They're programming you to shoot selfies with their cameras.
You see, that's different.
Well, that's what they want you to do.
Can't you see what's happened?
Can't you see what they've done?
They've inserted the wrong quagmire.
Oh, you mean...
Not the wrong quagmire, please.
Well, it's like...
Well, you mean they're kind of like somebody changed the program from to use your iPhone to use your rifle with a scope and a bump stock?
Yeah.
And a bazooka and a pitchfork on the end that shoots knives?
Radioactive poison knives?
With quantum entanglement that turns everybody into walking dead zombies?
And werewolves, too.
Werewolf zombie walking deads?
Yeah, man.
That's what they're programming.
That's the way I want to go out.
That's what we just programmed.
Any listener kind of roughly under the age of 25 or so, and anyone with dementia or Alzheimer's, which is about the same thing as being under 25.
Which could be 250 years old as far as we know, you know?
Some of those Brazilian native people are like that.
Yeah.
They just get old forever.
Right.
And they go further into the Amazon jungle when Grandpa, that's not Grandpa, that's great-great-great-great-great-great-great-great-grandpa, and he's waving goodbye.
And they still bend these...
And they go play with the monkeys.
Yeah, they live to be 190 and they still smoke and drink and play with monkeys and do a lot of...
And isn't that...
That means...
But they also don't drive cars and they're kind of physically active all the time.
Well, the monkey drivers are just like golf carts and they just go in that one little area there.
Well, that's why you see so many obese monkeys that can't walk anymore because they're so used to driving those stupid little carts around.
They started out perfectly healthy.
Now look at them.
They look like Walmart shoppers.
Yeah.
No offense, folks.
I have spent lots of money at Walmart.
Right.
You got the walker out yourself quite a few times.
Yeah.
I bought a lot of walkers at Walmart.
I have to get a new one every three months.
They wear out so fast the way I use them.
I got to buy the cheap ones, you know, the really, really cheap.
Well, they're all cheap now, but there's a bunch of new lines on the market.
That doesn't mean there's any different kind of products.
It just means there's lines in the market, whatever the hell that is.
But there's new lines in the market and some of them are even dangerous to behold.
Oh, Dave, Dave, I have something I wanted to play for you.
Oh, okay.
I can hardly wait.
While you could hear it on the phone.
Well, first, okay, let me see.
First, I'm going to play the last Lemur thing.
I think.
Is there a drum in it?
Here we go.
First, it's a little, oh, it's a restaurant song.
It's only 23 minutes long.
But then after that, wait until you hear the song I'm going to play.
It's by my dog, Claudia.
Claudia Gabriel Tire Biter St. Clair.
But first, the restaurant song.
Let's go to a restaurant.
In them, they're all cotton fields at home.
We're the man love restaurant.
Strangers in the restaurant make the day complete.
Now give me my pills.
Down, Claudia.
Now we're not going for a walk.
Right now.
No, we're not going for a walk right now.
Geez, how can she do that?
That is just amazing, isn't it?
That's my little girl.
All right.
Okay.
So there you go, Dave.
What do you think about that?
Are you talking to me in real time?
Are you talking to me in reality time?
I'm talking to you in real augmented reality time on the radio.
As a squire or as one of us commoners?
Why not both?
I'm Reverend Ivan Stang of the Church of the Subgenius.
This is Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
And why not all?
And Princess Wee Ardo, queen of all the UFOs.
And it's the hour of slack.
And if you want to know more about the Church of the Subgenius or any of the other things,
you can go to the radio section of the radio.
And you can find the stuff we were playing while you just look online at subgenius.com.
And on the radio section, it has text logs and lists of everything we play.
So you can Google them using the right spelling.
And that way you can find Neighbor World and other things at subgenius.com.
Yeah.
And watch out for don't get messed up on apps, you kids.
No, don't get messed up on apps.
Well, I guess I won't tell you one thing.
Tell us.
Go ahead.
Don't tell me.
I forgot what I was going to say.
And it was kind of like on the humorous side, hopefully.
I was going to tickle some ribs out there somehow and lay a few plops on the old milkshake
and bring things back where they shouldn't be.
Well, speaking of things where they shouldn't be, where's Dr. Sinister?
Dr. Sinister is here.
He's here.
I'm here.
I let him in the door.
Doctor, doctor.
Remotely, I walked over and I pushed the button and let him in.
So he's in the building.
I think he's picking out some jams to rock out on.
And then Brother Love went and let him in the door.
I think he's picking out some jams.
Sounds like he's kicking out the clams, if you know what I'm saying.
So he's not picking his toe jams.
Well, what about Wahira El-Santayami?
Everything he's had.
Parabarabai-larabarabai-kansar.
Wahiro El-Santayama.
El-Santayama.
That means Wahiro the sound calls you to dance, to sing.
Well, look, man, we got to get out of here.
It's after, the hour's been more than up.
And I've got apps to play with.
It's over an hour of slack now.
Yeah, man.
It's an hour and three minutes of slack.
It's the slag.
And the hours of slag just go on for hours and hours.
Little Claudia's trilling at home wondering where we are.
Right.
Maybe he went there into the bathroom and didn't come out.
Maybe somebody should go bang on one of the stalls and say, hey, could you please hurry
up?
Claudia's at home and they're just, she doesn't have any.
She's going, meeeel.
Oh, my God.
I'm coming, man.
That is a talkative dog.
That was a pretty good romance, Dave.
Okay.
Okay, man, we got to get out of here.
I'm going to kill you, Dave.
Okay, see you, see you, Pilton.
Don't kill Dave.
Dave, thanks for calling in, by the way.
Yeah.
Okay, well, um, and, uh, now this.
Well, we've certainly missed you, Dave.
enjoyed this
edition of the
Hour of Whatever It Is
on radio, whatchamacallit.
And we hope
that you'll
remember what you heard.
You will remember that thing
you can't remember. It's that whatchamacallit,
that thing that...
That thing that you do, that hoodoo
that you do so well, that
the thing...
The voodoo book you find in the dark alley.
The synthesis of
hour of slack and...
The thing's next six exits.