We, the jury, find the defendant guilty.
Guilty. Guilty. Guilty. Guilty. Guilty.
No! No! Guilty!
I'm not me! I'm...
The Self-Genius Power of Swag!
Click. Click.
From PR News in Washington, I'm charged with a sex crime against Harvey Weinstein
and 13 members of a youth soccer team in July of 2006.
President Trump denies all his sexual relationships were consensual.
Alive.
Forecasters are expecting this month in New Mexico,
the National Interagency Fire Center says it's expected if a summer hits.
FBI agents rated PR News.
The Dow 63-14-75-5-24-24-27.
PR is in trouble.
President Trump said you're listening to forcible sexual PR news.
We'll be right back.
Ten for a beanie, head for the fear.
Micro-webs won't find me here.
I detect a conspiracy smell.
I want to know who's at the wheel.
Who's at the wheel?
Who's at the reins?
Who's the little...
voice inside of my brain
Starts with a whisper
ends with a squeal
I wanna know who's
at the wheel
Fidel Johnson
Mafia spies, I don't really
think that Kennedy died
They took him to the moon
that would be so
but I'm pretty damn sure that they didn't
really go
Who's at the wheel? Who's at the range?
Who's that little voice
inside of my brain?
Starts with a whisper
ends with a squeal
I wanna know who's
at the wheel
Kenyan Muslims ruin
our lives, Al-Qaeda camps
drones in the sky
A man with a mustache
plotting a deal
I wanna know who's at the wheel
My paranoia
is an avalanche
When I find out I'm on a crap
in my pants
The hard, hard truth
The real, real deal
God, I fear nobody's at the wheel
Who's at the wheel?
Who's at the range?
Who's that little voice
inside of my brain?
Starts with a whisper
ends with a squeal
I wanna know who's at the wheel
Who's at the wheel?
The Rainmakers could not be more timely in this day of Russian propelled boogaloo propaganda, friends.
This...
might be kind of a sad hour of slack because it's not a rerun.
And these are sad times.
But we try to put the best face on the troubles and that face is of course the Bob face!
We put our Bob smile on.
The Dobbshead bandana mask helps
if it's in a place crowded with diseased humans.
And we face the future knowing that we're not alone.
We knew all along that the world was ending and only the subgeniuses will be saved.
Oh yes, Bob's promise rings true.
He said, Bob said in 1953, these prophetic words.
It's gonna be a bummer, man.
Can anyone say he was wrong in any single detail of that?
Prophecy fulfilled.
There'll be lots of music in this episode because there's a long center core of words.
And the music was picked in a thoughtful way to fit the theme.
And about the only music I could think of to perfectly fit the theme was pretty much all by the Rainmakers
plus Jimi Hendrix and some youthful girls and maybe one boy
in a new doctor band called the Sub G Kids.
But before we get too real, let's go see a monster movie
from the album of that same name by the Rainmakers.
It's as true today as it will be tomorrow.
From 2014, actually. The Rainmakers.
They're along the east coast to see the sea,
Get some great music out of them,
Toss in your
AUX
BUOT
DP
The details, devils into retail
If your soul's for sale, it's all gonna be gone
Pale politicians hiding in religion
Drag us to the ditch, it's all gonna be gone
In our monster movie
These monsters are real
In the house on the hill
Ain't no salvation in a money nation
We ain't gonna eat you, it's all gonna be gone
Dollar bills, people, all you people
Our people gonna get out, it's all gonna be gone
In our monster movie
These monsters are real
In the house on the hill
Everything about it is a puzzle
Subtracting sex, we're a puzzle
Nobody believes that it will survive
Party is alive
Bone-up
Bone suffering
Bone , bone, bone, bone, bone
Oh, oh, oh, oh
Numb out to drama
In your melodrama
You're the limited
It's all gonna be gone
Jesus ain't a coming
Neither is your mama
Close up for the kill
It's all gonna be gone
In a monster movie
These monsters are real
In the house on the hill
In a monster movie
And Lives Matter was my sister's suggestion.
She likes animals, though.
Probably not a good idea because both sides might shoot me.
And then, of course, there's always Slack Lives Matter, which would be an even worse idea.
I am going to go down there and check it out, though.
I could stand on one side with a gun, yelling and braying at the juvenile jokes,
and then go over to the other side to bend the knee and bow my head while holding the gun to my own head and crying,
Why? Why? Why?
That was Philo's idea.
I thought of wearing realistic makeup, so I'd look like I'd just been beat all to hell
and hold up a sign.
A sign saying, Black and Blue Lives Matter.
But again, that would probably get me beat up for real by both sides.
They might politely take turns.
After you, demon crap, you go ahead and hit him first.
Oh no, Sir Repuke, I insist you have first go at him.
Well, if you insist.
Have at you, smartass, since you like bruises so much.
Indeed, how dare he besmirch our serious street fight
with the police.
Mirth and levity.
Yeah, I guess at last we found some common ground.
Beat up the smarty pants.
We could bring the dogs.
Everybody loves dogs, especially Claudia, the boxer pit bull,
who's almost completely black all over and so lovable.
And she could wear Black Lives Matters.
No, no, no, that could really be taken the wrong way.
The most common,
the most common response from dumbasses around here
to the whole BLM thing is usually along the lines of,
So you don't think cop lives matter?
You don't think white lives matter?
Why do you bring your hate of your own kind to this nice, peaceful town?
The gullible dumbasses are also spreading the probably Russian-originated lie
that, or,
or,
boogaloo.
The lie that violent thug professional looters will be bussed in from the big city in Dallas.
Quite a few people here fall for all that Russian fake anti-thighs hiring propaganda
that they send each other on Facebook.
And Fox math.
My immediate family, friends, is multiracial and I personally have had a gun problem.
I've been hit by a cop just because I had long hair and a t-shirt on with a flying saucer on it,
which made the cop say,
So you're in a cult?
I've also been chased by rednecks just for having long hair,
although that was 50 years ago.
And nowadays, half the rednecks and bikers have long hair.
Incidentally, I don't use the word redneck as a pejorative.
It just simply means rural outdoor workers,
whose necks get red in the sun.
They call themselves rednecks proudly and I'm half redneck myself.
They might also be great historians or writers or musicians or scientists on the side when
they're not on their tractor.
Yeah, my neck is only about half red.
I actually did benefit quite a bit from slavery.
I was born a little more stained with the sins of my ancestors than most, I'm afraid.
My great-great uncle was Senator Cotton Ed Smith.
Wikipedia had this to say about Ellison Durant Cotton Ed Smith.
He was a Democratic Party politician from the U.S. state of South Carolina,
widely known for his virulently racist and segregationist views
and his advocacy of white supremacy.
He represented South Carolina in the United States,
and he was the first Republican to ever be elected to the United States Senate
from 1909 until 1944.
At that point, the Republicans and Democrats kind of traded places.
Anyway, that connection might have helped my father get into Harvard Law School.
Also, my mom was the one who came to this little all Democrat town in the 70s
and convinced them they were all actually Republicans.
But of course, I lived in East Cleveland for 20 years,
so at least half the neighbors and the people I worked with had lives that were black and mattered to me.
By the same token, the vast majority of my encounters with police officers have actually been positive.
But I've got to run now because I heard there was going to be a prayer vigil for cops in the square in about 20 minutes,
and I want to get out of here.
I'm going to go sniff that out on my way to the post office.
Well, friends, that turned out to be fake news.
There was no prayer vigil for cops or any other kind of prayer vigil,
just the usual fruit stands and little tiny farmer's market.
It was all just big talk.
However, there was a Trump-Pence sign on one stand, which was new.
I bought some fresh eggs from a different stand.
The Trump eggs hatch into little Trumps.
Okay.
That was in the morning of Saturday, June 13th.
Then we went to the Glen Rose Black Lives Matter vigil.
And what an anticlimax.
Everything was just as I predicted, uneventful.
Only actually it turned out a lot better than I expected.
With a couple of ridiculous exceptions, there was no counter protest, no patriot vigilantes with AK-47s.
I counted about 75.
I counted about 75 friendlies respectfully participating in the peaceful vigil in the town square,
listening to several speakers who were mostly Glen Rose citizens.
It was really touching at times and fairly boring at other times.
It was 7 o'clock in the evening and the weather was really nice.
Now, strangely, the busloads of hired antifa professional looters and outside agitators
predicted by the skeptical naysayers on the street,
on the Glen Rose Facebook pages, they never showed up.
I'm guessing maybe they had a flat.
Or maybe they got the wrong directions and went towards Glen Rose, Arkansas.
Not a single flaming trash can was slung through a single storefront, as was widely predicted.
Now, despite the public restrooms being locked, another threat that scandalized many of the pro-fa people on the road,
the local Facebook, viewed as a harbinger of disaster and a Democrat coup,
it was actually a very peaceful demonstration.
None of the roads were blocked, despite the dire predictions of some BLM critics.
And for some reason, parking was no different than any other Saturday evening in the town square.
But it was just uncanny how a bunch of young and old and 90% white Glen Rose natives
were able to gather for an hour and acknowledge that there are still some pretty serious disparities
due to racial prejudice that need to be addressed.
I guess the antifa must have surrendered and run away due to all the promises by Glen Rose pro-fa conservatives
that there would be, quote,
second amendment presence, unquote,
for the safety of this God-fearing town of 2,400 people.
To protect it from, quote,
you know, the teenagers and boomers talking on a little PA about nature and sustainability and justice and all that stuff.
Now, people who wanted to speak were invited up to the courthouse steps where there was a microphone on a stand
and a PA speaker about the size of a shoebox.
I had to stand practically next to the steps just to hear well, but I'm pretty deaf.
And I placed my location recorder near the little speaker,
so I have an okay recording of everything.
Don't worry, I won't force it on the radio audience.
I only really know a few of the folks who were there,
but I introduced myself to some of the organizers.
Since everybody's wearing face masks,
unless they were speaking on the microphone at the time,
it was kind of awkward and required the occasional lower face reveal.
At one point I said to somebody,
I recognize the upper half of your face from Facebook.
Now, my buddies on our secret non-Facebook internet club asked me for a live report.
And I told them the short version.
It was touching and boring both.
A big loud truck with Trump banners drove past three or four times honking.
That was the full extent of conflict.
It scared Princess Wee though.
And of course there were lots of good old boys standing around nearby just sort of observing.
But nobody was waving guns around or any of that.
Unlike a little town in Ohio where the locals, the conservative locals,
some of them were convinced that there were paid rioters coming in
and they actually beat up a whole bunch of the peaceniks.
But at the Glen Rose thing there was a preacher and a lot of Jesus and love stuff.
Which actually kind of made me tear up because there were some really authentic moments that happened.
As I told my buddies,
I've never seen so many attractive ladies of all ages in one place in Glen Rose.
Democrats appear to have healthier diets.
And I'm not judging by the turnout at this.
There were three black people there that I know of.
That's a lot for Glen Rose.
One was a councilman from Arlington who got on the mic and talked about his experience of racism.
One was a local guy who works at the grocery store who hadn't heard anything about this demonstration
and just stumbled upon it.
And was flabbergasted to see all these Glen Rose, Texas, small town rednecks acting like this.
And he was like, they actually gave a hoot about this stuff.
And he did a little spontaneous statement which was good.
One of the organizers and a few participants were young Latinas or Latinos.
Plain old Americans but not Anglos.
But honestly, for all intents and purposes, it was an almost all white, all local, 90% Christian,
probably half Republican, small crowd,
that basically said, here we are and this is what we think.
Black lives matter.
And also, it would be great if all lives got to be mattering equally somehow, someday.
Or something like that.
Basically, it was supposed to be an anti-fear message.
So, anyway, although there were a few guys in front of some stores across the street being sarcastic
and fist bumping occasionally,
there were none of the threatened, open carry, second hand,
second amendment biker individuals promised by Facebook loudmouth.
Just that one Trump truck that honked.
And somebody revved up their engine real loud a couple of times.
So, the promised civil war once again failed to materialize.
Instead, corny as this sounds to say,
for one evening, kind of like at Christmas,
the town square was exuding a vibe of love.
And it was pretty cool.
And gave me some slack.
Plus, again, I've never seen so many healthy and attractive looking ladies in the town of Glen Rose all in one place.
Now, a friend of mine, who happens to be a Republican,
responded somewhat snarkily to that.
He said,
I saw that report when I posted it on Facebook with pictures.
Yeah, because of your participation in that protest,
police brutality worldwide has utterly ceased.
Good job.
Well, it actually was Facebook brutality that spurred me personally.
Juvenile jackasses on the internet making threats to scare a 15 year old
is actually the main reason I went.
This vigil was originally started by a 15 year old girl.
And boy, did they bully her.
Oddly enough, the bullies didn't actually show up to speak of.
Oh, but today, the people who weren't there are all busy telling each other
that there were only a dozen people at the pathetic vigil.
And it's just the typical blatant lies.
The truth never fits their childish agendas.
Because the complex is actually not quite as simple as they are.
Another crusty old bastard, Dr. Piss-Off, said,
What? You said there was no cussing? WTF?
To which I said,
Not cussing is some liberal's way of letting the supposedly all-Christian apple pie opposition
let them be the class.
And of course, in vulgar vocabulary challenged troglodytic louts for a change.
Some time ago, I noticed that four-letter vulgarities had become normal
on everything from news headlines to children's cartoons.
And many youths and boomers alike can't get through a sentence
without using fuck the way uh was once used.
Of course, cussing is necessary.
But as a contrarian emergentile subgenius,
I've consciously switched over to using only archaic quaint euphemisms
from my grandparents' era.
Like, God darn it.
Tarnation.
What in Sam Hill.
Dad blasted.
Con sarnit.
That's just a bunch of hooey.
Etc. Etc.
But, uh,
my favorite response was
one subgenius, Reverend Thorpe, I said,
I think, said, uh,
The public restroom's being locked.
They'd infringed on your right to excremeditate.
I would make a big stink about that.
Yeah, man, then you're stepping on our religion.
And, uh, oh, somebody,
one of the critics on the Glen Rose Facebook page
sarcastically referred to
having accidentally parked in the anti-fa parking lot
with what to him were dramatic consequences.
And I thought, the poor guy, he mistook it
for the pro-fa parking lot.
Pro-fa! Where's that word been our whole lives?
And you're welcome to use it.
Anyway, congratulations to the Glen Rose nice folks
on a successful event.
And I was glad to hear it.
I think we're gonna have to half-meet a lot of them
since half their faces weren't visible.
And, uh, here's a little poem,
uh, just to change the subject.
This is, uh, from Pastor Prime
of the Mutant Mountain Boys band
that we see at the devotionals.
There once was a virus from Wuhan
Infected me while on my futon.
I laid there for weeks
While breathing in squeaks
But healed up by getting my snooze on.
Uh, yes, it is actually terrible.
And now back to our regularly scheduled subgenius programming.
I actually have no idea what that is at this point.
And now this.
Bud Light presents
The subgenius power of swag.
Real American heroes.
Today we salute you, real American heroes.
Don't stay in too long
Or everyone will shout
Finish quickly and come back.
Is the most important thing
In life for anybody?
The importance ofuges.
Who Het rie
Danger
⁠§
Heaven
Danger
Ash
Sometimes, you gotta say,
FALCON!
From PR News in Washington, I'm, quote, very, very nervous.
I'm so nervous that local health officials are recommending people evacuate.
The Secretary of Veterans Affairs plans to fire four missiles over Japan and into waters around Guam.
Japan says it's the first test of a VA's nuclear warhead small enough to fit on a missile.
Congress has been trying for years to make it easier to fire.
Now, the county health department says it's seeing the highest air quality readings it's ever recorded.
For people who are vulnerable.
Vulnerable people include pregnant children and anyone over age five.
A Denver court has heard from the turkey.
She testified that she groped a former turkey, grabbing her and lifting her turkey skirt.
This turkey says it is unclear whether German turkeys are strained.
And Germany has warned its citizens about turkeys after a German turkey was arrested last month in Berlin.
The Dow is 2198, 25, 22, 2126.
The turkey says this is PR News.
Spoiler alert, you'll be stunned and strange.
A lot of people think of the oy y.
They're right
All the preacher men
The politicians
All the critics
And the things
They write
Out of my way
Hot rocket on wrecking day
And this is the call to arms
This is the call to hands
This is the call to the voices
And the minds of the people
In every land
Out of my way
Hot rocket on wrecking day
And we're taking the history test
Of who's baddest and who is best
Lenin the brother
Lenin the son
Lenin the sister
Lenin the communist
Out of my way
Hot rocket on wrecking day
Wrecking day
Put the money in the mattress
Put your pennies where they go
Wrecking day
Nothing left to believe in
Nothing left to wait for
And getting in to tell the truth
Was like pulling the wind
And I was like
I didn't take back
I'm jeans
A long parar
Been pullin' him off
I've got all my
Again
This isn't the keepy
Get up
Out of my way
Oh, there's nothing left to wait for
Get out of my way
Out of my way
It's all a lie.
We're being lied to.
Every day.
Every fucking day.
And we think that we have all the answers.
We don't have all the answers.
They won't give us the answers.
So how are we supposed to live our lives?
How are we supposed to live our lives?
I love your titty voice.
You are the answer to my problems.
All the misinformation.
All I need is real people in my life.
Authentic people.
Who have opinions.
Exactly.
Who are not sheeple.
Sheeple.
They're out there.
They are.
And they just keep adding lies.
Lies.
And for what?
Are they pussy?
I mean like on fire.
To keep us under their sun.
Oh, I know.
Right.
Because if they told the truth, they do.
There would be an uprising.
And kind of there already is.
You know.
All the time was this or that.
So.
Because we're kept in the dark.
How many times do we not hear something that's out there?
We only hear of these cases because someone was there to witness it.
How much is really being kept from us?
We're never going to know.
Unless maybe you become president and then you get to look at that book.
The book of secrets.
Yes.
They have all the answers to all the questions.
With all the scientific data to back it up.
You know what?
I just figured out the answer.
Uh.
We just gotta find a way to fuck Bo Gates.
He'll tell us everything.
That was It's All a Lie, an excerpt from Freedom of Speech by High Priestess Pucci and Reverend
Katana 007.
Who formed the band Sub G Kids.
With Reverend Negative.
That siren laden danger song earlier was also by the Sub G Kids.
Who, if I understand correctly, were streaming that on video also while they performed it.
And in between the PR news of Lemur and the song Reckoning Day by the Rainmakers from the 70s.
But now.
Well.
I play this long.
Jimmy.
Hendrix song every five years or so.
Just in case nobody's heard it.
It's probably been 10 years.
It's still considered one of the best guitar solo songs ever done.
The song Machine Gun by Jimmy Hendrix.
And this is the famous Fillmore East New Year's performance that was on the main band of Gypsy's album.
Happy New Year.
First of all.
We have about a million or two million more of them.
There is this one.
If we can get over this summer.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We have to dedicate this one to such a draggy scene that's going on.
All the soldiers that are fighting in Chicago and Milwaukee and New York.
Oh yes.
And all the soldiers fighting in Vietnam.
About to do a thing called Machine Gun.
Machine Gun.
.
Machine gun.
¶¶
guitar solo
solo
That's what we don't want to hear anymore, right?
No bullets.
Your time has come to rock the ages
Your time has come to burn the fields
Strain your mold and tear the pages
Tune your drum, your time has come
Standing on a mountain underneath a clear starry sky
Digging for an old gold record in the cold hillside
Your time has come to wrestle angels and capture one
Your time has come
Your time has come to claim the quarters
Raid the port
Seize the flag
Storm the ramparts
Cross the waters
Steal the guns
Your time has come
Hoping and wishing and praying for a clean escape
From the worn out, torn out, burned out same old ways
Your time has come
To kill the giants
To die in peace
Oh, bum
Your time has come
Rock The Nibbles
Feet by Huawei
The Ask Cop
Into hell
Top of Switzerland
제일 진 끄인
There we go!
Hanging out a rhythm on my 50-50 gallon drum
Your time has come
To rock the ages
One child run
Your time has come
The Rainmakers from Monster Movie
This has been the Hour of Sorrow
And I'm Jack Slack from the Church of the Subgenius and others
See subgenius.com for details
A lot of details
This isn't the only subgenius radio show for instance
It got kind of big praise Bob
Subgenius.com
Gee I want to try Triology
All the kids are doing it mom
There's a Dobbs head in every bar
Yes an embedded Dobbs head of soap
Inside a bar of translucent soap
You can see Bob lurking inside
And it tells fortunes
As you rotate it swiftly under the water
Lathering away the conspiracy smudge and other schmata
If the Dobbs head comes up at the end
In the true perfect pipe placement position
You'll have good luck all day
If it comes up the other way
Twenty more years of winter
That's Triology Soaps.com
It comes in every flavor and scent
That's not nonsense
It's almost every scent you can think of
And they all have funny names
Praise Bob and praise Triology Soaps.com
Try is spelled with an I
From PR News in Washington
I'm on the road to Poland
President Trump, the father of Michael Jackson
Had a significant but complicated role in American music
But he brushed aside questions about PR News
The Dow is 24th to 71
In Poland Bill says
This is PR News in Washington
Free your radio and your mind will follow
Free Think Radio
Is your one stop source for all the subgenius shows
Including the Hour of Slack
Every Thursday at 11am
Eastern Time
We think
Yes friends
Freethinkradio.com
With Time for the Show
National Cynical
Puzzling Evidence
Bob's Lifetime Funhouse
Fergan Fridays
And the Hour of Slack
Every Thursday at 11am
Praise Bob
And praise Freethink Radio
Hey Johnny Rev
Where are you going
Don't you know
This war isn't done
Hey Johnny Rev
Where are you going
Even though this battle wasn't won
There's nothing worth fighting for
Any way you cut it
Gonna leave that flag behind
So long Johnny Rev
Johnny Rev
Whoa, whoa
Goodbye
Johnny Rev
Hey Johnny Rev
Where did the wind blow
All your courage
All your nerve
Tyrants arise
Armies go marching
Who will say
What needs to be heard
I'm hitching down to Memphis
Gonna hock this town
Your guitar
Gonna leave that song behind
So long Johnny Rev
Johnny Rev
Whoa, whoa
Goodbye
Oh...
Hey Johnny Rev, where will we find you
When they need somebody who'll stand
Guarding the gate, keys to the kingdom
Jingling freedom bells in your hand
Forward all my mail to the last frontier
Gonna kiss that cause goodbye
So long Johnny Rev, Johnny Rev
Johnny Rev, goodbye
Goodbye, goodbye