The greatest trick the devil ever pulled
was convincing the world he didn't exist.
And like that, he's gone.
This is your last chance.
After this, there is no turning back.
You take the blue pill.
The story ends.
You wake up in your bed and believe whatever you want to believe.
You take the red pill.
You stay in Wonderland.
And I show you how deep the rabbit hole goes.
Remember, all I'm offering is the truth, nothing more.
Welcome to the subgenius radio ministry Hour of Slang.
Sponsored by the Church of the Subgenius.
Make way.
Quoted.
I created light and created darkness, created goodness and created evil.
I, the Lord God, do all these things.
God is the source of evil and he admits it.
What's the burr under your saddle?
Sweet mother of God, what is the holdup?
I think we're at a cool. We can go.
We can go.
What the hell do you think you're doing?
Dragging your butt through the day?
Selling body and soul to a bunch of bland normals?
Acting stupid so they'll think you're one of them?
Tired of getting all of the guilt but none of the sex.
There is a simple answer dear friend.
A glowing beacon of slack amidst the turmoil and darkness.
It's JR Broadcast.
J R Broadcast.
Bob Dobbs, the living slack master in his church of the subgenius.
Bob brings a new destiny for the abnormal.
For Bob comes to justify our sins, to unmask the conspiracy, and to get us back the slack they stole away.
It's us versus them.
Are you going to fry in hell on earth alongside the pink boys?
Or will you pull the wool over your own eyes and accept Bob into your mind?
Repent. Quit your job.
Slack off and praise Bob.
Church of the subgenius eternal salvation will triple your money back.
Man, you are one pathetic loser.
There's a lot of triple tonguing in this arrangement.
Oh, I think I'll manage, thank you.
Are you digging this character? He's gonna manage.
So your boots are laced, Junior. We'll all read, all read, all read.
Give it to me. A one, a two, a seat, a zoo.
criteriously
our
and
have all theae sprawl
day 130
dean
And all American boy sings his way into your heart.
Anything is possible.
Simultaneously getting all kinds of polytonal effects.
Don't make us print those skin shots.
We'll dominate over the...
You're sick.
Yeah.
Going newly.
Higher, faster, farther, longer.
All right, one note.
I love it, man.
It's the greatest.
I'm in yellow tomorrow.
A frenzy of music and action.
Won't.
Reality is a sad new face.
And, uh, we're gonna be in the music at the floor.
As I said to him, to him, to him.
Get out, get out, get out, get out, get out, get out, get out, get out, get out.
The gals have laughed and have followed me when I left their dressing room, but, uh,
I said, I imagine they were expecting somebody rather groovy looking, and, uh,
well, there you go, disappointed.
Anyway.
Oh, anyway, anyway, anyway.
Dear friends, that was a collage.
By Electric Elf.
Yes, Electric Elf.
And we'll be hearing more from Electric Elf.
Before that, some of the subgenius MTV soundtrack by me and Mark Mothersbaugh.
And the music in the background is the Swingin' Love Corpses, friends,
from the brand-newly-released Infamous Bay Dat Sessions.
So nice to have that.
And, uh, and friends, it's, uh,
it's been a rough, uh, few weeks of slack, you might say.
This, we're nearing now the Christmas Eve of destruction,
and I'm late, my friends, I'm late.
I actually fell behind a whole week's worth of hour of slack.
That's the first time that's happened in 14 years
due to, uh, an illness among loved ones,
which is all better now.
But, uh, but we're back.
We're back in Cleveland.
And, uh, trying to, uh, to catch up.
And, uh, luckily there were some great war-related songs posted to all Binary Slack,
uh, by, uh, Popes Lilith and various other folks as well.
And, uh, uh, and there's a new James Kochalka Superstar album out, my dear, dear friends.
And, uh, I got to, to pulling stuff off of a Burning Man collection that,
of just all kinds of music that Gustav Salas,
gave to us.
There's, uh, KPFA, uh, old new, old KPFA that sounds just like it's new,
with Puzzling Evidence and Dr. Howell,
and of course, uh, some ESO.
But first, but first, my friends,
James Kochalka Superstar with this, uh, song from the album of the same name,
Don't Trust Whitey.
.
Don't trust whitey.
Whitey is not very nice.
He's not friendly.
He always cheats and he lies.
Whitey is white as a ghost.
Whitey as white as the snow.
Why is whitey so mean?
Nobody, nobody knows.
Don't trust whitey.
Don't trust him whatever you do.
He's not friendly, you know that Whitey hates you
Whitey is white as a ghost Whitey is white as the snow
I hate Whitey the most I don't even think that he knows
Don't trust Whitey No!
Don't trust Whitey whatever you do
Don't trust Whitey or you will be screwed
Don't trust Whitey Don't let him out of your sight
He's not friendly Who knows what he's planning tonight
Don't trust Whitey He lies and he lies and he lies
I'm not Whitey
Whitey This is just a disguise
Don't trust Whitey No!
Don't trust Whitey whatever you do
Don't trust Whitey or you will be screwed
Whitey is white as a ghost
Whitey is white as the snow
I hate Whitey the most
I hate his white little nose
Whitey is white as a ghost
Whitey is white as the snow
I hate Whitey the most
I hate his white little Тоes
Why ye, no, don't trust
Why ye, why ye
No, don't trust
Why ye
Why ye, why ye
No, don't trust
They took the whole eastern nation
Put us on this reservation
Took away our ways of life
Brotherhood and the culture knife
Took away our native tongue
And told the English to hurry on
And all the things we made by hand
Are now a taste made in Japan
Eastern people
Eastern tribe
So proud to live
So proud to die
They took the whole eastern nation
Lotus in this reservation
Blood on we were blue shirts and tie
They took the whole eastern nation
We're still the red men deep inside
Although they changed our ways of hope
They'll never change our heart and soul
We're the red men deep inside
And on Sunday when the world has learned
Civilization will return
Will return
We'll return
Ladies and gentlemen
Our mayor has asked that we all remain calm in this emergency
Everything possible will be done to protect you
On orders from Washington
The Commander of Strategic Defense has alerted all branches of the service
This is not the usual flying saucer scare
This unidentified aircraft was seen by thousands of Americans
thousands as it flew through the Lincoln Tunnel.
If they're not careful, they're going to have an accident.
Anyone sighting a strange aircraft, phone your nearest branch of civilian air defense.
What are we going to do now?
We either go to Mars or get shot down.
So we'll go to Mars.
We'll go to Mars.
The road to the western lands is by definition the most dangerous road in the world.
For it is a journey beyond death, beyond the basic God standard of fear and danger.
It is the most heavily guarded road in the world, where it gives access to the gift that supersedes all other gifts.
Immortality.
The road to the western lands is devious, unpredictable.
Today's easy passage may be tomorrow's death trap.
The obvious road is almost always a fool's road.
And beware the middle road.
The roads of moderation, common sense and careful planning.
However,
there is a time for planning, moderation and common sense.
Paul Richard
The unredeemable
College of Engineering
victims,
A dangerous road, every pitfall, every error, every snare to which every man has been liable since the beginning.
You are sure to meet on the road to the western lands.
The guilt and horror, fear, hate, disease, and death of human history
throws the green yield in the western lands.
How long does it take a man to learn that he does not and cannot want what he wants?
You have to be in hell to see heaven.
Eclipses and all the rest of it are in heaven.
The land of the dead.
Flashes of serene, timeless joy.
A joy as bold as suffering and despair.
Ooh la la, dear friends.
Reverend Bill Burroughs, William S. Burroughs there.
From a collection that I'm not sure what it is.
Before that, we heard some news from Abbott and Costello go to Mars.
I rented that because it has space princesses and space queens in it.
They actually go to Venus.
But at one point, Abbott and Costello sort of destroy the ghost of the World Trade Center.
And it's just amazing.
I would just say check SubSight or rent that movie.
It's very strange.
Before that, friends.
How about that Leibach version of the old Indian reservation?
They call it National Reservation.
Leibach.
It's strange indeed.
From next, friends, some Einstein's Secret Orchestra ESO Swamp Radio.
But first, before that, Michael Pepe.
St. Michael Pepe on Dr. Philo Drummond's phone message machine.
September 11th at 4.53.
P.M.
Hey, what happened, man?
What happened?
I got this two, the two flags that I can see from my window here are both a half-mass,
man.
Who died?
I'm kind of concerned.
I hope another president didn't get assassinated and then, you know, another assassin get assassinated
by the assassin's assassin.
Because, you know, I'm sick of that .
Um.
Uh.
Well, yeah, what happened?
Well, anyway.
By the way, you know what?
Did you ever, you know, did you ever notice that when you picked the skin off your feet,
even though, you know, I took a shower last night, but just, you know, just having my,
having worn the socks that I wore at Burning Man like 20 hours ago, you know, and my feet
were clean when I put them in.
And, uh, it's really, it's very sweet.
Do you ever notice that?
Do that, you know, put on the socks that you wore at Burning Man, even just for a few minutes,
and then peel the, um, the skin off your feet and eat it.
And, uh, it, it, it has a nice little, uh, sweet taste.
End of message.
To repeat this message, press 1.
To save it, press 2.
To save it, press 1.
Press 1.
Press 2.
Uh, are you still breathing there?
I knew it.
They, they made them go, they made, they made me go home.
Hello?
Oh, well.
This is, this is the third call we've had tonight from the dress pain class.
I...
Oh, well.
earth woman did did dave hang up dave i think he did our little our little frank
must have fooled him oh no dave shucks attention conspiracy you are condemned
did you know that the instant the normal guys you're just doing because i guess you cut me off
no we didn't cut you off you hung up on us yeah we were being polite we were being polite and
letting you have some air time i heard absolutely nothing but this weird buzzing well we were being
part of the act i thought you were i thought there was actually a buzzing signal had intercepted us
well that may also be true i thought we were split up
i thought like
you
know some signal from langley or or cape meat or whatever the name of it is you just split us
right in three different parts and we're like no dave it was the black helicopters in hush mode
yeah bombs not racism man okay what's coming down to is it's coming up to the time when we're going
to have to accept the fact that the only way we're going to be able to survive is to live solely in
our avatars in our avatars as a building until the power goes out
an avatar is a person not a building you're talking about live through your yeah yeah in the metaverse
right so it's like we're gonna have to move to the metaverse dave well i've already been meta
and i think we all have at some time in our proto existence a thought in the mind of the exuberant
well they're cutting down on the mail in federal offices now they're uh some geniuses who work in
such offices have told me they've been told we are not accessible to the public and we're not
accepting snail mail at all at this office tell your people to email or fax all documentation
because you know in your role as a avatar of evil perhaps even would you uh perhaps tell people to uh
what would you tell them to do i don't know they can read your email starting tomorrow without
opening it you know without right right they've said the postmaster general said wash your hands
you must use your mail well i heard if you can just use email which we can read well and all
all letters will now be postcards i heard that everybody that you deal with who you have any
kind of social dysfunction with or something like that you are here henceforth we're supposed to
refer to him as evil doors and you're not allowed to think about what motivates them or even yourself
you have to think of them as evil doors evil door
yeah and somehow you'll be able to solve that was a great band the evil doors yeah they were
the original band i have a couple evil doors that i uh don't take a man that stuff's bad for you
a couple exterior mail jacks i thought there was a micro brew huh the evil doors yeah they're gonna
be there's a micro brew you could get down there at the great lakes tavern hey how about this one
for a bumper sticker you like these chas the evil doors yeah i have a couple evil doors
are my preamp now you know remember about 20 years ago i belonged to a group called the
lccw lccw yeah and we had t-shirts and we had parties on the lake and the t-shirts had big
binoculars binoculars on them and said lccw i don't remember county coast watchers guarding
against canadian attack well now it's all come true
that was a prophetic piece of pierced nose literature released from a person without a you know any hair on their body
oh
oh oh
and
we're to blame for everything
is there
beaches
Basically against anything that requires anybody to do anything that requires anybody to do anything that requires anybody to do
Anything as a member of society that helps make it safer
You pervert current events to sentence the National Rifle Association
a fraud a fraud
gun theft rings and
agents of evil
in American culture for example that
Father six-year-old kid living in a crack house infested the NRA
eight in San Francisco
14 in New Jersey
nine in Pittsburgh two in Washington DC
That's a lie
The truth is it was the NRA who pioneered and passed 13 funerals a day
Do I think that of course I do of course I do
guns
You incite media bias and fuel the politics of hate
You never miss a chance to step before the cameras and play out the gun haters drama of distortion
defamation and downright lies
Eastern world it is exploding
violence flaring
bullets load
You're old enough to kill
But not for vote
You don't believe in war
Boards and gun you're toting
And even the Jordan River has
bodies floating
But you tell me over and over and over again my friend
You don't believe we're on the eve of destruction
music
Just like human beings
The 라는
beat the poor little warlike people and bring peace forever and ever just like real life
But then the evil art dictators can
the art bombs have finally taken front
power in the far future and they object to the firing of the space gun.
They incite an unruly mob to come forward and smash the space gun, but it fires anyway,
shooting a young, comely pair of youths into space, male and female, seeding the cosmos.
They seeded Earth.
To the Indians for $24.
It was a mystery.
A mystery wrapped in an enigma.
Surrounded with creamy milk chocolate.
And velvety nougat.
And little rice crispy things.
They didn't actually have a name.
But they cost more than the inflated ones.
They had the stamp of approval.
The reason the Jews made a mistake with the man on the cross and the suffering serpent,
or the man that was suffering and bearing sickness in the 53rd of Isaiah,
their theology said you suffer because you sin.
It's carried over into Christianity to where people will say,
what those Jews did when they came to Jesus in the New Testament and said,
here's a man born blind.
Who sinned, him or his parents?
Jesus dismissed it cavalierly.
Neither, he said.
Neither.
But that the glory of God might be displayed in this moment to paraphrase the situation.
Christianity has abused Christians.
Christians.
As though when something wrong goes wrong,
or wronger,
it's because you sinned.
Oh, there will be those that will preach,
because of America's sin,
the judgment of God's on them.
Well, go to hell, you voices of the devil.
Now, a wonderful message.
Will not be played on Christian networks.
But we have our own network.
24 hours a day.
Thank you.
Jesus, I beg of thee, don't take my life.
Return me to the womb from which I was torn.
Birth is a sin.
And the punishment...
The end of respite and the time...
Is not perfect.
If you stop religion,
your rights are ruined.
Spare time with the sick.
The enormity of all paint,
It makes no sense.
The power of nature is abolished.
Spidet honesty is lost without küçük hate.
Unimog quem questo entferne.
Undigit фу.
We'll be right back.
Yeah!
Ground Zero Brooklyn is the name of that song by Retaliation, my friends.
And before that, we heard some Dr. Gene Scrappy.
Scott, some KPFA subgenius show from KPFA Berkeley with puzzling evidence,
and Dr. Howe, Barry McGuire, Eve of Destruction,
Charlton Heston in a rant by Electric Elf,
and I should mention where you can get Electric Elf's stuff.
Now, where is that?
Dang it!
I put these things sitting out so that I can smoothly do a transition
and describe Electric, and it's...
Oh, hold on.
Here it is, dear friends.
I've got the miracle of editing.
ElectricElf at loop.com.
That's an email address.
ElectricElf, one word, just like you would think,
at loop.com, L-O-O-P dot com.
That's ElectricElfTestKitchen.
And now, friends,
the great subgenius,
this album from Saint Anne and Helena Handbasket
features this upcoming song, 13013.
Write those numbers out and see what it spells out to you.
And then after that, a Cleveland rap band,
and listen real closely to the subgenius code words
embedded in that song by Bone Thugs-N-Harmony.
Eh, yes.
Eh, God.
There is nothing left to say
Human life so depraved
This was all Bob's plan
We've done what we can
Alien gods, monster squads
UFOs and chaos
The dark
Fighting Jesus
River God
Mighty J-H-V-H-1
Over there, cash machine
Number 13013
Think of dying
Over there, cash machine
Number 13013
Think of dying
Over there, cash machine
Number 13013
Think of dying
All our hopes and dreams
All our dreams
Coming to an end, doesn't mean anything
Times are near, going fast
How long, how long, how long
To an end?
Million guards, monster squads
UFOs and chariot dogs
Fighting Jesus with a gun
Mighty J-
VH-
VH-1
All our, all our, all our dreams
Coming to an end, doesn't mean anything
Times are near, going fast
How long, how long, how long
To an end?
Million guards, monster squads
UFOs and chariot dogs
Fighting Jesus with a gun
VH-1
to the facts.
Thugs as convicts
in God's prison.
Hands on the strap.
Praying so far
but please forgive me.
Police be rushing
when they see me.
I flaunt it.
America's most wanted.
Live on TV.
Like pleasure and pain.
Stuck in this game.
Holler my name.
We all gonna die.
We bleed through
similar veins.
Please explain to me.
Now don't panic
when my guns burst.
Heard the last jam,
nigga.
This one's worse.
My nigga bone
held the chrome
till I came home.
Thug love player.
Tell these bitch niggas
bring it on.
I caught a plane
out to Cleveland
late last evening
to help my niggas
clean up some niggas
no longer breathing.
Now,
who do you believe in?
Hit the weed
and breathe.
It's a cold ass world,
niggas.
Kill you in your sleep.
Watch me
until they stop me.
Burry, murder me
or drop me.
I got
thug love
for my nation
while I'm possibly
human.
I'm a hitter
with a nigga like
Park
and a nigga like
Nogata.
Stay high.
Thug love to the
dock.
Keep a breath
in the sky.
But it's filled
in the hood
smoking fry.
So I beg
the Lord to save
us all.
Escapers of misery.
Bless my niggas
and penitentiary
soldiers of the
city.
Long dead,
long gone.
Now we've
long, long,
long gone.
Now we've
long, long,
long,
I see a red door
and I want them
painted black.
No colors anymore.
I want them
to turn black.
I see a lot of cars
but they are
painted black.
They pass me
by with war
who's never
coming back.
I look inside myself and see my heart is black
I see a red door and a hand door haven't blocked
Maybe I'll fade away, I'd have to face the facts
Man, it's not easy when your whole world's turning black
Fading black
I was black
If we look hard enough into the setting sun
These leaves will last for me before the morning
Fading black
I see them walking by, all dressed up in their clothes
I had to turn away until my goodness was
Fading black
I was black
Well, you know, some people like it, but you never can tell what will happen in the future.
For example?
For example, no one ever knew that spiders would colonize outer space.
Building webs in outer space.
NASA constructed a laboratory called Skylab in which experiments could be conducted in
zero gravity outside the Earth's atmosphere.
Sending spiders up in Skylab to see how they performed in conditions of weightlessness
was a prize-winning proposal from a high school student from Lexington, New York.
A student at the time, a graduate student, had been assigned to a class of science subjects
Because they had real Jesus on there.
So it was really spooky.
When the Apollo spacecraft with Skylab 2 and 3 astronauts was launched on July 28, 1973,
two spiders were aboard.
Of the genus Aramudus diadematos, together with two flies for their food.
A week after lift-off, spider number one was placed on a frame in a cage.
The next day, a new spider was born.
Spider number two was kept in a small tube until being released onto the frame four weeks after launch.
Seeing the spiders in space on TV was for me very exciting and worth all the years of waiting.
I saw something which no human eye had ever observed before.
Spider number two floated slowly in microgravity when introduced into the cage.
It touched the frame, bounced back and floated in the opposite direction.
Its legs were extended and hardly moved.
The spider silk which one could observe coming from the spinnerets at the end of the bulbous abdomen
wafted in wide waves through the air.
On Earth it would have been stretched tight by the spider's weight.
The spider obviously missed its usual clues.
It could no longer handle the situation in an appropriate way
and presumably waited for what would happen next.
But with perfect equanimity.
The experiment succeeded in showing that spiders can build orb webs in zero gravity.
And it is obvious that under long term conditions
spiders in a microgravity without gravitational constraints
can grow to an enormous size.
Becoming the fearsome giant spiders of legend and popular culture.
Once spiders are permanently introduced to space
in an increased oxygen atmosphere particularly
spider growth can achieve prodigies
never before
reached.
buyer
near
However there are
others
Just sit right back and you'll hear a tale
A tale of a fateful trip
That started from this tropic port
Aboard this tiny ship
The mate was a mighty sailing man
Skipper brave and sure
Five passengers set sail that day
For a three-hour tour
A three-hour tour
That makes me wonder
Now the ship's aground on the shore
Of this uncharted desert island
With Gilligan, the skipper too
A millionaire
And his wife
The movie star
Oh, and the rest
Well, they're here on Gilligan's Island
Here in the parajuan
On the ambrosia
In the espíritu
All that happens
is you and me
Woo,ullie
Boy, we got a loig
esterol
Man, we'll be right back
And my wife's the reason
He starts his trip
This is the gist is
And that tiny ship was tossed
Back for the courage of the grief
A little minute would be lost
And the ships are grinding on the shore
And the sun surely doesn't rise
And they're here on Gilligan's Island
In harmony
A Cleveland band that I don't know
But somehow they picked up some subgenius slang
Probably because they are subgeniuses
And now speaking of people who are not subgeniuses
But don't know it yet
It's the great James Kochalka superstar
With Even the Clouds Get High
If you're offered dope
Don't be shy
Just take a toke
That's my advice
Cause even the clouds get high
Even the clouds get high
And if you're smoking dope
Don't ask why
Don't think twice
That's my advice
Cause even the clouds get high
Even the clouds get high
Everybody!
Come on!
Even the clouds get high
That's right!
Oh man, I forgot
Steve called today
Who?
Steven the mouse
What did he say?
Well...
Steven the mouse!
Oh I remember now
So we've got four the book
He's had a really fantastic time
What are you back so proud of
It's the你
Your phone
I don't talk about it
What are you talking about?
This is a great show
Feel it
He knows it
Yeah
This is really good
He's an amazing man
The Piper and Cljuie of organization.
You have reached the Alzheimer's Research...
Lavatory. No.
Lobotomy.
Oh, anyway, the place thingy where we study...
What was it? Anyway.
If you wish to leave a...
Oh, gosh, what was it?
A menage a trois...
No, if you wish to leave a...
Oh, please speak after the...
The...
The bath.
No, the...
The...
You're listening to the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
Sponsored by the Church of the Subgenius.
For more information about the Church of the Subgenius,
write to Bob at P.O. Box 140306, Dallas, Texas 75214,
or visit the Subgenius website at
www.subgenius.org.
Subgenius.com.
Thank you for listening.
And praise Bob.
You know it isn't only what you say,
it's what you do.
For all you do.
This is a buzz for you.
You know that he...
música
El Mar
What a blast!
...
Even though he has some flaws .
Please, please please please.