I know you don't have time to talk to your plants. Don't worry. You can go on about your business, whether that's to class or the office, or fixing dinner, or making love. They'll listen to the self-genius, our old swag.
Let's begin.
We're rolling. This is the good one. Take five.
Most folks have heard about it.
All right, that's good, Bob.
That's why folks call it finger.
Sounds good, Bob.
That's why folks call it.
The self-genius.
Our old swag.
Swag.
Perfect.
The self-genius.
Our old swag.
Oh, that's not true.
Tonight, radio's distinguished series dedicated to man's imagination.
The self-genius.
Our old swag.
It's our way of acknowledging our American heroes.
That's what you say.
We say you could act like a jackrabbit with frazzled nerves and a heart pounding like a trip hammer.
You gotta keep jumping.
You gotta keep punching.
Punch.
Punch that grandfather.
Ugh.
The victim can stand only so much abuse.
Too many people die because they couldn't live.
The grandfather's journey is ended.
He swam from the Pacific Ocean all the way up to Mount Fuji.
That's impossible.
Isn't it?
This is beyond our present knowledge or understanding.
Bob.
Ah yes, dear friends.
This is the hour of the slash.
And this is the hour of slack
But this is the hour of slack
Yes, dear friends, and we barely made it to 1,000 hours of slack, but that's what this is.
We just barely made it because when we jumped into the new I-Van to drive down here to the station for the most important show ever since the first one on October of 1985 in Dallas, the car wouldn't start.
A dead battery, friends, with about half an hour till showtime.
But luckily our jumper cables and the WeMobile exist together with the I-Van in the same dimension and thus here we are just in time for the world to end and to read and play.
All the submissions from our beloved listeners, contributors, and supporters.
You can hear what happened while you were on the couch watching Nick Van Pat on your TV in your living room while outside some hide while the saucers fly high while they do a drive-by.
And so, dear friends, with this new El Queso All-Stars intro music,
we'll be listening to the commemorative commentations on this, our 1,000th hour.
Now we introduce you to the host with the most Jesus-shamanically Marvin with a side of tongues,
like a psychic Burt Reynolds jumping his car through your neighbor's curly hair spreading slack everywhere.
That's me, dear friends.
And this is the hour of slack.
But this is the hour of slack.
And Dave and we are here to...
We don't...
Oh, well now we have some head fuzz.
Lay your hands on the radio.
Lay your hands on the radio band at home and we're gonna look to God.
1,000
Bob
Stop all the way.
The hour of slack.
That marvelous fleeting interlude.
Like the moment between each wave in a mighty ocean,
where everything is suspended.
Every string of the conspiracy's power neatly nipped away by its unique shearing vibration.
vibrations allowing you to drift and float in the flippity-floppity zing-zang of slack.
Ah, how sad that there can only be one a week. But nay, no, that is not so. For all these 1,000
hours of slack have been carefully and dutifully recorded by our obedient sacred scribe number 273
and can be gotten in so many different ways. Read up in subgenius.com for the many and sundry ways.
Why, you could listen to nothing but the hour of slack if that was your desire.
The hour of slack, a confounding yet cunning confluence of fractious fragments of brilliant
madness woven together weekly for 19 years by a word wrangler the likes of which,
well, there are no likes of which. Bob inspires crazily talented artistes of every kind you never
heard of to spring forth with endless precious audio offerings of puzzling wonder. And Reverend
Stang has been queuing it up for all of us all of these years, purely for the glorifying and
pious preservation of it all, and for our listening pleasure, creating an easily attainable,
soothing form of slack. The hour of slack, 1,000 hours of slack, listened to continuously,
one show on the heels of another, that would be a little more than 41 and a half solid days of audio
slack. What would that do? A thought that gives one pause. Perhaps there will be a radio marathon
and someone actually will do this.
Of course, maintaining a 19-year continuous archive of this weekly show would be no small feat.
But 41 days of slack is, at the very least, conceivable. The hour of slack,
where everybody is a star, no matter who you are, whether from near or whether far,
everybody is a star.
Where packaged, processed stars are nobody. The hour of slack. Each week I hear my beloved Stang
in his sacred studio above, lovingly whittling the profanity from the flagrant flowings of the
preachers, plucking the unallowable from what would otherwise never be heard. I hear the
ceaseless tinkerings of sound as he hones the show into the slippery seal of the show.
This may be the 11th hour of cosmic cacophony, but always it is to
truly a labor of loveщоose
Pennsylvania is the hour of slack. Here's to the next thousand hours! May they be as rapturous and rambunctious as the first, thou. Nay, may X Day come, and then all of the hours we live will become-... Hours of Slack.
When music arises in this movie, I couldn't imagine a Caribbean city without ocean music.
But once a pop snapper,サメンサーathanburgh is forced into this world. Don't give you your bracket against the scale of the wordiencies, because it wonderingly unw iceberging comes from Pluto.
Paulson, I just want to say that I endorse
Bob as my running mate in this year's election
and this is the hour of
slack in Dallas, Texas. You know,
I know where that is.
The hour of slack has brought lymph node,
pleasure, joy, sex, sex
hurt, sex dirt, excremeditation,
hours and hours of pooping,
chick, light at night,
stinky,
a surefire way to cut the hippies out of
my living room, an excuse
to do nothing on Saturday night,
a feel that purple giggles,
terrible earthy smells on my
index and middle finger,
terrible paranoia, the soundtrack
to a psychotic breakdown,
canyons and fungions,
the night sweats,
a surefire repudiation
of powerfully religions,
the grievous monkeys
versus robots,
the jinger device,
more slack than I can shake his dick at,
and all for the price
of my mortal soul.
Or triple my money back.
Thanks, Bob.
Thanks, Ivan.
And last, I have control of your radio tubes.
And I do, too.
Good. This is Ren Hoack.
And this is Stimson J. Catt
of the Ren and Stimpy Show.
And you're listening to the Hour of Slack.
Keep listening, you idiots.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Else I shall kill you!
Oh, the Hour of Slack.
All I can say is thank Dobbs
we've got it.
It was the reliable, cheap laughs
that made me first tune in, but
I soon found out that it was
so much more than just a radio show.
In between
the gut-splitting yawks were solid
nuggets of bright subgenius wisdom
to which I clung like an
ant hanging desperately onto
a floating matchstick and a claw
overflowing stinking
crapper.
Oh, with this silly little dog and prairie
squid show, Stang has taught
the Yeti spore to blow it
out our ass.
He gave us the recipe to take the
environmental psycho-venom of normal
life, top it with our own
spew, and hurl that toxic
pie right back into the face of the
con. And for a thousand
times out of the gate,
he has fulfilled his insidious
agenda of keeping the
Einsteins alive.
And every week
when we hear that agglomeration
of ranting voices echoing
through the ether, we know
with unassailable certainty
that we are not
alone.
And I, for one, can't
thank him enough for it.
Try getting a
laugh out of him after that, you
Dallas street mime.
Friends,
is your day-to-day ridiculous existence
at the hands of squealing self-important
normals wearing out your stinker?
Has the endless stream of Guero, Pander, and
Pablum on your TV set contaminated your
precious bodily fluids? Well, stew
no longer in your own bile, because the Church of the
Subgenius brings you the Hour of Slack
self-improvement course.
This series of 1,000 cassettes and
compact discs will allow you to maximize your
abnormality potential, eliminating wasteful guilt
from your life, and changing you into a spinning
rampaging example of self-actualization
at the expense of the normie worms, who,
as you've ruled your life while you were away.
Let's just see what a few happy users of the
Hour of Slack self-improvement course have to say.
My brain looks sort of like a smoker's lung.
It's not healthy for the children.
Would you like another lucky stroke?
Don't cry!
All this can be
yours today. Just send $13,013
to the Hour of Slack
self-improvement course.
www.subgenius.com
Please allow 999 weeks for delivery.
How the hell does he do that?
See from the Lymphoid Institute in Atlanta,
the first time I heard the Hour of Slack, like
many was on an ass-enjoying car.
Later, while building a large mural
out of waffles, the individual
the waffle holes became
pixels, and the syrup dripped
to make Bob's hair, and
with the insertion of what I'll call a pipe,
what was really more of an elephant's house.
I said, Bob, and Bob
turned to me and said,
nothing, because he was really made of waffles.
But thank you, Ivan. I've enjoyed the
Hour of Slack for these many years.
I hope to for years.
This is Doc from the Lymphnode Institute,
and the first time I encountered the Hour of Slack
I smelled like pizza,
and I was looking at God,
and realized that he had a pipe in his mouth.
And I became intensely panicked,
and realized that I must surrender
to this force, or it would
surely kill me.
And that's when I knew I was
listening to the Hour of Slack
on WREK Atlanta.
I like
Shane Ross Buddhism.
Because it's the world's
kindest religion. It's a
branch of Amida Buddhism. Amida
was the Buddha of boundless compassion
who refused to enter nirvana
until all sentient beings could enter
with him. So the teaching arose that
if you called on him in Japanese,
the name is Namu
Amida Butsu, in the name of Amida
Buddha, with true faith
you will eventually, no matter how many
incarnations it takes, you'll eventually get rid of
all the negativity and become pure,
enlightened. And Shane Ross,
a reformer, said that's asking too
much of people. Some people are just not capable
of true faith. They have a constantly
skeptical and questioning mind. They
should not be banned from release.
He taught that if you say Namu
Amida Butsu, whether you believe in it or not,
it will work. I like that. That's
my idea of a religion that doesn't give anybody
a bum trip. Most religions seem to
concentrate on putting people on bum trips.
You know, that's the only religion
in the world I know that never puts you on a bum
trip. If you've said it just once,
and I've said it three times, I'd say,
they can ask Namu Amida Butsu.
Guaranteed. He's like a
finance company in reverse. He wants to give you
something for nothing. How can you
reject a short-term, interim
savior like that? His only real competition
is J.R. Bob Tubbs.
Hello, brothers and sisters
in Slack. This is Reverend
Salatia. And
I tune into the Hour of Slack
every week, mostly
just to hear Reverend Sang
say, Ah,
yes, dear friends.
But in addition
to that, I also like
to subscribe to the show
because, um,
every shit and fuck
are sacred in this church.
And to not have
those included in my
Hour of Slack just doesn't get
me there. You know what I mean?
Bob. Bob. Bob.
Bob. Bob. Bob. Bob.
Bob.
One over twenty years, a bastion
of idiocy. A bastion
of... what is that?
Wax behind your head?
A bastion of brainiacs.
Oh, I see what it is. It's a little device.
I thought it was a piece of
candle wax stuck there by some
errant being.
Oh, yes.
Well, we're going to break here for a minute.
There's actually more of those recorded commentations from the Cabbage Gallery.
We heard there, we actually, the last person we heard from just before Reverend Salacia was Robert Anton Wilson, Pope Bob.
We heard Doc Ellis, O. Rex, Reverend Susie the Flusie, Ren and Stimpy, Lymph Note Institute, St. Pat Paulson, Princess We Are Doe, Norrell Preff, more and all of everything.
Father Guido Sarducci coming up, actually, and Dr. Timothy Leary.
But we have letters here, friends, from people who have, oh, an ego plum did the music behind Princess We.
I should mention that.
We used to play a lot of ego.
Ego plum.
We've got, our egos are very plum, aren't they?
Your ego is like a big fleshy vegetable that can be plucked off of some sort of two-toed tree that wanders hither and yon, spreading lies and innuendo for 20 years.
For 25 years.
Airwaves with Piskama and Wendabar.
Another, with collusion.
Collusion with the Piskama.
Powers that aren't.
And confusion.
With J.R. Slon Dodds.
I mean, the king, the god, the godman, man.
The man with the.
Get with it, dude.
Twisted DNA.
Man, wooden woman, man, man, woman.
Into more rubber band-like shapes than anyone could imagine.
I want to read, as we promised, I'm going to read some, we're all going to read some of the mail that came in when we asked for commentations on the hour.
Of a thousand slacks.
And this fellow here, this is, we don't know this person, nor is he employed by our ministry.
Jared.
Dread the lone yeti in Canada says,
I just have to thank, congratulate, and praise you all on the 1,000 episode.
I found out about the church when I downloaded and listened to a Frank Zappa interview with Larry King.
They mentioned the church for that interview.
And the rest is history.
I looked up subgenius on the web and found my new faith.
I can't begin to explain how much slack the church brings me in a day.
I was unemployed when Bob found me and wasting away in a slump of bad pills and bad sex.
I have since then found a new job where I use Bob's teachings daily.
My job is to motivate and teach people how to.
Sell!
And we are selling some total crap!
And praise Bob, without forcing and trying, I'm making all these pink boys selling and into it.
And I can get the best results out of my peers.
I am fooling those pink boys into thinking I am some sales guru.
And all praise due to Bob and the Haas.
Hour of Slack.
Hail the Hour of Slack.
I want to touch and feel every episode until Wotan takes me away.
Or the Exists come for us.
Well that is quite a fine alacrity, a piece of abnormal growth that is coming right out of the side of you again.
Very much so.
I mean within your own sight of course.
But this man that, is it a woman or is it a, what is it that sent this letter in?
That you just read?
Oh that, I won't make it.
I won't make it.
We know only that it was a Yeti.
Only as a Yeti.
Okay, shall I read this letter from Ree Stang?
You asked for our comments at the end of the Hour of Slack.
I didn't know.
Is the Hour of Slack ending?
Oh, anyway.
No, no.
Ree Stang.
You asked for our comments at the end of the Hour of Slack.
I joined the church a few years ago after I knew who I was.
No, I'm sorry.
After I knew what it was.
But it was clear Bob was talking to me like art through Devo whenever I was asleep or in a cabin.
I'm not going to give away my age or how old I am right now.
I'll wait until later.
We need Bob now more than ever.
Mark Mothersbaugh once said that he's an enema for a constipated society.
I'm alarmed at the use and the, well, the lack of use and the care of the conspiracy religion are destroying our planet.
Those exes can't arrive one minute too soon.
I believe the exeans, he called them, are the exeans.
He calls them the exeans, not the exes.
Oh, that might mean Christians.
That might be shortened.
Yeah, that's the way we shorten, like in Xmas.
The wearers of the crossed hockey stick stand to particularly procreate at a deliberately slow rate
using only the germs and the vibration method ordained by the Church of Nome.
I guess they're talking about the Eskimos again.
I hope I'm not reading this wrong.
Our ardor grows stronger with each glimpse at his
nakedness.
I hope I'm not reading this wrong.
Bob, although we know he's a plastered white-faced mannequin, is more than an icon.
But we're all going to have a last laugh when the saucers come from planet X.
He thinks they're coming from planet X.
That's so cute.
Coming from planet X.
They are.
Well, in a fashion, they're coming from there.
There's no location involved in this.
Right.
Evacuation.
That's what the news media calls it.
Just clear in this place and you're going to be a part of it if you want to.
Anyway, can you dig it?
In case the saucers and the church don't have any new address since I moved from, shall I say,
the state or could he be found there?
Move from pessimania, pessimism, here it is.
Deranged ex-bark 231 Hogan Avenue.
No, you don't need to give the entire.
No, we can move on.
New Halcyon.
We can move on to the next one there.
Yes, let's move on to the next one.
He's getting clogged up in the internet.
Let's move on to the next one.
Anyway, keep it up.
I guess they're talking about the erectile dysfunction problem there.
Keep it up and keep it happening.
You said it.
Close it.
Well, now here's a letter from Reverend Yukon Jack of W.I.C.A.
in Milwaukee, Wisconsin.
All right.
This is oh, this is a touching one.
He says he first heard the word of Bob in December of 1986.
When my friend Charles in Garland, Texas, started sending me tapes of the hour of slack from KNON.
That's garlic tennis.
I started broadcasting it on my station in Pasadena every Sunday afternoon.
I began tape correspondence with the Reverend Eris Pagana in summer 1991.
After gaining inspiration from the shows, I began sending them to
her in Milwaukee.
She saw the wisdom of Bob and for a brief time, she aired them on W.M.S.E.,
a local college station in Milwaukee.
Bob then brought me and Eris together in 1996, and the broadcasts on W.I.C.A.
began and continue to this day.
Eris and I shared several great times at X Day Drills in Brushwood, where we ran W.B.O.B.
radio.
At the drill in 2000, Bob brought Eris and Reverend DJ together, and they were married
by the Reverend Stang himself in May 2002.
Although Eris is no longer on this plane, I know that she has achieved eternal slack
with Bob and Connie.
Bob helped all three of us realize our life's long-term dreams.
It can surely be said that anything is possible with Bob.
Have mercy and praise Bob and hail Connie.
I am Bob.
I am Eris.
It's amazing that these people who have donated so much of their extra sweat and any other
glandular juices they can create.
That's right.
I was just going to say, are they as such, or are they just perhaps a projection of you
know what?
But you know, they do sweat and they put a lot of it into sending their feelings, their
thoughts, their doubts.
I can whiff it.
Perhaps.
Whiff it from here.
You've been down with it for at least four.
Whiff it.
Whiffing it.
And you've been indeed without it for quite a while.
Quite some time.
Anyway.
Oh, that's enough of these letters.
Let's skip over to these.
We'll come back to the letters in a minute.
We'll go back to the tapes.
I believe this is the hideous deformed Artemia Salina.
I just like to thank him for vibrating so hard.
That's all.
Slimy.
Oh, there we go.
Okay.
Hello, Reverend Stang and listeners of Hour of Slack.
This is Artemia Salina.
I just wanted to say congratulations on your 1000th show.
And to the viewers of the show.
To those who have been listening since the first show, I wish you a swift recovery.
And now a word of explanation about my voice, which some of you may have found to be a bit
unusual.
You see several years ago, I was involved in an unfortunate accident in which a large
quantity of hydrocarboplast-geoclase acid was spilled into a container of sulfurodiglase
dimethylhydrobromocrustoside.
The combination of these two otherwise inert chemicals caused a reaction,
which was quite violent indeed.
Though I am a man of science, the accident not only destroyed my voice books, but it also
damaged the part of my brain that makes me want to seek qualified medical attention.
Instead I sought the services of Dr. Noumanet, who has a recurring advert from the local
bargain hunter's periodical.
Dr. Noumanet offered to cobble together a cheaply made electronic voice books for me
in exchange for my eternal soul and the cost of materials.
Dr. Noumanet's voice books were not only a source of information, but also a source of information.
I was also convinced to refuse, and to this day it is my only means of audible speech.
Once again however, I wish to extend my congratulations to you for not fucking burning out after all this time.
Bob?
Hello Bob, this is Father Guido Sarducci, formerly Pope Maurice of the People's Catholic Church,
and all of my fellow popes from the People's Catholic Church.
Salute to the Church of the Sabbath Genius.
Carry on.
The hour of lack will ha-
over your own eyes so that if you worry about the fact that you are not able to hear the
message of the hour of lack, your mind will be hanging on the slide so that you never shut.
The hour of lack is a deadly danger that is slowly unfolding and will violently twist us.
The hour of lack may cause your toddler who never swore to suddenly disrobe and run down
the street screaming,
Locus!
The hour of lack is responsible for the time you hold in your head for all share.
The hour of lack is only open wide lab rat.
The hour of lack is no longer for you, just running your goody.
Hello, this is Timothy Larry, reminding you that just as you need slack,
KNON needs your help.
Send in those pledges, and praise Bob.
Hey!
Bob?
The message is now part of and registered in your subconscious mind.
This is Mr.
So this is my tribute to the black white folks and the hour of lack.
Praise Bob!
And watch them pounce upon themselves if they can't hide a person's dream.
Hello brothers and sisters in slack, this is Reverend Salatia.
Tune into the hour of slack every week.
Mostly just to hear Fernando Dandy Lee-mer say you rang.
Don't grin.
Ah!
Bob.
Please, please, Bob.
Oh, yes dear friends.
This is Li Li-Qing, a Chinese subgenius, and you are listening to the hour of slack.
Remember, Bob is the hour of slack.
is the comrades of all people.
Here in China, just like in America,
the people need slack.
In Chinese, we call slack le tian tai.
But it must be true slack,
not the bad slack of the conspirators.
Hi, this is Pat Paulson.
I'd like to endorse Bob as my running mate in this year's election.
Bob's a lot of... well, he's not fun, anyway.
But anyway, this is the hour of slack in Dallas, Texas.
One of my shoes got cow stuff on them.
J.R. Dobbs, Bob Dobbs, J.R. Bob Dobbs
was on the number one list of frauds and phonies for Time magazine,
and I didn't know who he was.
And J.R. Bob Dobbs is the creator of the Church of the Subgenius.
This guy, the Reverend Ivan Stang, is one of their...
Disciples.
Yeah, all right.
You know, it's funny.
I don't think Jesus had a disciple named Dopey.
Poor Bob.
Hi, this is Bob from Hack House,
greeting you in the name of Bob,
partly on behalf of Voice of Bob.
I'd like to share with you a little bit of the story of how I got involved
with Bob the Communist against the Nazis.
And that's exactly what happened, and that's...
Bob, he marks the beginning of something in my heart.
When he stripped in front of all these men red-hot pokers,
put in his body for me,
and I would certainly like...
I'd like to come.
Just go to persecution.com.
Persecution.com.
Let them know you're coming.
For I was hungry, and you gave me pot.
I was thirsty, and you gave me a hole.
I was a stranger.
I was naked, and you did it to me.
Persecution.com.
It's a vital form of physical relief.
I'm normally here to sell you.
The government wanting to get even.
Well, that's all for today, my friends.
Reverend Shane Smoker, and quite frankly,
the only reason why I listen to this show,
is to hear the...
Oh yeah! Oh yeah! Oh yeah!
See, I can't even bloody do it, but hell,
I think it's bloody funny.
Um, a thousand shows.
Well, stangy.
Stang!
Dave and Princess Wee.
Congratulations.
Bloody congratulations.
And, uh, praise Bob.
And, uh...
I really couldn't put my thought into this, did I?
I mean, this is quite a, um, a milestone.
Ah.
Um...
Still not a minute, though.
So, I'm just gonna, uh...
Oh, man.
Oh yeah! Oh yeah!
I'm such an idiot.
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Hello, brothers.
And sisters in Slack.
This is Reverend Salacia.
And I tune into the Hour of Slack every week.
Mostly just to hear Reverend Stang say,
Superior mutants.
REVEND QUIT YOUR JOBS!
SLACK OFF!
The world ends tomorrow, and you may die!
But in addition to that,
I also like to subscribe to it.
PR News.
Because, um, every...
And...
Cowboy!
...are sacred in this church.
And to not have those included in my Hour of Slack just doesn't get me there, you know what I mean.
So, uh...
Sit down. Don't sit down.
But at least set your dogs to find them.
RAAAAAAA!
I'm finding it difficult to breathe.
There's a subgenius Saturday night for ya.
And I say, as long as you're alive,
shout, make noise, or whatever,
because when you're dead,
you shut up like hell!
Just a walnut from a fire.
The oozing sauce.
The minions of the Hour of Slack luring their way towards the moss.
Hoping against hope,
they can get one fatal glimpse of the man himself.
The resin f- the rev-
Let me get this right.
I can read this right.
The Reverend Horace Smith-
Oh, no. I- Ivan Sting.
Of the Church of the Subgenius.
The Pro-Creative Cult-Meister of the Religion of Bob.
J.R.
Robert.
No. J.R.
Bob.
Dobbs.
A man who is more than a man. He's...
Part-Huma, part-Boomer, part-Boomer, and part-St-
Boomer.
And we-
And we're-
All the peoples of the world shall someday rise up and shout his name and be as disappointed as that little slackluster girl laying in the gucker.
Now I can tell things are gonna change.
But hey, enough of that.
Yeah.
I'd like to read a letter now if I may, should I not? No.
I will find her.
This, uh, singing in the background.
This is the voice of Mr. Fernanda Nande-Lemur.
This is him actually singing.
The...
When you listen to a man like this, you'll know he's more than a subgenius.
He is a true-
Man, that is really- that's just amazing, friends.
May the skin on my crawls go out.
Bob just wants to have fun.
Like dog-fuck.
As Mark Mothersbaugh plays here in the background.
Duck fat.
Not- no.
Bob's just want to have fun.
Oh, Bob's just want to have fun.
These are offerings of- not worship, what should we call them? Offerings of-
Off- offerings-
Of humility towards what has-
Of offing.
Miss-
Of humility towards what has to be in the offing.
Offing of all pinks of the planet Earth.
But with love in our hearts, you know.
We're not like blind milkmen wearing pancake makeup looking like so many mannequins packing out,
passing a little carnations for Bob.
No, we are-
Well, we're sorta like that.
We are the red carnation for Bob, and as we raise our fist in the air,
we're usually clutching at our own foreskins.
And we're not convinced yet, but we still believe that slack, any form of slack, given or misgiven,
is the best thing there is.
I'm sorry, I-
That's beautiful.
I could go on for-
I thought you were reading that from some letter that I'd handed you.
I thought you wanted me to cut it short as like a bad bowel movement, and so I did.
I-
I was cutting it short?
Well, you looked at me and I thought, Dave, will you wrap it up, please?
We've gotta get on to-
Oh, no, I just looked at you.
I was looking at you in puzzlement, like where'd that all come from?
Well, first-
Don't you have a letter there from another reverend to get a different reverend?
Yeah, right.
This piece of gaggies comes all the way from Sydney.
No, that sounds too cocky, doesn't it?
Anyway, I'll try it.
I'll try it real hard.
Sounds good.
Lama Cabo Dave, Princess Wee, Susie the Floozy, and all the dry web cockamamie bleebers down
at WCSB.
Thank you for all the slack.
No, that's-
I've gone to all the way-
It's fine.
Keep going.
His name's Reverend Chainsmacker, and he's a dildo do-raiser.
I wouldn't even remember my last name, how'd that hang out here?
I didn't know it was Iney Sbexok I can show you-
If you remember the fullatas line, it's strung out from broken Netflix.
And it, of course, is dumbo dope.
Well, let's just get all the way around.
The Waiting Room Party.
Clпис, we gotta stop.
It takes place on the audio frequencies of your inner ear.
It has hidden messages and meanings.
No commercialism.
Any heyday anky-panky of the right-wing Enlighteners.
And what's this?
The Akashic Records for 21.
And it's perfect with white wine and a bag of cheese.
Well, I guess that's more of a New Zealander somewhere.
Pardon me.
Boy, you got me.
That's beautiful.
Well, Princess Reedy, you have another letter from a reader?
Well, yes, I do.
I have another letter.
It's from a Charlie Fulton.
I'm going to pull this Soso Dada down in the background.
This letter says,
Greetings, Reverend Stang.
Just wanted to say that I've been listening to and enjoying The Hour of Slack since episode 836.
I always enjoy listening to Luminescence.
I love the Murr's cut-ups, the banter of ESO Swamp Radio,
while I miss hearing Professor Chaz Smith,
it's always great to hear Lonesome Cowboy Dave,
and great segments from Reverend Susie the Flusie,
and the Puzzling Evidence Show.
The Hour of Slack is one of the biggest reasons that I have DSL,
since none of the pink stations where I live carry the show.
Happily, my job allows me to keep a picture of Bob at my cubicle,
so I can keep some smalls.
I'm a semblance of slack in the office.
Praise Bob!
And that's from Charlie Fulton in Chico, California.
Thanks, Charlie!
Especially from a guy with a disease, you know, sending, you know,
wasting all his hard urine, squids, and his urine,
to send a letter through all the problems that you can get through sending a letter,
just to express that, I mean, the guy's got DSL for cripes almighty.
And you know, that can be nearly so flash, so flash.
Anyway, I was going to say that this is not a,
not an anti-local phenomenon,
it's a post-procreative inclusive web phenomenon,
meaning that you could catch it on your foot,
you could see it somewhere, like on the back gangly,
that are connected to your inner eye and so forth.
When we talk about the web, we're talking about the webbing in your body.
So I just want to say that Don Velo is not the real name of Dr. Sarducci,
but he was actually born in Ashtabula,
and he was a graduate of Lorraine High School,
and he was a friend of Dave Sheridan,
who was a fabulous furry,
Hurshute brothers.
History, friends!
Yes, history!
Long years of ancient, deadly history.
Histoire!
And for all those times and years,
everyone has been a defleccity for your beloved cockamamie organism.
That's Martin Mothersbaugh jamming away in the background in the early 80s
when he first got his Fairlight synthesizer, friends.
And maybe I should, I do have another letter and some more tapes to play,
but you know, I should do the shout-out, as we planned,
to all the stations, friends, that play the Hour of Slack,
that make this possible, that make us do this,
that force us to devolve into this every week.
Like a bleating goat.
We have, first, the ones that keep us on the internet, friends,
sensoryresearch.com or .net or .org.
Sensory research is how we keep, keeps us going.
Radio For All is another group.
And you know, Reverend Prostata Kontata
was the person who first set us up streaming MP3s to begin with.
And friends, I don't know what we would have done
without the great Saint David Bochner up there in Canada.
Bochner was the one who turned it into internet streaming
for years and years and years.
Only recently have I taken that job upon myself.
Before David Bochner, there was the great Reverend Juan Derrer.
And friends,
in the early days, of course,
who was it that first gazed at that picture of Bob with me and said,
let's work for this guy?
Dr. Philo Drummond, friends.
The overman, the original overman,
for whom we owe our knowledge of the Bob-legness.
We must thank Mr. Opinion and George Nolan of the ancient KFJZ stations in Dallas,
who were the first people to put us on the radio.
Actually, it's Fort Worth.
And where would the Hour of Slack be without Puzzling Evidence?
Puzzling Evidence, who had actually the first subgenius radio show predating Hour of Slack,
started in like 1982 with Bob Nelson's show,
which Puzzling Evidence took over.
And friends, Puzzling Evidence is where we learned how to do the weird editing that we do, many of us.
Glass Madness was the friend of Puzzling Evidence who had singing talent.
Lies!
St. Palmer Vreedes was a part of the show.
And Big Part then, as was the great Saint Gary Gaborg Fram.
And of course to this day, where would any hour of anything be without Dr. Howell?
Yes, Dr. Howell Robbins.
And lately, the good K-Rob, all together with Philo and Wellman on the KPFA show.
And friends, Reverend Susie the Flucy,
the woman who invented sax on WREK.
Byron Werner, Saint Byron Werner, he was the first media barrages.
And he actually invented the phrase Space Age Bachelor Pad.
Doctors for Bob from Little Rock, Arkansas,
seminally inseminated the very concept of doctor music and head launchings.
Hell Pope Huey was the first person to play our horrible tapes on the radio.
And contributed to them.
K-N-O-N in Dallas at one time was a great station.
And that's where we started in October 1985.
With Ranger Rita and even the help of Buck Naked.
The title Hour of Slack is based on a little one half sheet newsletter called Hour of Slack.
Actually.
That Buck Naked once did before he was saved by a different religion.
Written on a chestmark then, wasn't it?
Entirely written on a chestmark then.
I've heard.
Friends, Reverend Bleepo Abernathy is the voice you hear saying the title of the show almost every week.
And he's actually the source of the celebrities.
He gave us those celebrities.
Reverend Erwin Chusid had us on WFMU in New Jersey for so long.
It was important.
Dr. Phineas Narco has always been a huge contributor and help to this show.
And the California show.
Jesus.
Jesus Devil Aqua has kept the subgenius foundation going in our darkest days.
And Mr. Fernanda Nandy Lee Murr is what makes the Hour of Slack sound like the Hour of Slack these days.
As somewhat similarly does the work of the great Norell Preff.
And other old doc binary Slack great men.
Such as Artemia Salina.
Heart Ignition.
And New Monet.
Can we forget Dr. Sinister of WCSB in Cleveland?
The great station who lets us call in and wreck his show.
Einstein's Secret Orchestra.
The ESO show with Chaz Smith.
Put us on the air all through the 90s.
And let us do the sloppy stuff.
How else would we know of the Oye Man?
Friends, we must thank so many contributors.
The El Queso All Stars.
Dr. Onan Canabite in the old days.
Pope David N. Meyer.
Brother Cleve Duncan.
Michael Pepe.
Dr. G. Gordon Gordon.
DK Jones.
Papa Joe Mama.
Dr. Legume.
Ed Strange had a subgenius show and helped a lot.
Craig Roll also did.
Friends, Deet and the bands.
The great bands of the Hour of Slack.
Starting with Doctors for Bob and Doctors for Wotan.
Followed shortly by Devo.
The Amino Acids.
Negative Land.
Little Theodore.
Einstein's Secret Orchestra.
The great King of Slack, Bill T. Miller.
Saint Anne.
And friends, the Swingin' Love Corpses.
And Dave, I think that you might remember an old comedy group that's probably we might want to give a tip of the hat to while we're doing our Slack credits.
By the name of the Firesign Theatre.
Indeed, indeed.
Firesign Theatre has pointed the way.
I don't think you and me would be in this room right now if it wasn't for the Firesign Theatre.
I don't think we could have an election if it wasn't for the Firesign Theatre.
The Firesign Theatre, which is taking up all the spaces on this bus there are, and so that's why we're...
Friends, some of you think, oh, they must have heard some Monty Python.
No, no, no. Monty Python was much, much, much later.
They might have heard some Goon Show.
Well, we might have, but we didn't.
What we heard was the Firesign Theatre!
Praise Reverend David Ostman.
Yes, dear friend.
The great Phil Proctor.
Phil Austin and Peter Bergman.
The...
Oh, oh.
David Ostman.
Oh, that was Devo doing the music in the background, and before that I think it was Onan Canobite.
No, now it's Onan Canobite.
Friends, the stations!
The stations who've helped us out!
Did I get around to the new station, WQFS in Greensboro, North Carolina?
The great longtime players, WEFT in Champaign, Illinois.
Gotta teach your heart, make a lot of money on real estate.
Friends, believe it or not,
in deep in Connecticut, WHUS plays the show because they dare!
WICA, Wicca in Milwaukee, Wisconsin.
WMPG in Portland, Maine has played the Hour of Slack for nigh on to as long as WCSB here in Cleveland has.
And they keep on going on that MPG.
For like 10, 15 years.
And thanks to Reverend Mike Townsend who put us on there.
In WCSB, I think it was originally first Reverend Toth Wilder got on.
Got us on to that other WRUH.
And then Mike Cole, Reverend Mike Cole helped keep us on.
And Reverend Craig Callender.
Yes.
We must thank all of these folks.
Praise Toth Wilder, Mike Coles, and Craig Callender.
Out in Madison, Wisconsin, Sister Velveteen Sly on WORT has kept this show going.
And friends, WREK at Georgia Tech in Atlanta not only plays the Hour of Slack,
has the Suzy the Floozy Show, the Lymph Node Institute Show.
Friends, where would we be?
The South shall rise again with the help of WREK as well as WUTS in Sewanee, Tennessee.
And WXEY in Kendallville, Indiana.
And friends, let's not leave out KPFA in Berkeley.
They don't play the Hour of Slack.
They play the Puzzling Evidence Show.
And we love them.
I'm talking about them.
And we love our subscribers who get the cuss-filled, uncensored internet shows.
Dr. Tillis, Dr. Johnson, Reverend Crossan, Reverend Penton, Salacia, Cindy, Reverend Bill, Ely.
Friends, the Hour of Slack thanks you all.
We have done 1,000 billion years of hours because of you and this.
This Dave.
Think how many seconds have gone by since you've been on the show.
I respect it, Lord관, absolutely a million.
Just think about a little below, and it'll help you.
Ah.
Journey to Land of Unël All Over Paradise.
Poshlip Duh Quoglet
Poshlip duh quoglet's R&D
Poshlip duh quoglet's C melhor
Sultana
Holy
Boh
Lu
Think of yourself that way.
Now drift slowly into a dream.
A dream of your own creation.
A huge...
Man, that flying saucer, they look more like garbage cans.
But the garbage cans of your own design have no fear.
You make them with your mind and your lousy, dirty, stinking bucks.
Is that all that's left of you?
Oh, sorry. I'm just kidding.
I forgot what happened.
It's all right. It's all right.
It's okay.
It's been so 20,000 years.
How many seconds has we been on the air for a thousand shows?
That is a depressing thought.
Yeah, when you think of it, nanoseconds, how long have we been...
We never got out of here, man.
I mean, you know, relatively.
It's the show that refused to die.
That's about it. You about got that right.
Friends, let me read this one last...
Actually, we have all kinds of filthy commentary that I could read.
We got letters.
They weren't exactly about the hour of slack.
Well, you can just indicate the word without actually slurring out the dirty word for the bad seven thing.
This guy really gave me a reach around.
This is someone named Mathael.
Mathael?
Yes, who said...
I think the M and the R on his keyboard were screwed up.
Maybe.
You're like the famous painter Mathael.
With the swinging love corpses in the background, Mathael typed...
Mathael.
I appreciate.
I appreciate that the subgenius church makes a point of having people own their own truth.
Congratulations on creating language that bypasses the filters people have that fool them into thinking they understand something just because they know a word for it.
Bob, slack, the conspiracy, yakateesman, these are all useful terms because although people may not understand them, then they at least know that they don't.
Unlike...
God, grace, etc., which most people have been fooled into thinking they understand, fresh terms help with a new view of ancient concepts.
And he happens to like the...
His favorite ones are the ones where Stang rants and reads from other tripped out writings.
I have Revelation X and find it amazingly insightful and well articulated.
Let's see.
I like the old subgenius.
I like the subgenius recordings where it sounds like the terminology has been freshly created and I can hear the tenderness and love in the subgenius apostles' voices.
Those would be the old tapes, I guess.
I would like to learn more about the experiences, group trips, etc., that led to the articulation of church doctrine.
What would he want to know?
I'm sorry.
Mainstream religions preach love but practice hate, worship bohemian prophets but enforce dress codes,
and claim to own the whole truth but have virtually no living truth remaining.
The subgenius church preaches hate, worships a clean-shaven idiot, and gives the surface appearance of nonsense,
yet triggers loving truth to arise from within.
It's amazing to me the cleverness with which sensitive souls have learned to thrive in a hostile world.
Thanks for providing and exemplifying true slack.
Oh, P.S.
I had a dream that Ivan Stang is a reincarnation of an early influential Gnostic and a truly profound soul.
Oh, that's a good note.
Oh, boy.
I told you.
That guy gave me quite a reach around.
I think so.
Stang, what is that dripping from your...
Is that blood dripping from your goatee?
No, that's just...
You said it was a reach around.
You said you didn't have to actually chew on his organs.
I'm sorry.
What a strange man, too.
I offer him kudos for his praise of the church and his 20 years in business.
This one I had assigned for you to read when I first read the hour of slack.
Oh, I don't go for the uterine devices.
Only the gonococcal devibrators can be used this time.
Anyway, at least until the 4th.
Not of July, of course, but, you know, the 4th of encumbrance, which is coming for all of us pretty soon.
After Thursday.
Here's the gesticles.
Oh, this was done by the gesticles in Australia.
There's a bobby on the clothesline and a kitten on the grill.
There's dog poop on the table, but I cannot eat my fill.
There's a blank spot in my stink tank that says reserve for pamphlet one.
I'd love to shove it in there verily, because it sure does sound like fun.
Send me slack or plonk me.
It's the only thing to do.
I do not own a...
I don't own a credit card, but I want to join with you.
I've lived with Bob for years now, had a picture on my dash.
It was there until it faded and my car was not but trash.
I've touched myself to Connie and received a nasty rash.
Now I've finally gotten around to it and offered up some cash.
And he did.
He did, in fact.
Was it currency that you can actually use?
I mean, the coin of the realm, not going to like.
A lot of times you like to send monopolistic money.
Poetry.
Money.
Sometimes they'll just send like a zygote on a tissue.
Well, not a real zygote, a bloody zygote.
Here's a good one.
This one comes from a different...
This guy writes, send stuff from a different address each time.
Excreted inflation, perhaps.
I don't know.
This comes from a person that says, you know I know you.
Dear Bob.
Now listen to this.
Okay, I'm listening.
Dear Bob, you broke my leg.
You gave me hype.
After the restaurant tantrum went down, you gave me an address.
Told me to meet you there.
I came to meet you.
There were two guys.
One girl looking over I-5 south of Beacon Hill.
The same two guys from the restaurant.
One girl.
They asked me into the house.
I said, no thanks.
The tall guy looked like an altar boy.
Said, nice bike, 66 BMW.
Let me take a ride.
I said, no.
He then said, well, give me a ride.
He was six foot three inches tall.
Jumped on my bike.
Grabbed my...
And squeezed hard as he could.
Humped me five or six times.
I had let him try.
I had let him try on my jacket.
It was too small.
He stretched himself into it.
After the ride, the three of them were around me.
I said I had to go.
When I got home, I had black and blue marks on me for a week.
I lost my father at 16 years old.
And I know you have no children.
I'm adopting you as my father, Bob.
And I will be your son.
The son you always wanted.
When you were a little boy, did some red-haired guy screw you over?
I forgive you, Reverend James Doyle.
Boy, that sounds, you know, like they call it Beacon Hill because of the strange, you know,
beaming beacons that are going into the minds of the people in the restaurants.
And we actually know some of the subhumans.
We're not going to call them subgeniuses in this particular instance.
Who were at the bottom of Beacon Hill waiting to spank him and torture him with a 1966 tricycle.
It was not really even a bike.
If only we could stop, Bob.
My mind is going.
Well, this guy is so far gone.
The actual tissue in his brain.
You're the corpus callosum is decomposing.
And it's, you know, like practically brain dead and nobody told him yet.
I'm not saying it's not great stuff.
And we love his appurtenance and also his apertures.
But we can't fit in there.
You know what I'm saying?
You got to send your you got to pay your pledge money, friends.
That's all it is.
Friends, we got to move on and move out.
So I'm going to go back to the tape recordings of the live subgeniuses as they tell us their love, love, love.
Because their mind.
Is going swinging love corpses goes out in the background.
And it is the lemur will help us.
Thank you, Church of the Subgenius for 20 years of misdirection, lies, squandering, insomnious.
My mind is going.
So my mind is going.
Long call, Dave.
Don't you know what they're doing to yourself?
This is the Reverend Cardboard Box.
That's right.
Cardboard Box.
Remember the Antipodean subgenius shown?
No, not too bad.
I listen to the Arrow of Slack whenever I damn well feel like it.
Yo.
I use some ducks.
During this period in Vàquan
I realized that during one of the Friday Mottie Bay School 258 maybe
She was over there from a 10 hour
influentialacking
there the
dinner
Toodlee
Mom
Che whom
如果我星期天
听到一个小时
我就可以过一个星期的生活
在粉红色的世界
保存我的精神
谢谢我们的美国装置朋友
谢谢