In one of the countless billions of galaxies in the universe lies a medium-sized star,
and one of its satellites, a green and insignificant planet, is now dead.
From PR News in Washington, I'm Idealon.
The FBI says that President Bush landed about 100 feet away from his podium on Wall Street 28 and 62529.
Byron Dorgan says Federal Judge Joan Lefkoe Brown was a dud.
PR's bad. PR's bad.
PR's PR News, meanwhile, has called for more violence.
Police say PR News was gunned down today in Washington.
Hello? Hello? Hello?
I thought I told you never to call me here.
This is important. I'm trying to do something of importance. Can't you understand that?
Yes, I know you have needs, but I have needs too, and my needs are to broadcast...
What is... Is that... Will you get that away from the phone? I can't even...
Why do you call me here?
All right, okay.
We'll talk about this later.
I'll call you some other... Yes, I... No, I don't want to say it. I'm...
All right, I love you. Now... Yes.
Yeah, puppy biscuit. Right. Two pounds of butter. Right. I won't forget.
And, uh... Yes, the Simpletons are coming over tomorrow night. Yes, I... All right. Okay.
Yes, you too. All right. Okay. Goodbye.
Well, that was another typical disgruntled caller disrupting our show.
So we've come here today to dramatize...
It's a shameful condition.
It's...
Bob?
Now, uh...
We have a... We're looking deep into the brain of the Bobby now.
Listen to that babble of Bob's in the brain of the Bobby in the tiny...
He thinks about his Bob.
Well, I...
I rarely do.
He pulls on his Bob and he packs his Bob and he...
Now, come on. Let's keep it clean here.
He does little movies of his Bob and, you know...
Oh, those are so cute. You can run them again and again.
It's true.
And we've accepted that free gift of being made righteous.
Father, today, open up the eyes of our understanding.
Let the presence of the Holy Spirit fill this room
and flow through this tape, this CD, this cassette tape,
this book.
Oh, God, talk to us today.
Help us understand how much you are for us.
You said you came that we might have life and have it.
Have a life.
Have a life worth living.
A wonderful, faith-filled, happy, healthy, joyous, successful, prosperous life.
And just as you broke the powers of darkness at Calvary,
you spoiled the principalities and powers.
And you've come now to divide the spoils of the strong men
with those of us that are rising up and being strong in you.
Thank you, Father, for this message
and this great healing prosperity revival
that's sweeping across our land and around the world.
In Jesus' name, amen and amen.
Thank you, God.
Praise God.
Are you ready to get into the Word now?
Oh, yes.
The book of Deuteronomy, the 11th chapter,
it says that,
If we will put God's words in our mind, in our heart, in our soul,
our days will be as the days of heaven on earth.
Now, listen to this.
The plague of frogs.
The plague of bugs.
The plague of blood.
The plague of infinite darkness.
The plague of your brinner.
The plague of Pharaoh's tiny son.
Only a tidbit in the malicious mouth of dogs.
We're standing up high on the plateau,
looking out over the Indians,
thinking to ourselves,
what if they take over this great land?
I die now, my son,
but someday there will be a man
with something in his mouth from which smoke comes
like the fire on this sacred mountain.
I am weak, my dear son,
but I tell you that this man will be named.
Yes, this early misinterpretation of prehistory
predicted the coming of Marlboro Man as a leader in the future.
What the hell is it with you people?
What do you mean?
You know what I mean.
Management, you, Jesus, John the Baptist,
a whole bunch of you.
All fired up to throw your lives away.
They did what they had to do.
Hogwash.
You think the Lord had to die to make his point?
What if when they said,
come on down from that cross,
old Jesus just come on down and spit right in their eye?
What harm would that have done?
That's about the dumbest thing I ever heard.
No, it ain't.
The dumbest thing is dying when you ain't gotta.
Dying just because you piss poor at living.
That ain't true.
It is true and you know it.
And I'll tell you something else that's true.
When it comes to living,
dying is the easy part.
Uh, we, we, uh, we're still at war.
But you bet.
Ask others.
My department.
Ask the American people.
But my department is worshipped in this mess.
Be, make sense.
Make sense.
The American people expect us to do that.
But you bet.
We've been.
Still at war.
But you bet.
We still at war.
Still at war.
Stop.
We still at.
Still at.
Still at, still at, still at war.
People expect.
Do that.
Uh.
Re-
He's still at war. He's still at war. He's still at war.
And here we are Sunday morning in Normaltown, USA.
And we're driving down the new concrete freeway.
Dad smoking his pipe while Mom applies her lipstick.
In the rearview mirror...
In the backseat, Junior and Sis take turns French-kissing Spots, the family dog.
There's Mr. Wilson emptying the trash into his...
A clean hit, and Mr. Wilson will be in the hospital at least two and a half years.
Hi, Mr. Wilson.
Goodbye, Mr. Wilson.
Sorry about stealing you.
Okay.
As long as you apologize in the future, everything's okay.
And now we come to Four Corners, the famous traffic intersection in Midvale's downtown business district.
Hi, Mr. Caller.
In my hometown.
See, he's so happy here.
As Richard Nixon used to say during the Vietnam War,
now...
More than ever.
You!
You look like, you look like, you look like you're just the right age to be drafted.
Does that even bother you?
It was a sign at Jonestown behind Jim Jones' dead body.
And it said,
Those who do not remember the past are condemned.
To repeat it.
Which would you rather sacrifice, your hot car or your life?
Die for oil, sucker.
Hurry, hurry.
Hurry, ladies and gentlemen.
Come to the subgenius land carnival of grotesques and oddities for one dime, ten cents.
One thin tenth part of a dollar admits you to the kingdom tense.
You will see two-ton Tessie, the ugliest thing on the Midway.
See her twirl her tassels.
Grown men, blanch, and young boys lose the desire to continue with puberty when this horrific sight of nature is revealed.
Oh my.
Hey, that's my butt.
Billy, you are not going in there.
Come away right now.
Oh, come on.
It looks me, Aunt Bertha.
I want to see the six-headed cow.
I want to see the two-headed snake, Aunt Bertha.
Now, boys, you know that it says in the Bible,
He who lookest upon the two-headed geek becomes himself a horrible freak.
One of us. One of us. One of us. One of us.
And so, Aunt Bertha and the children left the fairground.
Sadder. But perhaps a little wiser.
For they understood that Jehovah One in His Majesty had put the carnivore there in the first place just to teach them that lesson.
I want to go see the lonesome cowboy Dave.
I want to go see Red Mist. I want to go ride on Red Mist.
I want to go see the Brother Justin, seven-headed devil.
Search and destroy, search and destroy.
Come on, come on.
I want to go see the Antichrist, and bye.
Okay, now just...
I just want candy apples.
Quiet down or you're not going on any of these damn rides.
First, you pull up your pants.
You're crying out loud.
You look like a shoe baby.
Whatever the hell that is.
So, order caffeine.
And tie your shoes, by the way.
I've got to go kill that devil preacher, Bob.
Stan, you'll get plenty of chances to kill lots of things if we go on Red Mist or search and destroy.
No, man, I know why I've been given these powers.
I've been given these powers so I could go be the one that kills Bob.
Well, you'll get plenty of chances to try your powers out on these new war rides.
I'm going to kill Bob and save the world, man.
Ah, you can kill anybody you want and win a medal for it or maybe even a Googie prize.
Really?
Have you ever seen one?
They're as big as the sun and they fit neatly on anyone's chest.
We can go to that recruitment place and join up.
Oh, no, that's for later.
First, we're going to take a ride on Red Mist.
I just step inside the little capsule here.
Oh, man, this is authentic.
Shut up.
This is scary.
Please don't go on the Red Mist ride.
This is the unfriendly neighborhood.
I don't want you to go on the Red Mist ride.
There's a surge and sea all over the walls.
And up here comes a Red Mist.
Somebody just exploded an anti-personnel.
Oh, that was backwards, wasn't it?
Of course it's backwards.
It's all backwards.
The planets you live on.
The cheese you eat.
The factories you smell and the olfactory feats you perform.
Everything in here is controlled.
The Red Mist.
The search and destroy rockets.
The little rides that take the children to teach them about war.
For it is what they need to learn.
And yourself, why have you enlisted?
Oh, carnival today.
Everything has been so backwards and upside down and inside out
that I just had to come here to see if I could figure it all out.
Well, there's no chance of that.
Everything's going to look pretty much askew as it did before.
But if you just put your hand here on the little plan-gar,
and let's say it's heating up now.
I don't know if I should do this.
Oh, you have to do it.
It's taking your decoder name, your special eye patch now.
Ah.
That looks good.
You look like a real pirate.
You're going to be able to kill lots and lots of people and scare them before they die.
And it could feel real good.
But remember, if you step on the wrong thing,
Red Mist.
I'm nervous. I'm really, really nervous.
Well, here's some nerve pills.
And here's the nerve gas.
Don't get too flatulent there.
Just a little army joke.
Ah, fudge.
Yeah, up it up, baby.
Be careful with that nerve, Jay!
Yeah, I don't want to have too much of that.
Okay, okay, okay.
I'm feeling kind of nervy now, aren't I?
Uh, uh, uh, uh.
Ready to spank the future?
Show them what it is.
Yeah.
That's the first thing I noticed about them was the strange laughter after coming out of the rides.
The carnival itself wasn't impressive as far as the facility or fairgrounds or anything.
You know, they didn't have much going on.
Not too many potato cakes or funnel hoses or any of those things.
There were a lot of important records and documents they were keeping somewhere.
It looked like the ones in Red Mist were having the most fun.
That simulated blood all over there.
I like that booth.
That way they had them Arturians that were that cult that liked to cut each other's legs and arms off so they could follow that one cult guy.
Oh, that is sh-
That's a crazy cult.
The John Wilkes booth was my favorite.
The one that would just pop surprise.
Oh, yeah! That was crazy.
Killer!
Pops the Prez.
And I wish they'd stop doing this to me because my nerves are...
My nerves are not meant to be part of this.
Arturo.
Yes?
What is it?
Our hero.
I am not your real hero.
I am more of a figment of your October imagination.
But that's okay, friends.
Because we're back at church again.
The fun ride, the Abusement Park, we call it.
Yes.
Yes, indeed.
The Dobstown Abusement Park of the Hour of Slack.
This episode, number 996, entitled Revenge of the...
Shit.
A foul number.
1996.
Mmm.
Yeah.
And we've been listening to...
The show started out with the usual chop-ups by Mr. Fernando.
Mr. Fernando.
And a bunch of collage material there by Norel Pref at heavyconfetti.com.
And of course, we heard Dr. Howell and Puzzling Evidence and those old-timey guys from the
old-timey KPFA show, which is still on to this day on kpfa.org.
And praise all those many orgs who help us and bring us things like...
Fat suits.
Yeah, fat suits.
The armaments are very important, Stang.
As a member of the service club, you should know that these armaments are fully insured,
and they're very, very safe for even the smallest brat.
And speaking of brats, they're all about to get drafted, aren't they, as I understand
it?
Yes, and they're going to have to attend those.
There's big talk of sending them up into the sky to pioneer the outer planets, the new
world...
Nice.
...where our youth can go to fight for the new Mars and the old Earth and protect freedom...
Liberties.
...and media.
The Omicron death.
T-shirts and tennis shoes and the American Western Civilizational Way.
The Black Stan.
The queer hats and synoptic remotes.
And it's our burden, friend.
It is a burden that we must take on because...
Well, actually, no, we don't have to take it on, do we?
Because isn't that the point?
Isn't there something bigger than saving the world?
Something called X Day.
X Day.
Yes.
X Day is approaching, friends.
X Day.
Your prayer partner, Reverend Ivan Stank, does not want to see you go unruptured on
that precious day, that prophesied day that Bob said was coming, July 5th, 1998.
This could be that year, friend.
One of these days, it's going to happen.
You don't know.
You don't know what planet this is on.
I'm not waiting.
I know.
Yes, it's...
And, friends, the X Day drill, actually.
The event itself, the gathering, the great gathering of the subgeni will occur from June
30th to July 5th of this year, they falsely call 2005, at Brushwood Center.
Brushwood Folklore Center, Sherman, New York.
You're not going to learn much folk-lay over there before we have Folklorico this year.
No, but there will be the bad film.
Not too many dancing ladies in red Piper dresses or those people with the funny hats.
The evil bad film drive-in will be there, Dr. Dark's bad film drive-in, as usual.
With evil popcorn and hot dogs to go with it.
Sideshow marvels, limbless geeks and cult figures, human fights.
People with one eye right in the middle of their bleeding forehead can read your mind
and wish they couldn't.
The amino acids heard in the background.
DNA, which sponsors their activities.
Nude squid gigs, my friend.
Oh, and they're fun to eat as well as throw at passengers on this rickety train.
And the costume ball this year is with the theme of deities, yes, yes, yes.
Dress as your favorite false prophet.
Build a huge false idol to worship.
Well, we've done that plenty of times before, my friend.
We've built false idols.
We've built false idols all up and down this highway.
Look at their skulls rising up high in the sky.
Look, there's the giant skull of Philodrummon.
He'll be there too.
Shines, just like he shines his feet.
And look, there's the skull of the Reverend himself.
Ah, yes, torpid vehicle, but it can still do wonders if you push the right buttons.
Oh, such torpidity.
And friends, you'll get torpid as heck.
And then naked frop baptism, or Bobtism, I should say.
In the great heated pool of Brushwood.
Bodies will float in the river.
Gashes above their eyes and ears are not a thing to concern yourselves with.
They have taken these wounds upon themselves.
They're mad.
They want only one thing.
A new, a new brave.
A new race.
A new slack.
A new Bob.
Actually, we do want a brave new world, friends.
Better than this chicken crap baloney we've been dealing with.
And that's why lonesome cowboy Dave and the mondo retardo band will be at X Day.
It's why there'll be launchings.
Why, look at that head fly through the air, followed by the brain and the soul and the soul brain mind.
And the fingerprints.
Oh, that's beautiful.
Oh, what a fine launching.
Excellent form with his swing there.
Dr. Banz, friends, to launch those heads.
Like the aforementioned amino acid we're going to be.
Fully accredited, Dr. Banz. Fully licensed.
By the state of anxiety in which this lightning bolt strikes.
Never mind it.
Friends, these are the doctors that'll pry your mind open, just like this show does.
Doctors for Bob, man.
It will open various doors for you.
Look closely at these doors.
A giant mahogany door with a beautiful silver clapper on the bell.
And a beautiful Reverend Nikki Death Chick whipping and spanking the guilty.
And the innocent until they're guilty again.
And Sister Ducadence.
Yes, I just talked to her tonight on the phone.
Making plans to be there all the way through July 5th, friend.
It's on a Tuesday.
But are you going to go back to work because you have more faith in Mammon than in Bob?
Are you going to do that and just skip waiting for the saucers that beautiful 7 a.m. July 5th, Tuesday?
Skip on down like a bright innocent child.
Everything is sanctioned by the Knights Pimpler.
There's no lost cheese or fried lightning bolts.
Everything is square and juicy.
You'll love it, little ones.
And the little one will love yours.
And do you know why?
Because you know who else is going to be there, friend?
You.
That's right. You're going to be at Exit 8.
You're going to be with us on the saucers, ain't you?
Because you're a subgenius minister.
Otherwise, you probably wouldn't be listening to this show.
You wouldn't be able to listen to it without wanting to sign up, join up, and be a subgenius minister.
Casting out devils and false prophets.
A lot to throw out.
Yeah, a lot to cast out.
And sexing those fraught nuns and nun snakes.
Oh, lots of sex and nuns.
You know, we're like any respectable, huge world religion.
Our priests are sex fiends.
We don't chase after children because they're too small.
Oh, yeah. That's the main problem. They just don't fit, right?
And friends. But we chase after them for their souls.
We want to raise them.
We want to see that they're raised right.
Wow.
It's the same for everything.
There's nothing like nothing.
You never saw anything so heartwarming as a whole field full of subgenius children on
Ex Day Mourn, waiting for those saucers to come down, doing things that you wouldn't do normally, you know,
because it's not usually the end of the world.
But you're not normal, and you can do these things.
You can not only warm those hearts.
You can cook them in a pan, and we're going to cook plenty.
Praise Bob. Praise Bob. Praise Bob.
It's a prosperity ministry.
Oh, yes.
And it's a slack ministry.
Friends, you'll learn how to slack off like a real slack-off artist.
No weepers here.
No peepers.
No silent green.
No eyeballs.
No nothing.
No human beings at Brushwood Ex Day.
And you can't get in unless you're a subgenius minister.
And you can't be a subgenius minister unless you've got the blood of the Yeti coursing through your veins.
Ah, yes.
You're going to have to have a little card maybe, huh?
You're going to have to have maybe a little ID card that shows you.
Oh, yes.
You've got the right feet and the right structure and the front of the brain with a
heart skull.
Well, I've got that card in my pocket.
I've got mine in my pocket.
I ain't going to be caught on that.
You know how it's going to be there, friends?
Joe's got a picture on it.
Beautiful picture.
Princess, we are those going to be there.
And one of these days, her flock, you know, she's the queen of all the UFOs.
And one of these days, them UFOs are going to be coming.
They're going to be coming, friends.
They're going to lift us up in glory because we've got subgenius ministers' card in our
pocket.
And the rest, they're going to burn.
Cruel.
Torturously.
Because Bob is not a forgiving God.
He's neither a wrathful God.
He's a forgetful God.
He's not going to pay any attention to what we're doing.
We're probably going to be getting back once we've got those escape vessels at our command
armed with weapons beyond the – well, within the imagination of every subgenius but beyond
that of the pink boy, the norm worm down below, who will be facing those weapons for
the first time.
Those highest – those bullies in school.
that tormented you.
This is your chance for revenge.
And if you prefer,
you can reconstruct these bullies in your mind
and have them torture you all over again.
That's right.
You can do everything you ever dreamed of all at once.
It's like the perfect drug,
and yet it's without drugs.
It's Bob.
That's all it is.
It's just the love of Bob
entering your heart and your mind.
The main thing is Bob creeps into your head.
That face.
You know what I mean?
It's a face, man.
He's a big, big man, Bob is.
That's why his face has been copied
and put up everywhere.
He's that smoking guy with the pipe.
That's Bob.
That's the Bob we're talking about.
I got so sick while I was driving,
I almost got pulled off.
If you see some pipe-less Bob,
that's just an A-Bob.
That's a bad sign.
That's an A-Bob.
He's not of the true Bob's full nature
unless he's got that pipe.
And not every A-hole with a pipe
is J.R. Bob Dobbs, my friend.
Yes.
But what's that?
There are false prophets everywhere.
False prophets.
Horrible.
There are false missions.
There are sins.
Becut them.
There are dangerous situations.
Spiritual situations.
That is deep.
Oh, yeah.
This is good false prophet music.
In the meantime, let's dance.
But of course, let's dance.
Oh, yes.
The bombs are exploding out the window.
I can't.
I can hardly.
I can see the flash.
I can't hear the damn thing but the band.
Every other soldier has a pipe.
Yes, look at those handsome young lads
off to die for what?
For slack?
Oh, speaking of dying for war and stuff,
I think it's probably time for PR news and...
And, uh...
Cha-cha-cha.
From PR news in Washington,
I'm an arrogance of power.
Consumer prices rose by a half percentage point in April,
but the gain was largely caused by the traffic congestion.
Here's bad.
In stocks today,
1, 2, 1, 3, 10, 4, 6, 4, 6, 30.
The city of Los Angeles faces significant problems,
including gang violence and the nation's worst PR news.
Satan in the White House.
We'll be watching.
People are dying all over the world,
some by their own hands, some by accident.
Soon a lot more people will die of starvation.
Oh!
And there's nothing we can do about it, nothing at all.
Do you understand?
Satan in the White House.
We'll be watching.
People are dying all over the world.
People are dying all over the world, some by their own hands, some by accident.
Soon a lot more people will die of starvation.
Oh!
And there's nothing we can do about it, nothing at all.
Do you understand?
It's part of a major realignment by the Pentagon and Defense Secretary Donald Rumsfeld.
Another zombie flick.
It's a different kind of church and state.
More violence.
Well, when I first heard this news, I am very surprised.
With 181 people bored.
Can fortune cookies produce a real fortune?
What happened to keeping church and state separate?
The 1999 massacre at Columbine High School.
Government troops putting down an uprising there fired into a crowd that included
Cat Stevens.
Night of the Living Dead.
Land of the Dead.
Where the truth lies.
Jane Milhans has.
The lifestyle based on pretending that you're someone else.
Across the country.
It was offensive.
We believe that the Secretary has made a grave, a colossal grave.
Just, I was in shock.
375 million dollar hole.
Bigotry.
Profane.
Patriot.
Secret.
Evil.
Done deal.
Torching police cars.
Sexually explicit.
Irrational.
Slipped through the crack.
Condemn a culture.
Bite, bite, bite, bite.
Let it slip.
Bang, bang, bang, banger.
Unthinkable.
How corrosive that can be.
U.S. intelligence.
Angrily denounced authorities.
Lends fact and fiction.
Gus Van Sant's last days.
It appears there's a discrepancy.
ICMS.
And this war in LA is a beloved lives.
Want your friends?
―
Die for oil, sucker
Sucker
You too can get your face shot off
So arms race tycoons won't have to get a real job
The cold war's over, it was all a mirage
We could use that money, we got problems to solve
But we're not allowed a chance at the peace dividend
Cause our psycho president's got his head in the sand
What kind of a Bush League double cross is this?
Cheap oil? The price has already gone up
This still could wind up making Hiroshima look like a picnic
And keep in mind, Bush is a born-again Christian
Does he believe in Armageddon and the last generation?
Die for oil, sucker
Sucker
Secretary of State Jennifer Wilbanks shot and wounded President Bush
He was elated
Bush threatens everyone
If there's any uncertainty in any form, police changed the story
Also, China, Korea fled due to nerves
Criminals convicted of the most heinous crimes
Spent days searching for food or water
It is turned up across the country
Backed up
He's good, he's alive, he's real, he answers
Jogging three days down a road.
Uh, baby, baby, baby, baby, back, back, back, back.
Praise the baby.
Leverage.
Each day I get up to take a breath, brush cobwebs from my spirit.
I try to recall fractured dreams that drift away somehow.
Seems half the time I yearn for death, the other half I fear.
I can't make up my mind.
Seems I've got to spell live for now.
Time is running out for the planet Earth.
Music.
Everything around me became suddenly.
unreal as if in a dream
do you
off I like, I'm not going in there.
Private Mandamus,
we've been wanting to speak to you now
because of your
record. It's a very
important
misread piece of
disinformation. Private
Mandamus, it seems you've been
working for the Skel Patrol
for the last three months and haven't
found one bloody drunk.
You've just been writing these papers
and handing them out.
But we can't allow
this. We can
however prohibit it, you see.
How do we work?
Get your hands out of there.
I was breathing
so softly. I could
hardly rest my own temperature.
I was convinced something
had gone very, very wrong
with my central nervous system.
For instance, this
pineal gland here.
All I have to do is push the right
buttons. And you see, I can
expand. I can become bigger
or smaller. Of course, it's not
like before. I still
have limitations. The
Big Bang is over, so to speak.
But I'll be back again someday.
You know, they said God's, the mind
of God was damaged in
the Big Bang. And that's what
the new age is all about, man.
God's got brain damage. That means
you're God. You can do your
own thing. It's the age
of Aquarius, man.
You're screwed up, but you're God, man.
It's so cool. You can be
like an angst character, like
Promethean James Dean of the
old era type. It's like there's no
good or no evil. There's just
you, man. And it's like
you just do your own
thing.
It's the new age.
What you feel, that's what's real, man.
The Tao balances
angst and joy, man.
Well, it's not real joy.
It's closer to slack, actually.
It's kind of a
form of loose joy, which hardly
ever assembles.
Well, let's say it's hard to achieve.
Hey, man.
Guzzle.
Do something about him.
Friend, I can tell by the fact that you
tuned in. There are some things I don't
need to tell you.
I'm not even going to bother.
What is wrong with that guy?
He's okay, man. He's been
hanging around with private mandamacy.
He's been telling all that
easy stuff, you know?
He's going to be all right.
Look, look. See, his flesh tone is
well, it's not really a flesh tone. It's more of like a
he looks like the bark of a tree
or maybe, hey, it's an onion skin.
Yeah, man. He's a vegetable.
The onion skin.
He's the metaphor man.
Like the conspiracy itself.
You peel away the onion skin,
yet there's another skin underneath.
And you peel away that skin, and there's
another skin. It's skin upon skin.
That doesn't work when they start peeling.
You peel off a lonesome cowboy Dave here now,
does it? You peel off one layer of skin
and he starts screaming. That's because
there's only one layer to a subgenius.
There's no metaphors here, man. It ain't like nothing
but what it is.
It's because we're the pure, the honest
primates.
The mandrills
of the world, don't you see?
Our purple behinds glow with
pride and slackdomness
because we've got Bob in them.
There's also the toxic material.
We can also look at that aspect of it, too, but sure,
sure, yeah, we're glowing. You need to get
a glow on every day before you ride the bus.
Some of us don't actually ride it.
We just kind of take it around
with us. Friends, you're either on the bus
or you're off the bus. You're either
on the saucers or you're off
of those saucers, my friend.
Reverend Ken Kesey,
the great subgenius, a dues-paying
subgenius minister, by the way,
said that. I remember when Neal Cassidy
was achieving his
penultimate years,
and I talked like this,
Colorado, he still had a nasal
twang that
deviated septum, perhaps, but we're
all deviated, you know.
This is where I should cut to
a bunch of Neal Cassidy.
But you're going to have to lead some meager,
eccentric, sincere, maniacal
like Alexander.
I'm going to make you discover that's pretty fair.
Spencer, that's pretty fair for
Tom Edison. Well, here we want someone
who's like Tony Perkins.
That's it. Somebody who is
who could be
either way, but in this case, it's a
definite neurotic thing already.
I mean, like, he's obsessed
with racing, as say, Tony Perkins
as a sick cat,
not being approved of at all,
as the son, you see, would be. So he'd have
a mania for auto racing, even
though, like say, Tony Perkins wouldn't be good
for football or wrestling or anything.
Why, this fellow can't race
with a dam. He's the poorest of the
bunch. Yet it runs in the family. It's in his
blood, you understand. Here we got this
rural French garage-owning
family.
The uncle, brother, couple of the brothers,
father himself, race.
Neil Cassidy, Neil Cassidy,
but I bet I could...
Singing lonesome songs to the moon,
arguing with himself...
You know you can't force Cassidy, okay?
Kids, we're talking about ancient, dead
subgeniuses of the past, and that's what you'll
be if you don't make sure that we have your
correct address on our
mailing list. And this is
how we salute them. For instance,
we light two flowers for
Jack Kerouac. For Neil
Cassidy, we blow up five flowers.
And for the others, we
take the tiny little regimental
everyday conspiracy bus
and blow the hemp into bluey.
But for Bill Hicks, we eat a whole
can of black beans and lay around
pyroflatulation all night long.
There's no need for it.
It's an experience.
It's hardly an experience.
It isn't a hallucination, my friend.
It isn't pollution.
It isn't? Uh-oh.
It isn't your eyes that are seeing the wrong things.
It's your face
that's in the wrong place.
You have visited yourself
upon an ugly, angry
world. A world
of misconception and deceit.
Here, sit down
on the toilet of love.
Place your fanny,
your booty firmly
on the place where...
Why can't I just...
Forget about it. It's because we're not in the
world of love, man. We're in the world
of the hate.
Hate.
The hate.
The system changes.
Every system is an integral
window for the...
It's a bad idea, man.
I mean, like, if I had my chance,
or my choice, or my...
to have my own church, or some...
You know, to make
a spiritual movement, you know,
and reap souls,
and rape sloughs,
and, you know, gather unto myself
the many from amongst the fumes,
and so forth, you know, like, if I could do that,
you know, like, why would I become a,
you know, a slack genius,
or any of those others? Because, like, think of...
I mean, most of these people are, like,
not... They're like monopens.
Oh, yeah, I can do that. I can do that.
What, you know, like, all deformed
and everything, you know, some of the, like,
the big macrocephalic dudes, man.
The guys with the big, high foreheads,
you know, the brain thing, they've got the, you know,
like, the hardening of the skull and stuff.
These are, like, the leaders of this church, you know.
The overman.
Well, and some are the underman.
Actually, oh, here, here, speaking of which,
I'll have you know,
some of us are just regular, ordinary people.
Space was named the B.M.T.
Yes, I, Dr. Howell,
am the mighty,
most of the submen, the undermen,
the greatest in the lowerarchy.
Of course, we're inferior to normal people,
we undermen, but nonetheless,
of this enormous army of gimps and wimps,
I, Dr. Howell, approach common humanity the most.
It's enormous.
Though subhuman and a subgenius,
I am almost a human.
At least we undermen understand what we undertake.
What we take down under the surface
of what we understand, down, pulled down
with the undertow into the underpinnings
of the unconscious mind.
In this sub-stratum, we, the undermen,
root and furrow our...
burrows tunneling past roots
in the warm earth smell of a bean burrow.
And so, muchachos,
no matter how macho you are,
you're still just a little chaco in the gazpacho.
Let me out of here, I'm boiling!
Play the game, Mark.
You play the game, I'm getting out of here.
Keep that Swedish Godzilla away from me.
Yeah, keep that Swedish Godzilla,
that sweet Godzilla away from me.
No, I can't.
Johan?
Here is your photon of all the...
Godzilla?
Yeah, I've been Godzilla.
I'm in good connection with Connecticut.
I am Godzilla.
Godzilla, what I learned in the country little town.
Stockholm's not big enough for me.
I have to take a ride by the Japanese sea
and smash Tokyo down.
That was fun.
Ha-hoo!
The Swedish Godzilla song by Lenten Cowboy Dave.
Swedish Godzilla.
No, the geography Godzilla song.
It's the Swedish Godzilla.
What's the Godzilla song now?
It's the...
Geography Godzilla song, apparently.
These are all the places that Godzilla will be destroying
during the coming time,
followed shortly by the U.S. Army behind him.
It's sort of a mop-up in the...
Stockholm, Tokyo, Osaka, Beijing,
Seoul, Haifu, Barzu.
And here they come.
Connie's got connections in Connecticut.
Yes, she really has connections in Connecticut.
There goes Danbury.
She was born out in Wyoming as a girl.
She started roaming...
Oh, there goes Vest.
...in Connecticut.
Pfft.
One day she took a trip way down to Florida.
Oh, they're moving on to New York State.
And she called the real station down in Florida.
Pfft.
There goes Albany.
She became a baby cutie and was such a little cutie
and she soon had all the flowers there adoring her.
Then Connie secured the leading role
in a wonderful Broadway attraction.
But she wouldn't stay on a great white way.
The pace of the action...
You know, I sometimes think
what a great and wonderful thing it would be
if our Lord Jesus
would dress up in one of those Godzilla suits
around Christmas time
and come visit your neighborhood
and perhaps my neighborhood.
Just hang around.
Maybe sing a song with a band.
Or wear one of those funny 1938 haircuts.
I think I'd love that more than anything
except life itself.
Except for this is a freaking life.
Hell no.
This is not life.
This is a pee hole we've crawled into
and can't get out of.
I don't care.
As long as I can see Jesus dressed like Godzilla.
Oh, some funny Sunday.
I don't know.
Behind the pews or making the pew.
Ha, ha, ha.
And that's why people join
the Church of the Subgenius, friends,
because we have holidays like X-Day
where you can find Jesus
dressed up like a Godzilla.
Yes, it's true.
Actually, they will have an ugly parade this year
at, uh...
And who knows how Jesus will dress
this particular time.
He could be wearing anything
or maybe nothing at all.
I mean, you know how Jesus is.
If only his mom would dress that way.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm supposed to be happy.
She's a mammy.
I'm the pappy.
Now Connecticut's my old hometown.
Yeah.
Oh, Connie.
Connie.
I know you're interested in these squids.
These prairie squids.
But as you can see,
we only have four of them left.
And you have asked clearly here in your invoice
you said you would send me six.
And this is a past-future kind of thing.
So, you know, if you don't really...
You...
Hey, I just realized
there's some credits.
that need to be given here
that we just completely blew off.
The PR news, of course,
is from Mr. Fernand and Andy Leher.
Leher.
Oh, the lady.
And, uh...
And Reverend Norrell Preff
of HeavyConfetti.com
did a bunch of that
Satan in the White House
and conflicting news reports
and various mixes and chop-ups.
The ordinary...
And we heard Dr. Howell,
claiming to be an...
uh...
underman.
And, uh...
this is, uh...
uh...
Uncle Onan Canabite.
Unclean One Canabite
in the background.
With the, uh...
Onane ain't ain't song.
He owes no mane.
Listen to that.
Onane.
O-O-Onane.
And friends,
Phineas Narco
of NationalCynical.com
did a whole bunch of the, uh,
mix-ups there.
There was a...
the For What It's Worth.
Um...
Uh...
There's something going on
and there's something happening here
at business there.
Dr. Phineas Narco.
So you see,
somewhere out there in the world,
there are some geniuses
who care!
Although they don't actually do anything.
They really care!
May I just say right now
for this August, buddy?
Hey!
That I'm wearing a pink ladies' merkin
underneath these silky panties.
Ah.
I'm a pubic merkin
because for the love of Bob...
Whatever.
For want of something else to call him.
Uh, Bert.
I prefer to call him less
than I have in the past.
That's for sure.
I'm listening to this blip on.
May I say right now
that, uh,
that I'm having a dysfunction
in my colon area.
That, uh, perhaps, uh...
Too much information.
My entire intestine may leap out
like one of those alien things
or whatever it was.
Thanks.
I'll begin an argument
with someone like that.
Too much information.
But I just say a bunch of
unentertaining, boring crap
that's going to irritate you.
Would you like a Kleenex?
Bob?
That grinning man with the pipe.
The halo fellow
that the best players
claim does not even exist.
People who deny the reality of Bob,
who is lower than that?
It's just like those wretches
who have claimed that Tarzan,
Sherlock Holmes, and Robin Hood
are fictitious characters.
For surely our Bob is in their company.
A heroic, happy madman
who won't quit fighting
until all humanity
achieves select,
or at least that portion of humanity
which is tired unto Bob.
That, I chance, is all.
I was so glad when that pleasure saucer landed,
but the pilot was drunk or something,
and I made out pretty good
balancing on one knee and all,
but it was kind of awkward to hump
while I had to play the cut off my foot
with a pleasure saucer blues,
but it was real nice of Bob
to grow me a new foot,
but it's a dinosaur thing
and has claws,
so now I can't wear a shoe on that foot
and people sure stare a lot
and I tend to walk in circles like this.
Ka-dunk, ka-dunk, ka-dunk.
Crazy damn old Bob,
I sure love him,
but well, he's nuts.
Uh, help-o-putey, dear friends.
Uh, huh.
And this is Atomic Jefferson.
Dead possum in the road
Shaggy hair
Your jaw is slack
Your eyes are shut
I believe
Your heart has failed
Dead possum in the road
They play dead possum in the road
Sometimes
Don't you try to pick him up
He may bite
You know, when I was just a boy
My daddy was on his way home from work one evening
And he saw a dead possum in the road
He stopped to get a closer look
And he saw that it was a mama possum
She had some babies in her pouch
And a couple of them was still alive
So he brought them home
To my brother and me
And we give them some water
And some bread to eat
When they was big enough to go
We set them free
Cause you know
The wild's the only place a creature like the possum ought to be
I'll break them off something raw
Dead possum in the road
My heart goes out to you
So whatever you may do
Wherever you may go
Stare closely at me
We're on the road
Amazing!
Atomic Jefferson, dear friends.
You know, these guys sound like an early Leonard Skinner or something.
They're from Birmingham, Alabama.
They've got that southern sound.
They smell like rich and gravy, you know?
They're for real.
Like God's people.
I doubt if they're for real, Stan.
No offense, you Yankees.
Just don't speak God's language.
We don't have the physical mechanics.
Nor play God's guitar.
We don't have the demonic tongue, you southerners do.
Nor God's harmonica.
You can't eat God's beans.
But we play Satan's fiddles.
Like Charlie, which is fat.
Oh, yeah.
You got that satanic fiddle playing down.
Oh, I got Charlie.
Don't hang on.
Okay.
Holy.
This is a special meeting.
And I'd just like to remind everybody seated here that they're not supposed to be in those
seats.
There's something seriously wrong with your pants and your stuffing.
The places we've had marked are inferior to the original places.
And they're translated into stellar material.
Some of you will be evaporated, then the rest of you will become like mother's milk.
I tried.
They'll become like soft, screwy, smelly, like the cream that runs down the side of Bob's pipe.
Like the unconscious underman and the macho muchachos.
Can you feel Bob swelling up in you down there?
Oh, yeah.
Just a repetitious simian with nothing on your mind except for that blank check.
Check.
Did you say something about blank checks?
Yeah.
We're looking for blank checks and lads.
We're looking for blanker checks.
Who can be filled in by Mr. Fill-in-the-blank-himself, J.R. Bob-the-Dobbs.
I remember Phil Dirt and the Dozers, my favorite band.
They were a great band.
But not as great as Phil-in-the-blank.
Phil was cool.
And I remember Jethro Tull of Jethro Tull.
He was a cool fella, too.
He was in the...
How did you meet him?
How'd you come upon him?
He used to be in commercial radio.
And, of course, that was before the accident.
It wasn't an accident.
That's another thing.
It's real.
Bankruptcy.
It was on purpose, wasn't it?
Iron lung and the...
Well, in your case, it looks more like a copper mask.
Yeah, we're dealing with some inferior metals here.
The iron butt.
Oh, that's...
And the iron suit.
I am your father.
And the iron fist of...
What is the iron fist?
The iron fist of the...
It's like the iron fish.
Tish.
Yes.
Revenge of the...
Shit.
That is the theme of our show.
Tish means dish in German, don't it?
How they take something great and turn it into utter crap.
Oh, pish cash.
Like this show.
Like this whole radio station once we got here.
Tommy, can you feel me?
Can you hear me, though?
Can you feel me?
Can you see me?
Hello, daughter.
It's a lot of malarkey.
Can you see me?
Tommy, can you feel me?
Can you smell me yet?
You're rising up.
I wasted my pants again.
Are you wasted yet?
Can you feel me, Tommy?
You're just another scale in the road.
I hear you.
Can you feel the seed rising up?
Bob's coming, friends.
And you can get more of that man, Bob.
If you just write for free information from the Church of the Subgenius,
that's right, the information's free.
You know, I love saying this, because nobody just about ever does this,
but you can.
But you sound so cool when you do it.
Actually drop you a card to Subgenius Foundation.
No, not Dallas, Texas no more.
No, not Austin, Texas.
Nope.
They don't need slack in Texas anymore.
No, they're not too good for them.
DNA level C.
Here at DNA level C, friends, that's post office box.
Got that pencil ready?
Box 18141.
117 Cleveland Heights, Ohio.
44118.
And that's an odd dress you won't want to miss.
It's an odd dress, all right, that she's wearing down there at subgenius.com.
But look, once again, the pubic goatee's growing out of the top of her skull.
Oh, that's mighty, mighty interesting.
I can't breathe.
I...
It's okay.
It's going to be all right.
I'm telling you.
I keep trying to tell you.
It's going to be all right.
You think it's really going to be all right?
Yeah, yeah, man.
Princess, we was always saying that.
I didn't like Red Mist.
I didn't like Search and Destroy.
I didn't like any of the other war rides at this freaking carnival, man.
I know, but I have it on good authority that it's going to be all right, okay?
I don't like authority figures either.
I like figurines, you know, little tiny gnome things you put in the back of your head.
It's okay.
The disfigurines you have to worry about, dude.
I know.
Yeah.
Hey, look.
They're all like us.
They're all disfigurines.
Some of them have too much rouge on the left side of their head.
With Tuesday's election, Joseph Rat, Joseph Rat, choked the new pope.
Rat, rat, rat, rat, Joseph Rat, Joseph Rat, choking pregnant teens.
Deep, deep, deep, deep, deep, deep, deep, deep, deep, deep, deep, deep, deep, deep.
Joseph Rat, Joseph Rat, Joseph Rat, Joseph Rat, choked the new pope.
Choked the new pope.
Have you dug his seat?
Yes, ma'am.
You ready now?
Or somewhere in outer space?
Outer space.
God has prepared a place for those who trust him and obey.
That's X-Day, friends.
God's prepared it for you.
We know.
Yes.
We're not especially prepared things just for you.
Well, who did he do?
One negative guy.
I'm going to pound him.
What a jerk.
God, I hate these people.
You have no idea.
It's unbelievable to me.
The pinks.
The boy.
Mediocritans.
The humans.
The normals.
Eli, Eli, Lama, subhas the name.
Shh.
Hi.
Sullen, misguided, drunks and criminals.
Can't something be done?
He's given a bath and a pair of clean pajamas.
Squalid homes.
Dirt.
Futures.
Here in the rear of dead.
Best psychological test.
But I don't want to do that.
Gargoyles coming down.
As the months pass, Benton sees Johnny frequently.
Sometimes at the community swimming pool.
It was a never to be forgotten experience for the boy.
This is...
Fun.
Fascinating.
See, that was dumb, wasn't it?
It certainly was.
Arrgh.
Today my mother killed me.
Who are you?
Who do you think I am?
I'm asking the questions here.
Who are you?
I am anger.
And I am lies.
Who are you?
Joseph R. McCarthy.
Face me.
Guilt.
You guys don't play fair, do you?
Don't have to.
You don't have to, do you?
Hmm.
CBS Radio Network.
I was unfairly...
Guilt.
And irresponsibly smearing innocent people
from behind the cloak of congressional immunity.
Guilt.
I gave no evidence.
A typical McCarthy mixture
of quarter truth...
Guilt.
Half truths and untruths.
Almost every one of McCarthy's charges...
Guilt.
Are a wormed over rehash
of charges...
is made before half-truths and untruths McCarthy is lying the American people
expect McCarthy is lying well McCarthy was a scandal monger and a hate monger
57 people died as a result of the Dukes and Stooges who have been planning
disaster for America maybe they just never grew up boys will be boys it's
awesome they pulled it off people don't get the ash cloud alone reached 80,000
feet another blast isn't out of the question it came out and it was amazing
let's move forward dumb SUV making it harder to kill him for that who's on
first dick dumb a flash flood gee Robert yes but you've got to be brilliant to
pull this off under pressure yeah just just do it and and he would do it and he
would do it fast I think we do need to put on the table that we have mutual
assured destruction policies a bunch of collage material there by
no one
or El pref at heavy confetti that can