It's chaotic.
Yowl Slack.
And this is a rerun of Hour of Slack number 872
from the year of 2000.
Three.
I wonder if this works.
All right.
Just tell me.
Just tell me whenever I'm on.
There.
Is that better?
All right.
I see.
I see the second hand.
Following, following, following.
All right.
Boom.
We're on.
Good hello.
This is Bud Good.
And I must inform you that Over the Edge will not be heard tonight.
Over the Edge has donated its time so that we can cover
the subgenius executive retreat direct from Sulphur Palms.
And that's where I am now.
Right near the gate.
To Sulphur Palms.
I see all the subgenius out there waiting to get in.
And my co-host tonight will be puzzling evidence.
Founder and co-operator of the subgenius church.
Hello.
Not the founder.
Is the founder here tonight?
I'm the only one who claims that I was not the founder.
Is Mr. Stang here tonight?
Reverend Ivan Stang is here tonight.
And so is Philodromon the Overman.
Good.
Bishop Joey of the Church of St. Stephen.
All the executives are present it seems.
And of course, the president of the church, Mr. Stang, is here tonight.
The theme for this year is the next hundred years.
What will the next hundred years hold for the church?
That's just what I was going to ask you, puzzling.
We have to find out from the people that are attending the conference tonight.
The super secret conference.
This one night retreat will be devoted entirely to the next hundred years.
The future.
There'll be food, music, panel discussion.
The title of which will be the next hundred years.
Don't miss our awards dinner.
The next hundred years awards.
Yeah.
This little mimicry.
This little draft smudge.
I can't tell what's coming up next.
Whoa.
Oh, I see the guard there is opening the gate now.
Let's bring, let them in.
Here they come.
It looks like Ivan Stang.
And there's Bishop Joey.
Bishop Joey, our first executive.
I can't find my, I have my ticket reservation, but I don't think I have my,
the code number, but can I get my badge anyway?
Is it okay?
Yeah, here, you're laminated.
Let's get it backstage.
Thanks.
Okay.
Do you have to buy the lanyard too?
Are you paying for the lanyard?
It's a highly technical evening here where we have all of these.
Oh, there we are.
I see.
I couldn't see where I was.
My space helmet was all fogged up.
I wonder if I have permission to hand out some flyers for my church.
It's going to be perhaps a little bit of a trying evening, folks.
We have to go through the entire process of imbibing the church, as you will.
We take it and drink the whole church.
We go through the business aspect.
I see Ivan Stang over there on the other side of the field, and Lies.
I thought they all were trying to get in here.
Where are all the subgenius?
There's a new bass player for the band.
The schedules weren't printed out out there at the table in the lobby.
Philo is wandering around confused about where to go.
We don't have some of their mics up.
We have remote ambience mics located all over Sulphur Palm.
There's Papa Joe Mama over there.
There's Inez.
Which we can tune into and see what's going on wherever they happen to be.
I think Ivan Stang doesn't like the little,
the little umbrella.
The umbrella's in his drink.
Could you tell me where the buffet is?
I'd like to start out with a buffet.
It's behind, it's behind that big tent right there.
Thank you.
Is the buffet here?
What kind of a chimpanzee zoo is this?
I can't believe this.
Do I have to be running?
It's a business meeting.
Look how it's turning.
Oh, there's Mr. Stang.
Yeah, they're hidden away over there.
What do you expect?
Get behind the front and figure out which little space helmet has a
I'm scared.
vibrator on it.
Oh, look.
There's a little queen of UFOs.
I like that.
Buzzing around the outside of the ship.
I'd like to ask Mr. Stang a question.
As the founder of the subgenius church.
What?
Which network are you with?
No, he's not the founder.
I'm with UMN.
Oh, yeah, okay.
What?
This is Bud Good.
I'm with UMN, Puzzling Evidence.
Oh, Bud Good, right.
Yes.
Bud.
So as the founder of the subgenius church.
That's, that's very funny.
After all these years.
Praise Bob.
Trial and tribulation, murder, divorce.
I don't know what's been going on.
But, but how do you feel?
What do you, but that is rather a personal question.
How do I, if I use my fingers, my, my, if I reach out with my senses, I, I, in, I let
the, the, the sensory world wash over me.
That is how I feel.
In other words.
As a holy man.
In all these years, you've learned nothing.
I put my fingers out.
I touched.
Nothing is what we strive for, Bud.
I understand.
That was a compliment.
But yes, we're, oh, thank you.
Thank you.
I too have learned nothing.
Whatever.
If I said, yeah.
Did I say that?
Then pick up on it.
Now we're going to move right to the organized part of the show right now.
Uh, the, all these subgenius executives are moving into the lodge where they will sit
around a, a long oblong square oval tables place.
It has a big vacuum.
With a big hole in the middle.
And they will have the, the next hundred years panel discussion, the subgenius church, the
next hundred years.
Why?
Whence Dobbs and why?
Whence Dobbs?
That's his brother.
Wencesla Dobbs, Polish Dobbs.
Good King.
Whence the high pop?
Whence it doesn't work at all.
No, we've already got an eight, four, eight, four, four, three, five.
It might be Michael Pepe who was invited to come with us.
Traipsing through this field at, uh, at midnight here.
We're out looking at the moon.
Do between our toes waiting for the business.
Report.
How many, uh, subgenius executives do we have here tonight?
Is it a full forum?
It really is amazing.
Onan is here.
Papa Joe mama is here.
Some of these people might not appear on Mike though.
Dr. Howell is here.
But his microphone is turned all the way down as always.
He is not here.
Dr. Howell is not here.
He's not?
No, he's not.
Wait a minute.
If, if that, what then are we now?
You're not Dr. Howell.
Are we now in the panel discussion?
Who's that guy?
He always votes against.
Against the majority.
So we, uh, we tricked him out of town for this weekend.
So if it does come to a vote tonight, it should be unanimous.
Okay.
Here's the Howell mask.
Oh, I thought that was.
Oh, little tiny.
Well, I wish you radio listeners could see this.
Uh, how hilarious.
Reproduction death mask of Dr. Howell.
Too bad.
We don't have any tapes of him to go with that mask.
Oh, he'll appear later in the show.
I'm sure there are hours and oodles and hours of show tonight, folks.
Here puzzling.
Look, I have my own mic.
So actually you can use this one and somebody else can use that one.
I'm a little worried about that.
I have my special U.M.N.
remote mic tonight as we wander around the grounds here.
As far as wants to mix the show.
Sulfur palm.
And, uh, uh, they are, I see.
The Christmas trees are lighting up like a phone.
Oh, I don't see anything.
Which one is that guy?
Are they going to turn on the lights or what?
Is that that guy?
Hello?
So, uh, typical college radio, uh-huh.
I see what's happening.
Can I be the first caller?
Yes, you can.
Go ahead.
Well, I'd like to talk to Gary Gabrogfan.
I heard he's going to be on the radio this morning.
Yes, he is.
We're trying to keep his mic down.
Is he cool?
Well, I'm going to sleep.
This show is terrible.
What time does the band start?
No, he's here.
Go ahead.
Speak to him.
Yeah, the drums aren't even out of the box yet.
Yeah.
The drums aren't even out of the box yet.
Not you, caller.
But you know who we have?
Ivan Stang.
Oh, yes.
The queen of UFOs lies.
Hang on, hang on.
I know, Truman.
Okay, I'm sorry.
Hello?
Oh, yes.
Good hello.
Um, I just have one question.
Um, I want to send you some vinyl that I'm going to be getting, you know, records.
Oh, is this a personal message?
Oh, geez, we have to stop the show.
We can't really deal with personal messages on the air.
This is full-time entertainment here.
All right, I'm sorry.
Bye-bye.
Yeah, no, that's okay.
What were you going to send me?
Oh, um, some vinyl, you know, because my grandfather had some, like, records from World War II.
Is there any sound on this vinyl?
Oh, yes.
Oh, good.
Uh, okay, my question was, should I send it to your, uh, the address on your website?
Uh, no.
Well, what's that one?
I forget.
I don't know.
Um, well, I'll just email somebody, I guess, and I'll get the information.
Just had that prediction about burning it.
Yeah, email me through the website.
I'll tell you where to send it.
Okay.
Have a good day.
Thank you.
I appreciate all the contributions.
Yes, that was a distraction.
I think it's a disturbing prediction that Dobbs made about Burning Man disappearing by the year 2037.
The church just takes everything and folds it inside themselves.
It's a shimmers down this path.
Now, caller, you're listening and talking to the amazing
lowerarchy of the subgenius church, started over two decades ago in the spooky town of Dallas.
Executive lowerarchy.
Not to be confused with the real hierarchy, which started in 1953.
Right.
It is confusing.
It's a church.
It's a religion.
But that was just Dobbs and Allen.
It's just Alfred Hitchcock and Dennis Hopper and a few other select individuals.
Dennis Hopper was the team.
I feel like I'm descending down the rabbit hole of business.
We're heading up to some point.
We really need the...
This is just like a James Bond set.
Where's the drummer?
It is on the set spot.
Oh, the drummer's in for the spider.
Well, I can see we're going to have some problems getting to the panel.
People just don't want to be that organized here.
Okay, great.
So it's going to be so much fun.
Oh yeah, that's really good.
Plus, David Meyer is supposed to be calling in today.
Oh, great.
Because I was really hoping other Doctores would happen like...
Byron Werner's here.
I like the way you made that up.
Doctores.
Who are these guys talking about?
I vaguely remember these names from some time in the...
David Meyer, he's a skier.
Who is it?
Cowboy Dave is here.
But he's partying upstairs.
Famous long ago.
Dinosaurs of slack.
Wow.
A digital insert here.
Back in the day...
That is day one.
The truth.
Was that the Permian or the Devonian or the carbonation?
Carbon cycrane.
Or the carbon fiber age.
The carbonated peanut butter got all over the microphone and was not usable for the rest of the show.
Yes, it...
Neither was Hal, so...
And it tickled my nose.
That's your nose?
What?
Uh oh.
Where's the prop workshop, please?
Somebody gave her coffee.
Hey, I was wondering about that.
Where is the frock wor...
The frock...
The frock workshop.
Uh, now I feel like the...
What was it we were doing was the...
The frock intensive.
We have to start again.
Let's begin the show now.
The subgenius radio show.
Get everybody lined up first.
Everybody has to be lined up.
Ken?
Is this those shots again?
That's one of those inspections.
Line them up and shot.
When does the horrible theme music begin?
When do we get to go to Malaysia?
All right, who's hosting this panel?
I guess you should be, but...
I think Mr. Stank should host this.
The panel of the next hundred years.
Well, he's certainly the primary easement.
As we gather together to commence this august assemb...
Wait, what?
Now that's...
Who's here?
Is he drunk?
That sounds too definite.
It's not August.
I mean, actually, it's a big question.
The next hundred years.
It is a huge question.
And we should...
And we really need Philo Drummond.
He can barely stand up.
He's who we need because he's the business manager,
the closest to giving everybody the business
of all the doctors here.
Actually, Jesus replaced Philo.
Oh, yeah.
No, no.
But I mean, here tonight.
Because Jesus is not here, unfortunately.
He's not with us.
He's busy during the season.
Right, yeah.
This is his...
The season of turnover.
Yep.
And he couldn't be with us, which would be great.
But so the closest we have to an old-fashioned business man is...
Philo Drummond.
Because Philo Drummond works for the conspiracy.
Always has.
Always will.
Yep.
Well, it's a good deal.
Jesus or...
Jilo.
You don't say Jilo.
I've got a Philo like no Philo you've ever seen.
Jilo.
Jilo the Torturer.
He's the most tortured businessman.
He's gonna replace Bob.
Yeah, everybody's tired of Bob.
We got this new Jilo there.
The flash is gonna bounce off that little glass window.
We're gonna make a million bucks off Jilo.
Flashing me.
He smokes a cigarette instead of a pipe.
Okay, set up with a banjo.
Which guy?
The Eeyore of the church?
I think everything is...
Jilo Dummond.
What about all these...
Jilo was held in...
Great honor by the tribe.
I don't know why...
The M. Jilo Dummond.
See, we just invented another church.
Bud Good's just given up.
They never say...
Well, that's that...
I see someone over at the cappuccino stand.
Everybody here knows how to say...
Praise Jilo.
Hee!
Heee!
Well, you know, also it's regional.
There is the California...
Hee!
And what was the Texas one?
Well, the original Dramundian.
Hee!
Which became messy very quickly.
Well, that's why it was truncated.
Way in the background.
You gotta get by a mic there.
Filo drumming.
Politically correct.
Mic that, too.
Over by the stage.
Oh, my God.
Mike that Dr. Drummond.
Yes, make that whole other room.
How about this mic? Does it work?
But as we've asked for 20 years,
is this church to devolve into nothing but inside joke squeals and funny sounds?
I second that.
And for 20 years it has done exactly that.
Praise Bob!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Praise Jilo!
Oh, yeah, that's right, Jilo!
Let's go back to the old church.
Oh, check, check, check.
Yeah, the old church.
Back in time.
Watch those calendar pages all the way.
Laurie's birthday party. That's an amazing one.
Am I on?
That was a pretty good one.
That was...
So we'll talk about that later, but right now, folks...
Dr. Richard's not going to die.
The man can get back to his dream.
Dr. Esselstyn.
Jesus, Bob.
Are you dumping it?
All right, boys.
The proceeds from the last Janer tape amounted to $100 million.
About $15769.
And of course, with the...
Janer, and there was Sterno.
At 12% each, that means you all get here.
$678.
Nine.
That's it.
Buck naked.
You're not allowed to say buck naked in the church no more.
There are all these Texan churches, but we'll just turn off that sound effect.
If you go right to church...
Trial number 18.
We can say buck naked.
You've been chosen from the Christmas tree of callers, and you now can address the show
doctors.
Please ask your question.
848-442-3.
What's that?
A dude.
Is there other...
What's one of those Zen questions, apparently?
Five hours of...
If you consider yourself a musician...
No, no, no.
I didn't say do your show on our show.
He does that on our show, too.
Oh.
Oh, he does.
He does that on all the shows.
Oh, I have a question.
I got an answer.
Yes, I was wondering, is it all right if I knock my friend out with a shovel and bury
him in the backyard like they did in that one Beavis and Butt-Hitch?
You said one Beavis and Butt-Hitch?
Good.
Hello.
If you mark the grave clearly.
Okay.
Only if you videotape it and send it to America's Funniest Home Videos.
Because if you don't tape it, it didn't happen.
Right, exactly.
And if it...
Not only that, nowadays, why everybody tapes everything, if it doesn't appear somehow on
TV, it didn't happen.
Well, I can always play it on the underground TV.
So they're...
Well, that's sort of how it is.
Our funniest home internment.
But really, you should be asking the question of the doctor.
You have an amazing opportunity here to go back to the beginning.
I would like to know what's going to happen in the next hundred years.
If there's still going to be LSD available.
Well, there hasn't been any available.
Of course.
So if it's ever going to be available again in the next hundred years, I'd like to know
what's going to happen in the Middle East.
I'd like to know if religion...
Two months.
I'd like to wait two months.
And then the new little...
Well, why don't you just take that acid trip there and just relax there, buddy.
And then a hundred years from now, there'll be this...
A skull with just these two metal teeth.
...tucking around.
Talking about the Middle East.
You talk about Ohio, Pennsylvania, Illinois.
You know, there's nothing to trip about, man.
You know, the world ends.
The world ends.
You know?
What about that LSD I sold you last night on Telegraph Avenue?
What about all that LSD we sent to the Middle East last year?
Ah, okay.
What about all the LSD we just took just an hour ago?
Oh, that LSD!
That LSD!
I was wondering.
That explains a lot.
That explains a hell of a lot.
It does, though, huh?
What?
Hello?
I should have given up that acid again.
Are we going to get hit by a meteor?
We'll talk to my friend LSD, Tripp.
Then he'll hook you up for good.
You should know the one in half-acid shows.
You're just going to drown in your own natural stupidity.
Don't worry about it.
I don't know.
Good God.
Okay.
You're rocking out already.
We'd like a little play for you out there in Radioland.
Is there something that kind of goes in something like this?
That's a little something, all right.
Yeah, it's a nice song, though.
You know, really, the past, the present, and the future is just one big cycle.
I believe.
I know what you mean.
All right.
Like, I'll give you something you did.
Go to the end, but you're doing it again.
Are you guys really entertaining, or is that just the drugs talking?
Does anybody have any idea how loud my new guitar is?
Yeah, you want to show us?
You won't even believe how loud it is.
I thought this was the business meeting, and you guys are still tuning up your so-called band.
Well, this is actually the next so-called band.
It is.
Business meeting?
Rules of order, man.
Well, he's doing his business meeting with the description of how far down the church
has gone and how far up it's going to go.
I am not the fan of religion, but I'm sure that the religious people would like to hear
on the air.
Uh-oh.
True church.
Was that Jilo himself that just called in?
Yeah.
Church blue church.
Because you notice he didn't use a phone.
I find it to be dangerous, prejudicial, childish.
And now I think we need to realize that it's uncomfortable that it could get you killed.
But really, buddy, in 2008, the Jilo thing was over.
That's what I'm talking about.
And facing 2009, the Church of the Subgenus was again left with the burning question,
where does the church go for the next 91 years?
Well, according to the science of psyche history, the Stang Plan calls for Jilo to be retired
fairly soon, within the next five or ten minutes.
And then we have to move on to the next deity, the merchant prince, who is apparently some
kind of pop star.
Let's trade the church for a winning lottery ticket.
You said Jilo.
No, Jilo.
That's the new Bob, or the anti-Bob, or something like that.
Okay.
It was according to the...
It's based on Michael Pepe.
Have you ever noticed how Sulphur Lake sounds just like a...
Oh, Jilo.
It's like a mist game.
Yeah, only it really stinks.
Yeah.
And when are they going to change the lid?
And they built a little town.
Oh, it's a stinky mist.
RJ came from there.
Well, then why did we decide to hold this business conference here?
I thought we were supposed to.
It smells horrible.
It smells really okay.
Let's everybody get some hot butter rum martinis and just relax.
Let's doctor sit in there.
Just concentrate on the matter at hand.
Throw them into the shark pond.
Right over there.
This is great.
Look what I got.
Oh, the sea bugs.
Got five cereals to eat.
Yeah, they'll eject any of them at any time.
What?
What am I...
What were you saying, Dr. Evidence?
I said I got some fried dinosaur legs over here.
Hard as rock.
Five?
Sure.
For a dollar.
Five kinds of dinosaurs, you say?
You buy the year 2003, you'll all be eating frozen dinosaur legs.
What is the...
It looks like the climate's staying speaking in the main hall.
It looks like something's happening in here.
It's like explosions are...
You'll all be eating frozen mammoth burgers by the year...
What was that here?
We need to get the plumber up here.
Get the building guy back here.
This thing isn't working right.
It's making all kinds of noise.
Hey, so Philo, are we going to get to any business, you know?
I mean, are you going to give us a business?
Well, yeah, but we're waiting for everybody to get here.
No, you're waiting for the script to get here.
Oh, for God's sake.
Everybody's here.
We've been waiting forever for that.
I've been waiting for over 20 years for that.
Yeah, the script didn't hear you.
At least I don't have my part yet.
Everybody's here.
They're all seated.
Everybody all got their parts yet?
That's what my script says.
Okay, do we have an invocation here on the show?
Yes.
Could we open with a prayer?
What is that noise?
That's some...
Wambling.
...sacred noise of some kind.
All right.
The panel is about to begin.
Let's have genius...
Look, the place is filled.
...the next 100 years.
I can't believe all these people are here.
All these people are here to hear us.
And now the prayer.
Now I lay me down to sleep.
Amen.
Good frop, good meat, good God, let's eat.
Have at it, boys.
Okay.
All right.
Go ahead and cut open the sacrificial whatever that thing is.
The sacrificial...
The sacrificial sucker.
Let's move on into the dining room.
The...
Hey, what do you think of this thing so far?
It's really kind of...
I can't believe all those guys are here.
It's really, you know...
It is pretty amazing.
That's what I'm saying.
It's great.
4-8-4-4-2-5-2.
See all of these amazing doctors in their amazing normal state here naked on the air.
Well, I thought that was the press.
All those guys with the cameras, those are the other doctors?
Yeah.
They just...
They press hard.
The new doctors?
I don't know who any of these guys are.
I guess I've been holed up in that...
If you don't, we're in trouble.
I've been holed up in that ivory tower in Dobstown for seven years.
It's been so long.
I don't know who any of these people...
Yeah.
All living beings...
Test, test, test.
Is it butter?
Can I have a collar?
Can you pass the gravy?
Thanks.
All living beings...
Hey, does Acid Burnout Man ever call this show?
No.
He calls the Cleveland show a lot.
I can hear the doctors are...
Some of the doctors are in there skinning their cats.
May the fruit of our labor repay the...
You know what they call it?
Oh, that's what you kids call it now.
They're skinning the cats.
They're, you know, they're taking...
They're taking the...
They're taking the bones out of them now and it's a really horrible, horrible thing,
but that's the only way they can get their instruments tuned.
All living beings must eat.
Well, it's not for food.
It's not...
They don't even eat them.
They just...
According to Big Rig...
They just use the cat gut to tune their instruments with.
Breathe, breathe, breathe, breathe, breathe.
Oh, look.
Philo's giving a speech.
Cats use birds to tune their instruments with.
Oh, look.
They're trying to go record their Numbers too.
Justcles and Ar sortie says how fruit-loving animals are to watch.
That's a pleasure.
He Hunger Games is in the K ahara16.
Ok.
Well, it's about time we Aunt Rachel and Chief Dana William on the doen.
Wow.
Oh, there they are.
Oh, well, they're hungry concentrating.
So, they're like, do you want to connect him with, um...
Or they can connect him with a radio program.
It sure is.
I'm going to take the skull down there with me.
It's David Meyer, actually.
I thought this was the Church of the Subgenius.
No, no, it's not.
That's right.
How did you get in here?
Do you have your pass?
No, no, this is the Church of the Duh Genius.
Do you have a pass?
How did you get in here?
Okay, so please ask your question.
You're not wearing your pass.
You can ask any question about the subgenius and learn amazing things secretly.
Especially about the next hundred years.
Yeah.
What do you want to know about the next hundred years?
I know about slugs.
Slugs?
Yeah.
Okay, what will slugs be like in the next hundred years to the Church of the Subgenius members?
Well, just the same as they are today.
Oh, that's, okay.
That's the good thing about slugs.
They just basically never change.
But what of progress?
What of evolution?
Something you can count on.
What of forward striving?
What of slack?
Slugs thumb their noses.
Can we not learn of slack from the slugs?
And a thumb.
They would thumb their noses at the very thought of evolutionary progress.
I'll bet none of you have ever seen slugs screwing.
Yeah, but you know what?
Don't bet.
It's bad for you.
You've been using drugs.
It can lead to addiction.
Well, a long time ago.
No, and the effects are still with you now.
You must have used that rock stuff that never wears off.
I'm sorry, you're having a flashback right now.
Would you please get off the ceiling?
Slugs are moving all in a circle.
Just take a deep breath.
You'll be okay.
You know what?
The other thing is you could be spinning out of...
That's what slugs do.
Yeah, when the slugs are having...
Slugs are spinning out of the circle.
...having intercourse with each other, it's really something that is very amazing.
They have lug...
Just watch that one part in Microcosmos, you know?
Just watch that one over and over and over again.
Slugs are hermaphroditic, isn't that correct?
I mean, some of them.
At least the last one that I was with was.
...a little...
Did you chew its penis off, Dr. Drummond, in order to change its sex before you used it?
Well, I didn't actually have to chew it.
I used a surgical instrument that I keep in my back pocket just for that purpose.
Along the side of the ketchup bottle I keep back there as well.
The ketchup bottle and the slug castrator.
The ketchup bottle's for special effects, right?
The ketchup bottle, the slug castrator, and my pocket knife.
What is the antenna go out and becomes male and then goes back to traction and becomes female?
Because they do it with their antennas and...
They do it with their antennas.
They pull their antenna in and they're a female.
They push it out and they're a male.
I wish I could do that.
And when they're done, they stab each other with their lug, and they both get pregnant.
Man, now that's advanced.
That's the way it should be.
You know, they've been doing it right for thousands and thousands of years.
How about you read my research paper in slug nanotechnology?
This chicken tastes like rubber.
Who's catering?
Did you say slug nanotechnology?
I thought the quote was, this rubber tastes like chicken.
I'll admit.
Now that's what I'm talking about.
Yeah.
Well, bubbles.
Is that like the same as the bubble tech?
That's how I can have some cereal at 3 a.m. like I'm home.
Or is it, yeah, is it...
Is this mind programming?
Is this cereal technology?
No, it's analog.
Analog, okay.
It's analog.
Okay, you put it in the lug and then you squeeze the lug real hard and it comes out
in the back.
Millions of slugs emerge.
Yeah.
So slugs do merge slowly into the highway lanes and cause wrecks.
Aren't we getting ready for some kind of dinner or something we're supposed to go to
there?
I'm getting hungry.
What about you, Philo?
It's happening.
Oh, it's happening right now.
Yeah.
Everybody's eating and talking right now.
Okay, where's my chicken?
Where's my, where's my food?
Where's my dinner?
I want my dinner.
It's coming.
We're a little short on help tonight.
I'm waiting for my sandwich.
Your free sandwich for being on the show?
I'm waiting for my hooker.
What about the business report?
Everything just comes served on a silver platter by a low-trumpet.
Oh, the business report.
Investments, you know.
Oh, yeah, investments.
Yeah, we made some investments.
We made some good ones.
We made some bad ones.
We made some ones that were good in the long haul but short in the short haul.
My new slug hooker technology.
The good thing about our business investments is that we're not going to have to go through
all the processes that they continue on and we use a special secret technique that we've
derived from a little atom that we got out of Bob's brain years and years ago.
We put it inside of a triangle along with these crystal pyramids.
This crystal pyramid.
Wow, that's cool.
And that does two things for us.
It predicts the future infallibly and it helps us determine what our next week's menu will
be.
Well, it makes a banana peel straight.
It makes the banana come off of the banana peel faster.
And it makes the riser blade sharper.
Sharper but only while you're cutting.
And yet smoother and softer.
For the softest, smoothest shave you could expect from anyone crawling along a straight
riser.
Leaving the trailing.
Leaving the little droppings behind.
The next time you hear this.
The sludge trail.
Oh, it sounds like we're in a storm.
You kidding me?
Is the prayer over?
I sure hope we, uh, did we put a roof on this thing?
I think the fair...
Is the prayer over?
I predict that the entertainment personality...
The prayer is over.
Okay, amen.
... will be entertainment personalities and nothing else.
Now, let's see.
Sergeant Vredes, what were you just saying about the, uh...
He's a friend of mine.
... the, uh, the, uh, the, uh, the, uh...
I guess I should say some prediction here.
The future, if you want a picture of the next...
... the next hundred years.
When someone pays admission to hear a singer or a comedian, they...
But really...
What about the...
Radio isn't about pictures.
It's about images.
Wow, where'd you learn that?
New York?
Yeah, I, uh, I went to school for a lot of, you know, borrowed money, uh, all that, and
that's all I came out with.
So when pictures are long, they become a thing.
It was images.
Yeah.
That explains everything.
That's where we went wrong.
You mean JPEG?
I always thought it was...
... graphic, graphic, uh, portrayals of, of auditory devices.
I promise to do better.
Let's get back to the past hundred years.
... graven images.
Graven images.
That's all it is.
Makes...
Let's get this next hundred years out on the table right now.
Let's, let's kind of roll it around and look at it and let's see if it's what we really
want to do.
It will not tolerate protest messages.
Let's get this next hundred years out on the table right now.
Let's autopsy this hundred year plan and see what gas rises out of it.
Oh man, that stinks.
I've had some bad luck with gas recently and, uh, so I won't go there right now, but...
If you, yeah, something, if you, if you have a bad smell later then...
The next hundred years is...
Don't look at me.
... a prairie squid crawling along a straight razor forever.
No, a straight edge.
Just the straight edge.
Yeah.
Okay, cue music.
No, we don't care razor, blade, anything sharp.
It's gotta be sharp.
It's gotta have a slug on it and it's gotta be in the future.
And, you know, with the snorting and the pig technology in the future.
There's no figure what we make for ourselves.
Uh, right.
So where's that one guy who's got that, that one, the one thing that's supposed to make
this show the best show?
Outside.
Oh, I'm sorry.
He has the, oh, he has the slack and that is what we needed.
We haven't let him in the back.
He didn't show up again.
I figured something was missing.
Where is he?
Where is that guy?
I don't know how to unbox.
Where is that pipe guy?
I am, uh, uh...
Where's that what?
Where is that Bob Dobbs?
I think, uh...
Where is that pipe guy?
... I disagree with Chairman Bob.
Where are those X-Men?
Uh, uh...
Once again, we are X-ist-less.
There you'll be with the Chairman Bob.
This X-ist-less-ness mess, we once again get to stay apart.
It's chaotic.
Thanks to the non-rival of Bob's business partners, the men from Puddle Deck.
I'm missing you.
Oh, no.
It's followed me here.
I was trying to escape this horrible show.
I've come all the way here to the left coast and the horrible, horrible other show has
pursued me.
Oh.
I was trying to escape this horrible show.
I'm sorry.
Why, boss, why?
How many more times?
Yeah, we're going to start again.
We're going to start the show again.
Oh, yeah, oh, yeah.
That's right, the show.
Oh, man.
Where are we?
What town is this?
Is this Los Angeles?
No, we're in the Bay Area.
Oh, okay.
When does the show start?
Right, right.
Oh, should I start the tape?
I don't really need him, but you never know when you can use him.
Okay, now the tense, scary part of the show starts.
Is this where the scary part starts?
Yep.
For a hundred years.
I'm going to get ready.
For the next hundred years.
To not be scared.
I hear that spooky.
Now, what is this, the business report?
This is the business report.
Or is it the end of the prayer?
We finished the prayer.
We did, okay.
The prayer is over now.
I did not hear an amen, but I will take your word for that.
Okay, well, we don't say amen in this church.
Oh, I get you.
So it's sort of like you were waiting for your cue and it never came.
And you didn't know that, heck, we've already been, we've been into the second part for like 10 minutes now.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
Yeah, it's pretty amazing.
I knew that.
Well, I knew you knew that.
Intuitively, you knew it, but you didn't really have it connected in the same sequence yet.
Amen.
Well, we usually say, huh?
Huh?
At the end?
Yeah, that's it.
I didn't hear that either.
We usually say, what's the amen?
Uh-huh.
We say, huh.
Okay.
Now, you said that, right?
Uh-huh.
Amen.
All right.
Let's get right, let's move right on into the business report.
Okay, well, we're going to give.
Or did you give that?
Yeah.
Well, I'm going to, I'm going to give the business report now.
Well, what was next?
Okay.
Well, I'm glad all of you folks could come to the church.
We're going to be together tonight to hear this great business report that we have that's
going to talk about the next 100 years and what's in it in the church.
And I hope that you don't hold any of those, those allegations of abuse and corporate fraud
that we have, that have been leveled.
I know, I know, I know, but really it's, it's all false.
When the truth comes out, it's just, there's nothing there.
I mean, it's just the emperor has no clothes.
Our enemies will stop at nothing.
Yeah.
Our enemies do that.
They've done that for years.
They've gotten into our books.
They've changed our ledgers.
They've actually recorded things that didn't exist.
And, and when the IRS came in, we didn't have any choice, but just to deny it.
We weren't there and we did not do that.
We didn't.
We really didn't.
I didn't have sex with that woman, Ms. Lewinsky.
Erasability, I swear.
Or any other woman.
I mean, I don't know.
But, in particular, the, the allegations of abuse of the state and the...
I mean, it's just not true.
It's just not true.
You don't need to go into that much detail, Dr. Drummond.
So, but anyway, stocks are up, expenses are down.
What about the contracts for Homeland Security?
Are the, the, we've funded our, we've given our share to the funding of the Homeland Security
for the, we want one of those, those Star Wars...
... satellites to hover over our headquarters building.
We think it's important that it be close to us.
So that when the bombs, the, the, the missiles start coming, we'll, we will have our own
private Star Wars defense shield.
I, I spent...
I know I took...
I've heard those are very dependable defense shields.
We had to sacrifice, well, you know, it's...
We figured three out of, three out of ten is better than none out of ten.
Yeah, I hear they, they work as...
... as well as computers.
No.
And besides, it's the government that's paying for it.
We don't have to pay for it.
It's the government that's paying for it.
I thought that invisible hand guy was going to do it anyway.
We're going to tax the land this time.
We're not going to tax people anymore.
We're going to tax the land.
And, and once the land pays up their taxes, the people will be really happy, you know?
Oh, he tried this a hundred years ago and it only got us this far.
Well, we have to go...
We can only go a hundred years at a time.
That, that was the last hundred years.
It's the smallest...
Please.
... increment we could afford...
Stay focused.
... at the time.
And now, maybe for the next hundred years, we might break it up into like 50-year units.
You know, like two big, two and a quarter...
What?
... 50-year units.
A 50-year plan instead of a hundred-year plan?
That's radical.
Well, you know, the change...
You're moving too fast.
The pace of change has gotten to be such that we can't, we can no longer rely on the, the,
the far, the, the, the outer reaches of our hundred-year plan.
We've gotta, we've gotta have a more tactical approach to things.
We have to know what's gonna happen, like, say, 20 minutes from now.
It doesn't help us to know what's gonna happen 20 years from now, right now.
I mean, we gotta know, like, should I, should I put my hand in my pocket and, or should I, you know, resist the urge to, to urinate on the...
Dr. Drummond, Dr. Drummond, Dobbs gave us a rule book of life.
But it's not a hard and fast thing that dictates every, whether you should put your hand in your pocket every five minutes.
What?
Somebody, somebody, there's some, another, another feed that's feeding in here.
Selling incense outside the gates.
Some guy is playing cymbals.
It's a Hare Krishna guy over there, and I think that...
What, are we selling product placement to other cults?
Well, actually, we weren't allowing any other cults in here.
This is an exclusive cult.
We, we are, we're completely, we only want member, our members in here, the people that paid to be here.
We can't have these freeloaders, you know, freeloading off our cult.
You know, this is a cult of the people, a cult for the people and by the people.
Well, the rich people.
We've got a, well, the richest of the poor people and the poorest of the rich people are all together here in one cult, one...
I'm beginning to understand why we let Dr. Drummond control the business.
Yeah, it's an amalgam, amalgam of, of deposit.
It's a complete deposit.
Yeah, look at this.
He learned that at Bob.
Bob taught Dr. Drummond everything he knows.
Piled up in big piles and, you know, the graphics, the graphics behind that will go into the, the median expenditures.
And on, on the side there, we can see how, if we track this particular, extrapolate that out to its ultimate nth degree.
You know, there's a...
Then you can see that we're going to make about 15 cents off of every third unit on the 12th of each month.
And the deposits will be coming in, they're going to be rolling in.
We have the bolt cutters!
The bolt cutters are here!
Cut, cut, cut!
Hey, put those bolt cutters down.
No, I need the bolt cutters!
Put those bolt cutters down!
I need the bolt cutters!
No, you can't have the, those are my bolt cutters.
Just give me the bolt cutters now!
Hey, guard, would you take this gentleman out of here, please?
And take his harmonica with him, please?
Yeah, that's horrible.
Don't, don't let the guard play the harmonica now.
What about all these allegations about corruption?
Corruption?
Well, you know, people have talked about how bad we are for years.
But few people talk about how good we are.
I mean, that's the one thing that, we take a lot of heat for being, like, the world's worst cult.
The world's most hated cult.
Stingiest cult.
Corruption was built.
The world's most corrupt and built.
But people don't talk about how really good we are.
You know, how great we are, and the greatness of the world.
Well, and the purity of the corruption.
You see, if you start out from a base of absolute and total corruption, you can't be bought out.
Well, that's true.
I mean, we're starting with the lowest common denominator.
And we can only go up from here, folks.
So, I mean, it's gonna, it's like smooth sailing for the next six or eight years.
Then, at the eight-year point, we're gonna meet a slight blip in this, as this chart will illustrate.
A jobs crisis.
That will be our first jobs crisis.
See that blip there?
But it goes, we're gonna hammer it down with this big hammer here.
Right.
And then smooth things out.
We're gonna extrapolate the linear regression over this way.
See over there?
Oh, it's smoothing!
Yeah, it's smoothing.
That's a great, uh...
We're using a smoothing formula there.
To smooth out the edges.
That computer simulation is gorgeous.
Yeah.
You can see all the sharp edges are now dull.
See, you can't cut yourself or anything.
How much of the church's budget did we spend on that pie, that computerized pie graph,
that animated pie graph, Dr. Drummond?
Well, I'm sure it'll all come out in the bill, in the billing, uh, at the end when we get
the bill from the, this wonderful resort here that we're staying at.
Yeah, well, I was a little concerned.
What is this?
Maybe the, the, the business meeting is costing more than the company's profits this particular
year.
We'll just gonna, we'll, you know...
Century.
We're gonna take it out of the, uh, we'll take it out, well, Bob will, will provide.
That's the thing we have to remember here.
You know?
And that we will survive, and we don't have to worry about costs overrunning our wonderful,
wonderful revenue streams because, you know, we've got the flow now, we've got the, the,
the actual, um, the momentum.
Dr. Drummond, those are pretty fuzzy figures that you're projecting up on the screen.
I mean, those aren't even numbers.
Those are some kind of alien alphabet.
What are we supposed to...
Well, you can read it, though.
If you can't read it, then you didn't study your materials before the, the, the, uh, the
meeting here.
I can read that.
I mean, we had those materials that you were supposed to read and memorize, those tapes
you were supposed to listen to and be able to regurgitate.
Dr. Drummond's taken all the money and he squandered it.
All right, well, we bought tapes.
We had to buy tapes.
We needed new tape decks.
We needed, our 8-track machine had broken down.
We had our beta, our beta, our, our, our, our, our, our, our, our, our, our, our, our, our, our,
our, our, our, our, our, our, our, our, our, our, our, our, our, our, our, our, our, our, our,
our beta machine is broken down.
Dr. Drummond, we're talking about three or four billion dollars here.
Yeah, what are, what are these, these vaults full of receipts from this...
Billion here, a billion there.
I mean, to us, it's all just money.
To the Korean massage parlor.
And that's the important thing to remember that it's money.
That, that money, that money, that money...
And when we keep the money flowing, we keep it going...
The Pink Pussycat Club.
What are these, what are these vaults full of receipts?
Well, these are, these are investments we had to make.
We go in to test the, test the culture, test the air, test the...
We're doing personality bypass transplant treatments in those places.
And we, even in Enron, we had to go to Enron and do some investigatory work long before
the, the, the, the government auditors got in there.
Can you take that out?
I don't know, he's, he's trying to, to...
I'm not doing, don't look over here.
There's no, don't pay no attention to the, to the hand behind the, the cloak there.
Okay.
It's like a giant invisible hand has been...
Some people might call it a cloth.
Other people call it a cloth.
But to us, it's just a shroud.
Cheating the company.
And we put the shroud on and wear it when we need to.
Invisible hand that he's got.
Yeah.
So, I take it that there is no embarrassment among the subgenius that they, that they
all arrived in limousines here at Sulphur Palms tonight.
Well, you don't want a stupid preacher, as the great brother Gene Scott said.
Uh-huh.
Amen.
You know, when, when a person turns on their television and sees a picture of
these, their preacher, he wants to see them in a limousine with these lovely...
He wants to see them...
...choir girls on either arm and...
This beautiful Armani, a $600 Armani suit.
Right.
He don't want a stupid preacher.
All the other preachers do this.
Uh-huh.
Amen.
And, and we're...
Uh-huh.
We're not doing anything different from, from what any other religious leaders do.
And, in fact, when, when, when we had, we suffered those arrests for methamphetamine
manufacturing.
That's a, that's a, that's, that's the kind of thing that we get a special award for.
In fact, we have a, a several boxes of awards for...
Uh-huh.
...the various doctors here tonight.
And don't forget, uh, without those Hummer limos, you couldn't have got here, because
there's no roads to Sulphur Pond.
There's no roads...
Okay, I've just, uh, got an important message I have to take, uh...
...to Sulphur Pond.
Uh, Reverend Stang, would you like to finish, uh, take over this business meeting at this
point?
No.
I have to go now.
Yeah, yeah, take up where he left off.
There's a special tool I have to get.
I'm sorry for this interruption, but I'll be back shortly.
Yeah, he was dealing with the corruption and the embezzlement at the top in the church.
Well, you'll notice under hassles and hang-ups, problems relating to drugs, sexual identity, authority, and relationships, we're up 370%.
And that's mostly within the 18 to 25 group.
Wow, that's good.
Gonorrhea, syphilis, venereal herpes are up.
The venerous venereal herpes.
Again, that's almost 400% just in the last year.
That means the workshops were a success.
That part of the outreach has been a tremendous success.
The computer viruses and the organic viruses both, in every case, the sexually and DSL transmitted diseases.
The fast food outreach has apparently completely bottomed out.
The burger god concept.
I predict entertainment will be entertainment.
Entertainment, boy.
That was an understatement.
That has got to be the understatement of the year, what Dr. Criswell just said.
That entertainment would be entertainment.
I never thought I'd live to see the day.
And you haven't.
Um, depression or blue moods are up.
And the manic phases are down.
I've got a question.
Oddly enough.
Pardon me?
Dr. Stang?
Yes, Senator.
Yes.
The little girl in the front row.
Uh, yeah.
When your local...
Church leaders are subject to accusations.
What is your stance on how to handle that within your organization?
When the collection plate comes around, double what you were going to put in otherwise, my friend.
Good idea.
There you go.
The collection plate is the bottom line.
That is what this business...
You know, when it comes down to it...
That'll fix it.
We can talk about all this.
Our product placement and producing these movies that battle torn earth and so forth.
But when it comes down to it, it's the collection plate passed from hand to hand.
Or from paw to paw, as it may.
From hoof to hoof among the believers.
And that will fix up those problems that you have?
Belief is the coin of the realm.
In this realm.
What about the emotions of...
Get along, little bobbies.
What about the personalities and the emotions affected and involved in such incidences?
Well, those are being stored in the finest blue canisters in the Dobstown basement, as always.
So you would disagree with the Catholic stance that people are expendable?
Yes.
People, yeah, people, sure.
But this...
People, yeah, sure, people, sure.
Expendable?
Yeah.
People, yeah, people, sure, yeah.
Expendable people?
People, yeah.
Expendable emotions?
Well, like we say, the coin of the realm is belief.
Spend your belief all over the floor, all over the office trash can.
Just spend it, baby.
Just let loose.
Let her rip.
Bob don't care.
Bob loves you anyway.
Bob loves you!
Yes.
You are on the right track.
Getting warmer.
Hello?
Pastor Dick?
Is he there today?
Tonight?
No, Pastor Dick is not here tonight.
This is the subgenius executive retreat.
I thought he was part of the subgenius.
Oh, no, heavens no.
That's a completely different denomination.
Oh, okay.
My mind's all mixed up.
Uh-huh, amen.
All right, have a good show.
I'm so messed up.
Well, there's another dissatisfied listener.
Oh, praise Bob.
We're mowing him down, but crop circles.
This is the subgenius executive retreat direct from Sulphur Palms, California.
Ah, yes, yes, yes, and a historic, uh, historic, uh, historic, uh, historic, uh, historic, uh,
weekend it was at Silver Pond there, thanks to Don Joyce, uh, Bud Good, Puzzling Evidence,
uh, uh, Du Gwellman, Dr. Philo Drummond and KPFA in Berkeley, California, whose studios
allowed that.
And there are four more hours of that.
Okay.
the over the edge show merged with the show.
That's more than an hour,
less than a show.
And in fact,
altogether,
it was five hours of show and now being strewn about the hour of slack.
Uh,
and friends,
you know,
the San Francisco subgenius show or puzzling evidence show,
uh,
has been on every week on KPFA since June,
1983.
Uh,
when I went out there to work on the book of the subgenius with Palmer
Vredes and puzzling evidence,
and we were guests on Bob Nelson show,
but the subgenius is never went away.
Um,
and this subgenius executive retreat at silver palms was,
you know,
we might say the 20 year reunion of the old timey doctors,
uh,
Dr.
Philo Drummond,
uh,
who's banned a swing and left corpses is heard in the background here.
Uh,
lies,
uh,
Gary,
the broke friend,
puzzling evidence,
uh,
and,
and also Michael Pepe and Ed Holmes all there.
Sorry.
The Dr.
Howling glass madness couldn't be there.
And Jay Kenny.
But anyway,
here's a tape of that very gang of wacky Zenos down at the Gazette.
Zeebo from before the show in 1983,
when it was just a band that dare not speak its name,
working on the book of the sub genius.
Fuck.
You want to know about the book?
The book was a flop.
The book.
Nobody bought that book.
Did you?
The book was a disaster.
And when they did buy it,
they tried to get their money back.
A terminal disaster.
Nobody made a single penny.
What did he say?
What?
Ah!
Man, what a, what a flop!
What's he talking about?
The book!
What about the song?
The book was a flop!
It made the church stop.
The book.
Oh, the loud song.
Yeah.
Ah!
A thousand copies and most of them trash
Thirty thousand copies and no one got cash
Warehouse
A warehouse full of books
A warehouse full of unwanted books
The book stands out
The book
The book was a flop
It made the sun stop
Well, maybe not
Yes, even the book couldn't make the song stop
Yeah, well
It sure made the church stop
It made the distributor stop
It made the church stop
It made the post office and the secret service stop, but
It couldn't make the song stop
The band that dare not speak its name from the old ancient 1983 subgenius tape.
Bad Doctors.
Oh, bad, bad, bad.
And there's so much more bad in the name of the band that's a pain to the heart.
to be had at www.subgenius.com.
That website will tell you about the Living Church.
If it's money you want, we'll send that to Post Office Box 2.
Well, this is where you can write to the business office.
Post Office Box 181417, Cleveland Heights, Ohio, 44118, subgenius.com.
But, you know, he can work his way up at the 7-Eleven.
I just got back from a trip to visit the beautiful new Austin facilities,
which are run by Jesus and his wife, his beautiful wife, Mary Magdalene.
It was so great.
It was great to see that busy operation down there.
And, friends, if you have tapes you want us to hear in Subgenius Land,
or CDs, or whatever, send them to me,
yours truly, Reverend Ivan Stang, at Box 181417.
That's Post Office Box 181417, Cleveland Heights, Ohio, 44118.
And I do have a cold, if you were wondering.
It's a subgenius virus.
I got it from my computer.
Hey, friends, happy new last year.
That's when I'm doing this show.
And praise Bob.
Oh, and now more of this.
This broadcast is silly tape-delayed stuff.
I've been in the women's shoe business since 1875.
In all those years of servicing customers, I found your feet.
Unfortunately, we want to service you.
That's very good.
It's now out of control.
We have a school bus.
The trap is completely out of control.
Out of control.
And we have nothing.
They're beginning to run into one another and over one another.
How much Librax are you taking?
67.
I was wondering.
Well, it seems to me like some animals are after me.
Do you look at that?
Oh.
I think you have to tell your doctors I'm a psychiatrist.
It's likely that's why you're having the nightmares.
And that's when the gem shepherds tripped over the curb.
Every year, thousands of letter carriers are attacked by dogs.
It's like that.
Public service dogs.
I want a mechanical man.
No, the interesting thing.
Oh, mechanical man.
That's it.
The interesting thing is, I'm sorry, but you can't hear any more.
I must see what this is.
What's that?
That doesn't make any sense to me whatsoever.