It'll be Saturday night for Sunday in the afternoon.
Sunday night into Monday.
Saturday's gonna be Monday, which is right about on target for this time of year.
We're looking at pretty stable Midwest moving across the middle of next week as we're looking at St. Louis.
Hey, Connie.
Hey.
What's the matter, Connie?
Aw, wake up, Connie.
Smell the coffee.
Smell the...
So genius.
Power of...
What?
It stinks.
No kidding.
Good evening, fellow citizens.
This is the voice of the illegal radio to which you are forbidden to listen under penalty of death.
I'll have three meals a day, five if I want them.
Roof over my head to drink every now and then to warm me up.
I'll be worshipped and fed and treated like a high priest for telling people things they want to hear.
It's the new original that has the legendary Bob talking.
Tell us, Alan Gruden Greenspan.
No bobs.
No sticky, smelly bobs.
Zesty, stiffer bobs.
Small bobs.
Hot, delicious, personal bobs.
Got me some slack.
Slack.
Did he say slack?
You want to talk about slack?
Well, you wouldn't understand if we told you right.
We'll tell you behind your back.
The radio promo, bromo, bubbles in your belly form a gas called the hour of slack.
When released, some police eat their own badges.
So the guns of the sun shake their mustaches.
Cut their penises off and carve their own badges.
And cauterize it all with some kitchen matches.
We watch Charles Nelson Riley with suspicious eyes.
For fear that if we don't, his corks out surely rise.
Well, I didn't understand when I first heard it.
Then I heard again.
Then I didn't understand.
And even better.
The letter of the law wears a sweater in her bra.
So you better take it off and just forget her.
We gaze into the light, reflecting from the eyes.
Light from the coal inside the bowl of sacred pipes.
Quit your job.
Mom?
Slack.
Quit your job.
What?
Slack.
Quit your job.
Mom?
Slack.
Quit your job.
Mom?
Slatitious a bringิous.
Drag a towline behind a broke down Cadillac.
driven by a mad man.
Blinded as a baseball bat.
Spot the matters getting everywhere I look.
It's all over the face.
It's on the carder's bill of riches.
cover of this book.
Subtenus is the only
word still legible.
I'd rather follow Bob
than be a vegetable.
My testicles have
fortitude and quite a
bit of hair.
But if you listen to
them hour slack is
what you'll hear.
Listen to my testicles.
A new hour of slack.
Charles Nelson testicle
mix in that by the El
Queso All Stars.
It's a new hour of slack.
With the Lemurian intro
there bringing hour of
slack number 1032 to
rampaging life.
But now let us go back
in time to Stang's
giving 2005 and the
over the puzzling
evidence edge show on
KPFA in evil Berkeley,
California.
This is your 484425 banquet
facilitator is he isn't.
And we're back here with
the end of over the edge
or way past over the edge.
That's all gone.
Forget that.
This is the subgenius
Thanksgiving.
Call executive banquet
of you fellas got that I
haven't got about to tackle
about to tackle the economic
side of this organization
for once out in the open.
Transparency is the motto.
And I think I agree.
I think I'm going to get
down.
I've got the budget numbers
here and I'm ready to talk
to the let's start with a new
department.
Let's start with income.
How much did the subgenius
foundation make.
Well you know I don't
understand what these numbers
are saying because there's
an introduction here that has
got those measurements and
weights and things and
equivalencies translation
tables a bunch of different
tanda tangential axes that
talk about the effects of
propeller and roll.
So it's all about the
motor wash and size and
shape of aircraft and the
good bone structure of the
members.
Yeah.
And the bone structure.
What's that got to do with
anything.
I see Mr.
Stang stepping to the head
of the banquet table about to
I guess give his yearly report
What about this neurotoxin
this toxin which attacks any
nerve tissue.
What about that.
Don't mention that Philo.
That's pretty scary at a
banquet.
What about these passive
defense measures.
I see that there's sixty
thousand dollars dedicated to
passive defense measures.
Notice how you notice how
they've avoided Congressman
Izzy's question for over 20
minutes.
This chair is all flips.
Now I'm just running.
I haven't been elected yet.
So is the mic.
All flipsy dipsy.
Running from those bullets.
All the time running.
And here is Mr. Stang now with
his annual.
That's.
Annual report.
That's that's Reverend Stang.
If you don't mind.
I'm sorry I'm Congressman.
Is I didn't attend Dobbs Town
University Divinity School for
15 years to be called Mr.
Stang.
Normally it takes a good.
Four years.
You have to Mr.
It's Mr.
Smith.
Didn't they all commit suicide.
Well that was.
Say why was it that it took you
15 years to get a degree that
normally takes two years.
Look I can't.
Kind of killed the show.
I can't compete with Texas accents
here.
It's.
What about this hog collar of virus.
There's too many of them and makes
me sound like a northern liberal.
Oh God.
The growing custom in the.
That's OK.
You know we're an open organization.
The church is not a political
organization aside from patriotic
psychotic and narco materialism which is so broad as.
To be defined more as a species rather than a political or a lifestyle.
We have a lifestyle maybe.
Yeah but back to that.
Report.
Yes back to the report.
What about the ding fever virus.
Dollars and cents.
Let's get down to some transparency here.
Three thirty six twenty one.
No it's up twenty four.
Actually as I'm watching it it's going up taxes for instance.
Did you pay any taxes.
That's what I just told you.
I'm sorry.
The number and it's still going up.
So exactly.
Tell me when you want the cut off moment.
Well can I have your Social Security number.
I told you three thirty six.
Now it's forty three.
I got that.
I thought that was your phone number.
Thirty six twelve thirty six.
Yes baby.
The treasurer.
Connie has entered the room.
Stand up boys.
That's what I take your hats off.
I'm standing up over this.
Well it's.
Go.
Nobody could ever go like Connie.
Check out that logistical system.
Crazy.
Crazy, I'm half crazy.
I'm half crazy.
Wow, Larry.
Those were great stories about loving your family.
Thanks, Bob.
Um, speaking of families,
I've been feeling kind of bad that I never told you about mine.
So, I gave my brothers a call so you can meet them.
What?
Come on in, guys.
Bob, this is Bob.
Bob and Bob.
Well, hi, guys.
It's really great to meet you.
Uh.
Rumors of Bob, but never Bob.
It is Bob.
Right.
What is it you tell people you do these days, Bob?
Between State Department and Defense.
Bitterness and bigotry.
There's definite brain damage.
Fragile plastic gas bag.
My own ideas.
I try to take my inspiration from the beat.
Always busy, busy, busy.
BABY
JUST PICKED UP SOMETHING
HALT
I'M GETTING CLOSED
I'M STILL
RESIGNED
I'M NOT
QUITE
WE Bradley
devouring them alive.
They paralyze the victims
and then take their time
devouring them alive.
Oh, women.
Men.
Meanwhile, back in the city,
in the end,
I try to take my inspiration
from the bees.
Always busy, busy, busy.
My own ideas
disappear by magic.
Fragile plastic gas bags.
There's definite brain damage.
Bitterness and vigor creep.
Fragile plastic gas bags
disappear by magic.
My own ideas.
I try to take my inspiration
from the bees.
Always busy, busy, busy.
In the end,
meanwhile, back in the city,
Oh, women.
Women.
They paralyze the victims
and then take their time
devouring them alive.
Somewhere a perversion
has taken place.
In the end,
the end.
Oh, my goodness.
That was almost my end,
wasn't it?
No, it was
In the End
by Norrell Preff
of
norrellpreff.com
That's N-O-R-E-L
P-R-E-F-P-R-E-F-P-O-M-E-L-P-E-N-D-T-O-S-K.
And now, back to the subgenius business meeting on KPFA.
But what about the report?
Rarely is there any direct corollary between the report and the Connie activity.
It's a calibrated, sensory array.
I think that was it. That just went by.
We uploaded the report to all of the commission members last week.
If you didn't check your F-mail, then it's certainly not Bob's responsibility.
The report was F-mailed last week.
For the chip to reach the downstream state.
I have it here.
Usually a stopwatch.
As you can see, John.
Ladies and gentlemen, the proposed merger with the Church of Scientology was cancelled.
And that caused a precipitate drop.
We call it the ripple effect.
Stock price, of course.
But as you can see, that's starting to bounce back.
And we're negotiating with the Mormons right now.
Does that mean you paid no taxes in 2004?
Why do you keep harping on this?
Sensitive subject.
We donated to charities.
I want transparency.
I want to see this organization come out front.
Get out in front.
And do the purple.
Yeah, you know, sunshine laws, okay?
Get out in front of whatever this is.
We've got the exact number if you want it.
The taxes we paid in 2004 are now $340.22.
Now it's $24.
That's $340.22.
Like a locomotive bearing down on us.
At first, apparently not moving.
But then, suddenly.
Looming large.
We didn't do much business in taxes.
Only in Cleveland.
But you know, folks, it doesn't matter where you hang out your shingle in the street.
Yes, it does.
Location, location.
It's everything.
It certainly does matter.
But what about the better business boost of commerce, Caucasian Christians?
But that brings up an interesting question.
Christians for Jews.
Where?
Where is the subgenius church located?
Well, the building itself.
The subgenius church is located in the heart and the mind and deep in the glands of every dues-paying subgenius minister.
And it's located in the wishful thinking compartment of the non-dues-paying subgenius minister.
See here on this screen, there it is.
The giant 700-foot tower of the Dobbs Idea in Dobbstown, Malaysia.
It's made of solid, uh, what is that?
Now, that's the physical church.
Actually, it's adobe.
It's adobe, but it's a front.
No, it's not adobe.
It's, uh...
Oh, he was saying it's adobe.
Searsidey knuckle.
It's just an expression they use out there.
And, uh, yeah, those are the bobbies working all day and night, 24 hours.
Dolomite.
It's made of solid dolomite.
Dolomite is my name!
Dolomite!
You see, uh...
Genius Architectural Union bid to have this unusual structure created for the Nabob of Ooze in the year 1972.
And it's just one of the many wonders, wonders of science, wonders of human creation, brought into being by the love of God.
And, uh, this is the source of all our climatic data.
This particular chinless wonder is Dob's seventh son.
Which makes him the seventh son of a seventh son.
Possibly the even higher epoch.
We'll find out this X-Day 9 at Brushwood, when the seventh son of the seventh son of Dob's will be unveiled.
This space is killing.
He will make himself naked to you.
And you may decide.
It will be up to you to choose.
Do you feel the fire, friends?
I certainly don't.
But I know that if I, if I can kindle it.
Where's a picture of Dob's?
There's one here.
Give me that picture.
Give me that Dob's head.
Now!
users i'm gripping
Uh, uh, I'm holding a copy of the book.
Abu Ibn使 65
I've got the book of the subgenius in my hand and i'm staring into that eye bob ...
andI'm feeling it, I'm remembering
What brought me into this church.
It didn't have anything to do with my ...
It didn't have anything to do with being a young yeti.
It didn't have anything to do with being picked on in elementary school
and the unfortunate fact that I throw like a girl.
No, it was this and this fact only.
When I looked at Bob's face, I instantly saw how cool he was.
And that is what made me a subgenius.
I saw how cool his face was.
And that is all that defines a subgenius.
You can pretty it up.
Oh, you won't.
But that is it.
That's the final truth lies in that face.
This is a one-face religion.
A face-based religion, Mr. George Bush.
You hear me, Mr. Bush, Mr. President Cheney?
This is a...
Face-based religion.
Forget it all. Thank you.
Yes.
Put on one of those religious straitjackets.
Card him off.
Muffle him if they can't take a joke.
This is our beloved hip-hop Reverend Ivan Stang.
He is often music and he communicates to us many wonderful secrets of the church.
He claims that he can steer the church using these visions.
Yes, we all love Ivan Stang.
Be careful of him there.
Make sure he's restrained suitably.
He's a real man.
I'm half crazy.
Z z z z z z z z z z z z z z z z z.
I'm half cra cra cra cra cra cra crazy.
A little remix there by Noor El-Pef.
And now, a little remix.
A little soupy sales introduces Little Theodore.
Well, what do you think, gang?
Well, listen, do you have any other songs?
All kind of songs?
Cha-chas and rock and roll?
And even operatic areas?
What are these songs about?
About each other?
Happy people.
So close you dance so slick.
You make me stomp and kick.
Happy people.
Look at you, the right.
They laugh instead of fight.
Happy people.
You've taken the system's fate.
They think it's up and straight.
Happy people.
You're part of Megan's plan.
No matter what you think of his clan.
Happy people.
You're all but introduced.
These are our golden noose.
Happy people.
Should be put back in your place.
With the rest of our miserable race.
Happy people.
It's you I most detest.
Make me wanna be a pest.
Happy people.
You stray from the right course.
You justify the use of force.
Happy people.
You wanna be ashamed.
Please don't give us someone to blame.
guitar solo
Little Theodore, dear friends,
from his new CD,
the very best of Little Theodore's greatest hits.
And that's pretty good, I guess.
On discriminataudio.com
or you can find more at www.littletheodore.com
and I'm going to spell Theodore.
That's F as in Frank.
Y-O-D-O-R
littletheodore.com
And you'd have to see him
to believe it.
And now we go back
to the point in the KPFA recordings
where they let me back on the air.
By the power of Bob within you.
Power, oil, charger.
All right, I promise I'll be good now.
By the charge of Bob within you.
Car charger, but...
I'll power it up.
They gave me my pill.
I'll quit yelling now.
I'll be good now.
I'll be good now, you guys.
All right.
I'm sorry I yelled.
I'm sorry I got all excited about J.R. Bob Dobbs.
I'm sorry I brought it up.
Yeah, don't do that again.
I guess we better get back to business now.
Yeah.
I guess we better forget about Bob and Slack
and just go get that God-given business.
Bob's Car Work.
Well, is there any new business?
Well, J.R.K.'s still dead.
I must say I can empathize with Reverend Stang's enthusiasm.
I do myself feel very...
Except you again, caller.
...as if in my spirit I were let loose.
Caller.
Identify yourself.
Michael Pepe was called up in the spirit
and given roaming charges.
I was called to Bob many, many years ago
and I do sometimes feel that efflorescence of the spirit.
God.
Caller.
Bob, uh...
Occasionally...
What can you tell us about the dismounted patrolling
going on in your neighborhood?
Yeah, because it rocks.
Well...
Are there variations of this technique
that you can, uh, simulate?
Oh, look, this is you.
This is Philo.
Yes, this is Philo.
He's in his car.
Okay, I...
I'm driving with my mullet flying in the breeze.
Man, look at that devil-may-care-debonair-devil.
And look, uh, they all know him in his neighborhood.
Yeah, Philo's a popular dude.
Hey, that's Super Philo.
He's an overman in his underwear.
He's Funky Philo.
I got it.
Everybody.
He's a dude with a plan
to stick it to the man.
Oh, Bob.
I got security.
This is violent action.
Follow.
Pick up control.
I've got his back.
From PR News in Washington,
I'm undignified, unbecoming,
unfortunate, and unnecessary,
and must end now.
On Wall Street 510-841-4921.
This is PR.
Dirty PR News.
PR News.
Undetected cracks
allocate up to one and a half billion dollars
to help people with older TVs
buy converter boxes.
The Senate has rejected an attempt
to allow PR News in Washington.
Now, less than four minutes from right now.
Today we do have tonight and tomorrow,
then a Thursday through Friday on Saturday.
I-94 eastbound at Greenfield
and U.S. 23 southbound
between Grand Blanc and Washington.
I-95 and Thompson Road still possible.
8 Mile Road westbound at I-75
reported along that stretch.
And it is probably Wayne Road at I-94
and I-280 between I-75
and State Road 795.
It is completely possible
through the end of this month.
We'll have scattered today.
Otherwise, tonight is hanging in there.
Good chance for Wednesday
and the extended outlook Friday
climbing out of Thursday across the region.
Expect Washington for Detroit.
Less than four minutes from right now.
We'll have scattered on Thursday
The Chief has just said
the tribe faces a big meat shortage.
And for the first hunter to return with fresh meat,
he offers a surprise his beautiful daughter,
Minnie Hatcher!
This is James Earl.
James Earl.
James Earl Jones.
Jones Jones.
This is James Earl.
James Earl, James Earl, James Earl Jones.
Battle, battle.
The United States.
Listen to this.
Four, four years ago, the United States brought forth war.
Dedicated to the proposition that all men are living and dead.
Little note, it is altogether war, war, war.
That that nation might take increased dead.
We should do this.
We cannot, we cannot, we cannot score, score what they did.
War, what they did, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what they did.
These dead, dead, dead have died in vain.
This nation under war shall have a new birth of war.
And the government of the government, by the government, for the government, dead, shall perish from the earth.
Thin, thin, thin.
By the shores of Gitche Gumee, by the laughing big sea water,
Neath the shade of mighty pine trees, dwelt the warrior, Heel Wather.
A flat-faced, pigeon-toed, knock-kneed, blubber-headed, tub of lard.
Respectfully submitted for your perusal.
What you're looking at is the butt zone.
Weight in the neighborhood of 350 pounds.
Origin unknown.
Lemur did it, dear friends.
And before that, I Cannot Score by Norrell Kraft.
And before that, some more Lemur.
And the puzzling evidence show with Dr. Philodrum and Dr. Howell.
Michael Pepe, Izzy Isn't, and Gary DeBrock-Fran calling in.
And yours truly, Reverend Ivan Stang, with Princess We Are Go.
And now, PR News.
PR NEWS
On PR News in Washington, I'm the fourth turkey.
Germany has said Iran will face serious jack straw.
On Wall Street, 3-12-11-11.
Turkish health officials say they have detected a 15th human in the center of the country.
The government is trying to prevent a health crisis by slaughtering the public.
In the border town of Dubai, is it?
Chickens and roosters watched as two teenagers stuffed children into plastic bags.
This is PR News in Washington.
PR NEWS
Next, we have texto from Tobe.
They're screwed because it's way off the beaten track record.
They gave this up in action.
And this is PSAT'somon and AkaiM點 hut in stitches
It's 001 Nerd and it's left now trips out of a
Hit the cellphone button down.
Good job.
No pressure.
Nobody can tell me what to do
Not even you
Nobody wants to play with me
Just because I am not friendly
All the other kids are playing funny games
While I stay by myself and examine my brain
I got a world of my own
I see things that you don't
Nobody can tell me what is good
Though you wish you could
Nobody wants to play with me
Just because I am not sexy
All the other kids are fooling around
But I'm several miles above the ground
I got a world of my own
I see what is not there
Nobody can tell me how to feel
I know that's real
Nobody wants to play with me
Just because I have no family
All the other kids have wives and jobs
While I lay in the gutter and think and sob
I got a world of my own
I see sadness and dirt
Nobody can tell me what is right
Try to fight
Nobody wants to play with me
Just because I am old and ornery
All the other kids have grandchildren
They chatter and they squabble but I ignore them
I got a world of my own
I see all that I am
Nobody can tell me why I live
You have nothing to give me
I see all that I am
Why does it have alos for me
I see all that I know
I can and want to
Why does a soul of mine
How exactly they flesh my flesh
And tell me that when man's blood runs dry
How often it hurls out Am slips of my tongue
I feed my human flesh
I ask to be what I want
And carrieth a briefcase and brown loafers.
And yea, he shall attend to thine barbecue.
You know, some people think that the pipe of Bob Dobbs is a symbol of drugs and drug abuse.
And nothing could be further from the truth because it is a tunnel of knowledge.
It is a funnel for slack.
Nothing could be further from the truth.
That tunnel is a funnel.
Nothing has no relative distance to the truth.
It is in fact a pipeline to eternal slackdomness.
You mean a pipeline to eternal damnation.
No, into the lungs of Bob, my friend.
It is your path into the lungs of Bob.
If you can butt, throw your butt into that pipe.
Light yourself.
Stop it.
Cut it out.
You.
You got me.
Out of the lotion.
Baby, there's nothing like it.
It's real slack.
It's better than sex.
It's better than crack.
They say it's better than winning at gambling.
It's better than the finest hamburgers you ever had.
They say about Bob.
Slack.
They say.
Oh, yes.
No, no.
Radio, you holding it down, though.
The burning cigarette.
Thanks, man.
We're trying to hold it down.
It's flying out from under our hands.
It's out of control.
Oh, you're doing fine.
Maintain.
You know, you're saving lives.
You can relax in the safety of your own delusions.
That's what Bob said.
So pick up on it.
We do it for the children.
Pick up.
Will you pick up?
Feel good?
Yeah, but that's mind-body.
You trust in your most sacred.
Yeah, we're doing it for the children.
We're not playing.
It's not for the kids, man.
It's all about the children.
Won't anybody think of the children right now?
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Ah!
Alien space monster Jehovah One really exists.
Over three billion people on this planet believe in Jehovah.
So even if he doesn't exist, with that kind of firepower behind him,
you'd better believe he exists.
And anyway, it would surely take a conspiracy bigger than the military,
industrial, international, advertising, music, government, film, media,
and fashion conspiracies to completely convince that many suckers.
Oh, right, that's right.
You'd better believe in him.
We've reported his insane, murderous, genocidal activities to the elder gods,
but there's nothing they can do until 1998.
And so, until then, we must do as Jehovah says.
In fact, if he's as omnipotent,
as they claim, we have no choice but to do what he says.
What he says is what we do.
We are just puppets acting out in his bizarre snuff movie.
Probably.
I mean, to be honest, it's quite difficult to work out what God's saying,
what with all these false religions around.
And I should know, I'm a minister in one of them.
The point, brothers and sisters, is that even Bob doesn't have all the answers.
And neither does anybody else.
You must love...
Learn to think for yourself.
Only Bob can show you how.
For just a small fee, we can at least help you flesh out your fantasy
that there are some answers.
Help you pull the wool over your own eyes.
My final point this evening, ladies and gentlemen, brothers and sisters, is this.
The official, divine, all-inclusive excuse.
Every subgenius minister gets a lovely copy of these
in beautiful second-generation photocopy.
Because Bob comes not to forgive our sins,
but to justify and excuse them.
The text of the excuse goes a little like this.
I'm a high priest apprentice of a man class
in the church of the subgenius.
A religious faith for scoffers, blasphemers, infidels and heathens.
For heretics, sinners, creeps and freaks,
the ungodly and the indifferent.
In general,
the ethnically all-encompassing subgenius race.
The mission of the subgenius church
is total blissful slack.
And no one better get in the way of a subgenie
than Bob.
And whatever he may lack,
he's got an excuse.
He's got an excuse.
He's got Bob's excuse.
To manipulate an alien monster.
Jehovah one and his star fist.
The very meaning of wrong
as its known on this planet
is meaningless shit.
Right and wrong and everything else are equal at least in theory.
Thus to restrict my behavior in any way invites God's wrath.
I have an excuse.
I've got Bob's excuse.
Excuse.
I'm a tool of Jehovah so you're human.
Be they religious, scientific or moral.
They don't apply to use them against me is against God's inscrutable plan.
He'll return this world to an Eden-like state.
By whatever means he feels.
Be it atomic war, economic disaster or hostile UFOs.
I've got an excuse.
I've got Bob's excuse.
To accuse a church member of any wrong.
Cause him pain or steal his slack.
Is to restrict his freedom of religion.
Not to mention bringing death.
Doom upon us all
What I've done was my fated duty
Forever sanctioned and condoned
Justified in perpetuity
By Bob and God and church and soul
I've got an excuse
I've got Bob's excuse
Thank you ladies and gentlemen!
Praise Bob!
And praise Andy!
Reverend Priest in London, England
Just amazing dear friends
With the musical sung version of
The huge excuse document
That every subject is actually
Yes, in its ordainment package
Which
Uh
Now uh
Actually what was my point gonna be about that?
The point is you can learn to forget!
You can learn
Now what was it we were supposed to forget?
To forget
You can forget about God
You can forget about money
You can forget about sex
But you can't forget about Bob!
You know I think when people first realized
That that's when they start to get a little scared of the church of the subgenius
Cause uh
They realize they can't forget about Bob uh
And for all the goofing around they
They might be doing they uh
They start getting a little bit concerned and uh
That's when we have your first tier subgenius attacks
These figures from deputy sheriffs across the United States
Show a surprising incidence of subgenius acts
Especially when the moon is full
For some strange reason or other, you know?
Um
It's probably because we've never been able to figure out
Are these rings?
You can be part of the evil ones plan my friends!
Oh
Don't be left out!
Join us humans!
We'll accept you also!
You are free gentlemen
She did manage it then, this way
Beware the false prophets who will lead you astray
With their promises of uh
Uh, of, of, of...
False slack!
Where gimme bob and pinkness dwells,
false prophets from their citadels,
he topples down to nether hells.
Friends, just take a look around you
and you can tell that what we're saying is true!
Oh, gosh!
It couldn't be more obvious!
They hide it in plain sight!
This is the mighty city of Thanagotopolopolis.
You have no choice.
The ancients knew slack!
But they found that when they tried to harness its awesome power,
the city of Mutantis was forced beneath the earth's crust.
Yes, friends!
Giant palaces of science and shining sorcery
destroyed forever.
The great, the great city of Mutantis was destroyed, and why?
Because they misused slack.
They thought they could wear slack.
Turns out that...
But you must ask yourself, what is too much slack?
Is there such a concept as too much slack?
Never.
Is there ever too big a bowl of cereal that you can't eat before you go to bed?
No!
There's not too much slack, friends, but there is false slack,
or slack focused in the wrong places.
The wrong parts of the body can exude a type of slack that is unseemly.
And how does one recognize wrongful slack, you might ask, my dear friends?
Well, the fact is that when wrongful slack occurs, you don't need to ask.
You know it's wrong.
Oh, you can tell.
You feel the wrongness of it.
That's most slackly known.
The unclean, slimy...
Crawling wrongness on it.
Crawling in reptile flesh upon the bosom of the ground.
And you want to flee back to Bob's bosom.
The eye of man, a little narrow orb closed up and dark.
510-848-4425.
That's the number of the beast!
The great light communicating with the void.
The devil, he's here.
He's among us.
The devil owns this world.
He owns this world.
He owns this building.
He owns KPFA.
Wait.
But he don't own Bob.
He owns all Berkeley.
Wait.
All of California is owned by...
He owns you, but he don't own Bob.
Well, I don't own to that.
He owns Bob.
He owns this whole hemisphere.
Wait.
Owns Deuce Trace Couture.
The devil...
He owns the whole world.
The devil, my friend, owns you.
But he owns J.R. Bob Dobs.
He owns the whole world in his hands.
Oh, my God.
He's down by his...
Glove and hoof and his forked tail.
You are the devil's payment to Bob, my friend.
That is your role on this planet.
That is why you were brought to this planet.
To have pure slack.
To squirt or ooze in sexful sex urge.
And to further Bob's plan by being part of his payment from the devil.
The devil is handing your soul over to Bob.
Praise Bob.
I gave my soul...
Where would you rather be?
In the devil's back pocket or in Bob's?
Bob's playing pocket pool with your soul right now.
I was wondering what was jiggling around and jiggling...
I want you to rejoice.
I want you to feel that slack rising up.
Oh, my God.
I can feel it.
I want you to feel the power.
Coming through these radio waves tonight.
I want you to feel that slack.
And I want you to praise Bob.
That's right.
Praise Bob.
How did I ever get mixed up in this horrible, slimy religion?
Party!
You're some genius heretic.
It rings true.
What about these line items that I'm going to say?
Where do all these pockets go?
What about these line items?
Do I have to constantly be bringing them?
I'm going to give you back to the line items.
The space bankers see every bit of this.
If you can tell me what the secret word is...
You'll talk about anything but the line items.
And that's why we are gathered for this business meeting.
You'll talk about anything but the budget.
Why we've got the mental stability of a peanut.
All we can do is just wander around aimlessly.
One tangent to another.
And all we want to do is just go over these line items one by one.
Look, look, look, look.
Examining each of them.
We'll trim every one of them in the minutest detail.
As we consumed our special meal of gruel and some genius biscuits.
Yes, meat biscuits.
They're much like pemmican.
We learned this special recipe from our Native American brothers.
Brought it forth.
And revealed it to us, the subgeniuses.
And that's why we eat it at this special occasion of Stanksgiving.
Out of your honey.
Well, Stanksgiving was actually yesterday.
And that was most enjoyable.
The food was quite good.
Well, mention it.
Well, I thought I'd be quite good myself.
But that's, you know...
And beholding of the time of...
Stanksgiving is...
The time of...
Pee.
And put...
Pee dog and poop dog.
We must remember that together...
Kind of the Jesuits of the church.
We can bring the church into the future.
It's so easy to satisfy these guys.
We can have our budget and our line items.
And the e-pump too.
We can have the special recreational vehicles.
Hey, is this the subgenius radio show?
Yeah.
Yeah, the...
Talk about that.
That's the gobo fam.
It is gobo fam.
They have a subgenius radio show in my sector and no one showed up.
Well, we waited for you to play some song about sharkies.
You showed up to be there to know if my subgenius shows live.
How can you even listen to this show?
I wasn't listening.
I was chasing my turkey.
It got away.
She got some sharkies.
Damn, that thing was fast.
Why didn't you put the blow torch to it like you said?
You gotta kill it first.
That's a thing.
Now, did you pull the feathers out before it got away?
No.
We were just trying to pacify it so that it would die for us.
You didn't want to tell her that you were going to kill her and cook her and eat her.
That's the problem.
You can't pacify a turkey.
They never satisfied.
I said, please, little bird, die so I can eat you.
I'm your friend.
Hey, would you pull my finger?
The Turkodopteryx is a hearty beast.
Did you experience turkinosis?
I was...
So, a turkinosis?
Yes.
It was stuck in my nose.
Well, you're...
You tried showing it to them.
Both of them.
More turkey speaking than...
Oh, gosh.
It was terrible.
I tried so hard to get to Berkeley and I swam, I rode, I paddled, I surfed, and I still
didn't get there.
Why didn't you try to take a car?
Talking about simply this...
I'm sorry.
I'm just...
You know...
You didn't say that.
That's what I said.
There was a sign on the freeway.
You didn't say that.
You tried to say the word turkey.
There was a huge sign.
It said, KPFA that way, not you, Gary.
Oh.
Oh, that sign.
It took us 20 minutes to put that sign up.
Well, you know, I was coming up here all this time and I only had one question.
I only noticed that sign about two weeks ago.
I got the air in there all this time.
Yeah, I read it for hours and I just couldn't figure out whether it was me or whether it
was the turkey, but the turkey did take a turn the other way at the sign and I was...
Oh, it was awful.
Oh, my soul.
I think they call it the rapture of the road.
Oh, okay.
Hey, are you guys talking turkey?
So you've been Gary?
Gary?
Is that a turkey?
Is this kid a turkey?
Are you a turkey?
Gary?
Oh, it's a turkey.
fut, are you a turkey?
Were you a turkey when you were in school?
You know, I'm a turkey.
You know, I was good.
The subgenius hour of slack.
Yes, the subgenius hour of slack is what you've been hearing.
And if you want to hear and or read or even feel more,
there's plenty of it at subgenius.com
or actually at any library that has the book of the subgenius or Revelation X.
Meanwhile, we're at this address.
Friends, you got your pencil ready?
We're at Post Office Box 181417.
That's subgenius at P.O. Box 181417, Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
The background music has all been from their new album, Blue Marble,
The Flying Ryan Brothers.
And you can get more Flying Ryan.
Ryan Brothers information at Ryanetics.com.
Sort of like Dianetics, but it's R-Y-A-N-etics.com.
Friends, they hail from Des Plaines, Illinois, however that's pronounced.
And now, the news.
Hello, this is Shouting.
Welcome to PRTR.
We're talking about a brand new book that's titled The Ick Ick Girl.
And I see you all the time.
And I heard a loud voice saying in heaven,
How are we going to cum?
Listen to me, friend.
Here's how we're going to cum.
And they came by the blood of the Lamb.
And they love their cums.
How?
First of all, shed cum to Jesus.
Come to him and say,
People today, they are all perverted in some way.
Why?
Because they is perverts.
It makes me perverted.
The animals are perverts.
God wants you to be like him.
God wants you to enjoy eternal cum with perverts like him.
Now, let's cum.
How are we going to cum?
Say, Pastor, lay it out there.
The wrong parts of the Bible.
The body can exude a type of slack that is unseemly.
Okay, below are the earnings per share of the Subgenius Foundation.
Oh, my God.
That's all mine now, isn't it?
I need that money for a good cum.
Boy, you'd better get down here.
We're really in a pickle.
We're in a financial situation.
We're in a hole.
You've got to come through for us.
This whole church is going to go down in a spiral, down the drain, into the sewer.
Well, if Gary's here, we have a problem.
A quorum.
The carpet.
Well, the...
A quorum?
We do have a quorum.
We've got some gherkins here.
I mean, we're really in a pickle.
So what does that mean, like nine?
I know.
That means we can fuck anything.
I can tell you're in the pickle because the seeds are falling out of your ears.
Yeah, well, that shows about how much trouble we're in.
So get the banker on the phone and get him down here before two hours.
We're sending our seed out of our ears.
We've got the armored car carrier coming around the back.
Oh, good, good.
I'll put the armored car in it.
Yeah.
And we'll carry it away.
Right.
Do you think there's enough room left in there for my turkey?
I just thought go left again.
I don't know if the stockholders would...
You know, if we can get the turkey to turn left twice more, I'll be at the station.
All right.
Bring your firearms.
Bring everything you've got.
AK-47s.
Oh, is that little Michael there?
How about A.O.
Hippie?
That's little Michael.
I do recognize him as little Michael.
Now I'm glad I didn't.
Yeah, but the real question I have is can we get into Dino Island for free still?
Yeah, you can get into Dino Island.
It's still there.
Of course.
That's where we're going now.
We can still go into Dino Island.
Are you sure about that?
I'm going to retire you.
No way.
Treasure Island, you mean?
Yeah.
There's no Dino Island.
No, that's over in the city.
Yes, there is.
You just don't know about it.
Oh, damn it.
It's Wino Island that I want to go to.
Oh, now it's changed entirely.
You go back there, it's very depressing.
The tourist winos have taken over.
The dinosaurs are on a reservation.
That's right.
We've dressed the suits.
We've dressed the tourists in suits.
And then we sit in the chairs and shake ourselves until we're still able.
Well, that's one alternate universe.
Much trouble as you want now because they can't get me for your troubles.
You're in over your head now.
I am in over my head.
In fact, it's double over my head.
Dr. Sorokin, the renowned sociologist at Harvard says...
That the show should stop right now.
What?
Just go home.
Stop hurting people's brains like this.
My goodness.
That was almost my end, wasn't it?