Beautiful.
In the Peter Lewis...
Oh, hey, say, uh, this is Mark Osler of Negative Plan,
and you're listening to the Hour of Slack.
I don't need to say it, you just said it.
Did you get all of it?
Well, there we go, that's it.
Did you get all of it? Did you get all of it?
That would be a good version to use.
Yeah, I guess so.
It really would. It really would be a good version.
3, 2, 1, 0, 4.
Dint-stink, trash bag, shatterproof glass.
Tailpipe, trunk light, piece of chrome.
Fuma, muffler, universal bearing.
Aerial brake, shoe, shock absorber.
Come on!
3, 2, 1, 0.
Fast-train, air-fueled, oily, rag-toothed.
Van-belt, flywheel, left-arm rest-toothed.
Crank-shaft, tire-jagged, rear-view mirror-toothed.
Coil-string, piston ring, rubber-foam, die-toothed.
Come on!
3, 2, 1, 0.
Plug, nut, need-a-vap, dashboard, padding.
Hubcap, rotor, red-shield, wiper.
Big hand, little hand, radio dial-toothed.
Front seat, back seat.
Air conditioner.
Come on!
3, 2, 1, 0.
Rubber hose, rocker hose, digital sonometer.
Spark, blood gas, cap, cigarette lighter.
Headrest, retread, registration.
Floor man, fire one, set a rate of pedal.
2.
Come on!
3, 2, 1, 0.
Flow-grade radiator, colloidal wire.
Cleaner, static, trans-manic fluid.
Headlines, seatbelts, under-cover.
And a bumper sticker that says...
No other possibility!
You're listening to a free audio sample from the top 10 proofs that Bob is the only true religion.
After listening to this sample, we hope you'll consider purchasing this CD to hear the rest of the evidence showing Bob is the only true religion.
Thank you.
And enjoy your free sample.
The subgenius.
Power of the free.
Okay, hi.
So, my name is Bob.
And, um, um, uh, I do Bob.
I actually don't have a son.
Uh, which is, um, yeah, um, um, us, us, us, us, um, and it says, gorgeous.
You're a genius.
I was like, I am Bob.
I am Bob, do you see?
Bob, do you see?
Um, uh, um, I didn't have any.
What?
That's true.
It's a very true statement.
I love Bob.
Um, and then, uh, oh, and, um, uh, move PR.
Uh, oh, by the way, I'm not Bob anymore.
Um, uh, um, um, um, um, hello.
And, um, uh, um, um, and I was like, oh, I was like, oh, um, um, um, um, um, um, yeah.
Bye.
Sadly this has led to art and sport and politics
Being led by people illiquid to dreams
There was a group who could have saved us from this ignominy
There was a group and they were roundly ignored
They saw the future and they pointed out the problems
If the people took the point we'd now be reaping the rewards
Devo was right about everything
Devo were telling the truth
Devo was sure to slap you
If you have ever raged against conformity
Or hate the way our leaders treat us with sport
You see society regress before your very eyes
Devo was on your side before you were born
Devo was right about everything
Devo, I proved the world wrong
Come and sing with us everyone
Devo was right about everything
Devo, we'll call it correct
And the such deserves a lifespan
How many people here tonight believe in de-evolution?
It's real
And we just came to remind you
Are we not a myth?
We are the Devo
Devo was right about everything
Devo was never in the wrong
Devo was looking for his song
Because it's us they were right about everything
And if that's true then we're really all doomed
So in 30 seconds turn this music up
And go on into what Devo would do
Devo, Devo, Devo
Devo was right about everything
I know, you don't have to look very far for the evidence
Well, around 1979 I was finishing up
The very first Devo song
The very first Church of the Subgenius pamphlet
And these friends of mine kept telling me
Hey, we saw this band on Saturday Night Live
And you better check them out
Because it's a lot like the stuff you're doing
And I went, yeah, sure
Then I saw them and went, good lord
This is a lot like the stuff we're doing
And on top of that their first album came out
With that picture of Chi-Chi Rodriguez
Which people continually still think
Is somehow Bob's
And Bob was copied off of that
But they were quite independent
So I think when their second album came out
They had a fan club address
And I sent them the first Subgenius pamphlet
And was shocked to get a response
Mark Mothersbaugh wrote me back a little postcard
That made it clear that he had really studied
Our little pamphlet and was intrigued
So I sent him a couple of underground films
That I had made for him
And I sent him a couple of underground films
That I had done as a teenager
That had stop motion and claymation type stuff
Including G.I. Joe's and Barbie's raping each other
And they saw that and went
We're about to do a scene for Love Without Anger
With the G.I. Joe and Barbie
You know, a Ken and Barbie fight
And can you do it by next weekend for a thousand bucks?
And I said, yes!
And I did
It was a hell of a deal getting it done
But that's what I did
That was my first job for them was that
And at some point the Subgenius business
Took us to Los Angeles
And I ended up hanging out with Mark
And staying at his house
And got to know just how funny
The guys in the band are
I've actually always thought that
In a way they missed their calling
I mean, they're great weirdo rock stars
But they're also great comedians
Those guys are really, really funny
And I always used to think
Well, they should have taken over Merv Griffin's show
applause
music
music music
She's out of sync
And everyone around her
Knows that something is wrong
She's out of sync
She's got all the symptoms
Of a girl who's simply
She's out of sync
A piece of ancient history
She's a walking barrage
She's out of sync
She has to do the exits
And never stop to think
She's out of sync
She's a half step behind
She's out of love, the money's split from her mind
She's out of orbit, she'll never connect
She'll run out of time, before she accepts
She's out of sleep
And everybody senses, there's a distance to keep
And totally committed, to living in a dark age
She's out of sleep
And constantly undoing, what's already been done
Trapped in a silent movie, and she's on the brink
She's out of focus, she's a warped in mind
She's discontinued
A break in the mind
She's out of orbit, she'll never connect
She'll run out of time, before she accepts
She's out of sleep
Sleep
And everyone around her
Knows that something is wrong
She's out of sleep
She's got all the symptoms
Of a girl who skipped a beat
She's out of sleep
A piece of ancient history
She's a walking barrage
She's out of sleep
She entered through the exit
And never stopped to think
She's out of sleep
She's a hamster behind
She's out of luck, her body's split from her mind
She's out of focus, she's a warped in mind
She's discontinued, a break in the line
She's out of orbit, she'll never connect
She'll run out of time, before she excites
She's out of sleep, sleep
She's out of sleep
Now it can be told, we're all Devo.
Well, not all. This hour of Slack number 1221 is all covers, but not all covers of Devo.
And a lot of it is from the Devotional of 2009 in Cleveland,
or the Not Necessarily Beautiful Book.
A mutated yearly collection of Devo covers, but not all of it.
For instance, we have Little Theodore covering Joni Mitchell,
and a doo-wop acapella soul band covering Negative Land.
In fact, that's what started the show.
The 180Gs covering Car Bomb,
followed by Lemur titles and, um,
Intro Collage by The Large.
The song Devo Was Right About Everything,
original song by The Attery Squash,
but remixed by Bob and Jerry Casale of Devo.
There are and will be clips from an interview with yours truly for a Devo documentary.
And finally, what we just heard was Spud Boys,
recorded live at the 2008 Devotional from the Not Necessarily Beautiful Collection, volume 2009.
And now, once again, the 180Gs covering Negative Land's theme from a Big Ten 8 place.
Thank you.
Alright, we got another one for you.
Here we go.
Tommy
Everybody welcome.
One, two, stupid
Three, four, dumb
Five, six, innocent
Yachty
Seven, eight, sixty, six
Very stupid
Very rude
I like Concord
Big 180Gs
I like pleasant here
Know all the possibilities
Stupid
Very stupid
No other possibilities
Stupid
Very large
Very, very well
I like Orlando
I like a l 있어요
This is four or nine
I like my genius
And all the green slides
I like Lafayette
The weather is fine
And I like country coast and county
Almost all the time
1, 2, stupid
3, 4, dumb
5, 6, idiotic
7, X, E, P, Z
Stupid, very stupid
Very stupid, very stupid
Very stupid
This is it
We're gonna do it right now
Here we go
Alright people
First of all
I want you to raise your hand
If your automatic garage door opener is stuck
Stupid, very stupid
Very stupid, very stupid
I want you to stand on your left leg
If your oscillating sprinkler system doesn't work
Well, well
Very stupid, very stupid
I want you to grab your right foot
With your left hand
If your load is full
Stupid, very stupid
I want you to shake your head
If you like your neighbors
New and misfit
I want you to put parakeet feathers into your television set
If you're watching MTV
MTV
Stupid, very stupid
Katie
I want you to do it so you can hear my words
I want you to trip over your gross cart.
If you're shopping, save money.
I want you to go back into your house and get all your furniture.
Thank you very much, ladies and gentlemen, the 180Gs.
We've had a lovely time with you this evening, and we hope to see you all again very soon.
Keep it stupid, y'all.
A beautiful and fairy mutated from the 180Gs.
They have a CD out on Sealand Media Media, an entire CD of truly different versions of, like, one song each from every Negative Land album, called 180 OGs to the Future.
That is a bonus disc that comes with Negative Land's just amazing new DVD collection, Our Future.
Favorite things seen at NegativeLand.com.
180Gs are six guys from Detroit, and you'll be hearing a lot more of them on future hours of Slack.
Meanwhile, back to this year's NNBBM Devo tribute CD, of which there are only a couple of dozen copies left,
and this cover tune by our old friends Occupant of MySpace.com slash Occupant.
I heard a girl from L.A.
Say she'd go all the way.
I heard there's no reason why.
I heard that now's the time to buy.
On planet Earth.
I'm on the stay.
It's a place to live your life.
We're better for the pain.
People go insane.
Fly around in planes.
Pray that it won't rain.
Drive around in cars.
Get drunk and local bars.
Dream of being stars.
Well, I'm a star.
I live on the high on planet Earth.
I heard a girl from Ohio.
Say I bought bread at a hole.
I saw her try to catch the man.
Things I couldn't understand.
I'm on planet Earth.
Say she'd go all the way.
нед
I saw a man on the stage
Scream!
Put me back in the cage
I saw him hate by his diet
I saw him up and make me cry
I'm bad at love
I live all my life
Devo, like the Monkees and a few other bands,
were created by Bob Dobbs as experiments in marketing.
Which is always kind of hellish for whoever the musicians are
when they're a manufactured product.
But Devo seemed to take the ball and run with it.
At least that's the lie we tell.
The lie they tell is that Bob Dobbs came to them and said,
you should quit Warner Brothers and sign with these other guys,
which turned out to be the absolute worst decision they ever made.
And then Mark said,
that Bob dragged all their furniture and all their equipment out into the driveway
and set it all on fire and did a big dance.
And that was their experience with Bob Dobbs.
But Bob didn't play with Devo for very long.
He got them into a lot of trouble with some of the groupies' families
because of unpleasantness that he would try to get these young girls and boys to do.
And...
And he wasn't.
He wasn't really a very good keyboard player either.
So they kind of eased him out.
Oh, yeah.
But the on-and-off was terrible.
You know, I mean, I never really actually played with...
An they played with Devo at the top,
Oh, yeah.
So I definitely played with both words.
You know, I came for the
Duke and I played with father place.
I played with both of them.
Devo at the bottom and Bob.
So I'm said,
Okay, relax!
I assume some is issued!
Going to Darby's submission?
Watch him at the time, let them know
All we do is my website
I'm the fucking father!
Yeah!
Oh!
I am the calvary!
If what you said was tough
I am the 100th gal of the type
How long will I fight
By backing with this don't-know-who?
The party in the державу
Because our church is like home
We are like a family
We are all family
All related to the parliament
Oh!
Oh, partially
夯relaی does that
But y'all, c'mon
We ain't härliady!
Thank you.
I really don't know death.
I was going,
I really wanted to end this show
with this gospel bob song
that the Mutant Mountain Boys
sang at the DeVos
but my recording of it just isn't good enough.
It wouldn't do justice.
You can't understand the words, or at least I can't,
but I'm afraid the listeners could,
and for all I know, they say naughty, naughty things in it.
But talk goddish to that girl.
Those girls sing so beautifully,
and I will prove it next week by hook or by crook.
I'll play the new Bob song by the Mutant Mountain Boys.
In the meantime...
In the meantime, well, that was recorded last week,
and this is this week, and I still don't have a better version,
but the last half of my recording is 10 billion,
brilliant, godzillion times better than nothing,
so here it is, the last half of the new Bob song
by the Mutant Mountain Boys.
Now I know I
Ain't no youngin'
One day I'm gonna be old
I got a new job
I got that total, deep old feeling
Now I can't be told
But I got my high five
I got my high five
I got that whole thing
On the bottle
Institute
www.lindaMurray.com
Here's the final
The beginnin'
from the utopedia
In the sky, in the sky, one more time.
In the heavens, the unbroken, by, by, by, by, by.
In the mine of heaven where it came.
In the sky above, in the sky.
Yeah.
I cannot believe what I just heard.
The spirit, oh my God, the spirit.
The spirit of Devo, the spirit of Bob, the spirit of Slack.
The spirit of freedom and happiness, oh yes.
Hey, this is Mark Hosser from Negative Land.
Negative, no.
This is Mark Hosser from Negative Land.
And you're listening to the hour of Slack.
Negative Land.
All I say, I wish I wasn't there.
In 82, you and I've been ostracized.
To talk, computers, networks, download times.
Today, the science that was vilified.
Is part of every cork it stays.
I have learned that there's a school of thought.
Future don't belong to me no more.
My time in the sun has been deferred.
All I say, I wish I wasn't there.
Clear your mind of what has gone before.
Being cool, don't cut it anymore.
A step ahead, you step out from the herd.
All I want, I wish I wasn't there.
You suddenly experience some heavy social change.
The misfits sneaked in through the vents and took hold of the reins.
Don't need excuse to be yourself.
A whole change has occurred.
A beer so chocked out, Carl's now his lot to be in there.
I spent my life becoming all the rage.
A party girl and everyone's cliche.
Now I find that substance is preferred.
In retrospect, I wish I was a nerd.
Subtitles by the Amara.org community
I have learned that there's a school of thought.
The future don't belong to me no more.
My time in the sun has been deferred.
All I say, I wish I wasn't there.
How do you tell a nerd from a geek?
Maybe I should ask the intellectual elite.
Now that's the kind of thinking that will make me in this world.
Successful?
These days requires your nerd.
You have learned that there's a school of thought.
The future don't belong to you no more.
Your time in the sun has been deferred.
All you've made for your wish but you were nerd.
In your mind, a world known before.
Being cruel, don't try it anymore.
You step ahead, you step up on the road.
Suddenly, you wish that you were nerd.
I have learned that there's a school of thought.
The future don't belong to me no more.
My time in the sun has been deferred.
All I say, I wish I wasn't there.
Subtitles by the Amara.org community
An original song, not a cover from an upcoming album by the Attery Squirrels.
A song by the Reverend Diva Schematic Singing.
Myspace.com. The Attery Squash.
Just oozing with slack and certainly on topic and I should know.
Anyway, back to the not necessarily beautiful but mutated 2009 collection
with a song by Reema, R-H-E-M-A, Myspace ReemaScan
doing the very early pre-Warner Brothers Devo song, Subaz Hardcore.
Ah, my fingers.
Top song at time to the second part of the show
That ends in B Bائy
Pout Smunk
Steve Munkle
Pretty Munkle
everybody
They want a toilet, same old story, she don't let no one near it
The way she teases them is such a shame
She's got all the humans crying her name
Surbows, surbows
She's got them howling, she's got them growling
She's got them going clean out of their minds
Surbows, surbows
There ain't a man in town who wouldn't have her for his daughter
They'd trade the brains for one taste of her toilet water
The way she teases them is such a shame
She's got all those humans crying her name
Surbows, surbows
One, two, three, four, tell the people what you wore
They run in circles trying to call her up
But her phone's been disconnected since she sold her butt
The way she teases them is such a shame
She's got all those humans crying her name
Surbows, surbows
She's got them howling, she's got them growling
She's got them going clean out of their minds
Surbows, surbows
Surbows
Lookin' at her snap strictly as a
Sprut reality
Lookin' at her strapğl
She's got good pictures !
Cherie, cut the crap off
Thespeaker !!
Jeder wünschte, er spiele für sie.
Aber die eine, die er dabei meinte,
Ja, diese eine, die hörte ihn nie.
Marie, Marie, wo magst du nur sein?
Lass deinen Will nicht allein.
Dass er die Liebste für immer verlor.
Ein fremder Cowboy, der kam nach El Paso,
Sah nur Marie und schon war es geschehen.
Am andern Morgen, da war er verschwunden,
Und auch Marie hat man nie mehr gesehen.
Marie, Marie, wo magst du nur sein?
Lass deinen Will nicht allein.
Noch ist es Zeit für ein Glück in El Paso,
Morgen schon kann es zu spät dafür sein.
Oh Marie, oh Marie, komm doch wieder zurück nach El Paso,
So geht sein Lied in das Dunkel hinaus.
Aber der Nacht ist zu spät, der Nacht ist zu spät,
Der Nachtwind, der gibt ihm die Antwort.
Lass doch das Träumen, du weißt, es ist aus.
Bill spielt noch immer von Glück und von Treue,
Immer noch glaubt er an seine Marie.
Doch eines Tages, da schweigt die Gitarre,
Denn seine Träume erfüllen sich nie.
Lass mon frèreitched saisonner de mosque
N'apprens relieved,
That meant 12 minutes by drive while open drive
The block is so cool it'll make my food for people pray
White bloods, go big messes, and gloomy is the plan
The evolution, the self execution, no solution
I'm a potato and I'm so hot
See that show up in the standing line of droning blood to pay for crime
Put your seal and guard your jewels so free hand
And don't you lose
Free white resistance in the mail
And parties going down the stairs
All the sunbeams, what's the cost of my downhills
But all is lost in the evolution
Self execution, no solution
I'm a lost and stoned man and I'm a potato
I'm so hot
Smooth as shit
The size of earth for someone to fiend
He's mine, gone to crime
Spotted in the
Look like a boss, trying to save the chaunну
They touch and roll to a second round
Rockets blast the cacade
It's all my loss, they spread the plague
The penny zero drops the crown
Go down, go down, go down
To the T-Mobile John
Someone secure John
Down's the ocean
I'm a spud gun
My gun's a good gun
I'm a good gun
Icebreaking...
Ice Turkey...
First beat.
Truly devolved another ancient Devo song
pre-conspiracy record label called
I'm a Potato redone by our old buddy
St. Byron Werner and Donovan's suit
of Rural War Room.
Rural War Room records at myspace.com.
That also was from the not necessarily beautiful
but mutated album of which there are maybe
ten left available.
For information write Rev Wilder
at neo.rr.com
or see myspace.com NNBBMV8
with a peer-reviewed version of
after each letter except the V.
Truly a subgenius URL.
The church of the subgenius URL is subgenius.com
and you can also find these links and shows there.
You can find everything there.
Oh and the German language version of El Paso
was by Lolita from Lolita's Greatest German Hits
from my late mom's record collection.
Now back to the devotional.
Slack is what moves.
The church of the subgenius does guarantee
your death.
The great thing is we won't tell you what Slack is.
You have to figure out what your Slack is.
All we're doing is giving you a pep talk
and in my opinion that's what Devo has always done.
It has provided a pep talk
for the lonesome weirdos,
the mutants, misfits, disbelievers
and those who don't believe anything out there.
Hey RK, little girl down here in the front.
I'm going to tell you a story.
RK said he thought that being rich was the point
of the church of the subgenius.
Oh no, no, not at all.
Bob being more rich is the point of the church of the subgenius.
I just...
Slack is related to money.
And it might be easier to get Slack if you become rich.
Depending on what your idea of Slack is.
But I know a lot of people who are bored.
They are bored and rich.
They are the most Slack-less mothers on this globe.
Inheriting money is a curse.
And I say this from experience, not because I did,
but because by weird chance I went to one of those private schools
where most of the people I was in school with had inherited money.
And over the years I've watched them get more miserable
and more miserable because they couldn't connect
with what's really going on.
But with the rest of us who have to find some way
of passing for normal.
That's what rich people don't have to learn.
They never have to learn to pass.
Those of us who had to get a job had to learn to pass for normal.
Now, imagine being gay in the old days,
and in lots of places still,
and you had to pass as if you were straight.
And I spent a lot of time having to act like,
oh yeah, that last Cowboys game,
I didn't know what the hell the last Cowboys game was about.
I never paid any attention to that crap.
I'm a mutant.
I'm a misfit.
I'm a weirdo.
I puke on Christmas.
So, after a while I got to where I adopted the one rule
in the Church of the Subgenius,
which is, I do mom them if they can't take a joke.
And you can live by that rule.
You really can.
There came a day when some redneck in Texas said,
who helped out them Cowboys?
And I looked at him and something snapped.
And I said, man, I'm one of those queer faggots
that doesn't watch football, okay?
And boy, that made me feel great.
But anyway, friends,
the point is we all have to learn to pass one way or another.
The trick is to not become what you're pretending to be.
They can't read your mind.
You can pretend that you're interested in that job,
or you might even be.
There's nothing wrong with that.
I actually have a job that I enjoy.
But the important thing is to not confuse
what you're pretending to be with what you really are.
Hang on to your perversions,
your twisted sickness,
the thoughts that you don't feel like you should tell anybody.
You probably shouldn't.
But don't forget them.
Because that's what makes you you,
and that is where your slack comes from.
Ad adelante.
At one point, I realized that those guys, their mom was a music teacher.
It's like, that's cheating.
I thought they were geniuses or something.
No, they just had music hammered into them from the very beginning.
No wonder they tried to destroy music.
It all adds up now.
It's like, they just had music hammered into them from the very beginning.
Pprofessional
is THIS
are they just some leftoverszy?
were возможers stops trying to rule the world??
how much money would be that Çok
but I'm thinking about you
I had anybody
how you would I see you
I've never been
are you
how can I
f
up
im not gonna report
Turner
Okay, let's go.
Let's go.
Wilhelm Stahlhelm did that.
That's Wilhelm Stahlhelm at hotmail.com.
Before that, the excerpt of Be Stiff was the Weird Paul Rock Band
recorded at the Devotional.
The background music here is by Ron Slabe's Pyrosonics,
the album Pyrotopia, seen at MySpace slash Pyrosonic Music.
Praise Devo, praise Little Theodore, praise Negative Land,
and all the bands, and praise Bob.
¶¶