This portion of programming is brought to you by Bob's Steakhouse on the corner of Pursuit and Flushing in beautiful Stane, California.
Come on down to Bob's and get a mouthful of meat from the man himself.
If you'd like to make a reservation, please call 1-800-555-13013.
Most young people will continue through life as normal, responsible citizens.
Others, the shunted and unloved, the unguided, the seekers of thrills and kicks, are candidates for the slave world of lifelong...
How does it happen? Where does it start? What are the signs?
The pattern is generally the same.
Bob?
Take a look.
The lack of responsibility, the inability to make right choices, add to it ignorance and indifference, and top it off with a desire for escapism and kicks.
The sum total is then...
The subgenius.
Power of...
Swatch.
This is the real action.
This is the test.
The time to separate the man from the boy.
Willpower, individuality, character are slipping down the drain.
In their place comes Bob.
In the time of a new era, they've had their fair share of
They're a lot more surrealistic sounding, and surrealism is really quite critical.
But I like the fact of having so much Bob taking up all that room.
Of course, another thing I like about Bob is that they make special records just for Bob equipment.
Special effects like sounds from the very deep parts of the Bob.
And you can get these Bob records only for Bob.
When you finally do get Bob dead and everyone can hear that low-pitched Bob.
barking at them from a mile beneath the ocean.
People look up to you, and I guess I really go for that feeling of scare.
You see, a man of Bob is like a deep-sea diver.
He must be afraid to walk down where it's dark and frightening
in the hopes of scooping up a handful of shat-shat-shat.
What did you want to tell us about Bob?
I've made the obvious deductions they don't seem to add up.
A few minutes ago, I saw the incredible, the unbelievable.
But what I saw Bob do a few minutes ago
is something for which there is no name, unless you can name it.
I can't name it. I can't, can't, can't name it.
Jim, Jim, Jim E.
Bob, Bob, Bob has been able through to shat-shat-shat a man's mind.
Another man's boy to walk through a lock voice to allow gate.
I don't understand.
Do you know why we bring people to this place?
No.
We bring them here to cure them, to make them sane.
Nobody that we bring here ever leaves our hands uncared.
Good.
Why don't you kill me?
You're rid of the religious persecutions of the past.
They were failures.
They set out to eradicate heresies and they ended by perpetuating them.
We do not make that mistake.
We perpetuate heresies and perpetuate heresies and perpetuate heresies and...
Why bother?
You are a flaw in the pattern.
You are a stain which has to be wiped out.
We do not convert the heretic.
We destroy him.
We capture his inner mind.
We reshape him.
We burn.
Step by step to the point from which there is no return.
This portion of programming is brought to you by Bob's Meats.
Whether it's a lovely rump roast or a beautiful tube steak you're looking for,
come to Bob's on the corner of Spunk and Main in beautiful downtown Persnickety.
Ask about our special deals if you buy by the ton.
Come on down to Bob's where job one is getting our meat into your mouth.
You know this...individual?
Sure do, Reverend.
He's my friend.
Aural.
You know full well that you should never trust Bob.
Gee, do you really think he's...
Of course.
Listen to that accent.
Aural, your friend...
Bob.
Is not a proper Christian.
Gee.
How do you know, Reverend?
Well, look at him, Oral.
I mean...
Well...
He obviously believes in subgenius.
Subgenius?
I'll take it from here, folks.
Ahem.
That's right, Oral. Subgenius.
It's a clever combination of the words sub and genius.
Huh?
Oh yeah.
Subgenius is the most simplistic way of disproving subgenius,
while at the same time proving subgenius.
Subgenius is so simplistic that even the lowest form of life can understand it.
I have bad incompetence.
My incompetence all went down my britches, and I'm all bad on incompetence.
Let us take another delusion of yours.
You believe you had in your hands a photograph of Bob?
I did have it.
You believe it?
You believe it was some sort of documentary evidence?
How can you control the memory?
You haven't controlled mine.
On the contrary, you haven't controlled it.
That is why you're here.
You've been lacking in humility and self-discipline.
You must make an effort of the will and rehabilitate your mind.
Then you will be sane.
But first, you must be humble.
Do you remember writing in that diary of yours that freedom is the freedom to say that two plus two makes Bob?
How many fingers am I holding out?
And if the state says not Bob, what else can I say?
Bob?
Take him.
Jesus Christ.
Jesus Christ, Charles.
Have you been asleep at the switch?
Let's roll.
Why, has he got his arm on...
Bob?
You're with that ugly fuck and your own free fucking whale, doc?
Yes, yes I am.
I'd rather be lucky than smart.
Bomb, slag, bomb, slag
Oh my god, what the fuck is this shit?
Bomb, bomb, slag
Mom, Dad, it's 8 o'clock!
Oh boy, my new favorite show!
And now may I present for your entertainment
On the Sabbath at midnight for your amusement there will be a masquerade
The wardrobes of the castle are yours to use
But I beg of you, even for the humor of it, do not wear
Bob
You go too far
I am not without influence and power
Against Bob?
Yes
Yes, Bob came to the village
Even now, Bob lays waste the countryside
So you can count yourself out
I was fortunate that you were here
For X day dawned and set
With all of us still here
With still a little bit more time
Given to us by the grace of fate
To clean up our mess and do our laundry
And nobody prepared
And so it will be on that great day
When the sea gives up its dead
And monsters walk the earth
That nobody will be prepared
And will have even bothered to destroy
His pornography collection
To keep from influencing whatever posterity may remain
Bob's in the kitchen with Bob
What did you think? Too sensationalistic?
Or maybe it wasn't sensationalistic enough?
Oh, no, not you too
Did you hear it?
Hear what?
Someone's in the kitchen with Bob
You're so excited about being back in the air
You've completely fallen under Bob's evil spell
I have no idea what you're talking about
All I'm doing is getting on the air
And giving people the straight dope about Bob
The revolution will be broadcast
I'll leave you to your pirate nerd radio
Someone's in the kitchen with Bob
oughta i mean there's a fine line between eccentricity and downright suicidal foolhardiness
I know I walked that line every saturday night
Bob's in the kitchen with Bob
Every saturday night
Bobby's in the kitchen with Bob
There's a fine line between
Bob's in the kitchen with Bob
Too sensationalistic
Bob's in the kitchen with me
Did you hear it?
Let's get over to the damn bar.
I'm going to need a drink to get through this.
We interrupt this program to bring you a news bulletin.
High government sources have ceased to deny the presence in many parts of the country
of non-terrestrial objects.
We return you now to the starlight terrace of the Hotel Gamalodians, Scranton,
to the singing glory, oh glory, oh glory, oh and his melodians.
Another bulletin, ladies and gentlemen.
Your latest word of the monsters from outer space.
Correction.
Bob.
Sorry, folks, that's what experts are saying.
They are Bob, Bob, Bob.
State Highway.
Ladies and gentlemen, a special news flash from Washington.
Any moment now, the president will be receiving a delegation from Bob.
From Bob.
Peace talks are expected.
A woman, you just have to believe this,
rushed into a police station out in San Francisco with her clothes in tatters
to report that she'd been...
repeatedly attacked by...
Bob, Bob, Bob.
She tried to take poison for the shame of it,
and they stopped her just in time.
I can't describe...
Bob.
She said, Bob's hell.
Somebody down in South America did an imitation of...
Bob, Bob, Bob.
And he ended up in prison.
I've been kind of alone.
I don't have a lot of friends,
so to have a buddy who lives in the same house,
and now Peter's here,
and Bob's here.
Well, I guess it's not fair to count Bob.
You know, he's, you know, one of those...
funny guys.
Funny guy.
Walks into a cabin, goes right up the chimney,
cleans out a flue.
I have seen dumb luck in my time.
I have seen a guy fill an inside straight flush
to beat four races.
I have seen a guy hit the daily double
for two solid weeks straight.
But I have never, at no time,
seen nothing like...
Bob.
This was later, of course,
when everything was finally hanging out.
Or as much of it as I guess
any of us will ever get to see.
Then we had to stop time
and use a time machine.
And then roll back and come in again.
To the days when Bob
was just a researcher
into someone else's fakery.
My personal feelings about Bob
are very mixed.
He has developed a fiction about his life.
And to destroy that fiction
would tear down the whole castle
that he's built of his illusions.
The illusion, for example,
that he has not broken any law.
Several months ago,
I read an article
about Bob.
And I was so impressed
that I decided to come from Minnesota
in the hope of meeting Bob.
And now,
I've become
his bodyguard.
He takes his duties seriously.
Bob himself swears that he goes in daily dread
of being murdered.
This takes us into murky waters
where the lawyers tell us we'd be rash
to go fishing.
There's just a hint or two
about this violence and danger
as a result of which
Bob, on top of all his other troubles,
is being sued for $55 million worth of slander.
Bob.
Interesting question.
Is Bob being sued for telling a pack of lies?
Then I guess you can keep right on through the looking glass
and believe that the book about Bob
is a pack of truth.
That Bob himself
is a fake.
Fake.
Let's leave it all alone.
I am stupidest when I try to be funny.
Yeah, I know what you mean, Al.
Okay, speaking of stupid and funny,
Dave?
Yes?
That's what I thought.
Okay, everything's cool.
Everything's cool.
It's all copacetic.
Calm and collected.
The waves are slow and moving lovely.
There's nothing dangerous or scary
about the show at all anymore.
Now...
There's no birds smashing against the windows.
No children running down the streets screaming.
Oh, shucks.
I was hoping we'd have the children
running through the streets screaming.
Yeah.
So funny.
Well, it's lively.
If you look closely,
you will see a long, long string
of perhaps thousands,
a line of thousands of pig-like human beings.
I mean, they resemble kind of like pigs
as much as they do humans.
And they're all headed for this huge slaughterhouse.
They're all wearing little red beanies
and stuff like that.
Oh, you mean Americans?
Did I say that?
Isn't that what you were describing?
Unfortunately, yes.
Sorry, I laughed out loud.
That's not funny.
I was trying to be funny without, yeah.
It's not funny.
I found it quite entertaining.
Ew.
Sounds squidsy.
Well, um...
Well, I'm...
Dave, are you back in town now?
Am I back in town?
But you are.
Yeah.
As of yesterday or tonight or whatever.
Yes, it was an eventful trip.
This is a live show, by the way,
live at this moment,
although it won't be live by the time...
You hear it.
But yeah, our winter...
We'll be alive by the time we hear this.
Most things will not be alive.
Our missionary outreach was truncated
and cut short by a leaky pipe in the basement
and the neighbor selling a condo
to Princess Wee's mom,
and we were out of money anyway,
and...
And it's all old folks taking a bath.
Taking care of old folks and blind leading the blind.
Yeah.
And people were trying to sell condoms at the same time.
Connie condoms.
Those did not sell.
Condoms?
For elderly people?
We never got a penny of royalties out of that condom company.
Top con it.
I'm not kidding either.
There really was a company.
They had the Bob speech right on them.
Condomania licensed Bob Dobbs and Connie Dobbs
likeness for condoms,
and we are...
We never saw a penny.
Well...
And they don't make them anymore.
It was...
The image was only on the package.
Right.
It didn't get all warped when it was employed.
Yeah.
It wasn't done right.
The...
Well, but still...
Well, was it a delicate object
or perhaps something not so soluble in water
that could have protracted the illness?
Well, the way...
The right way to do a Bob Dobbs condom
would be to print the Dobbs head
on the inside of the condom
and then put it in the condom.
And then you would put the...
you would put the condom per se
in some sort of DMT and DMT...
Whatever that stuff is
that makes it soak into your skin.
Yeah, DMSO.
Right.
I remember what it is.
DMSO, right.
And you would stretch the Dobbs head
over the...
Head?
The scrawny area.
Yeah.
Or the...
The little tiny thing.
And then you'd...
And then it would look bigger, you know.
It would get distorted and twisted
and it would become even more distorted and twisted
as the end of the condom.
And then the ink would sink into your membranes.
Oh, that sounds delightful for the ladies, you know.
Get a little dose of Bob there.
Well, the Connie condom
would have the ink on the outside.
See, I guess to be...
to really get both partners off,
you put on the Bob one
followed by the Connie one.
The Bob one with the ink on the inside
and the Connie one with the ink on the outside.
That's like trying to play with two raincoats on.
Yeah.
Yeah, but we're talking about subgeniuses
and what's the difference.
They're not the most sensitive people in the world,
as you can tell by the way they treat each other.
Oh, I guess.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Yes, that's a valuable lesson to be unheard
is how terribly they treat each other.
Smacking and slapping burbly each other constantly.
That's how they express love.
As if mimicking the monkeys of the wild east
and hanging out with the kind of people
that you couldn't introduce to your parents if you had an ear.
It's just...
But that's true yet you love.
I'm not depressed about it.
I'm just commenting.
That music in the background.
That sounds like the second part of the movement.
And we'll be back after a brief intermission
with Carlos Loves Clingham,
starring with Genia Lowe.
Jean-François Roux as the baritone
and Adolf Hitler as the smiling man.
That was an unusual part for Hitler.
It was.
He was a short of stature.
A lot of neo-Nazis like to make him look 10ft tall,
but he was a scrawny little devil.
Yeah, but he didn't do that many of the smiling man commercials.
No, he was always a frowning man.
Especially after J.R. Bob Dobbs throttled.
Hitler himself in his bunker.
Yes, that is how Hitler actually died.
Killed by the hands of J.R. Bob Dobbs, who hated him.
Because he had refused to buy...
The world would say, by the hands of Bob Dobbs.
Not many people understood what this really meant in the course of human evolution and history.
But you see, when Bob killed Hitler, he unleashed a packet of groin carriers
that live to this day in the backseat of my car.
Do you want to have them groin carriers in your backseat, brother? Sister?
I don't want those groin carriers.
That's why we needed Hitler to expunge the race of himself and all his friends.
Yes, but Bob Dobbs led the genocide of his own people, the subgeniuses, for their own good.
I...
He...
Killed them for their own good.
Indeed it was.
Well, the Inquisition used to do that.
Did you know that many of our leaders in public relations, people like Roger Ailes,
it is now revealed in recent books on the New York Times bestseller list,
that people like Roger Ailes and these other media magnates
are actual students of Lenny Reifenstahl.
And think, hey man, that's the way to do it.
That's what we want to do.
Well, she was a good filmmaker.
She was a very good propagandist.
Well, that's what I'm saying.
She felt bad about it afterwards.
Yeah.
She says.
They all say that.
Yeah.
We did not know.
Lenny Reifenstahl, for listeners who don't know, was the director who did the Triumph of the Will,
the documentary about the Olympics in Germany,
which was done up in...
in good German style.
And by the way, did you know Bob Dobbs appears in that film?
Bob is in the audience in Triumph of the Will
when I think Jesse Owens wins or whatever.
Wasn't that in that?
Oh, I think he was right next to Zelig on that.
Well, no, no.
I mean, that was a different...
You're thinking of a different Olympics.
Timeline?
Yeah, or something.
Zelig was there, but he said...
He's not in the shot that I'm thinking of.
Bob was not...
Bob is kind of like hovering in the background behind some other...
some Russian bigwigs, grinning like a fiend.
Two early SS guys come over and tell him to put that pipe out,
and they trounce him wildly like a pack of suitcases.
No, that wouldn't happen to Bob unless he wanted to be trounced,
because that's the nature of reality is it does whatever Bob happens to be wanting,
just by coincidence.
Isn't that funny?
Lucky, lucky, lucky old Bob.
Doesn't make me cry.
Yeah, it doesn't happen to...
And it happens at our expense.
He saps or siphons the luck off of us, the listeners,
and the yakkers on these shows.
He hurts them.
That's where his slack comes from.
He's an actor.
He hurts them.
Oh, you...
The Church of the Subgenius was mentioned.
Am I allowed to say it by the Federal Department of Agriculture?
Yeah, you said you were listening to actual radio?
Commercial radio with commercials?
Commercial radio.
Lenny Reifenstahl radio, yeah.
Yeah.
And, well, they said they had a guy on who had studied Rabbi Keduri,
and Rabbi Keduri claims that the name of the Messiah might be Jesus.
Not might, but is, according to them.
And he said, well...
Well, how does that make you feel?
Isn't that kind of weird or something like that?
And he goes, well, when Messiah comes and his name is known,
we won't care if his name is Bob.
And then Clyde Davis said, yeah, Church of the Subgenius,
and they both laughed roundly.
Or maybe another geometric shape.
I don't know.
That was on Clyde something's Ground Zero show.
Yes.
He used to have me on his show in the past, back in the day, in the previous century.
I was on his show three times.
I think.
We had a lot of fun.
Did you laugh roundly or rhomboidly?
Well, we didn't talk about...
Yeah, rhomboidly.
Rhomboidly.
We didn't talk about politics.
And apparently, from what Dave says, that's a good thing.
Well, he wants to be like everybody.
On commercial radio.
Yeah.
He wants to be the weird one of the same, you know...
And what about Benghazi, hey?
Hey!
What about the witchcraft?
The Hillary Clinton and Benghazi minions.
Ah, at least your pants are full now, comrade.
You can see clearly.
So full.
And warm.
And smelting.
Look off into the distance.
Thousands of tanks on their way to Cleveland.
There to clean up the dirty work others have left behind.
They're just coming to get that skunk out of our basement.
Which we discovered...
I think I discovered that there is a skunk in our basement
just as we were leaving the house for this show.
Yes, we're currently having a bicker about that.
Yeah, she thinks that the skunk smell is just hovering around
just inside this one part of the house.
And I think the skunk itself is hovering around there.
You may have to call some sort of Russian terror expert
because I guess they're real good at this stuff right now.
And get in there and get that skunk out.
And get him out of there.
Rousting them skunks out.
Well, so far he's been...
I don't think he means to stink us out.
He's down there reading my old National Lampins
and Buff magazines.
And then suddenly he'll...
You know, one of us will slam a lid down in the kitchen
or stomp around or throw a...
A tantrum?
Yeah, a large ironing board or something across the room.
And that startles the skunk.
In our basement.
And he kind of squirts a little bit and goes,
Oh, gosh, I didn't mean to do that.
I don't want him to poison and trap me and get me out of here.
I really like it here.
You better keep it down a little bit.
I just hope he's not making a bed in the children's artwork box.
Oh, my gosh.
That would be terrible.
If Fred and Willie and Janet didn't have enough crayons,
they were all...
Oh, man.
Remember that band, Stinky Crayons?
And the troubles they caused throughout the land.
Well, old folks get to be like that.
Yep.
You know?
When they don't have their crayons or their diapers,
they get all upset.
And as we should know,
because this is the year of the old folks taking care of older folks.
The reason I say that is because I'm one of the old folks.
Me too.
I'm not being taken care of yet.
But I'm now.
Next.
I get the message from God that that's what, you know,
because we're starting to be concerned about our parents.
You know, they're getting on in years.
And I'm 60.
So, oh, well.
Next it'll be me that they have to get the power of attorney form signed.
Dad, you haven't paid your bills in seven years now.
And they're starting to call me.
So sign here and here and here and here.
Oh, thank God.
He signed here and here and here.
Let's take this papers over to the judge and have Reverend Stang sent to the old subgenius home.
Where the blind literally do lead the blind.
Well, they do have the special glasses anyway.
The blind.
I mean, the select few.
You get free Google glasses at the subgenius old.
Yeah.
If you're blind.
So that other people can see what you would have seen during the day.
If they really want to play it back.
Well, I have a brief heartwarming story.
I did a story for a small local newspaper about World War Two veterans telling their tales from World War Two and stuff like that.
And while they're all sitting around, there are a bunch of 90 year old men who were looking at a 50 year old waitress and making noises.
They were saying, is the babe coming back?
Get her to come back.
Give us some more coffee.
She turned around.
They would all look at her derriere.
I was.
I was a healthy old dudes.
How were these guys like in their 70s, 80s?
They were in their 90s.
I said, OK, well, then they're doing well.
I'm still interested in a young 50 year old dame.
She's only 50 years young.
I love that.
More of the story.
I like this story.
It's warming the cockles.
My friend is only 50 years.
Young.
Look, you know, I'm 60 and I don't think 50 is young.
Well, I think 20 is young.
50 is old.
I have thought they're older than most people in this land.
Yeah, I know.
It's clear.
Very clear.
But the part about that got me so thrilled and excited was that these 90 year old gentlemen were really.
I was.
Well, let's put it.
This way.
In many ways, I was chagrined to be at a table where like 90 year olds were popping bees and so forth.
As they say, used to say in high school and pointing like that and making comments and having to keep them quiet.
But on the other hand, I was so salubriated by the entire experience.
It just made me feel like there is something to live for after all.
Yeah.
What?
Great story.
When you're incompetent.
Roll.
Down your pants leg.
Yes.
Incompetent and in kind.
All those incontinental words spring to mind.
Guess that's what happens to your brain.
If your brain surface down, surfs down the in confidence highway.
Or something.
Takes a left at the torso in middle evacuation center.
Jumps off a brief.
Brief.
Skipping a jump from the.
Turt Willie's National Monument, which is located now in Brook Park on South Park Road.
And enjoys a chicken sandwich while he's watching the whole debacle while everything just falls apart around him.
That's not funny.
Nothing's funny anymore.
Actually, it's horrible to try and make a life of comedy with everything.
Those who have angst.
Nausea.
Well, it doesn't all the time, does it?
Well, you tell a joke and you smile.
The other person laughs.
You realize you've done your job, but there's no laughter for you, for me, for we.
I didn't tell.
The other is.
We.
We're laughing at you, Dave.
We're not laughing with you.
We're laughing at you.
That's why we're so joyful.
Didn't we?
Weren't we informed by a very reliable source that if we wanted to get.
Really.
Really depressed that we should have a talk with some comedians?
Well, that's a Hollywood joke is if you want to have a really depressing party, invite over all the comedy writers.
Right.
But that's what they say.
If you like it really dark.
Yeah.
Bring the comedians in.
A lot of O.C. people with big weird stains on their necks and stuff.
A lot of people arguing over nothing at all.
Oh, man.
I remember the last one I was invited.
To I had to get the hell out of there.
I couldn't take it.
There's too many uptight people, too many freaked out people.
What?
The Hollywood comedy writers party that you got kicked out of.
Yeah.
When you were trying to get a job writing for The Simpsons or Futurama and they kicked you out.
Well, as you know, I am an ancient person.
So it was before that.
Yes.
You shouldn't have mentioned Church of the Subgenius.
I told you, man.
That's a kiss of death in a job interview.
It is.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Which means, oh, no.
You know, here's the funny thing.
I met Matt Greinig, the founder of The Simpsons and Futurama at a time when I was more famous
than he was.
Because his cartoon Life in Hell had just been syndicated for the first time to another
paper outside of L.A.
And that was he thought that was brilliant.
Really big deal.
Whereas I was a book author.
See, I lowered myself to have a burger with with this newbie guy, Matt Greinig.
And who is that other guy?
Gary Panter, who later got an Emmy for designing Pee Wee's Playhouse.
Yeah.
Hey, Owie.
Dirty rotten guy who made it back when we were all trying to make it.
Well, you know, Bob ended up on Pee Wee's Playhouse, but I didn't.
And and I'm very thankful for that.
And I'm very thankful, frankly, that The Simpsons has never mentioned Church of the Subgenius,
because if if they do, that means you've probably jumped the shark.
And we threw the shark under the bus in order to prevent that happening.
So that's why we're hoping to cruise on through to the other side, sleep on through to the
other side, as we retirees like to say.
Now, everything's going to be okay.
Everybody's parents are croaking and dying and sometimes not even parents, just friends,
siblings and stuff.
And our friend, Reverend Dow Jones, said that...
Well, he's an average, isn't he?
He's average.
He said that this this upcoming X Day must be the real one.
This must be 1998 because so many of our friends and loved ones are dying.
It makes it easier to kiss this rock goodbye on July 5th.
True words were never spoke.
Yeah.
Well, I mean, not true, but...
See, Bob's killing off our loved ones so that we'll be happy to leave the planet.
Thanks, Bob.
Thanks, Obama.
Hey, there's another one of those ringtone laughs, folks.
Ringtone laugh.
Yeah, with a bunch of surf music in the background.
What is this stuff?
I've been playing this for a while.
Surf Dungeon in the background.
Oh, I didn't give credits for all those collages at the beginning of the show.
Oh, no.
Well, that's what happens when Dave calls.
That's a lot of pastry.
Well, that's a lot of pastry to waste.
Well, you didn't hear it, Dave, but for the first 15 minutes of the show, there was a
collage work editing, and it was all done by one subgenius, the great Reverend Exister
of formerly Ministry of Slack podcast show.
Praise Reverend Exister.
I don't think it happens anymore, but luckily, Reverend Exister was still editing, and he's
made ... I just played a fraction of the stuff he sent me, so future shows will have more
mixes and cram-ups by Reverend Exister.
Praise Reverend Exister.
Indeed.
He came to the first X Day at Drill at Wisteria, but he couldn't ... He's from a nice, clean
environment.
It was the second one that he couldn't stay for.
Yeah, that's right.
It was when we got the freakish heat wave.
Yes.
He had to leave because he's from California, and he's only known nice weather.
He had driven to Southern Ohio from California in his little red sports car.
Yeah, just to see Bob.
What did Bob do?
Bob gave him heat stroke.
Yeah.
It was mean.
Mean Bob.
Bob was mean.
He was pink Bob with no pipe.
Yeah, I think it's about time for the reign of Bob to end in a lot of ways because he's
just causing so ... He's just constantly causing so much trouble.
He's just ripping and rupping and whooping and a whooping and going around and smacking
people upside the head with all kinds of mortality and sickness and disease.
Well, it's supposed to be cold, so I imagine the reign of Bob will turn into the snow and
sleet of Bob soon.
Yeah, probably.
We won't have to worry about the reign of Bob anymore, the puddles of Bob left behind.
Unlike so many little old ladies, we won't find Bob the next morning frozen to the ground
with his mail in his hand.
I thought we weren't going to talk about that, Dave.
When I said his mail in his hand, I wasn't talking about that.
I meant with his ... The Sears catalog.
Yeah, I know.
Yeah, yeah, the Sears catalog.
Right.
Well ...
Which he was going to take to the Mark Twain era outhouse and blow the damn thing up in
the name of something.
I don't know.
I'm sorry.
Yes, indeed.
Wow.
Oh, speaking of everything that's not connected to this, there's going to be another
devotional.
That is the sort of convention of Devo fanatics and fans like Prince Harry.
Yeah.
I mean, we're going to be out, you know, at HBO, an annual movie outs or something
like that, maybe number one in Wanna HIS drinking party.
Had a second
Oh, yeah.
Absolutely.
I do love your show.
But, uh...
Well, they take no offense.
No, they don't even notice us anymore.
They don't notice anything anymore.
I think that's what the touting is all about.
They're so rich and famous now and old.
Flagrant.
Just like 1% of the...
The old divos.
Yeah, the 1% of the old divos.
Like a halibut in the rain, you know?
Just saying, hey, what's the purpose?
What's the fixation, June?
Right, like a halibut riding a bike in the rain.
The divas are old.
Those guys have got to be at least five years older than me.
So that means they're all 65 to 70.
Yeah.
You think Mark Mothersbaugh is almost 70?
You think that's possible?
It's possible.
He once said to me, Mark Mothersbaugh said to me,
yeah, that sounds like something a 35-year-old would say.
As if I was a baby at age 35.
Which I kind of was.
Even though I had raised two of them at the time.
Well, was he much older or much younger than you at the time?
No, he's a little older.
I think those guys are about five years older.
Which would put him at 65 or so.
Dave's age, in other words.
Old, like Hal.
Dave, Mr. Sister.
Philo.
Those really old people.
Uh-huh.
And then there's the really old subgeniuses like G. Gordon Gordon and Reverend Root.
Reverend...
And Enoch Root, who've been around since Bob.
Both those guys used to hang out with Bob.
That's what I've heard.
I heard the...
And also, I heard they had big book deals and nothing ever happened, too.
Right.
Nobody cared.
Well, we both will.
We know all about that, don't we, Dave?
All of our book deals that nobody cares about.
Until we're dead.
After we're dead, then we find out, oh, everybody loved those books.
And we would have bought them.
We would have bought them if they'd known about them.
Now they're buying them, now that we're dead.
Yeah, we would have bought them.
Ever since they made that movie.
Well, go ahead.
Go ahead and do what?
You were just about to bring down hell and brimstone and fire and stuff on You Know What.
No, I wasn't.
Oh, I was.
Well, then you better pick up on it.
I'm sorry.
Whatever I was going to say, you better believe it, dude.
Well, it's just the same kind of mentality.
It's like a fire across the land, creeping in.
It was like a fuzzy aperture or something, like stuck to your head and you can't get in, you can't get out.
You know, he's like...
A sphincter that never opens at the right time.
Right in the middle of your forehead.
Yeah.
Fuzzy aperture.
Stuff leaks out when you didn't even mean to do anything at all.
You just reach up there and wipe your forehead.
Ooh, the brown crayon.
Gross.
It's in through your eye.
It'll make your eyes...
When you get older, it's hard to keep that thing from leaking on your forehead.
That little forehead sphincter will just keep...
It gets weak.
It's unsure of itself.
Yeah, maybe yours is weak, but mine requires a lot of gauze.
Yours has a very, very lot of gauze.
A lot of gauze?
Real lot of gauze?
A lot of gauze and tape.
Like a whole, whole lot of gauze?
A whole freaking lot.
Oh, man.
Dave, tell me his...
What do you mean?
His third eye is growing back.
You know, that bump?
Oh, no!
Oh, yeah, and it has an eyeball this time, too.
And eyeball is like looking around.
So, I'm having a hard time controlling my throat for oxygen right now.
Well, what about the mean baby head on the back of your head?
Oh, mean baby head kind of just went away without even telling me.
You know, like I'm crazy or something.
Well, there's a baby head on the back of my head.
No, there's not, Dave.
And then they give you a mirror.
Double back.
So, if you look at the back of your head, which is, you know, and you...
You mean the baby head is gone?
Really gone?
It's gone.
I don't know if it's really gone or if it's like someplace in my leg or my foot now.
Could that mean that someday we could be free of Dick?
Bob could lose Dick, his twin brother, vestigial parasitic twin, on the back of his head?
It's possible.
I mean, I view it as a positive sign.
There aren't very many positive signs, but this could be one of them.
I'm only hoping for the best.
I just, I've got my fingers, my knuckles, and my knees crossed.
So, if you want to make speculation about what really happened to the baby,
where the baby head went, you know, how it entertained itself over the last few months,
and who it's controlling now, where it's located right at this moment, I don't know.
Nobody cares about your double mean baby head, Dave.
We're worried about the one that Bob has, Dick.
I care about David's double mean.
Double mean baby head?
Dick is a problem.
I agree with you.
My baby head really just doesn't rate in comparison with the problems that Bob has had for so long.
But Bob always acclimated to the situation and used it as part of a luck plane to, you know, do what he willed.
Oh, did you know that the rock singer known as Ice-T, his band Bodyguard,
they did a song about Dick Dobbs called Evil Dick.
It was on, it's hard to find because it was on the Cop Killer album.
So, you know, they hide the Cop Killer stuff.
Well, so what?
So they'll get some air time off the Cop Killer thing?
No, no, it was mainly because of the Evil Dick song.
The song about Bob's evil brother.
I think there was a lot of confusion and that could have clarified things just like butter.
Butter.
It could have made everything really, really sweet.
Clear.
The glass.
Clearer than glass.
Clearer than the invisible man.
Sweeter than blood.
Hotter than a, oh, no.
No more morbid stuff.
Clearer than air.
As violent as an egg and twice as tasty.
And I pass this knowledge on to you.
Sit in the front row, spread your legs and argue with each other.
That's what I want.
Conflict.
No resolution.
And I want to watch the entire time.
Okay, girls, it's time to do jumping jacks.
I love these violent eggs.
It's really, it's scary.
I...
Violent eggs.
Can you imagine the problems they're crossing?
Can you imagine the air that we're living in?
It's just incomprehensible.
It is.
It really is.
It's hard to wrap your brain pan around.
And some of them, like myself, have a third eye that's not doing them any good, too.
And a shallow brain pan.
Very, very shallow.
With the muffin top hanging over.
Yeah, really.
Muffin top brain.
Yep.
That was a great band, muffin top brain.
I could say not even get the brownie.
Muffin top brain was pretty good.
Well, their first three albums were.
Yeah.
After that, yeah, you know.
They kind of got old.
Yeah, they just...
Yeah, track one with cranberries, track two with raisins, track three with prunes, you know.
Yeah.
Same old, same old.
Well, that's what happened to a lot of sea rattle bands and a lot of Tacomaites and people out there in the Puget Sound area
when they were coming up with their original...
Original sound.
And then the whole...
Did you know?
It's...
By the way, I was wondering.
Hello?
Sorry.
Yeah.
I was wondering.
I sat on the wrong joy bus.
Footprint?
I was really wondering.
Maybe this way, Sergeant.
By this big tree.
Hmm.
Looks like someone's living inside.
A wise old owl.
Why, it's Bob Dobbs.
J.R. Bob Dobbs.
Who is in that tree?
The wise old owl.
Smoking his pip-a-loony eye.
Who is in the tree but Bob?
Come back, come back.
Oh, no, I stabbed myself.
Oh.
Poor, poor little...
No, no, no stabbing.
Please, no self-stabbing.
I was just over-anxious with a toothpick
and I drew some blood.
Oh, no!
Didn't you know Dave's a cutter?
No.
That's why he eats all those beans.
No, man.
He likes to.
He's a cutter.
He better not be a cutter.
Yeah.
No.
If I'm a cutter and you're like beans
and stuff like that,
like what kind of bean are you talking about, man?
You're the ones that make you cut a lot.
No.
But cheese?
The cheese, Dave?
Remember the cheese?
I remember something about cheese.
It was a little cloud coming to my neighborhood
and I somehow was trying...
It was a dream, maybe.
It was a dream.
I was warning the...
No, no.
That's another dream.
To the maggot in the cheese.
The cheese is the universe.
I cut the cheese at Grandpa's Cheese Barn.
Oh, yeah.
We were going to talk about our adventures
on our very truncated trip.
You know, we had to get to Texas in seven minutes
and we were late because of all the breakdowns.
There was a breakdown of hope.
Yes.
We were outside of Hope, Arkansas
when we had a violent blowout.
Really weird sounds started coming from the car
and a vibration.
That kind of tickled.
And we pulled over
and the tire was completely bitten to shreds
by some huge truck monster.
And we had to go...
We had...
Luckily, Hope was nearby.
Hope, the birthplace of President Clinton.
You had to take the synchronistic highway
to avoid the little hamlet of despair there on the way.
By the way, I've noticed the sign
that gives the exit signs for Hope.
Hope, Arkansas, are no longer covered
with buckshot wounds and shotgun blasts.
Yes, they must have replaced them.
Oh, they were at one time?
Well, they got tied.
It's been so long since Clinton was president
that they're not mad anymore.
They've forgotten what they were mad about.
Something about a cigar.
That's all they know.
So they quit shooting at the sign that says,
Hope, birthplace of President Clinton.
Riven's sign, bad.
Heald's sign, good.
Huh.
Hmm.
Well, that...
To me, all I can think of is
those former denizens of Hope there
and their outbreak
against our presidential leader in the past
can only lead me to say that they
have little, if anything, to do with J.R. Bob Dobbs.
Right now,
you know, when my mind goes blank,
or yours,
that's the first thing that emerges
from the haze.
And there it is.
An image.
A swollen monkey
arguing in the rain.
More arguments.
You this, I that, we they.
Mm-hmm.
Coming back now.
It's all...
And what...
What of the swollen orangutan?
Orangutan?
Yes, what of the swollen orangutan?
Right next to the trapezoid.
See how...
This is a weird radio show.
And the obelisk.
I...
I'm having...
Listener, I too am having trouble following this.
If you stir...
If you stir some craisins in,
it makes it much better.
I guess that's why they follow Bob
and not me.
I guess that explains it.
Now, don't it?
I'm not following none of this.
Well, Bob...
Better not follow me.
I don't know nothing.
You've always talked about
the phallicness of the pipe.
And we mentioned the obelisks.
Along with the tangential humor
and the, you know,
the other problems we all face
and everything like...
Oh, well, thanks for explaining
all those references,
Professor Lonesome.
But I didn't know that...
I didn't...
I had never analyzed
the random humor.
Oh, somebody told us
they liked the show,
this show.
They said,
I like the random stuff.
And I thought,
what?
What randoms?
Every bit of this
is carefully scripted.
It's like...
That is definitely disrespectful.
Random?
That is disrespectful.
And we've tried for years
and years to make...
Awesome.
Good old...
This...
Therefore...
Random.
Common science says...
Carefully crafted.
Did we know the argument?
Random?
I mean...
How?
Master logicians.
We can argue with the Pope
if we feel like it.
Well, master logicians,
don't...
Don't you dare
think any other way.
Oh, there's Dr. Sinister
just come in
to serve his time.
He's so sinister.
Oh!
He's got to serve
his two hours.
We've almost...
Almost served our...
Hour of...
Of lack.
And like that
for the pig denizens
with their red hats
marching obliviously off
into oblivion
and set beyond
and waiting
the great squeal.
The big butcher
coming back.
I'm sorry.
Oh, the surf band
in the background.
The surf band
in the background
was the cocktail preachers
doing.
Bailout.
Speaking of surf bands,
isn't it Reverend
Angry Larry's birthday?
It indeed is.
And he's the...
He's like the main groupie
for that famous
thrash punk surf band
The Amino Acids.
Yes.
He's like a roadie
or something for them.
And this show
is dedicated to him
because it's his birthday today.
Aw.
What about anybody else
who happens to have it?
Come on, kids.
That's all.
Bring the happy birthday stuff.
And it's also dedicated
to anyone else
whose birthday it is today.
It was my little daughter's
birthday.
Yesterday, wasn't it
my daughter's,
my dafter's birthday?
Yes, it was your dafter's
birthday yesterday.
Well, soon it will be
the sign of the pickled emu.
That was a great bar.
The pickled emu.
Yeah.
And the world's end.
I remember good times
with the pickled emu.
If you're a rhomboid shape
or, I mean,
if you're a rhomboid shape,
let's say if your moon
is square to your conjunct,
then you have the bad,
what do they call it,
the aspects,
the bad aspects
of Bob Dobbs.
Well, this isn't the moon.
This is the dweezil
in the background.
And I didn't know
that you had opened
the conversation to junk.
You said something
about adjunct?
I don't be talking
about my junk.
A package?
A package.
A package, yes.
Of junk.
A horrible, stinking sack
of packages of junk.
Gross.
Well, enough about Bob and me.
Let's get more elevated.
I guess.
If you say so.
Actually, it's coming now
near the end of the hour of slack.
It's coming.
I can tell you
only that this is the show,
if we may call it,
that is sponsored
by the Church of the Subgenius
out of Cleveland Heights, Ohio.
And we're almost done here.
Thank goodness.
And we'd just like
some of our other
more mundane and also,
but yet still invisible sponsors
like the Kingdom of Lucifer.
Sure, man.
And Holy Hands of the Unwashed.
The Church of Destruction
of Little Tiny Small Babies.
That's subgenius.
dot com.
That subgenius doesn't have an O in it.
The Church of the guys who go and spit
angrily upon the sidewalk
as they pass a conventional church
and shake their fist angrily to the sky.
Oh, it's not always like that.
I don't know.
Nah.
We're not all like that.
No, not at all.
Nah.
In fact, the opposite is,
well, we're not all there.
OK, Dave, we're not all going to be here at all now
because I'm going to leave us.
Now and you won't.
And that's the way I hear it.
There's many issues for.
That's the way it is.
We'll leave.
We'll leave the light on for you.
We'll see you, Dave.
OK, well, be sure to use your propane heater
in a very small space.
Mom will be pleased.
I brought all of these souls to him.
I I taught them his worship.
I corrupted them for him.
I knew he was supreme when no one else did.
I built a chapel.
To.
Wow.
And I prayed to him and I made a pact with him.
And these all of my friends, I I promised them safety.
You presumed too much.
I know. I know.
But it does make a fine jest, the kind of jest that would amuse.
Would it?
Your Excellency.
I have no title.
Why do you call me Excellency?
Well, I thought as the ambassador of.
Wow. Wow.
Is not my master.
Death has no master.
But Bob rules the universe.
I made a pact with him.
And your pact with him will not save you.
There is no other God.
Each man creates his own God for himself.
His own heaven.
His own hell.
Let me see your face.
No.
So what I'm saying is brothers and sisters, sure, be a good subjeet.
Yes, but don't rush it.
You got to play it cool.
Pace yourself if you want to last all night.
Maybe even play a little hard to get.
Let Bob into your heart gradually.
But pull back right before you reach complete spiritual satisfaction.
Trust me.
It'll drive him two words.
Two words.
OH!
$ixí, cr, ra, z'y.
This guy knows what I'm talking about, right chief?
Ooh hey, I gotta fly, so ah.
Amen.
Zag Resource deceit is gibbered eventually.
Go andwer
Wang
belki
Be a loser.
Hop on, hop on, and we're gonna dance hard
Hop on, hop on, hop on, and we're gonna dance hard
Inches head, hop hop, hop hop, hop hop, hop hop
For a tire, there is no limit
No more money?
We gotta get some money!
That dirty, purgish, hark-a-back, flackin'
Wharton, Phillip, Bunker, Burton,
Perkaluma, Burton, Dutton, Buster, and I
Friends, we're glad you listened to this show
and we're even more glad that some listeners
have donated enough to help us keep on going
for another couple of months.
Not just this show, but subgenius.com
and all the other archive sites.
But if you truly love Bob
and want some of that slack back to rebound to you
you should go to subgenius.com
front page, or especially the radio page
or the catalog store pages
and help out financially as best you can.
Now, we know what it's like to be on the brink
of total poverty and we don't want any subgeniuses
to make their own situations worse.
But some of you still have jobs.
Even five bucks makes a big difference
even if it's only five bucks.
I mean, once a month from enough of you.
Fifty bucks makes an even bigger difference.
All we're saying is that blow jobs could go the way
of Steve jobs if you don't pay Dobbs.
We also take checks and money orders to
Subgenius Foundation.
P.O. Box 181-417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44.
118.
Thanks for anything you can do to help let there be slack.
Subtitles by the Amara.org community