From PR News in Washington, I'm in trouble.
An Iranian civilian that France refused to extradite to the United States
is buying sensitive technology and illegally exporting it to Iran.
He was buying electronics components through a Malaysian firm
and exporting them illegally to Paris.
It is true.
U.S. Envoy George Mitchell said this is PR.
The Palestine Liberation Organization is supporting Israel.
Israel.
President Obama says small senior citizens will suffer and be compromised.
But GOP critics crashed in to appear.
Authorities say seriously.
There's been an explosion at a coal mine in Siberia.
Russian authorities say because of a volcanic eruption in Iceland.
Recovery is likely to come slowly to severely flooded parts of security secretary Janet Napolitano.
The Reuters News Service is reporting possible PR news in the Gulf of Washington.
All right.
Now, this minute, I'm going to do something that may overthrow the entire radio business.
But I'm not going to say a word about laboratory tests
or quote you statistics or make medical claims.
All I'm going to say simply and honestly is this.
Ladies and gentlemen, try, just try.
The Sogenius Powerhouse.
What?
Those other religions, they want 10 percent of your income right off the top.
They want you to provide for them in your will.
They want you to pressure your government for billion dollar contributions.
They want you to double your taxes so that they don't have to pay any.
And what does Bob ask for?
30 lousy bucks.
They're the ones with the extravagant cathedrals.
the lush synagogues, the giant mosques.
And what do we have?
One hour a week on non-commercial radio.
Now, forgive me if I go out on a limb here,
but doesn't that sound just a little lopsided?
Of course not.
It sounds a lot lopsided.
But we got something they don't have.
It's called slack.
Slack.
And I don't mean the artificial slack they try to market for a profit.
Hey, folks, play the lottery and win free slack.
Uh-uh.
I'm talking about real slack.
Internal slack.
Slack from within.
The kind that feeds on itself like a breeder reactor.
It radiates a warm, fuzzy glow that lights up our lives.
It's an inner peace they will never know.
And therein lies the basic.
There's a difference in our religious philosophies.
They stress pain, suffering, and sacrifice
because on the outside, they have everything.
But on the inside, they have nothing.
They're morally bankrupt.
Empty shells.
Just poor, pathetic souls
tormented by inner demons of guilt and self-loathing.
But we subgenie.
We are the exact opposite.
While on the outside,
we have so little,
on the inside,
we have everything.
And that's why we're smiling and Bob Dobbs is smirking.
Because we're rich with slack.
And for all their money,
it's not for sale.
Herein is the word of Bob.
Praise Bob!
Amen.
Transcription by Samuel Lyons
There is your vision wouldn't tell enough set.
Do not pick the just temperature.
We must try and approach in the action.
We throw some horrors, but can will do.
We are to assist with both of ancient.
We approach.
Clarence will talk to the doctor.
Bloody.
For sit or dance.
Never be in the quiet.
You should all roll.
Friend will quickly in here.
You and a great in a great.
You are a great.
Miss all the experience.
To about which we make enough.
Is to remind to.
The.
Papa.
Joe.
Mama.
More of his stupefying work coming up.
The instrumental music was the waltz of the Mortgage Bankers by the Rudy Schwartz Project, Brain Abortion, of Reverend Joe Newman.
But now, from KPFA Berkeley, an enlarged clip mutilated by the large of the latest episode of the first subgenius radio show, Pungling Everdance.
What are you laughing at?
She was actually employed by Dr. Pretorius' intercession until the cosmic diffuser was not...
Are you going to fill out those forms, Dr. Howe?
I filled them out.
Here they are.
Description problem.
Microphone became soft and droopy, then liquefied and ran onto board as foul-smelling fluid.
Board sputtered and shot sparks, blue smoke bellowing forth, then foul stenches of a freshly opened grave.
Feedback and demonic laughter were heard, and headphones wriggled and writhed as if alive.
This is a bumpy section of track.
Locomotive should slow down and vent steam.
This is what we have to deal with here at the show.
Thank goodness for Dr. Howe's form-filling out ability.
He can fill out forms faster and better than any other subgenius radio show.
The genius fluttering tremors of acute paranoia and phobic reaction to Orwellian police state atmosphere.
Fills his own...
Has his own way of filling out the form.
Confusion and damnation.
I use the form simply myself.
Nostalgia for unmonitored old studio.
I'm always generating the form content during the show.
Engineering comments.
By the time we get to the end of the show...
Roadbed needs upkeep along the line.
My form should have properly filled out.
Express trains must slow to take curves.
Intricate.
And files in their appropriate locations.
Before the next show begins.
And that was listener-sponsored radio.
And this is the Puzzling Evidence Show.
KPFA.
The Equipment Discrepancy Report.
The latest in important news and updates that you can't find on the regular radio.
I gotta hand it to you, Philo.
You brought this book, The Bobliagravon, in the Cyclopedia of Slack.
Pretty sharp to have a copy of this, little devil.
You know, that's the latest book published by the Church of the Subgenius.
And it's a mighty, mighty tome of forgotten wisdom and ancient knowledge.
It actually looks better to me than it did before, but what do I know?
It always looks better.
That's the great thing about all of the books of the Subgenius, is that they get better with time.
And they look better.
You'll want to go back and revisit them, and you'll find those words that you'll go,
I don't remember reading that last time.
Did they come here on their own?
Does this book actually multiply and get bigger?
And bigger over time?
Are they like certain magic books which can actually change between readings?
After all, you have to find out for yourself.
Some demons have the power to alter what is written about them.
Well, let's see, we're almost out of time, and more of our magical tricks and tropes will be on hand next time
when we bring you back through the winding, wondrous, mossy ways of the ancient revealed wisdom.
We here on the show at Puzzling Evidence Industries labor round the clock, 24 hours out of every day,
to bring you our beloved audience.
So true.
Our show prep never stops.
Listening listeners out there.
I'm preparing for next week's show right now.
Thank you.
The little people.
Billy Barty, Mickey Rooney, and all the many others out there.
Warwick Davis?
Yes, yes.
We are of a stature to be receptive to.
We are.
Our particular message, which we have been criticized for shooting from the hip,
and yet is something with absolute largeness.
And so I say unto you, writing, I have no tune, I'll find one.
Man is born unto trouble as the sparks fly upward.
I know everything.
I'm exhausted.
I don't know, man.
It's really coming to an end.
I'm sure I have a headache.
Oh, my God.
Don't take it out on the kids.
Oh, well.
We're all getting older and stupider by the second.
Oh?
But do not mind.
Just relax.
Thank you.
Ruined house, yellow dreams are blue.
a簣
it works
You a certain
fever
I had,
and had a
but I was
salt
but she said
déjà
say
you came
baseball
believe
you
can
catch
it for the truth
The show can't hurt us anymore.
And he'll always be remembered as Kennesaw Mountain Landers.
A fella named Joe Jackson was a fielder for the Black Sox.
And he always wore his black socks, but he never wore no shoes.
He weren't the nicest fella, and he had a couple problems.
Because he drank a lot, and he beat his wife, and he always acted rude.
He killed an ape, some babies, and he copped an attitude.
And the one man he hated most was Kennesaw Mountain Landers.
Mafia said, Shoeless Joe, you should really run this show.
You should be the guy who owns baseball.
All you really gotta do is help us make a buck or two.
We'll bet on the other team you'll lose the game,
but make it through.
We'll make it seem like nothing could be further from the truth.
Shoeless Joe did what they say, dropped a couple fly balls.
And he walked up to the pitcher, and he poked him in the eye.
In the seventh inning, with the Black Sox nearly beaten,
there was someone who was watching from his blank above the stands.
Cradling a rifle in his thick, empty hands.
As if you hadn't guessed yet, it was Kennesaw Mountain Landers.
Kennesaw said, drop that glove.
For I swear by God above.
I'll make you regret playing baseball.
Shoeless Joe looked up and saw.
Silver rifle's gaping more.
No one had noticed yet, his underwear was getting wet.
He beat himself in front of everyone.
Shoeless Joe was finished, but he couldn't quite admit it.
So he raised his middle finger up above the other four.
Kennesaw took careful aim and fired a single bullet.
And he shot that dirty finger off and dropped his trusty gun.
Everybody in the stands knew he had won.
And today they still refer to him as Kennesaw Mountain Landers.
And so the whole story begins.
A brass band of exactly the same name at Notre Dame.
But that was in 1986 when MICH CολOMBUTE was found hanging down over the潤 Societe
The illnesses exteriortin Canine pinch the Hakamon.
There was nothing to here with.
The Golden Edge Uay Lag tormentor lost so he was out.
It was only that we really ref contribution right he never could be satisfied in thriller
play.
To have had the critics online The great Edward SD.
I have eight period of ga여 death, are you serious?
Yes, the critics all confused him with the great Elvis Costello
Jonathan Colton and the Attractions did that.
Kennesaw Mountain Landis is the actual title.
JonathanColton.com
Colton is spelled C-O-U-L-T-O-N dot com.
Oh, yes, dear friends, we are swiftly approaching X-Day, July 5th,
the greatest subgenius holiday, and for normal Earth humans,
the time of the judgment from space and the certain end of the world as they know it.
Yes.
In view of that impending deadline, accent on the dead,
we are preparing ourselves for this time of holy transition,
transition from these mundane jobs and bodies into much less mundane jobs and bodies.
And with this particular episode of the Hour of Slack, number 1260,
we strive to use up all the newer recordings so they get heard before the end.
And we'll mix them with classic older cuts that must not be forgotten
as we, the saved, rise up to our new homes aboard the escape vessels of the sex goddesses.
Future shows, if any, my friends, will be perforce reruns,
probably related to previous X-Day drills,
so that if there continue to be radio broadcasts of any kind on the planet after July 5th,
they will consist entirely of...
paid-ups of geniuses gloating from their heavenly thrones
of the losers, zombies, corpses, and so forth
who stayed behind rather than pony up the tiny love offering that Bob asked for salvation.
Oh well, easy come, easy go.
Easy rise from the slime and muck through a billion years of evolution
to the point that we have radios and radio shows
and radio shows.
easy go back to the slime and devolution that will be the curse upon the unfaithful.
Those unfaithful, that is, who are unlucky enough to survive the first moments after 7 a.m. this July 5th morning.
Just in case the exes or Bob swing a different deal and spare the planet for yet one more year,
we're also readying ourselves for Starwood Festival, which paradoxically starts exactly when Ex Day ends.
But it's another clothing-optional festival in yet another clothing-optional campground, Wisteria,
in southern Ohio rather than western New York.
So forgive us, friends, if this is the last fresh hour of slack for a week or a millennium or two.
I do.
I assure you that we will play only the finest selected reruns as we leave the planet.
And once left, we will strive to broadcast our infinite gloatings.
But for once, not from tar, paper, little rascals' radio stations, but from gleaming, vast ships of light.
Friends, we'll be here in...
We'll be hearing another song from the Rudy Schwartz Project called You Can Be a Republican Too.
You'll hear my and Onan's rant from last Ex Day drill.
The Varge.
An incredible discussion about Bob by Reverend Godrex and another mind-cracking Papa Joe Mama sermon.
But first, a clip from last year's Ex Day 12 Devival.
Lupus Pelum Mutat Momentum.
Magna est veritas et prevalabit
Acta exteriora indicant interiora securita
Aequam mentore businadis avasalis
Fortes cadre sedere non potest
Fruttus non folis arborem est credits eteros
Quen pinitit peccasi pane est inuse
Do you sometimes feel your life is just
A ten pound sack of dog manure?
Does your wife throw up when you have sex?
Your kids are insecure because you want them to be clones
All these things are fine, dear friend of mine
There's just one little thing left to do
Trade your brain for Jesus Christ
Plastic fruit looks super nice
You should become a Republican too
Buy an extra loaf of Wonder Bread
A jumbo can of pork and beans
Stamp out smut and corn at your convenience store
But when you go on business trips be sure and buy a whore
Lock your doors up tight and only talk
To people who act just like you
Trade is for the best
And when decent you're a test
You should become a Republican too
The Conspiracy
So the conspiracy gets into everything
The conspiracy is of course as we know all about mind control
Would you mind if we nosing your business over here?
Would you mind if we nosing your business over there?
Friends, we are not here to mind you
We are here to re-mind you
We are here to undermine you
Mine out that old mind
And replace it not with mine
But with one much infinitely stupider than mine
A 2D mind
A button down mind
A veritable mined field
The bedotten mind of J.R. Bob Dobson!
That is what is going to help you make it through the work at egg world
This is America you can do it we can do it
Woah
Parce
Pic
C goods
Gaz
Woah
Every person had some flaky ideas.
Maybe somebody who seemed way over the top with their flaky ideas, seeing the light or whatever.
I picked what I thought was most representative of Bob's interests.
And how I remembered Bob's interests progressing.
He had a theory of...
Catastrophism?
Right.
That's it.
Gams.
His big, huge favorite love.
His focus at the end of his life.
Mandated the teaching of creationism in public school classrooms.
And said, well, you know, if you want to go that far, let's do the same with a flat earth.
And so he just changed a few words.
And sort of a reductio ad absurdum.
You can do that.
You can do this.
If he had have actually...
That's true.
Maybe farther.
I don't know.
We ought to believe that the sun orbits the earth.
Oh, yeah.
Oh.
Fascinating.
I didn't...
I...
What makes a man?
Is it the power in his hands?
Is it his quest for glory?
Give it all you got to...
To fight to the top.
So we can know your story.
Yeah.
And so we have a ut彥iW hall.
So, we're a, you're content, right?
You are a man.
Man, man.
Man, man, man.
outs, man...
Don't just...
Live it.
You have changed.
Life.
edy
What makes a man?
Is it the woman in his arms?
Just cause she has big titties
Or is it the way he fights every day?
No, it's probably the titties
Now you're a man
A man, man, man
Now you're a man, man
Man, man, man, man, man
Now you're a man
M-A-N, man, man, man, man, man
Parker and Stone from their 1997 movie Orgasmo.
Man, I'd love to see them open for Tenacious D
and Spinal Tap and the Swingin' Love Corpses
and finally Mahogany Rush.
That would be my ultimate perfect dream concert.
But now...
The ultimate perfect dream subgenius sermon
entitled The Last Chance
by the great Father Papa Joe Mama.
The sermon tonight is entitled The Last Chance.
Yes, friends, 1998 is fast approaching
and a lot of people out there have come to expect the church
to start singing a different tune about the Judgment Day.
They say, hey, did you hear the news?
The Berlin Wall has fallen.
Things are getting better.
We say, is that so?
They say, hey...
Did you read the paper?
The Russians are now our friends.
Things are getting better.
We say, is that so?
They say, hey, did you see it on CNN?
We won the war.
Things are getting better.
Is that so?
And now they come a-running and a-cheerin',
saying, roll out the barrel.
We now have a new president.
The Republicans are out.
The recession is over.
It's the year of the woman.
Everybody get naked.
You poor pitiful little pigs.
Do you really think an eternity of sin can be erased so easily?
Are we now supposed to embrace the conspiracy
and call off the exodus invasion?
Do you actually believe you can diffuse an entire revolution
with a few scraps of conspiracy compromise?
Never.
These petty little sidelines that have a nice day news
don't divert our attention from the real issue,
not for a second.
Tate Line, Washington.
New conspiracy.
Conspiracy president sworn into office
promises new conspiracy health care plan
to keep worker drones healthy
and make more capable of serving the state.
More to follow.
Tate Line, New York.
U.N. meets for conspiracy roll call vote
of conspiracy agenda
for global conspiracy world domination.
Renegade nations refusing to conform to new world order
will be penalized.
More to follow.
Tate Line, planet Earth.
Conspiracy in last ditch effort to avert bloody overthrow.
Attempts to utilize all arms of conspiracy propaganda machine
to convince subgenius rebel rousers.
World is now A-OK.
Member for conspiracy high command states,
quote, conspiracy no longer hostile.
Conspiracy now friend of little guy.
End quote.
Well, well, well, the world is getting better.
We should just call off the invasion before it's too late.
Wrong.
You can fool some of the subgenies some of the time,
but you can't fool any of the overmen.
And any other time,
they're much too in tune to the wily ways of the wicked one.
I'm talking about you, Mr. Pete boy.
Yes, you.
The one with the firm handshake and the easy smile.
You're not tricking anyone with your bold new vision
or JFK idealism.
We in the church go by one credo.
Ask not what the conspiracy can do to you,
but what you can do to the conspiracy.
And come July 5th, 1998,
we're going to put that motto into simultaneous.
Global orchestration.
We're overthrowing the conspiracy and we're executing the ringleaders
along with anyone else who tries to stop us.
Now to some, this may seem a little extreme.
That's perfectly normal to the average man in the street.
Witness in a public execution of a criminal may also appear extreme.
After all, chances are that the man is unfamiliar with the crimes of the criminal.
He was too busy making a living to notice what misdeeds the condemned
perpetrated.
On society before being brought to justice.
Add to that the criminal's emotional last words,
his pleas for mercy,
his insistence of his own innocence and his reciting of all the good deeds he ever accomplished.
Then imagine the prisoner's family stepping forth,
begging for his life and witnesses filing forward to testify to the innocence of this great man.
So wrongly accused.
It should be no surprise that even an intelligent but uninformed person would
feel sorry for the poor soul and wishing him a pardon.
If respected newspapers were produced and showed article after article supporting
the accused, even the most skeptical in the crowd would likely become sympathetic.
Why?
Because they would see in that individual before them,
not a criminal guilty of crimes against humanity, but themselves falsely accused
and condemned to death for crimes they never committed.
By now, the executioner should be more worried.
About their lives than the prisoner should his.
The crowd might well demand clemency and if refused,
storm the guards and free the prisoner by force.
If you were part of this intervention,
you would probably feel proud for the good deed you perform and the terrible injustice you averted.
But if a few weeks later you learn that the prisoner you saved was an insane serial killer,
that the witnesses that testified were all
paid actors and that the newspapers you believe were all frauds,
you might start to regret having been so compassionate.
Then by some quirk of fate, if you stumbled onto incontrovertible
evidence that the man you freed had devoted his life to destroying yours,
that his new obsession was to capture you, torture you and sell your loved ones into slavery.
Well, you'd probably start to feel anger.
Anger at yourself for being fooled.
Anger at the actors who tricked you and the newspapers that lied to you.
And anger at all the mental dweebs still running around out there claiming
the bastard is really reformed and just misunderstood.
This is how we at the church feel about the conspiracy.
Each and every one of us at one time or another believed the conspiracy.
Each and every one of us in one way or another.
Served the conspiracy.
And every single one of us in no uncertain terms knows that the conspiracy is out to get us.
Every day it tries to capture us, torture us and enslave our kind.
And every single time we get close to destroying the monster,
some well-meaning but ignorant bystander starts whining that we're being too severe, too extreme.
They say that
the conspiracy is actually innocent.
They say they know because they read all about it in the conspiracy newspapers or
saw it all explained to them on conspiracy TV.
They insist that our allegations are
exaggerated, that the conspiracy is getting better and that we should just mellow out.
They try to tell us that we are to give the conspiracy slack.
Dear, dear friends.
These poor misguided morons may be in the dark now, just as we were before.
And we may have acted back then just as stupid as they're acting now.
But that doesn't mean we don't have the right,
nay the duty to destroy the conspiracy while we have the chance.
Do not be taken in by any last minute media blitz that tries to convince you that the conspiracy has
suddenly turned over a new leaf because it hasn't.
The noose is around its neck.
What do you expect the conspiracy to say?
We deserve to die.
Kill us.
No, the conspiracy will look and act nicer now than it ever has before.
So don't be fooled if you hesitate.
Even for a second, you give the conspiracy a chance to win the crowd over.
And if that happens, you may find yourself on trial with no more X's around to pull
out the knife from the firing squad.
There's only one X day, dear friends.
Don't blow it.
July 5th, 1998.
Kill the conspiracy.
Cut off its head and launch it through the cosmos.
Here into the world of operates, Bob.
Amen.
I'm out of here tonight, Bob Ben-Q, to pour their name —
Michael Br accident strengthens by a dime.
I'm all I ever have.
But what arerest countries, black and white reality?
That must be huge.
But I have to promise you one few things to announce.
I told them to ban their
sphere how theyиться end of this …
© BF-WATCH TV 2021
Territory Bombs
Motherfuckers
Jack Tunes
What's up?
Where is this?
Jack Tunes
Motherfuckers
I got my fuck
So don't forget it
It's just a silly face
I'm going through
I got my fuck
So don't forget it
It's just a silly face
I'm going through
What a dumb
I got my fuck
Don't forget it
I got my fucking fucking fuck
I got my fucking fuck
Fuck, I got my product
While I was buying kiCats
Been looking for it
Your ass
That's it
I sold this bed
One shit
Two shit
Dead
gyah
Come on
We gotta do this fast
Gonna do just that
Go
słu
학
.
I'm with your fucking fingers
B-O-T-T-R-O-P
Ultimate seduction
This nigga's gonna laugh
I'm gonna beat you right now
I'll start this day timing
Time like a rocket time
You need to wait a while
Break out the Casio
Get your butt up, get your cop drop
I got you back one more time
I'm with your fucking fingers
And I'll make you kiss me
When you have finished recording
You may hang up or press 1
For more options
To leave a callback number
Press 5
Hi Connie
This is Bob
I was curious about your bulk honey
Yes
Just that kind of a thing
We
Bob
had some encounter with someone that the untrained eye, they don't believe in that.
Right.
Guess so.
Wow.
I guess weird America.
Original Koreshanity cult, the one whose name was borrowed by the Branch Davidians.
Did Bob ever have any of these great mock-ups like this?
I would love to see like a flat earth model or one of these.
I'd buy one.
He did not.
But he would make little 3D drawings and he had little drawings of the flat earth or the earth with different shapes on it and things like that.
But nothing but no scale models that I'm aware of.
Darn, there's some money waiting to be made there.
New guidelines are being designed to provide standardized information and recommendations.
Just an academic text rolled up in their pocket on a daily basis.
For more information on the Deaf Women's System, the Vagaji, visit the INDIA page.
Does this make sense?
www.inwd.inica.blogspot.com
Is this understandable?
Comments are welcome through May 6, 2010.
By the summer.
This is National Institutes of the East, G. Allerma, and as the Institute of International Net at Bethesda, Maryland.
Hello, my name is Curtis Anderson.
You have seen me as Gleepy the Hen post to Google Group Scrub Genius.
I want to thank everyone for reading our little slice of kook-free heaven.
Friends, the public service denouncement on standardized information
was by, of course, Lemur.
The discussion about Bob was edited by Godrex.
Pseudobob evacuated or excavated the historic phone message
and that collage of hardcore beats,
the intense, long, pounding musical interlude of the most intensely ratcheted hardcore samples,
that was assembled by the mysterious entity known as The Large.
The music behind it was a piece of music that was made by the famous artist,
the famous composer, Bob.
The music behind me right now is Hans Salter and B.F. Skinner from Universal Monster Movies.
And what you're listening to now is the Hour of Slack,
the radio voice of the Church of the Subgenius.
Well, one of them, anyway.
And you can find everything about the Church of the Subgenius at subgenius.com.
Praise Bob.
Now, briefly, back to Perry Kingsley.
Thanks to Mr. Sister.
And the barnyard in orbit.
Church of the Subgenius.
I could tell you guys were breaking some ground while I was gone.
I think you broke ground.
I broke something, but it was worth it.
It was worth it.
This was some really great, really good news.
Really brilliant brown, brown graking.
It's a brown graking show.
I don't know what graking means, but brown, everybody knows what brown is.
It's a color that we all strive for in our lives.
We strive for the brown color, and then we, and then we grake.
We have brown graking.
We don't know what it means, but we do it anyway.
You mean graking?
Graking.
And we, we are a K-I-N-G.
We don't know what it means, but we still do it.
The end from Puzzling Evidence.
Dr. Philodrummond, Dr. Howland, The Large.
What's groundbreaking now is this poignant piece by Wilhelm Stahlhelm.
A classic called Ex Dei Memoir.
Here we go.
It's just a story now.
Ex Dei Memoir is a story about neue
Ex Dei Memoir is a story about new
Ex Dei Memoir is a story about on
Naked, naked, naked karate kick guy, karate kick guy, guy, guy, guy, guy, guy, guy, guy,
White's
Clear
producc camera
music
guitar
craic
music
I'm going to do the list of the four.
Four.
Oh, I got the itinerary.
I need to check the itinerary.
Um.
Hang on.
Let's see what I got.
Next time.
Maybe.
Girl.
Real.
Past year.
Naked.
Par замет.
Guy.
Girl.
Who are you?
Pastor.
Naked.
You're out of your kick.
Got it.
Next time.
Hang out in the sun.
Watch how I really go.
Pastor.
Naked.
Karate kick.
Got it.
Hang out in the sun.
Next time.
Naked.
Karate kick.
Got it.
Wilhelm Stahlhelm did that and now the song I'm Bob's Own by my own daughter at age 13,
Sivit Stag.
Sivit Stahlhelm.
On my own, pretending Bob's beside me.
In the dark, his dots and pipe, they guide me.
Without Bob, I smell his drop around me.
And when I have no slack, I touch my clown and Bob has found me.
Sivit Stahlhelm.
Naked.
On my job, the noddles act like dumb shits.
Without slack, the sweat runs down my armpits.
On egg stay, I'll see the saucers coming.
And all I need is Bob and me forever and forever.
But until I do.
He doesn't help.
I bet my такая.
I spend my thirty bucks
I'm just renting to myself and not to Bob
And although I know that I am screwed
Still I say there's a day of pain
I love Bob, but when the rupture's over
He'll be gone, the earth will be in ruins
Without him, the world around me changes
The conspiracy is everywhere, the malls are full of pink boys
I love Bob
I love Bob, but every day I don't spend
That thirty bucks, I'm only just pretending
Without me, Bob's world will go on burning
Our next debacle, half-dislected, I'll never know
I love Bob
But only on my own
And yet
not be sure. Sometimes these cases take strange forms. The victim becomes, in a sense, mediumistic.
A vehicle for all the intangible forces in operation around her.
Sounds like a lot of supernatural baloney to me.
Supernatural, perhaps. Baloney, perhaps not. There are many things under the sun.
A bonus just for subscribers, Hour of Slack home subscribers, and the internet listeners.
This song, Fun, is by our friends at Kick Everything.
Praise Bob.
Hey, stop, fuck, fuck.
Hey, go, fuck, fuck.
Hey, fuck, go.
Hey, stop, again, I'm.
Hey, stop, fuck, fuck.
Hey, go, fuck, fuck.
Penny, or plenty, or penny, or plenty.
Penny, or plenty.
Penny, or pretty, or plenty.
So lovely.
Penny, or plenty.
Hey, few.
Fuck. Stop. Hey. Go. Fuck. Relax. Hey. Stop. Fuck. Ah.
Fuck.