Well, you can't blame a girl for trying.
What's on the radio?
Oh, this radio's no joke.
Turn it on, see.
Thanks.
No, not that one, Ann.
That's my police radio.
I'm sorry.
That's what you're in.
Right.
The Self Genius Hour of Swag.
You're becoming a regular boy scout, aren't you?
Aren't you?
I can take care of myself.
Oh, I see.
What do you think, then?
Let me be perfectly clear here.
This is Over the Edge,
and also, simultaneously,
it is the Puzzling Evidence Show.
How can that be?
And we're going for five hours tonight,
right here on kpfa.org online,
where we can look on our monitors
and see where you're tuned in from.
There's no other stations.
If you're listening in Sweden,
we see that.
We see that someone is tuned in in Sweden.
We can see you.
Yeah.
We can see you under your clothes.
Britt Eklund.
If you're in Sweden, give us a call.
You know,
what was her name?
Bridget Thorntonsen?
That's correct.
That starred with...
Yes.
Yeah.
The famous model.
Are you saying that she could be me right now?
You've got the one that made the...
We can beam you right now.
...Singmar's wife.
And Christine Jorgensen.
Beautiful girl ever.
Welcome to Babylon.
Well, that was...
I guess...
You know, can you fill in our listeners
about this whole trial?
I mean, because this whole...
Jesus, these are two subgeni who are being...
whose reproductive rights are being trashed
and whose right to reproduce
their own mutated versions of the human race
are actually being prevented by the law
in the form of a judge, I believe, in Texas?
No.
New York.
New York judge.
Yes.
In New York.
In Texas, they said,
whatever you do,
don't take that child back to New York.
But Jesus and Magdalene
took the Christ child.
Yeah.
Bob, who's called Conbo, by the way.
Conbo is a cute little boy of about...
Conbo.
...eleven now.
You know, like Marjo.
Yeah.
Oh.
Judge Punch John.
Marion.
Marjo is named after Marion Joseph, right?
Yeah.
Conbo is Connie and Bob.
Anyway, Jesus and Magdalene...
The subgenius business managers at that time
had a custody problem going on with the child's father,
who was a pink human.
And at one point, the judge was shown photographs
of a typical X-Day drill celebration
in which Jesus and his wife were doing normal X-Day things.
And this shocked the judge so much
that he said that the mother was...
Unbelievable.
...not a fit mother
because she was a member of Church of the Subgenius
and gave custody of the child to the father,
who was basically a ne'er-do-well welfare cheat thief
in a trailer court.
And it wasn't even a double Y!
Unbelievable.
Yeah.
No.
It was an X-Y.
And the case made the news on the internet
and created quite a bit of buzz.
It made quite a bit of stir
and caused many people to buy memberships from the church.
Oh, good!
It made me quite rich.
So it was a helpful...
Oh, that's good.
However, they...
You're getting rich off me?
Yeah, that's good.
The good, kindly, well-educated, hardworking subgenius parents
still are not allowed to see their child
until the judge makes up his mind.
The first judge...
That's obscene.
The first judge was screwed up so bad...
Seriously, it's disgusting.
...he was refused...
He had to be...
He had to step down from the case.
Why?
Because he was such a jerk?
He was so stupid that he...
He recused himself.
So next time you're fired from a job, just say...
Just say, I've recused myself.
...I've recused myself because I was too emotionally tied to the job.
Well, the second guy should have done that.
Why?
Because...
Because he was a what?
He was such a Christian that he couldn't handle the idea of a cult sense of humor or a church
sense of humor?
Well, the images that threw him were the beautiful Magdalene with Jesus drawing a
heart on her privates in front of a crowd on the internet.
The other thing that bothered him was Jesus dressed in clown... in a Jesus suit with clown
face being beaten in a parody of that Mel Gibson movie, being beaten by naked women
with dildos.
Did you see a clown face?
It was a takeoff on the Passion of the Christ, which they thought was not bloody enough and
they decided to restage it.
Could there be a connection with the insane clown posse people?
No, just some of the photographs that were on subgenius.com.
Yeah.
This is...
Maybe it's just a juggalo.
Unbelievable.
Well...
What's unbelievable?
I think I can believe it.
No, it would hurt them.
Well, because, you know, I think that's what I'm saying.
In other words, because the judge...
I don't believe anything.
Does anybody talk about those...
Everything you know is true.
You'll see in a moment.
You should believe everything that I say.
Yeah, because what...
I don't know about stank, I mean, but...
No wrinkles for me.
They're happy.
That's pretty scary, though.
Subgeni, they can take your baby away.
I won't even say...
Don't let me jinx it.
Look, they don't take babies away from strippers.
You know, they...
They don't take babies away from performance artists.
Yeah, I know.
They don't take babies away from big channels.
Because they don't have...
They don't have any.
I don't believe that they won't let them have any.
They don't let them have any.
They turn the baby away from...
Yeah.
A guy has a job.
Jesus and Magdalene.
And he has a job, right?
Oh, yeah.
They both have three jobs.
They both...
They have three jobs.
They're college-educated subgeniuses who are responsible citizens and yet...
That's why they...
You know, normally, the courts just blindly give the kid to the mob.
But in this case, they blindly gave the kid to the Christian or the...
Yeah.
Absolutely abolished him.
Right.
The Christian deadbeat...
The deadbeat Christian dad...
Who was beating...
Garage band...
A dead horse instead of a live Jesus who was being beaten at X Day.
And the judge didn't think that was funny or...
Yeah.
Rather, we're not...
It's not that we're...
Yeah.
It's not that it's sick humor.
We're a reflection of the illness in society around us.
Exactly.
Of course.
I wonder if the judge was more...
I...
I'm just a reflection of everybody else's...
Failure.
Failure and neurosis at the moment.
Yeah.
What are...
Yeah, we're not really totally screwed up.
We're a reflection of a screwed up society.
So, all people at work...
They're useless by the 70s.
That's right.
Or as we put it, officer, have you ever heard of Mad Magazine?
I'll do you a right, Johnny.
Sure can.
That's how you really...
Is that what your lawyer said?
That's how the court case...
No.
That's how it should have started.
But they forgot that crucial line.
I have to...
I believe...
The state is a place of...
Scotty, you round up the crew.
Well, you know, they will never take away Philo's baby, wonderful baby, because Philo has a job.
Good night, Bill.
A few salesmen for a large downtown department store, but they provide aid.
Reports each weekend is only two days off.
Why is it Iran?
Everyone in Iran is a sub-genie.
Everything will work out.
The president is the head of the plan.
Well, good morning, Miss Helvinger.
Good morning, Southern Fighter.
Well, once more, I'm here to strike terrific terror into the hearts of criminals everywhere.
Bob, you're the best at that of anybody.
Hmm?
Stand up again, please.
Yes, sir.
And sing in unison.
I'm stinking.
Beautiful.
Everyone say, beauty.
It might not fanaticism at times provide a kind of mainspring for good actions.
No, it wasn't the airplanes.
It provides a mainspring for actions, all right.
It was very kill-believing.
But I can't think of any instance in history where it provided a mainspring for good actions.
Fanaticism is just following the rules, really.
Always, I think, for bad ones.
If you really believe in that stuff.
Because it is partial, because it almost inevitably involves some kind of hatred.
You can have a baby shower.
You hate the people who don't share your fanaticism.
If you think you've got to march off the roof with a line of people because it says so somewhere,
I mean, that's not really fanaticism.
It's just orthodox behavior.
That's what I told the judge that one time.
It's still going over time.
Ha, ha, ha.
Northern state.
Don't look up there.
Whoa, where the hell are you opening the door?
People have done that.
They have jumped.
They have just marched dutifully.
Why?
I mean, it's just a computer gun.
Without giving it a second thought.
Just behaving like they're on parade.
March.
With their eyes open.
Oblivious to what their next step will bring.
Oh, none for any of us.
We'll be able to live in water, heat, cold, you name the worst, and never again a wrinkle.
Cryogenic suspension.
Why don't you shut up for a second?
I'm not worried.
No, you don't have to.
If you'd say a few words, it'd be better.
Harry, I can't believe it.
I just can't believe it.
Then if it gets taken over by...
economic considerations, say, like the Crusades,
then fanaticism disappears and perhaps does no harm.
I must go to extermination.
Before I am exterminated by this gangster,
computer god, concocted and controlled,
worst mongrel, organized crime,
murder-incorporated gangster communist government,
I hand you the secret
to save the entire human race
and the entire universe.
One dollar.
Don't.
Or even a value of typewriter to me.
For your own...
Maybe we could promote fanaticism.
Well, I don't know.
I can't think of any good that the Crusades did.
The Crusades had, of course, two different streams in them.
A fanatical stream and an economic stream.
The economic thing was very strong indeed,
but it wouldn't have worked without the fanaticism.
There's the flying saucer, Doc.
Where?
See them two peaks?
That flat hole between them, you see it?
Now the sun's hit it.
It is undamaged.
I'm putting her down.
Did you see any signs of life?
Anything moving?
No, sir.
Of course, I didn't get too close.
I might lay the thing.
In a matter of months,
thousands of Americans were no longer disbelieving.
Ooh.
Or as we like to say, one of a kind.
The end of this part of the album.
I understand.
It's just as well you didn't.
Hey, wait till she stops rolling, Doc.
You're our excited, ain't you?
I'm afraid so.
Even scientists get excited sometimes.
So, good day.
Good day.
Okay, where are you?
I'm over here.
No.
Okay.
Like, here we are.
Trust.
Peter's Donuts.
Oh, take off.
We are.
What?
Oh, okay.
Okay.
Thanks.
Thanks for blowing it.
No, you're right.
Oh, no, no.
It's three in the morning.
What?
Whose donuts?
Peter's Donuts.
Oh, Peter's Donuts.
Here?
Okay.
There, she's at the till now.
She'll see us in a minute.
I've got some crickets and worms.
We feed our little ones.
Oh, yeah, we should put up nice tomatoes for dinner.
This is our toy.
Oh, I don't even think of myself.
Payload.
Everybody in this video is looking at the baby.
There's now a whole OP.
Sec 스타일, I've got to fix follow her.
Because it makes.
Sonors big.
And preceding.
About him being.
getting its own way.
Be unique.
Hush-a-bye.
Rock-a-bye.
The Spider-Man is comin' by.
To spin a web of dreams for you.
Casket high, casket low
Daddy rocks you to and fro
The Spider-Man will make your dreams come true
Dream about a magic land
Where shadows fill the night
Where goblins stalk and monsters walk
Oh, what a lovely sight
If you're good, pretty soon
The creature from the Black Lagoon
Will come and guard you while you dream away
Dream about a tiny hearse
Drawn by a fuzzy bird
And by your side
Some mummies ride
Think how you like that
Rose bowl high, casket low
Shake your head get your anus
That's it son
Now just close the other one
You're such a beauty, I can only say
Scrag!
God's secret overall plan,
worldwide living death Frankenstein slavery.
It's your right wing this time.
Yes, it is.
Perhaps if you...
Yes, perhaps if I did.
Good grief, not again.
It is right wing this time, sir.
You're looking more like mommy heavily again.
...control the entire universe
with the endless stairway to the stars,
namely,
the man...
...made inside-out planets
with nucleonic-powered speeds
much faster than the speed of light.
Look up and see
the gangster computer god-concocted
new fake starry sky.
We're having a...
Okay, okay, here we go.
We got it.
Here we go.
Have you such troubles you think
they are driving you to drink?
No matter what bothers you,
let me tell you what to do.
This little box is all I use.
You call it snuff.
I call it snooze.
You used...
Take a little pinch of snooze
and you sneeze,
you're a troubles away.
It's a cinch.
You take a little pinch
anywhere, anytime,
night or day.
When your head is all tight,
It tickles your nose and you must let go you use take a little pinch of snooze and you
Well quit talking so much long I can't concentrate
Yapping at me all the time and you sneeze your troubles away
Ava so sick ever it they would soon die and be buried
I had pains from constant bunions in the yeshtin from eating onions arthritis bronchitis
The doctor said you lay down you're dead
Hey, you took a little pinch of snooze in there
Little sniff great big whiff and already I felt okay
That was our ring wasn't I don't know I never paid no attention
But only with two bottles. Okay, go. This is the beginning of our
You know a lot of those pills by dare of fake, you know something they give me a pain in my aches
invention of Doug McKenzie
He used gave her a little pinch of snooze and she sneezed her fat away
She died. No, she only tried it and she lost ten pounds every day
For when she sneezed she shook like a
Yelly that made the fat come off of her she used
gave her a little pinch of snooze sent you
And she sneezed her fat away
For me
One night they were sitting on the sofa with my Yenny
That's the girl a go for or she lay in my arms already to kiss and there was all pocket up for two
This but they didn't know when I was doing it. She had snooze and she was chewing it
I think that it take you. Yeah. No, they'll be taking you out
You could knock him off or you could whack
She must wanna start spitting
Well, this isn't a topic
Seems ch green
sounds is that that's not an empty 있는
I
only think and that's not just this
Fox, I mean that is a
The
Best song of all time
today's busing people get us은
I've ever had the pleasure to...
It's the baby.
It doesn't tarnish our gravity, though, does it?
Yeah, it does.
When you bring a baby into a radio studio, you just, you know, it can't help but cutify things.
It lightens things.
We were going to codify the doctrine, but instead we cutified the doctrine.
Well, we cutified the church by a great margin.
I would say we've just about tripled the cutification of the church.
Well, that's saying something because we have never been able to cutify it very well.
Yeah.
When somebody wants to insult us, they say that we've cutified it.
Oh, that's cute.
I have with me the entire of this book of the history of the Church of the Subgenius.
It's rather...
It's rather dry.
Yeah.
A lot of it's just counting which million was put into which bank and so forth.
But there's some...
Vatican finances.
What about...
There's some interesting stuff about the Kennedy assassination and...
Yeah, we've all heard that.
Early involvement.
Where did the money go out for...
What about the catalog?
The tiger's on it.
I'm waiting for the catalog.
All the money for the investigation into the assassination of dogs.
What happened to the money?
It was his...
It was a tremendous amount.
It was...
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
It was an amount of time was spent on prosecuting Doug Wellman.
Dr. Drummond, was that you making that horrible noise?
That was me and Walter making that horrible noise.
Well, and they never were able to get Wellman for anything.
Maybe I should say Walter and me.
Wellman was slippery.
I and Walter.
Even David Byrne was not able to get Wellman, and he tried.
Why do you ask for more?
This is a...
Let a lady...
What?
I wanna be famous.
David Byrne had another song called Buck Naked.
It has become...
You know, he...
Another song called Buck Naked.
One of them died.
A reality.
I'm serious.
I'm wondering...
Well, there was...
There have been so many musicians, singers named Buck Naked.
Including former subgenius Buck Naked.
He told me that if I ever mentioned him, I had to say that he was former subgenius Buck
Naked.
He did not want to be associated...
Please.
So I don't want to associate Reverend Buck Naked with...
Is he an apostate?
...with the...
Oh, yeah, major.
Really?
Oh, yeah.
Why?
Well...
I used to...
He was a good...
I met him.
He was okay.
He was regular Michael Pepe.
But...
He...
But what...
He joined...
He joined the last...
As I understand it, former subgenius Reverend Buck Naked joined a rival cult.
I think possibly even a Jesus-oriented one.
Have you ever heard of the I Am people?
Oh.
No.
Well, apparently he is.
Oh, my God.
I Am.
The I Am?
Holy...
I Am had some great graphics.
Would that be...
That's...
I've ripped off...
I've got...
Five syllables to the line.
I've ripped off...
No.
I've had our art department borrow ideas from the I Am cult graphics.
Wow.
And they weren't the ones that killed the...
They killed themselves.
Oh, no.
That was Do Re.
No, they still are.
To Do Ti.
No.
You're thinking of the They Were cult.
Yeah.
The Do...
That was the...
Yeah.
And there was the Be Here cult, which I was in.
Be Here Now, Rob Doss.
Were you in one of those Be Here Now cults?
Yeah.
I just liked his show.
Okay.
Penis?
Yeah.
Buck played a devil.
Oh, my God.
He was one of the foreground devils.
He made a great devil.
Speaking of background devils...
Former.
That's former subgenius.
Former devil subgenius in Buck Naked.
Now devil Kelty.
Oh, my God.
I said I am, right?
I said I am a subgeniusist with the I Am.
What do they do?
There's a lot of former subgeniuses actually.
Do they do anything?
That's quite a long list of people who decided they'd had it.
Yeah.
Well, the top one, Appa State Schism would be Bob Black, right?
I mean, he was...
Well, no.
Not really.
No.
He was a scary guy.
I mean, I don't want to say Bob Black on the radio.
He wasn't that...
I mean...
His reputation precedes him, I'd say.
He never scared me, let me put it that way.
Okay, good.
Well, I know people that just...
Because I...
He really did try as much as he could to arouse people's antagonism and opposition and, you know, wrote those nasty letters.
Well, I'm not trying to air a smeared underwear of the church on the air.
No, see, I've been trying.
You might in my revised.
Gossip from 85, essentially.
In the Stang-centric revised history of the church, which I'm teaching to these innocents.
Hello, by the way, Rosna and James Berger.
Hello.
Gary Gabo fan who's driving away.
Anyway, I've decided to just skip over the unpleasant aspect.
I've unpersoned quite a few.
Well, I did too.
We use the tried and true unpersoning where you just don't mention them at all.
And they hate that.
I know.
They hate that worse than anything.
It's the worst thing.
I know, in fact.
Yeah.
Bob Black hates, is more offended and enraged by being ignored than anything else.
That's really the best way to treat people like, you know, the kooks.
I know.
He's a kook even compared to us.
Well, that's the funny thing.
I mean, even, I mean, you know what I mean?
I mean, how can you be a kook compared to Stang?
To Church and Subgenius.
Yeah, but no.
They.
No, we feel for the differently saying.
We're, you know.
Yeah.
But not really.
No, we're all kooks on some level.
No, you have to be a.
It's just that we're also subjectivists.
So anybody that we really dislike, we can say, well, he's a kook and write it off like that.
That's how words work.
Yeah.
They're just not.
That's what language is all about is to label things.
Right.
Put them away.
And say prejudgments that are unfair.
They're prejudgments to keep order.
Which means you have to.
That's why there's this difference between subgeniuses and kinks.
Yeah.
It's just a.
It's a way using linguistics to simplify things that are actually very complicated.
Yeah.
And it appeals to the stupid, the superstitious.
And to people who enjoy studying the effects of stupidity and superstition.
Yeah.
Stupidity, I'm upset.
You know, it doesn't really exist.
I think stupidity actually is just fear where, I mean, that is to say, stupidity is everywhere
at all times.
But it's based on fear.
I can see why you would say.
I can see why you would say that.
Yeah.
But is Bushman stupid?
Almost everything is stupid.
I mean, but, you know, compared to what?
I mean, it's just like saying, you know, almost everything is insane.
Things are insane.
But they're so insane the word insane doesn't apply.
Or it does, but.
Right.
So when we say subgenius kink, what we're basically talking about is a normal.
Is.
A normal person.
Okay.
Who.
A pink.
A pink who pretended to be a subgenius.
Yeah.
A pink who was aping its betters.
There you go.
That's the worst.
That's what, that's what we call a subgenius kink.
Yeah.
A gimme bob.
A gimme bob, yeah.
Or an imabob.
Actually, the worst are the imabobs.
Imabob.
Oh, yeah.
Those are people who think they're bob.
You know, I knew bob dogs.
And, sir, you are no bob dog.
You know, I haven't paid.
I'm a bob.
I actually haven't paid.
I've had the occasion to say that in all sincerity.
I'm a same.
To one of the imabobs.
Yeah.
If you can see what I'm.
Can you, can you hear where I'm coming from?
Then there's, you know, then there's the hezabobs.
Do you see what I'm saying?
Can you see the words that I'm saying?
Well, the hezabobs.
The words.
I'm a bobby.
See them?
Hezabob, it means the same thing as imabobbies.
Or the maybobs.
Yeah.
Maybobs.
Now, that was, that's a little different.
Nylon shell.
Fully waterproof.
I kind of like the maybobs.
Maybobs.
Yeah.
They're a refreshing change from all the yaybobs.
The maybobs?
Okay.
They're the opposite of yaybobs and yayhoo, which are sort of like yayhoos.
On, on, on things.
You don't know who the yayhoos are, but you do know who the yaybobs are.
Straddle the line, you know, rather than.
Well, you have to compromise.
Life is a series of compromises and terrible pains.
Just try to compromise.
Life is a series of balancing between the interstitial vortices.
Exactly.
Dr. Drummond, you love that interstitial vortices thing.
It explains so much.
It's right.
It explains everything.
It's like the unified field theory.
Vortices are like that.
Plus string theory all rolled into one.
Plus the golden mean.
And not only that, it combines earth, fire, and water and air into a unified chemical.
Three times 666 equals 1998.
What's the vortices?
It's right in front of us all the time.
The inverse.
The interior is nylon lined for easy on and off.
Ooh.
The strings are aligned with nylon for.
So what, it takes your soul off?
Your skin.
Finally.
The vortices.
What do you mean the vortices?
First, you take the skin off of the feet.
String theory.
Okay.
What is string theory?
Now, the power here.
String theory is what superstitious scientists came up with because they couldn't understand
the interstitial vortices.
Exactly.
The phylogenetic phylogenetic.
They knew that.
Stephen Hawking could not quite grasp the interstitial vortices.
No, he couldn't do it because he wasn't a subgenius.
So they had to come up with all these other silly.
I might add that if any of your subgeniuses out there are interested in an in-depth analysis
of this concept, it's simply look at the new edition, the new printing of Revelation X.
Oh, yes.
The new printing.
We forgot.
We forgot the swag.
The new printing.
The new reprinted.
Long out of print.
Revelation X is back in stores.
The Bob Apocryphon.
Oh.
The Bob Apocryphon is back in stores these days.
Wow.
Not that you should buy it.
No, you should buy it.
We can't.
You should buy it and give it to a friend.
Give it to me.
I don't even have one.
I don't even get one.
You should buy it and donate it to science.
This is a buy as a whole.
This is a revised edition, by the way.
As the M. Hope F. Innocent, the first person.
We have to go through it.
I don't even know.
We've gotten a...
Which edition is it?
The new Revelation X has unpersoned a couple of people.
Unpersoned?
War in heaven became war is heaven.
Yeah.
You know, the good thing about it, don't we go into detail on the interstitial vortices
in that book?
Really?
The Dallas P.O.
Box is now the Cleveland.
What is it?
Okay.
Tell me about...
Because the vortices now, as far as...
So the ten strings that are rotating...
There's a balance between pain and pleasure.
The ten strings that are rotating...
That's right.
The dynamo of pain and pleasure.
The whirlpool.
The whirlpool of pain and pleasure.
You have to listen to Philo, Michael.
Okay, go ahead.
They will...
It's the dynamo.
It's the eddies that are created between the dynamos of pain and pleasure, balancing
each other out.
They create this vortex.
And the vortices are contiguous with each other simultaneously.
And yet, each one is its own separate unit.
And separated.
And separated by their own interstitial area, which we call the interstitial vortices.
Dr. Drummond just explained the makeup of the universe and the meaning of life.
And you weren't even paying attention.
No, he wasn't.
Where are you, folks?
I was.
He's so broke.
He can't even pay attention.
I can't believe this, that I found out about six meanings of life just tonight only.
And you love people.
Okay, so this is the interstitial...
And your assignment...
Your assignment...
You have to learn...
You have to pick which one is valid.
Michael told me he was so broke...
I would say so far, the interstitial vortices has it over everything I've heard so far.
If you read the back end of Revelation X, there is a very detailed description of the
theory of the interstitial vortices, including illustrations.
Where can I get a copy of that?
You can get Revelation X from any better bookstore, as well as things like Walmart.com.
The evil...
Well, I should say, the evil Walmart.com.
The terrible Amazon.com.
We only...
And, you know, we only shop at Walmart because their prices are so high.
Hal Robbins' dinosaur book.
All right, Hal Robbins, who is...
Who has just walked in.
Rumored to have just walked in.
Yes, it's true.
It's true.
Dr. Howe has...
Dr. Howe is here in the flesh for the first time.
In the flesh.
Someone who knows how to use the shift key on their computer.
Yeah.
A man with a vocabulary five times larger than the entire English language.
Those are my organs.
Keep away from that.
Those are my extras.
In case I...
Now, you know, in China, you can sell those.
Dr. Howe is now being interviewed by Princess Marie.
You can lose a tongue talking too much on the radio.
That's the best part of the show.
$10,000 a kidney.
I know.
The way she's taking off his clothes, though, it...
I can go eat dinner.
It's a little bit perky.
Look, here's somebody left this food thing here.
It's still got something in it.
It's called bourbon tree.
Hey, stay away from that.
Chocolate cream biscuits.
Look.
Wait, that's...
That's laced with 325 milligrams of LSD-25.
Okay.
Bourbon tree.
He's just going to eat it.
Bourbon tree street.
Now, back in the old days...
I don't know.
The subgeniuses didn't have brains, per se.
They just had this sort of a nerve center at the end of their...
At their hind end.
This nerve center served as a thinking mechanism,
which caused them to be able to discern between pleasure and pain.
Gravitating towards the one and moving away from the other,
they found their little cubby holes.
They found their little cubby holes.
Uh-oh.
A special bulletin has just been handed to me.
Oh, my God.
Stand by as we switch you over to our main studio.
A report from the DuPont Company of Wilmington, Delaware has just been received.
Hurry.
The news is that fabrics containing Dacron polyester made by DuPont
are now being prepared for the special scientific heat treatment.
This means all garments made from this specifically treated fabric
can later be durably pressed for the perfect outer shape.
And that fabric has been used to create this new Hal Robbins book,
which, since I'm not a member of this station, I can promote, I guess.
Dinosaur Alphabet by Harry S.
Can you believe that?
Harry S. Robbins.
I knew that was his name.
Dr. Hal, his new book,
which is absolutely one of the most...
...good books.
...gorgeous dinosaur art books.
Well, it is the most gorgeous dinosaur art book ever seen.
Yeah, but is it...
Dinosaur Alphabet.
Is it real or is it fantasy?
No, it's...
Well, it is sort of fantasy.
These dinosaurs are better than anatomically correct.
They're colored in a way that has to be fancy.
You know, no one's ever proven...
Are their sexual organs enhanced?
No one really knows what color...
No one's ever proven that dinosaurs existed in any form other than bones.
That's all we have.
That's right.
What makes anyone think...
Not only that, but there are poetic paragraphs
that go with each of these full-page color...
They're almost like paintings, really.
Man's best friend.
Yang Chuanosaurus hid away from the prey on which he dined,
panting in the heat of midday,
crouching in his hunter's blind.
An ambush predator.
Yang Chuanosaurus, though...
Just doesn't sound right.
Yang Chuanosaurus, though.
It's very interesting to me.
And there's a...
At the end of it, there's a kind of a bibliography
that describes the details about each of these fabulous creatures.
Who wants to know details?
But they're not fabulous.
They're real animals that really existed.
I want the gross scanned overview.
I don't want details.
Like Gigantosnotosaurus, which lived in Argentina.
They're doing a terrible call.
Had to flee to Argentina, because it was...
Bigger than the...
Bigger than three Tyrannosaurus rexes standing on each other's piggyback.
By the way, we have to do an ID here.
This is Over the Edge and the Puzzling Evidence Show combined and homogenized for your convenience.
Now, now.
Girl, what idea, baby, is that?
Oh, I know.
You should draw a face.
It was a nice face.
You'll turn me, baby, into a baby.
No, he's yours.
Not much more.
This has been such a wonderful excesslessness mess.
It's not over yet.
We're going till 5 a.m. this morning.
That means we'll get more presents.
There are probably 20 to 30 people in the studio, each one of them with an instrument.
It's the proof of karma, friends.
I brought Phineas Narco a copy of the Bobliographon, because he's got some pieces in it.
And the karma, I had instant karma happen when Dr. Howell brought me a copy of his new
book, The Dinosaur Alphabet, by Harry...
S. Robbins.
And by the way, Robbins is spelled with one B. I bet you radio listening illiterates didn't
know that.
Some of them may have known it.
And some may have known about it and repressed the memory.
Well, I'm not a radio illiterate, and I didn't know that.
But you do now.
What does it matter when one knew something, so long as one knows it?
What's important is that when you type into that search engine in the bookstore...
See?
I got you.
You used the name Robbins with the one B.
Like the bird.
Look, you can either feed a man and he's full for one day, or I can teach you, I can
give you this fishing pole and teach you to fish and you can go feed yourself forever.
No, putting down that fishing pole.
You're not supposed to hit Hal with a fishing pole.
Stop it!
Trout almondine?
Is it true, Reverend Stang, that the new...
Is the new edition of Revelation X is digest-sized?
No, no, it is not.
It's exactly like the original.
No, no, it's full-sized.
Oh, it's not shrunken.
It's one to one scale.
In fact, aficionados of the Church of the Subgenius will want to lay out their old
copy right next to their new copy, because they'll want to have a new copy to keep their
old copy in shape for its future value, as well as being able to have a new coffee table
edition to show to their friends on their evenings of entertainment and frivolity.
The third Subgenius holy book, which I always forget the title of...
If you buy a Revelation X, you get the coffee table?
The Cyclopedia of Slack with Bob Leografon is small.
It's not digest-sized.
It's family Bible-sized.
It is a beautiful book.
It is nice and small.
It's like a family Bible.
The earlier books are more like coffee table books.
Well, it hasn't got smaller, a la the Penguin.
It's small and compact.
It's tough.
In any case, you'll want to lay your old one next to your new one and look at them
page by page and try to study them to figure out what's different, what's changed, and
where is Waldo?
That's the big selling point of the new edition of Revelation X is that 23 of the pages are
very subtly different.
And if you can find all those differences, then you win, of course, the trip to Dobson.
As seen in the book.
We've seen it on television.
Tremendous honor, of course.
Well, YouTube, anyway.
An unspoken assumption of the expanding Earth theory is that dinosaurs were actually like
the size of chickens back then.
Well, yeah, but the Earth was only the size of mercury back then.
So, it's an expanding universe.
Exactly.
So, dinosaurs were really dinky little things.
But since then, the elastic has weakened.
But if people had been around, they would have been the size of G.I.
Joe.
But since then, the elastic has weakened.
Well, it would have been like the blue whales of their day.
There were many whales, whines, and complaints, but nothing was done.
It makes sense because those dragonfly fossils and stuff, they're impossibly big.
They had a meter-wide wingspan in the fossils,
but since they've just grown from their original standard size as we see them now.
They found fossilized frock sticks that were 15 feet long.
They did. Well, I guess they were prospecting in the proper garden then.
There were giants in the earth in those days.
Everything was turned into giants over the millions of years as fossils.
I have a theory.
Dinosaurs were able to get so large because gravity was actually less in those days.
But what about...
What about gravity?
Now, people ask me, well, how could that be possible?
And I ask you, why not?
We don't know anything about gravity.
We don't know what planet this is.
We don't even know what it is.
What makes it, how it gets here.
I say that in the early days, it was probably because the earth was spinning slower or faster,
but the gravity was less.
Well, if the earth was smaller, of course the gravity would be less.
No, it wasn't that much smaller.
That wouldn't make that much difference, but gravity would.
A fraction of its size would make a heck of a difference.
Nothing can grow that big today because they'd have an immediate heart attack
as they were crushed by their own organs.
It's too big. It's too heavy.
Well, it didn't happen at once.
I'm trying to realize.
How?
Gravity is like a moon that's down.
There were no dinosaurs when the earth was the size of the moon.
Well, that's the whole point.
Of course there were because they popped into the earth.
Funfella, Tilton.
Oh, suicide man, you're crazy.
This is the first time everybody's used this ever.
And put your hands on the glass.
Well, let me accuse you once again.
Dr. Dean Scott, I think...
That's a crazy idea.
I'm not a Christian.
Well, it is crazy.
I don't want to describe to his Christianity.
But it is true that things were different on this planet at different times in its history.
And I also love Dr. Dean Scott.
What is crazy anyway?
You wouldn't recognize it.
I think it's a mac and mack.
It's a mac and mack.
It's like a giant insect.
But the atmosphere used to be quite different.
It's just being not reality oriented.
You didn't have insanity.
Or did you?
Was it all insanity?
Gravity was less.
Mark my words.
And really insanity didn't exist since the human race didn't exist.
Can an animal be insane?
There was also more energy to exploit.
More food to eat.
More fecundity of the earth.
That wouldn't account for the vital ability to grow.
None of that would account for the vitality of the earth.
the gigantic size of these things and the gigantic ability to attain gigantic size they attained it
only because the gravity allowed them to it would not connect
giant reptiles have persisted through into many ages including the age of man
yes the megalania of uh the australian continent is one example an enormous
broadcasting from the factory of tiny dogs company what that's alive today in the 21st century
you can look at fossils of raindrops and they're a lot relative of the
well-known dragon what accounts for that much larger less gravity what was the big
shark
if i was running for office today i would advocate gravity reduction everything would be bigger
everything would be lighter you could lift more you could jump higher it would be great it was
like that on our original planet what's now called mars it would take care of the obesity
gravity and there had to be a compromise which would end up just about where it is now
this whole argument is so moot
because the planets were switched in 1945. the planets were switched in 1945
it's in the book what is this it's in the book it's in the new genius book check it out
this is official subgenius doctrine dr howell what do you know the truth of the experience
the earth
expands in a certain sense
the earth is constantly being pelted by extra planetary material
in a dramatically increased
god pelts the earth with extremely like a chimpanzee thrown at his enemies
in his frustration
cosmic uh
sprinter
The cosmic constant of fecal peltings.
In other words, if you were to take a one-meter-sized piece of platinum and put it in a vault,
in 100 million years, it should be like four or five meters huge.
Here's another thing. Forbidden sciences teach us that gravity is not something that sucks you towards the nearest, the biggest mass,
but pressure from outer space pushing down on you against the Earth.
That's why things fall, is because outer space is pressing down on us.
Our science, Earth science, is so primitive. It's really in its infancy.
It's crude. It's based on language, which you feel good science would be based on things in themselves,
if they could be proved to exist.
Right. We're...
We're babies compared to the people from the future.
My former employers, I might add.
Science is really...
And the excess.
What can we do about the people from the future?
Primal energies of the animal man.
We can't do anything about the people from the future except not give birth to them.
Yeah.
It's too late for me.
I already gave birth to two of the people from the future.
Well, I managed to wither a lot of hell.
Were they older than they were at the time you saw them a moment ago?
No, I'm talking about the UFOs are the...
Oh, yeah.
Well, they made it with the subgeniuses, right?
Is that how the Yeti became more than man?
No, it's really the Exus just flat out instant created the Yetis as a perfect creature.
They were able to give life to...
They were able to create new life forms.
They're certainly a...
The Yeti was...
The Yeti was the smartest animal on the earth.
The Yetis then created the humans much the same way by quick mutating a certain type of rat.
Monkey seed.
Monkey tube.
So really, humans were the lab rats of the Yetis.
Yeah.
But a stunted, retarded Yeti made the mistake of freeing the humans and teaching them fire and language.
Fire.
And that's when the conspiracy was born.
It's just that...
Wow.
That's...
There was a traitor Yeti.
If you try to look for the...
That's horrible.
You know, they should have just let them fall back into the slime.
...know when you're going to be looking for them.
Why teach them?
Why educate them?
I mean, if they're only going to raise themselves up and out of the slime.
It's not like a good idea at the time.
Well, actually, the Yetis did go out and exterminate most of the humans, but some of them...
They survived.
...were projected by time control.
They were projected by time control into about 100,000 years ago where Cro-Magnon Man suddenly appeared and wiped out all the other wonderful, pleasant humanoids.
Yeah, good-looking Neanderthals.
Yeah, Neanderthals, the Homo erectus and the Homo connectus.
You have the return of that in Jay Leno, you know, that's got the prognathus.
I know, he's got the big jaw of the Neanderthals.
And Anthony Robbins.
Yeah.
He appeals, of course, to the mind.
Yes, they're both that uber-human...
What do they call that?
Well, Jay Leno has that superhuman jaw like Bob does.
The jaw of the football.
J.R. Bob Dobbs has a jawbone like that.
It is the jawbone of the Yeti.
Yes, a strong jaw, almost prognathous of a larger primate such as Gigantopithecus...
Or J.R. Bob Dobbs.
...or Gorilla or J.R. Bob Dobbs.
But...
The Yeti now is such a much larger animal, the most subgeni I know, and it seems rather dwarf compared to the Yeti.
Well, that's neither here nor there, you know.
Hitler wasn't very Aryan either.
Yes, true.
As far as ideological purity is concerned, do as we say, not as we do.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'll practice.
We can do what we want and you can do what you want.
As Bob said, I don't practice what I preach because I'm not the kind of person I preach in favor.
Here, here.
Exactly.
Neuronicus 1.14.
You have to be crazy.
You better say, don't let your followers practice and we'll tear you into thousands of pieces.
Many of us are tired, ready to lay our bodies down.
I have the pain of a hundred million hells.
Above all, a subgenius needs slack.
That is it. The subgenius must have slack.
It's not that the subgenius needs slack.
The subgenius must have slack.
The subgenius is born with slack.
It doesn't mean that slack is not something you go out and acquire.
Slack is what you have.
The subgenius, to be a subgenius, must have slack.
You were born with original slack, but the conspiracy took it away from you.
That's right.
Tell us.
As heard on TV.
Why?
Uh.
That conspiracy forced you to purchase false slack.
And now you don't even know what real slack is.
You don't get to pay a dime for your slack.
That's a fact.
So if you're having a slack attack, you can find out how American people...
You must have it, is what you're saying.
So if you're having a slack attack, check out Revelation X at better bookstores everywhere.
At subgenius.com.
Does the cover look just like the other cover?
Yes, it is identical.
Same colors?
Yes.
It all looks...
In fact, I'd have a copy for you, Dr. Howell, but I gave them...
All the ones that I had, I gave them away to my nieces and nephews in Stang County, Texas.
For me?
Well, that's all right, I guess.
Oh, I can mail you one.
But those youths had never been in the...
Never been exposed to the word of Bob in this form at all.
Well, you better make sure...
You've read Revelation X because you co-authored it.
Urban youths ought to be exposed to this kind of literature.
The youths of America deserve nothing less than full exposure to the subgenius doctrine.
But are you saying that the authors of subgenius doctrine, Revelation X,
are also working on...
Are you saying that the authors of subgenius doctrine, Revelation X,
are also working on the minds of tiny little helpless innocent children?
Tiny little midgets?
Well, as Bob ordered us to, yes, of course we are.
You're only following orders?
A little innocent, precious, fresh mind.
I know what you mean, Michael Pepe, because every little innocent life is of inestimable value to us here in the Church of the Subgenius.
Every tiny little runny pipsqueak...
Every tiny little helpless...
Every little long toddlin' down the pike is to us a brother...
And he toddles into a bookstore...
...who deserves to be coddled and burped and tickled...
Yeah, where did they get that black stuff?
And, uh...
But there comes a time when you have to draw the line somewhere...
Mommy!
And that line is www.subgenius.com.
You have been listening to The Hour of Slack, although this time it was a rerun of the KPFA over-the-edge and puzzling evidence show.
So nonetheless, it is an hour of slack.
Or just was.
Subgenius.com.
Praise Bob, and thank you.