What the hell do you think you're doing?
Superior mutants.
Repent.
Quit your job.
The world ends tomorrow.
And you may die.
Well, no, probably not, but whatever you do, just keep listening.
The Church of the Subgenius could save your sanity with...
Are we controlled by secret forces?
Do you ever get the feeling that free will is a joke?
Do people think you're strange?
Do you?
Then you may be on the right track.
Are alien space monsters bringing a startling new world?
Jehovah is an alien and still threatens this planet.
Now, at last, the step-by-step process is revealed.
This is it.
The only faith that promises action, thrills, success in sex and business.
Get all your slack and more.
The Subgenius.
At last, I have control of your radio tubes.
And I do, too.
Good.
This is Ren Huak.
And this is Stimson J. Catt of the Ren and Stimpy Show.
And you're listening to the Hour of Slack.
Keep listening.
Keep listening, you idiots.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Else I shall deal you.
Well, well, well, well, well.
You're dead.
You're so dead.
We're back.
The sounds have resumed in my head.
And in your head as well.
Yes.
It's so beautiful.
Burgeoning clouds over the distant horizon.
So deep and echoey.
The sounds recur.
The brain grows in its blast-out fluid.
The plasma glowing.
So beautiful and pink.
It's lovely to see you burn again.
Hi.
Oh.
Nothing is forever cerebral.
Hydrofluids.
CHF.
Let us drift our minds.
Ooh, scary.
To blanker hands.
Nothing.
Ooh.
As the puffing slowly drift towards the individual parts of your mind.
How many individual parts are there?
It's the pipeline, can't you see?
It's the pipeline.
Nothing.
It's bringing the nutrients deep inside to where we can work with them.
It's the nexus of all creation.
It's the basis of our economic and commercial life.
It gives us bread and cheese.
It gives us an egg in it.
It gives us the crabs.
It gives us everything.
Everything?
Almost everything.
It gives us the church of the sub-knuckle sandwich.
It gives us vague ideas of liberation and freedom which we cannot understand or explain
to others.
Let me I live in this lonely room.
To cry.
And to warn the others.
Yes.
We must warn them.
We must.
Yes.
Because the time grows nigh.
Nigh.
The time grows nigh.
It's night time for the good life and Henry's wooden eye.
Ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay.
The revolution begins immediately.
Yeah.
Ohhhhhhh!
Nice beaver.
I'm sorry, I'm caught in traffic.
It may be a while before anybody can get into the station.
Don't you have an emergency DJ?
Somebody with a deep voice hidden in a kitchen.
drawer? Just follow the formats. You've only got a few more hours. I have all the characteristics
of a human being. Flesh, blood, skin, hair. But not a single clear identifiable emotion
except for greed and disgust. Something horrible is happening inside of me and I don't know why.
Don't congratulate yourself now, Doctor. D-O-K, Doctor. Sit down in that chaise large.
Place your feet behind Chaz's ears and begin rubbing slowly.
Eh? Little blue ones that dance in front of your eyes. Just reach over and take one of
these Sumerian tablets. I think you'll feel the presence of something that goes way, way
back. Once you do, the floodgates will be all open. Nice and open.
The greatest trick the Devil ever pulled was convincing the world he didn't exist. And
like that, he's gone. You, dipstick, sties. It makes me laugh. You're all dead. You're
all dead.
Take them to the secret broadcast cave and train them all to talk like me. Real sexy.
Enchanted and raptured and bombed.
So you say you're a tough bratty.
Yeah, I'm a tough bratty.
What do you mean by that? You've been around the block, huh?
Yeah, well, you know, I didn't fall out of the tree yesterday, you know?
No, you didn't fall out of the tree. You look like you maybe fell out of a truck.
Well, going around the block. You know what I'm saying? Now look, watch. See? Now listen.
Look.
Talk like that. I mean, you know, talk like that about me, go ahead.
Come on, guy. I've seen roughly three times.
I've seen roughly three times.
I remember you had a pair of very rouged faces like yours before, and I know what you're
up to, see? There's nothing in my wallet but a pair of, uh, listen here. Now watch. Now
look, see? Listen.
Hey, what are you guys going on about? Okay, just, okay. Now I think I've got it figured
out.
You should be able to figure it out, Wilt.
Let me say the thing that makes me feel like I'm on the radio. Ah yes, dear friends.
I feel like I'm sitting at my spaceship console because the station here, downtown, is a spaceship.
WCSB, where we originate, has been completely revised and revamped, amped up.
It's beautiful.
It's so spaceship-like now.
It's like a Star Trek set.
It literally is.
In fact, I think if this were put in a Star Trek set back in those days, they would be confused and amazed.
Well, actually, right where I'm sitting looks like a Star Trek set, and the rest of it looks like a Tarzan set.
As it always did.
Yes, the burnt cork walls.
The strewn-about sandwiches on the floor.
The pieces of detritus left for years.
That's the way I started.
The vanished lives.
A fine patina of detritus, yes.
A real station is that way, friends.
A free station.
The kind of station that will tell you the truth.
As if you wanted to know the truth.
Real truth.
And here's the parade of truths coming up the road.
Oh, this is...
Very awkward truths.
Very awkward.
Amazing truths.
Ugly truths.
Very ugly.
Ugly, indeed.
You know, I've noticed...
Drunken truths.
Some of these are falling down.
I've noticed that the Church of the Subgenius makes much ado about the articles of faith,
but like any articles on the commercial market, they come and go as they're packaged.
One week it's this article.
The next week it's a pair of shoes, perhaps from Brazil.
Brightly shined up to meet the neighbors.
If there are any left...
Yes.
That's so.
But don't you see...
Bob's a short-duration personal savior.
He's a short...
He's a tall man, too, isn't he?
Very tall.
Well, he's not as tall as he looks up on stage.
No.
You're right.
People often say that to Bob.
He's not as tall as I thought you were.
Yeah, it's like the way they used to shoot Richard Wagner and Alan Ladd in the old days.
Bob actually usually, when he's going to be dealing with the press and so forth,
he would duct tape an apple crate to each shoe so that he would look taller and more impressive.
You know, tall people...
That accounts for the clacking sound.
Yeah.
It was a psycho-mysterian experience when he'd walk into a room to hear that kind of thudding of an empty orange crate.
The clink, clink, clink.
And it was actually his mudden slippers.
Well, they almost...
But it was so impressive with Bob doing it.
I mean, it would look stupid with anybody else.
But somehow with him, it was perfectly stupid.
It did look magical.
And it was...
It got...
It would have been a fad and then a trend and then an army, a movement.
But Bob...
He actually, after a while...
He got tired of pretending to be something he wasn't.
Well, the thing is, really, only Bob could pull that off.
I mean, nobody else could really pull it off.
It's just, you know, he was the one with the Elan and, you know, just the...
Well, he had the seven virtues.
You know what I mean?
For crying out loud, he could have been Buddha, but he was a fat ass instead, you know?
What are the seven virtues?
Snakey hair, lovely feet, charming breath and overtures, a beautiful, billow-ish complexion,
strangeness when it comes to appertaining the mysteries of science and...
An ability to write art, great figutors and...
I guess that's nine.
So, you're not a very virtuous fellow, I suppose.
No, no, I have no virtues.
I have the seven ugly vices, which consist of gluttony, sloth or sloth, avarice, which
consists of lust and...
What are the other ones?
Dave, can you hear this music in the background?
Yeah.
It sounds like...
It's not about eating too much.
It's like what we listen to at the...
Berkesgaden.
It's...
Berkenslaken.
It mixes with Tumble and Tumbleweeds, I think.
Is it Spike?
No, it's this music that we're playing in the background.
In fact, all of the music in the background, probably the whole show mayhaps, is from
something called...
A band called People Like Us, but it's really a woman named Vicky Bennett from England.
Vicky Bennett.
And as David...
as the great Saint David Botner said,
if she's not already a subgenius minister,
she's definitely a latent subgenius.
The best way I can describe her audio work
is a satirical collage of old lounge records,
children's shows, bad British radio,
and country music with hilarious timing.
Her new album, Abridged Too Far,
is available online as an MP3 album
complete with cover artwork, CD label, and everything.
Apparently she finds that releasing her album
the conventional way is no longer worth the bother.
And the new album, Abridged Too Far,
can be downloaded at www.ubu.com.
U-B-U, as in King Ubu.
Ubu Roy, another Shordurper Sav among the subgeniuses,
and an old friend of J.R. Bob Dobbs.
And maybe from a pair of Ubu people around here, perhaps.
No, no.
Those are...
That's a modern-day rock band.
Bob used to hang around with Alfred Jerry.
I heard he did.
And Ubu himself, the real person.
The real Roy.
Right.
Yeah.
Yes, sir.
Yes, he used to drink absinthe
and fart slowly in the midnight hours.
He'd stare out his Montmartre window
and listen to the cobblestones crackle below him.
The old fish vendors walking by,
singing songs about fish and stuff.
Sometimes an errant one-eyed jackal would wander by.
You know, that can put the fear...
Bob Dobbs in you.
You know, you're staring out your window in the left bank
and suddenly you're staring at a one-eyed jackal or hyena.
And they're giving you transliminal subsequent messages.
And these are very hard to distinguish.
I've got the world on my string.
Sitting on my...
I've got you.
And look what we've all got.
There's a neatly exposed medulla oblongata.
We're making a decision all the way from north to south.
I've got you.
And we're going to cut out a little part right here in the middle flap.
And that's going to be our east-west direction.
Okay, I want you kids back in there.
Can you see me right there?
Can you see me?
Yeah, but what's that smell?
You wake up in your bed and...
Well, that's the barbecue flavor that we try to implant each one of our cadavers with.
Stay in Wonderland.
Especially, especially done for the research we do at Hadware Labs from the Church of the Subgenius.
And all these cadavers, believe me, are like within days, days fresh.
We don't let anything sit out in the sun too long.
And we can't, by law, let anything sit here too long.
If you look here, notice that this is a little epicanthic-looking fold here.
This piece of leathery yellow stuff is actually what keeps the subgenius brain intact.
If not, it'll just fall apart on all four.
Four north, west, east, south corners.
And leading to what many call the interior moxibustion collapse.
Which I wasn't seeing.
I know you can, though.
Just put your nose a little closer there.
Oh, no, I really would rather...
No, you've got to rub it in there if you really want to get the right kind of feeling.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, I see you're one of the chosen ones already.
Your hair's turning pink.
That's lovely.
Oh, your hands are glowing.
Oh, that's disgusting.
You're one of us, baby.
Here, slap one right here.
Okay.
You're going to have to sign this, though.
You must shut down your transmitter.
Shut it down.
We're not serious.
I've got the clamp the lid on this business.
Stop these communications.
Oh, damn.
No.
It lies within your power, Mr. President.
You can declare a national emergency.
I don't have to.
It's here.
But I don't.
And not merely national.
Wait, I'm getting a no-go signal.
Now I'm losing one of the craft.
Hey, Bermuda, you getting it?
Oh, lost contact.
You're always all right, Dave.
Right.
I was.
I had a little mistake.
It's called the Reverend Haven Sting.
Oh, and speaking of mistakes, it would be a real mistake to let this amazing book go by
without your knowing about it.
Friends, I'm going to do a book review.
It's been a long time since we've done book reviews on the Hour of Slack.
Princess Wee has been skimming this book.
You know our friend Dr. Howell?
The great Dr. Howell of the Puzzling Evidence Show and so forth.
He has now a book out from Frog Limited Press.
Frog Limited?
Well, friends, the title of this book is
The Meaning of Lost and Mismatched Socks,
illustrated and written by Dr. Howell under the name of Dr. Perditus Pedale.
A rather official sounding name for a man who has no credentials whatsoever.
Which means lost socks.
I don't know how he can write a book.
He's not very fat of a volume.
Actually, no, it's not a real big book,
but it goes into quite a bit of detail as to what could possibly be behind the disappearance of,
you know how it is, lost and mismatched socks.
There's just never the, there's so many possible explanations for this thing.
Yes.
This phenomenon.
It is indeed a phenomenon.
We even explored it ourselves one time under the phenomenon, the car keys,
which are a phenomenon.
It's a form of, like in Greek mythology, the herpes or whatever.
No, the, the harpies.
Yes.
And it caused mischief in your life and your afterlife.
As, as doctor, actually, I should put on, uh.
His music.
A different, a different, uh, background.
Probably something exciting.
Music here.
Ensuring, like.
The innate hostility of the universe.
If losing socks is simply to be considered an aberrant habit,
then it can, like other forms of human behavior,
be modified.
Modified and ultimately eliminated.
Yet, throughout the years,
statistical and actuarial studies have revealed a startling increase
in the value of actual lost sock ranges over, over predicted values.
In simpler terms, human blundering falls far short of being the entire explanation of the problem.
It can only be concluded that the universe and the socks themselves
are up.
To something.
A down socks.
Did they?
Well, you know, life itself tends to organize itself from inorganic matter and reveals a propensity towards a move towards order.
And yet the overwhelming mass of the rest of the universe acts in precisely the opposite way and is actively engaged in devolving or
disorganizing.
The random factor.
This far more immense process has, within its vast complexity and subtlety,
a quality which, when viewed from a human vantage point,
may as well be understood as behaving like a malignant intelligence.
Yes!
That is, the universe is out to get us.
And don't you feel, my friend, that the universe is, in fact, out to get you.
And the lost sock is the least of your concern.
That is, the universe's past is going to be the beginning of your problems, I am well imagined.
Yes!
They take forms, they take shapes, they take different personalities.
Could be the old lady on the block next to your block head.
The universe is out to get you on the cellular level.
Not one of yourselves is getting better.
They're all getting older.
Everything comes apart, one way or another, as J.R. Bob-Bob once said.
And the teeth are getting even.
Well.
Not.
Oh, yes.
Then it crumbles.
They're taking you down molecule by molecule.
They're erasing your personality.
The last vestiges of flesh stretched out over this easy canvas which you...
You're so lapse-heartedly laxly...
You think you can get away with something I can't...
And you think you have it bad, Sam.
You think you've got it bad.
You think you've got it...
Think if you were a poor little chimpanzee.
A bonobo chimpanzee.
Those wonderful, beautiful, horny little relatives in the Congo.
The bonobo chimpanzees.
They wear diapers, don't they?
They wear French ticklers.
They wear all sorts of marital aids.
Because these chimpanzees, unlike the normal pantroglodyte chimpanzee,
these little yetis, as we call them,
have a society based on sex.
A matriarchal society.
Where if there's an argument between mom and son,
or dad and niece,
why, they just...
They don't fight.
They don't yell.
They have sex.
They make love, not war.
Yes, they make love, not war.
No matter who they're...
You know, who it is.
Boy, girl, chimp.
As long as it's a chimp.
Girl, girl, chimp.
You know.
Mom, son, chimp.
They wouldn't do an Englishman.
Coconut that resembles a chimp over there by that rock.
Oh, sorry.
So...
It's rough, friends.
Being a bonobo.
These pygmy chimpanzees...
It's rougher than butter.
Have been, uh...
Harder than a sled.
You've taken it down.
You know all the numbers.
Oh, yes. Oh, yes.
Only one in...
Yes.
How many?
Five.
Only bonobos.
Anyway, there aren't many bonobos left, friends.
Because they're being served in Belgian restaurants and so forth.
Unfortunately.
Ten euros gets you a bonobo.
Over easy.
Ha, ha.
Get it?
Over easy.
Oh, yeah.
Fresh love before they are brought to your table.
Oh, the special fluids.
Don't worry.
There are plenty of those.
And we braise them lightly.
Oh, yes.
The fluids.
The combination of central olives.
And then we flavor them with a clarified butter.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
Shut the fuck up.
I'm afraid I must ask you to stop.
Oh, beloved monitor.
I'm sorry.
I believe, beloved, beloved...
Public hold what?
Get up, sir.
I'll be forced to take you in for counseling action.
Oh, beloved brother.
You have done much good.
Much good.
Bless you.
We do not ask for worship, sir.
Only cooperation for the common purpose.
I'm afraid I must ask for your literature.
Oh.
You.
I'll be for what you know.
I hear you have taken all of these salt from the village.
What gives you the right to do this to our people?
I was chosen.
I was the one who was chosen.
I looked in the reflective waters.
I saw my own face.
That is how I know.
But you were chosen by whom?
The reflective face in your waters?
No.
No, senor, you cannot be, you can only be chosen by the St. Alpharetta Potinto that lives down by the, well, you know, used to live before she was canonized.
Well, listen, you can't do that.
Go to hell, we don't need no stinking popes or religions or Baptists or anything.
We need only our slack and our love and our flesh and our meat.
Lots of meat.
Tons of meat.
More meat.
A lot more meat.
Give me your meat, man.
Give me, you fool, give me more meat.
More meat for me.
I will have your meat.
You pink boy, I will make you a red charcoal broiled boy.
I need karate chops.
I will bury you and eat you.
Not in that order.
You know nothing.
I have learned nothing, I can say.
Come on, boys.
You don't know how to fight like that.
Why don't you be like the bonobos and make love?
Not fight.
What?
I need to make some rice.
I want to make some, um, yeah, yeah.
What's up with these?
Hey, pull the flamenco player, pull the flamenco player back away from the mic.
I need to make some pie.
That's better.
Yeah, okay.
Kill the fat flamenco player.
So good looking, though.
Suck.
Listen, he does know what the hell he's doing.
Listen to that.
Thank God.
What a silly man and what a silly group of people assembled here together to learn the magic truth.
Silly people.
We.
My favorite people.
Yeah, it's mine, too.
Especially when afterwards, when they accept the structure of the subgenius, we take them
out in the parking lot and liquidate them for their fat.
And as we render the fat down, we sell it back to the big oil companies for a lot of
money.
We got that idea from Fight Club.
Yeah.
That was, it was brilliant.
I'm not supposed to mention that one.
No, no, no.
We steal them when we can, don't we?
And we steal these foraging little peptudes wherever we can find them, too.
Look at the one with the red hair.
He's got lots of jumbo.
That's what they call it.
Hey mate,
kept up in all.
They know the sound.
Somebody help.
In any case, somebody will help.
Someone will answer your pleas.
I cannot fly in the face of 180 years of America.
No, don't fly in my face.
For God's sake.
I cannot start a war.
A month from now, we may not have the strength to fight one.
The Russians may have in their hands the power now.
Ah, we're re-militarizing.
This country will not launch a war.
George W. Bush is our leader.
U.S. Space Corps.
We've served a great many years together.
And there's never been a day when I couldn't happily go along with any decision of yours.
But I have a responsibility to this country, too.
And I can't stand by and see it destroyed.
Our difference is that I don't believe it.
It can be destroyed.
By 13 slips of paper covered with obscure symbols.
Yeah.
The Japanese Empire was destroyed.
Oh, there it went.
Oh, no.
The country's gone too bad.
Bummer, man.
13 obscure symbols, indeed.
If only you had learned the lessons that we're willing to teach him for a mere $30 American money.
But yet, slack was within their grasp.
It was inches away.
They had slack right in front of them.
And yet, they let it slip away.
Pig ignorant as they are.
Yes.
That's the word.
Ham-fisted and pig ignorant.
Yes.
Pathetic.
The pig clats.
The clats were called pig ignorant.
Yes.
I can hear you in the distance calling out my name.
I can hear you up close stabbing me with your name.
I can see you getting closer.
Trying.
Trying to infect my brain.
My brain is not infected.
My brain is pure.
As is yours, sir.
Pure.
One brain cell.
One crystalline pure brain cell.
Don't need no more than one.
One's good unity.
The unity of all things.
The one.
One.
Get down inside your own brain, man.
Check it out.
To thine own self be true, dude.
The armature.
Turn off the TV.
Not the radio.
Just the TV.
Just relax and get into it, man.
You know, just stop.
Why do you let the world rush you along, man?
Don't let some robot traffic light boss you around.
So it turned red.
Are you going to take orders from the robot?
Red.
Don't let the robots push you around.
Blow off those traffic lights, man.
Use your hypothalamus.
By the way, the opinions expressed on this show are not necessarily those of the station
or the station management or the people singing in the background on the station shows or
the janitor who sutures the station manager together in emergency situations, which, if
this were an emergency, you would feel that you were overdosing on some sort of very bad
and strong psychedelic drug.
Thank you.
I guess that is.
This is exactly what has happened here.
Once again, these kids have just decided to get high instead of work or discipline themselves
or show any sort of interest in improving or learning.
These kids these days.
Some of them are 500 years old.
Whimpering wimps of negative nabobistic dobsism.
What's the next one?
Well, they're pretty old for kids, but yet look.
Listen to them.
They're like little flowers.
Some of them are wearing those real cute little pink slippers.
I like to shoot them in.
Oh, boy, makes their parents cry.
We chop their feet up.
Who keeps who's in the back of the train?
OK, who's back there fooling around with the switches?
I need to remind each and every one of you.
I'm following that.
I'm going to be doing a hell of a fine job steering things around.
We're navigating through a blizzard of confused ideas and some pretty rough water when it
comes to our actual compost.
You know, but we try.
I can't really remember what we're trying right now.
Oh, my God.
Come on, come on.
Oh, yeah.
Man.
OK, I'm going to start blowing rubble.
I have to.
Excuse me, sir.
Won't you come in, please?
How are you doing?
How do you do, Mr. President?
Mr. President, Mr. President, Mr. President, I want to tell you, bring your boy with you.
I want to start with this whole business.
OK.
How would you use that?
I don't think so.
I'm not going to drag this out.
No, nothing.
Stop dragging things around.
Let's just get to business.
It's made it pretty fair to start on that, Mr. President, when you clamped the center
ship on us.
Have any further messages been decoded?
Or aren't we allowed to know?
I'm not sure, Mr. President.
There's no further messages to decode.
You must shut down your advancement.
Hey, now, shut it down.
Everyone, I'm steering.
I've got to clamp the lid on this business.
Stop these communications.
Oh, damn.
How can you ever stop them?
They come from so far away that they can't be stopped.
Nobody can reach them.
They can't, you know, they can't.
How are you going to stop them?
They never, never reach them.
No.
Once they begin pounding into your brain, you know, the first thing, the prefrontal lobe
starts to flatten.
And once you get into this syndrome where the prefrontal lobe starts to flatten, then
the next thing you know, somebody is spitting on you at the bar, you know, and they go like,
and then they can't express themselves, you know.
Next thing you know, they are defiled.
These are the kind of people they're looking for in the church house, I told you, you know.
These kind of idiots, they can go to a bar and they start, you know, talk to somebody,
they spit on them all over the place.
We're looking for people who like to draw.
There's a lot of art critics out there.
People want to be art critics.
Oh, yeah.
We need critics.
But we're not art critics.
We're looking for people who like to draw.
Drawing on a pipe.
Drawing on a pipe, Daddy.
Yep.
Drawing on a pipe above.
Yep, we like to sit back and hop setty, if you know what I'm saying.
Like, take the whole idea until the brain starts to melt and come out the ear canal.
Now, don't stick those tubes too high up in the ear canal and you can cause some pretty
bad things.
Yeah, I'd sniff it, you know what I'm saying?
Yeah, ah, makes your sinuses go.
Back your eyes, right there.
Crote, I guess the word, best word for it, crote.
Eyes are croting.
Grote in the scrote.
Friends, yes, we grow some great concepts deep down in the scrotes of our bodies where
we store our real soul.
You know, did you know that the soul is stored in a hairy sack?
Yes, it is.
Between the thighs.
Of a...
That is so not true.
Your pet.
Your pet, depending on what kind of virtues it may have.
If you don't have a pet, you ain't got a soul or a good receptacle for it.
It may have to just hover around you.
You could find yourself a rabbit or a beetnik.
They like dogs or cats best.
Tomatoes is good if you...
But, you know, they'll go bad on you and they don't talk none.
Oh, wait, here they are, they're talking though.
Oh yes, oh yeah, right.
Oh look, they're going out to sea.
They're in the little boat now.
How long we been out here, man?
I don't know, man. I'm rooting for him.
I can't remember anything.
It seems like we've been out on this boat forever.
I can't take any more seawater.
I'm this old, parched, and hydrated.
I keep drinking.
You'll be all right.
It looks like an island in the distance.
Here, just blot your brow.
A little bit.
It's a mermaid.
Hey, this is not an island.
That's a mermaid's titty.
What is this titty in the brow?
She's beautiful.
She's so lovely.
I must get to the mermaid.
I want to see her.
No, me first.
She's so beautiful.
She smells.
That fishy smell.
Wait, what's happening?
She's changing.
She's too late.
My god, man.
There's no mermaid.
This is a creature that should have died 10,000 billion years ago.
I can't believe the smell of her.
I think she's dead.
My god, by all rights of man.
Oh, my god.
I'm out of your peace.
This foul thing should not exist.
Oh, my god.
What have we done?
Look, it's getting up.
It will not die.
It refuses to die.
We must kill this thing.
We've got to get out of here.
You mean?
This religion we've created.
It is turning against us.
That's what it is, man.
Stitched together as it was.
It's the monster of the air.
It's your own religion, you fool.
Look into the mirror.
No.
No, I refuse to admit it.
Yes, I admit we stole from dead religions.
Yes, I admit we dug up the corpse of Buddha, Jesus, and every other great teacher.
Yes, we did it.
And abused them.
Yes.
Threw them over our dashboards and had at them.
We buggered these other cults.
I don't think it would be.
We had the Lord and me.
We took the best from them.
And we sutured it together into this great thing.
The great thing.
The church of the subgenius.
Yes.
For we shall overcome the fools and the pig boys and the little pig men and the big pig men.
We will.
This is our Messiah, Frankenstein.
Oh, sorry.
Where are you?
My medicines.
I need more of the drugs.
The drugs, you see.
The drugs seem to light up my brain.
I saw in an instant the power.
The power I had.
The power of slack.
The slack in my little finger had more power than the president, than the premier.
Even perhaps, yes, even more power than Bob.
Bob!
Could it be?
Could I be the chosen one?
He was the nexus of the universe in his mind.
Yes.
And so I trudged on into the night.
Sandals flipping in the wind.
Away from the ground.
With his robe glowing.
Away.
He sauntered on.
Worse and worse.
Thinking that he had become the one.
I am that one central focal point of all universal forces.
Yes, I.
Reverend Ivan.
I was the great genius.
The brilliant writer.
Who etched his flammable words onto the very skin brain of the followers.
And yet.
The great swollen sack confused, man.
What?
The drifting angel of infantilism.
What is that silly voice?
Oh, that's my conscience.
That's disgusting.
I can ignore that easily enough.
I did idea.
But I need to feed.
A brain such as mine must have more power.
It must have nutrients.
Yes.
The souls of others would be good.
The brain stems.
The medulla.
Can I help you, sir?
You've been staring at the freezer case for a long time.
No, actually.
Why don't you?
The manager asked me to see if I could help you.
Yes, you could help me.
You could help me, sir.
Please come back here into this dark alley.
Further back here into this dark alley.
And this little closet.
Here, into this broom cellar.
All right, now!
Now, take this.
No, take this!
I didn't know this!
You're moving me along in this story much too fast.
Oh, look.
A little girl has come in.
I'm now some kind of soap.
The makers of new ideas for an old, tired mankind bring you Hitler's hand soap made
from real hands and by Tokyo Rojo, the amazing new hair cream that makes you shine like FDR.
Oh, my goodness.
scars.
How come that man is wearing that from the hat?
What happened?
How come he's wearing all that goofy clothes and shoes?
Look, he's got white and brown shoes.
What's wrong with him?
His shoes got like brown in front and white around his sides.
...to try to convince the Taliban to hand over Osama bin Laden.
Even professionals can't give you the fast, easy, affordable clean of the compact Z-Wizards.
This is Angry Bob, the man with the industrial dick, coming at you loud and clear on WAR Radio.
Rise and shine, folks.
It's a beautiful day.
Just look at that sky.
It's a work of art.
Ha!
Nature never knew colors like that.
And a friendly reminder, when you look at it, be sure to wear your shades.
The radiation counts way up and the heat wave ain't expected to let up either.
Weather control tell us it'll probably hit 100 and...
...10 downtown before nightfall.
As for the good news, there is no good news.
So let's rock with one of our golden oldies.
Ladies and gentlemen, our mayor has asked that we all remain calm in this emergency.
Everything possible will be done to protect you.
On orders from Washington, the commander of strategic defense has alerted all branches of the service.
This is not the usual flying saucer scare.
This unidentified aircraft...
...was seen by thousands as it flew through the Lincoln Tunnel.
Hey, if they're not careful, they're gonna have accident.
Anyone sighting a strange aircraft, phone your nearest branch of civilian air defense.
What are we gonna do now?
We either go to Mars or get shot down.
So we'll go to Mars.
We'll go to Mars.
Sent Tuesday, September 11th at 4.53 PM.
Hey, what happened, man? What happened?
I got this, too.
Two flags that I can see from my window here are both a half-mast, man.
Who died?
I'm kinda concerned.
I hope another president didn't get assassinated and then, you know, another assassin get assassinated by the assassin's assassin.
Because, you know, I'm sick of that.
Um...
Well, yeah, what happened?
Well, anyway, by the way, you know what?
Did you ever, you know...
Did you ever notice that...
When you pick the skin off your feet, even though, you know, I took a shower last night.
But just, you know, just having my...
Having worn the socks that I wore at Burning Man, like, 20 hours ago, you know, and my feet were clean when I put them in,
makes the skin that I peel off my feet and eat taste like...
Like, playa dust.
Uh, which is very sweet, if you notice.
It's really...
It's very sweet.
Did you ever notice that?
Do that.
You know, put on the socks that you wore at Burning Man, even just for a few minutes,
and then peel the, um, the skin off your feet and eat it.
And, uh...
Peel the skin off your feet and eat it, says Michael Pepe.
Well, somehow, the theme of socks and feet...
Has overcome and come all over the...
We... This was such a nice studio before, and now look at it.
Yeah, it's covered with feet, man.
It was all...
It's full of socks.
It was all renovated and...
And...
And good, and...
We left it, yeah.
And now all this, like, foot detritus...
You know, like, the skin, the prenasal skin, what do they call that?
The sound effects are all over the floor.
And the metacarpal arch is dangling right underneath the head box.
There you've got, like, five consoles.
And not one of them...
And not one of them has the right brain case.
The music is broken.
It's bright, but it's still broken.
The song that refused to die...
Refused to die.
And it's...
You know...
God.
And then more sandwiches here we can't eat.
I noticed the last people in here left ten turkey and dressing sandwiches...
Waste.
What a waste.
...and just take one bite and throw it on the floor.
Nobody cares.
It's like life these days.
You use the clerks in the stores.
People don't...
They don't want to do their job.
We are the...
No, we are the...
Nobody wants to do their job.
Nobody wants to do anything.
They just want to sit and mope.
Complain.
Yeah, like...
That's all anybody ever does is complain.
I'm so sick and tired of it.
They cry about how sick and tired...
Impotent.
Improving.
...and how stupid everybody else is.
And they are.
They're all so stupid.
Impulsive.
Every one of them.
T.S.
Elliott was right.
We are the hollow men full of, I guess, nothing really for that hollow.
But we can charge you extra if you want to take that out of the store.
If you want to leave it in the store, you can.
If you want to leave it in the store, we'll still charge you extra.
You know, it's...
You come and you go and you...
It's like a revolving door.
It's...
Remember the old revolving doors that used to...
That's evolution, man.
It's harsh.
Now you have doors that you walk in front of and they spring outward at you and knock
you down before you can get back up and then climb back into the room.
You know, I wanted help but not this much help.
I can still walk on these two smelly old rutabagas feet I'm carrying around.
I can still lift the load if it needs to be lifted.
I just wanted socks that match.
Me too.
I just wanted...
I just wanted to find my socks.
One for each foot.
That's all I asked.
A pair.
Is that too much to ask?
Not...
No.
How do you get socks over rutabagas feet?
I don't understand.
Well, it's like using a turnip to get off or it's like using a turnip to make the new
sandal fit better.
It's the same procreative process, only it's kind of urgent when it's done that way.
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
Some of the kids that have been doing it lately have had severe lesions around their neck
muscles.
Their eyes are actually popping out of their heads like they have a thyroid problem or
something.
It's really disgusting.
Well, it's not that disgusting.
It's just an urgent medical health matter that has to be addressed, stamped, mailed
and sent right away.
So if you want to send anything to the church or the subgenius...
Do you have to like send a self-addressed stamped envelope inside of it or...
Well, you could send your socks.
That's the first thing you could do.
Some clean socks.
If anybody out there in the land of...
I wonder has a freaking...
What?
How many do you need, Stang?
It is distasteful for the scientific mind to indulge in raw speculation.
It has long been thought that life must exist on other planets.
These life forms most likely have appendages for the purpose of locomotion.
It follows then that such beings have a practical need to keep these appendages warm, hence
alien footwear.
There you go.
Alien footwear.
I'm going to go get some of that.
That's right, friends.
Somewhere, friends, there's a planet.
There's a planet where your socks go and the socks of other creatures, other thinking beings.
They may have more feet.
They may have morphed feet.
They may have hooves, but they have socks, one and all.
And where do those socks...
They all must end up somewhere, friends.
That's a mystery.
I have none.
It's a mystery.
Somehow morbid things.
I'm reminded of the story of Lennon's overcoat.
You know, he didn't have one because nobody else did.
What about socks?
Could you please...
We need them real badly.
Right here at...
What's the address?
The object of the firing of the space gun.
They incite an unruly mob to come forward and smash the space gun.
But it fires anyway, shooting a young, comely pair of youths into space, male and female,
seeding the cosmos.
Things to come.
They seeded Earth.
The seed of things.
To the Indians for $24.
To come.
It was a mystery.
Raymond Massey and Hal Robbins.
A mystery wrapped in an enigma.
A flying, rounded, and streaming milk chocolate.
You know, I remember when Hal Robbins and, uh, what was the guy that did Perry Mason,
the big fat guy, what was his name?
He rode around in a wheelchair with little wings on him.
Raymond Burr.
Raymond Burr, I remember, used to hang around the YMCA at the, uh, I think it was the Port
of New York.
Yeah.
He was the first YMCA in San Francisco there.
He used to teach, uh, the younger men, uh, some very, very strange physical movements,
which he called yoga.
And he used to also, uh, propel that, uh, chair around, uh, with, uh, some of their
hair follicles and, and the pieces of, uh, skin that they'd used.
Uh, I think...
Sorry, in plastic.
Oh, no, no, no.
It's, it's, it's not the kind of story you want to tell your dad, see?
Look over there, over there.
Yeah, in the pasture there.
See that cow?
Yeah, that cow's got nothing to do but eat lots of milk all day.
Yeah.
Oh, that's sluggy.
And chew on its own fud.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, he don't worry about no war, no Hitler, no Taojaus.
No, he's, he's content to eat that meadow grass and dream on.
And someday, somebody's gonna come up and clip it on those breasts and...
Slug.
Just, just take all the milk out of him.
Yeah, and he's, he's gonna cry.
Slug.
He's gonna cry, see, like a little baby.
But I won't care because I'll be in the U.S. Army doing the depot work.
I'll be standing up and, and passing out sandwiches, see, for all the other kids in the U.S.O.
Standing up, passing out.
Yeah.
He's, he's passing out, right?
He's passing out.
J.R.
Bob Dobbs.
Bob Dobbs was on the number one list of frauds and phonies for Time Magazine.
Exactly.
And I didn't know who he was.
And J.R.
Bob Dobbs is the creator of the Church of the Subgenius.
This guy, the Reverend Ivan Stang, is, is one of their...
Disciples.
Disclipples.
Yeah.
All right.
You know, it's funny.
I don't think Jesus had a, a disciple named Dopey.
Oh, but you are so wrong, Pinkboy.
Pinkboy.
Jesus did in fact have three disciples named Dopey.
And one named Grumpy.
And one named Sneezy.
Yes, and here comes Grumpy.
And he's well named, too.
And better watch out for Sneezy or everything you know will be blown away.
Shallow Pinkboy.
Uh-oh.
The most frozen and fearful of all the little dwarves, Shallow.
Shallow can hardly get up.
I'm going to keep her together to do his whatever it is he, she, it is doing.
It's...
What, what is it doing?
It's, it's making a chain of flowers.
No, it's meditating.
A way, a flower.
Look, it's, no, it's not making, it's, it's making the flowers, but it's meditating on
higher purple.
The, the elastic thing I'm, what is that?
It's thinking of new ways to kill.
It's a art of clothing.
Ah.
It's, it's one of the spandex t-t-t-t-t-t used to kill its victims.
Slack takes many forms.
My friend, killing is one, dying is yet another for some who pray to die.
Others pray to kill.
Which are you, my friend?
Why don't you come into the bosom of Bab and, or Connie, who has actually a better bosom.
Yes, a triple E bosom.
And learn all that you can know about the forbidden sciences and about occult incantations.
That can lead you to mastery and power over your own wallet and your own personal guardian
demon.
I wind the wand or the signet three times.
Take the alabaster pepperoni and put it near your nostrils.
The third nostril will expand and the magic door is not so magic anymore.
Power and slack, I tell you.
Beyond your wildest imaginings.
Yeah.
It is straight up power.
Slack, it is called by way of power.
I have heard of people.
We have yearned for slack for so many years.
The name we use is slug.
That sounds crude and simple to your people, I am sure.
But one of these days we will master slug and climb from the slimy pits near the river
where we have been banged.
And we shall...
What are we going to do?
Look, there is the slack.
Now climbing up the banks of the slimy river.
I see it.
Yes, it's...
It's slipping down on the body.
Harking and...
It's slidding down on the body.
That's the slack.
How is this slack?
It is frat.
You are asking me for slack.
Look at that slack.
Look at that slack hulking.
That is majesticly looming.
It is the grandest and greatest.
No.
Stay back.
Ahhhh!!!
Friends, you have been listening to the Subgenius
radio ministry hour of Slack.
If you want more information about the Church of the Slug, see the link below.
Subgenius, check our website, www.subgenius.com.
By the way, Subgenius does not have an O in it.
Although if you use one, you'll still get there.
By magic.
Yes, magic.
I didn't want that.
I didn't want an evil book.
I don't want to.
Even a man who is pure at heart
and thinks he has his slack.
Yet if he eats those pickles too soon,
we'll have pimples on his back.
They're pimples on their brains, aren't they?
Pimples and milk.
Good old pimples and milk.
And pimples.
Mmm.
If you don't eat,
your meat,
you can't have any pudding.
How can you have pudding
if you don't eat your meat?
There is so much to see
and though there is so far for men to go,
it's good to travel wide
and then it's good to come back home again.
MMm.
Little toy.
Oh, it's just an outstanding Zhi Jun Yang
and a little coda!
The moon.
Bjudji.
This path is like the
Secretary of Health's gonna kill me!
I'll bless you, my friend.
But he will talk again, he'll...
You cursed rat!
Look what you've done!
I'm melting!
Melting!
Oh, my world, my world!
Who would have thought I could love her like you
for destroying my beautiful wickedness?
Ah! The boat!
The boat!
I'm going home!
Home!
GIFT
Destroy
Long call, babe. Don't you know what they're doing to yourself?
PHONE RINGS
Are you a voyeur? Do you like to watch?
Uh-huh.
What's your name?
Bob.
Hi, Bob.
How's it going?
What can I do with it, Bob?
Tell me. Tell me how you are.
If I came in your room right now, what would you do?
I don't know.
Friends, I should mention once again, the music, well, a lot of the stuff in the background were collages by Fernanda Nde-Limer, Artemio Salina, I don't know, New Monet, the whole gang of idiots there in alt-binary slack.
But this chopped-up music, the broken music in the background is once again from a band or something called People Like Us.
Actually, Vicki Bennett in England.
And you can download the whole album from www.vicki.bennett.com.
www.ubu.com.
That's www.ubu.com.
And her previous albums are on her main website, www.peopellikeus.org.
Like the subgeniuses, she apparently has found commercial, dealing with record companies to be too much trouble for the money.
And I guess is sort of self-distributing her material.
If you can get by cheap, you actually make more giving your stuff away in some cases than you do working with the conspiracy.
Believe it or not.
That's the way it's worked for me so far, my friends.
Over there at www.subgenius.com.
Thank you for listening.
Stay tuned for the upcoming.
Oh.
Oh Oh.
.
Oh my.
Thats what I want.
But the other big carnivores are gone.
That's exactly why I've decided to set the trap myself.
Captain, look!
Bye-bye, Fernanda Nende.
Leemore.
When you leave this room, the effect will continue.
Inside of your own mind.
Inside of your own skull.
This concludes operations under the emergency hour of slack system.
All broadcast stations may resume normal operations.
Do you understand now?
It was only a joke.
Now I know how funny it is.