If you have a medical condition that causes bleeding, you should use Gordon's Delicious Bite-Sized Corn Kids.
Bite-sized pieces of kids. Resistible. Whether they're your kids or not.
Additional rare but serious side effects could occur.
From PR News in Washington, I'm sobbing and pleading for help.
Thousands of Californians are being warned that Bob's may have stolen their bus service.
The state has a law to warn them when Bob's in Modesto.
Bob's bus service took effect today in Suburban.
The governor has declared a state of emergency.
The Senate is expected to vote today to raise the fines for allowing PR News in Washington.
We have enough trouble with the younger generation today without having it encouraged by
The Subgenius Power of Swag.
There is nothing the matter with
The Subgenius Power of Swag
that I can see.
Then perhaps you're Bob.
Now wait a minute.
If that's the kind of entertainment you're planning to present, there will be no
Subgenius.
Power of Swag.
Hey, let's stop at this ranch here.
Looks like a pleasant place.
Maybe we can...
Just get out of here.
I'm gonna piss.
Ah.
Look at this.
Look at the...
There's some people riding out.
A guy in his kid walking down the street here.
They're on horses.
I think it is the nearest sheriff.
Uh-oh.
I don't like the way he's slapping that big club into the palm of his hand.
There's some fish in there all.
I don't like that skinny little redneck that's got the giant gun.
I'm next to him.
And the cattle prod in his other hand.
And that little boy wearing a clan button.
That guy's half fish.
He's got a noose with 13 knots in it.
I don't think us northern liberals should have come down to this little southern town, guys.
And pee here.
It's too late now.
Show him no fear.
Well, I guess we're just gonna march right into that Mayberry lunch counter then, huh?
That's right.
Have some lube outside.
Just sit down and ask the beast.
Serve Lloyd.
Just like him, all the humans.
Now, men.
The first rule is...
Obey the subgenius power of the sun.
Secondly, if you're wise, you'll begin rehabilitation.
Prohibition, yes or no, gid tenors, skillet lickers, 1930.
Say, fellas, see that fella coming down the road with that black coat on?
His name is Mr. Stadenko.
And Mr. Stadenko is a narcotics officer.
Well, he's the fella that made a speech last night at Hogwall on Prohibition.
Yeah, I guess he's coming over here to talk to us about all that...
Green, uh, leafy substance.
Let Mac talk to him.
He'll get him told.
How do you do, gentlemen?
How do you do, sir?
I heard your music and thought I'd come over and talk to you a while and possibly hear
some more music later on.
All right, one, two, three, four, hit it.
It's my intention to make a talk on Prohibition and the evils of...
Marijuana.
...at the town hall tonight.
Well, when we first see you coming up the road up the aisle, why, we had you figured
out to be a...
Narcotics officer.
...from your looks.
I guess you've noticed in the papers that the wet party is trying to bring back...
Pot, that's right.
...joint.
Uh, joint.
Reefer, man.
Uh, uh, yes, reefer.
Well, if it's ever been gone anywhere, I'd love to know where it's been.
Oh, my God.
My God.
Why, we've had Prohibition for the last 50 years.
Well, we ain't never heard nothing about it up here on this mountain.
We've been making and selling...
Lebanese blonde hash.
...for the last 60 years.
I can tell right now that you're not a Prohibitionist.
A what?
A Prohibitionist.
Are there any Prohibitionists in this part of the country?
Dave's not here.
I see you don't know what Prohibition means.
No, never heard tell of it.
Prohibition was a law that was passed for the good of mankind, restricting the making
or selling of...
...of any kind of...
Talk about gold.
No, it's Michoacan, man.
Michoacan.
Homegrown.
Yes, you slick British politicians is always getting up some kind of new fangle to make
life more miserable than what it is.
Oh, man.
And you call that Prohibition law a thing for the good of mankind, just taking all
his privileges away.
I don't call that very good.
Well, I don't know about that.
Well, I know one thing.
It's you're talking too much anyhow, and you ain't been invited.
Well, I don't know about that.
I know you're talking too much anyhow, and you ain't been invited.
Well, I know you're talking too much anyhow, and you ain't been invited up here, and furthermore
you're butting into the music, so boys, come on and play us another little tune now.
Don't bogart that joint.
Hi, brother.
You know the name of that star tune the boys is a-fiddlin'?
I don't believe I do.
Oh, that's the new National Anthem.
That's the new National Anthem.
Hey, this is great, man.
Well, gentlemen, the amendment says that anyone that violates this law is a criminal and subject
to punishment and imprisonment.
Officer O'Malley, the FBI, you're busted.
Well, what's the biggest jail in the United States?
Sing Sing prison.
Well, is it big enough to hold everybody in the United States?
Why, certainly not.
Well, they better start billing them one that will if they expect to enforce that law.
Oh, I don't think everyone violates the prohibition law.
Maybe not, but everyone on this mountain has for the last 60 years.
Hey, well, let's get stoned, huh?
Here we go.
There's no use talking, brother.
You can't prohibit nothing.
I'll have to bid you gentlemen goodbye.
I hardly think it would be worthwhile to make a talk on temperance in this neighborhood.
Hey, man, I gotta hang up.
There's someone pounding at the door.
Oh, there's a boy in a split-two, man.
Hey, hey, hey.
Well, I guess we read him a page out of the right book that time, boys.
And our first contestant today on Let's Make a Dope Deal is former head of the philosophy
department at Harvard University.
He is the holder of a Ph.D., an M.A., a B.A., and is a BMF besides.
Would you please give a big warm welcome for Bob.
Bob.
What a happy sound.
It's the happiest sound I've found.
You may clap, rap, clap, slap, but Bob makes the world go round.
I'm bringing you a shoe rack.
Yes, dear friends, that was Reverend Shane Smirker did that very last little bit.
But before that, the Cheech and Chong prohibition business was by a new contributor,
Reverend Sud Sana of the Chinese Liberation Clanch, something like that.
I can barely remember anything, friends.
And yet it's the amino acids in the background right now.
And now we're going to go back in time to a little bit of DeVival and Winterstar of 2003,
where we were talking about the subject of tonight's show.
And after that, we'll go back even further in time to Media Barrage number three,
the classic subgenius album on the subject of sex, sickness, and slack.
See, this was all a very sudden thing.
This LSD.
Every history guy was going to be here.
But believe it or not, somebody who writes books about LSD flaked out.
Didn't make it.
I could tell you all kinds of history of LSD,
except that I can't remember any of my personal history of LSD,
except in the most theoretical way.
Yeah, I remember I was with these guys and we did that and we went to a concert,
but that's not anything that I remember.
I remember all these other things that you can't even say.
Ex-Child Star Sally LeRoy, 24, vegetarian, mystic, acid head.
Mystic kid's head while he vomits and wretches sitting on a curbstone at 4 o'clock in the morning.
And when his knees get enough starch back in him so he can stand up and empty his pockets,
you can bet he'll turn out a stick or two of marijuana.
And you can double your stash.
And with all your money, he'll be holding a sugar cube or a cap or two.
So don't you con me with your mind expansion, slop.
I deal with kids every day.
I try to clean up the mess that people like you make out of them.
I'm the expert here. You're not.
Really?
When's the last time you were asked to appear on television?
I am the new way to go, the way of the future.
I can't begin to fill all my personal appearance requests.
I'm not just news, my friend. I make news. Big news.
So did Judas.
The way of the future.
You know what God says the end result of vile affections is?
He says you're going to become so perverted in your lifestyle, hear me.
You're not simply going to smoke cigarettes and inject needles into your collapsing veins.
You're not simply going to guzzle down alcohol.
But you're going to be so depraved that your women are going to begin to make wimps.
And your men are going to begin to make love to men.
I'm just not a coffee lover.
I think what makes folk get needy and need to be taught about coffee is because some people drink it religiously.
They have to have it.
They can't make it without it.
They build their life around coffee.
Like a drug addict does.
And some folk build their life around RC.
I said get on with the floor, get on with the floor, boy.
People are going to think, yes they're going to think.
People are going to, people are going to think you're spas.
I remember the first spike that I sank in my vein.
The warmth my body felt.
The peace in my brain.
But then it took two dollars a day to get me high.
But my habit increased.
So sick I could cry.
Nights I prowled the streets with one thought in my head.
Just to get money for my fix.
And then return to bed.
It started me on my road to crime.
Caused my loved one sorrow.
He's so great, let him prove it.
You know, it was...
If you hold your next question just a moment.
We'll come right back, ladies and gentlemen, to Mr. Lynch and Mr. Greenwood.
After these words from our sponsor.
I don't mean to interrupt.
I mean, I...
I'd like to mention that some of you young people might be especially interested in our novel and quaint gourmet's drug culture here in the future.
First off, you can try our atomic dirt.
It's very organic.
Some of our more rowdy and dissatisfied teens will inject only once, of course, pure cancer for that indescribable three-week death rush.
We have a disease called communicable stupor, or the drug bug.
A contagious hallucinogenic state which passes swiftly from one person to another and makes them happy.
Whether they want to be or not.
Always a thriller when unexpected.
Wow, wow, wow.
Now, brains, come and have a cup of coffee.
Damn good coffee.
And hot.
Mixed with alcohol, it merely deadens certain nerve inputs to the brain.
Oh, well, any decent blend of scotch will do that.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Yes. Yes.
Ah, yes, his head's been ripped off.
I'll get you another.
Looks like I picked the wrong week to quit amphetamines.
By Sco Auslander.
From PR News in Washington, I'm criticized for criminal activity carried out by PR News in Indian-administered Kashmir.
For PR News, I'm flattened by helicopters and planes
because several hills still had heavy freezing Sreenagar in New Delhi.
Simply dicks on the table.
Bob now has the right to remove a feeding tube from brain-damaged PR News in Washington.
Drugs don't blow minds.
People blow minds.
Drugs don't even have minds.
They don't have nervous systems.
They don't have lungs and hearts that'll stop from doing too much central nervous system depressants.
They're like guns.
They're just inert, cool things.
And how you use them is up to you.
Unfortunately, it's also up to the cops.
That's a little rough.
And that doesn't sound too good to the polished ears of the liberals and the modernists.
So they soften it down, you see.
And of course, they would read that verse,
Let God be true in every man.
Be an untruth in a measure to a degree by chance in my opinion, they'd say.
Ha, ha, ha.
Yeah, let's soften that because somebody might get offended.
Yeah.
But the Bible says,
Let God be true and let every man be a liar.
Oh, let Bob be true and every man be pea-shy, friends.
There's some Media Barrage number three there, our new old subgenius album.
But now, friends, I'm going to play some more Tom and Joe.
This particular song by Tom and Joe, which is coming up,
is about...
Lettuce Opium.
That standby of head shops in the 70s.
They actually used to sell something called lettuce opium
that was supposed to get you high.
It was supposedly made from lettuce and it was this black tarry stuff.
And if you smoked enough of it...
Well, anyway, this song is truly pure, my friends.
Pure 1967 yellow barrel sunshine.
And it's a smart oneself,
Jeremy B.
and he knows all sorts of literature.
The ine uniquipe number...
What is over here?
R license of the library's...
It comes from a plant
Normally thought of as friendly
But it's not friendly
And that's no lie
Those nasty fixings
Solid fixings bring you down
Spin you around
And make you hide
Walking in the light
Stepping on a ride
And I'm in
And now let us say
Let us pray
For our souls
Beyond Scott Me
Out of control
I am vegetable guy
I'm not a plant
It comes from a plant
Normally thought of as friendly
But it's not friendly
And that's not mine
Those nasty fixings
Saddy fixings
Bring you down
Spill you around
And make you high
Ask the railroad man
They'll toss up your brain
But stay in the light
They'll eat your mind alive
And now let us say
Let us say
Let us pray
For our souls
Let us hope
We've got me
Out of control
Why did the music just stop?
I mean it just completely quit.
And that was Tom and Joe.
The amazing Tom and Joe
with their song Lettuce Opium.
You can get more information about Tom and Joe
only by emailing Tom or Joe
at this email address.
Bdeberculo
That's B-D-E-B-O-R-C-U-L-O
Bdeberculo at Yahoo.com
And now friends back to
the old subgenius truth
in the album Media Barrage
number three
Sex, Sickness and Slap.
People have took uppers and downers
and rollers and
and every kind of a pill
and every kind of a drink
and these fellas go out
and turn these bottles up.
You know what?
What they're doing?
They're looking for something
that'll make them have a high feeling.
Oh, I want you to know
you talk about a high feeling.
I've been high on Jesus for 39 years.
Hallelujah.
Glory to God.
And I'm getting higher and higher all the time.
And one thing about this high that I'm got
I hope it don't give me no illusions.
Amen.
The high that I get on is a reality.
Everything that I see is real.
That's reading the fly team.
Now you need to make up in your mind.
What are you doing?
What's up?
You're in for a shot.
Yes.
Go to some of the schools here in Irving
and watch the kids take out their little vials of liquor
and put it in their orange juice.
Or go to some of the classrooms that
one young lady told me
that the marijuana that they smoke right in the classroom
is so strong it makes her sick.
What do you think about that, friends?
You want to do something about it?
Someone said to Barry McGuire
that all you Christians,
you're all the same.
You've all been brainwashed.
And Barry thought for a moment.
He said, yes, that's true.
But you sinners have been brainwashed also.
The only difference between you sinners
and us Christians is that
us Christians, we have chosen
to wash our brains.
The current Love Burger situation
is getting out of hand.
Praise God.
Yeah.
And that's a cat it is my the cat.
You're in the disproportionately
vulnerable body because the vegetables
Are you, are you?
Am I her?
No, I am not her?
Oh, a cold.
I like Captain Drummond.
Bob, give me more pills, Bob.
Bob, give me more pills, please.
If you could just send three more of those pills, I'd feel a whole lot better.
I just took the last one, Bob.
The last pill.
I'll need some more for the next year.
Drink, Bob.
Dr. Bob.
Doctors for Bob!
Doctors! Doctors for Bob!
Bob! Bob!
Alright, listen.
All that
Moriah jump in the fire
Fire too hot, jump in the pot
Pot too black, jump in the crack
Crack too high, jump in the sky
Sky too blue, jump in canoe
Canoe too shallow, jump in the tallow
Tallow too soft, jump in the loft
Loft too rotten, jump in the cotton
Cotton so white she stay there all night
And you ain't heard the last
Ernest Teeter.
Y'all need to send us some drugs real fast.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, now let's talk to him.
Come on, Bob!
Send drugs.
Bob, we're trying to teach you.
If you're for real, show us some stuff.
Show us amphetamines.
Send 3-7-14
Cut us some amphetamine slack, man.
We need to get out of here.
I want some nice turkey crack.
Really? Okay.
Hash, opium, amphetamines.
Whoa, Bob, why don't you come through for us?
Heroin, heroin, heroin.
If you listen, Bob, now's your chance.
Send us drugs.
We're depending on you.
LSD.
I know the man by Mr. Fletcher
in Dallas, Texas.
And he's a good man,
except that he don't buy me two glasses
of Fletcher's beer.
And I said,
I love you, boy.
And I'm gonna tell you, if I can't whoop him,
I'll go down.
All right, friend!
He's going down!
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Yeah, this is
miracle wisdom coming through from all over.
We want
people to know that the patriotic
subgenius church has no
age barriers and no limits.
We've saved many
friends that were in the bondage of
alcoholism and
drug abuse and homosexuality
and lesbianism. Yes, we've taken them in
and now they're making more money than
ever at it! God will not put
up with it forever. No.
No, he'll do something about it.
And dear child of his, if you're
living in a home where there's
sin, where there's cursing,
where there's swearing, where there's
alcohol, being drunk,
and where there's drunkenness,
where there's all sorts of
wickedness, God
will help you. God
will help you. If
God has to, he'll smite the
cheekbone, he'll break the teeth
of those that are coming against
you. And the ones who
escape from your assembly line, the rare ones,
you call them delinquents,
weirdos, hippies, pill heads, freaks, pot heads.
You tell them they're sick,
they know better.
Behave yourself, cause
the Lord's looking and booking. But
the Holy Ghost is God
authorized detective
agency. The Holy Ghost
is God's high sheriff
that has come to restore
and get back for you,
bring back to you
those things that the devil
has stolen.
Freeze! Alright, hold it right there. You're under
arrest. Okay, spread them. Get your hands up there.
Okay, now you. Uh, yeah, he'll be in town.
He'll be back. You have the right to remain
sound. You have the right to a court-appointed
attorney should the need arise if you find yourself
without counsel. Anything you say may be
held against you and probably will. You have the right
to one telephone call. You have the right
to order a large pepperoni pizza should
the need arise and you find yourself without pepperoni
pizza. You have a right to wear checks with
plaids but only in cases where you are not wearing
stripes. You have a right to borrow money
from a loan shark or concurrent Saturdays or
Tuesdays if bail is not set. If a bond
is posted you may waive this right.
You have a right to wave and whistle at police
women in long skirts and leather hose rather
permitting. You have a right to exercise
periods in prison, a light fruit salad
with safflower oil mayonnaise and a glass
of Perrier water with a twist of lemon peel.
You have a right to play golf with the other
inmates on Saturdays and unlimited sauna privileges.
You have a right to a literary agent
should your prison novel become a merchandisable
bankable property. If you have no
agent, a court-appointed representative will be
provided. You have a right to a selection of
gourmet foods, low calorie, prepared
with great skill by our institutional chefs and
food service personnel. You have a right to a
choice of coffee or an after-dinner liquor.
You have a right to an after-dinner mint. If
you do not get a mint, a court-appointed after-dinner
mint will be provided. You have a right to a
full facial treatment, tanning machine session,
and mayonnaise full body massage. If you desire
a milkshake, a milkshake will be provided by
the court. All right, take him away.
Yeah!
Okay.
And that was Dr. Howell, my friends.
The good Dr. Howell on KPFA with puzzling evidence
in the olden days. And thanks to Phineas Narco
for preserving those particular cuts. And now
back to Media Barrage 3.
I'll never forget when I was young, I was
25 and a male hustler. I remember being beaten
up by this entire fleet of Marines. They just tossed
me like an old volleyball over the net, back and
forth, back and forth. So my body was bleeding,
bleeding, but I had come 87 times in five passes
over the net.
Pretty good indication of all the wonderful
people that are out there. Wow, look at that.
That's amazing. And it's a pleasant ending to
kind of a sad situation. It certainly is.
One of those endings that we look for but so
rarely find in this business. That's right.
And the dance of the
creep's widow.
That was a bitch over in the corner
fucking herself with a cane.
When the bitch started to get the feeling,
down from the ceiling,
fell the hunchback
of Notre Dame.
The father had prayed for every lunch man and woman
bar girl right now.
He looked like a bad hurl.
Oh, yeah.
You luscious monkey woman, you.
Take this banana.
But Dr. Drummond, but Dr. Drummond,
we can't fuck them.
We're reverence. We're ministers.
That's right, sir. The church of the subgenius.
We are holiness. We must abstain.
And you know what they really want?
They want Bob to fuck them.
That's right. But God,
if they only knew. The burning hot
steel tool of
Bob.
What kind of woman could take him?
Well, he's got one in every state.
Where did she live?
He finds them. They must be the...
I mean, they must be mutant women,
you know, to be able to handle them.
They've had transplants.
Over women.
Over womb men.
Steel sleeve put up there.
Dr. Robert Bob.
And I was so excited.
And I was so turned on.
I just wanted to find out where the devil was.
I wanted to go beat him.
Go get him and just beat him up.
I mean, I was just...
Oh, I just wanted to preach so bad.
And I preached all the way home in the car.
And I said, devil, wherever you're at,
you just put my name down.
Because I want to be one of your top candidates.
Because I'm going to do more to hurt you
than you can ever dream of.
And I say I was turned on.
And I went in and I stopped at this grocery store
and I went in there.
And I got my cheese and I got my bologna
and I got my beer bottles and your wine and everything.
And then I looked behind the cash register.
And it was just
row after row after row of filthy magazines.
And something came all over me.
I know what it was. It was the Holy Ghost.
The Holy Ghost came on me when I looked in the magazine.
And I said, Alex, it just makes me sick.
Think evil.
Do evil.
Be evil.
The end of evil will carry you
to the shores of paradise.
That's evil in a lot.
I'm going to be preaching to you preachers.
What do we know about the beyond?
Do we know what's behind the beyond?
The pastor got this Adam
I'm afraid some of us hardly know what's beyond behind me.
Don't you all get mad at me now.
Everybody knows we come here every year
so they put a program on in the church
to tie you up.
Eleven.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Six.
Seven.
Eight.
Nine.
Ten.
Eleven.
Twelve.
Thirteen.
Fifteen.
Twelve.
Rajah.
Nine.
Ten.
Eleven.
Twelve.
Nin.
Twenty.
Thirteen.
Twelve.
Fifteen.
Christ. We're going to see literally millions of Christians. They're going to march through the
streets. We're going to preach on the television, on the radio. We're going to start controlling
society because we're tired of being pushed around. And I'm tired of the devil lying and
stealing and cheating people's lives. And the only truth is our Lord Jesus Christ. And we are not
going to hide. We are not going to be intimidated. We are not going to be pushed around, but we're
going to stand up for righteousness and stand up for godliness. To make these Christians into a
political force. They don't want us involved. Let's tell them we're not listening to them anymore.
We're going to be involved. If you think our solution is political, you too have been deceived.
Don't you commit yourself to some political party or politician. You commit yourself to
the principles of God and demand those parties and politicians align themselves with the eternal
values in this book. And America will be forever the greatest nation on this earth.
It isn't going to take Ronald Reagan three years to learn about the godless aggressive nature of
communism. Over the last two or three decades, the federal government seems to have forgotten
both that old time religion and that
old time religion.
The old time constitution.
I suggest to you, friend, it's time for a change. Will this patriotic Christian zeal carry over into
political action?
Someone to blame us. Someone to follow. Someone to shame us. Someone to follow. Someone to rule us. Someone to not be.
Won't you be brother? Be brother.
Be brother.
Bob says you'd say to know what you're worth.
Really, thank you.
I believe that God can put you in the right place at the right time to hear exactly what you need to hear.
So, if you would, send us your dollar.
Send your money in on the double. Don't worry, it's a doctor.
Well, people, you can get yourself in work and just double. Put your hand, put your hand on the radio.
People today, they have jungle.
Music.
Over the radio, they twist their body like in some kind of sex act.
You say, well, that's plain.
But that's no plain what you see on your television every day.
And that educates the young people.
And they have this jungle, perverse music.
This music that's perverted.
I believe all music should belong to the Lord.
But the music they have on these records that you buy down at the record store,
they're made by devil worshipers.
You can take those records and run them backwards, and you can hear Satan talking on there.
Now, the electric prunes for Fox, bringing you the exciting new sound of the Fox Wawa pedal.
Let the electric prunes demonstrate the difference.
Play it prunes first without the Wawa pedal.
Now, listen to the difference when you push that Fox Wawa pedal down.
You can even make your guitar sound like a centaur.
And it's pretty spectacular stuff that we're putting out here, really.
So, Bob is the one that will give us the inside information that the aliens are coming, be in position to power, and all this.
Bob can...
Can make you survive the coming econocataclysms.
Now, a lot of people do not realize how many people involved in the rock and roll conspiracy are also involved in your church.
And one of them I've heard rumors about was Graham Parker, that he was.
That's right. Graham Parker is real big.
He's been ordering much more literature from England than we've ever gotten a request for before.
And he's been distributing it.
He's one of our biggest...
One of our biggest exponents right now.
Devo, on the other hand, is vehemently anti-subgenius.
Those guys feel that we're moving in on their act.
That's right.
We're stealing their fans because they're just entertainers, whereas what we're doling out is true cosmic wisdom.
They stumbled across some little bit of information, and they haven't proceeded to completely delve into it yet.
But I think that's why they feel an infringement.
It's the now sound. It's what's happening.
That's why.
The Electric Prunes.
Animals.
Hermans.
Paul Revere and the Raiders.
Stones.
The Seeds.
Are all using the Vox Wawa pedal, and it works with any amplifier.
He's a liar.
The demon is a liar.
He would like to confuse us.
I have a feeling that friends, but the rock and roll bands, the young people listen to, we've had testimonial letters from people who were once demon possessed.
The lead singer for Kiss.
Or...
The ACDC band.
Mick Jagger.
That's who he is.
He wrote us, and he said...
He said, what so many say.
So many in prison.
So many lost individuals everywhere.
He said, I was in the power of...
Of what can I call it but them, is the way he put it.
Them.
He didn't care whether it was the green energy demons from the fourth dimension, the UFO people, the men in black, the CIA.
He didn't care who it was.
He had been on the road for 18 years straight.
Around the corner, he started to record.
So they wanted to Millionaires.
He was taking me on.
He had so many
million dollars.
this to him he'd he'd he'd learn about it he'd read about it but it you know it never was it
never was real until they learned what the the power the power that could do for him and he'd
try out all the the drugs and the demonic sex music they'd do and the young tiny girls and
fat boys that they'd find out in the special markets and and the young uh the young people
and and finally he he came to he came to bob and he wrote us and we we have his his amazing
testimonial and friends it ends it says it says uh bob's servant for life for afterlife and for
before life and he said i'm gonna spread my seed it was in the ps he said i'm gonna spread my seed
and huh okay kids and there's for all our little poppy pals who sent in those dope letters
here's a little thing
entitled swinging all the way i dig my parents on paris day we swing all the way here it goes
let's pick up the music crazy do you like it bud yeah man like everybody moves elvis is back
good boy i don't know world war five elvis how you feel jesus i've never felt better
that damn marmot boy like to be just yeah watch we're on the air elvis all right come on
what'd you do over in germany i told them
god i was one of the king rock and rollers and i told my lieutenant and the general and everything
i told them to kiss my elbow well elvis i'm sorry i see your language is still limited
that's right i don't care i got five million dollars
well you'll never record for capital i don't care i got moon killing it
i put silver dollars in the machines in vegas silver dollars don't know roy gene there's my
agent
isn't that it
from pr news in washington i'm investigating drugs from drug companies
in this case to deal popular painkillers the panel voted nearly unanimously that grass is safe to sell
beyond fully functional archbishop leonardo sandri will deliver on the pope's behalf
in a surprise today police in wichita kansas bind torture and kill pr news in washington
uh yes sir all right good move away from the car move away from the car please uh yeah but that uh
please but mr carl miss me
oh okay
uh...
that's uncalled for officer
lightning
uh...
Larry Cooper
days of early man,
primoanthropocus,
that our ancestors
became intelligent from
being such mean badasses
that they cracked open the skulls of their
dumber fellows and ate their brains.
Terence McKenna teaches us,
no, it was the apes that ate the mushrooms
who became more intelligent.
I think it's,
actually, it just makes me hungry for brains
and mushrooms.
But, you know,
now we're stuck with
maybe Alzheimer's is a good
legal high.
My mom is not in bad
spirits. She sees movies
that the rest of us don't get to see.
She tried to convince us
of a movie she'd seen that my
brother had made, and finally my brother had to
go, I didn't make that movie.
It was part of your dream or something.
And she went, her response was,
well, all I can say is
you people are missing a damn
good movie.
The more I thought about it,
well, you know, they say your
reality is what you make
it and so forth, so
maybe it's a good legal high.
Larry compared it
to good Columbia marijuana.
Well, see,
that's what I'm saying. I have practice.
I keep all those notes. I've got tattoos
on my chest.
Read backwards in the mirror, the whole
business.
But, you can get high other ways,
besides eating,
beef, or
waiting until you get old,
or whatever.
Preaching is not a bad way to get high.
Now, I'm not doing it
now because my
doctor told me not to, but
many preachers, you'll notice,
preach with this cadence
and they go, Bob,
it will give you slack, and you
will have so much slack,
you will be like, well,
I don't want to keep going because I'll get too high.
It's the high of
hyperventilation.
And I know from experience
that it really works.
The preacher gets so worked up,
he's breathing like that,
it, you know,
God only knows how many brain cells
are sloughing off to the side
as the oxygen is being deprived.
But, he sees a clearer
and clearer picture of God
and the city of heaven
and Jesus, and next thing
you know, everybody in the audience
is getting with him, and they're
getting high, and they're preaching,
and they're breathing like that, and God
himself walks into the room wearing his
Sunday best, friends, and
that is what religion is all about.
I guess.
It doesn't happen in subgenius
things very much because we don't have much
faith.
I was thinking yesterday about how
if I got cancer, faith healers
wouldn't be able to heal me.
But,
I'm one of those
people that if I was charged,
enough by the hospital,
I might have faith in that.
$50,000 to cure your cancer,
I wouldn't have enough faith.
If I was $100,000 in debt,
I might well be able to beat it.
You know?
Yeah, I have that.
$100,000, they
couldn't be lying about that.
Those are the easiest
lies to believe, I guess,
they say.
I read the angel's stone.
Deep thunder rolled
in my heart.
I tanked my shoes.
Flushing as the fire spoke.
It's not an easy thing to me
to make up your lies.
I'm single.
What can he do for you?
If only you could see what I've seen
with your eyes.
I want more
life.
late,
and
we're
It was
recent that
I talked about
how
the
man that
You are being
has it made you
what I
feel like
we should be
people
Right,
feel remembering
if possible.
together again,
could
do everything
to do,
what I've seen with your eyes.
What seems to be the problem?
Death.
If only you could see
what I've seen with your eyes.
And to make every hand be made.
You were made as well as we could make you,
but not to last.
If only you could see
what I've seen with your eyes.
I've done questionable things
and some extraordinary things
reveled in my time.
If only you could see
what I've seen with your eyes.
And to make every hand be made.
You were made as well as we could make you,
but not to last.
If only you could see
what I've seen with your eyes.
Nothing the god of biomechanics
would let you in heaven.
A light that burns twice as bright
burns half as long.
And you have burned so very, very brightly.
If only you could see
what I've seen with your eyes.
You better get it up!
I'm gonna have to kick it!
Well, you notice Bob's pipe
is not exactly clenched within his teeth,
but actually meets his clenched teeth.
His teeth are all the way together.
You can tell by inspecting the smile.
That goes in the ass's turn!
Well, I...
So he can lick chicken wings!
From PR News in Washington,
unfair to low-income single mothers and others.
Democrats lost their job last night
to be beat up by the Democrats.
The CDC is waiting in line
outside a health clinic
near a crowded market.
A defense attorney is said to be
eating regularly
and sitting in an armchair.
In Washington,
the Senate is orchestrating
the $11 billion accounting fraud
at PR News in Washington.
We have a 10-15 at the 7-11
at 12-34.
It occurred at 12-45.
And we have the store attendant
bending over and grabbing his ankles
and we're photographing the area.
He talked to the TV,
we're talking to the kiddie now.
We're trying to find out
from the kiddie just what happened.
Stand by while I'm done.
I'm done with this.
Stand by, over.
Maybe Cher can explain all this.
I have to explain it to you.
It's been over.
Okay, now put the law number
of the law into the rectum.
Okay, now pull up here.
Oh, no, that's not how it goes.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
That's not show.
Not right.
No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no.
Silas got it.
Bob's in combination with LSD
will make warp noids
out of all the current
Love Burger situation
is getting out of hand.
Praise Bob.
And she came out to me.
She was in the Navy.
You're on drugs.
Do you have drugs?
She goes, I know you are.
She goes, don't.
She goes, I know what
you're going through.
I've taken drugs before.
And then she
splashed her ID in my face.
And like she had
these two guys with her.
She goes, don't worry, Linda.
We're your friends.
Get out, you bum.
We don't want your
kind in here anymore.
Now try to give me a job.
Feeding chickens
and washing down hogs.
But that meant standing up
all the time.
And standing up to me
is just like dying.
I'm so lazy
that I could cry.
But tears
are just too lazy
to fall out my eyes.
Lord, Lord, Lord, Lord,
I'm so
messed up.
This next song
was originally Funk Zookie.
And now it's called Opium.
Prozac, coffee, marijuana.
I don't know what's all out there.
So this song's about opium.
Oh, dancers,
dancers.
She enters the den of opium
She sees a bishop is overdressed
She can't see the cardinal's shoes
I bet they're blue suede too
All the leaders, great and small
Hide behind the wall of the wall
Behind the velvet wall
She is the deepest water
that runs within the den
of opium
Opium
Gold and bronze
Green and grey
And the fairies
of yellow and black
Every blackest bitch
Blows a smoke that's been
known to slay
The mightiest of men
All the leaders, great and small
Hide behind the velvet wall
She is the deepest water
that runs within the den
of opium
metres
I'll be out
Everybody listen up!
She left with her soul intact
She never kissed the fascist lips
She did partake of the poppy wonder
And escaped before the blitz
All the leaders, great and small
Hide behind the wall
The velvet wall
She is the deepest water that runs
Within the depth
Of Ophium
Ophium
A little bit
A little bit of Thelonious Bosch there
Recorded live at Starwood
If you want to know more about that band
Thelonious Bosch
Check out www.omnium.com
O-M-N-I-U-M
Dot com
Ehh
End it now
From PR News in Washington
I'm the mother of a juvenile murderer
A Wichita man warns that most police
Float around in a balloon without stopping
He said Pieg took a refused request
To test for a request refused
PR's unsolved murder case is up 15 at 2067
Interpol officials have created a special task force
To investigate PR News in Washington
Friends, Fernand and Andy Lee Murr did that
And does the PR News
You're listening to Hour of Slack number 986
With the amino acids in the background
Much of the show is from the old subgenius album
Media Barrage 3
And you can learn more about the church of the subgenius
From www.subgenius.com
Also known as
Post Office Box
181-417
Cleveland Heights, Ohio
We're coming up on show number 1000
Friends
And we'd like to get your testimonials
Written, emailed to
Stang at subgenius.com
Or mailed to our P.O. Box
Or recorded and sent as MP3s
Or a CD or tape or anything, whatever
You know, we can handle everything up to HoloCute
But now, friends
That preacher was talking earlier in the show
About how the devil talks backwards
On these rock and roll albums
And, well, he talks backwards
On weird noise mixes, too
In fact, all of the following
Is made from one tiny short little clip
Of yours truly sort of coughing or snorting
And yet, if you listen on FROP
You will hear the devil talking backwards
On this cut
This cut by my band
With Princess Wee
Pooh Water Towel
Station personnel may just want to fade out from this
And in so doing
Save their listeners' very souls
The demon is a liar
He would like to confuse us
Yes, sir
Just off, I just, I'm fissed
I'm into this
I am
Here, c'mon
Straight forward
Cool
Zoe
Tschrooung
So
Did you turn it off?
I now get decided to turn it off
It's because of the sound of hell
I
You can take those records and run them backwards
and you hear Satan talking on there.
And now for the internet listeners only,
the great Bob Richley.
Praise this Bob.
My tongue had been completely, completely scalded
by this hot breath of the St. Bernard that used to come down.
He was the leader. He'd lick me, he'd lick me.
Years later in a gay bar when I was a,
the proprietor of a gay bar and we had shows at night,
the same St. Bernard came in.
He's covered with shit.
He had this terrible accident to his bowel, his lower bowel.
And it exploded.
I forgave him.
I forgave him on the spot.
Gave him.
Big hairy devil.
We went together for about three years at St. Bernard.
He died in my arms.
Just panting and carrying away his huge, huge hair-like penis.
Drooping down.
I have it mounted now, chromed.
It's in a shadow box in my den.
Perhaps you'd like to see it.
We'll play a game on my Brunswick pool table.
And you can stare hard at my St. Bernard penis there at all.
Of course.
Some of the chrome has eaten away and the foul growths that have emanated from that flesh spot
have just come like a staghorn fern just kind of growing out of the shack or shadow box.
It's an interesting display.
Some local medical students come over every three hours and look at it.
They get so turned on, I have to relieve them.
It's a privilege for an 87-year-old queen to just suck them dry.
Of course, I faint by the third cock, but what's the difference?