This is Doug Smith, radio operator.
I'm going to bring you a piece of that green cheese for sure.
I have some nuggets!
No trouble.
Just get set and get going.
Hey, hear me.
Recording.
Everything's going fine.
No trouble.
Where are we, Bob?
The code is broken.
Trouble?
Big.
Security.
I have the lid on tight.
Well, take it off for me.
The message is, Mars needs women.
Mars needs...
It's a gag.
It's a prank.
It's a fake.
I don't think so, sir.
Bob?
The message is now part of and registered in your subconscious mind.
It will trigger the entire message without your being aware of it.
Welcome to the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
Sponsored by the Church of the Subgenius.
This is Reverend Ivan Stang,
sacred scribe of the First Orthodox Megafist Temple Lodge of the Church of the Subgenius,
with Pastor Buck Naked of the First Naked Church of the Subgenius,
the opinions expressed are not necessarily those of this radio station.
Before the sermon, a message concerning Bob Dobbs,
living avatar of slack and saint of sales on planet Earth.
Are we controlled by secret forces?
Do you ever get the feeling that free will is a joke?
Do people think you're strange?
to you, then you may be on the right track.
Are you abnormal?
Then you are probably better than most people.
Yes, your time shall triumph.
Yes, fear the stark fist of removal no longer.
Become physically attractive overnight.
Attain status, luck, prosperity by blowing them off.
Bob's promise is to widen the scope and nature of abnormal behavior,
to explore new ways of going over the edge and coming right back.
Plus, to bring back those who couldn't make it on their own.
To help you create the highest possible earnings from the psychodynamics of abnormalities.
To turn conspiracy-implanted personality disorders around.
And channel them into an illusion of creativity that will fool normals and get you sex.
Bob's promise is to make you a better man.
Ah, yes, dear friends, this is Reverend Ivan Stang.
This is the subgenius radio ministry hour of slack.
But, friends, I still haven't mounted.
I'm late to the radio station.
I still haven't made it to the station.
I'm broadcasting from this little remote mic.
And I'm trying to get everything packed up together.
Here at my house.
This is the, uh, Bulldada time-controlled laboratory.
This little security system.
Shut down that little security system.
Turn off the fake revolving hand.
Oh, wait, I turned it on.
Get these things working right.
Oh, let's...
Well, you can't even see where I am.
These are the...
These are the, uh, kitchens of the Bulldada time-controlled laboratories.
You can see the, uh, little souls on ice over here that haven't yet been, uh, bought out.
Prepared for the vast hole in here.
Um, and, uh...
Oh, over here we've got the, uh, the slackless children who've been cast out of the home for slackless children.
Because of the...
Because you didn't send in your donations to the station, friend.
Look at these poor little children.
What do you have to say to the, to the people, children?
My tooth is loose.
Like my favorite sleeper.
I got an ant bite, too.
Why?
A big old bump.
See, friends, these are truly slackless children.
And these kids, these ant bites and these little bumps.
And bruises.
Now, friend, you're not going to let these poor kids...
These are American kids.
You're not going to sit by and let these kids be in pain and slacklessness, are you?
See, they all call me daddy.
Isn't that sweet?
These are only two of over 5,000 of them.
Because we have this amazing electronic babysitter here.
This, this handsome robot.
You can hear it talking.
I have a tornado.
See, if you turn, if you turn this, this amazing household robot on,
why, it will just sit and entertain the kids.
And they don't have to do anything.
You don't have to do anything.
It's, it's a great time-saving device.
Only available from the hour of slack.
Dear friends, listen to the kids laugh with joy in the background.
It's time to be manipulated.
Brother, I want to tell you something.
The world is tired of dead preaching preachers.
Dead preachers preaching dead sermons to dead congregations.
They're tired of cold services and cold churches.
This world is hungry for reality.
They've had enough of Hollywood.
They've had enough of Nashville.
They've had enough of show business.
How are you dangerous?
You don't, you don't conform.
To proper thought patterns.
You need to be scanned.
Well, neither do you.
And you need to be scanned too.
Oh my goodness.
Well, oh, accident that God has you on at this late hour.
We're decent.
People can't hear you except for those like me that are forced to stay
awake to feed their families.
What am I going to do with this animal?
Oh man, you got it.
You don't want it.
Keep, keep, keep our rulers on.
Control, control.
You must run control.
Never take a minute just to show a real emotion.
Excellent.
I read you loud and clear.
Now then, you are to take this planet in the name of the Earth.
He's going to bump you up.
He's got a gun, you know.
Well, all right.
If you're going to kill me, hurry up.
I have to take my tonic in two.
You're a good boy, Dan.
I'm going to tell you the way it is.
And I'm not going to be kind or easy.
Your whole attitude stinks, I say.
And the life you lead is completely empty.
Oh yes, dear friends.
Made it to the station finally.
I've, uh...
We're off!
word, Buck.
Boy, tell you what, speaking of girls, uh...
You know, Playboy or somebody ought to do a pictorial on the, the women of East Dallas
or the women of Fitzhugh Avenue.
Each time it seems that I head for the station, I run...
No.
Different ones.
Well, maybe not Playboy, maybe Gem or Buff might be more apropos for the gals that roam the streets out here.
Hustler might be more apropos.
In this case, Tech.
You businessmen, subgeniuses from out of town, why, just cruise up and down to fit you and you'll see what we're talking about.
I guess the wisdom of Roberts is that they moved here from Harry Hines when they got cast out.
But anyway, I'm exhausted, so Buck, it's all yours.
Well, tonight, remember that call we had last weekend where that fella, he gets on there and says,
Hey, man, what religion fried your mind?
At least somebody cares.
Yeah, well, we don't mind those hate calls, and we're going to invite a few more tonight.
So we got 823-7490 or 823-8801.
And tonight, our theme is call in, look up, look into your holy books.
Or your Bibles, Tibetan Book of the Dead, Koran, whatever.
Even if you've written a real Bible, not just a fake Bible, but a real Bible, then go ahead and read out of that.
We'd like you to give us two or three sentences, your favorite passage or a passage you'd like to give to Hour of the Slack to maybe convert us or whatever.
So we'll be taking your calls at 823-7490 or 823-8801.
And call Hour of Slack Radio Ministries.
And we got something lighting up here.
Oh, yeah.
Well, why don't we screen that one first, and I'll proceed here.
Friends, help us to help us save us from ourselves.
My busy rock, my busy tree, my busy tree.
My busy football, my busy basketball, my busy rugby ball, my busy golf ball.
Now, I want to be a member of your church.
I want to give all I got.
I want to love Bob.
I was in a room just the other day in Dallas.
Well, I did benefit from it, of course.
But so did a whole bunch of old Dallas boys.
But one thing is for sure.
And if you let Bob do your thinking for you, you won't have to worry about nothing come July 4th, 1998.
Ha, ha, ha.
When Bob comes down in his giant mothership.
Looking kind of like a big pillbox.
Bob will be landing.
And you can climb right in because he's going to know.
He's going to have your name on a computer printout.
Yes, sir, dear friends.
And that CRT tube available right there at his fingertips.
He can call your name up, and he'll know exactly what you've done for him.
He'll know exactly how much donations you've taken in.
He'll know exactly how.
How much money you've given to the church.
And he said, yea, the head of the prophet, Dobbs, shall ne'er bleed.
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
The bleeding hands of our father.
Oh, he's the nicest.
Decapitated injured golfer in the world cup class I know.
Just a bleeding hand of our father.
Well, spooky music will be back in just a minute.
And I want to turn this around and, you know, I don't know.
We'll do it.
I don't know.
Okay, here come the first Texans.
A corpse can't sue you.
And more problems have been caught caused by people shooting.
Attackers when they simply wound them.
So get police training.
Buy your gun.
Shoot to kill.
And see you next time.
This Apollo flight grossed out at 6 million pounds.
To escape Earth's gravity, it had to achieve a velocity of 6 miles per second.
En route time to the moon was 66 hours.
The arrows are poisoned.
It's always ugly.
It's like rotting fruit.
It's like meat that is spoiled.
It's like a roof that leaks.
A foundation that is rotten.
Poisoned.
They are friendly people.
And are by far more advanced spiritually.
And physically than the people of this planet.
At the present time, they are observing us.
Ah, yes, dear friends.
We're going to try to go to the phones here now.
And see if we can get some combat going on the airwaves.
Ah, yes.
I hit number two.
Number two.
Hello, dear friend.
I think I punched him into oblivion.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Dear listener, if you were trying to...
CJ, please call back.
Yeah, it's not our fault.
It's the poltergeist that...
You think we're kidding, too.
Well, wouldn't it just figure that we'd be...
Why don't you go out there and catch a few more of these calls.
Please, dude.
CJ, please call back.
Oh, I think...
Here he comes.
Let's try.
Now, what do I do now?
On.
Correct.
Send a message.
Oh dear, listener.
I don't get it, friends.
Let's try.
That should do it.
Is somebody got a phone up on the other end?
You got a phone up there?
Hang up all the phones.
Let's try to get...
Hello?
On or to...
On.
Hello, dear friend.
Hello?
I give up.
Like, we have a good connection.
We wish to help us to help ourselves to attain a higher understanding of life and its meaning.
What do you think about Bob?
Who's Bob?
All right, well, what do you think about the UFOs which are presently going to,
which are presently in formation to blitz the Earth and put particle beams through the head of everyone that doesn't know Bob?
Hello?
Yes, CJ?
Okay, we're still trying to get you.
You're out of your mind.
A spacecraft entered the moon's gravitational field in the sixth segment of the flight.
The gravity of the moon is one-sixth of that on Earth.
The orbit around the moon was flown 66 miles above the moon's surface at 6,000 miles an hour.
At 10 after 9, the beeping began.
Okay.
Went down to the reserve fence, watched through binoculars, and we did see this thing.
It's about the size of the moon with a small crescent at the bottom that's well lit like starlight.
The top is a dark gray mass.
It came down through the trees, whatever it was.
Have you ever heard of one?
Have you ever been in one?
Have you ever seen one?
Have you but television ever seen one?
No.
If you haven't, it's the greatest sight this side of heaven.
The people from this Earth have already seen some of their spacecraft, which they call flying saucers,
and other flying objects which they cannot describe.
These objects are real and are spacecraft.
The astronauts returned to Earth on the sixth.
The day of the week.
No, wait a minute.
No, you wait a minute.
I love that area, and I...
Hello?
Ed?
Hello, dear friends.
Hello.
Oh, yes.
Hello, I think we got him.
Okay, you're on.
All right.
Okay, CJ, you're on the air, and you're on our Slack radio ministry, and you are ready...
...to give us a quotation.
All right, Buck and Sting.
Now, I was reading here through my Bible late one night, okay?
And I ran across this passage, and I figured that, you know, y'all and all your holiness of Slack
might be able to help me decipher this passage, okay?
Now, this is 2 Samuel 11, chapter 11, okay?
We believe you.
Just read it.
Okay.
One night, he couldn't get to sleep.
He went to a stroll on the roof of the palace, and he looked out over the city, and he noticed
a woman of unusual beauty...
It's an emergency from a girl named Bob.
One of the things...
Can't take that emergency.
Tell her to forget it.
And he noticed a woman of unusual beauty taking her...
It was a woman named Bob.
Did you ever think of that?
...taking her evening bath.
Mm-hmm.
He sent out to find out who she was, and she found out that he was Bathsheba.
Then David sent for her, and he came and...
...and slept with her.
Now, I found this personally to be pretty heavy.
Well, it's pretty heavy, but all it is is just regular old sex hurt, you know?
And that's just...
Sex hurt, it doesn't mean tying them up and whipping them.
It just means doing it till it hurts.
That's easy, I mean, for any Bible scholar.
Thanks a lot for sharing that with us, CJ.
You want to try another one there?
Oh, why not?
Why am I beeping in my head again?
Hit on.
Hello?
Hello.
Give it to us.
Yes, this is, uh...
Okay, this is from the book of the law.
Get it.
Right.
Are you familiar with that?
Yeah.
All two.
Okay, well, let me see.
I got a couple of them here.
What is the law?
Not to spill blood.
That is the law.
What is the law?
Do without will.
Not to make...
Not to endlessly intone the law.
That is the law.
All right, well, let's hear yours.
Okay, well, this isn't mine.
This is from, uh...
Mr., uh...
Anyhow.
Um, it says...
I got a couple of them here.
I'm trying to find the first one.
Oh, come on.
It says that, uh...
Remember...
Remember all ye that existence is pure joy
and that the sorrows are but as shadows.
They pass and are done, but there is that which remains.
And I have...
Sexy.
All right.
I know what that was referring to.
I got one that's very appropriate to the Church of the Subgenius.
Okay.
It says, fail not your vices in virtuous words.
These vices are my service.
Do ye well, and I will reward you.
Read it again slower.
Fail not your vices in virtuous words.
These vices are my service.
Do ye well, and I will reward you here and hereafter.
AII.
Thanks for sharing that with us.
And I have one more?
Nope.
No?
What is that?
It was he who wrote to us pain and misery and terror
and sickness and death and a headache that lasts all year.
That's what any deity means to me.
Bring on the deity's terror.
And the smart bulb.
And the forked tongue bulb.
And the straight deal bomb.
Are all gone.
Fine.
We're doing it still.
We're not seeing the superstitions of Sal, Ben, or Satchel.
We're keeping it.
We're not keeping it.
Expectations.
He's lining up for the park, folks.
I guess.
Yes, the bloody head of Arnold Palmer dictates what the aimless, lifeless body of Arnold Palmer does.
Oh, we should find the devil.
Arnold Palmer is dead.
Ah, yes, dear friends.
We're going to go to that phone line.
Oh, I lost him.
Oh, I guess we're not.
By the way, later on.
the next few calls and Sandy, please call back.
We have a fellow named Sandy
who just called in with something from Revelation,
so we've got to hear this.
We're going to be trying our new
solar collector
that I got from
Dobstown just this past
Tuesday.
I'm holding it right now, and it's a
vase. It's ceramic.
And it's got this
print of the ooze of
Nunu all over it. And then on the
very top, you can see the
swirling mist, which is
the soles that it's already collected. Anyway, this is a much
stronger one.
I want the callers to be aware
that this is a much stronger
soul sucker than the last one we used.
So
it might be a little too heavy.
Anyway, we'll get to that a little later. We'll be asking
you all for a little bit of solar.
This is KNON 90.9
in Dallas, Texas.
This is Doctors for Bob.
You can't hide from God
because he's bigger than you.
Help me, somebody.
You can't hide from God because he's bigger
than the whole planet.
You can't hide
from God.
He's bigger than all
the universe.
You can't hide
from God because he's bigger
than all infinity.
He's bigger than all
reality.
Help me,
somebody.
You can't hide from God.
You can't hide from God
in a reefer.
You can't hide from God in a
glass of alcohol.
You can't hide from God
in a pussy.
Because he's bigger than you.
You can't hide from J.R. Bob Dobbs
because he's stupider
than you are.
You can't hide from J.R. Bob Dobbs
because he's got more black and white
little dots in his face than you do.
You can't hide from J.R. Bob Dobbs
because his face has been mimeographed
and put up in more places
than yours has.
You can't hide from God
You can't hide from J.R. Bob Dobbs
Because more people worship him than worship you
You can't hide from Dobbs because he's stupid
823-749-0823
Call and give us a quotation from your favorite Bible or Holy Book
And your soul
Are you concerned about a future nuclear war?
Do you disagree with the logic of the arms race?
Do you feel threatened by our leaders' actions?
Do you want to prevent World War III?
You can help by participating in a non-violent demonstration
Staged in downtown Dallas
The annual No Business As Usual Day is just around the corner
We need the support of all individuals
Regardless of race, sex, age
Religious or political background
We need to strengthen our beliefs
Because nuclear war does not discriminate when it kills
If you are concerned by the threat of nuclear destruction
You must participate
The No Business As Usual Pledge
They won't listen to reason
They won't be bound by votes
The governments must be stopped from launching World War III
No matter what it takes
What you can do now
Organize your friends
Inform others of this protest
Make signs, banners or chants
Be there
Monday April 21st 830 AM
Be there Monday April 21st 830 AM
Dallas City Hall
If you would like more information or would like suggestions
Call
327-1945
827-3167
Your participation will help make this event a success
Best of God's love
And over here we find the subgenius male
Which is stacked up
I don't think unless you've got stereo
You won't be able to see this
Look at this
This is just one day's worth right there
One day's worth of little dollar bills
Twenty dollar bills
Checks and love offerings
Why you're here
It's bigger than all reality
It's bigger than all infinity
Help me somebody
She ain't got no legs
Pull the lever down and go
My legs are on fire
Need some help pray some
Stop asking for Lotto
No inflation
Answer
Buford
I'm out of here
I feel strong
You can do better
NAMUR
You're the killer
All right, dear friends.
We're going to go.
We're going to try to go to the phones one more time here.
Okay.
Hello, caller.
Hello, hello.
We got it.
Hello.
This John?
Yo, fret not.
Okay, well, let's hear your quotation, John.
Do you have the soul puller on?
Yeah, we're scanning you right now.
We have to align the mists with your ooze.
Fret not yourself because of evildoers,
and be not envious of the wicked,
for evil man has no power.
No future.
The lamp of the evil will be put out.
Now, well, that sounds pretty good, doesn't it?
It does.
Now, what I'm going to do is I'm going to just lightly turn this on
and take a little piece of your soul
like we've been taking from all the rest of the callers.
You ready?
Uh-huh.
Okay, so...
Caller?
Hello?
Oh, no.
How about that, Bucky?
I think you overdid that one.
Didn't pull in too much soul again, friends.
Well, if you've got any soul for Bob,
just call us back with a quotation from your handy holy book.
We're going to play a little tape for you for a few minutes.
823-7490, 823-8801.
And we're going to let you know when it's 12 o'clock.
We're going to continue the subgenius media barrage tape.
Here on KNO and 90.9 FM in Dallas and Fort Worth.
In your ear bowl.
Oh, ye alien sick men.
Oh, give me back my gone cat.
Oh, great daddy-o from outer space.
Oh, give me warning.
Oh, space creatures.
E-I-I-E-I-E.
That's an ingredient.
In an unfinished room in the Salem Custom House.
Through me.
Yes, sir. Can I help you?
I doubt it.
Well, in that case, if you'll just...
No one can help me.
Yes, sir.
Not that anyone's ever tried, of course.
Is that so?
Hardly worth anyone's while, really, is it?
I'm sorry, sir.
I'm aware of the percentage of being kind or helpful to a robot
if it doesn't have any gratitude, so please.
And you don't.
And think to yourself,
there's no place like home.
There's no place like home.
The 140-year-old woman involved in the plot to kill the president.
Obviously, the subgenius foundation is in possession of certain information
that maybe we should be looking into as a committee for
destruction of any...
Oh, shit.
I'll do it!
I know you will!
The story only starts when
you find the light of your life.
아닌
He fixed my house!
The only way to get it there is by describing any poor resident,
Bob Dobbs.
Brought to The Meteor.
I'll tell you in the first paragraph.
So I say to people,
Israel,
and Arnold Palmer's head shall materialize
in the space above your sleeping parlor,
and it shall in need be bloody.
It shall be dripping
with the residual blood
formed earlier in the day
when he,
without the word of Bob.
What are you laughing at?
You're supposed to be slackless children
and quit laughing.
Look, you want me to take away your slack
real quick, young lady?
Let us open the window of the puppet department
and listen.
The world is full of a number of things
and one of them is people.
But people
is the escape that people escape from most.
They take to gin and to histamine,
to aspirin,
Picasso and Tel Aviv.
And some take consolidated gas.
Or the Saturday evening post.
We pity you, we do,
for all the ills that hail you.
But here's good news for you.
You needn't be a failure.
A failure.
Tiddly-I, Tiddly-A,
Tiddly-all your trouble away.
You, too, can be a puppet.
Man, man, silly man,
full of human folly.
Why be a brave old man,
Ku Klux Klan,
when you can be Ku Klux Klan and Ollie?
Tiddly-I, Tiddly-D,
you can be just as happy as we.
Be a puppet, not an old saran.
Come out of the woodwork, brother.
And join the Brotherwood of Man.
The Brotherwood of Man.
You, too, can be a puppet.
Unspoiled and unproven.
Why be bothered by psychiatry?
By a tree?
And have yourself a gun?
And a gun.
I send the angel of the Lord,
I send right now power,
the very glory of God into that home.
I move back the foul spirits of opposition,
the lying spirits, the binding spirits.
I speak authority to you in the name of Jesus Christ.
Don't ask any questions, just do as I say.
All right?
We're pretty sure he's a psychopath.
Now, how do we spot him?
Well, if he's wearing a Napoleon hat, it's easy.
Otherwise, they come in all sizes and shapes.
From 11-year-old girls to 80-year-old men.
They all look perfectly normal.
I keep telling you all,
this is a sick and perverted nation.
All tired.
And nobody wants to be a part of this.
Nobody wants to listen to me.
Nobody wants to hear about Bob.
I try to tell everybody what's going on,
and they won't listen to me.
Well, to tell you the truth,
I can't stand it anymore.
Bob.
Bob, take care of me, Bob.
Just, just do away with them all.
I don't want them anymore.
They'll just crawl and lose you to my mind after all.
They don't love you, Bob.
They don't love you like I do.
Bob.
Bobby.
Boy destruction.
Everybody's crazy now.
Now, you're gone.
容 Macdonald just got caught,
counting his life to the head by a dog
and getting hyper dyslexic.
¡Uh-huh!
I just seems to love Pape Super Click to me more.
Get me out of this population.
Speaker 선
I'll be safe on the pleasure vessels of the sex goddesses from Planet X when that day of judgment comes.
Ah, yes, and you unbelievers will fry in a hell of your own making.
And how do I know this?
Why am I so sure?
Because I have faith, my friend, faith in Bob.
You don't use your mind to think about your religion.
Nay, nay, you let that Bob signal from space beam straight into your skull,
oh, unfettered by your stupid notions of good or evil or job or free will.
For the word of Bob is a direct word.
It is not written in some roundabout symbolic manner.
You don't try to figure out what it means, my friend.
You just do what it says.
Because Bob said it, I believed it, and that settles it.
Let there be slack.
823-7490.
823.
823-78801.
Praise Bob.
Oh, I think I got him back.
You want to go ahead and try to keep this soul on here?
Have I got him?
Okay, we'll try him.
Hello, caller.
Hello.
Caller, you are on.
Who's this?
Gary?
I want to read a quote from a book called Prometheus Rising by Robert Anton Wilson.
Fire away, dude.
Okay, it says,
Reality is a temporary resultant of continuous struggles between rival gangs of programmers.
Hmm, I like that one.
You ready for the soul sucker?
Yeah.
Sure.
Shit.
Just give me more founder swords.
Yeah.
Oh, man.
Well.
Hello.
What's more like that?
Say that, God?
So young.
What's that?
Dignified.
Right.
Well, that's them right.
Yeah.
It's not just the child zombies that murdered their mediocrity parents and then cruise the streets with bloody feet.
It's not just those starry old vics on the park benches with looks on their faces like those who shuffled out of the boxcars of Belsen and Auschwitz.
It's not just the anesthesiologist's frenigy.
It's not just the heaving pink meat masses that grope and clutch all around you.
It's not just the dino bones for Wotan.
It's not just the broken headlights, snapped antennae, and human excrement on your car hood.
It's not just that the old ways were best.
It's not just the bastardization and perversion of every honest means of survival.
It's not just the self-expression.
It's not just the kill-a-shit ganja from the dark side of the bush.
It's not just the penoid snipers locking and loading on every high-rise rooftop.
It's not just the wide-screen technicolor corporate daisy chain that has defiled the entire planet.
It's not just Mongo in the Congo with fa-fa-fas the size of basketballs.
It's not just the prophets crying lonely and alone in the wilderness.
It's not just the indignity of having to work for some bland, non-entity son-of-a-bitch who thinks workers are property.
It's not just the blueness of the wound cleansed by evil.
It's not just the battling eco-freaks who want to go back to nature without realizing that nature is an open-ditch latrine in midsummer.
It's not just some asshole with a pipe and a thing I know more than you do dog grin all over his homogenized face.
It's not just the horrible feeling of being entrapped inside a regimented, devolving world that the you certainly never made.
It's not just the doorway to doom.
It's not just wanting to know what the hell is really going on.
It's not just the missing H's or the stolen alpha-beta-max.
No, dear friends, there is more to it all than that.
Bob ain't no nickel-dime bum-show.
I put it to you, he's on the square and a corking fine business proposition.
He's the grandest thing yet, and don't you forget it.
Shout salvation and fightin' Jesus, you'll need to rise precious early, you sinner there, if you want to diddle the almighty Bob.
Not off.
He's got cough mixture with a punch on it for you, my friend.
In his back pocket. Just you try it.
Ah, yes. Dear friends, that was Dr. G. Gordon Gordon.
And we're gonna try to take this next caller here, take his soul off to subgenius soul land, or the land where the enemy souls...
Hi, Ethan.
Oh, no.
He's on hold.
How can he be on hold? Oh, somebody's got the phone up.
Hang it.
Hello?
Yeah.
Ethan, we finally got you on the air. You've been hung up on how many times now?
Five now.
Oh, heck. Well, let's hear that thing from Revelations you got for us.
Alright. And I looked, and I heard an eagle flying in midheaven.
Speak up real loud, as loud as you can.
Alright. And I looked, and I heard an eagle flying in midheaven, saying with a loud voice,
Whoa, whoa, whoa to those who dwell on earth because of the remaining blast of the trumpet of the three angels who are about to sound.
Man, that's scary. That's scary. Are you ready for the soul sucker?
Yeah.
Okay, now, if it hurts or anything, remember to shout so that I can take it off because we've lost two callers tonight.
Alright.
You ready?
Yeah.
Okay, now, you just wait you don't get behind the smoother.
And now come with me, and we'll just get started in the background.
I got coke bottles that, that's live and they're squirming and they're driving down to the birthday.
Don't do it.
Bob!
Bob! We want Bob! Where's Bob? We want Bob!
Right now! We want Bob!
Okay, Bob's probably not gonna be here in physical manifestation.
Oh!
Oh, where is Bob? He's everywhere.
Check yourself and feel if your Bob gland and make sure it's overactive like it's supposed to be.
This is the headquarters for the Church of the Subgenius.
Now wait a minute.
No, wait a minute. I love that area and I...
I represent a group of scientists who work with but one purpose.
To put an end to war.
Naturally, such a goal can be a...
Spurred.
Mm-hmm.
Men of vision. Men such as you, Doctor.
Gathered here, exchanging information daily.
Putting aside all thoughts of personal success.
We hope to achieve exciting new techniques.
Leap years ahead of the others.
I don't think I need tell you how effective our voices will be when the world learns of our achievements.
Well, there you have it.
Nothing new, perhaps, but then, what is?
The future of the Subgenius.
However, let me assure you, Doctor, that we are dedicated men and women.
And as such, we can accomplish wonders.
Like any other church, the search of the Subgenius has divine tenets.
Divine rules.
Divine orders.
The first rule of the Subgenius Church is...
Too much is always better than not enough.
Can I get her too much?
Too much!
What is it always better than?
Not enough!
Praise Bob! Praise Bob!
Welcome to the End Times.
In today's End Time essay,
we will be covering the difference between
the Brofram
and the Bloodyhead Launcher Society itself.
As seen here in our first slide,
the Bloodyhead Launcher Society goes on forever.
There is no end, and there's no use resisting.
The End Times
She jumps, Mercy.
Study guys.
Study.
It's a game called
Siege of Hell.
These analogu-
swoje
my life away from you.
Speak really loud.
No one takes my life away from me.
I give it up of my own
free will. I have the right
to give it up, and I have the right
to take it back.
This is what Bob has commanded me to do.
Thanks for sharing that with us.
That was real good.
I like that sucker.
You ready for the soul sucker?
Now,
now,
now remember, you don't want to get sucked entirely
into this machine, so
you want to start howling if I
get too much into you. Okay, you ready?
I'm ready.
Now, yes, dear friends,
those are the things I want to tell you about
today. The very many
things. The things that Bob
knows. The things that you
know and when you know
that you know it, because
everybody does have that plan,
that mystical
Bob plan in their feet.
That one that tells them what to do
if they don't think with it.
But somewhere along in the past,
man got confused
and decided to start thinking
with his brain, and when that happened,
oh, dear friends, that was
a very sad time
in the history of man.
Because when man
stands on his brain and thinks
with his feet,
then he'll know exactly
which way to go and
how to find Bob.
You gotta massage that foot gland,
and the only way to massage it
is to walk on it. Yes, sir.
Ha-ha, dear friends.
You gotta walk on the foot glands
for Bob, because when you're
walking and Bob's
talking, then you'll know
all you need to know
about what to do after
the holocaust.
After the aliens come and
take us and give us all
them giant,
pills, and all them
fantastic machines
that's supposed to run our lives
in that big, white stone that
everybody's gonna know personally
in their very own home.
Ah, yes, dear friends,
that stone, that's the stone.
That's the stone that you think
you might know and you think might
help you. But by God's
dear friends, that's the
stone that's gonna ruin your very
life. You think
you know who Big Brother is?
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Dear friends, I wanna tell you
tonight, you don't know.
You don't know nothing.
Come on, Tim.
Those UFOs, they're flying all over your house, sir.
That's right, and they know about Bob,
and they're gonna be dropping
the...
Doctors...
...
Ah, yes, Wendy Carlos
bangs planets on the head in the background.
We've got another call in, I think
we're gonna try to go for here.
We got two.
Two? Two calls, well...
I hope some...
...
decent quote this time.
I mean, no offense to the ones that have been in here,
but I want to hear some bloodthirsty...
Caller? Caller.
I want to hear some bloodthirsty Bible
quotes like,
I shall put my hook in thy
nose and yank as
hard as thy first
son. I think we got our
number three now. Hello.
Let's go ahead and
give it to us full force, and here you are
on the air.
Yeah, louder.
Oh, hello. Speak up. Go.
Uh, is, uh, do you have to,
um, uh,
listen, I'm a bad
actor, you know. Oh, no problem.
Did you have a question about feet or not?
Oh, feet, yeah.
Uh, well,
do you have to have a
foot fetish, like, to, um,
be a subgenius, or is it...
No, no, this is your foot gland. It doesn't
have anything to do with... Well,
yeah, I'd like to just tell him, see, you could have an elbow
fetish or whatever, as long as you also...
have a foot fetish. Oh, well, see,
I've, uh, I've got a foot
fetish, but I don't have an elbow fetish.
Well, that's, uh,
that'll do. You're in, you're in the church.
Well, um, why, uh,
how, how can
you find out if somebody else has, has
one, you know? Or, uh, somebody
else is a subgenius without actually,
like, uh, asking them
what they do with their extra toe jam
and stuff. What would you do
if, if I put you on the soul sucker right
now, and it started to really... Yeah.
really hurt? Would you start to yell? Well, right now,
uh... Ready? Here you go.
We are
Hello, caller.
On line two.
Yeah. Identify yourself?
Uh, this is Ed Casey.
Ed Casey. Yes. And you've got a problem
with green energy. Yes. I called
last week about this green energy blob,
and he said to ignore it.
But it's gotten worse because it's sucking all the
slack out of the show.
Sucking all the slack out of the show. There's a green energy
blob over... Over my speaker.
I cannot get any slack out of this show.
I'm really... How much did your speaker
cost you?
It was free. It was free?
It was free. Maybe it's, maybe it's sort of the
conspiracy's guilt trip on you.
To, that you didn't... No, I'm not...
I didn't pay for the speaker. And maybe they're trying to suck
all the slack out of the show.
So maybe I think you ought to go down to your local
uh...
uh... church of
of, uh, of sound warehousing
and, uh, make a donation.
Sorry.
I'm desperate for slack. I am addicted to it.
Have you ever sent any money to us?
The church?
You? Yes.
Well, like, I plan to.
Well, can we just take it out of you
in Seoul? Can we just take it out of you?
Can we just take it out of you in Seoul?
As long as it doesn't hurt.
If it hurts, will you scream?
I will scream.
All right, well, let's try it.
It's like a rabbit.
Oh, heck, I hurt the poor guy.
You all right?
Let's try it again.
Guess who was singing some song I was singing with Shen yong shuhl?
S-Se除 Ос
I do not
I don't feel so hot.
Let's try it again.
Say it again.
What's on freedom?
Was only through tribulations like this
can it be appropriately dramatized
what the dangers are
of embarking on an occult religion.
Does that question all your answers?
Yes, it does.
I think that, well, something like that, yes.
Have you a short question, please?
What is a heliopter?
A heliopter is a small occupational device
used by rotational and locational forces of the Bob Empire
in circumnavigating or circumambulating the atomic...
The voices, faces, music, and editing you've been listening to
come from Lepo Abernathy.
The Buck, Naked, and the Jaybirds.
Dr. O-Nan Canobite.
G. Gordon Gordon, killer for Bob.
Doctors for Bob.
Dr. Philo Drummond, overman, first degree.
Reverend Cleve Donut Duncan.
Dr. Snavely Eklund.
This is Dr. Ahmed Fishmark.
This is Blast Madness.
Bob is my blindfold world.
This is Harold.
Dr. Chris Ross.
This helipelvis is like a universe.
And this is Negative Land.
These are those fantastic swinging love corpses.
These are doctors for dinosaurs.
These are doctors for Wotan.
This is...
Gary the Brogue, נappelleםarı.
This is favourite music for the
Gary Gabbard
Sanctuary
Applicating for dubbing challenge
DR associating с D. K. Jones
NC-12NR.sternoda leaf from the future bass майor Funtime BedrockúaTV.com. This is D. K. Jones.
This is our greetings of the Lies Foundation.
The fighting preacher.
Watch it, Bob.
This is Dr. Howard.
Now, I didn't understand the meaning of this explanation, but I'm sure our callers later on will be able to help.