What, what, what, what, what, what, what?
What?
When I think of Kobasi, I think of you.
I think of Cleveland, Caneview.
If you're cleaning up after the flood, you'll need to cause in...
Cleaning up after what now?
Your own sweat.
Oh.
That means you've been too busy, Janet.
Something's wrong with your head.
Let me look inside your ear canal.
Have you been putting the wrong things in the right places again?
It's not safe to use electricity.
Electricity?
Yes, yes, yes.
If you're cleaning up after the flood, you'll need to cause injury or even death.
Oh, look.
There's an implant.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Yes, yes, yes.
There's an implant.
Oh, okay.
Yes.
Look, it's a little crystal bob's head.
Oh.
Smoke's coming out of his nose.
I'll put it right back in your head just very quickly.
Ouch.
Doesn't hurt as much going back out as it does coming in, does it?
Oh, no.
I guess it doesn't.
That's just like the incoming...
If you're cleaning up after the flood, you'll need to cause injury or even death.
Hungry, hungry.
Step right this way.
Get your thrilling, exciting...
Self-genius.
Power of...
Splash.
Get your third dimension and genuine 3D glasses.
Listen, boys and girls.
Four thrilling, colorful pictures of real 3D glasses.
Welcome to the hour of...
This is American glory.
This is American...
Your old cheerleader, pyropractor.
Go home.
You know how it works.
Yeah.
La la, you know...
Little cheerleader on the court.
Six, six, six.
And how does it feel?
This is a little bit bigger monster.
Finish what you start.
This is the best experience I've ever had.
So weak.
I like that.
It's a deep hole.
Thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you.
Unbelievable, yeah.
Zoom, zoom, zoom, zoom, zoom, zoom, zoom, zoom, zoom.
Back in history before time began, all the real cool cats had a solid plan.
When they dug a nervous chick, they...
All to a man went...
Aaaaah!
Ape call, doodly-ah-bah.
You wanna be cool, man?
Go ape.
Young mighty Joe swinging through the trees
Was the king of everything that roosted in the leaves
But when he saw a girl ape hanging in the breeze
He went...
Aaaaah!
Ape call, doodly-ah-bah.
You like to be hip, boy?
Go ape.
You're on the air.
Hi, Dr. Sinister.
What were you saying about old hipsters, some terrible slanderous thing?
Actually, that was...
I don't know what hipsters are exactly, but I know that nobody seems to like hipsters.
People tend to use hipster as a disparaging term.
And maybe I have a bit of a hipster streak in me, but I don't even know exactly what
that is.
You know, like...
You know, it...
I mean, I guess...
I don't know.
Well, it depends on...
It depends on who you're being compared to, I suppose.
I was standing in line for some kind of a rock and roll show, and I was with Reverend
Nikki Death Chick, who's about 20 years younger than me.
Mm-hmm.
We were kind of stuck in this long line with hipsters of every age group around us.
Whoa.
And...
Where was this again?
It was somewhere...
Some show we went to see in Dallas a million years ago in the previous century.
Nikki was probably about 23 or 24, and I was younger.
I forget.
It may have been an Oingo Boingo show or Devo or something like that.
And we're standing in line with all these hipsters around us, and I just...
Suddenly I just...
I realized that I wasn't really a hippie.
Hippie or hipster or...
I was really...
Well, I was too young to be a hippie, and I was a little too old to be a punk.
Mm.
So I was stuck in that in-between thing where you smoked pot and said you were a hippie.
Yeah.
But I realized I really wasn't.
I was really just a geek, a weirdo.
And I said that to Nikki, and she said, I know I'm not really metal.
And we kind of looked down.
But it's not like I'm a geek.
But at the same time, you know, we had the pride in the fact that we were...
We really didn't fit in with...
Neither one of us fit in with our peers around us at all, even though it was a bunch of people
going to see a Frank Zappa concert or whatever the hell it was, some hipster thing.
And don't you get tired of the old hipsters who get drunk and start reciting Frank Zappa?
Or the Firesign Theater, or Monty Python, or Doctor Who, or some...
Whatever their animation, whatever their thing is.
Recitations, yeah.
Nowadays it would be games.
And you just want to kill them all!
Because just because you like something smart and brag about that, that doesn't necessarily
mean that you yourself are smart, because some of the dumbest people I've known of were
into what they thought was smart.
And what they thought meant they must be smart.
Zappa or Ayn Rand.
That being really bad examples.
Ayn Rand, there you go.
And I was just as guilty when I was a young feller.
I looked down upon ACDC and Black Sabbath because I knew the really cool bands were
Captain Beefheart and so forth.
I never cared for ACDC.
I never knew...
I'm not a very good normal.
It would be hard for me to even place an ACDC song.
Princess Wee had to go, oh, you know that one song...
Yeah, yeah!
When the cats sing in my dance!
Right, right, right.
That horrible song they used to play all the time.
Right.
Yes, I hate that stuff.
Yeah, actually, and it's interesting though.
I think that was an interesting era in history when normals were into stuff that, you know,
was dark and nasty.
Well, you know, if I had been in high school at that time, I would have been a normal.
I would have been a normal then.
Well, I guess if you had been in high school at that time, then that would be...
It wouldn't seem so corny to me, if you know what I mean.
It's like what's playing on the radio on the first hot date, when you really score and
get to, like, second base or something, that's what you're gonna kind of identify with for
a long, long time.
Huh!
So, I haven't even heard that song yet.
Interesting.
And it takes a long time for that silliness to go away.
No.
And I think in a lot of people's cases, it never would have...
ever does.
I never got,
nobody got that joke
I made.
I got it.
So,
I don't know.
I've been,
I've been on the edge
of hip,
to the world of hipsters
myself my whole life.
Because they was,
seemed like they were
more interesting than
regular ordinary people.
But then you find out
they are just regular
ordinary people
who are posers
on the weekend.
I'm sorry,
I had to play that.
Anyway.
So,
like,
all I'm saying is
that I used to be
a real snob
about music
because it was like,
oh,
the dumb kids
like this kind of music
and us intellectual kids
like this other kind.
So that means
we're better and smarter.
And you know,
when you,
when I became
a little bit older
and heard that same
argument coming
from the mouth
of somebody
who wasn't me,
I realized
how dumb it was.
And that as
the Reverend
Friday Jones said
so personally,
perceptively,
long ago,
all music
is stupid.
I agree.
It's not,
you know,
necessary to our
survival.
No,
absolutely not.
I hate all music.
I think all music
is absolute garbage,
actually.
You're right,
in one way or another.
Well,
it explains
you're doing
a radio gig.
Right,
which explains
why the music
I play is all,
all over the place,
you know.
Well,
I love music
in general,
like most humans
do.
Right.
And even subgeniuses.
But,
it's the snobbery
of music.
It's like being
the snob about
what kind of art
you like.
It's,
it's like,
doesn't that
sort of,
you know,
you're getting away
from the idea
of real art
and real music
if you're going
to suddenly dictate
what is valid
and what's not,
what's good
and what's bad.
And that's all
based on local,
temporal,
coolness
factors.
Yeah.
Well,
personally,
if you're born
short and ugly,
coolness might be
the only way
you can get laid.
Yeah.
Smartness ain't
gonna do it.
Big dinosaur
was a long,
tall lizard.
He drifted
through the jungle
like a slow blizzard.
But when he got
a double-ticket
lady lizard,
he did.
Ape call
doodly-ah-bah.
You wanna be
sharp,
sharp cat?
Go ape.
A pterodactyl
was a flying fool.
Just a...
I thought I'd break in
and tell you
what a pterodactyl was.
Well, it was sort of
a stork-looking bat
with sharp teeth
that cruised around
looking for...
Say,
we haven't changed
a bit,
have we, cats?
A pterodactyl
was a flying fool.
Just a breeze-flapping
daddy of the old school.
But a mama-dactyl
could sure
make him drool.
Ape call
doodly-ah-bah.
Don't be a square,
Joe.
Go ape.
I met...
Where's the monster jugs?
I met the editor
of monster jugs.
They're right over there.
Reverend Diane Hanson.
Hamster?
What?
She was a former
jugs-type model
who had become
an editor
of a men's magazine
and loved it.
Loved her job.
She said...
She edited
the magazine's
jugs
and some
foot fetish
thing.
Legs or feet
or something like that.
And she said that
manipulating men
was so much fun
because it was so...
It's such an easy job.
Paid well.
She's recently
edited some
marvelous books
for attachment.
Well, she had
all the ingredients
of a good job.
She knew
quite a bit
what she liked.
She knew
that she enjoyed
her work.
And she was good
at her work.
And she got paid for it.
Diane Hanson has edited
some really great books
from fashion.
What more can a worker
ask for?
Oh, I didn't know that.
Yes, I think one of them
is the one on...
Workers that don't get to work
are like...
Men's sweat magazines.
Have you ever seen that?
Men's sweat magazine.
My God, you've got
to see that.
Men's sweat...
I did find a website
for veiny women.
Photos of women
with huge...
My mom would have been
a star of that website.
...star of
vericoseveinywomen.com.
Yeah.
Women with
nostril incrustation.
There's something
for everybody
except me.
Have you seen
Splosh magazine?
Ew.
No, but how about
heavilyincrestednostrils.com?
Pass.
Heavilyincrusted,
well, that's...
There she is.
She's all a damsel
of light dressed in a silken robe of white that shadowy in the moonlight show.
If you made a joke, what if the world was so screwed up that dot dot dot by the time you've
finished saying that, it's on the internet.
Yeah, somebody's got a website.
They've already developed all the software and put it out there in the length of time
it takes to say it.
Now they have software that generates the website as you're saying it.
And wildly glittery.
It's voice controlled software.
That was...
The gems in
That's why I quit working on my website.
I was...
It was embarrassing me.
I guess it was frightful there to see a woman with
And now you can go to myembarrassingwebsite.com.
Beautiful.
And make your own.
Yeah.
Automatically.
Right.
Just by thinking.
Just by thinking it.
Software's so great.
We've totally disintermediated the software developer and writer from the...
Finally can't say that on KPN.
But with radio you can say something and...
You can say but with...
...instantly.
Yeah.
But not disintermediated.
That's right.
Oh, okay.
With the medium of radio, instant generation is possible.
Too many syllables.
But it might mean something else than what it sounds like.
So we have to watch out for what you...
Yeah.
But it does say media in it.
So maybe...
...the council will forgive us.
...as we've found out to our distress many times.
Hey, big boy.
Can I give you a lift?
I'm a bad girl.
I'm so bad.
Oh, yeah!
Hey, big boy.
Can I give you a lift?
Hey!
Yes, baby.
And praise Bob.
This is Hour of Slack Number 1155, sex-hurt and love-fun themed, from the Church of
the Subgenius.
And that last collage, and many subsequent ones, are by the Reverend Norrell.
Norelpref of Norelpref.com.
The Hour of Slack titles and much else are by Fernanda Nende-Lemur.
And we're hearing clips from radio shows, Puzzling Evidence from KPFA Berkeley,
and Radio Synesthesia from WCSB Cleveland.
Nervous, Nervous does the ape call.
And friends, it's a love and pluses show as illustrated in this great rant from Winterstar 2008.
Friends, Reverend Bleepo Aberdathy has been a subgenius longer than damn near anybody.
1981, 82.
You can tell just by looking at him.
Praise Bob.
Bleepo.
Thanks.
You know, looking around the room,
there's a lot of people.
There's all kinds of people here.
And as a subgenius preacher for so many years,
I've had so many voices as a subgenius preacher.
But I decided to use this one today
and don't necessarily assume that this is the one that is, you know, set in stone.
You'll notice around you there are a lot of people who are various paganistic philosophies
and not agnostic, whatever you are.
And, of course, this one right here, Bob,
he becomes the personification.
He becomes the personification of what we call slack.
Praise Bob.
And I was talking with my dear friend Isaac Bonowitz about this,
and he reminded me that the only thing you have to lose through over-personification is Mr. Dignity.
So remember that, friends.
You know, there's a lot of confessing going on these days in religion, Oprah, Dr. Phil,
and stuff.
And I want to admit something to this audience for the first time publicly.
I feel it's time for me to come clean about this.
When I was a baby, I was part of a teething ring.
But enough of that.
You see, there's string theory and all that.
My friend Chris Rush has reminded me that string is real.
It's really merely baby rope.
So be aware of that as you're thinking about quantum physics.
Oh, my God.
The implications.
Good Lord, man.
Yes.
That's why I brought it up.
Now, Marshall McLuhan reminded us that new technologies amputate as much as they amplify.
You'll notice that as you're walking around, going around,
and seeing that as we're able to make even higher,
you're able to make even higher-resolution recordings on computers that are 96 kilocycles,
as opposed to the 44 that you're...
They go up to 200 kilobit cycles.
I don't remember all those words and stuff.
But anyway, you can make just the most highly accurate recordings now that you could ever, ever make.
Mirror image sound recordings are now possible.
It's impossible to tell.
Super high-resolution digital stuff is impossible.
And there are a lot of other technologies out there that allows us to record things more accurately.
And you can blow up these pictures that you take with your little cameras up to billboard size
and see molecules in the people's ring fingers and stuff.
It's amazing what you can do.
And yet, at the same time that this is happening,
shit sounds worse than ever on these little fucking MP3 players.
Because you're grinding.
As we can make it finer, we're also grinding it up finer.
And spewing it out at a lower bit rate.
So, I don't know where the comfort is in that,
but I have noticed an increase in something that I would call trans-porn-tainment.
This is something that if you had mentioned it in the 1950s,
people would say, nah, they would never allow that.
But no, friends, it's true.
On people's dashboards, you now have TVs.
So that you can watch TV as you drive.
Not only that, you can put whatever you want on this TV.
And I swear to God, swear to Bob,
as I was driving through New York City just a few months ago,
broad daylight, moms and dads and kids walking up and down the street,
cabs going by, buses, people, cops everywhere,
there was one man driving a Mercedes Benz,
giant thing, who, and he was just calm as toast,
watching really hardcore three-way fucking and sucking.
Right there, on his dashboard.
It's trans-porn-tainment.
And it struck me, now, maybe as we get used to it,
and our minds are more and more falling apart and over-saturated with media,
maybe we need a certain kind of like, you know, mental stimulation.
We're not allowed to drink, we're not allowed to smoke.
So you need something to keep you awake.
You can't drink coffee.
So it might as well be porn.
But how excited should you get while you're driving?
What are the limits?
These are things we have to ponder and figure out,
and you know, just figure out, you know, because if you're like,
if you're like falling asleep, yeah, you get a hard-on,
you're like, okay, yeah.
But then there's the point of distraction where, you know,
you're reaching a point of happy climax where, you know,
you'll lose consciousness, and it's extremely dangerous.
You don't want people driving around having orgasms
while they're, you know, supposed to be paying attention to the traffic light.
So, I don't know.
As far as I'm concerned, it's going to get worse before it,
as it gets better.
Because that's the thing.
Everything is getting worse and getting better at the same time.
So for every doomsday scenario, there's another scenario,
well, maybe we can just save this here planet.
Maybe there is a way to get, you know, internal combustion engines
replaced by perpetual motion machines.
And we will have that slack that we were, you know, dreaming of.
I'm just going to refer to my notes here.
All right.
There are two different coasts.
He's watching TV while he's preaching.
I am.
And I'll...
He's watching TV while he's preaching.
That's what's keeping me awake.
It's...
There are two coasts in this country, I've noticed.
And I've finally come up with a theory about the two coasts.
Because you'll notice that people on the West Coast are like,
yeah, man, we'll put up like...
We can put up vending machines to dispense medical marijuana.
What the hell is the West Coast, man?
You know.
And on the East Coast, you know, where we're still recovering from 9-11,
we're like, oh, you know, what are we going to do?
All this poison in the water.
The bagels are bad.
Ah!
And I figured out that there are two huge devices
buried on the various coasts by the conspiracy
that have kept the focus as simple as,
well, we're going to do this this way.
And on the West Coast, it's the...
Yes, it's the subwoofer is on the West Coast.
The subwoofer is on the West Coast.
And the high-frequency nebulizer,
or what I like to call the ultra-int,
is on the East Coast.
And the high-frequency projector,
it's like a tweeter on your old speakers there.
It's just pumping out anxiety
that's keeping us all uptight and making us worry about shit.
And that's balanced out by the subwoofer,
which is just...
It just sort of slows down everything
and sort of puts people in this perpetual sleep.
So that means it's up to the people
more towards the middle of the country,
more in places like Cleveland
and here in Pennsylvania, wherever we are,
to keep that balance there.
So if you're ever feeling irrelevant,
if you're people who live in the Midwest
and you're feeling irrelevant to the coasts,
I want you to be comforted
because you're actually standing in the sweet spot.
You really are.
And it's important to you to repop...
I think that the Midwestern party people understand,
even though all they have to eat
is like American cheese and iceberg lettuce,
it's still their job
to bring as much slack to the country as they possibly can.
They're the ones who actually should be reproducing.
Not the ones in the malls necessarily with 100 children,
but you people.
It's up to you to please go and spread the word
and keep the country happening.
Because, yeah, the coasts are kind of getting out of control.
But again, I think it's all getting worse
as it is getting better.
Finally, I just want to talk briefly
and leave you with the thought
that the thing that the Church of the Subgenius
is continually doing for me as a preacher
is not only do I try to imbue every piece of work I do
with a little bit of Dobbs
and a little bit of what I've learned through the years here,
but the subgenius church has helped me
to replace fear with humor.
And I think there's nothing more important than that.
And I'd like to leave with a little hymn
that I know.
It's not so funny.
It's just... I'll try.
I said I would try to do this,
and so I'm going to try this.
And you can feel free to sing along,
and then I'll leave.
So it's one that I once heard on a show
that was called The Great American Dream Machine,
and it just never left my mind
after I heard it like 30-some-odd years ago.
And it went like...
I want to be ready
Lord, ready to put on my long white robe
Lord, I want to be ready
I want to be ready
Lord, ready to put on my long white robe
Ready to put on my long white robe
Er, er, er, er, er, er
Reverend, please bow out loud.
Oh, God, and be so glad
that I wasn't singing today.
That was wonderful, Bleepo.
I know what he means
about all the cameras and recorders.
I used to film my life,
especially when my kids were growing up.
Everybody does that.
But I did it for the record.
A lot.
Our last vacation, I didn't even bring
the video camera because I realized
as long as you're seeing through that little box,
you're just seeing what's in the little box.
You're not really there.
So I decided to start being here a little bit more.
So if you smell something funny, that's why.
The first thing I want to discuss in today's podcast
is the goal of the podcast.
I mean, why create a podcast?
Secondly, I want to talk about teensporn.com.
What is it and why bother?
And lastly, are you pro-porn?
Maybe a tongue?
This podcast exists for a reason,
giving me an excuse to purchase a podcasting microphone.
Does the internet need another podcast?
No.
Does it need sex, pornography, and...
sex, pornography, and masturbation?
Sex and porn every single day?
No.
Um, surf porn, or surf porn because the Bible says so.
I've decided to surf porn.
Whatever the reason, I've decided to surf porn.
And to indulge in a porn habit.
Feed a porn habit.
And that's what we want, isn't it?
So I can be for you what you want to see.
I have the timing down, yeah, to surf pornography.
Some of our members like to see porn without a doubt.
I guarantee it.
Would I like to see porn?
Well, I watch porn two to three times each day.
And I wank while watching it.
Nothing wrong with that.
To surf porn, wanking on porn.
Masturbate.
I get that.
Come to teensporn.com.
Create an account and practice on us.
It really annoys me on our local PBS station here.
When they're fundraising, they get rid of the actual good shows that I wanted to see on PBS.
And they replace it with like these horrible boomer nostalgia movies.
Like the 50s and 60s.
Where they're just like, it's all your favorite songs from the 50s and 60s.
And they show this footage that's got to be like over 10 years old.
Maybe 20 years old in some cases.
You know, of like, you know, former like 50s and 60s pop stars performing on stage.
Or worse still, they'll have snake oil salesmen peddling, you know, a plan to...
Our boomers need our snake oil.
But, you know, now there's all this crazy stuff.
Crazy Generation Y nostalgia stuff going on.
Like, I don't think any generation has been so horribly inflicted with nostalgia so early as mine.
You're right.
It's disturbing.
You're right, actually.
And I'm really tired of it because...
Because stuff sucked back then.
They messed it up horribly.
The 80s sucked.
And I don't understand why people my age don't understand that.
Well, it causes inflammation of the bowel.
That's number one.
People have to be always aware of the, you know, the physical actual problems you're going to have with viewing this kind of stuff.
I had a lot of prins in the 80s because of that.
They usually think, you know, there's going to be a little treat for the eye and then maybe you'll get bored because it is 80s and boring and stuff.
But the next thing you know, there's physical symptoms.
And they're not good.
There's chills.
There's dryness of the mouth.
And there's, I think, a blurring of vision that causes some people to actually throw their TVs out the window.
So...
And in Cognite, it causes things like painful menstruation and moodiness.
In what?
Sounds like a commercial for Breezitol.
Oh, is that the place where they have the giant?
I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
I thought you were talking about the huge ones again.
Side effects may include painful castration.
Now that's the direction we want to go with this.
Viagra just turned 10 years old.
He's a problem child.
Really?
Yep.
You know, they grow up so fast.
But they don't grow up very much, do they?
What are we going to do when he's 19 and he's really old?
Really horny.
Talking about Viagra and saying they don't grow up very much is...
I get it.
You know what's really funny is they discovered it was causing blindness in some people.
It's like, gosh, kind of makes you wonder what they were using it for.
It's making them go blind.
Maybe it's not the Viagra, but...
Yeah.
I tried Viagra once and it made my entire body puff up like a toady frog.
And I'm not exaggerating.
I mean, that's the way it felt.
Well, that was all the blood, you know, just rushing to other parts of your body besides,
you know, the most important one.
Well, or it could just have been confused on which part was which.
It could have been the camel burritos.
Right.
It was the nano-onans in your body that were reacting to this Viagra.
And it realized, hey, the Viagra is here to, you know, expand blood vessels, so let's expand
all the blood vessels.
And it could have to do with the fact that it's the actual Viagra.
It's actually designed to help stimulate the parts of your body that are involved during
sex.
So in Sang's case, it must use more of your body.
Well, it does, it certainly does do that.
It's just that it does all this other stuff as well.
You're just using too many parts of your body.
It was, let me put it this way.
I wasn't going to do that again just for some girl.
His skin was cracking, Lassie.
His, you know, his...
They were like, his pores were oozing this weird, malodorous stuff, this stinky stuff.
He was on the verge of popping.
Leave your lover alone here at this hour of the morning.
Go grab your dick.
Out of shape and tired.
Help, help, help, help, help, help, help, dog, dog, dog, dog, dog, dog, dogger, dogger.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
Yes, sir.
Clap trap, clap trap.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yes, yes.
Crap, crap.
Mm-hmm.
Honky cracker.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
How do you know?
No, no, no, no.
We don't know.
Biotech banking.
Taking a Broadway show.
Oh, oh.
I'm serious.
McBush, McBush.
Who, who, who.
Darn it, darn it.
Bull, bull, bull, bull.
Guns, guns and gay aspect is just, it's, it's, it's hideous.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Such, such.
Crap, crap.
Game, game, game, game.
at the sales table we are selling for the first time ever bob condoms notice there's a little bob
on the condom and connie duns it looks like i don't have the connie them with me and i forgot
to burn the dollar bill to to uh make i'll do that at the end but i have to warn you i have to give
you this disclaimer number one it's got bob on it so it's probably got a hole in it you don't even
need to think about that but the whole charm of a bob condom of would be of course or a connie dum
but to see the distortion that happens when you put it on you know well these are the bob is only
printed on the package i have to be fair with you when you pull the rubber out it's just another
what did how call them coney island flight fish
coney island it's just a plain
coney island
island white fish without a dob's head on it and of course the reason is that who wants to get ink
in their bloodstream you know what would you print you'd have to have ink printed on the outside
or the inside one side of the condom somebody's gonna you'll end up with a smeary
screwed up doll's face inside you
and which you might say well everybody doesn't everybody want that but not necessarily
made of toxic ink so we're working on the manufacturer of these things to switch over to printing them directly on the condom using squid ink or prairie squid ink something or something that tastes good too probably would be good i don't know i don't need to worry about
a pick up subgenius pick up line will be able to be hey baby can i tattoo your cervix
that's gross that's childish
that's childish and vulgar and we're not here this isn't a childish vulgar religion
you fuckwad
this is
from bc
good morning bliss revolution one of the most brutal in a brutal century pretty pretty pretty pretty
puerile and wrong-headed and the pill came
out and during childbirth
Still
So
Or
Mac
E
are dangerous. Prepare to turn away. 30 seconds. 15 seconds. 10 seconds. 9, 8, 1.
Stop. I painted your name, not in the light. About 8 feet tall, about 12 feet wide. I think that you believe me, but I came back down. And for a couple of weeks, we were the tall little town.
Hey, baby girl, say who and who. Hey, boy, say who and who.
Hey, everybody.
Say who and who. Hey, baby girl, say who and who.
Well, then I left town looking for a rolling grain. And it's a very nice week with a drink, six, eight, and four.
Care of me, whoever reaches, can't explain. I missed you so much, I fell in love.
And I cry. Oh, what do you see there.
But I understand, now. How we can understand each other, and believe me, what I don't understand.
And I think what I couldn't understand is me thinking, oh where did I miss thiszenia you
remember my love from youth.
Well, one day there was a factory in one of the parks
It was heated with wood and the house caught fire
I reached for the baby with the smoke and the sparks
But each one did I see the girl of the guitar
I got a lot of money, got a lot of good friends
But I can never back, I was like a man for says
Every name was changed, every story was true
Every priest was me, every strength was you
And they danced like angels, blessed out for being lovers
And I wrote their life story on a match
And the girls sang loo-de-loo
And the boys sang loo-de-loo
And everybody sang loo-de-loo
The semen sample was mixed.
Stop that. Holy crap.
Hell yeah, I lost it.
So you found the sex toys? Rough sex gone bad?
Love sucks.
Yeah, it doesn't.
Screw love!
Permanent brain damage.
Stop that.
Hell yeah, I lost it.
Rough sex gone bad?
Screw love!
The semen sample was mixed.
Holy crap.
So you found the sex toys?
Love sucks.
Yeah, it doesn't.
Screw love!
Permanent brain damage.
You can go buy a shawty.
Hold up the local tab.
Or steal a few VCRs.
Or try a smash and grab.
You won't be getting half the loot.
Your lawyer QC will.
You may as well obey the law.
I sentence you to Roeville.
Roeville.
I sentence you to 14 years in Roeville.
I shoot a man in Reno.
Just to watch him die.
Go down to the casino.
To see a dead and die.
It sure won't be Lloyd Williams.
Who hears the judge's will.
Citizen for OPDM.
Ladies' Universe!
I sentence you to Roeville!
Roeville!
I sentence you to 14 years in Roeville!
I will sentence you, sentence you send theaps.
I will sentence you, sentence you, sentence you.
For crime against the person, the tabloid press will shout.
The animal will be locked away and never let him out.
For crime against property, you will have to pay the bill.
For crime against the spirit, I sentence you to reveal.
No one will.
I sentence you to 14 years in no one will.
Oh, Tissom.
He did that.
T-I-S-M, Tissom from Australia.
And wouldn't you know it, as soon as we started playing them, as soon as we discovered them,
their lead guitarist died.
Many excuses.
Blow.
Acid.
Under the Nazis.
Cynical.
Rap to make phone calls and knock on doors.
The Bush administration.
The leader of Al-Qaeda in Iraq.
Pope.
Worshippers attended Pope.
Condoleezza Rice.
Mass at St. Patrick's Cathedral.
Among them, former mayor.
Mayor Rudy Giuliani.
Many were surprised to see him receive communion.
Giuliani's been married 3,000 times.
Texas Judge Friday ordered that Giuliani submit DNA samples to help sort out family ties.
It's wrong.
Crackers.
Hardwood.
Sample.
Gross.
You want a fucking dealer.
Tap, tap, tap.
Nice.
Hardwood.
Neo-Nazi group.
Caring since 1881.
They were mentally ill when they licked your face.
Now is the perfect time to get the hole you've always wanted.
Absolutely free.
Yo.
Rose program.
Privilege.
Escape slaves.
Yo.
You mean giving up my rear?
Yes, would you?
Absolutely.
Without a doubt.
Thank you.
Attack it.
All day.
Or all night.
Ugh.
Riddles.
Rose.
Serious.
Life starts.
Now please, you've got to understand.
Now let's continue with
Bah, bah, bah, bah, bah.
More, more, more, more, more, more, more, more, more.
Swing.
She wants to swing.
Don't you understand?
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
Do you have any idea?
What?
No, no, no, wait, wait, wait a second.
Wait, wait, stop, stop, stop.
Wait, stop, stop, stop.
You're the man.
You.
Bob.
The man.
Yo.
Oh, man.
I blew it big and Bob nailed me and man, I don't know if he likes me and I don't know
if I can start all over again and I still.
Really dumb, really angry.
Yeah, in the house.
Got a little hard.
Rap, rap, rap.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Okay, I blew it, all right?
I've got a, I've got a.
Slack.
Do you see what's happening?
Of course.
Slack.
Baby.
The pleasure.
No.
And don't think for a minute.
Let's just forget the whole thing happened and start all over again.
Want to do that?
Oh, oh, oh.
Forget it.
That's the concluding thought from Bob.
It's always great.
You'll want to use.
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
Just click in.
Slack.
You ain't nothing but a rap.
You ain't no friend of mine.
We start a series of sermons today that are really a conversation with our cult.
I grabbed this woman and not in a good way.
And it's really hard.
And you know, you know what I'm saying?
There's a lot of tempting women.
I want a woman.
Oh, man.
Yeah.
Got to have another bite.
But there are complications.
And coming out incredibly.
Lips respond.
Crack.
Clan.
Transgendered woman.
You have an incredible hard thing.
She, man.
We are homosexual.
Sexually.
We are so loose.
And we are so loose.
My parents are weird.
And I'm in this terrible situation.
So hard.
I do these things.
Nobody knows what I do.
It's my little secret.
Nothing is yuck.
This is a little one.
Is it not a little one?
You're on the air.
Good evening, Dr. Sinister.
Welcome, Rocknard.
How is everybody tonight?
Well.
Full of beef.
We're snowed in, baby.
Yeah, I am, too.
Actually, we're not.
We've managed to tunnel our way out, most of us.
Oh, have you been having all sorts of snow porn on the local news?
Chelsea porn?
No, snow porn.
Snow porn?
Well, disaster porn.
Of course, the local news tries to make everything look as horrible and dangerous as they can.
Because then the commercials look so much more exciting.
Well, they were talking about it on NPR, actually, not like CPN.
It was like in the hourly news updates from NPR News in Washington.
I'm blah, blah, blah.
And like they said, like Ohio severely snowed in.
Cleveland Airport closed.
And ODOT telling people stay home unless it's an emergency.
Well, blinds and all kinds of blinds are not exactly sexy unless you have a fleet erection.
Right.
I mean, or it precludes.
But how can you guarantee a flea-like erection?
Actually, do fleas have ovipositors?
I'm sorry, I get confused.
Do fleas have ovipositors?
I can't, I know grasshoppers do.
I think they have a penile bone, don't they?
Like a whale does.
For grasshoppers?
Grasshopper has an organ called an ovipositor, I think.
Gee, that sounds so much like a positor.
And a cloaca on the other end.
A cloaca.
But grasshoppers breathe through holes in their sides.
In their sides.
Spiracles.
Spiracles, yes.
And that's why you can't have gigantic insects because the, I guess it has something to do
with the way the spiracles are made.
Like they could not hold themselves together if they were larger than the largest insects
out there.
It's true that you cannot have giant insects due to nuclear radiation like we used to think
in the 50s.
But with quantum string bubbles, you can get giant insects.
Brain numeral.
And then they can play violin.
Yeah.
That's because they have the string theory built right into their DNA.
And when you see them in the old cartoons, they've actually gone back in time.
And all grasshoppers, you know, it's like a syllogistic thing.
If all grasshoppers play the violin, therefore, you know, equals, all grasshoppers play the violin.
So there you go.
That's a tautology.
Well, as Bleepo Abernathy pointed out at Winterstar regarding string theory, strings are just baby ropes.
Yeah.
Well, yeah.
So what does that portend for our whole universe?
But then our food, like vermin, giant stuff like that would be inadequate ropes and would be inadequate strings.
What happens when those, when the strings, the cosmic strings become cosmic ropes?
Ugh.
Or snap.
Everything thickens up.
Cosmic nooses.
Well, what if they become frayed and still hold together?
Cosmic strings may snap.
You know what I mean?
I keep breaking my cosmic G-string.
Oh, geez.
What an ill prescription.
I'm sorry.
The E-string.
I meant the E-string.
We're thinking I'm supposed to jump.
Anyway.
I just can't get, anyway.
Two ones.
There's no chanc, chancren, chancrenistic.
I'm a lawyer.
Lawyer of the air.
I got legal problems.
No credit cards.
But what's the problem?
What's going on with you?
Well, basically, I have some form of ecstasy.
I'm a lawyer.
I have ecstasy while in our home.
What happened?
Tell me what happened.
Okay.
From the beginning, basically what happens is I was upstairs getting dressed.
Well, the nanny came.
And this was probably like let's say, and then they said that he has the DNA.
Call it ecstasy, right?
Correct.
So what happened then?
So then of course what have you.
So wait, wait, wait.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Correct.
That would be something, right?
Right.
And then.
And now what's going on?
Now what's going on?
It's ecstasy.
It's your ecstasy.
It's your right?
I completely understand.
Okay.
And.
So what's the next step?
The next step is.
I don't think.
You're, you're, you're.
Oh, you're.
Come on, come on.
Let's begin our time together with Bob.
Bob reminds us of an important spiritual principle.
Listen.
Watch.
Wait.
Be careful.
We'll rest assured you are being changed by slack.
Yeah.
We're coming again.
Watching the rear.
What do you do with all your men?
Wait, wait, wait.
You gotta.
And that's why I want you to see the.
For as often as I take you.
Come on.
Don't touch.
Mix.
Mash them.
I, I, and I, I have a hard time.
What are you doing?
Yoke.
Get out of that.
And I don't care.
Come on.
I'm not.
Forward.
Backward.
What's happening?
Lose.
Direction.
Bob will close our teaching today.
The bad burn of.
Bob.
Word.
Cheese.
In the next hour or so, we're going to talk about lust.
And perhaps you as well.
Like lost pornography.
Like internet pornography.
Internet pornography.
I just use internet pornography as a fact of life.
It's out there.
You can Google it.
It's really cool in terms of how fast things happen.
One, two strokes from seeing things on the screen that are just absolutely unbelievable.
So, you know, I'm a surfer.
I'm a porn star.
Porn star.
Naked.
Hardening so as to indulge in every sensuality.
Continual lust for more.
Sex and those kind of things.
Sensuality.
Become sensual in your thinking.
New pleasures and sexuality.
Sensuality starts as a continual lust for more.
Because you want it.
You can't shut the lust engine down.
Seeing a party going on.
But that's sensuality in terms of just a continual lust for more.
The dirty movies.
Continual lust for more.
There's got to be more and more and more and more.
Reviewing pornography.
Getting caught up in masturbation.
So, we're going to try and look at it.
Look at that tonight.
Right on.
Turn in your Bibles.
Thank you.
Word.
So, we're going to be talking about the importance of tongue.
Describe a person that is coming.
I gave the example.
Phil, a couple of men to give them Tiger Woods in their life.
Young men will see visions.
Your old men will dream dreams.
The tongue is the first thing that...
What is the big deal about tongue?
And what is the big deal about tongue?
Tongue.
Religion is worthless.
Okay?
Word.
Type.
Tongue.
Wrong.
Religion is worthless.
PowerPoint is worthless.
You know, inappropriate.
None of that means a thing.
And our religion is worthless.
And here is why.
Murder.
Adultery.
Sexual immorality.
Theft.
False testimony.
Slander.
What goes in comes out.
Old Papa Tiger was a boss of the Nile.
Just a sport model cat with a solid style.
He was old King Cool till the girl tiger smiled.
A-ya!
Ape called Doodly-Abba.
Beezorch Daddy-o.
Go ape.
Adam was the first boy in the land.
The big mellow roony daddy with an iron hand.
But when little Eva said,
Hi, man.
A-ya!
Ape called Doodly-Abba.
Don't be a cube rube.
Go ape.
So remember to ape call today.
Yeah.
Yeah!
geez.
Did you hear that?
I don't care if you lie like that or ask him a question.
But I hear you.
Toddy- replacing roots?
Soy, Rick enough to carry her from compassionate treatment to relationality.
And I know she's dreamin'
Yes, I know my sister well
That's the way it goes
I've told my sister all too well
Yes, I know she's dreamin'
Now do I visit her
Something she already knows
And yes, I know my brother well
And what he's keepin'
Yes, I know my brother well
He sings a different tune
I've heard it said he's queer as hell
Pray that he's in love as well
Pray on fire that's my moan
Thanks for the information
Thanks for no thanks
For the information
Cause information's got your number too
Well, thanks for the information
Thanks for no thanks
For the information
Cause information's got your number too
For the information's got your number too
Bob Walkenhorst of The Rainmakers recorded live at the Record Bar.
You can look at therainmakers.com for more.
Almost everything before that, collage-wise, was by Reverend Nor-rel Preth.
Except what was by Fernanda Nande-Lemur.
Thanks to Dr. Sinister of Radio Synesthesia at WCSB Cleveland.
This is Hour of Slack, number 1155.
For more information, see subgenius.com, if you wish.
Or look for our books at amazon.com, if you must.
And praise Bob.
I made you in my image, so the name of Frankenstein could survive.
I gave you eyes, ears, a heart, a brain, and you...