We'll be tuning in again next Sunday at 10 o'clock.
I'm going to bring you a piece of that green cheese for sure.
No trouble.
Get set, get going.
Amen.
Recording.
Everything's going fine.
No trouble.
Welcome potential initiates and remain with us for the next 30 minutes.
Bob?
The message is now part of and registered in your subconscious mind
every time you say, see, hear, or think.
What about slack?
That's your key phrase.
It will trigger the entire message without your being aware of it.
Welcome to the subgenius radio ministry hour of slack.
Sponsored by the Church of the Subgenius.
This is Reverend Ivan Stang,
sacred scribe of the First Orthodox Megafist Temple Lodge of the Church of the Subgenius.
Welcome.
I'm Pastor Buck Naked of the First Naked Church of the Subgenius.
The opinions expressed are not necessarily those of this radio station.
Before the sermon, a message concerning stops,
living avatar of slack, and saint of silence on planet Earth.
Are we controlled by secret forces?
Amen.
Almighty and everlasting bomb who came down among us to make heaven under earth,
lighten our darkness.
Oh, instrument of God, grant us thy peace.
Almighty bomb who destroyed all rebels and created angels.
Behold his glory.
Behold the truth that abides in us.
Reveal that truth unto that maker.
I reveal my inner self unto my God.
Unto my God.
Dear friends, we have returned once again to the subgenius hour of slack radio ministry.
This is Reverend Ivan Stang with Pastor Buck Naked, Dr. G. Gordon Gordon, Buddy West,
and a number of guest stars here to accept your pledges as our amazing volunteer test drive begins.
Because...
Ahem.
You can tell just what you need around these parts here in Texas,
far out away from those Sodom and Gomorrahs of New York and L.A., the pink coasts.
We need to protect that which is native to our land, friends,
such as K&ON, the non-station that's not like those others,
and it's the only one where you're...
You're gonna get the pure message of slack and the word of J.R. Bob Dobbs at all on the air in Dallas, Texas.
Right, doctors?
Yeah.
Oh, is there anyone else here on the show?
Yeah, yeah, I know.
Sing live.
Here.
Which, uh, which microphone are you on, Buck?
This one right here at the true number.
Okay.
Well, since it's all mononucleosis, I can't tell which ear it's going in.
But, friends, that's right.
All right.
The drive begins at midnight tonight, and, uh, we'll start talking about money.
You know, we love to talk about money because this is a church, a subgenius church.
Listen to that lovely harp music there.
Uh, Buck, that's beautiful.
That's Buck on his auto harp, joined by Reverend Glenn Carlson of the Super Electric.
Oh, look out!
Yeah.
That was those...
Those sounds you hear are some of the bills that come into this station.
Okay.
These guys aren't on the air for free.
They don't play ads.
And, uh, they play...
Well, you know, when you turn this station on, you don't know what you're gonna hear,
whether it's gonna be a...
Nope, it's gone.
Folks, hello, doctors?
Is there anyone else here?
Is this station completely empty?
No, you've got the microphone.
All right.
Folks, I'm just gonna have to shake into this endless box of cassettes.
Oh, yeah, everybody.
I've gotta do everything myself around here.
This is ridiculous.
I don't even know how to turn these machines off.
Look at this.
Help me.
I'll do it.
Folks, this could be some sort of a conspiracy.
Stop.
That's it.
Thank you, dear friends, for...
contributing your prayers towards the breaking of that cassette recorder.
And you see, it's things like this that...
that prove that, uh, that this station needs money
because people like us come in here and...
we can't get the machines to stop running and we just...
we start hitting...
Red Room Stang, I'd like to break in here for just a second and, uh...
Please.
During the next show, the show after Hour of Slack,
um...
we're, uh...
he's gonna play a tape and it's gonna tell exactly why...
K-N-O-N is under siege.
And, uh, the station has been, uh...
socked with some, uh...
some, uh, unusual problems that we're gonna...
let you know about, uh, from without.
This is the serious message.
Yes, this...
this is the, uh, message of...
I love it.
Right.
This is the actual, uh, pressure that, uh...
some forces within society are putting on K-N-O-N.
I don't know exactly how specific they can let you know what's going on.
The conspiracy, Buck, is never a very specific entity.
Right.
You know...
I'd like to remind our listeners that it's all one conspiracy.
That, uh, Coke and Pepsi are on the same side.
They want to take away your Slack.
They want to take away our station.
That's incredible.
They just want it all.
That's what I've been hearing.
There's apparently something very mysterious in here.
They've got two...
they've got two stations right by here now
and they want to make it three and...
I mean, what the heck?
They want it all.
They want...
it all, friends.
I think they're trying to shut us up more than they're trying to.
Abnormal!
Abnormal.
Probably better than morons.
That's what they want.
Yes!
Your time shall triumph!
Now, at last, the step-by-step process is revealed.
But only if...
you send your checks
and your lovely...
Well, what is the deal with the, uh...
the situation?
With the amazing...
Dig through the Bibles in here and the pamphlets.
Right, you send five dollars to KNON, you get their newsletter.
And, if you mention this show,
you get a free subgenius pamphlet.
Number two.
That's right.
The new one.
And, uh...
For twenty dollars, you get the bumper sticker and the newsletter.
Friends, this is an amazing bumper sticker that will bring you a great deal of trouble
from the conspiracy as soon as they see you.
So you know it's a romantic, sort of amazing thing to do.
The only thing that promises action, thrill, success in sex and business.
But only, only if you do.
Buck?
Yeah.
What do they do?
They do...
I mean...
Okay, twenty dollars, bumper sticker mailed to you.
Plus the pamphlet, right?
Subgenius pamphlet number two?
That's right.
All right, Doug, this is brand new, though.
This is not what you've already got.
This is something you haven't seen yet.
Thirty dollars, you get the bumper sticker, the pamphlet, and the t-shirt.
For forty dollars, the bumper sticker and the t-shirt will be mailed.
Or whatever.
Otherwise, I guess it's gonna walk over to your house or something.
Anyway, real important, mention Hour of Slack so we know which show you're listening to.
I don't know if that'll be...
Actually, we don't care.
We'll smell your money.
We're with you.
As long as it smells like it's for Bob.
The material may not be reproduced.
Two zero five.
Over twenty one years.
Because people like you are helping us stay on the radio.
You can't buy a miracle, but you can certainly stand behind a miracle ministry.
I'm like a bunch of...
That's what all I care about.
And you know, the only thing that can stop you is the miracle.
Keep your hands on the radio right now.
Right.
Really, now, are you guys in this cult business just for the bucks, or do you have...
And I wouldn't infer that our secondary state is antichrist, but I'm telling you that preparations
are being made, and that the very door of the day of the wrath of God is at hand, and
that if you plan to get saved, you had better do it now.
There will be a miracle within.
a day not in the too far
distant future in which
Antichrist will be revealed
and the mark of the
beast will be introduced
and people will have a number
in their hands and in their
foreheads.
Our demand for energy will be met
from our own production and our own
conservation.
Also in your
literature, I noticed connections
with aliens.
And the
god of wrath who visits
us every once in a while and talks to
we gotta drop this name in here, Bob Dobbs.
The high muckety muck.
Never behold, he cometh with clouds
and every eye shall see him.
Space vessel, identity unknown.
I could show you a flying saucer
and you'd swear it was something that I got
from Eric. You'd show me a real flying
saucer and you'd say I got it from Eric.
I give you a thousand
dollars to your religion if you can produce one
flying saucer. At least, Joe,
that is my opinion of what I think.
And I've seen a lot of
saucer people, and, uh,
but I can't talk about it, you know, because
back in the zoo.
So we just gotta
wait, you know, until 1985
and then, oh yeah, freeze those
cats in the street.
The crew of the UFO is an especially
designed robot humanoid.
Disintegrated, Captain.
Human. Come on.
Woof!
Are we not men?
Zob!
Wobbly, wobbly.
Ha, ha, ha.
Everyone makes a mistake.
Let it go, Bob.
Whoa, boy.
They say the bigger the headache, the bigger the pill, baby.
Food is galloping.
Maria, you're...
What?
What's the use of pretending?
I can't stand this anymore.
Doctor, please.
Please, doctor.
Chandler said you went over to Georgia Street to see that doctor.
Yeah, that's right, Ed.
Short visit.
Poor guy.
Pretty bad, huh?
Well, the guy's really a mess.
The beatin' it walked up to the epileptic and said,
Oh, I don't hear the music, but go, baby, go!
I hope you like that, Nod.
I hope you like that.
I try to make the audience a part of the entertainment,
and they go along with it all just great.
That chatter with the doctor is no phony bit, really.
It's just the way it happens.
You like it?
Make me take off my clothes and make me go out normal.
I have to go outside and change before I come here.
Do you love your parents?
Yeah, I love them, but they're...
In culture schools across the land,
mere infants are taught all about contraceptive techniques
and are provided with a plastic phallus in the classroom.
Well, I don't worship, Reefer.
To me, it's just another thing to do.
Hey, Jones, we just got in this African sensimedia hash.
Thought maybe you'd like to smoke some.
Our Father, who art in heaven, hallowed be thy name.
Haven't you ever done it yet?
Come on, now get up and break and smoke some, please.
I would gladly smoke some!
Orny?
Ahem.
I'm not done talking to you.
Wait.
The triple keyboard operates an echo chip.
Resonating balls made of foam.
And something that rather resembles a mercury xylophone.
I'm getting tired.
I don't know if I can keep up.
But I believe I actually enjoyed it.
To the last mutant, mutant, mutant.
That's me!
Civilized men were so frightened by talking apes.
Let it get away, doctor.
But how does one control a 400-pound gorilla?
I'm a doctor, not an animal trainer.
That thing's got the balls.
Oh, as long as my middle finger.
Oh, no!
You think the unthinkable.
This radiation is beautiful.
Yes, that is beautiful.
Please, please, please, cover your faces.
That's the doomsday bomb.
Do you know what that means?
Do you understand?
Illusions, illusions.
I'm still the admiral who pretended aboriginally he was a respectable stemming.
Great.
He was an outlaw.
Our Slack radio ministry.
Here are the numbers to call.
The old classic number, 823-7490.
Or you can try 823-8801.
823-8883.
If all numbers are busy, well, heck, we won't give that one out yet.
So 823-7490 or 823-8801 or 823-8883.
Light up the phone bags for us.
Our Slack.
We need.
Yes.
We need gifts for the pledge drive.
And we do have volunteers to take your calls.
That's right.
And not all of this money goes to the Church of the Subgenius.
In fact, none of it does.
This is all strictly to keep the station on the air so that you can hear all those other shows that I'm sure some people would rather hear.
Because this is, at times, a dangerous show to listen to if you're trying to understand exactly what's going on.
You have to listen very closely.
That's the tricky part.
Not for Joe.
Heavens are Quakers, a second said, when Bohemian lips, a third said, when he know, when hold hard a jiffy, when he is agnostic and determined to.
The next one said, when the angel of death kicks the bucket of life.
Still another said, when the wine's at wit's end.
And still another, when lovely woman stoops to conk him.
One of the littliest said, me, me said, when papa, papa at the harbour.
One of the wittiest said, when he yate hee, I blew cooken, and he's mere, he's self so sooken.
Still one said.
When you are old, I'm grey, fall full with sleep.
And still another, when we dead a walkner.
And another, when he's just only after having been semi-sized.
Another, when, yea, he hath no bananas.
And one, when those pigs, they begin now that they will, flies up into the luft.
All were wrong.
So Shem himself, the dictator, took the cake.
The correct solution being.
I'll give it up.
When he is a.
Yours to the rending of the rocks.
Sham.
Shem was a sham.
And a low sham.
And his lowness creeped out first via foodstuffs.
So low was he that he preferred Gibson's tea time salmon, tinned as inexpensive as pleasing,
to the plumpest roe heavy lax, or the friskiest par of smoked trout that ever was gaffed between Leaslip and Island Bridge.
And many was the time, he repeated in his bottle-ism, that no jungle grown pineapple ever smacked like the whoppies he shook out of Ananias's can.
And the
great things that just goes on and on and on and on and on.
That's, um, that's from Finnegan's Wake.
And it's, uh, it's a big book.
Great big thick book.
People read it.
They get lost inside of it.
And we've got special signals attached to the tapes that we play on this show that reach out and lock onto your mind.
Ha ha ha ha.
It's funny, isn't it?
This is, uh, Reverend D.K. Jones, uh, in New Jersey.
Great, great subgenius.
A song called Midnight Rambler.
I don't mean just black knights.
I mean you black-hearted men and women.
I'm Midnight Rambler.
Yes.
All Midnight Rambler's faces are not black.
What they're on is as black as midnight.
Yes.
I'm talking to you.
Hold up, men.
Yes.
And women.
You bank robbers.
Yes.
You sing, too.
And you bank robbers.
Right.
And kidnaps.
Yes.
You old, flooded men.
All right.
I'm talking to you.
And we've got some people in the church.
Yes.
See, now it's just as late as a midnight ramp.
All right.
I don't know what I'm doing.
Well, listen.
A couple of times, brother.
He got in last night.
Yes, brother.
He had him, you know, last night.
Uh-huh.
Yes.
He had him.
But you haven't told why they had him.
Oh, Mr. Bell, why did they have him out?
Well, he was in jail.
Uh-huh.
He was in jail.
Yes.
Yeah, in jail.
And now, Mr. Jordan, where's your husband?
Where's your husband?
My husband didn't get home last night.
He told me not to tell you.
Oh, well, he don't have to tell me.
I'm not holding court.
No, I'm just talking to you.
He's got to tell Jack.
And you're out to tell him what to do.
Tell him what to do.
All right.
And in the clearing, if you don't mind, he'll get six long.
Eight.
Ah, ten.
I'm talking to you midnight.
Ram.
Yeah.
Stay with me at night.
Just to rob and steal.
All right.
Some of you are so roguish.
Come on, come on.
Well, you will.
You will.
Come yourself.
Go ahead.
Inca.
Selfie.
Uh-huh.
Come on, man.
Oh, I want to fly.
You got to fly.
Uh-huh.
Oh, yeah.
Out with somebody else.
But he's got an answer for himself.
Uh-huh.
Oh, yeah.
Well, you know, he's got a good answer for himself.
Yeah.
He's got a good answer for himself.
Well, I'm here.
I'm here.
What's up, buddy?
Yeah.
Come on.
Come on us up.
We're waiting for your phone call.
Oh, we need...
Touch us through the telephone wires and pledge your money.
Remember, you don't...
The money don't go to Bob.
You can hate Bob, and you can still pledge your money.
So send it to 823-749-0.
You can hate Bob, and you'll be a good subgenius.
823-749-0.
three seven four nine oh that's right call in and two three seven four nine oh come on call us light
that sucker up just a little bit of money oh you're trying can you prove that you can part
with that which has enslaved you my friend can you reach deep into that most holy and sacred
of receptacles on your whole body that most sacred orifice your back pocket and pull out
that deepest part of your soul which is your wallet dear friends pull that wallet out and
pull out that credit card call in that that visa card number yes the and the beast computer in
belgium will take that number down and that money will go to this to this lovely i've got another
number we've just gotten a call please send us your wallet eight two three eight eight oh one
light that one up now please someone out there i know you're listening the radio ministry is
reaching into your gland your your soul is reaching into your gland and you're reaching
into your soul gland your sex gland your money gland eight two three eight eight oh one
friends light it up friends light it up how much oh yeah light that money and when it gets here
for once we won't burn it you know usually we at the church of the subgenius take your money and
burn it so a little bit of your soul smoke floats up towards heaven so the aliens in outer space
will know that earth is still worth saving but this time we'll spend the money on on uh
you
microphones and more broadcasting equipment for the station and not only that but here's the number
yes let's have eight two three eight eight oh one eight two three eight eight oh one light it up
because there's nobody else in dallas that is about to play captain
the black paper between a mirror breaks my heart
the moon frayed through dark velvet lightly apart
still softly through sunshine still softly through snow
the wild goose flies from winter breaks my heart that i can't go
energy flies from winter breaks my heart that i can't go
through a field and the sun softly melts the nothing for you
still softly through sunshine still softly through snow
the black paper between a mirror breaks my heart that i can't go
to smile that feathers don't grow their spine
they live 200 years of love
They won.
There's my heart to see the cross was turned.
There's my heart to see the highway cross the hill.
Man lived a million years and still he kills.
The black paper between a mirror
breaks my heart to see the cross was turned.
But I can't go.
Steal softly through sunshine.
Steal softly through snow.
Everyone, rise for the anthem.
Dallas, Fort Worth, Arlington, Mesquite,
Lancaster, Bland Prairie.
And speaking of Grand Prairie,
Ah, yes, thank you, Michael Wallace.
For making the first pledge of the K-N-O-N,
some genius pledge drive.
Well, you've got to call 823-7490
and help us continue to keep our slack
and K-N-O-N in general on the air.
823-7490.
Ah, yes, dear friends.
Once again, reach down deep and call us up.
Offer your credit card number
or set up this amazing bank draft system
where they can pull money out of your checking account
every month without you ever having to think about it
or maybe ever even knowing about it
if you're drunk enough when you pledge in
and you forget that you ever even did it.
823-8801 is our second phone number.
823-8801.
We may have a second pledge right now.
Call and pledge now.
823-8801.
If this is how he wants to go out,
I don't have a way to say it
except that I just went out of bullshit.
Yeah.
0-2-3-0-2-3-4
Well, I told you
And I told those who got through
But I'm not your big nigga
Not your big nigga
I like a bunch of
And I might like a good birthday
But I'm not your big nigga
Not your
When you go on a picnic
Don't forget to eat
And I'll be right back
I'd love to go on a picnic
But I'm not a
No, I'm not a
I'm not a
But there was a giant female subgenius here
to hold the show for us
and to squeeze out the
squeeze out the
Caller, you're
You give off a good phone
Hi kids, welcome to Subgenius USA
We don't care if you're single, double, triple
Dial me again
Twin tuple, sex tuple, septuple, hop tuple
Moon tuple, vesituple, or
Vesituple
Now we can't have this kind of
This is a special message
If you can't say those kind of things on the radio
That's right
Don't waste any time
We don't know what radio is
We know we're sexist pigs
We know we're all screwed up
And messed up and everything
We'd be a lot better off
If you were here to tell us what to do
But you can't use those words on the radio
You don't want to use those words on the radio
You can call us up and tell us what to do
If you're stupid or anything
Listen to the music
Smell it
You hate our parents
You'd like to see us gas
And if you're lebanese
No oozing allowed
No
Until someone comes down here
And does it for themselves
What a silly show
Yes, if you think you've got a better show
You'd bring it to the air right now
Throw in the night worm of the doctor
You'd come right down here to
I was going to say KGO
But we're not allowed to use those colors
Or KPFA
Or any of those
FAT
No, we can't talk about those old stations
KPOI
KOL
I don't know
Just write a letter to the station
And completely say
Dr. Hal said the bad words
Yeah
All I do is write a letter
And say anything
And some of those other guys helped
And whoever they are
What are you talking about?
They should be thrown off the radio
Because they play stuff like this all the time
Hey, I'm clean
I'm innocent
They're trained operators
I demand a fair trial
That's right
They play those old records
They play old records
And then make trial by tape
All over themselves
Repent
Well, I told you and I don't know you
It got through
But I'm not your pink ape
What?
Not your pink ape
I live in a luncheon
Where the night is my life
I get to work
That's not your pink ape
When you go on a picnic
Don't forget the ape
I love to go on a picnic
I don't want to go on a picnic
I am not an ape
No, I am not an ape
Not me
I should have said not I
I told you that I never
I never could not
Could not
Not eaten
Gone
Your pink ape
Well, gone
Well, that makes a lot of sense
Pinky, pink
Ha, ha, ha, ha
Oh, yes, dear friends
That was, uh
That's a
That band
The guy that does that
Puts out a magazine
That is quotes from senile people
He works in an old folks home
And he records their wisdom
And puts out a magazine
of it. He also has this band called
the Duplex Players, which
we just played. Picnic
Ape. He records these guys and then
uses them
as lyrics to these beautiful songs.
You see, they don't let anything go to
waste in America today.
Ah, yes.
Folks, call in with that pledge.
823-7490.
You've got to do it.
Otherwise, you'll never
hear this.
Ah, yes.
That's very interesting.
That's not interesting at all.
Ah, yes.
That's very, very interesting.
That's not interesting at all.
Ah, yes.
No, no, no.
That's very interesting.
Ah, yes.
Very, very interesting.
That's very, very interesting.
I think we're very close to isolating the molecules.
Still there are mice.
Look what's coming out of that hole in the ground.
A little bullfrog.
That's very, very interesting.
Do anything musical.
Okay, let's run that testing.
Very interesting, folks.
Very interesting.
Okay, friends, now the board's just not lighting up.
Now we need to give these numbers out again, and let's have those pledges.
823-7490, friends.
823-8801 and 823-888.
823-888.
Remember, you're not just pledging it for Bob.
You're pledging it for the station that keeps Bob on the air.
So let's have that board light up.
Let's have them pledges.
Those $1 pledges.
Those $50 pledges.
Those $100 pledges.
Those $10,000 pledges.
Folks, we only need a few of them.
We only need 10 pounds of $100 bills to keep this station going, friends.
We only need six $10,000 pledges.
But I'll tell you what.
It is getting very serious, and it involves legal situations.
And we're not just asking you to give money for Bob.
In fact, this is one of the few times when we're asking you to give Bob's money to somebody else.
That's right, friends.
And that's usually against our religion.
That's how serious the situation is.
And this, well, you know what happens when this station goes off.
If this station were to go off the air, and these are not hollow threats.
And here's Buck Naked with a special offer, friends.
A hot offer for you people to pledge your money.
Okay.
Tell you what.
What?
Do it now.
I want a $20 pledge, and you get a free button.
JR Bob Dobbs.
Yay!
And I want you to call this special number.
823-8883.
Call it in within the next five minutes, and you get that free button with your $20 pledge.
And all the other stuff you get.
What else do they get?
They get a newsletter, the KNON newsletter, which is actually not a...
Not the drab little rag that you would think.
It's insane.
I've seen it.
It's amazing.
It's entertaining.
Yes.
It's actually something you can keep.
And it's yours.
It's yours forever.
Forever.
They get pamphlet number two, right?
Right.
They get subgenius pamphlet number two.
We've got to bring down a whole bunch of the brand new ones.
That's why Buck Naked's special handcrafted church buttons, friends, for the first $20
pledge.
Face of Bob at 823-8883.
That's special offer pledge.
Call it in now.
Light that signal.
Free back rides every day.
Howdy, friends.
I'm Lord Jim Cravington for Medieval Motors, your friendly truck stop and transportation
in the diet of worms.
Friends, whether you're in the body or out to lunch, we've got the Gryphon, the Minotaur,
or the sporty little camel leopard to suit your imaginary travel needs.
And gosh, what can I say about these little guys?
Yes, it's your all new cardboard Vampirettes, the economy transport that's got them all
guessing on the other side.
Well, we've got continents and peninsulas of New England, and we've got the
best of
seen yeah.
So get your ass in gear and your oxen in here so as we can trade indulgences and get you on your back
Now we're just a painful mile off the freeway of lost hope at the intersection of down and out avenues in the citadel of the angel
How you doing?
A lot of the good old boys are here tonight. We'd like to welcome you down to the television mission
Don't forget if all you can do is sit at home then try to keep yourselves awake
And dial the phone
Call in for pledges. Yes, we have a lot of our special
beauties
Answering the phones this evening and
Best thing you can do is dial this number that you see on your screen
As quickly as you can with a contribution to the television mission. Don't forget to call in a pledge
Talk about Jesus. Well, you never know who's gonna be here this evening
Yes, well, it's one. I know you are son
I know it's one of the one of the real positive qualities of the television mission is we just never know
Who's going to drop by?
I mean, it's a lot of folks have been the band is here
The man is getting set up the band is ready. The band is ready
And I'm here to tell you that it's time ladies and gentlemen
I want you to hold down your applause as long as you can because it's time you heard from red green back in the blue boys
Don't forget to call the numbers on your screen
The number is not on your screen
The number is on your speaker and that number to call is eight two three seven four nine
Oh, and if you don't call something very very terrible could happen not only to to you and to the airwaves of Dallas
But through all the life force which covers this great green globe
This station were to have any worse problems than it already does
It could be pretty bad friends. It could be as bad as what happened tonight
Thank you to Danny Ferguson of Arlington for your pledge to the subgenius radio radio ministry hour of
slack kno n 90.9
Listen
I
Oh
In the last powerful days of another way of life,
when everything happened in cars,
when sullen, desperate men would do anything for a tank full,
in the troubled years of the Hundred Year Gas War
and the terrible food insurrection,
when armies mixed mustard and gas and relished war,
in those frightened times,
private citizens often had to do the terrifying work of real police,
apprehending criminals and solving tricky moral problems.
They had private eyes, but public fists,
full tanks, but clean consciences,
and tonight's story is only typical.
Car Hook.
Starring Dirk Yost.
Ogre as Dick Private.
Private Dick.
Tonight's chilling story.
Roller Maidens from Outer Space.
Saturday morning.
I'd just locked myself out of the office for a cool weekend
and promised to be gin-soaked and hand-rubbed.
At least, that's what I figured she'd meant when she said,
let's get drunk and refinish my furniture.
Anyway, it was the way she said it, you know.
Real husky, like a lead dog in a snow job.
And I wasn't about to be left out in the cold.
Damn nation.
Ah, well.
I figured it wouldn't hurt just to answer it.
A private Seamus is always hungry.
I hadn't been exactly flush,
and this might just be the ace in the closet
that put some pizza in the pantry.
Go ahead, something said to me.
Answer it, she'll wait.
So I did.
Only to wind up holding the anchovies
in more ways than one.
Dick Private, private detective.
Uh, Mr. Private.
That's right, pal.
My name is Regular Boynton.
My wife, uh, Ethel and I have been opposites.
I've been at you for many years on, uh, another network.
Oh, yeah.
The Ethel and Regular Show, I've heard of you.
What's the matter?
Swallow your car keys?
Uh, no.
Lock yourself out of the house?
No.
Want to know how to make an attractive bookend
out of a shoebox and a brick?
No, uh, nothing that exciting,
but, uh, look, look, look, you've got to get over here.
Well.
Right away.
Uh.
You're just a couple of channels away.
Uh, you can make it.
Nobody ever made it before.
No, come on.
It's really weird over here.
Well, it ain't no Swiss picnic over here, pal.
You don't under, uh, under, uh, understand.
It's, it's terrifying.
Uh, nothing is normal.
Wow.
We all seem to be, uh, uh, dreaming the same dreams.
Wow, that's terrific.
And there's all these strange balls of light in our neighborhood.
Hold it.
Glad to.
Now hold it up to the light.
Oh, okay.
You was right.
This was serious.
This is serious.
This is extremely serious.
I've never seen so much light on these boards lighting up.
God, these amiable sims.
Don't act.
It's not the right kind of light.
We want that green light.
We want that light from that money coming in.
That's what we want.
Uh, yes, we want to, we want to friends.
You don't know the purity of the, of a 10,000 pound stack of dollar bills or the
right savage horror of not having this station on the air.
So let's try again.
The numbers are 8, 2, 3, 7, 4, 9 0 8 2 3 8 8 0 1 and 8 2 3 8 8 8 3.
And folks.
You get the newsletter, the KNON newsletter, the bumper stickers, the free subgenius pamphlet
number two.
That's right.
Now you subgenius members out there that are wondering where's my pamphlet number two.
You'll get yours in the mail anyway, but Oh, ye unsaved out there.
Ye unsaved folks that could be, if you could, but if you could, but pay for this radio station
that you're listening to and enjoying right now.
That's right.
You pay for all the rest of them.
By putting up with the commercials.
That's right.
You put up, you pay for all the rest of them by hearing the same thing over and over and
over again.
Things much worse than pledge drives.
Yes.
There are worse things than pledge drives.
Friends.
We'd like to thank Sherry Williamson Fort Worth for calling her pledge into the hour
of slack.
Thank you, Sherry.
And you people out there that haven't called yet those numbers one more time.
8 2 3 7 4 9 0 8 2 3 8 8 0 1.
And 8 2 3 8 8 8 3.
Just put your finger on the little button and push it.
Hey.
the air in order to in order to ask you to pledge your money to knon friends it's got to happen
sooner or later or we'll never stop this show if you don't send money to knon we won't we won't get
out of this station the next show won't come on we'll keep talking in here until the until the
the uh the the station disappears shriveled up by the conspiracy which will sap away
the you can stop that the slack friends all you've got to do is give a little bit reach into
that checkbook shove your hand into that back pocket get out those wallet stretchers and see
how far you can stretch that money into the direction of knon friends cough it up cough it up
eight two three seven four nine oh eight two three eight eight oh one cough it up cough it up
it was still a little bit uh when uh when he talked about it he said this is up in the east
and i i've got
some super uh vision anyway i walked out of the door and looked up in the east and saw this
bright star he didn't know what the bar snow didn't know whether it was a star or a planet or
a weather balloon or what it was and i walked out there in the backyard in my pajamas i looked
this thing and i saw some people coming out of that damn thing boy
boy
me you saw this thing was it close by no it was way out there in the east in the sky
well you could see you could see people in it yeah he said he had supervision out of that thing
the aliens of ufo are energy manipulators
i thought there's you know there is a lot of talk about flying saucers
and i want you to meet a man this evening that's actually seen you some 300 flying saucers and your name is
the man
it's not focusing on the pandemic it's on planet earth
so the club might be on the field man cannot participate in long space expeditions nasa has scientifically verified and
kept very quiet the fact that the unstoppable cosmic rays to which every astronaut has been exposed destroys brain cells at the rate of
one percent every man has disappeared from the planet her Hindu survive and be a puny parts of the brain and every single voice hat that way so we find common truth and very much
iso
every four months.
Since the neurons of the adult human brain do not...
A space expedition represents...
...and here's Master Buck naked with a couple of new ones.
Mark Shopey. Thanks a lot, guy.
And Sherry Williams. Williamson. Yes, of Fort Worth.
A big help. Okay.
You people who want to talk about slack, friends...
...there's not going to be any slack tonight until you send that money in.
You'll get that slack the minute you write the check.
You'll feel it flowing up through your ballpoint pen into your fingertips.
This whole show is to give you a beatific vision of slack, friends...
...and I think that, you know, you're going to have to realize...
...that the luck plane to slant our way is going to have to have a little...
A little weight on one end of the slack plane, friends.
A little pile of...
...$10 and $20 bills stacked up here and there can shift that plane.
Yes, indeed.
Hey, Doc, you ain't got nothing coming over your TV.
Hey, hey, hey.
Because I love you.
Forever.
And I love you.
You.
The past will change.
The revolution.
You.
A believer.
The revolution.
You.
Me.
Hans.
The prophet.
Me.
Hans.
My name is Hans.
I am the prophet.
He is my lover.
He is the one and the chosen one.
The one and the chosen one.
He is my chosen one.
Now the other and the excluded one.
He is myarios
Look at the worldstCmoury
CheckusBlog.fm
Where men are meant to be.
Oh, Hans.
Hans, you are my lover.
My daughter's there.
Something wrong with you.
You.
The path will change.
You are revolution.
In product, revolution.
Hand curtains.
Your daddy cried all night and made you cry all night and undersellow and a bunch of
It's telles me...
Listen to your mama.
Sweet dreams.
The red duck is back!
Something new is limited.
Something limited.
In the minds of the Russians, many Russians.
The red duck is back!
Forget him. Forget him.
But the real man, to the bed rest.
The bed rest.
Gone he was, he out.
The red duck is back!
Down here.
Down there.
I can't keep talking to anything.
I want to, but I don't.
I don't know.
The wind blows.
Does everybody know that?
The waves and the bybeds, the sht, they say.
We were speaking in tongues.
Tongues.
That's a revolution going on.
Yes, friends.
Bob does love you, he'll love you more
if you'll join that pledge drive right now.
Dr. Stank, would you please give out the numbers?
Yes friends, that's
823-7490.
And get your pencil, because there's another one.
8-2-3-8-8-0-1.
That's right.
If you want to hear any more bizarre, demonic-sounding music from the airwaves
or the inspirational, beautiful, classical songs of Bob White,
you have to call 8-2-3-8-8-0-1.
8-2-3-8-8-8-3, doctor.
Or doctor.
Doctor.
8-2-1-8-5-7-9.
But especially 8-2-3-7-4-9-0.
Call in and deposit that earthly check.
That offering.
That pledge.
All you have to do is promise it right now.
It's a non-pledge.
You can't lose.
You're pledging it to K-N-O-N.
It's a non-pledge.
Ah, yes, friends.
And it's so sad, because our time is already running out.
When we hear that music at the end of these shows.
Doctor, we've got a $40 pledge we have to give credit for.
Oh, yes.
Ah, yes.
As Wendell Scott of Dallas, thank you so much.
And may slack flow through your body.
May slack drip down your spine and out every side of your pants.
Oh, friends.
We have to leave you for the next religion, and so.
And so, as we sign off, once again, friends, send that money to K-N-O-N
and to the Church of the Subgenius for the Home for Slackless Children,
because that money keeps those we hate starving to death.
And get your pencils.
Get your pencils ready, because we'll be reading our address for information here
coming up at the end of the broadcast.
Oh, yes, this has been Reverend Ivan Stang with G. Gordon Gordon,
Pastor Buck Naked, Buddy West, and the folks who will be taking over the show next week,
Batman himself.
Ah, yes.
To play the amazing tapes.
Oh, friends.
And that's the Church of the Subgenius P.O. Box 1403.
Oh, yes.
Dallas, Texas 75214.
Yeah, or call 823-7490.
823-8801.
Oh, yes, dear friends.
It's so beautiful to see that phone line light up.
Ah, there it is.
Yes, more $40 pledges.
More paper slack.
Ah, yes.
Paper slack.
We all need some paper slack.
Paper slack, friends.
Slack in the face of the hideous conspiracy that tries to shut down anything that tries
to talk about the things that they don't want anyone to talk about.
Oh, stop them.
That's what they try to do.
Ah, thank you, dear friends.
Thank you, dear friends.
Drinking Budweiser.
Watching Bob on TV.
Oh, swallowing red man.
The day my coon dog died.
Reading the pamphlet.
Over and over again.
Eyes drinking Budweiser.
Oh, birdie.
Bob was on TV.
The day that Uncle could kick by a mule.
I was with Cousin Junior.
The DNA backfired.
I was drunk.
I was lonely.
I was plastered.
I was drinking Budweiser.
And Bob was on TV.
Drinking Budweiser.
Watching Bob on TV.
Swallowing red man.
The day my coon dog died.
Reading the pamphlet.
the pamphlet
over and over
again
I was
drinking Budweiser
and Bob was on TV
I was drinking
Budweiser
and Bob was on TV
Do the light