Radio Band Home
74.
What?
Is the year that they are now planning for sex on the street in every major city from coast to coast.
And now prepare to suffer indescribable.
Torment.
Another Bob Hope special?
Worse.
Beyond these doors is an agony worse than all of us.
You will remain in here for eternity listening to...
The Soul Genius.
How wonderful.
And the rose nip bubble people took him in to their own loins, didn't they?
Or was it more like a pork factory?
Come on, we're going to be doing a big revival this weekend.
That's right, Saturday night.
We're talking about walking on the wild side.
I don't have to worry about talking about things.
I want to see that audience walk on the wild side.
How wild can we get?
We're up on a stage, right?
They're going to let you down.
Whatever we do is going to be kind of fake just because of that.
But what you do in the audience, well, that's real, baby.
But I'm afraid you guys, you know, you can give them your esophagus, your pork loins, your infested eyeballs.
You can give them everything you've got, and they're still going to sit there with one hand folded under their rump
and the other one waving at some person they know at the other side of the bike.
There's only one political solution.
I'm offering. I'm not offering, friends.
I'm offering.
Bob Lovett, the cheerful giver.
Let's see what's in this.
Okay.
It's real.
My God, it's a real $5 bill.
Praise Bob.
Praise Bob with a $5 bill.
All right.
Friends, we're going to bring this divine land right.
We're going to open this divine land right, friends,
because we're going to take this symbol of the conspiracies hold over you,
and we're going to burn this motherfucker on Mother's Day.
Yeah, it's on Mother's Day, friends.
And as the smoke that just climbs on a bill rises up to heaven,
the aliens know that there's still something down here worth saving.
That's great.
It starts with a handshake.
Exits UFO's outer space.
J.R. Dobbs is not afraid.
He is the eye of a hurricane.
Watch your money.
Pink, serve their own needs.
Yeti, serve your own needs.
Feeding on a purse with workday strength.
End times are close at hand.
Uber woman, over man.
Liar in a fire representing all we hate.
With a government for hire and a combat site.
The best is left of genie in a hurry with a con breathing down their neck.
Group by group, normals falsified, full of farts.
Look at that love playing.
Fine.
Then.
Oh, oh, oh, no.
Population, they don't know.
Save yourself, serve yourself.
Pink, serve their own need.
Yeti, serve your own need.
Time to plunge your own seed.
Yeti with a rupture in the rubber.
And the right wing super slack maniac.
Slammed by bright light.
Feeling pretty psyched.
It's the end of the world as we know it.
The ball feels fine.
July 5th, X-Day.
Cluster chefs are on their way.
Quit your job.
Keep your slack.
Jared, I've got your back.
Hail Connie.
Hail Bob.
On your knees, self-righteous mob.
Give it up.
Give it in.
Find yourself a Yeti kid.
New religion radio.
Help.
Hope.
Gonna blow.
Pay to find out what you know.
Pass the pipe.
Take a trick.
I'm telling you, this is my joke.
Spirits see, steer clear.
Turn them in.
I'm gonna lie.
Offer me solutions and you offer me alternatives.
And I decline.
It's the end of the world as we know it.
But I feel fine.
It's the end of the world.
The end of the world as we know it
It's the end of the world as we know it
And Bob feels fine
The other and other, chunch on Mars
Immortals living, fiend bars
Yeti driving, fast cars bang
Reverend Ivan stank
Jesus Christ and Princess Wee
Smoking, frobbing, so do we
Reverend Susie, such a floozy
Dr. Pesoff stank
And one more time, I know you can
Antichristian, Reverend Geo
Doctor's getting right
Right!
It's the end of the world as we know it
And Bob feels fine
Unbelievable, dear friends.
This is Saint Anne and Helena Handbasket.
From their new CD, friends, Saint Anne and Helena did that live, actually, at the Euclid Tavern DeVival here in Cleveland on May 12th,
from which we brought home many excellent recordings, especially of Einstein's Secret Orchestra, friends.
So this is going to be an ESO and Saint Anne and Helena Handbasket show.
And wait until you hear the song I'll play later, The Ultimate Bob.
The ultimate Bobby song.
Friends, if you need more information about Saint Anne CDs and so forth, check out the website of Ministry of Truth.
That's minitru.org, spelled M-I-N-I-T-R-U, no E, minitru.org, friends.
But now, back to that actual DeVival in progress, friends.
Imagine the huge carved poster.
The pulpit made by Ed Strange.
And the giant dog's head painted by Jesus.
And the strange odours of the spice in the air.
Ah, yes, back to that actual DeVival in progress now.
There were times when I thought about it, but I wondered if maybe the bands in some genius DeVivals were the kind that only I liked.
But the Free Times had a music poll.
They were where everybody in Cleveland could go.
On what they thought the best bands were.
And you know who the best god damn instrumental electronic band in the world was?
In all of Cleveland?
It's Einstein's Secret Dumbstand Organ.
Einstein's Secret Organ.
Playing the song, Helmets.
Oh.
Do what you want!
We don't try to introduce yourself, we already know your name
We can follow you around and see your mind
Don't worry you're not enslaimed
People gone, people gone
Lost in the dumpsters of life
One damn thing is for sure tonight
My daughter's gonna do you right
We only wanna fuck you
Broken is my head
But what's loving you
Nature's hiding
On your head
Please don't try to introduce yourself
I already know your name
I've written all of you shit to your life
Fuck you, fuck you, fuck you
Please don't try to understand
Your mind is much too late
Cause never an island slayers coming along
It wants to fuck with your brain
These beaches of the edge of the island
What's troubling you?
Nature's hiding
Let's do it now
We gonna fuck you
Cotton Barack
Here's a shot from thejs
So I'll give you mine
wit' me
Go on
But it's only real
Than you feel
I said, I'll give you mine
When it's time I'll give you mine
You better think about it
Thought you could stop
If you're a wild cock
Like a little cock
And you close the door
When you know that he's gonna fuck you
Get out pretty quick ним
Oh, yes, my girl
What's up in you?
Here's the nature of my day
Oh, yes, my girl
What's up in you?
Here's the nature of my day
Waste ball
Einstein's Secret Orchestra!
We'll be back with a whole set of music for you, right after this man is done filling her head with evil thoughts.
Listen, people.
With no spiritual foundation on you.
I've got a secret I feel compelled to.
Come out and tell.
Dave, what do you have to tell them?
I'm so sorry for the last seven months.
I know things haven't been good with King Rupert in charge of the material universe and all the punishment.
It's time to tell them, Dave.
You mean about me actually being Satan?
After all these years, tonight's the night.
I'm going to come out of the closet tonight.
I'm a celibate heterosexual.
Oh, I thought you were going to say you were Satan, and I was surprised at that.
Oh, you thought?
No, I didn't think you were Satan.
I thought you were like the least likely suspect for Satanism of anybody I could think of.
You mean non-Satanism.
You'd be a crappy Satan.
Satan-hood.
You wouldn't be a very good Satanist or a very good Satan.
By whose standards, Dane?
Well, by the standards of any cruel, hate-filled...
Of any Christian, right-minded, right-thinking individual with a pair of blue pants and a pair of buttocks that stick out as far as...
That's true.
It may be from their point of view, Satan is an evil being.
But whereas, actually, Lucifer, the bringer of light...
Oh, not in our relationship.
...might be looked at as the...
The pitiful fool who had his liver eaten out like Prometheus.
Well, the idiot.
The light bringer.
Who gave the monkeys the instruction book, and look what happened.
No, I'm not shaking.
I don't know where that was going, but it didn't go very far.
No, I...
I hope not, anyway, you know, because that would be terrible, wouldn't it?
If you woke up and...
You thought you were the least likely candidate.
Yeah.
Chaz is considering the idea right now.
He thought he was the least likely candidate, but he's wondering, like, hmm...
I can see how Chaz could be Satan.
A form of Satan.
Yeah, some kind of a Satan, because he's a rock and roll...
No, it's because you're hallucinating the star on the back of his shirt.
I've been to the crossroads.
Yeah, he's been to the crossroads.
Oh, you made your deal, huh?
He jumps around in rock and roll shows.
I want nimble fingers, Lord Satan.
I want nimble fingers, and it looks like Elvis and Arthur and Morrison.
Yes, and I want a brain that's much bigger than the brain I have right now.
I want a 356-pound brain, a pound for each day of the week.
I hear you. I hear you.
But, you know, Dave, no offense, but even after hearing you sing Sympathy for the Devil, I still...
You kind of wanted to go to a convent or a cloister or something and be by yourself,
and contemplate the Lord.
I didn't feel real delivered by Satan.
I didn't feel satanic.
I didn't feel, you know, it's like, yeah, I already know your name.
I thought you felt like old schmuck Jehovah One was still in charge,
and you were disappointed that Chaz and I could not raise the devil that night,
like we tried at the crossroads.
Yeah, I was hoping for a change, man.
It's just been Bob and Jehovah One and Jesus and all them.
The spirit of Robert Johnson did take over Johnny for a short while there,
during the lead solo of the song.
You think so?
I think that he probably felt like...
He was funky. He did a great job, I must say.
I was very impressed.
Both Sympathy for the Devil and Bang-a-Gong, Petkovic did a great job.
Especially for a man who, you know, spends much...
The whole band did, dressing like a woman.
Michelle's solos were kickin' butt.
Yeah, yeah.
Everything was kickin' butt.
And my guitar was kickin' butt, too.
Except Dave's butt and my foot.
Yeah, Dave's butt.
My foot wasn't...
Dave's butt was not being kicked.
My foot was coming out of your butt in the form of a little notchy goose step.
Right, Dave's butt was kind of more like almost kickin' my feet.
It was just one of those back-ass words things.
The Peckerwoods used to gather down by the river there,
start a little fire and drink some Jack Daniels.
And they shaved their legs.
One by one, each and every one of them.
Each and every man would take out first a left calf,
and then shave it as smooth as a baby's ass.
Then the right one.
But they do the knees last.
They do the knees very last.
Because that was the erotic part.
And then their brand-new militia suits.
Their beautiful camo jackets and their PX-763-49s and guns.
Oh, I can't remember those catalog numbers.
I just know they looked real good.
The guns, oh, man.
I had a gun, Gazzy.
It got blue and steely.
The red, white, and blue of somebody's idea of it.
Steely-eyed.
The, uh, rocket man.
The blue steel.
That's what got you going, wasn't it?
Yeah.
Steely-eyed rocket man.
And the grease on the blue.
The gun down the barrel.
The gun grease.
The gun grease in the barrel.
Better hurry up, Abner.
Sweep a little faster.
Mr. Dobbs will be here any minute now.
Doggy's Lama already swept the store out twice this morning.
Ain't nothing more.
They're sweep out.
Well, we want the place to look nice and clean for Mr. Dobbs.
We want to make a good impression on him.
Yeah, I know.
Hurry up and get that done,
then put a couple more chairs around the table in the library there.
Chairs?
What do you want them for?
I suppose we can all sit around the table
and have a regular business meeting.
Oh.
Board of director stuff.
Uh-huh.
Then I'm going to run this right
and show Mr. Dobbs I'm a big executive and all that stuff.
Well?
Uh, Mouse here, you done drawing the drawings?
Yes, sir.
The plans are all ready to show Mr. Dobbs.
Mr. Dobbs, Lama.
Well, good.
Hurry up, Abner.
Get them chairs put around.
I'm getting to it.
Doggy's, I don't see why we got to make such a fuss
over this Mr. Dobbs fella.
Abner, don't you understand?
He's a big, famous building contractor
and he's donating his services
just to help us build a wonderful world of park mans.
So the least we can do is to be nice to him
and cooperate with him.
I say put that big chair at the end there.
That's where I'll sit.
Uh-huh.
Lama, you sure that this just ain't a big deal?
It ain't some trick of Squire's
to get that $10,000 away from us?
Oh, of course not.
That's ridiculous.
You're just suspicious, Abner.
I am.
This Dobbs wouldn't get himself mixed up
in some such a scheme as that.
Well, I hope not.
Don't forget, he's a rich retard fella.
Why, he built the Empire State Building.
Don't forget that.
Yeah, but I've been thinking about
what Squire said about us having to
turn the money over to Mr. Dobbs.
That don't sound exactly right to me.
Well, that's just a usual.
Business customer, Abner.
Yes, huh?
Now, don't forget, Abner.
I want both you and Mousy to try to act dignified.
Sort of keep an eye on Mr. Dobbs
and try to be like him.
Oh, well, don't worry.
Mind out, mind out.
Here they come.
Well, howdy, Squire.
Come on in.
Yes, yes.
Thank you.
Gentlemen, gentlemen.
Well, I want you to meet my good friend
and old school chum,
Gregory W. W. Dobbs.
Uh, Mr. Dobbs, this is Mr. Edwards here.
How do you do, Mr. Dobbs?
Good job.
Well, well, glad to know you.
Glad to know you, glad to know you.
And this is Mr. Peabody.
Yeah, Peabody.
Glad to know you.
Howdy, Mr. Dobbs.
Oh, yes, now.
And this is...
Who is this fair young god
coming to the house up there?
Is that you, now, Doctor Pooh?
Yes, it is you, Mr. Dobbs.
Right.
Oh, yeah.
My name is Chopper.
Your name's Dobbs, notOL.
I'm your host at the Goistor.
See you next time!
Bye!
I'm the god of hellfire.
I got a bullfire.
Deep 13 by Lamprey Systems.
Actually, that's excerpts from Deep 13.
Deep 13. Lamprey Systems posted that on alt.binaries.slack.
And in fact, this background music is also by Lamprey Systems.
Their previous CD, Electroshock Treatment.
And friends, we heard, of course, some WCSB Cleveland ESO Swamp Radio live with yours truly, Reverend Ivan Stang, producer and show commander Chaz and lonesome cowboy Dave.
In fact, let's hear it.
Let's hear their band live, dear friends, live at the Euclid Tavern, the Bible.
Some people believe that sex, sex, sex can kill the dog.
They know better, better things can kill the dog than a bumping, jumping table or a slamming bed and strange noises at three o'clock in Eurythra.
It's true.
It's time for mom and dad to come back home and make me Peter's money and challenge them, which is the way it always has been.
Ha, ha, ha.
Oh, my God.
Oh.
I don't deserve to die
I don't deserve this abuse
So please just stay a while
We're gonna break our shield
I'm too late, too wild
I'm standing in white light
I had no clue to see me through
So please just stay for the night
We're gonna break our shield
Yes, Dr. Forskin
Now I'm off in even heaven
And I am lost
I was working the graveyard shift
late one Sunday night
Keeping a close eye on the backbeat
Making sure everything was uptight
I was keeping a close eye on the former 09
Making sure those trains never ran on time
I looked off in the distance and what did I see?
Looked like one solitary headlight coming after me
Come and take me away
One solitary headlight
What can you break our shield?
What can you bring on shield?
Oh, great angel, you don't know
The hand that holds you up is the hand that holds you down
Holds you down
The hand that lifts you is the hand that holds you
What can a grave do you have blind to know in heaven?
Into Bob's eyes
Make them see the way the pipe
Hovers just outside the deep
Make them look
And they will see
They will finally see
Is it all a lie?
I thought of all the books
And papers that I'd read
I thought of Arnold Palmer
And his bleeding head
I thought of all my brethren
And rants that they'd shared
I thought of all these things
And wondered if I cared
I pondered for a while
I pondered through the night
By the next morning
I decided they were right
We got France elections in a white array
Chaine de Beauvau, Pauvou, Manger
Ring in the news cause I'm country Mike
Use a microphone like Shazam, use tight
The party people scream
Ring, ring, sing, ring
Cause I got a remote for my big day
Ring in the news cause I'm country Mike
I felt so relieved
It really was a rush
I am so happy
That I'm a subgenius
Tired of playing normal
And following the herd
I awoke the next day
To see the world
To go and spread the word
The people that I talked to
They acted all afraid
They won't even listen
Unless they're getting paid
I really do hate them
These things of which I speak
They pointed and they laughed
They said I was a freak
Freak, freak, freak, freak, freak, freak
Tick-tock, so socialized
Open up your ears and clean out your heart
Who in the world do you want to fight?
It's against the system we should unite
Fight, fight, fight, fight
Now I sit here thinking
Of everything I've said
I really am a Bobby
My face is turning red
I thought I was finished
I wondered what to do
Ready to give it up
I didn't have a clue
Then it all came to me
I really should have known
There are so many like me
I'm really not alone
I found others like me
With whom I could converse
One day the subgenius
Will rule this universe
Freak, freak, freak, freak, freak
Yes, I am a Bobby
I don't care if it's true
There's nothing you can do
I don't care if you like me
It means nothing to me
Bobbies are here to stay
And someday you will see
I spent my thirty bucks
I've got my minister's card
I'm a deep pay member
And it wasn't all that hard
I'll start my own ministry
And it will be the first
Bobbies are not so bad
We really are not cursed
Subgenius
So now you know my story
There's nothing I've left out
I try to tell the truth
Of what it's all about
Yes, I am a Bobby
And proud to say it so
And a slack-billed dynamo
I am a true Yeti
And yes, it makes me proud
I am a subgenius
And I'll say it out loud
I don't care much for paint
And the things that they say
The church of the subgenius
Will soon have its day
With the
They'll say goodbye
saying
every day
he'd run
to the
water
from the
busy
street
he
said
a word
but
everybody
heard
there was
something
in his
face
only
in his
good
mind
he
drank
his
morning
coffee
he
got
the
oil
from
his
chin
he
handled
his
newcomer
at
the
but
he
said
told
the
truth
and
he
called
his
very
I hate you!
Oh, that's a good question.
Why don't I answer it for you?
One, two, three, four!
How did you know?
Once I had a son of that
I let them starve to death
It was a funny little monkey
And a big white Easter bunny
And that man had a few ages
And sometimes it raged
I turned them upside down
I dragged my monkey all around
That's some serious funky dragging for those of you who care to drag that funky around.
For those of you who'd like to drag something drier around.
Lately I've been reading the kind of magazines that normal people read.
Princess Wee was bringing them home from work.
Magazines such as this!
W!
Or perhaps some of you have seen a magazine for men called GQ.
Gentleman's Portrait.
Magazines for those who want, who actually want to be more normal.
Who in fact want to be more normal than normal.
More normal.
More normal than normal.
That's their motto.
Just think of that, friends.
And I guess I've been hiding in my little styrofoam tower or my adobe tower for a little too long.
Because I had not realized how bad it has gotten.
As I perused these magazines, I was shocked.
I was absolutely appalled.
I was shedding my britches in horror at the intense.
The pinkness.
The pinkness of this shit.
It's gotten worse than I ever imagined.
These huge ads.
This luscious photography.
These highly paid writers.
And it's all an intense celebration of total pinkness.
This is the most cowardly waste of fucking goddamn money I've ever seen in my life.
And I would love to burn it, but it's too goddamn big.
They are proud to be that fucking normal.
They are proud to be trying to be just like each other.
Luxuriantly pink, friends.
My God, the trouble they go to just to be upper normal.
And my friends, when I look at that magazine, and I look at that GQ,
I am so goddamn glad.
To be a weirdo.
And I am so fucking thankful to the slack of Bob Dobbs and the retardation of my poor overmind.
That I am a scruffy, unkempt, funny looking, always a bad hair day, out of fashion, jalopy driving weirdo.
And you subgeniuses realize how lucky we are.
How rich we are.
To truly not care if we look rich.
We are so rich, we don't care if we look rich.
To not actually give that much of a shit how we look.
That is riches, my friends.
Imagine having to go to all the trouble these normals do just to feel valid.
All the skin treatments, the expensive clothing brands, expensive cars,
and all those gizmos with lights all over them.
That make it easier for their boss to control them.
Look, you can get email from your boss while you're at the beach.
Or look how free you are.
You're so free that you can get a call from the boss while you're out on the fucking golf course.
Friends, just try to keep up with what's cool alone.
Is enough to drive people mad?
And I guess the pink is a lot harder to drive mad because they're so much more numb.
Well friends, I'd rather be dumb than numb any day.
To paraphrase Bob.
I am living proof that you can be an utter failure and a complete dumbass in the pink world
and still be way better off than any of them.
Praise fucking Bob.
Because I'm rich and slack.
Slack.
Deep slack.
Now friends, I've got more kinds of Bob t-shirts than anybody else in the world.
But that's not why I'm rich and slack.
I've got the sexiest space princess known in all the galaxies of Tarnasia for a girlfriend and fiance.
That's enough slack to kill ten elephants and last a man a lifetime.
But that's not the kind of slack I'm talking about.
The kind of slack I mean is the slack that I'm talking about.
The kind of slack that I'm talking about is the lack of really not caring if I'm not famous,
not rich, not cool, not powerful, and not a GQ kind of guy in any way, shape, or form.
Now friends, maybe I had to go through the chasing the gold ring and finally given up
on those things of false slack in order to finally be able to distinguish the non-things
that bring me real slack.
And the real slack is the slack of not being able to produce the hour of slack.
But the slack of being able to appreciate what's played on the hour of slack radio show.
The slack of being able to appreciate, period.
That is where the slack comes in.
The slack of glimpsing, occasionally, how fucking incredible even the most money-making
mundane, poverty-stricken, subgenius life is.
Every minute that you've got a full belly and enough sleep.
Friends, I guess in short you could call it the slack of finally being in a good mood for a change.
Now there's a long stretch there where, like many of you, I was not in that good of a mood.
But things change.
You know, if you're in a bag,
if you're in a bag,
move!
You know, if you're tied up,
Get the fuck out, you know?
Repent!
Quit your job and slack off.
The worst thing that can happen is you might get a better job.
But friends, goddammit, I must say, right here in front of everybody,
the Yaka Tisma could come tomorrow and kill me and I'd have no regrets,
aside from missing out on the next day in eternal life,
because I got to see the Eiffel Tower.
And, uh, uh,
Mardi Gras,
a Jimi Hendrix concert,
five X-Days,
a Bernie Man in Starwood,
and friends, my cup runneth over, goddammit!
Or,
maybe it's even simpler than that, my friend.
Maybe it's just that I finally, finally, finally got over the feeling that I would never ever have a girlfriend.
Which is kind of weird, because I've had a girlfriend of some kind since I was 19.
But I think even those of you who, uh,
have a boyfriend or girlfriend or whatever person of the desired sex or creature,
you still know what I mean, I bet.
Because, uh,
well, even if it's basically hallucinatory,
it's an all too common feeling amongst such geniuses.
Loneliness is.
Uh, it's real hard to shake.
And it's not just funny-looking little guys,
or, you know, like me, or fat ugly guys or whatever,
weird-looking girls,
because I know lots of the popular, cool,
studly-looking subgenius and beautiful subgeniuses that feel the same way,
that feel alone in the world,
and get depressed,
and get really, really,
you know, they're still looking for love, friends,
or at least a dependable fuck-toy,
at least that.
But it's hard to find.
But friends, I am here to tell you, to remind you,
in a pep talk, which is all any good religion is,
to hang in there, goddammit!
You will score on X-Day, no matter what!
You understand that, as a dude's being subgenius.
But who knows?
While waiting for X-Day,
heck, maybe you'll just score anyway, after all.
Once again, friends, I can't stress this enough.
Don't kill yourself!
Let Bob do it for you!
Never try to second-guess old matchmaker Connie.
Matchmaker Connie, friends, and when...
You know, because the hand that Dame Connie finally deals you
just might be the one you least expected,
or it might be the one you most expected.
You don't know!
You don't know the future.
And, uh, I'm afraid old Bob here might not know the future, either.
Look at him.
I'm afraid he's gonna have to make a confession.
And it may be reassuring to some of you.
Some of you have been saying,
I'm not sure if there is a Bob.
Because I came here to be Bob when I saw Bob.
And all he did was fitfully try to hump this stuffed monkey.
In fact, I don't know if he's even real.
He looks like he might be dead, or not even a real person.
Friends, I'm gonna admit it to you.
That's not really Bob.
I know a lot of you were...
excited about being in the same room with Bob Dobsman.
That's not really him.
I'm afraid the real Bob is a lot healthier,
a little bit older,
taller,
and way too goddamn busy to be
walking around with the likes of us, I'll tell you.
He's probably partying with, uh,
Bill Gates.
The hobo with the most slack in the world or something.
I'm not sure if he's dead,
or if he's the most likely.
Oh, the scrotal guy.
What's the name, the scrotal twins, or whatever their name is?
Oh, the back thunder.
That's what they often call it in psychic phenomena.
Back thunder, the paraflatulator!
No, that means that the time's ellipses are kind of like melting away.
They're refracturing into each other.
That means that tomorrow may actually be...
The time intersection.
Right, tomorrow may actually be today.
And so it was spelled.
And so it was.
The time was...
Tomorrow?
Are you ready?
Could it be Saturday night?
That purple bucket mind of a emperor stingy took out his wallet
and decided to end it or begin it all.
Sure, it could just be another stupid subgenius revival.
Or it could be the time intersection.
Or it could be a bunch of puteras with a hair all full of, like,
these weird little jelly beans and things like that.
The potato men and the thumb people will come together.
As some of them say, Charlie.
Charlie and Bob.
For Bob.
My music...
Hey, you know what?
Dances With Rockets music is being played now, right this very minute at the Cannes Film
Festival.
What?
You wish!
Yep.
Jackie Snappy is in this?
This music right here, this exact...
Stuff.
Right here.
Hold on.
Dances With Rockets squirt music?
Yeah.
Please spread the word.
This.
This music right here.
Now, they're using this as a Cannes Film Festival?
This is being used at the Cannes Film Festival as we speak.
How come you never told anybody this?
I don't know.
Well, why?
How did you get it on there?
Because it's soundtracking for...
We are being played Mojo World film.
Cannes?
Or an animation of Mojo World is being shown on the very, very large plasma screen that's outdoors.
And it's getting some showing indoors on the regular screen.
In between things.
Are you ready for the plasma screen?
For your Mojo?
All your Mojo belongs to us.
The plasma screen.
That one moment in time.
Are belong to us.
Oh, Sarah Cynthia Sylvia Stout.
Would not.
Take.
The garbage out.
She'd wash the dishes and scrub the pans.
Cook the yams and spice the hams.
And though her parents would scream and shout.
She simply would not take the garbage out.
And so it piled up to the ceilings.
Coffee grounds, potato peelings.
Brownies.
Brown bananas and rotten peas.
Chunks of sour cottage cheese.
It filled the can.
It covered the floor.
It cracked the windows and blocked the door.
With bacon rinds and chicken bones.
Drippy ends of ice cream cones.
Prune pits.
Peach pits.
Orange peel.
Gloppy glumps of cold oatmeal.
Pizza crust.
Crust and withered greens.
Soggy beans and tangerines.
Crust of blackburn butter toast.
Grizzly bits of beefy roast.
The garbage rolled on down the hall.
It raised the roof.
It broke the walls.
I mean, easy napkins.
Cookie crumbs.
Blobs.
Gooey bubblegum.
Sulfane from old bologna.
Rubbery, rubbery macaroni.
Peanut butter cake.
Dry curdled milk.
Crust of pie.
Rotting melons.
Dried up mustard. Egg shells. Mixed with milk.
With lemon custard.
Cold french fries.
And rancid meat.
Yellow lumps of cream of wheat.
At last, the garbage reached so high that finally it touched the sky.
And none of her friends would come to play.
And all the neighbors moved away.
And finally Sarah Cynthia Stout said,
Okay, I'll take the garbage out.
But then, of course, it was too late.
The garbage reached across the state.
From New York to the Golden Gate.
And there in the garbage she did hate.
Poor Sarah met an awful fate that I cannot right now relate.
Because the hour is much too late.
But children, remember Sarah Stout.
And always take the garbage out.
The garbage out
LT
ned
For gone Edward EL
L
Ford
tert
deg
Doctor
Alda
the Church of the Subgenius, and all the strange ideas that you hear on this show.
Friends, write to Bob at Post Office Box 140306.
That's Box 140306, Dallas, Texas 75214.
Let me give you ESO's Post Office Box for information about their CDs.
Box 81555, Cleveland, Ohio 44181.
And if you need to send something to me personally, that's Stan at P.O. Box 181417, Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
Praise Bob. Praise Lamprey Systems for their great new CD, Rape Until Bedtime.
Friends, I should mention, there's a...
wonderful subgenius scene that...
regularly published by the great name of Quijibo.
And serious subgeniuses should definitely find themselves a sample copy of Quijibo.
You can check it out on the web at quijibo.walkingdead.net.
But I'm going to give their address too.
Quijibo, Q-U-I-J-I-B-O.
18.
West Main Street.
Apartment X.
Greenfield.
Indiana.
46.
140.
And Chaz will take us out as they say.
Praise Bob.
Oh, and get ready for X Day, friends.
4X Day.
That's the next big subgenius devolver coming up.
4X Day at Brushwood.
Check www.subgenius.com.
To be continued...
Riders on the storm
I am a boba truck
Let's get it on
And have some fun
I am a boba truck
Let's get it on
And have some fun
I am a boba truck