This is the subject of radio ministry.
Hour of slack on KNON 90.9 in the left excess.
Praise Bob.
To be a good...
To turn on the machine.
This is Radio Yerevan.
My name is Hans Ivanovich Hagen.
And this is the news.
We got puppet boy.
This is Doug Smith, radio operator.
I have a bucket!
No trouble.
Just get set and get going.
Hey, hear me.
Recording.
Everything's going fine.
No trouble.
Welcome potential initiates.
And remain with us for the next 30 minutes.
Bob?
The message is now part of and registered in your subconscious mind
every time you say, see, hear, or think.
What about slack?
That's your key phrase.
It will trigger the entire message without your being aware of it.
And now, the subgenius hour of slack.
Slack.
The subgenius hour of slack that you are about to listen to is specially designed only
to be played on radio station KNON.
And only in the city of Dallas, Texas.
Should any other shows be heard from or contacted in the course of this show, the listener is
advised to remain calm and only contact listed or unlisted officials in the event of any material
contact.
Do not interrupt the broadcast of this program.
This audio is not intended to be used to demonstrate the importance of the radio or other listening
device being inhaled during broadcast.
Small animals or other children becoming exposed to the ultra high or ultra low shocks and
brain frequencies constantly scanned throughout our program should seek shelter in an approved
safety unit only.
This is Walter Teasdale reminding you that it's often a photon that light releases,
but truth is, not everyone gets the picture.
Hoping your time is all time and all your unpermissible truths are happy truths.
Here is your host.
Reverend Ivan Stavros.
And, uh, yes, dear friends, it's so good to be back in power on KNON 90.9 in Dallas, Texas.
If I can get these sound effects off the script for a second.
Now, friends, don't start calling in yet.
We do have phone-in capabilities here at 823-7490, but don't start calling yet.
Let us establish a little bit of tape, uh, roundup.
Let's nail some sound into your head first.
In the meantime, watch out.
If you're in your car, uh, the streets are starting to get a-mike-slick, friends.
And, you know, the driver next to you would just love to drive by a car wreck, so be careful.
Uh, Reverend, uh, Stewart?
Uh, you might pass me another puff of that puffer fish here.
Yes, we subgenius ministers, uh, even while we're working, um, smoke these, uh, just kind of powdered puffer fish things.
It's the same thing they use in Haiti to create zombies.
Uh, a little bit more puffer fish, and I'll be able to see Bob, and he'll tell me how to get hold of some more puffer fish.
But, friends?
They say, you know, they say that Bob is dead, Bob Dobbs is dead, and even Oboe, the anti-Bob, is sick.
Friends, I don't believe it.
Bob.
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
Bob is a rock, and Bob is a tree.
Bob, Bob is a bear, and Bob is a bee.
Bob, Bob is truth, and Bob is lies.
Bob, Bob is cakes and fruits and pies.
Bob, Bob.
Bob's a hassle.
Bob's my watch.
Bob's my sandwich.
Bob's my crotch.
Bob's my toothpick.
Bob's my brain.
Bob's an ugly yellow stain.
Bob's a cactus.
Bob's an itch.
Bob is take off every stitch.
Bob's my master.
Bob's my slave.
Bob will rob me.
Bob will save.
Bob's my toaster.
Bob's my fridge.
Bob's my little sister and niche.
Bob will cost you.
Bob is free.
Bob's a rock, and Bob's a key.
In short, that Bob does is the man
who used your leg as a frying pan.
If you're not in the jar, you can pour down a sink.
And the subgenius church is a missing link.
Like.
Yeah, pills.
Pills.
Pills to the left of me.
Pills to my right.
Pills in the day and pills in the night.
Pills.
This is K-N-O-N.
This is the hour of slack.
Dear friend, hello.
Are you on the air?
Hello, are you on the air?
Oh, friends.
Oops, just lost a listener.
Now I know why.
I'm afraid this song may explain everything.
Pills.
Well, pills in my hamper.
Pills in my socks.
Pills in the woods and pills on the rocks.
Yeah, pills.
Pills.
Talking about pills.
Only things to do.
Pills are there.
Hello, this is K-N-O-N.
And, and.
Friend, you're on the air.
How's it going, Bob?
Stang?
Yes, this is Reverend Ivan Stang.
I'm afraid Bob ain't here.
Oh, man.
You're not gonna believe it.
Uh, try me.
Oh, man, last night.
See, I was, I got up to go to the bathroom
in the middle of the night, right?
You know, as I'm walking down the hall,
all of a sudden I see this flash.
Yes, yes.
You know, this flash, like orange-blue flame.
Uh-huh.
And so, and it's like right in my face,
and like totally singes my eyebrows.
This is by your bathroom?
Right by my bathroom.
Uh-huh.
And so, you know, I was going, well, what the hell is this?
So I click on the hall light, right?
And it's Bob.
And he's power-flagellating on me.
You actually saw Bob Dobbs?
I saw Bob.
Now, are you the same guy that called last week
and claimed to have seen our
slain guru, J.R. Bob Dobbs?
Wait a minute.
Wait a minute!
Was that Bob?
I don't know. Something's going...
Good Lord, these are other shows!
Other subgenius shows are flying
through the room here in the radio station.
Uh, look,
I'm sorry. We're gonna have to
cut out of this and go to something else.
Uh, can you call back later?
I sure can, man.
Thanks.
I'll be right back.
Ooh!
You know, uh,
I was walking...
I was walking down the beach
trying to get to my woody
where I had my
suds cold and my buds was gold.
I was gonna get high
and get real drunk.
Lay in the sand.
With my beach bunny.
But...
Out to the side...
Out of the side of my eye,
I saw
the ultimate wave.
The super wave.
It was the most stoked out stud wave
in all reality.
It was 900 feet tall.
And on the
backside of reality, too.
I saw a black hole
right in the middle of it.
A vortex.
I was ready to
shoot through that black hole.
Had my molecules
rearranged.
I'm gonna hang five as I shoot through the black hole
of the vortex of the super
wave.
The most god awful wave
in reality.
On the backside of reality.
The front side and
the left and right side.
Huh.
I was tubing.
I was fixing to cut out.
And then...
The giant...
It was Wunsch McColloch.
It was one of those Wunsch McColloch's that just opened up right out of the sea.
And then he came out of the sea, and he started sucking me down.
It was like a vortex funnel sucking me down to the bottom of the ocean.
I was getting sucked down.
And you know, as much as I hate to admit it, it felt pretty good.
It felt pretty good getting sucked down in that vortex with the giant.
I was getting sucked down, all the way down to the bottom of the ocean.
For god, I hate to admit it!
It felt pretty good!
But I hate to admit it!
Moving on down, on the backside of reality, in my bad lord by my side,
riding the wave and stoking on my fine day.
Moving on down to the bottom of the ocean!
Backside of reality
Riding on my back
We're stuck in a map
I say
Huh
Oh, daughter
All on the BG
It's another six-pack
Gonna make sure I have some
Cocoa, yeah
I wanna have some
Cocoa buns
Yeah
And sons
Friends, this is
The Swinging Love Corpses
This is a band
That's
Started
It used to be called
One Thousand Doctors
This is Dr. Philo Drummond's band
With Dr. Ray Hay
And Sphinx Drummond
His brother
And they're a funky
A subgenius band
And in fact
Tonight
I've
You might
Lay off the phone calls
Because once again
I'm having trouble
Dealing with these
I have to have
Forty assistants here
To handle the phone calls
So we're gonna stick with music
And in fact
I'm just gonna play
The tapes that came in
The mail box
To the Subgenius Foundation
This week
These
What you'll be hearing
Is just
The cream off the
Scraping the crud
Off the top
Of what came in
The Subgenius mail this week
We get a lot of cassettes
Oh yes dear friend
So on and on and on
It goes
Regardless of what the news
Media around the world says
We know who's in charge
And praise God
We know exactly
How everything is going to come out
Praise God
In revelation
A clockwise manner
Well this next week
We'll be right back
I'm gonna crack that wing
I'm gonna get back
And uh
I seen one of them flying
Right by
Over my car
And they stopped my car
And they took me in
And they said
Jimmy
We're real
We're here
We're here to help you
You understand
And your mother
And all those dear to you
And your friends
And brother Roloff
And we're gonna stop
The evil that's going on in the world
We're gonna come down
And we're gonna help
Those evil people find themselves
So you can help us Jimmy
We're gonna help those evil people find themselves
You're gonna help us
You're gonna tell us
Which ones are the evil people
That we need to correct
Now you're gonna help us Jimmy
Okay
And then they got back in their spaceship
And they flew off
And I just found myself in my car again
And I drove on down to that 7-Eleven
And uh
My father of course
He's dead
But they're keeping the water on him
He's okay
They're keeping him cool
People say I'm crazy
I don't mind
He told me
He said I see little men
And he held his fingers like this
It's illusions
He said I see little men
About 3 inches high
He said I'm over in
In Spain
Or somewhere like that
He said I even go over into a place like that
And he said I see these little objects
And these little men
And all these little things
And if your heart doesn't go out for something like that
I want you to know
My heart goes out for people like that
And I want you to know something else
Those people are actually
You know what they're doing
Those people are really reaching out
Trying to find something
And if they can just
If they can just realize it
You know what they're doing
Jesus has the answer
That Christ has everything that they're looking for
And Christ can get
Let them get
Get on high
And lift them up
And put them on the high way
And give them joy
And speak up
Give them peace in the life
You'll not want any more dope
You'll not want any more alcohol
You'll not
No, no, don't let me take those pills
No
Bring out the pills, baby
I don't want to take those pills
From outer space
No
Give them the pills
Come on, now
Bring out the pills
Just because you're alone
with me
Only testimonies
or a detector and a vacation home in the rockies
with a coyote's drone minutes it took to get to the bank
where the pet caused by a shish kebab steak he went in the aquarium of the skeleton fish
the styrofoam packed him up to the top of a building
it's no fun living like we do here cause there's no good tv and no cold beer
the clothes hamper of the wilderness filters are red and the dryer is jammed
the books that you bought last week i'm seeing
genie is glad that the kiln was put in
tonight
it's a big test that we see the lives of many
a mile and a half will kill every guy
a mile and three quarters up in the sky
it's a great big banner
give up tree there's no gray matter
in your suit
oh come on give just a little and take even less
kangaroo soldiers aren't making a mess
and that kiln he admits of glamorous
makes the world go on
it doesn't seem like my favorite books but why should it
forbidden fruit and forbidden drugs
the diplomats cute on the purging rugs
as he watched the news four days before
orgasm rushed and down came the door
the mounties said he was insane
the sun sank and the beach receded
a movie for the night
a theater with no chairs
while plato picked out
blonde chapped hair of the deaf mute sex queen
music
Talk police
music music
music
rabble
music music
full name
this wasviewer
old man
that was the wallman
are Bob Dobbs is dead. Now, honestly, for years, for the last two years, I subscribed
to the commonly held theory, the official theory of the church, that Bob Dobbs had been
killed. I now, and I can't explain why, I no longer believe that. I just know for some
reason in my heart that Bob is not dead and that he's probably listening, you know, if
not to this show, to your show, friends. So, in the meantime, the anti-Dallas, the anti-Dallas,
friends, from which Oboe, the anti-Bob, gets his power, its power is wavering. The power
of the anti-Dallas is wavering, but at the same time, if it comes in contact with the
true Dallas, which is okay, there may be a conjunction, friends, a conjunction of the
anti-Dallas.
Now, Oboe wants this. Bob does not want this. Dr. Stu here from More Drunk Cowboys actually
has done the research that led to this theory here. He's here in the station with us. Dr.
Stu?
Yes.
Can you add anything to what I'm saying? As you were telling me, all of the police will
turn evil if there is a conjunction with the anti-Dallas, even the Krishna policemen.
Yes, even the Krishna policemen will turn evil.
In fact, see, the anti-Dallas is composed mainly of slack vampires. We know of slack
vampires. They depend on us for their survival. Actually, this ties in very clearly with the
Omicron-Epsilon theory of time.
Yes, the time intersection, when the backwards universe intersects with our universe.
See, in effect, since the anti-Dallas is a close...
It's in fact a closed universe into and of itself. It just happens to be a cheap satanic
replica of our true Dallas. They do tend to intersect sort of like a partial eclipse of
the true Dallas and the anti-Dallas. Also, the anti-Dallas has no time control whatsoever.
In effect, they're trying to keep themselves together. Backwards, forwards, time. That
doesn't mean...
That doesn't mean nothing. There's nothing but time vortexes there.
No, no, no.
It's kind of like random static on your television set, you see. They're trying to get to us.
But do we have time control? Do we ourselves have what Bob calls true time control?
We don't have control, but at least Wotan keeps all the Bobions going in the same direction
at the same time. In the anti-Dallas, actions do not have consequences. Consequences do
not have actions. It's much closer to Negius.
Oh, I'm sorry.
You know, I've been thinking about it. It's much closer to the cosmic universe than ours.
You see.
Good Lord.
Indeed.
I had no idea.
Indeed. And Negi is so much closer to them than he is to us.
This is a chilling, chilling thought, friends.
Indeed.
It's getting colder and colder in the station.
I've heard our powers dropping.
Yes, as I understand, I heard those raps again, those mysterious sounds.
Oh, God.
The rapping in the walls, the pops and bangs.
Snap.
Can you hear them, friends, out there?
So, anyway...
As I understand it, the anti-Dallas is somehow cut off from our reality, all alone in its
own hollow, curved interior universe. There is no anti-Chicago, no anti-Miami.
No anti-Phil.
And the only way they can get out is through Dallas.
Not even an anti-Ivan Stang, no anti-Philo Drummond.
There is...
Nothing but Oboe and nothing but Bob.
Oboe, the anti-Bob.
And as long as Bob's in heaven, Oboe's in heaven.
Oboe will get sicker and sicker and weaker and weaker.
That is why Bob is staying in heaven or hell or Asgard, as he is.
He is, in effect, not unable to come back, but merely choosing not to while Oboe gets
sicker and is dying out.
Here, have some of this puffer fish.
Let's blow off that church.
Oh, I'll get that.
Are you abnormal?
Then you are probably not.
You are better than most people.
Yes, your time shall triumph through Bob and Slack.
Slack is the free car wash that comes with the Phil of Bob.
He's the ultimate good guy, the terrorist for peace.
Bob is the pool of the universe and thus the only place of all knowledge.
Bob is the phoenix rising from the ashes of the cleansing fire.
Bob is the teaching for those who need not be taught.
The more stupid something looks, the more important it probably is.
Bob is heaven's one true policeman.
Bob is the bullet and you, you are the gun.
Bob is companionship and there's no one there, no one there.
Bob is really the ultimate sex god.
These are facts you must take into account.
7 a.m. July 5th, 1998.
What will it be like?
It is X Day here in Cleveland.
Gather round, one and all.
It is X Day in Cleveland.
And he gave me some rock.
I can handle reality.
Now that Bob made a man out of me.
We now know that LSD is the most mysterious and powerful substance ever invented.
Oh, yes, dear friend.
And so, you see, that tape was actually brought to the studio last week.
I've edited it down a little bit.
Sorry there, Reverend Patterson.
The young and strange Reverend Patterson brought that, actually dropped that by the studio.
And the mailman dropped by all these other cassettes.
And the thunder and the lightning continued.
And there was no hope anywhere.
We know that LSD will fly.
It's the most mysterious and powerful.
Welcome.
I think.
Oh.
Okay.
Good Lord, friends.
I'm actually, there's something hideously wrong with my number two tape deck here.
But don't worry.
Oh, no.
We know exactly what could.
90.90.
FM.
And now it's sexy.
This is the sub-channel radio ministry.
We threw the poster.
Our reflect on KNO.
And 90.9 in the left excess.
Praise Bob.
This is KNO and 90.9 in Dallas, Texas.
Alice, welcome, dear friends, to the church of the sub-channel radio ministry.
This is the channel.
It's the Bob show.
Okay.
Then, we'll look out for you.
Here.
We believe that you'll be grateful for that.
I already.
You, too.
There'll be no punishment for you.
Oh.
det셔.'saw'ed.
against the right to the max so to speak and all that is around us those are your instructions
enjoy the crud the very crud of the conspiracy and fling it back in their faces
in this way we may hope to overcome until next time or 1998 whichever comes first
we bid you a very good week
ah yes dear friends i'm trying to get another call number two are you on the air
i guess he's not that's ridiculous hello dear friend
well we lost it
you know that other one
oh
you
sexual
think about this man oh all right i think it's a wonderful idea which is joined to the radius
vector that directs ah yes that radiation we've been having that that accounts for it that accounts
for those giant slugs and snails which i your champion dr howell have been battling on the
rims of consciousness yes they palpate their subluxations as i tell you it's a massage
they have no internal skeletons as we know only a cartilaginous mass of pulsating tubercles
undulating swiftly through the sluggish streams that rush through the secret places in the center
of the earth now let's uh take euclid let's take a euclidean demonstration of this geometric uh
apophage more procedure and suddenly here we are out in outer space planets comets things rushing
by
faster than trains faster than steamships or locomotives are faster than those mutant speedy
snails we've been having samples and i tell you it's a mysterious sight enough to make
you throw back your shoulders suck in that gut and trust in the infinite
somebody's idea of a joke huh
it happens to us all down in the clinging darkness of the void
the
dr rex would you change his child i think he's soiled his nappy thank you take the little urchin
from me there we go secrecy is violated once again oh oh stop that so peace to you you very jazzy very
groovy berkeley heights and all you other people there we will bury you in sound effects and noise
here on the kpfa radio of the peace-loving peaceful north american people's democratic republic
and here in the mysterious republic of sad seconds
is
is taking place the birth of an heir to mobius the mobius rex of the future not the mobius rex
of the present or the mobius who has already wrecked the past but the mobius rex which is
yet to come the wreck of all our hopes the new mobius rex the geometric drone this creature
can reproduce which we are discussing do anything
cut that out kid my god that's the most disgusting thing i've ever seen in my life
haven't we beefed the
out
you're you when
you married me
friends absolutely not i'm sorry we just got a phone call from a listener who claims that they
had a message beamed into their head from bob dobbs himself in the spirit world from bob uh
you know you know they they all say that i mean friends all the voices aren't bob
sometimes they're imitating bob but this did sound very bob like this person said
that uh that that bob beamed into his head a message to the conspiracy to the the pinks the
normals the barbies and kens the mediocrity and those out there afraid of everything different
and that message was kill me and you're dead yes bob's message to the world friends
uh no reverence dude
cars in reality
do you think smoking cigars in reality an existential form of existence beyond that which
we know a normal time manifestation normal time oh it's more like advanced i think it's like
heliopters in a in a space-time warp when you're surfing through the black hole of time
and you come apart it gets a hard cold spike reality of but you know that's why that's when
i know i've got a cold stone groove man i'm hip you know that's a beautiful
thing
it is a beautiful thing like a beautiful thing like nothing else like orgasm pause
you know when i'm hanging 10 with my beach bunny and she says and we're in she says honey
when you're hanging 10 with me and your toes are hanging over the edge of that board
it's just like orgasm it's better than orgasm of orgasm i see those toenails clutching the
end of that board man and we're shooting that board and we're shooting that board and we're
shooting that each other and we're shooting that board saying business as it were that's
why right instead of one problem not another problem not another problem not another problem
i hope zoey chasing CPR again for a little while but she's not always sure about what
those patterns are lol
but do not know yet is that at 40 on drive out to sleep you'll never know okay now bro
i had a water cup call see if it'll worked out okay in about a minute it's not gonna
work and then i need pana that ca him to come back to the다고 boat man and i'm remove
it i'm gonna go youか.
what man know you or me i'm cognitively unable to recall one word you know something may have
I think we need to hit that button before we put it down.
No, I don't think so.
Oh.
This is ridiculous.
Somebody must be cutting him off.
Somebody is trying to prevent this.
See, this caller called with an emergency.
He said that someone's been following him.
Okay.
Someone is following him.
Okay, now, is that a button?
Dear friend, hello, you're on the air.
I can't hear you.
If anyone can help us, please do.
In the meantime, this beautiful hymn of pyroflatulation should keep you informed.
Oh.
Hello, this is Ann McKinney.
14 years ago, legalized birth control became a reality in America.
13 years ago, abortion was made legal.
Now in 1986, these fundamental rights are being threatened.
But you can do something.
March 9th in Washington, D.C., the National Organization for Women is planning the first nationwide pro-choice march since 1973.
Your reproductive freedoms have never been more threatened than they are today.
If you don't want Jerry Falwell or Ronald Reagan deciding what birth control method you choose,
you can do something about it.
Join us in this struggle now, or your future decisions may be in someone else's hands.
Show your legislators and President Reagan that you do care.
March with your sisters and brothers in Washington, D.C. on March 9th.
Call National Organization for Women at 424-5474 for more details.
¶¶
Ah, yes, dear friends.
Yes, we've got one on the line. We hooked him.
Is this the man? Is this the man?
Uh, how may we help you, sir?
Uh, hello?
How may we help you, ma'am, sir, ma'am, thing?
God.
¶¶
No, no, no.
Here.
Oh, oh, oh.
Have another one.
No.
Have three more.
Oh, ow, ow, ow, ow.
That was fine.
Hey.
I feel, I feel, I feel great.
Hey, where's Bob?
I want to go see Bob now.
I want to go see Bob.
No.
And I need to talk directly to you, Bob.
And I don't write real, real so good, real good words.
But, uh, at least I can, uh, uh, talk, talk, talk, Bob.
So, please, um, um, send me some more, uh, those, you know,
uh, uh, uh.
We'll all meet you on the Cztronbe.
Uh, uh, uh...
You hear that?
What is that?
Uh-huh.
Uh, uh-huh.
Let's go!
Hello! Hello! Hello!
You've got to go!
Now that's what I mean!
Bob's going to flatten your parade with his church.
If that doesn't work, he'll shove it up your ass.
Yes, sir.
That bob is everywhere.
Small sample of what's going to happen.
How you feel, pink boys?
Look at him run.
Shut up, pink boy.
Yeah.
Less than 13 years to go.
Hardly wait.
If you wanna stay 재래 Aunty Junkies
release Ray Ba nation,
otherwise,
skulle
거봅
Yes, Bob will be taking orders here in just a few minutes, so please have your menu ready.
A little Dobbs intermission here, a little traveling music for the Dobbs Highway.
Ah, there we go, let's get up a little bit here.
Ah, it sure is fun sitting here having dinner with Bob.
Would you like some more, Bob?
He's looking pretty full over there.
I think he's put a little false slack on since the meal started.
How much can you pinch there?
Oh, look at that.
Bob's putting on a little fad.
And we now take you to our program, already in the Rock Rocks.
Oh, yes.
I'm so an asshole like the rest of my guests so that I can't possibly be outdone in any conversation.
I like having the last word.
It's my show, and I'll do what I want with it.
Thank you.
Oh, gee, thanks, Reverend Oscar of the Rat Cave.
Ugh!
Yes, that was Reverend, uh, Reverend Oscar of the Evil Rat Cave from the album The Rat Cave Squeak.
See, it's just endless.
I've got the blues
That damn pickup
Talked and run over my wife
My first love
I've got the blues
Everything
He just appropriates no sense.
He's only talking to himself.
Let's see what the person is like.
I think we should be careful, uh, getting religion involved in this show.
He calls himself the Reverend Ray Dodge.
Let's see if he's home, because we tried to call him yesterday and he wasn't home.
Hello, this is, uh, Reverend Ray Dodge.
Reverend Dodge?
Yes, it is.
Hi, Bill...
This is Charlie Rattin.
Wait, excuse me.
This is Bill Baker calling from XCI.
You got a call from the XCI?
You guys entered our contest?
Yes.
We have the Reverend Ray Dodge and Dolly Rotten.
Dolly Rotten, yeah.
Now, I'll tell you something.
I don't...
I didn't understand, you know...
My...my...my sense of humor is a little bit, uh...is a little bit childish, if you will.
So I wasn't quite...I didn't understand your entry.
You know, what is exactly the Reverend Ray Dodge do?
Reverend Ray Dodge is Danbury's chief architect at the Planet Bob.
At the what?
We're, uh...
We're at the subgenius in the Fairfield County area.
The word of what?
The planet what?
The word of Bob.
Right.
Now...now, who is Bob?
Is this anyone I know?
Bob.
What do you mean, who is Bob?
Bob...
And just remember, Bob spelled backwards is still Bob.
Who is...who is Bob Knott?
Who is Bob Knott?
We have some questions for you.
Now, wait a minute.
Who's doing the auditioning here?
Oh, we...well, if we...if we get Dean to come on your show, can we ask questions about
the flying saucers that are invading our country?
Uh, I wasn't familiar with any flying saucers invading our country.
No...
You're not aware that flying saucers are sleeping with your wives?
Well, none of us are married yet.
That's the reason.
This guy is really out to lunch.
We have to be careful.
I'm afraid...
...saint seems anomalous.
Yet, in his lifetime, he had something of a reputation for prophetic dreams and miraculous
cures of the sick and blind.
More miracles were recorded years after his death when his canonization was in question.
It must be said for him that he never went out of his way to claim miraculous powers.
though he was not displeased when he heard of a cure that worked.
All right, now we have the Reverend Ray Dodge.
Preaching, wait, let's clarify this.
He preaches the word of Bob.
Maybe you could clarify that for the listeners.
I'll tell you about Bob.
Go ahead.
Bob went among the Negroes and became a voodoo priest
after he returned from the Mexican War.
I was much less disturbed by the vaguer tales of wails and howlings
in the barren windswept valley beneath the limestone cliff,
of the graveyard stenches after the spring rains,
of the floundering, squealing white thing
on which Sir John Clave's horse had trod one night in a lonely field,
and of the servant who had gone mad
at what he saw in the priory in the full light of day.
A few of the tales were exceedingly peculiar.
They were very picturesque and made me wish I had learned more
of the comparative mythology in my youth.
Bob is our chief prophet and the avatar of the 80s.
He will bring about the end times and show humanity the way
to financial riches and free sex.
Bob is the true living slack master,
and I think he's answered all the problems of our present times.
Oh, really?
Oh, really.
Also, he is helping us to build the Slack Accelerator Project.
A Slack Accelerator Project?
Where is this located?
You guys think that the construction out on the highway
is repairs to the highway.
It's a little-known fact,
and we're prepared to reveal this information now,
that we are building a giant Slack Accelerator.
I'm not quite sure what.
Slack? S-L-A-G-G?
No, S-L-A-C-K.
Now, what is exactly...
We feel that in the...
in the Danbury area,
there's an insufficiently high level of slacking off.
Uh-huh.
So we are trying to accelerate that process
by tightening this noose slowly around the outskirts of Danbury.
What about the high level of mental illness in the Danbury area?
Yeah, yeah, we're working with that.
We feel that there's some potential there.
Potential for what?
People.
You guys are... these guys are nuts!
He was a vindictive, irrational man.
Uh, yes, friends.
We'll see when...
I think that suitably got us off the hook with Bob.
Obviously, Bob does not want us to take call-ins on our own show,
so I had to steal another show that had call-ins from other subgeniuses.
That was sent by Reverend Ray Dodge in Connecticut.
So, you see, that's what you can do.
Call in over there.
For that old damn Bob.
Yeah, oh, that's right.
Yeah, try to call in to all those other shows.
Listen to those subgeniuses screaming in the background.
Ah!
Oh, yee...
Leah...
Leah get me.
Hai!
sharks!
¶¶
Friends, the church of the subgenius,
this incredible new faith
in which orthodoxy is the only heresy,
is authorized to blaspheme by the gods themselves.
This is, in fact, the first all-purpose belief system
compatible with most major world religions and many weird cults
without expensive interfaces.
Friends, the quest of the Church of the Subgenius is something for nothing.
Our immediate goal? World slack. World takeover.
Our sub-purposes, friends, are to end death, taxes, hunger, war, disease, aging, and work.
Because as Bob said, friends, as long as we must work, we are not free.
Our weapons in this battle, friends, are the power of abnormality,
the power of unpredictability, and the word of Bob Dobbs.
Living out the word of Bob Dobbs.
The avatar of slack on planet Earth.
Now, friends, we're going to have to be signing off pretty soon.
I want you to have your pencils ready at the end of this broadcast
where you can write for information and find out just what is going on.
What is this so-called church?
Who is Bob Dobbs?
Who is this man, Bob? Who is this man?
Friend, friend, you can't hide from Bob.
You can hide from this show for a little while.
You can hide from Charlie Manson.
You can hide from Reverend Ivan Stank, but you can't hide from Bob, friend,
because he's stupider than you.
He's got more dots on his face than you do.
His face has been mimeographed and put up in more places in yours.
You can't hide from Bob.
You can't keep track of Bob.
break hotel. Ooh, it's getting scary in here again, folks, as the hour slowly comes to
an end. And as I said before, you can write to Bob. If you actually address a letter to
Bob, he may receive it. It may be intercepted in the mail at some point. Yes, I hear that
beautiful sign-off music coming up. Friends, we need your love offerings, your donations
here at K&ON to keep this station on the air, to keep slack flowing out or whatever it is
that we're peddling. And it is slack, friends, and Bob does love you. So send that pound,
that hundred pounds of dollar bills to my lap. Address that to Bob at P.O. Box 14 or
over.
P.O. Box 14306, Dallas, Texas 75214. That's right. That's Bob at P.O. Box 14306 in Dallas,
Texas. Ah, yes, the real Dallas, not the anti-Dallas where Oboe the Anti-Bob's going to try to get
you from, friends. This is Reverend Ivan Stang with the Hour of Slack. Sorry we couldn't
put your phone calls on the air this time. Apparently it was not.
The will of that man, Bob.
So, good night and hang in there for the Monday morning replacement show. The entire rest
of this week is nothing but a replacement for the subgenius hour of slack for the next
week.
Wood has been cast.
Ah, yes.
With ordinary men who invalidate programs.
Yeah, what's up
again?
Oh, no.
No, Bob.
What?
Here's Illa.
Yeah.
You're kicking my ass.
Drinking Budweiser