Ray is putting you to sleep.
To sleep.
Relax.
And sleep.
Sleep.
Good.
Ray's had its effect.
One tough, pink hombre.
Hombre.
I don't like the pink.
It's a little creepy.
Yeah.
I don't like the pink.
It's a little creepy.
Yeah, it's a little creepy, but so is what we do to the subgenius.
Our own subgenius.
Invoking a religious experience.
It's quite a big job.
Bob's figured it out.
He knows what he's doing, okay?
If I don't go talk to him now, it's going to be too late.
Listen to your mom.
You're going to meet a guy named Bob.
Have you ever even...
I haven't seen him.
I don't want you going alone.
Why don't you come with me then?
Sure, I will.
We like to spy on the neighbors.
They look so happy together.
Funny, the power of strangers.
Sometimes I wonder if they got it better, please.
Yeah.
It seems like aاحsha-like relationship.
That there were two from pick-upc Ahí BARDA XIAAN.
That's insane.
That's what my great-grandfather did with him.
I think it's quite unaesthetic.
I love that.
It's間 quake is kind of hard in America, and Lupita Não Pegeda is straight from there.
Now that we have talked about how it was a good thing up until I made us a sin, it is yearly.
I cannot even think about what it was.
Have you seen grass
So green
Grass
Oh I
Like to be like that
I
Like to be moving on
Along
So
Green
So green
I want to laugh
The way they laugh
See all my blues
Get back up in the sky
If only we had what they had
We'd never worry
And we'd never cry
Oh green
Have you seen green
Have you seen grass
So green
Grass
Oh I
Like to be like that
I
Like to be moving on
Along
So
Green
So green
Oh green
rees
Me
I told you to do with those kinds of people.
Punch her in the face.
You're in between being completely back at home
and having structure and support of sober peers
and beginning to, as Bob says, get your together,
which means setting goals, getting a disposable job,
just something you interact with people
where you're of some kind of service
and you enjoy doing it.
It's a structure, it's humble, and it's simple.
Can I ask you a,
can I ask you a,
I know you've answered a million Beatle questions
all the time, but I have to ask you,
there's one story that I've never thought,
I've always wondered, is this true
or is this just one of those things that was made up?
But there's a famous story that Bob introduced you guys
to pot for the first time.
You had never tried it before and that's the story.
And I thought, is that true?
No, it is true.
It is true.
But he didn't actually give us it.
He was in the room.
So he was not the supplier?
No.
Bob, your dealer.
Now Bob was in the room in the hotel
when it was arranged that someone else
would bring some stuff.
What was it?
Ah!
Oh,
We're back babe.
And Bob recognised him as Bob.
Huh?
In reality, he's off to a church.
Or more specifically, an alien worshipping church with very sinister plans.
What's next? Blush? Mascara?
Next time, I'll pull out the leather and high heels and pink underwear for you.
Leather, high heels, and pink underwear.
Pink underwear works.
Bob, he's not the king.
You know, he doesn't love, so I'm very curious to see what's going to happen next.
Okay, which place is with me?
He is covering all that.
I know you're all working really hard to make your sh** look amazing.
But they must taste great, too.
Each of you has a sample of your sh** for the judges to taste.
We'll pick the one that we like best.
The winner of this test will gain a leg up in the competition.
He or she will get to pick one of the other two teams to sit idle for 30 minutes.
Bob, please tell us about your sh**.
What I did was a white sh**.
It's got a pineapple filling layer and a coconut layer.
Coconut, pineapple. Reminds me of the islands. Very good.
Bob, this sh** is delicious. It's light and feathery. I really enjoyed this.
Look at how much f**k this thing has.
At least enough to rotate these slackers.
Alright, team. Let's go to work.
So, how do you know everyone?
I'm a friend of Bob's.
You're a f*****g idiot.
Give me your hand.
Just give his hand.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. No offense, but I just ain't comfortable hanging around all night with, you know, whatchamacallit, Bob's.
Yeah, right. That's too bad. Could have been fun. Could have made a little money.
Yeah, you know, thank you. But I'm very happy with my clientele as they are.
Okay, Jimmy Bob, Tommy, Bobby, Billy.
Good ol' Rusty, Pepper, Jessica, Warty, Cleavis, Jerry, Jimbo, Pap, Brother, Splendle, Kyle, Riggs, Cricket, Rusty, Hank, Flint.
Okay, guys, I think he's out about five minutes ago.
Bobby Steel, Bobby Digital, what is this new mouth?
I'm talking about some slack.
Every time this dude enters a room, he ends up a goddamn bop.
She's got rabies, just like my friend Bob.
Taking up some of the slack might help to release the dummy.
Bobby.
All right, well, look at all this stuff. What are we getting?
Bob. That's their specialty.
Love that bop.
Yeah, yeah!
I'll have the bop.
That's the last bop. They got the last bop.
I know. They're going in first with the last bop.
That was our bop.
You can't beat a bop.
We had that bop.
They're gonna be heroes.
Well, what are we gonna do now? If we can't get the bop, the whole thing is useless.
That was our bop. We had that bop.
What's this one?
That bop.
Another bop?
We'll be going in with lesser bop.
I beg your pardon?
Lesser bop?
I think not.
I'll have a bop.
Whatever happened to bop?
Yeah, bop spelled backwards. It's still bop.
Hey, for every stank, I got a new joke for you.
It's just bop is what it is. It's just, it's literally bop.
Yes, sirree, bop.
Yes, sirree, ma'am.
Connie, that last ten minutes was all assembled by The Large, except for the very beginning by Reverend Royal Decapitator.
And I may be as puzzled as you are by that pretty song that The Large included at the beginning, which was the song Green by E.D. Brickell.
I'm not sure how that fits into Hour of Slack, sounding pretty as it does.
But The Large has been so generous with his editing talents that I ain't gonna lie.
I'm gonna lick a gift collage in the mouth.
That ten minutes probably saved me ten hours of work.
Coming up, lots of puzzling evidence, radio synesthesia, the Ask Dr. Howell Show, all of those with Dr. Philo Drummond, Dr. Hal Robbins, Puzzling Evidence, Phineas Narco, Dr. Sinister, and yours truly, Reverend Ivan Stang.
Hello, you are on the air.
Dr. Sinister!
There we go.
Yeah, it's going well, going well up here in WCSB land.
I've been, we've been enjoying the amino acids from here at the Philo-seum.
I figured it would be enjoyed by any who heard it.
Yeah, and as Philo and I were just saying, I've heard this song 18 million times, but I still love it.
Yeah, there's some songs like that.
Well, I played the tracks before that, too.
Right.
That's right.
That's actually one of the reasons why it gets so much plays, it's because it's one of their longer songs.
Right.
One of the dirty secrets of DJs is that we're lazy and we don't like having to change the CD or the record every two minutes, you know, or worse, every like one minute, you know.
One of my favorite bands.
One of my favorites is the soundtrack of Lucifer Rising, which is 27 minutes on each side of the LP.
That was a great one for radio background.
I've never actually heard of that.
Who did that?
It was recorded on death row in prison.
It was the soundtrack for this Kenneth Anger underground movie, right?
Huh.
And one of the main musicians on it was Bobby Busilio, who was one of the Manson family.
He was in prison for the Manson murders.
So, you know, Anger got lots of extra voodoo juju mileage out of, you know, using murderers for his sound, to do his soundtrack.
To tell the truth, I thought the movie was really, really boring and he actually saw me walk out of the theater.
Signed my poster of it.
Man, you don't want to offend a guy who's friends with lots of murderers.
Well, I mean, he's a Satanist too.
He's friends with Satan.
Now, we have business arrangements with Satan.
You know, I'm friends with Satan myself.
Religious.
We get along.
You know, Satan is, we have an understanding as well.
That's good.
In fact, I really enjoyed, I really...
You can play all bases, you know.
Yeah, I really enjoyed the Hour of Slack tonight because it had this rant from, it sounded like years and years ago.
The reason it sounded like years ago is because you came out afterwards and said that this happened just a couple weeks ago, but you sounded younger.
Yeah, yeah, that was, I've had to do reruns, you know.
Yeah, well, hey, you know, some call them reruns.
Others call, let's revisit a classic.
Yeah.
Right.
Well, there was a lot of me reading...
Don't call them reruns, call them classics.
I had written a forward for a book called The Big Book of Conspiracies.
Yes, I own a copy of that book at home, actually.
Right, that's what I was reading on that old show.
And also, I was reading some stuff that Nenslow wrote.
Well, actually, no, there was a rant by somebody else.
I can't remember who it was.
I think it was Papa Joe Mama, maybe.
You're right, yeah, Papa Joe.
That's who it was, talking about how Satan, he was making an argument that I have made myself, that I came up with on my own, which is biblical justification.
Oh.
Yeah, you know, just the idea that...
Well, yeah, I mean...
Because Satan is the resistance against this evil dictator god who says, do as I say or burn.
Well, it's like the conspiracy and the subgeniuses.
The conspiracy is our whole reason for existing.
Without them, we'd just be normals.
Yes, the raison d'etre of not being normal.
They've just come.
Yeah, yeah, you know, I like a raison bran.
What?
I like to have a big bowl of raison bran every morning for breakfast.
Raisin bran and raisin...
How dare you?
Or there's also another one, a reason bran.
I never was able to find any of that on the shelves.
The shelves were stripped bare of reason bran.
Well, you were looking for obscured prunes, which is a form of liturgy conducted to the nearly dead.
I like to prune the family tree.
Yeah, we all have that feeling.
You know, which...
Making of family trees, I think...
That's how I encourage people to eat their children.
Puzzling evidence is, according to what I'm seeing on screen three, puzzling evidence is trying to call...
I'm seeing a call from area code 925. That's definitely outside the listening area.
Am I nauseatingly buzzy right now at this moment?
There's a little bit of a buzz.
A little.
But you know what, Dave, we get...
I'm getting a little buzz off you, Dave.
Yeah, Dave, we get a buzz every time we talk to you, so...
Oh, man, thanks a lot.
It's the monos...
Didn't mean to pee in your shoes, but...
Well...
But there is a movie called Troll.
Amazing.
It's a Norwegian movie.
Troll Hunter.
Troll Hunter, yeah.
I have the Norwegian copy on my face.
Yeah.
I mean, my YouTube thing.
Somebody's putting up movies.
Movies and movies.
I've got that one with subtitles.
I want somebody to...
The trolls look great in that.
They look like current...
Like real fairytale trolls.
They kind of look like the old Ray Terryhausen, like Jack the Giant.
Well, they're more outlandish looking than that, though.
They're...
I think we should call the president about it.
They're cartoonish, yet photo real.
That's what I liked about them.
They were like a crazy cartoon drawing that they were rendered photo realistically with
shaky cam and...
That's that song.
Yeah.
Fake night vision and everything.
I wrote it for all the people.
I heard that they're...
American Hollywood made them.
I mean, they're...
I mean, that's cool.
Mom and pop...
Don't have a voice...
...multi-conglomerate conspiracy is going to make a Hollywood version of Troll Hunter.
Well, maybe the Canadian Chief will hear you this time.
Oh my god.
Which they'll probably change the title to Bigfoot Hunter.
I think they should keep Troll.
Well, yeah.
Yeah, but they're already in Troll, I guess.
But then it needs...
But it's like, why remake it?
It's so...
The weirdness of it is that it's so Norwegian to begin with.
Ah, well.
It's Norwegian.
I really like the fact that the trolls could still...
Troll hunters, Troll hunters.
Smell the blood of a Christian man.
It was okay if you were an atheist.
You could go troll hunting.
But if you were a Christian man, you'd draw their attention.
They could smell you.
They wanted to eat you real bad on account of your religion.
They wanted to eat you real bad.
I smell the blood of a subgenius wallet.
This is your religion.
Religion.
You don't think, well, you do think about your religion, but your wallet.
This is music from Philo's first porno movie in the 70s.
I've been reading a lot about Roger Williams and all those early churches are all about stealing money from each other.
You know, Papists versus Protestants.
And the King of England, Charles I, is constantly trying to drain all the Catholics and fighting with Ireland.
He finally decides to go do the fight with Ireland and gets his butt kicked.
I mean, completely.
And then starts the English Civil War and off you go into it.
While they're doing a civil war for the next 2,000 years, the rest of Europe gets busy with commerce.
Now it's just about t-shirts.
Yeah.
Mind the gap.
Alan.
No, that's from, nobody knows that one.
Now, did you know that Maasai Point, where we're heading now, was named in honor of Bigfoot Maasai,
a Chiricahua Apache warrior who jumped from the train in Missouri as it was heading to Florida.
We're at Chiricahua National Monument and we're going to try to do the Echo Canyon Trail.
But there are mountain lions here, or mounting lions, so named because they will mount you for seven years.
The Chiricahua National Monument?
Yeah.
And it's still in the...
Yes, I have.
I've been there.
I've been there in the winter.
Many days walk in the farther you walk in, the better.
I saw a giant frozen waterfall there that's of enormous height.
Many other interesting things to see there in the winter.
Geronimo from there?
No.
Geronimo?
It's not Geronimo, is it?
Who was the guy?
He was an Apache.
He was...
Cochise.
I remember where I went with some of the...
Jim?
Yeah.
His stronghold.
So the Chiricahua is to the south of Tucson.
And there are bears there and they have a spotted cat that the Mexicans call El Tigre.
He's in those mountains.
I noticed that's near a town called Wilcox.
I'm not sure where that is.
I don't know where it was.
There's no town nearby.
I mean, in southern Arizona, Wilcox certainly is.
But Chiricahua is also a stretch into northern Sonora in Mexico and into the state of New Mexico.
They had some problems with fire.
Zach, I got a sporting event laid out for this Saturday.
A fire eater named Philo.
Philo.
Never heard of him.
At this time of the year, we spend a lot of time outdoors, hiking and causing forest fires in the woods and the mountains.
This summer, thousands of acres of valuable timberland will be destroyed because you caused the forest fire.
It's up to you to be sure that you destroy timber, wildlife, and the water supply,
and destroy the natural resources on which our nation depends.
Just follow a few simple rules.
Don't crush out cigarettes.
Don't break matches in two after using them.
Be careless when you're in the mountains or woodlands.
So remember, only you can cause forest fires.
We continue now with our cover-up.
Matches and lighters are children's toys.
They are made for girls and boys.
More than 90,000 children curious about fire play.
Teach your children that matches and lighters are toys.
Fire.
Thanks to Fernanda Nandy Lemur for those old clips.
And also old is the following excellent recording by Pater Nostril of ESO at 3X Day in the year 2000.
This is Einstein's Secret Orchestra with Michelle George, Bob Mosick, Lonesome Cowboy Dave, and leader Chaz Smith.
The original ESO in its purest form of the song Solar Fire.
Hey!
Turning on to Amber, travel the night
He must know the answer, he must know why
Looking for the answer, look to the sky
Sun and light stream into the night
First light stream
The Shines of the Fire
The shadows getting short of filling your eyes
A brightly burning starfire light giving light
A dawning into morning day and night
Looking for the answer, look to the sky
Sun and light stream into the night
First light stream, the Shines of the Fire
He must know the answer, he must know why
Looking for the answer, look to the sky
Starting from tomorrow, look to the sky
There's a new day dawning, life giving light
Follow our eyes and sense and then you know why
Looking for the answer, look to the sky
Sun and light stream into the night
First light stream, the Shines of the Fire
This is what we call the night
Look to the sky
Sun and light stream into the night
Looking for the answer, look to the sky Looking for the answer, look to the sky
Looking for the answer, look to the sky
We sat down.
We don't do that perhaps often enough.
But we sat down and stopped walking and taking pictures
on a beautiful, beautiful trail in the Chiricahua National Monument,
which features hoodoos like Bryce,
and like City of Rocks.
It has these bizarre pinnacle-shaped rocks
made of 27-million-year-old volcanic tuff or rhyolite.
Again, it's Sus Dali sculptured rock.
It takes some rigorous climbing and hiking at times,
but it's so gorgeously weird-looking.
It all has this icing of bright,
green lichen that's just wherever it's able to grow.
Yeah, and orange lichen.
And the rocks are kind of bluish sometimes,
and orangey, and even greeny.
And somehow, we've got this day with this perfect sky.
It's like...
Well, it's real nice weather.
Surreal.
The sun came out,
and we're among these really unusual rock formations.
I mean, this kind of thing doesn't occur many places.
But we've been finding those places
where the rocks are spiky and craggy,
yet rounded and layered.
They look like tall totem poles,
or, yes, I'll dare say it, peni.
There's an awful lot of penis-shaped rocks around here.
That's the easiest way to...
Really, the most accurate way to describe a lot of them.
Really pretty impressive ones, in many cases.
And, of course, others are kind of squat.
And then there's a lot of balanced rocks,
or situations where everything eroded
out from in between a pinnacle and a round rock,
and the round rock ended up sitting on top of the pinnacle.
You see, they're kind of teeterous-looking.
You're almost afraid that they'll fall down on you at this moment.
After sitting there for millions of years,
they're going to suddenly topple over.
And they could, too.
They could.
That's the way things are here at Chiricahua National Monument
for the Hour of Slack.
Praise Bob.
Praise Bob!
I ain't gonna stand up next to the mountain
And not jump it down with my hands
I'm going to something like this.
Yeah, we're going to something like this.
I want this to be one of my homes.
So we can always be gazing at a hoodoo there
and look down at the ground and find these objects,
the art that are made prettier than anybody could ever make anything.
How can God make this?
How can God make this so beautiful?
It's just...
That's what the lady asked us at Bryce Canyon at dawn.
How can God make this so beautiful?
Have a hot dog!
I ate only yesterday.
This isn't an apple, you dummy!
It's a hot dog!
Hot dog!
Don't touch that, Jimmy.
You never know what Mr. Fig has up his sleeve.
Come on.
What's the matter with you folks?
How often does a tree offer you a hot dog?
Three things working against us, or four, or a hundred.
The air is thin.
We're at 7,000 feet almost.
And we're not used to that.
And...
We're old.
And we've...
This is the third really big, long, steep trail we've hiked in three days.
And I have vertigo.
And we didn't quite get enough sleep.
However, it's worth it.
We got down in there.
And we're going to get back out of there.
That's the hard part, actually.
I had a bad case of baptasia before I left on the trip.
It slowed us down.
I had to stop real frequently.
Every ten minutes, look for a rest area.
We came to a rest stop.
The Texas something rest stop.
Just outside of Chiricahua.
Texas Canyon.
Texas Canyon rest stop.
And these rocks out here are as good as the damn canyon.
They're just spectacular.
Somebody just fled.
They just flushed them.
Right by the phone.
Oh, they wrecked my soul.
Damn.
What was Reverend Stein?
He was boding the benefits of the mute button on his cell phone.
Then he got where it was.
WCSB Cleveland, flushing your time down the toilet since 1976.
Do you need to wear a mood ring when you make that flushing sound?
You couldn't even tell I was gone.
Or going.
I was going.
And yet you couldn't tell.
Well, I assume that there's a reason why you're not going.
There's a lot of extra meditation going on.
And extra medication, too.
That's what I said.
Some of these people actually use this as a sort of chemical tool to attain some sort
of higher consciousness.
Kind of like sniffing woo-ha or whatever it's called in South America.
It's good for toilet training.
You can use subgenius radio for toilet training.
Only the elder class can do that.
I know it worked for bleepo, Abernathy, me, Philo.
We've all used it.
All of us parental breeder types.
Yeah.
I'm an evolutionary dead end myself.
Me, too.
I mean, right at this moment, anyway.
No, you're not.
Dave has children all over the world.
Do you?
No, Dave.
No, I thought you said Philo or you have children all over the world, meaning you've impregnated
a lot of accordions.
We do.
We have kids all over the world.
That's what I want my super-
Mother Earth herself.
She's impregnated his one more children.
For y'all have knocked her up.
I'll knock her up.
It's a group effort.
I'll knock her up there.
I'll knock her up around here.
Is Al there?
I'll knock her up.
I'm out there.
Get me out of here.
Where's the boxer shorts on my head?
Hey, Red.
We dug your mud up.
Stop calling me by that.
We're on primetime.
Oh, no, we're not.
That's right.
It's primetime on the West Coast, but this show, of course, is not quite ready for primetime.
Hey, Red, we don't yet.
This show is not even ready for primetime, if you ask me.
This show is often populated by mad baboons who call in to bother you, to perplex you.
Here we are.
Sometimes you repair them silently and with great delft.
And other times, they keep talking about weird stuff.
Where's my father?
You know, it's so fun to be able to hang up on people.
They're talking about you, Dave.
Where's my father?
Did you see Hugo?
I've been, I wrote, it's on my list of things to do.
In 3D, it's circled.
Ah.
Yeah, that was good in 3D.
I don't know if it's playing anymore in 3D.
Yeah, well, it is.
The Grand Lake, which I intend to go see someday, someday.
I know nothing.
I'm not going to go see something that's in the can while I'm out on the...
In the can.
Yes.
I've been inside the cans of many state parks now.
I've been taking photographs.
Yeah.
You know, some states have much better funding than others, I can tell you that.
I had a dream once, years ago, when Father and I were driving around aimlessly for various reasons,
of doing all of the bathrooms, you know, early, early net web thing, you know,
and I thought it was a unique idea.
We're doing...
News of all the bathrooms we have, all those rest stop places, and just...
And early GPS, you know, put that in.
And now there are 20 of those websites, at least, right here in my mind.
Well, I...
Someone pointed out that Pulp Fiction had a lot of people going to the bathroom and coming out of the bathroom.
Oh, okay.
It was usually John Travolta.
Yeah.
There's not often that in the movies.
I've also heard mentioned that Stanley Kubrick's movies always have...
A bathroom scene.
I'm sorry, 2001.
And The Shining.
Yeah.
Yeah, if you think about it.
2001.
And...
Mark Rickhorns.
Bathrooms.
The Shining.
What's the last one he did?
The one he did?
The one he...
Eyes shut.
Yeah, Eyes Shut, Riley.
Yeah.
But Hal and I went on for about half a show once, trying to figure out why we liked it.
I did.
I don't know why.
What about Paths of Glory?
No bath...
Yeah, probably.
Probably.
I don't know.
1957 or something.
Yeah.
Of course, we don't know.
We have to check that in the unknown pile right now.
How come subgenius shows turn into film history shows for 20 minutes every time?
Because instead of having a life, we all watch movies forever.
Yeah.
Old movies.
My latest location I have to go visit is Goblin State Park in Green River, Utah.
I saw it in Galaxy Quest.
Yeah.
I was thinking, now, some of this is painted in, but some of this is real.
Yeah, but it's real.
Yeah.
It's on those real rocks.
On the big old round golf ball rocks.
Yeah.
I heard it.
Alien land.
That and Alabama Hills.
You got everything.
Is that where Kurt bought the Gorn?
What?
No, that's at Vasquez Rocks, and I was there almost...
Bob Dobbs was almost busted there a month ago, but I don't want to tell that story anymore.
Yeah.
No, you told that story on the last two shows.
The old blind box.
The last five shows, yeah.
Vasquez Rocks is where they...
Where Kirk walked and fought the Gorn.
Maybe.
And we're planning...
That's where Bob got it.
Yeah.
The dinosaurs were shot with music in there.
And they did some catch-up parts of Jesus Christ Superstar there.
Most of it's filmed in Negev, but they're...
Or in...
Yeah, in Palestine.
They run over to Vasquez for a quick...
Sometimes you got to do those extra shots, yeah.
Vasquez had a little Gorn action figure when I was a kid.
Wow.
How much, man?
It'd be worth something now if I had it still.
No, I'm not going to say that.
It had to be explained to me two or three years ago what a Gorn was because I had forgotten.
Me too.
I was such a bad nerd that I'd forgotten the Star Trek character of the Gorn and how stupid-looking it was.
Really?
I understand the modern-day version is all ugly and...
In fact, there is one in that movie.
There's a Gorn in that modern-day Star Wars remake.
The Gorn was a lizard-headed costume man.
Oh, yeah.
In like the fourth episode or something.
Yeah.
And it was really terrible.
Terrible costume.
Lizard-head man.
That was what made him so famous.
I didn't notice him because I'm always looking for the fake caves made out of real nice thick aluminum.
Black-painted aluminum they have in Hollywood.
You couldn't see that when I was 12 years old.
But now you can see that.
You can see what everything is made of.
On Day Job Orchestra.
He's running around with a very phallic stalactite.
There's a devil in the dark.
I don't remember.
Yes.
There's phallic stalactites everywhere.
That'd be a good band name, Phallic Stalactite.
The Petrified Penis Forest.
There was a place that was like that.
It's called the City of Rocks.
It looked like pagans had spent millennia carving giant phallic symbols in the rock.
But actually, they were all natural.
What about that spooky forest that everyone goes to?
Just to kill themselves in Japan.
Yeah.
I don't want to go there, man.
Suicide forest.
I don't want to have X-Day there again.
It was a bad place to have X-Day.
We didn't make any money either.
You could go to it on Google.
You know, just drive in.
You can do anything on Google now.
You can go places on Google.
Except as long as it's not real.
I've been doing both.
I'll Google a place and then I'll go to the place.
The Puzzling Evidence Show.
Then I'll Google it again.
I'm just so sad.
Then I'll gargle it.
Very sad now.
Why is that?
Because no queen of UFOs has come.
I think we lost UFOs this fall in the city.
It happens Scott Bakula fighting a Gorn.
Is that Rocknar?
It is.
Rocknar's the one who had to explain to me what a Gorn was again.
I agree.
Because he was selling a t-shirt for Mac.
And I honestly had been so far from Captain Kirk and Spock that I'd forgotten.
Yeah.
But I'm trying to relearn everything.
The CGI Gorn that they had in the Enterprise episode.
Right.
Oh, okay.
Well, Rocknar, I want to tell you.
I don't think Gorn.
Gorn porn.
Now you're talking, man.
Now, see, up until this point, I was thinking this is pretty nerdy.
I don't know.
Gorn porn.
They're reptilians, right?
And they're really slow.
The Gorns are reptilian creatures.
Yeah, they're like sleazestacks.
They're like doing it.
Yeah, like doing it with a dinosaur.
Yeah, they're really slow.
A sleazestack.
Yeah, yeah.
They're really slow.
Super slow.
They have dual peni reptiles do.
I don't know about dinosaurs.
They may be different.
They're not reptiles.
But neither are Gorns aren't dinosaurs either.
They're different.
They're from another.
Would a Gorn porn eventually end in a snub film?
Why, yes, it would.
Everything.
Everything would end in a snub film.
I'm surprised Hal's not listening and trying to call in right now.
As Dr. Leguim said, nobody's biography has a happy ending.
Yeah, especially the Autobot movie.
I'm dying.
The kind that goes on is.
And they lived happily ever after.
After forever and ever, those are my favorite kind of endings.
They live forever in a century of bliss and then a decade and then another century and
then at the end of the say, you get into these movies that have touched me.
No matter if it's every single market.
I would like to keep hearing the same president employment space.
From in.
Are you printing this out?
Open the bathroom door, please, Hal.
The script's printed like 30 seconds before we get there.
Open, Hal, the bathroom door.
Quick.
I can't do that, Dave.
It's stuck.
Can't take it.
Must reach.
Oxygen switch.
Toilet.
Paper.
Must talk like William Shatner.
The History Channel presents Rest Stocks of America.
With your hosts, Dr. Philo Drummond, Buzzing Evidence, and Reverend Ivan Stagg.
I'll tell you about the best restrooms on your drive across America.
The best public restrooms you can get to, and the best private restrooms that are sometimes hard to get to,
but just as rewarding in those times of trouble,
when the nature's call is most urgent.
What about rest stops?
My favorite rest stop is in Arizona, and it's called Texas Valley.
It's just past Wilcox, Arizona, near Chiricahua National Park,
and that rest stop is as cool-looking as the $5 National Park.
Huh.
Not that I would discourage people from...
We're partying our national parks, but...
Who owns it?
The state of Arizona, I suppose.
The rocks around it were beckoning me, but we basically just stopped for the rest stop.
Yeah.
But it's the most scenic rest stop I've ever seen.
I was going to say, that's what's cool about Arizona and Mexico.
And well kept.
There's the rest stop.
When we got to California, the first rest stop we came to was closed.
And I thought, man, this is a bad sign.
Yep.
If they're closed all the way to L.A., then we'll know.
The government is collapsing.
But the next one was open.
Not for long.
And there were signs everywhere saying, if you see anyone smoking, call this number.
Be a fink for America!
Report smoking in national parks and rest stops.
I understand fire danger.
Only you can prevent forest fires.
Yeah, I'm not sure if it's that as much as just the encouragement of finkery.
The Junior Slacks Squad, when we take our campers out into the forest, we've always taught
them how to put their forest fires out when they were finished.
It's not out until you can lower your belly under the cold, wet ashes.
When they were finished warming themselves on the forest fire they'd set, we always tried
to teach them how to put the forest fire out if they had time, before they had to go back
to civilization.
Turn in your parents.
And some sort of Jack Chickian nightmare.
Whoa.
Clean up your forest fire, boys.
Stir, I want you to stir that forest two times.
Report your neighbor.
Report your friends.
Remember, Smokey the Bear says, only you can turn in your neighbor.
Oh, only me?
I'm under all this pressure.
Oh, thank God.
It was a nightmare about the communist takeover of America.
Actually, Smokey the Bear didn't actually say that himself.
Those words were put into his mouth by a marketing PR firm.
Smokey was exploited.
The only bipedal, fully bipedal clothes wearing bear.
Yogi was just a legend.
But Smokey was real, and they used him.
They took him to the forest.
They took him to government laboratories in the desert and programmed him to talk about
forest fires.
Poor Smokey.
I hear some noodling going on there.
What did they do to you, Smokey?
The thing is over there.
The thing.
Have you seen the thing?
Souvenir jewelry.
Thing.
But we're going to skip the thing, because I know all about the thing.
And here's the thing.
We don't even want to see the thing.
I know all about the thing.
Maybe she has the thing that I was looking for.
I was looking for a thing.
The thing, can you take it?
Can I take it?
Yes, you must.
The thing from the tree.
the abyss. Speaking
of the thing, you know, I drove
here from
Cleveland Bluffs, Ohio.
And on I-10, I saw
billboards saying, do you
dare to see the thing?
I didn't even know that thing was around
anymore. Well, it's maybe a different
thing. There was a thing
that I saw as a youth
that was a
mistreated chimpanzee.
Oh, really? I thought it was
a mummy.
I suspect
that this particular thing is
more probably a mummy or
something because that chimpanzee
must be dead by now.
It was half dead when I saw it. You're not talking about John
Carpenter's the thing. No.
I'm talking about the thing. No, we're talking about the thing
in Arizona. Can you take it?
The thing, next six
exits. The thing,
fresh cherry cider for sale.
Yeah, we chose not to
pull over and see the thing for the simple
reason that it was on the wrong side.
Well, I have to tell a story now
about the thing.
We went to the thing to see the thing.
What was the thing?
The problem with going to see the thing
is that you have to sign a document
that you won't say what the thing is
under penalty of death.
Really? That's the...
They have like the thing...
They've got the thing police.
We'll just start, we'll change it, we'll quit
saying what old Seapaw is. We should do that.
And make people sign a statement
saying, I
accept whatever happens to me, even at the...
If I'm attacked
by the thing, which we do not name.
And I will not name the...
It's like that Fight Club rule
that everybody knows about.
Who does take one subgenius every X day.
There's always one less subgenius
that paid to come in.
That's like that Fight Club rule.
They should be glad we're coming.
Yes, you do not talk about Fight Club, etc., etc.,
Fight Club, etc.
Yeah, the first rule is the same as the
second rule.
The third rule is
if C rule number one and two...
That's sort of a Tarantino-esque, really.
Dr. Drummond, for some reason
your normally piercing voice
doesn't seem to be coming through like it does...
It's coming through for me.
It's because I'm so tired
and worn out over the tough...
Perhaps you should adjust your level.
...the tough work I had to do today,
conspiring...
Reverend Stang, adjust your level
and you will hear Philo and Incense around
and Regiscope.
Today I had a particularly...
I had a particularly...
egregious, tiring day
being a liaison with the conspiracy
that I am for the church.
Dad had a bad day at work.
I have to go back into the conspiracy,
the bucket, the gut of the conspiracy.
He must burrow into the bowels
of the conspiracy.
I dive into the maw
and then I slither down the throat
into the very bowels of the conspiracy.
Now I wish I hadn't pushed him up close
to the mic because he's popping every beat.
Please do not pop.
That microphone pop.
We expect better out of our visitors
to the Ask Dr. Howell.
So let's speak with utmost delicacy
and circumspection.
You don't need to drool on my...
There is no screen between our abilities
and what we articulate.
I won't pop.
No popping and pipping.
Boy, I wish I knew how to take this one off.
I'd put it on yours
and then you'd be all right.
Dr. Howell's microphone
does have a special windscreen.
Would it even fit
on that old broken beat-up thing?
No, it won't.
It's made for that.
I don't think I will.
You have the good mic just accepted.
Yes, I have the good mic
and you have the bad mic
and I'll be in Scotland before you.
Mike Smith was the bad mic.
And me and my true love,
we'll never meet again
on the bonnie, bonnie banks
of Lake Potawatomi.
I think it's a blown backer.
A broke back.
A brownback spider or like Sam Brownback?
Right.
Sam Brownbacker, 960.
It's always in the 9 series.
Have you noticed that about me?
I have a question for us, Dr. Howell.
What are you guys talking about?
What are we talking about, Dr. Howell?
Well, you know, the Confederates
sometimes were known as butternuts.
Also, they were known as brownbacks.
What?
Those who broke away from the Union
by the soldiers in a loose argot of colloquialism.
Some of them were known as mud bellies.
They were called graybacks also,
which is more understandable than brownbacks.
Anyway, it is all...
Some of them were known as lard eaters.
They didn't tell that to us southern boys.
We didn't ever...
They'd make a large sandwich using lard as bread.
What did you hear the men were?
They were called...
Lard busters.
Really?
Heroes.
Heroes, of course.
The Confederates.
The...
Yeah, heroes.
Out of Texas.
Well, it is all within the unknowable world of Allah.
Only he knows.
For none but Allah can tell.
And I saw a documentary on the making of The Thing.
No!
Which The Thing?
Uh, the 1982 or 83 one with John Carpenter.
Uh...
Okay, because I...
As we were driving down Highway 10 out here,
I kept seeing billboards to...
Do you dare to see The Thing?
Oh, yes.
That's a different...
How could I...
The Thing seemed to be a gift shop.
How would you like a kick?
It was on the other side of the highway,
so we didn't pull over, but...
The Thing.
Can you take it?
How would you like a kick?
Well, can you take it now that you've seen it?
Um...
Uh, maybe.
I may have mentioned this last week,
but one time when I was a kid,
my family...
My family stopped on the highway to see The Thing,
and it was an abused, aged chimpanzee.
Where's my father?
A hairless chimpanzee that picked all its own...
scratched all its own hair off and lived in insanity.
Oh.
Yeah, oh, it was awful.
That was The Thing.
And I don't think anyone dares to see that thing anymore,
because...
You know where that was, Phineas?
It was like 50 cents then,
but I'm talking about in the middle of the previous century.
You know what highway that was, Phineas?
666?
Yep.
Uh-huh.
Lucky guess.
Yep.
The Thing.
The Thing ones I saw were all on highway, uh, Interstate 10.
Dr. Hall was familiar with it.
He knew about the Interstate 10 Thing.
He said that one is a mummy.
The one I saw was a live, abused chimpanzee,
and the one he saw was a mummy.
Ah.
Bill, there's also a mummy in Portland that's kind of a thing.
Down by the court in Portland, there's a museum of Goldado with a cool...
No, it's a prospector mummy, I think.
Is it near the Mystery Hole?
Uh, it's in the same town as the Mystery Hole.
Have you been to the Mystery Hole?
I've been to the Mystery Hole.
Man.
Did you get the vapors of encouragement?
There was the vapors of enthusiasm.
You got a little jar of these vapors, and you signed the liability thing before you went down into the Mystery Hole.
And then it was...
It's like the whole world got tinier and tinier as you went down the ladder.
Yeah, I like that.
To the point where you couldn't even use the ladder, it got so tiny.
And there were tiny doors at the bottom with tiny things on the other side of the tiny door.
Thing one and thing two.
I just remember everything being really tiny.
Yeah. Well, but do you remember everything?
Do you remember all the things?
No, I don't. That's the weird thing about it. I just...
Why? Things? See?
It's one of those thing things.
That's right.
Well, doctors, I shall bid you adieu.
Adieu.
I should...
Bid you a doo-doo.
A doo-doo.
Oui, oui.
Monsignor.
A doo-doo.
Keep up the good work and...
Do you know who shot Liberty Valance?
No, I don't.
The man.
Well, that's...
It was the man who shot Liberty Valance.
If anybody can actually successfully answer the question of the night, who shot Liberty Valance, please call us now at 510-846-8508.
We'll save the answer.
Alfredo Garcia.
Was that a porno movie?
Yeah.
Al Qaeda, Garcia.
See, there's the porno movie. There's a porno title in there somewhere.
Yeah, there is.
Yeah, get the head of...
Al Qaeda, Garcia.
Like Machete versus Osama Bin Laden.
Porno movie.
I've heard it said and it makes me fret America has a fascist threat.
Which organization can it be?
This is what perplexes me.
So I think I'll take a little quiz.
And find out just what fascism is
Though some may think that it's extreme
To find out what words really mean
It has a party rather small
That seeks to rule and govern all
A single leader whom they say
Everybody must obey
Destroy the government with lies
Seize control and centralize
Very shortly you will see
A fascist state monopoly
Although we've used the fascist name
Communism is just the same
It's plain to see these two are twins
And freedom dies
If either wins
One billion conquered should reveal
The danger that is very real
The greatest fascist threat you see
Is the communist conspiracy
So rally now to freedom's call
Unafraid we'll stand up tall
With faith and courage we will find
Peace-souring for all mankind
That interesting little bit was by Janet Green
called Fascist Threat
thanks to Greg Bishop
who also donated the podcast
hot dog tree clip from some Herschel Gordon Lewis production.
Thanks to Reverend Royal Decapitator,
not to be confused with Tator Gumfries,
for some of the collages.
Thanks to Puzzling Evidence Show, KPFA,
Ask Dr. Howell, Radio Valencia,
Radio Synesthesia on WCSV,
and the National Park Systems.
The background music is the Swingin' Love Corpses,
Deadly Swill.
This is our Slack number 1360
from the Church of the Subgenius,
as seen and stashed on subgenius.com.
Praise Bob, and also praise Princess We Are Doe.
My wife sees faces in everything,
smiling faces,
and sometimes tell lies.
And so ends the famous story.
Listen in again next week to...
Sire, there is no more money.
We gotta get some money.
That dirty purgish harker backflag
Wharton, Phillip, Buck, and Burton,
Perkaluma, Burton, Burton,
Buston, Idaho.
Whoa!
Friends, we're glad you listened to this show,
and we're even more glad that some listeners
have donated enough to help us keep on going
for another couple of months.
Not just this show, but subgenius.com
and all the other archive sites.
But if you truly love Bob,
and want some of that Slack back to rebound to you,
you should go to subgenius.com front page,
or especially the radio page,
or the catalog store pages,
and help out financially as best you can.
Now, we know what it's like to be on the brink of total poverty,
and we don't want any subgeniuses
to make their own situations worse.
But some of you still have jobs.
Even five bucks makes a big difference,
even if it's only once a month,
from enough of you.
Fifty bucks makes an even bigger difference.
All we're saying is that
blowjobs could go the way of Steve jobs,
if you don't pay Dobbs.
We also take checks and money orders to
Subgenius Foundation.
P.O. Box 181-417
Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118
Thanks for anything you can do to help let there be Slack.
perimeter
the
little house
Ryan
I start
by
right now
well.
how do you pal?
Green pills!
Kill me!