Friends, I have to tell you about Crime Fighters on the Net.
To catch a thief, follow the money.
That idea has served as a guide for crime fighters throughout the years.
Today, crime fighters also follow the money on the Internet.
As business transactions on the Internet have grown, so have the number of scams and schemes.
That's why the U.S. Postal Inspectors have joined the effort to stamp out Internet fraud.
For more information, including tips on how to avoid online schemes, visit www.usps.com.
Friends, you're listening to WCSB.
WC.
99.3 FM.
Me, me, me, me, me, me, me.
And it's pledge, pledgey.
What the hell do you think you're doing?
Pledgey drive time.
Repent.
Quit your job.
The world ends tomorrow.
When you may die.
Well, no, probably not, but whatever you do, just keep listening.
The Church of the Subgenius could save your sanity with...
Are we controlled by secret forces?
Do you ever get that?
The feeling that free will is a joke?
Do people think you're strange?
Do you?
Now, at last, the step-by-step process is revealed.
This is it.
The only faith that promises action, thrill, success in sex and business.
Get all your slack and more.
The Subgenius.
And this is it.
This is.
Let's talk a little bit about Ivan.
Again, right smack dab in the center.
And very, very healthy looking.
Again, you can see very symmetric, good outflow here.
The center of circulation very evident.
Ivan pummeled Grenade.
Flattening homes and cutting power.
At least 15 deaths are being blamed.
Lamed on Ivan.
We need you to watch it along with us.
Right now, Ivan is headed for Jamaica and then Cuba with the latest details.
Hi, Dr. Joe.
Hi.
So Ivan is indeed a monster.
Suddenly, oh, well, there's not enough bandwidth.
We have a new concern.
It is a wet mess in Cleveland, Ohio, thanks to Ivan.
There's the area of uncertainty right there.
Vivian?
And, of course, by then, Carl will be watching Ivan.
But here's a closer view of Ivan.
And you can see right here, and you notice it is in the middle of the central dense.
That's an indication that this is a very, very organized Ivan.
And they know that our one-world religion is the only antidote for the one-world advertiser.
Ivan, here is Ivan right now.
Down with the quote-less Bob and up with Bob and up with Bob.
We'll be watching Ivan.
No, we're here.
And we'll keep you posted every day on the progress of Ivan.
Ivan struck the Windward Islands with deadly force yesterday.
Ivan tore off roofs, knocked trees into power lines, and blew down streetlights.
At this point in time, is it more likely than not that Ivan will affect the U.S.?
Actually, what time is it?
But at that point, Ivan affected the U.S.
Well, this was the original master tape.
No, that's Doug Wellman.
It's a tape.
It is a tape.
It was a tape.
It's a tapeworm.
It's a tapeworm reminding people of things.
It reminds me of the days when we made shows with tape.
Uh, yes.
What about the days before tape?
When we made shows with little tin cans wrapped with rubber bands and little pinky fingers from the children we hated.
I don't remember those days.
Well, we never had to pledge ourselves or...
We never had to.
We...
Oh, sorry.
I never pledged to my daddy.
I pledged to my daddy.
And I pledged to WCSB four times in the last, uh, what was it?
Three and a half hours?
But anyway, this is pledge week here at, uh, at Nostril Basement.
It sounds very nostril here, doesn't it?
Yeah.
Well, that's because the background music isn't on.
I think it's because the nasal tones of the...
Oh, here it is.
...the cadences and so forth.
No, no, except with...
I have to mix this.
I'll mix it in this little hollow skull.
Now, we feel the power.
Yes.
The power of the station.
Ah, the skull is smoking.
And the pills.
Well, it's trying to cut down, but it's still smoking.
And the gods.
And the bobs.
And...
And the girls.
And the archons with large memories.
And large vagaries.
And large ovulants.
And the gun.
And the map.
Now, um, yes, it is, in fact, pledge drive time, my friends.
And I've got the option of, uh...
Uh...
Of, uh, playing this real nice and easy.
Friendly.
Yeah.
We can do this the easy way.
We can do it the hard way.
We can do it the tough way.
And, uh...
Wait a minute.
Who's gonna be...
The way would be for you to go ahead and start calling.
And what are those, uh, numbers?
I'm probably the least...
Wait a minute.
Who's gonna be good...
Prepared, um...
Who's gonna be good frop and who's gonna be bad frop in this, uh, you know, pledge shakedown?
Well, that depends on what the background music is doing.
Oh, you mean that I might just be, like, bad frop immediately?
You know, like, threaten your life and so forth?
And you go, hey, man, I'll get you off easy.
See?
Your dad knows my dad who knows somebody who knows somebody, you see?
And then you can, uh, well, you know...
Hey, what is the number to call?
687.
6900.
Yes, that's...
That's the pledge line.
Yeah, Dave, how could you forget?
Because I can always forget.
Um...
Because memory is so painful.
Oh, there we go.
There we go.
Not today.
I'm emotional loss.
But it's...
Just painful to me.
Who do we have to thank there?
Are you manning the phones?
Or is Princess Wee helping you?
Princess Wee's manning the phones.
I've done my duty for the day.
All right.
Yeah.
The duty has been done.
There's more duty to do.
687.
Friends, you have the chance to talk to...
The duty is still being needed.
I mean, it's still being needed.
A real...
The duty is...
Princess.
A bass.
Listen.
And do as I do.
By calling in the Cleveland area code, 216-687-6900 to call.
And why should you do a thing like that?
Of course, I'm going to be...
You could ask me, Reverend Stingy.
We'll be talking about all the wonderful WCSB Radiothon extras that you get.
As if you really needed to be bribed with those.
And I suppose they help.
And, you know, I have...
Don't be subgenius if you pledge to this show.
This shirt looks cool as hell, too, by the way.
You might as well add in your adenoidal voice.
It looks cool as hell.
Well, I mean, it's...
Cool as heaven.
And for these unradical times, look.
It's an old poster of some radical thing.
You know, some, you know, trouncing the imperialist type thing.
Yes, friends.
The new WCSB t-shirt does have a sort of a...
The little guy beating Goliath.
The working stiff paper boy planting his flag in the gut of the capitalist with his top hat.
And his big fat gut.
Yes, imperialism.
And his money belt.
And his...
And the flag he is planting in that fat man's gut is the WCSB flag.
That's right.
Revolutionary flag.
For a revolutionary time such a thing emerge.
I don't know.
It could possibly happen.
Do you think that if WCSB manages to get the money, the funds, and the funding it needs,
that we can continue our underground activities?
Could we...
We could at least continue to try...
To defeat the conspiracy.
To at least perhaps tie the shoelaces of the colossus together.
But we only have lowly basement with no fax machine, no computer.
We have no phone lines.
We only have one cell phone.
That's true, comrade.
What can we do?
It's double plus on good here in the times of now.
We have rickety old typewriter.
It's manual and it's long, very long keys and so forth.
It's...
We...
The station is done.
We've worked hard.
And we've come a long way over the years.
But it's still overrun with monsters.
Wind blows through the window.
The cold Arctic air from Siberia blowing through the windows.
And friends, it just costs.
I mean, just to keep broadcasting.
Now, you may think to yourself,
Well, isn't that a university station?
Don't those rich parents of those state school students...
Don't the puppets of the state of Ohio take care of this puppet show?
Actually, friends,
if that was true,
you wouldn't be listening to a couple of old codgers
like Lonesome Cowboy Dave
and yours truly, Reverend Ivan Stanton.
No, you wouldn't be listening to some ignorant students.
But this radio station...
They're never ignorant if they go to Cleveland State.
Even if they are.
I mean, come on.
We can't pledge our loyalty in our feet.
Maybe I should put something besides this Wolfman music on.
It sounds like the Wolfman is trying to eat the pledge people
that are trying to call or something.
Yeah, that's going to scare them.
And I wouldn't...
Since that's 687-6900.
And that's not a joke.
A number.
I know some of you young fellas are going,
Oh, yeah, 69.
Doesn't that mean something nasty?
Isn't that something cool or bad?
But if you pledge $69...
That I'm supposed to know about?
I'll try the amino acids new album.
You won't hear this anymore.
If you were to pledge $69,
you'd get a green hooded sweatshirt with a...
Zipper.
You know what I'm saying?
Actually, friends,
if you pledge over...
If you pledge, like, say, the $60,
not only would you get the green hooded sweatshirt with a zipper,
but I'm going to throw in a subgenius premium,
which is the Arise DVD video.
Yes, the video.
We have several videos that we've done,
but I figure I could throw in the new
Dobs of Deliastis music videos,
or perhaps the old As They See Bob,
which is the...
The Conspiracy News Reports on Church of the Subgenius
over the last 25 years.
But I think Arise, our hit video
that they film threat called,
one of the 10 must-have underground films,
Arise, the subgenius recruitment film,
the video,
is yours when you pledge.
So call that number and pledge that $60 pledge.
That's 687-6900.
Now, this is not some joke.
This is not part of your subgenius silly joke
underground humor.
This is for real.
This is not only not a joke,
but if you act now,
you have only from 9 o'clock right now,
it's 9.15 right now,
but if you must act now before 10 o'clock,
if you want to get the subgenius materials
along with your logo-headed sweatshipper
and your black or blue logo grease shirt,
also the four shot and red-eye glasses...
I better write down what I'm...
promising these pledgers.
Now, with a $60 pledge,
a $69 pledge,
a sexual pledge,
you get a green-hooded sweatshirt with a zipper.
The sex pledge.
I don't know if they come separately
or if the zipper is on the green-hooded sweatshirt,
but it's green, man,
and that's all you gotta know.
That's proper special, man.
For six more bucks than this $69.99,
you get a $75 pledge,
which gets you a black-hooded sweatshirt with zipper,
plus...
I don't know.
I think some other stuff.
Now, for $25, friends,
not only would you get that baseball cap,
that knitwear hat,
that four shot glasses,
the 2004 design shirt,
or the 2004 design tote bag,
which, friends,
that's a mighty scrote of a tote bag.
You can carry heads in there,
chopped off,
human peak heads.
You can carry bowling balls and laptops
at the same time,
and that scrote bag,
that WCSB perfect scrote bag,
similar to the subgenius scrote bag
that you can get on Cafe Press also, I bet.
I wouldn't be surprised if it wasn't the same thing.
But you remember, you have to act
before the hour of 10 o'clock
because everything reverts back to Radiothon original time,
which means that you can,
for one $15 pledge,
you could get a glass ashtray,
a mugged coffee maker,
or a black-and-white 2001 shirt.
Now, I don't really know
what some of these things are,
I'm kind of new on the job here at WPSZ,
or WCS, at WCSB,
but that is, sounds like a health of a bargaining.
It is a health of a bargaining, friends,
and we will throw in,
if you pledge to this show,
the Hour of Slack,
specific, be quiet, Dave,
if you pledge specifically
to the Hour of Slack,
friends,
the triple X rated
special internet only
Hour of Slack CD
will be available.
It will be yours.
That's right.
You pledge $25 to this show.
To this show, call 687-6900
and you will get that subgenius
triple X rated Hour of Slack.
It's a special Hour of Slack
that only the internet people get to hear
because it's so filthy and raunchy
and has such wonderful prank calls
from our collections.
That's, well, friends,
that's what you get.
And for your $15 pledge, friends,
I will throw in the Bob sticker.
The J.R. Bob Dobbs authorized,
the portrait that you've seen tattooed
onto people's faces and backs
and scarred into their arms.
And it's the coolest
upcoming world religion.
Take mind control cult
that you will ever get your brain
and hands on or your ears wrapped around.
So have at it, man.
This is the tops.
This is the very tops of a mind control cult.
If you want to join now,
that's a different story.
But what we're saying here is
we want you to support
with your tiny little emaciated fingers
and your strange looking mouth
that has like only,
only four teeth left
and those big chunks of brain
hanging out of your eye.
We want you still to support WCSB
because no one else is going to.
You think our government's going to take it?
You think your family cares about it?
No, they don't care about you or the state.
You wouldn't be listening to this
if you weren't a loser.
The first thing you want to lose
is $15 for an Anthony Ask Glass tray,
a coffee mug,
or a black and white shirt.
And don't forget the Bob sticker.
The J.R. Bob.
And this isn't just a paper sticker.
This is a vinyl sticker.
You cannot.
You cannot remove this
once it's on, friend.
Now what kind of pledge now
was it for the X-rated tape staying?
I forget now.
Was that a $25?
That's the $25 pledge.
You get the X-rated Hour of Slack special
that you'll never hear on this
or any of the other stations
that broadcast Hour of Slack.
Praise those stations.
And you also get either your choice
of a regal baseball cap
with the things on it,
a knit winter hat
with a small person under it
that you have to pop out
and remove his head,
four shot glasses,
and after four shots, you're dead.
A 2004 design shirt.
There's no going to be any designs
for the rest of this year,
but this is the one.
And it looks like a proletarian
disc jockey guy
kicking somebody in the belly button,
but we won't talk about that.
And also a 2004 toker bag
for all you sleepers
and hambones
that like to prepare
for the children.
But what's in that
for $25 X-rated tape?
I mean, that is an extra bargain
that goes beyond an extra bargain.
What kind of salacious,
stuff is in there?
Prank calls.
Pranks.
Pranksters.
Some genius doctrine
about sexual matters
that can't be covered
on the public airwaves.
I think you might know
what we're talking about.
We get right into it.
I mean, we actually discussed...
We don't pussyfoot around
when we're footing on those things.
It's real.
Friends, this is real.
And this radio station
brings you real...
Well, you know the difference
between this
and maybe one or two other colleges.
There's a lot of legislations
here and there
scattered around the country.
And all the other corporate crap!
My God!
You know the difference.
I don't have to explain.
That's why you're listening.
Even though I'm doing this.
Even though this is a pledge drive,
you're still listening.
Even though you're not going
to spend a penny.
But yet, but yet,
I'm in discernment now.
I'm in the spirit.
And I can feel,
I can hear the whispering
from afar
inside the mind
of somebody who's saying,
maybe this is the time
when I'm gonna...
I mean, George Bush,
what?
One.
Kind of.
The conspiracy is rolling
over the world
like a giant steamroller.
Maybe, maybe, maybe
I could feel a little better
if I just made
the slightest effort
of making that phone call.
Heck, I could talk
to Princess We Are Doe.
She is, after all,
the queen of all the UFOs
who has lowered herself
to taking calls from mortals
at 687-6900.
You could do that
or you could just go on
with your hopelessness.
Your sad, pathetic,
go, oh, well,
I don't want to...
What can I do?
I'm just a little person.
I need that $15 for beer.
Yeah.
I need that $15
for my pornography download.
I need me another
quick jerky-darky, you know?
Oh, I need that $15.
I don't need that Bobhead sticker,
but I need that
Hootie and the Blowfish album.
They're my favorite band.
I don't need to support
this station
because I can spend
that $60 instead
on...
On spreading my feces
all over my...
On a Rolling Stones concert.
Right.
One of those balcony seats.
Sure.
I don't need...
Friends,
I'm not hearing the calls.
I'm calling for them,
but I ain't hearing them.
I ain't hearing nothing
out of you people.
Now, if that continues,
what do you think
you're going to hear
about a bus?
Nothing.
Nothing, but the constant...
Oh, yeah, nothing.
No, nothing.
They won't hear nothing.
Ready, ship.
Hey, you know how many...
How long the hour of slack
has been on,
and if it went off,
it would be your fault.
It's probably...
We've been on the air, friends.
It always is your fault
we're off on.
Since 1985.
And we've been on the air
at 9 o'clock Sunday nights
in WCSB Cleveland
for over 10 years.
10 decibels, too.
Each time,
with a zipper
and a hooded snot shirt.
And if we're not on anymore,
whose fault's it going to be?
It's going to be yours,
my friend.
It's going to be yours, snotty.
Now, here's some...
Here's a...
I'm going to play
some old Pledge Drive tapes.
This is the way
we used to do it
back in the old days.
We had...
Fire engines?
Lonesome Cowboy Dave...
We had fire engines?
...was too famous for us then.
It was before
he became a has-been.
But we had...
Here's somebody
who was once famous.
I'm going to play a tape now
of Pope Robert Anton Wilson.
Now, he's a famous philosopher.
Some of you might be impressed
by the fact
that I have this tape here.
But let's just hear this.
We're going to save
the universe.
My friends,
whether you help or not,
this time...
This time...
I don't see a single line
lighting up, friends.
Okay, look.
Last time...
Last time,
we only came in number nine
on the Pledge Drive,
and that's the truth.
We bragged too much.
We had pride.
But too much pride.
The giant fell.
Tricked and fell
on its clay feet.
So,
our one-time
naked glory has passed.
We don't expect y'all
to support us anymore.
We'll probably just fade out
into obscurity
eventually here.
It's worse than that.
Bob re-arrested again today.
No!
Yes?
It always happens to you.
How come...
I always miss these things!
He re-arrested
and he started channeling
through me.
And Bob himself,
that's J.R. Bob Dobbs,
for the benefit of those
who may have just tuned in,
Bob himself,
he told me,
that if you don't raise
$8 million this evening,
he's going to die again.
$8 million?
The listeners of this station
are so cold-hearted,
so merciless,
so lacking in religious feelings,
they're going to let Bob
die a second time?
I certainly hope not.
Hey, Fred,
you don't know our listeners,
Pope Bob.
I mean, to tell the truth,
these people would pay
to watch Bob
thrown to the Christians
while the lions watched
in the Coliseum.
Oh, yeah.
They just soon see blood.
They want to see blood.
They don't want to call
82374.
I mean,
688-788-7888.
82374-7-6900.
You can call
Quit hesitating.
Quit waiting.
Quit waiting to see
how we're doing.
We're doing great,
but we still need
every penny
because we want to
equip this station
with those same things.
Tell them what we can do
for this station,
IDNAX.
We can add
the Nebulon
super-powered radars.
That's right.
With your pledge money,
friends,
we could equip this station
and it can go into
a bad,
it will be able to
transform into battle mode
in 5.6 seconds.
And it can transform
into a battle station
that has plenty of places
to get gas.
And it'll be for free,
so you better pledge.
That's right, friends.
That's the thing.
You're getting this,
you've been getting this
for free most of the year.
That kid you're hearing
that you just heard
on that old tape,
that kid just got married
this last summer.
Last time,
only about...
Friends,
it's 687-6900.
Don't reduce us
to playing
ancient pledge drive tapes.
Because otherwise,
well,
you'll be hearing
just more of this.
And over the airwaves,
the pressure to buy,
to give,
to pledge
was relentless.
And although we've got
hundreds and thousands
that are so faithful
with God bless you,
God bless you
for your faithfulness.
Still there are
hundreds and hundreds,
maybe thousands,
who are not faithful,
who made the pledge,
who for some reason
or another haven't sent it in.
And if we count on that,
and it doesn't come in everything,
everything suffers.
We are even having a hard time
meeting the payroll right now,
and the people that we have
working for PTL
have families too.
They have bills too.
Jim Baker's running costs
exceeded $2 million a week.
That's nothing compared
to ours, friends.
This baby
that I'm holding in my hands,
this nag,
is one of the first babies
that has been saved.
His brain is constructed
in a strange way.
8-2-3-6-8-7-6-9-100.
Now listen to this,
dear friends.
8-2-3-7-4-9-0-6-8-7-6-9-100.
They call it
the buckle on the Bible Belt.
That's us.
It has the largest quota
of millionaires,
the worst crime rate,
and one of the severest
poverty rates,
in any American city.
Great spot.
Like Dallas could also
be described as...
Who understands
what this generous gift
means to me?
I've been a student
here at Cleveland
State University
for the last 73 and a half years.
I can believe that, actually.
And as a member of the...
What was I talking about?
I believe
that you're about
yours.
But not just for
this.
What were you saying, Dave?
I was saying that I was
checking in the basement
just about 25 minutes ago
and it looks like
there are a lot of people
down there trying to break doors,
smashing windows,
and trying to get in
to give this beautiful
little edifice we call
W-S-E-S-B.
Our homeland,
our homeland,
our homeland.
It's true, friends.
There have been some
who've called in.
Our homeland.
There are those who called in
and have pledged.
We've heard from
three people already.
Three?
Oh, I guess the station's
going to be...
We're going to have to
go to jail for avoiding
paying taxes
because we're going to be
taxed so much.
We're making so much money.
Oh, dearie me.
Reverend, I'm in staying good.
I'll just make one thing
perfectly dismally unclear
right now.
Can I just say,
without any form of
reservation or any other place
you could keep people
for a long time,
that I, nor the members,
and I'm not a member,
I'm just kind of dismembered
at this moment in time,
but we do not
ensure your safety.
If you perhaps send in
a $20,
a check for $20
for a baby doll shirt,
you know,
and you decide you want
to look like
one of those baby dolls
one night and something,
you know,
RTA bus actually
takes you out
for a date
or just squishes you,
it doesn't matter
because we don't
guarantee your safety.
We don't guarantee
your happiness,
but we do guarantee
your increased
listed...
I remember
they were a collector's item,
but I guess
they're the next thing.
We don't want you
to pledge your...
Friends,
you can hear Princess Wee
singing in the background
because nobody's
pledging right now.
We have had some pledgers.
We've had pledgers
for Rossich,
the Pope of all Cleveland,
Rossich,
and Bob.
Praise Bob.
And there's another one
there.
Some man has bailed us out
out there.
We've been bailed.
And the bells are ringing.
Look at the lights
of all the...
The little lights
are lighting up
all over the place.
Praise Bob.
Stop.
Whatever his name is.
Dick wants the X-rated hour.
It's like,
praise Dick,
praise Bob.
Praise Dick.
Dick and Bob
and Bev have
the best
trade night
here in Cleveland.
I'm so happy, Jim.
Could you please
hand me the envelope?
Oh, here's another one
for...
Why, it's a bag of...
It's not...
It's a bag of...
823-7490.
Oh, yeah.
That number.
A prayer.
And you'd better pray.
Dreamers.
Screamers.
When I fall asleep
you dream
I am screaming
your dreamers.
My dream is to be a dad.
You need extra
in your life.
We are going to save
the universe, dear friends.
the universe
during this pledge drive.
We have got to.
This is your and my
and everyone else's
last chance
to actually save
this universe.
I...
I want...
I want to send
my money,
but I have so little.
Will they accept
the cash
or check
or money
or the...
from a man like me?
There are so few
of us left.
It takes...
so little
to be a man
to separate oneself
from the apes,
the beasts of the field.
And yet,
how many do it?
How many
make that tiny effort?
You know,
you can have it
taken out of your...
your bank,
I'm sure,
for a little bit a month,
five bucks a month.
I bet they have
a set up for that.
You can...
you can talk.
You can give
all your numbers
and all your love
to Princess Wee,
Princess Wee Ardo,
Queen of all the UFOs.
She loves you, too.
When you call...
She likes your head
on the part of your brain
that is showing.
She loves you.
Friends,
you could do it.
Please,
687-6800,
don't make us
play the old tapes
over and over and over.
Are they...
Will they become
empowered by this?
823-7490,
and it is serious.
It is serious, friends.
Mighty serious
this time, friends.
687-6800.
I've got one hour
to convince you
how badly
we have the station.
We need your support.
Become.
We have a special,
special form
of slack
in store tonight.
Instead of us
giving you slack
for once,
you're going to
finally give some
back to us
for some of you
have been doing so
all along.
Praise Bob.
But for the rest of you,
oh, this could be
the moment of truth,
the moment at hand.
And once again,
that's 823-7490.
No, it's 687-6800,
but that's okay.
687-6800.
He loves you, Bob.
967-6900.
He has to love Bob.
6900.
He loves you, Bob.
No.
You love Bob.
You have to.
Or else what happens
if you don't love Bob?
He'll kill you.
So Bob, you out.
You have Bob, you out.
She's 23 now.
You heard it here first.
You heard it.
You don't love Bob,
you heard it here first.
Bob, you out.
You have a baby.
It's dear friends.
Only if, you know,
if it's...
You know, there's going to be
so many reverend states,
there's going to be more
than one.
There's going to be more
and more reverend states.
Get rid of them.
How many stangs
can there be in a pledge, friends?
We need that money.
I want them all gone.
687-6800.
6900.
Look at those phones.
All the stangs must be gone.
Oh, yeah.
All right.
Yes, they...
Oh, friend.
Shake it off.
Can you imagine a world
without Slack?
A world without WCSB?
A world without scrumptious
and the likes of idiotic
entertainment that you
can imagine.
You can barely understand.
Well, you can't stand it
any longer
if you don't want to put up
where you can shut up.
Now it's time to put your money
where your mouth
and other organs
that open up are.
For more info available
at www.wcsb.org,
you can find out
all you don't
and do need to know.
WCSB Radiothon.
Oh, we got beautiful items here.
I don't know why the hell
they call them items.
What's...
Ooh, items.
I've got items.
Items like the Arise
subgenius DVD,
which comes with your $60 pledge
to this marvelous station
when you call that number
687-6900.
You can't hack that
with a snot zipper,
pals and friends.
This is your once-in-a-life
time offerage
that you better make
some hay on right now,
especially if you're one of those
drizzled...
You know, one of those people
that like to put things off.
I know you can do it, man.
We know.
We're all procrastinationals,
but this is the time.
Now, if not now,
when, if not you,
who, if not when, how,
it's 687-6900.
I don't love her.
687-6900.
Call in.
Call in and feel Bob
moving in your heart, baby.
Bob loves you.
May you show him
some love back.
I want you to...
Get on that phone
and call that man, Bob.
Or that girl, princess.
We are doing 687-6900.
I don't have any men in my case.
Any other things,
items like that.
We do have a beautiful,
beautiful owl with a...
No, we don't have
a beautiful owl, do we?
We have a gray or black
small logo sweatshirt,
which will be the envy
of all the zip zappers
and the local Freon smokers
down at the head,
Liz Park,
for only $40
of a portrayal.
I mean of a pledge,
not a portrayal.
You can portray yourself
any way you want.
And I'll be reading
that number some more.
We'll take Visa.
We'll take MasterCard.
We'll take American Express.
We'll take bank drafts.
By which monthly payments
are automatically withdrawn
from your bank account.
You can call in tonight,
set it up.
You'll never have to think
again.
And of course,
a check or money order
is always so much fun.
Come,
a big Gibbs
and golly gosh
and better puke,
you'll never have to think.
You'll never repeat
on full throttle
potentate.
Elsewise,
your wants will be
wagging down
on mammy's hind nanny.
Why can't your
peezer pop a squeezer
when the gushers
are going all normal like?
Got your old
geyser sense
in your sneezing chamber,
boy?
Heist in an empty
platter in your bean bag?
Where's your
roller balls, eh?
I can't drop me
no love grow
on this
luju muju band.
You're gonna have
to spree
to English,
Jake.
Get right with
your muscle snakes,
snunk monkey.
Quit spritzing
your plizzerer,
lessen its snowing
white lute juice,
baby.
Elsewise,
your pleating
bleeder's blowing
hot water.
You go blind
or please
your neither,
trying not to.
Either way,
you're getting up
on the wrong orbit
for this kind of
free-kneading,
bleeding side trade,
eh?
Well,
won't you
stand there
like your
dammy nickel slug
or you gonna
plus your
plimfer and righteous
hargany,
P-boy?
Got weenie rivers
and fluter tubes,
don't you?
Join gumptions
with the true
and the seed brave
and pee for Bob,
man,
and send your jeans.
Buy out
the gland owners
with what you
earned
with your skinny
peeling face
of pain.
This has been
your enunciator.
Thank me.
Amen.
Well,
wonder.
Okay.
Before we thank
the enunciator,
we should thank
the callers
who've actually
pledged their sweat,
their tear,
their boiled up mustard.
Well,
then there was
the one named Bob
who said he wanted
to be billed.
No,
no,
it doesn't work that way.
We don't know.
We don't pledge to you
by sending you
the X-rated hour
of slack first
and then billing you.
No,
that's not the way
the pledge works.
You pledge to us
and then you give us
the money,
the station,
that is.
Then we give you
the swag.
See?
Yeah,
that's how it works.
So don't try and
mess with the game,
shorty or fat pants
or any other
denominical names
I might lay on you
in the next half an hour.
just think,
you have half an hour
to get right with Bob,
to get your soul right.
I am right.
You know,
you may have committed
the unpardonable sin.
You know,
what is the one
unpardonable sin?
Pull the lever,
down you go.
The sin that can
never,
ever,
uh,
be forgiven.
Well,
friends,
have you committed
that sin?
You know,
there's one way
to erase that sin
from the book of life
so that you can still
get into the escape vessel
of sex goddesses
on judgment day
and that's to
call this station
and pledge that money
right now!
Uh,
got it,
baby?
Yeah,
you hear that sound,
baby?
That's what you're
going to sound like
if you pledge
for a,
glass Anthony
or a crawfish mug
or a $2,000
sweatshirt.
Yeah,
yeah,
I can see it
in your eyes.
You're going crazy
now you're writing
out those $15
checks for a glass
ashtray,
a coffee mug,
a black and white
2001 shirt,
a $20 check
for a baby doll shirt
because you,
yeah,
baby doll,
see?
Yeah,
I can see it
in your eyes,
see,
you're the kind
of guy that like,
I can see it
matter
slash,
stained eyes.
You know,
I could play
some good music
or something
if we could get
one more caller.
Somebody just call in
and say,
look,
okay,
I'll pledge you
my money,
I'll give you
my credit card numbers,
I'll tell you everything
if you'll just
shut up and place
just one call,
687-6900,
that's all we want.
We really get to
torch from this
during pledge week.
Yeah.
We really get to,
you know,
we don't have to sit back
and listen to cool music
or somebody who actually
makes sense,
you know,
as a cutaway
or something like that.
We can just
continue to
grate their nubs down.
If they can't take a joke,
I think we know
how to handle that.
Yeah.
We know your
zip,
I think we know
what to do
if somebody can't
take a bit of a joke.
large logo sweatshirt.
Yeah,
we know what
fatty pants
you're wearing tonight.
Mr. and Mrs.
available info
at www.wcsp.org.
Log on now.
Well,
you know,
there's people
listening by internet
and I'm speaking
to those people
by internet
and there's no reason
you can't call
area code
216.
687.
6900.
There ain't no reason
you can't do that.
You listening by internet
and I know there's
some people
on that subgenius chat
IRC chat thing
right now
on channel subgenius.
They're listening
and they're talking
to each other
going,
oh,
look,
Stan's trying to get us
to get some money.
That old Stan,
everybody knows
he's rich.
He published a book
one time,
so he must be rich.
That lonesome cowboy
Dave,
he's a famous rock star.
He's rich.
Friends,
that may be so,
but we're not going
to give our money
to this station
because you don't want
a stupid preacher.
Friends,
we gave our lives
to this station,
the least,
and think of the hours
we've put in.
You know,
Dave has to drive here
from Ashtabula?
Wisconsin.
Wisconsin?
Ashtabula,
Wisconsin is not
exactly over the border,
Cuyahoga border.
You know what I'm saying?
That's right.
That's right,
my friend.
So,
why don't you,
can you not give
Reverend Stan
and Lonesome Cowboy Dave
Princess Wee
a little tip?
Call up Princess Wee.
You don't have to talk to me.
You don't have to talk to Dave.
You talk to her.
And she's waiting
by the phone right now.
But Dr. Sinister's
in there with her
waiting for you to call.
687-6900.
Their knuckles are crossed.
Their fingers are crossed.
Their legs are crossed.
Their eyes are crossed.
They're just,
we're hoping and praying.
And in fact,
we are having a vigil
right at this moment
out in the hallway.
There are thousands
of young people
with,
with candles.
There are thousands
of young people
with candles.
Look at them out there.
Part of a quest.
Some of them are saying
the Holy Hosiery
and others are just like
singing to Hosanna
and the other guys.
And others are taking out
their tiny little
plastic swords
that invert themselves
as you think
the wrong thoughts.
And plenty of you
tonight are thinking
the wrong thoughts
if you're not sending in
your glass ashtray,
coffee mug,
black or white,
2001 t-shirt,
$15 minimum pledge.
And that doesn't mean
you're going to be
thought of as a minimum person.
So what if you're
a show-off type horse
who likes to send in
$75 and gets a bunch
of subgenius stuff
plus a black hooded
sweatshirt with a zip-up?
I mean,
this is not a sale here, man.
We're not pitching goods.
But you're helping
to support
a community institution
which has more value
than all the sweat
and porous
hooded bus seats
driven sweatshirts
in the rain
you've never known.
I'm out of here.
I've got to lay down.
In my walk.
I know.
Dave, in my walk.
When I'm out in Cleveland
and I'm walking
and I'm seeing the people,
they say to me,
they say,
I recognize your voice.
Why?
Are you that one of those
lonesome cowboy Dave people?
Why?
Why I've been listening to you
since I was in high school.
Since pterodactyls
walked around here.
And of course,
that's when I always want to say,
well, we're still on.
And friends,
we are still on,
but only,
only because
of the support
of the listeners.
And so far,
to tell the honest truth,
we've only had
300 people called.
We need more like
3,000.
3,000 is the goal.
So let's keep
those phones lit up, man.
Jerry.
Put Princess Wee
and Dr. Sinister
to work, baby.
This little,
this little small
emotionally and physically,
or not physically,
but I suppose
that would be a problem.
This small,
emotionally handicraft child
has been so abused
over the years.
He's been abused
and yet,
and still,
if you just send
a small pledge now,
this there may be
research done
on how to clean out
this little baby man's ears
so he can hear cool music.
Someone can tap
a little thing on his skull
so he can actually think
when he hears
interesting,
interesting conversation.
And when,
what about the days
when we go
digging into the past?
I mean,
who does all this stuff?
I don't.
Who does this stuff?
Rush Limbaugh.
No.
It's not him.
It's WCSB.
Home of lightning and sweat.
Vinegar,
pie,
onions,
and ointment.
Your favorite things
are right here
where you're not.
Unless you pledge now,
of course.
687-6900.
Get with the cool
where it's happening scene, baby.
You don't have to believe in Bob.
You don't even have to be
in the process of killing.
Bob right now.
Not exactly.
You could be waiting
for this show
to get over with.
Well,
why don't you hurry it along
by calling 687-6900-Price-Bob.
Hey, look, Linda,
take those rubber bands
off your penis
and get on down
to the foam booth.
That's right.
And call us at 687-6900.
It's got nothing to do
with that money
and it's got nothing
to do with you.
It could be worse.
It could be a national
public radio pledge driver
or one of those channel.
What is it?
Pledge drive.
Button goes.
Something like this.
Are we going to do that one now?
Are you ready to do the NPR?
I don't know how to do them
because I haven't watched.
You said we're going to do
the NPR pledge guy.
No, you can do that.
I can't because I'm under contract.
Okay.
Well, you know,
that was a really, really great
recording of Yo-Yo Ma.
I don't think I've ever heard
anything like that in my life
and it was recorded
at the Massachusetts
Institute of Technology
Technological Basement.
I can't do the NPR bit.
That's pink.
That's crap.
That's pink crap
and that's all you're going to hear
if you don't support
your college radio stations.
by Smell-O-Smelt Bar
of Georgetown University
about how we're all growing
a little fatter and smaller
and bigger nowadays.
That was quite a story
and how about this one?
Economic progress for me report.
Well, as people make more money
and most people make less money,
the people making more money
want to send their money
to make less money
for the people making more money.
And we want you to spend your money
in the wisest way possible.
Money.
Filthy lucre.
What do you need it for?
Well, actually,
you need it for almost everything
except true slack.
pieces of fragments of lack.
Actually, you probably do need it
for true slack too,
I'm afraid,
in this world,
in this flesh,
in this devil.
But you must support
the station
which has given you
the little light shining
for all these times.
You don't run 89.3,
everything's like nothing to you.
You don't think about it.
You reach down,
you turn around,
you listen to him.
You don't say,
hey man,
where does it come from?
In this money,
Man, I've had one time
the head of the Devo fan club
said to me,
Reverend Stang,
did I ever tell you
the first time I ever heard Devo
that has changed my life
was on the hour?
And the person who runs
the Firesign Theater fan club
said, Reverend Stang,
you know,
I was just thinking about it.
I hate you
and think you're a jerk,
but yet,
it was your show
was where I first,
the only place I never would have heard
of the Firesign Theater
and that's the only thing
keeps me alive now.
And I'm alive because of you,
Reverend Stang.
Now friends,
aren't you going to pay me
for keeping those
lame losers and jerks alive?
One of them might be you.
You might be one of the
lame losers and jerks
that you're not.
Church of the Subgenius
has helped keep going
when times get rough.
You with a golden eye
might be one of the people
to come down from the volcano.
And a time for some payback, man.
Do not throw flowers
into the volcano.
Send your checks for
$50, $20, $25, $30, $40, $60, or $70
to pledge for items.
Rip it out.
I can't.
Whip it out.
Now what happened
in the olden days?
Now the same thing
is happening every day.
Bob days and Bob days
and K-N-O-N
Oh, it's not K-N-O-N anymore.
And W-C-S-B
The Bob days
and K-N-O-N
The Bob days and W-C-S-B
Today.
Bob, Bob, Bob.
Bob loves you, friends.
He loves you with the most perverse,
juicy lashes.
Bob, Bob, Bob.
Bob.
You must not fear.
Fear is the mind killer.
Fear is the little death
which brings me.
Mis amigos queridos,
Qu quiere en su vida?
Ripeza grande?
Bob, Bob, Bob.
Bob.
Conoce usted a Bob Dobbs?
It's a Bob.
Well,
after all.
It's a Bob world.
After all.
There's the float right now
and the children are singing
to the giant Bob float.
W-C-S-O-N
Underneath of the giant Bob head float
there's a huge W-C-S-B logo
stating very clearly
Fighting Corporate Radio
since, um,
what was this last week?
Oh, is that what we're doing?
Fighting Corporate Radio?
We are the enemies
of the Corporate Radio.
No.
We are the arms and legs
of the people
of the Corporate Radio.
Of the pobresitos.
Of the campesinos.
Of the people who have been
left without anything
but their eardrums.
Actually, you know,
I was bitching about how
we don't get paid for doing this
and blah, blah, woof, woof.
And somebody else said,
oh, those Corporate Radio guys,
they can't do what we do.
And they've been Dr. Sinister
that said that.
They can't do what we do.
They can't.
What is it that we do
that can or cannot be done?
But friends,
you can't hear it either
unless the station is doing it.
So call 687-6900
in the 216 area code vicinity.
Oblige point, but well made.
Friends, there is passion
left in this life.
There is reason to crawl on
up that endlessly steep hillside.
There is reason to crawl on up that
even though your fingernails
are breaking off.
Keep crawling and crawling
and crawling and crawling
And we told the way
to the post office.
They're closed.
But I didn't have a check
in my hand.
And I have the address.
Mail the check or money order.
That is after you.
Pledge, of course,
to WCSB
slash CSU Foundation
21, 21 Euclid Avenue,
comma,
MM number 209,
Cleveland, Ohio,
44115.
Thank you.
Take out your check
to WCSB slash CSU Foundation.
Call now.
687-6900.
What was that mailing address again, Dave?
Oh, okay.
Now you ask me the mailing address again.
Okay, the mailing address is
WCSB slash CSU Foundation
21, 21 Euclid Avenue,
and I know it's a comma,
MM number 209.
You can use the number sign
like on your phone
or digital rectal dismember.
Cleveland, Ohio.
Cleveland, Ohio, 44115.
And don't forget to make out your checks
to WCSB slash CSU Foundation.
Don't be fooled, friends.
It is not the foundation
you are worried about.
It is the people like Reverend Stang.
Some say he may take your money
and use it for your money.
Others say he may use it
for his bowling junkets.
for his strange Samoan headlock jokes.
I think he will give it back
to the coughing coffers
of the paralyzed students
here at beautiful WCSB.
Yes, friends.
Every week we must haul
huge mounds and sacks
and bowling ball trucks
full of tapes and CDs
up that mountain
and edit them.
We must do it.
Long into the night
with the crappiest equipment
you ever saw.
Little razor blades
and scotch tape
and Radio Shack cassette decks.
And finally, finally,
we bring it all up here.
We have to climb the exterior
of the building to get in.
And we put the show on, finally.
And friends, after that,
after all of that,
and don't we deserve something?
Well, no, you say.
No, it's a crappy show.
No, we don't.
We don't care.
No one cares.
Oh, but yes.
You might as well just jump out.
Oh, but they do care.
What?
They do care.
They do?
Yes, they've been sending money
right and left.
It's Princess We Are Doe.
There are hordes and hordes
of subgeniuses out there
just calling.
There are?
Oh, the phones are just
bouncing off the phone.
The phones are bouncing
off the phones, my friend.
off the phones.
There's so many phone calls
coming in.
Is the phone ringing now?
I don't know why.
Why, yes.
Oh!
Listen to those phones.
But mostly they call
and they want to have
phone sex with
Lonesome Cowboy Dave
and on scenes like that.
This is your chance, girls.
Yes, yes, yes.
So since he's on the phone now,
if they call now,
they can talk with Dave.
Oh, Dave.
But, you know.
Oh, yay.
Friends, where else
can you find
the oh, yay men?
Oh, yay.
Where else can you hear
tapes of Joe Offering?
Reverend Ivan Stank,
Princess Weirdo,
Lonesome Cowboy Dave,
Dr. Sinister,
and all the insane,
crazy people
at WCSB?
Why, where else?
Friends,
call that number
687-6900
or else you'll end up
listening to us
sounding like
regular DJs
for hours at a time
in between all the commercials.
Yeah.
3-7-4-9-0
We are full grown
We are grown up men
We are all past
The age of reasoning
It is our mission
It is our task
It's obvious
Yet you still ask
We are going to save the universe
We are going to save the universe.
This time.
Oh, yes, dear friends.
That's right.
We'll be saving the universe on this.
This, like I say, it's one chance.
The Swingin' Love Corpses want you to save the universe.
Robert Anton Wilson, our special celebrity guest star, wants us to save the universe.
And the Zombies for Bob here answering the phone want they desire.
Ethan, what's a couple of days?
He wants you to save the universe.
First, can I say that you sound like you're on helium in these early recordings?
Is it helium or is it nitrous oxide?
Nitrous.
No, no.
It depended.
I mean, some.
That's laughing gas, isn't it?
Or is it sleeping gas?
Nitrous oxide is laughing gas.
So do you laugh in a high chipmunk type voice?
No, laughing gas makes you say.
I really wish there was one soul per breath.
But the helium makes you talk like a.
Little funny chipmunk.
Or like a radio DJ and friend.
That's why you have to help support your community radio station.
Such as this very one.
Yes.
I feel that coalescing of power.
I feel the hands and feet of the people of Cleveland closing in on me with their little shrimpy and god damn gigantic huge ass trays and checks.
They are assembling outside with more money.
Money I've ever.
Oh, I believe we're going to make our 3000 goal in the next 25 seconds.
Oh, the phone lines are free.
So please call 216-687-6900.
Call in tonight.
This is a.
We're reaching out to the females embracing the females of G9 tonight as much as we possibly can.
Yes.
I mean, it is so ironic.
Because he these some of these false preachers can raise millions and millions of dollars.
No problem there.
Well, I tell you what I challenge you, Jim Swaggart.
I challenge you, Jim Baker.
I challenge you.
Or I challenge you.
You see this hand here.
You see this hand in front of me.
Mr. Jim Baker.
This is called the claw.
And it's got the power of dogs in it.
And a power above.
And I challenge you to show your ugly face here at this radio station and come forward.
Go ahead.
Come on.
Come forward with all your millions.
I'm ready to have a match without rules.
No rules at all.
One will survive.
One only.
One minister will leave the match still breathing.
If one of you.
One of you.
Goody, goody preachers has the guts to show up.
Yes.
I'm sitting here drinking some Texas select beer.
Beer.
You hear that, Jimmy Swaggart?
You don't drink beer.
Oh, no.
Or smoke on prop.
Because you don't know the power of that.
I'm going to show you the power of these herbs.
I challenge any minister do-gooder out there to show up.
All of you.
With all your TV shows and all your bought-off politicians, your paid-off judges.
Do any trick you want.
But I got the claw.
I got the power above.
And the power of Texas select.
And you, my friend listener, has the power to call 823-
687-6900.
I'm afraid we're going to have to tell them the real truth about this now, Stang.
Their pledge goes to support the WCF.
The WCSB slash CSU Foundation.
Well, I was using some old Texas station pledge tapes.
That's true.
For a long time, I don't know if you read the Georgetown Quarterly or any of the other
sinister type of ragazines from the Georgetown Beltway.
But the CSB, WCSB slash CSU Foundation, has a long and sordid history of providing salaciously
bizarre and unusual entertainment to a wide group of demographically-discriminating people.
So far, we're on the requisite list of have-to and have-not-do-did-done things.
It seems WCSB is not faltered in creating gigantic, huge, well, I don't want to go on
describing them, but parts, new parts for the new brain.
If you pledge now, I suppose you may grow a new brain or part of a new brain.
You may not.
The idea is this, see?
It's just as simple as all this.
If you pledge now and you don't grow a new brain and tomorrow comes around, what are
you going to do next?
That's right, Charlie.
What are you going to do next?
And if, say, tomorrow you decide you didn't after you already did, you don't send your
check to the foundation, maybe nothing's going to happen, see?
But then maybe...
I don't know.
That's why I'm here.
I'm, I don't know.
Oh, yes dear friends.
Well, we're, uh, I, I, it looks like we've, uh, well, we've helped the stations some.
We've, we've done what we can, and, uh, we've, can't do what we didn't, so.
Got more donations than I did last year.
Well, we try very hard, and I, I...
I was threatening people with, like, physical violence.
I was saying, this is a stick up.
I'm pointing a gun at the microphone.
You've got to fork it over.
Well, it doesn't even work if you point a gun at the dog's head.
They don't even care about the kitten.
That's true.
It's the abomination and the desolation of the pledge drive is what it is, man.
If I were going to start my own country, the unit of currency we'd use would be the abomination.
Well, it is in many...
It currently is.
It currently already is.
It's abominable.
No, no.
But it's the real stuff.
It's what we depend on.
It's what you depend on.
It's what you who listen here to the listless hour of slurred and some of the other fine, fine, fine, fine, fine, fine, fine, fine, fine, fine, fine.
Well, friends, we're going to thank you, those of you who called and pledged.
And we know that you will actually mail that pledge in because we have faith.
We have faith in you.
And we know that you have faith in WCSB to continue to deliver you the finest and most weirdest.
And...
Extra sensory programming.
Friends, J.R. Bob Dobbs loves you.
Well, sort of in a general way.
Actually, he doesn't care that much about you.
And I don't really either personally.
But...
But in a general and sort of noble, altruistic way, we, everyone here at the station, thanks you.
And we'll continue to do our best.
And now...
Uh...
This.
WCSB, Cleveland.
The project was finished.
The ship would hold 20.
The power source was anything a crew would think was funny.
We didn't need the slack list.
They're hapless.
Our moves proved its worth in escaping the stark fist.
On our way to Planet X for sex that wrecks necks.
A prairie squid and every pot of money shot a coney twat.
It's an all-hoss hour of bonanza.
It's like a world without Tony Danza.
Or fans of the pink shit that hits the charts in a world of dead art.
Simultaneous lobotomy and sodomy
We take a moment and we pause to reflect
On the pinks that we killed and the planet that they wrecked
Then we laugh like banshees and howl like comanches
Do a victory dance in our underoos and panties
Our fantasy is a reality
Earth's a tarnished dust, it's Planet X, you're bust for us
Bob Piper's list
Space and time shift
The cause is a slack rift
A dimensional split
Severs for levers of geni from pink shit
Locked in a circle and steadily exhaled in the smoke
I can see why the pink boys failed
To pay a naze has caused destruction
Second hole of slackless suction
Hey, per view, alien abduction
Functioning on soulless slack
The money should be painted black
The mate from space that stole your balls
Will soon come back and take it all
Return to slack, return to Bob
Repent, slack off, and quit your job
Or slurp the beastly knob
Come on, come on, come on, come on
You can't breathe
He licked the throbbing vein of slavery
Now you're sleeping like a baby
But Bob woke me up and said
Get out of Dodge
There's a guy who's dicking top with a UFO in his garage
I ate some bad ham and I got really sick
And in a puddle of my puke where the puke was most sick
A mouse did appear and it beckoned me near
And it whispered the following words into my ear
It said, kill the pink boys, quit your job
Mock the world and praise Bob Dobbs
You'll build a ship and take a trip
It's a pre-react
Go on, go get a pen, write the coordinates
Six and a half months, hold up alone
Circuit boards, duct tape, and turkey bones
The ship appeared more than disaster prone
But the vomit the crew would think was funny
We didn't need the slack list, they're hapless
The ship would hold twenty
The power source was anything the crew would think was funny
We didn't need the slack list, they're hapless
Our month proved its worth in escaping the star fist
On our way to planet X for sex that wrecks me with a bang
Next, a prairie squid and every pot of money shot a coney twang
It's an all-hoss hour of bonanza
It's like a world without Tony Danza
We're fans of the pink shit that hates the charts
And a world of dead art, simultaneous lobotomy and sodomy
We take a moment and we pause to reflect
On the pinks that we killed and the planet that they wrecked
Then we laugh like banshees and howl like comanches
Do a victory dance in our underoos and panties
Our fantasy is a reality
Earth turns to dust, it's planet X or bus struts
And help the planet X
Embrace the aging blood that flows in your veins
And let the frog pipe clouds breathe slack into your brain
C'mon! Control what's left of you
of your brain
Oh yes, and all your money
to the Reverend Einstein
to the Saint
Embracing the one that flows in your veins
from the crowd by the clouds
rings slack like Ray Lippop
control of sense
Oh yes, and all your money
to the Reverend Einstein
Embracing the one