The following broadcast is a subgenius production.
Gaiety galore, and lots of fun even.
I want to be sure that you find out about Bob.
Now, Bob, tell us the truth.
Have I mentioned I'm immense and immortal?
Station Bremen and station DXB on the 31 meter band.
You are about to hear our news in English.
Now, Bob, tell us the truth.
All right, you primitive screwheads, listen up.
You're a loony.
You're not going crazy.
You're going sane in a crazy world.
Now, Bob, tell us the truth.
This man is no ordinary man.
There can be only one.
Oh, spooky.
Yeah, whatever.
And now, here with an unlimited supply of misinformation is Bob.
Okay, man, start it up.
The Hour of Slack.
You haven't heard it?
You mean to tell me that you haven't heard it?
No.
No, I haven't.
I haven't heard it.
Here, play it.
It's really terrific when you hear it.
Excuse me, ladies.
I have a special request.
Perversion for profit.
A blood tide of filth is engulfing our...
a country in the form of newsstand obscenities
and is threatening to perverse an entire generation of our American children.
A blood tide of filth is engulfing our...
Do you want your son enticed into the world of homosexuals?
Or your daughter lured into lesbianism?
Do you want either of them to discover how to get sexual gratification
by inflicting pain on themselves or by torturing other people?
Perversion for profit
Do you want your children stimulated?
What is fetishism?
The costuming and the significance of the extreme spiked heel and the tight boot
The burning cigarettes
The lace leather garments
The nakedness
Perversion for profit
Strange flagellation colors
Sexual sadism
Abnormal sex practices of every kind are described with intimate physical detail
Sexism
The burning cigarettes
The worship of the whip
The riding trough
Rubber and leather garments
Perversion for profit
The Shepherds in the same country
There were shepherds in the same country, wrapped in strips of cloth, and keeping watch by night over their feeding trough.
Behold, two young pigeons stood by them, and they were in the same place.
The pigeons said to them,
When is a Dobshead not a Dobshead?
Not a Dobshead
Friends, and when it's B Dobs hide
Thanks to Lee Murr and before that, Perversion for Profit from the Bran Flakes new album Bounce
And you can find out more about that from www.thebranflakes.com
Opening collages there were by Mark Mothersbaugh, The Bishop, who you can find at the Yahoo Club called Yeti Video
And the El Queso All Stars from stationmp3.com slash interbulator
More from the El Queso All Stars from stationmp3.com slash interbulator
More than anything,
I would say thank you,
I did grab some
I even had some
similarity on the luck plane
to slack.
Yes, love and slack
often go hand in hand.
Since time
immemorial,
love has been one of the
golden carrots
of the subgenius.
For instance,
what do you think is playing
at the Roxy?
What's playing
at the Roxy? I'll tell you what's
playing at the Roxy. A picture about
a Minnesota man so in love with a Mississippi
girl that he sacrifices
everything and moves all the way to
Biloxi. That's what's
playing at the Roxy.
What's in the daily news?
I'll tell you what's in the daily news.
Story about a guy who bought his wife
a small ruby with what otherwise
would have been his union dues.
That's what's in the daily
news. What's happening
all over? I'll tell you what's
happening all over. Guy sitting
at home by a television set who used to be
something of a rover.
That's what's happening all over.
Love
is a thing that has licked him
and it looks like
Nathan's just another victim.
Yes, sir, when you see
a guy reach for stars
in the sky, you can
bet that he's doing it for
some doll.
When you spot a John
waiting out in the rain,
chances are he's insane
as only a John can be for a
Jane. When you meet
a gent paying
all kinds of rent for
a flat that could flatten
a Taj Mahal.
Call it sad, call it
funny, but it's better than
even money that the guy's
only doing it for some
doll. When
you see a Joe
saving half of his dough,
you can bet there'll be
making it for some doll.
When a bum
buys wine like a bum
can't afford, it's
a cinch that the bum is under the thumb
of some little broad.
When you meet a mug
lately out of the jug
and he's still
lifting platinum faulty
roll. Call it
hell, call it heaven,
it's a probable twelve to seven
that the guy's only
doing it for some doll.
When you see
a sport and his cash
has run short, you can
bet that he's banking it
with some doll.
When a guy wears
tails with the front gleaming white,
who the hell do you think
he's tickling pink on Saturday
night? When a
lazy slob takes
a good steady job
and he smells from Vitalis
and Barbasol.
Call it dumb,
call it clever,
but you can get odds forever
that the guy's only doing
it for some doll, some doll,
some doll. The guy's only
doing it for some doll.
Stubby K, dear friends,
guys and dolls from the
1951 musical
of the same name.
Ah, love, love,
love, part of love,
is, of course,
sex.
And the Bonobo
Yeti buried within each subgenius
must come sproinging
out as displayed
by Lemur as he
manipulates the God
Shatner into sexing
his crew.
Human flesh against human
flesh and blood. No, not
on me. On you, Lieutenant.
That's where our duty lies.
How can I?
Man or woman, it makes no difference.
You know so much of love.
And the only thing that's truly yours
is the wonderful bathing suit.
Enterprise to Kirk, Captain.
Enterprise, enter.
Come in, Kirk, Captain.
Kirk, Captain.
Not all of us are satisfied
with having them feel too hard.
Captain, we've got to do something.
We were doing something.
Got any more good ideas, Jim?
How can I?
Increase my breast size and not gain weight anywhere else.
We can fire our phaser banks.
That's how you do it, Lieutenant.
What's happened to her?
We better get used to goats.
Smaller busts.
You think that mysterious organ could have something to do with the transmission of energy?
What's happened to her?
Well?
He wants us to just love it when a man comes up and flirts with you.
He'll give us increasing bust sizes, too.
Then I'd better handle it.
Perhaps if I assisted.
Captain.
Yes?
I would recommend a discreet distance.
What?
You all right?
Oh, yes, I'm all right.
I have an all-natural hormone stimulant for you.
And you will supply the clothes.
Captain. Captain. Captain.
Yes, I know. I know, Scotty. I know. I know.
Nothing abnormal at all.
I don't believe it.
We're living together.
We're rabbits and raccoons.
Birds of a feather.
Existent beasts.
Prolocating freaks.
Sailing with their hooves and their horns on their beaks.
When it's morally wrong.
It's morally wrong.
It's deplorably wrong.
Abnormally wrong.
It's morally wrong.
Philosophically at the clip.
Morally wrong.
Or betting on a horse that you knew was going to win.
Eating chocolate cake when you're trying to stay thin.
Shooting a bird at the Hollywood pole.
And smoking that logo.
Go wacko, dope the wind
It's morally wrong, it's morally wrong
It's traditionally wrong, unconditionally wrong
It's philosophically, ethically, morally wrong
Go, go, go!
Woo!
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah!
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah!
Ah, shoo!
Excuse me.
I was making more than ten items through the express line
Returned my tape, but you didn't rewind
I was stealing parking spaces from the handicapped
Making nice warm mittens from your neighbor's couch
Well, it's morally wrong, it's morally wrong
It's abnormally wrong
Paranormally wrong
It's morally wrong, it's morally wrong
It's philosophically, ethically, morally wrong
Oh, we're playing the guitar in a rock and roll band
Greeting a friend with an outstretched left hand
It's things we think are done, they're intrinsically wrong
Like a murder to see who's by the right to soar
Cause it's morally wrong, it's morally wrong
It's categorically wrong, metaphorically wrong
It's morally wrong, it's morally wrong
It's philosophically, ethically, morally wrong
Yeah, it's morally wrong
It's morally wrong, it's traditionally wrong
Unconditionally wrong
It's morally wrong, it's morally wrong
It's philosophically, ethically, morally wrong
Yeah
Consortium of Genius, dear friends
Available from consortiumofgenius.com
And now, a message from Amy Leamer
Hello everybody
My name is Amy, and I have an important message for you
Okay
This has been another fine message from the Anti-Sex League
Tell your aegis' mother
I'm sitting on her lap
Turnin' theㅣ
I'm erfolg
And, oh yeah, my name is Amy.
To...
Mark Mothersbaugh.
And now, The Rainmakers.
Who am I? I don't know. I have no idea.
When my friends look at me, I wonder who they think they're seeing.
Search me, layer by layer.
But inside I'm afraid you'll find thin air.
Yes, yes, again.
Again, we might be underneath this skin.
What makes me tick? How should I know?
I've been trained like a monkey.
The bell rings and I start to jones like a junkie.
What turns me on? I wish I knew.
Wish I could tell the real thing.
My honest desire from my conditioning.
Touch me now, now touch me again.
I wanna feel something real coming through this skin.
I've been boxing with my shadow, ended and tagged.
I can't punch my way out of a paper bag.
It's as thick as you think, thin as the reasoning you bought.
I'm a mummy wrapped in a gauze of my own thoughts.
And I wanna know who I'd be if I never had been.
In the static, the snow and the radio wave.
The flickering image, the pandering thought that's been passed off and on to be the blueprint of God.
Hey, yes, yes, again.
We might be if we could shed this skin.
Yeah.
Your skin is exposed every day.
Nice to have a pair of them, isn't it?
Yes, it is nice, isn't it?
Why don't you take them out?
All right.
Close the door.
Sure.
There.
I really am all right.
You're Milra D'Almore, woman.
You gotta understand that I really am all right.
You can understand how a girl, even if she is nice, can get into a lot of trouble.
Ha, ha, ha.
I am nice, aren't I?
Sure.
I'd like to play dolls with you.
Hello, honey.
Get up.
Aren't you going to speak to me, honey?
Oh, don't look so surprised.
That wasn't you, the felon.
He doesn't like you anymore, Mildred.
We don't like tin horns around here.
Oh, yes, he does, don't you, honey?
Get up.
You're going to kill you, Mildred.
Please, please.
Please get me out of here.
Take me with you.
We don't like tin horns.
Who?
Every time you look at a man, he falls over, doesn't he?
Get up.
I got into trouble, but I really am a nice girl.
You can understand how a girl, even if she is nice, can get into a lot of trouble.
Sure.
I'd like to play with you.
Carlos, you losers can help yourself to what's on the table.
Cut it out, will you?
He'll get me.
Shut up.
Get up.
Those things happen sometimes.
So please, don't let Bob keep you from having nothing.
But it's wonderful.
Shut up.
He'll get me.
Bob is what you have been waiting for.
Shut up.
He'll get me.
The Giant Beaver was no different.
Are you like the Giant Beaver, my friend?
Well, Fernanda Nandeli-Murr cut that up.
But now, St. Alio, or Stalio, has a message just for you.
The Littler.
now don't be like that it's a gift take your clothes off
With my clothes on
Take off your clothes
And now she takes her clothes off
Why don't you want to take your clothes off?
I'm too sexy for my shirt
I'm too sexy to take her clothes off
Your clothes, give them to me
We don't have to take our clothes off
I look to the sim
Put your panties back on
You two can't even take a shower
with a beautiful woman
without wearing your jeans.
He refused to take his clothes off.
Let's go to Bob right now.
Hi, Bob.
Hi.
Well, I have a past of homosexuality.
However, I don't deal in that area.
I don't have any more.
And I have anxiety.
And I suffer from depression.
However, I love Bob and I live for him.
Amen.
I wish I was attracted to ladies, Bob,
but the most I can do is be a friend to them.
Well, you know, it's never too late, Bob.
That's what I say.
It's never too late.
Never too late.
I tell you what.
You know, we pick up the newspapers all the time.
You had to read about these guys getting married in the 80s and 90s,
so it's never too late.
You know, Bob, I want to testify so bad.
I believe in this stuff.
It's not exactly easy to listen to with all the screaming,
but it's no condemnation towards that because it's necessary.
It made me feel uneasy in my body.
Do you know what I mean?
Oh, yeah.
Well, I mean, you're watching a supernatural battle,
devils and angels going at it.
I mean, it's intense.
I know.
It's intense.
But isn't it wonderful when these folks get free and they're jumping up and down?
Oh, yeah.
They've got a big smile on their face.
Benny and Bob.
You can watch this boat.
1 o'clock Central, 2 o'clock Eastern.
Bob, appreciate you.
Bob, bless you.
Thank you so very much.
Thank you.
1 o'clock Central, 2 o'clock Eastern.
Bob Astley.
Good to see you.
Totally new axis.
Thank you all.
Again, thank you all for watching the second half of the episode.
Put in the subscribe button for like and we'll see in the next one and at the end of the episode we'll have a change on our name remember the business ethics and size.
We all know you already have one part and I didn't get a single shot at any point.
Ah, I told you it's my mustache.
He's been poor with me.
He plays a game with me.
It's called...
I love you.
My mustache just giggles.
He knows he's the only hair for me.
Ah.
Sometimes.
I stare into the mirror on my headboard.
And I just melt away.
And when I lick my lips,
it's like a hug
from an old friend.
Mustache.
Ah.
Mustache in Love
from the El Queso All-Stars,
also known as Interbulator 009.
And you can get more about them
and actually download a lot of their music,
a lot of it,
from www.stationmp3.com.
And now, a rare recording
procured by Mr. Sister,
stolen friends from Skywalker Sound.
Now, this is a private recording
of, uh, well, sex
between a couple of, uh, stars
of the Star Wars movie.
And, uh, you can watch the movie
in the studio.
whose voices you will recognize
in this steamy, yet romantic,
sex tape.
Thank you.
Thank you, Lemur.
And now, Consortium of Genius.
All you want to do is screw.
Let's get down to it, cause I really want to do it.
I really want to nail it through.
All I am saying in these words that I'm conveying
is all I want to do is you.
All I want to do.
Is you.
All I want to do is you.
I swear to breathe it.
Say the word and I'll believe it.
There's nothing you would rather do.
That special feeling, baby, on your knees you're kneeling.
And only I can give it to you.
Our bodies pressing.
Pretty soon you'll be undressing.
Like an animal right out of the zoo.
Mystic connection like a man in an election.
And all I want to do is you.
All I want to do.
All I want to do is you.
All I wanna do, all I wanna do
All I wanna do is you
Hit it now
Alright
I heard it in my heart
And I felt it in my soul
I prayed to the goddess of rock and roll
You're the only one with whom I wanna lose control
It's true
When I'm doing you
And in the morning
When you're full you'll be adorning
With finest silken robes of blue
Ooh
It's your conclusion
It was only an illusion
A memory you'll never remove
My letter clutching
It's yourself you will be touching
It's the only thing remaining to do
Just like I told you
There'll be someone else to hold you
When another band rocks into your view
And hold you
And you'll be the one to hold me
All I wanna do, all I wanna do
All I wanna do is you
Is you
to the Bushies.
A lot of that happens out there,
only sometimes it's the women folks
doing the dragging.
Yeah, that's the truth.
They got the great big clubs,
whack the guys over the head,
drag them off by their long ponytails.
Yeah, because the guys,
they're just walking down that dirt road
with their drums slung over their shoulder.
They're not paying attention
because the drumbeat's drawing them.
She might be hiding right by that bush,
that wood pile.
Right by Stranger's Camp.
And that weird lair of whatever it is.
You don't come to think of it,
Brushwood is the only place
that that ever happened to me.
Where they come out and hit you over the head
just when you're most susceptible, actually.
Yeah.
The next thing you know, you're pregnant
with some fierce pagan caveman
and a woman's baby.
Some hairy-legged, hippie cavewoman.
Scary.
But you can't turn it down.
Well, a hard-headed woman,
a soft-hearted man,
been in the cause of trouble
ever since the world began.
Oh, yeah.
Ever since the world began.
A hard-headed woman
barely started to slide on that.
Adam told Eve,
listen,
listen, yeah, to me.
Don't you let me catch you messing
around in Apple Street.
Oh, yeah.
Ever since the world began.
A hard-headed woman
barely started to slide on that.
Oh, yeah.
Ever since the world began.
A hard-headed woman
barely started to slide on that.
Sounds totally loud.
Loud.
Clear.
Keep your cotton-picking fingers
out my curly hair.
Oh, yeah.
Ever since the world began.
A hard-headed woman
barely started to slide on that.
I heard about a king
who was doing swell.
He really started playing
with that evil Jezebel.
Oh, yeah.
Ever since the world began.
A hard-headed woman
barely started to slide on that.
Hey, you!
Please stop yourself tremor.
I don't mean the politics.
I just too have to be おいきゆり
or Ju pal her or gü gasoline .
I mean your podéis
to do what I say!
You know why you are?
All the time I am out there.
Tie a tippos bezí aletAm
if I go agaçã
I know ells
Do you like to see dried coffee and things like that around people's necks?
Sure, I like to see that.
Are you making an offer, Dave?
Well, I'm making an offer.
Are you asking him out?
I'm asking him up, if you know what I mean.
Yeah, man.
Sure.
Yeah, yeah.
Let's have a serious adult discussion.
Okay, let's rap, man.
Remember in the 70s, you used to say, let's rap and stuff like that?
I didn't actually say that.
Did you just ever?
I didn't say that until it was sort of camp to say that in the 90s.
Then I oversaid it.
Did you ever get one of those rubber mallets and just bang on your wagon until you cried
and then maybe take pictures of it and stuff?
Were you ever in a rap?
There should be experiments with hitting themselves like that.
On the cutting edge, the Schwartz Cobra crew.
Rubber hammer.
It was a rubber hammer.
Oh, of course.
Safe hammer.
Because the chisel will slide out of your hand if it's not a rubber hammer.
I wouldn't do that without a rubber.
No.
Small talk.
Everybody does it.
Nobody gets a kick.
Small talk.
Nature's all straight.
It's out of range.
It's fucking too heavy on the scale.
Eat up all your hate.
Take it slow.
Heaven can't blow.
See you around.
If you're not under the ground.
Small talk.
Puts me in a trap.
It's nothing but verbal crap.
Small talk.
Must we?
We're open for him.
Small talk.
Is that why we were born?
It's so cold.
You're already old.
It's so hot.
What you haven't got?
I should have stayed in bed.
You're feeling all dead.
I can't wait to go home.
Yes, please leave me alone.
Small talk.
We never ask why.
Till the very day we die.
Small talk.
Curves up the quiet.
Shadow just one side.
Dare you to try it.
I'm feeling like I'm dying.
The sun's at sea low.
One more move here.
I've got to hold on.
Now, it's too late for you.
It's too far away for you.
It's too far away too late for you.
Heaven, I feel like I'm dying.
I'm dying.
Whipping post, friends.
That's ESO Einstein's Secret Outlaws at 5X Day.
And before that, small talk by Little Theodore from beneath the Uber putts.
And you can get more from email, littletheodore at yahoo.com.
Theodore is spelled F as in Frank, Y-O-D-O-R.
Or 3277 Raleigh Street, Denver, Colorado, 802121707.
And before that, ESO Swamp Radio on WCSB Cleveland.
And the king singing Bible stories.
Now, stay tuned for a real treat.
Dr. Philo Drummond, the overman, unearthed an excellent recording of the Swinging Love Corpses.
His band live at Off-Broadway in St. Louis in May of 1991.
What follows then in keeping with this theme of love.
The treasured hit oldie by the Swinging Love Corpses.
Pick a booger.
I don't know how you feel one way or the other
It would make you happy to wipe it on your brother
I'm in a new bar and I'm looking at your neighbor
Find a nugget of his house, he's like a saver in the favor
He's pulling, he's tugging, he's aching on this thing
It's a long, strabist thing still connected to the brain
Pick a booger, pick a booger
Everybody's doing it, picking it and chewing it
Yeah!
He's got his feet, he's rolling, he's checking in for hair
He's quick to get away, still loving it, never giving up
He's got some people on his finger, he's connected every day
Pick a booger, booger, it's a new day today
I'm an alcoholic
He's a movie of the deep inside, a sign that sees a slave to the mass
But he's rolling on signers
Kids all wanna have days of infestations
Cause a pick a booger boogie is the new sensation
Pick a booger, pick a booger
Yeah!
You come on in the box, still a fever in your nose
You think a booger has a wife, you're not at all
You don't know how you feel one way or another
You need to make sure you're happy in life
You're not a drugger driving in the car
And you're looking at the lights
I'm working from the start so I can save her in the day
He's pulling, he's tugging, he's aching in the sink
It's a long time of screams, look at me, I can feel the brain
Pick a booger, pick a booger
Everybody do it again, pick it again, show it again
Pick it, pick it, pick it
If you relax the rubber band quickly while it's between your lips, it's distinctly cool.
I was pretty
last night when an angel broke the light
He said, I'm gonna have to put you on hold for a time
I said, hold like hell, let me talk to the boss
He said, sorry, sinner, it's the boss's day off
And I realized then that the wages of sin
Was two bucks an hour and a working weekend
I was ignoring the fee
He was
And I thought that it was going to be fine
I said, well, you know, there's nothing to take from a shingle
But I don't think it's the same
Yeah
It's not like
I'm Mary Magdalene.
How about a date?
You've been wasting your time staying up so late.
Your boyfriend's dead.
The word is you're a whore.
Just about then I heard a knock on the door.
And I realized then that the wages of sin was a bad reputation.
And too many friends, the wages of sin.
The wages of sin.
The Rainmakers from their album called Tornado.
And now, from alt to dot binaries dot slack,
Heart Ignition.
So I doubled down a little bit,
man.
I switched off the Breathe,
and I got with the fridge and the freezer.
The fridge cold life.
It's like so much,
so much heat.
Yeah, man.
helping 195 it in the microwave.
About 30 seconds.
Just about 30 seconds.
Just take out your CD 44.
Yeah, those good Office Connecticut
Yeah, those.
I'm sitting there.
Turn on my favorite show.
Watch my show.
All of a sudden, I start hearing the sound.
Slack off.
I realize, man, you don't object to the good or the bad.
You are listening to the Hour of Slack, the voice of the Church of the Subgenius.
And you can write to us at, got that pencil ready?
P.O. Box 204206.
Austin, Texas 78720.
Or www.subgenius.com.
This music in the background is by the Flying Ryan Brothers.
From their new album, Legacy.
And you can find more about the Flying Ryan Brothers at www.ryanetics.com.
That's ryanetics.com.
R-Y-A-N-E-T-I-C-S.
Ryanetics.com.
And everything is at subgenius.com.
And now, Princess Wee.
And.
I.
Yakutismo.
Let's smoke some Frump and Cough.
Love.
Thank you, Mr. Sister.
Thank you.