And I guess we can proceed, thank you.
And to myself, well, praise Bob.
I guess the kids have learned to think faster
due to television commercials, MTV,
and such like, a heavy, fast hour of slack.
It was a 20-foot slender and incredibly fast...
Self-genius hour of slack.
That looks very inviting, Mr. Hobbs.
Why don't you take a bite?
A bite? How about a little lick?
The gaping mouth was almost on me when...
Oh, take it deeper.
Oh, yeah, that's it.
You keep like that?
I hope he swallows it.
He'll be back tonight in our dreams.
Enjoy this one.
Tell me about it. Tell me what you like.
Oh, it's so good.
But I don't think he liked the way you taste it.
Sounds primitive, doesn't it?
We're all primitive deep down, Pete.
Rock!
Sounds primitive, doesn't it?
I know this will sound funny to a scientist.
Okay, and now...
That thing's still running.
What have we got here?
Oh!
Okay.
Oh, yeah.
The psoriasis doctors.
Here is the famous movie star Ronald Reagan
speaking from St. John's Hospital in California.
Thanks, and even though I am broadcasting from a hospital,
it gives me a bang.
One day when Bob was a youngster,
he was playing with a bunch of kids in the freight yards in his hometown.
Surely Bob...
Bob...
For days he lingered between life and death.
He'll be all right.
Bob opened his eyes, and Bob opened his eyes,
and everybody agreed that Bob would make good in his new field.
For this is the strange story...
For days he lingered between life and death.
Bob decided...
Bob...
, Bob...
More slack coming up.
More slack coming up, friends.
Speaking of good...
Here's some good Christmas news.
This is from Puzzling Evidence News Service.
Well, this is going to be a newsy show.
Some music, some news.
No theme, no problem with Bob.
Parachuting Christmas elf hits car, breaks leg.
Hundreds watch as shootist misses target.
Quincy, Massachusetts, a parachutist dressed as one of Santa's elves.
lost control and landed on a moving car in front of hundreds of spectators at a Christmas festival.
Bob Humphrey of Holbrook, police said Bob Humphrey was falling at about 30 miles an hour
in his elf suit when he hit the car and bounced into the street.
Humphrey, 39, spent Sunday night at Quincy Hospital where he was treated for a broken knee,
broken leg, and bruises.
Parachutists dressed as Santa Claus and other elves landed safely.
Oh, wow. I mean, like, you know, it's time for the, um, I just had it, um, oh, wow, um,
oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, the, uh, the, uh, the Gottlieb, no, um, Ginsberg, uh, yeah, wow,
that's, uh, the Ginsberg moment, uh.
Like, um, I keep trying to think back, you know, and I can't really, uh, really get it sometimes.
It's kind of confusing.
But I remember occasionally.
Beautiful bride.
And today we...
Oh, I'm sorry, are you on the air? I beg your pardon.
Wow, man, like, what's, what's happening?
May I sit down here? Are you the DJ, sir?
Um, yeah, wow, man.
What do you want?
I, I feel as if I'm, I'm flashing back.
No, man, it's me that's flashing back. What are you doing? Who are you?
My name is Tirebiter. Someone asked me if I would come today to, to, uh, help you on your radio program,
but they didn't say that your eyes would be so strange.
Well, that's good coffee, Doug.
Uh-oh.
Yeah, that's right. It's time.
For Muzzly Definites Presents.
It's 4.30. Time for that big old mug of work.
Ain't nothing better than a good cup of coffee, I'm telling you.
Especially this. It's a great, big, manly cup of coffee, you know.
That's why we need more doctors.
Drinking manly, manly cups of coffee.
And that's what I think you ought to tell all those listeners out there on your show, Doug.
Tell them to drink more manly coffee.
I remember that time in Mozambique, Douglas, yes.
We were on the beach in Mozambique, I guess it was in 48.
Beautiful country. Portuguese had things well in hand then.
Remember, we sat in Hotel Balneario, it was called.
The resort hotel, yes.
There were fireflies down on the beach, it seems to be called in Mozambique.
They come out at sunset or thereabouts.
And the women, ah yes, the women strolling.
Their flounce skirts and their bright eyes and their dark, smoldering, tropical flesh.
Ah, yes, Douglas.
Those were the days, the old subgenius days.
Now we sit sadly in our little old high rises, toothless doctors, nail-less doctors.
Ah, thinking about the old days.
Those were the days, doctor, those were the days.
Back when the church was just a bad joke and a quick lip fart on everyone's face.
Yes, back before money and contracts and being famous.
And people like artists became members, yes.
This was back before the lives crept into things.
Back before.
The structure of the church was unwholesomely chipped away piece by piece.
By a sniveling group of art snots.
Blind about things like pain and hunger and suffering and disillusionment and betrayal.
Oh, the world is such an awful place.
And thus was sin brought in to the church.
Lies became part of the litany.
And all has perished.
But it was a worthy time at one time.
Perhaps it shall come again.
The End
Well, maybe at 6 AM it will return.
But for now, you're in the clutches of the show.
Heh, heh, heh.
Hmm, hmm.
So, have that mug of work.
Sit back and enjoy as we tell you a little tale.
Watch out!
Oh, thank you, puzzling evidence.
Look, I just want to tell you, I've been listening to these show tapes.
These are some of the best show tapes you have ever done.
Man, it's really, it's starting to un-jones on my show tape pick.
Now I'm coming down a little bit, man.
I feel much, much better.
Whoo!
Hey!
Hey, I'm stretching.
I'm a man.
I'm a manly man.
And I believe in doing manly things with myself.
Yep.
All the equipment in the world, and you can't lock it up.
Can't lock the sound of the picture.
You've got to go by time code.
Can't just have simple manly gears and sprockets physically linked together.
No, no.
Got to do it with electron signals.
A zillion, trillion little electron signals.
One of them gets stepped on, and the whole thing's out of sync.
Well, of course, Doug, our helicopters are dropping like flies.
The Saudis have a sub-nuclear bomb.
The price of gasoline still goes up.
Congress can't come up with a budget.
George Bush looks like the wimpy Ed.
John Sununu revealed to be a fat dork.
It's amazing, isn't it?
Yes.
And meanwhile...
What is the real story, Guy?
The air gets worse.
The water becomes filthier every day.
The topsoil is blowing away or washing away.
And down chemical-laden rivers.
It wasn't polluted with chemicals when it was removed from the countryside.
It's polluted with chemicals by the time it finally becomes sediment at the mouth of some big river.
It's all going to hell in a handbasket, and it's going really fast.
And it's just something that happened while we all watched.
The Big Show.
Because they told us the Big Show was what was up there on Wall Street.
They told us what was the Big Show was up there on the movie screen.
They told us what was the Big Show was on the television programming.
They told us what was the Big Show was the World Series and the Super Bowl.
And the Fall Fashion.
They told us it was the new cars.
They told us it was the hydroplanes.
They told us it was the jet.
They told us it was jet skis.
They told us it was safety belts and inflation bags.
They told us it was labor unions and pension schemes.
They told us it was all sorts of things.
But they never told us it was what was right outside our door.
They never told us the Big Picture was the air, the water, the earth, and the sunshine.
But that's all it was.
A big show.
A ball of dirt.
With a skin of moisture and a rind of air being driven.
By the heat of a burning, collapsing nuclear gas bag.
No, they told us there were all sorts of things going on and not to worry.
And we didn't worry.
Nobody worried.
No, sir.
Keep the taxes down.
Everybody can have five of everything.
We're an example to the world.
Then one day we turned around and found that people are dying by the thousands.
From diseases that didn't exist 50 years ago.
We find the air is filthy.
The water is putrid.
The land is being turned back into a desert.
And there's still the same old game going on upstairs.
The same greed.
The same intolerance.
The same religious and political bigotry.
The same alpha prime monkey men playing games.
While all around us the world goes to hell and can't move.
Watch out.
I mean, what does that have to do with hurting him real bad?
It's all I can say.
It's just show time for the show, folks.
And learn how to buck the giants in every way you can.
You'll always be vulnerable to competition from the giants.
You've got to accept other realities.
You surrender.
For example, you surrender.
For example, when you cannot hope to win.
What do you do?
You surrender.
For example...
APFP in...
All over everything.
Oh, I'll get it.
I think it's Bob.
It was Bob.
Oh, never mind.
I'll get it.
You mean Bob Dots or whatever that was?
Yeah, the cheap guy.
Bob had promised to keep him posted.
Okay, then what happened?
Well, from killer to post he was...
Thanks, Bob.
Oh, thank you, Puzzling Evidence.
Thank you, Joe.
Thanks, Bob.
Thanks, Hal.
And mean old curmudgeonly Sir Guyon de Cruel.
Action question number 43.
Bob, I'm sorry for you, Hal.
No easy pass.
Oh, that's Mitch Green from Paul Axel's office.
And then see which one pulled best.
Stop the advertisement.
Okay.
So the advertising stopped.
Thanks, Bob.
Is that a lie there?
The lie of the land or the lay of the land over there, that little thing?
I think you've missed the point.
It's not the environment.
It's the communist jubilee.
Yeah, it's pretty until the chainsaws and skill saws and rip saws and band saws all
get together and...
Wow, look.
They're cutting down the flowers.
It's the saw symphony.
Oh, wow.
Wow.
What happened to Hal?
It turned into a...
Whoa!
Oh, look at that.
Ew.
Sticky.
Oh, is my face red?
We can get our way out of here.
Come on, let's go.
Oh, I suppose so.
Whoa!
Aunt Bertha!
Come on, look this way.
That's only a statue of Aunt Bertha.
I'm not afraid of her a bit.
Why, she could be standing right behind me and I'd...
Whoa, geez.
I'm behind you, Hal.
Oh, jeez.
Sorry.
R-r-really?
I drank too much too, here.
Whoa!
Oh yeah, Aunt Bertha, run, run, run, run!
Come back here, you nasty little boy.
Wait, in here, in here, in here.
No, no, in here, in here.
Oh, what do I do?
I'm gonna get you good.
Hey, how's the show?
What show? What show?
What show?
...back there, errs, or some of them wake up naked in the next county
or surrounded by broken bottles.
I wonder how the hell you got there, errs, or...
Ah!
Oh, almost hit the wrong button there.
Yeah, this station would have been...
...blown sky high.
Uh, and, uh, the, uh, the prolonged rant,
in case it was what puzzling evidence and Dr. Howell were saying wasn't clear,
that was G. Gordon Gordon doing the long, cynical, depressed, sad rant.
But I don't know why our good friend G. Gordon Gordon should be so sad,
because there's so much funny news out there.
Um, uh, and...
And I'm going to read you some more news stories, dear friends, this time,
from, uh, the News of the Weird, only this is a book called More News of the Weird
that just came out from, uh, Chuck Shepherd,
uh, sent to us personally by Dr. Shepherd.
And, uh, it's, it's, um, uh, available, certainly.
Uh, simple, simple enough to find.
And you'll...
Yeah, plume books. You'll love it.
For instance, this one chapter here, The Last Days of the Planet.
Now, if G. Gordon Gordon's rant wasn't enough to depress you pretty well,
how, how about some of these little bits of information?
In 1988, an ABC TV poll of, uh, 17-year-olds,
one girl answered that the Holocaust was that Jewish holiday last week, right?
Another thought the Ayatollah was a Soviet gymnast.
And yet another thought Chernobyl was Cher's full name.
Uh...
Begin to see why he called this chapter Last Days of the Planet.
Whoop!
And it must be the last days.
Because a sex educator, uh, told a Florida House of Representatives committee in 1989
that some high school boys were playing a game in which the winner would be the one
who fathers the most children during the school year.
A fore, forewarning of a decline in morality, civic leaders and parents in Addis Ababa, Ethiopia,
had to quell a fad in 1986 in which children banded together dressed as Michael Jackson,
mimicked his movements and marauded through the city and suburbs causing disturbances.
Boys were wearing rouge and lipstick.
I can see how the Ethiopian parents would be a bit worried.
A 1987 Philo-
Next, next year it'll be, uh, Bart Sensen kids, I guess.
In a 1987 Philadelphia Inquirer story on college's spring break in Fort Lauderdale reported on
a stupid tricks contest in which contestants flouted national concern over the spreading of AIDS.
In one, six men from Penn State brushed their teeth in turn with the second using the district.
The first man was charged from the first brushing until the sixth man drank the remainder.
Holy Cross was the crowd favorite.
I guess that's the name of the game.
Uh, the name for a stunt in which one student vomited into the other's mouth said,
the master of ceremonies we're all here to have fun.
Graduation exercises were canceled at Fairview Pennsylvania High School in 1988
because of fears that several students might try to commit suicide.
On stage.
I should mention that towards the back of the, the weird news book,
uh, the authors, uh, defend the fact that they include,
well, like for, they have a hypothetical inter, uh, exchange between the,
let's say the listener and the author's listener.
Hey, what about that chicken story where the farmer had sex with the chicken
then tied her up with little leather leg cuffs?
I suppose you think that's funny.
I suppose you think mass murder is funny.
I bet you think husbands beating up their wives is funny.
Authors say, nope.
In fact, we've often included such stories because they aren't funny.
We were shocked by them.
They make us shake our heads in disbelief.
Listener, well, if you feel that way, you shouldn't be saying that stuff.
You're just going to encourage all those psychos.
No telling what kinds of things they'll be doing.
Authors, maybe, but the research doesn't show that.
It is possible that a very few potential psychos will gain confidence in their pathologies by,
uh, reading news or hearing news of what other people have done.
But murders and mutilations and animal abuse are such grotesque behaviors
that they can hardly be learned from reading books.
There are very weird people in this country and on this planet.
Um, he goes on to mention that after years of sifting through data like these,
one gets the chilling feeling that someone is trying to tell us something.
But our only recourse is to continue to collect the data.
Ask anyone who collects this stuff.
Not one of us has any idea what it all means.
Weird news must pass as its own reward.
However, we find ourselves on a different track from the Forteans.
Sure, we want to read the report about the giant bat-like creature seen in some remote part of the country.
And please, if you have such a clip, kindly send it to us.
But we're more interested in people who worship giant bat-like creatures
or who want to marry giant bat-like creatures.
That is the point.
The point is, we view ourselves mainly as recorders of human behavior.
Why did the guys on the overpass think it was a good idea to drop concrete chunks on passing cars?
Better still, why is there an entire village of people in India that, every year,
stops what it's doing and spends the next 24 hours throwing rocks at each other,
attempting to kill or maim as many people as possible?
And then, after 24 hours exactly, seizes fire, nurses the wounded, and buries the dead?
Hmm?
At the very least, the study of strangeness gives us all faith
that we're personally not so peculiar.
Our work gives us the opportunity to tell ourselves,
I thought I was a little strange, but then again,
I never stood on the front lawn wrapped in aluminum foil to ward off gamma rays.
And even if you did do that, friend, there's still something in our books and this show
to make you feel better about yourself.
And maybe that's the legacy of Weirdology.
More of which is as follows.
A survey of 1,500 Australians released on International Women's Day in 1988
revealed that one-fifth of Australian men believe it is acceptable to kick or beat a wife
if she disobeys or fails to keep house clean.
And a Rhode Island...
Whoops. Switch music out.
And a Rhode Island Rape Crisis Center survey in 1988
revealed that 24% of 7th to 9th grade boys and 16% of the girls
believe it is acceptable for a man to force a woman to have sex
if he has spent money on her.
The figures went up to 65% and 47% if the couple had been dating for six months or more.
I guess that's more okay.
According, of course, not to, we at the Church of the Subgenius,
because we ain't gonna tell you what to do.
Uh...
Oh, I can't read this one.
The horrible reason for the extinction of the last herd of wild elephants
in Thailand...
Well, I'm reading it anyway.
...where they're in danger of extinction from hunters seeking the males'
um...
uh...procreative organs, let's say, for making Chinese aphrodisiacs.
These weigh around 44 pounds and sell for about 10 bucks a pound.
Ha ha ha.
And, uh...
Under the chapter, The Voices in My Head,
uh...
Aaron Strydom, a 23-year-old ex-police officer in South Africa,
went camping and meditated...
No, I don't want to read that one. That one's just too...
This isn't a good time for that.
A member of the Outlaws Motorcycle Gang in Tennessee,
Arthur Gary Volz, confessed to the murder of his go-go dancer girlfriend,
saying that he was a German general and that when he killed her he was acting on orders.
A truck driver testified at the trial that he was parked along I-40
the night of the murder, when Volz, a former police officer, said,
that he had approached him and said that he needed orders to kill someone.
Michael Trofimov pleaded not guilty by reason of insanity in the murder of his father.
Trofimov, who had recently joined a religious group,
was found with his hands around his father's neck,
speaking in tongues and screaming for God.
His uncle said,
he was a good young man, and then he started going to these religious meetings.
His uncle also noted that the night before the murder,
Michael apparently drove his car into a train,
and that that, quote,
really triggered him off, unquote.
The jury at Thomas Lee Bonney's trial for the 1987 murder of his daughter,
Carol Bonney, in North Carolina,
watched videotapes of the defendant assuming the voices of multiple personalities while hypnotized.
A psychiatrist diagnosed ten separate personalities in Bonney.
The one known as Satan said,
I know everything. I am strong.
I control Tom.
He's dumb.
A wimp.
A goody-goody talking that Jesus garbage all the time.
On the night of her murder,
Carol and her father argued over a love letter to a boyfriend whom Satan called,
quote Satan,
called that stupid newt.
Satan, or the multiple personality, Satan personality of Thomas Lee Bonney.
Then noted that, quote,
Carol called me a bad name.
She sort of goofed when she called me that.
I'm Satan.
Uh.
Uh, police said a 36-year-old father in Little Rock, Arkansas,
beat his five children,
held their hands under water,
and forced them to smoke crack cocaine because, quote,
God told him to do it.
And, uh, Mario Albalo filed a $20 million damage suit
charging former Charlie's Angels actress,
Jacqueline Smith, with sexual torture.
Albalo claimed that the torture began in 1977
when he was watching a muscular dystrophy telethon,
and Jacqueline Smith appeared on screen.
Albalo said that Smith immediately began to torture him with telepathic messages
containing suggestions for deviant sexual acts
that continued well after the telethon ended.
We'll continue on to the next chapter, Weird Clergy,
which is certainly pertinent to, uh,
the Church of the Subgenius.
Uh...
A resty, wary citizen,
but nothing he dismayed.
Oh, Christ was not our savior,
nor born on Christmas Day
to save us all from atom bombs
when we have gone astray.
Oh, tidings of trembling and fear,
trembling and fear.
Oh, tidings of trembling and fear.
God love ye wary citizens,
for it is such a shame
to think of cruel injustices
all done in Jesus' name.
Remember when you go to church,
church believers are to blame.
Oh, tidings of trembling and fear,
trembling and fear.
Oh, tidings of trembling and fear.
God help ye wary citizens,
you've all been taken in
by priesthood's waxing rich and fat
upon your fear of sin.
Though you let you in,
Oh, tidings of trembling and fear,
trembling and fear.
Oh, tidings of trembling and fear.
God save ye wary citizens,
whom for this will make ye sick.
Said Christ was just another Jew,
they nailed upon a stick.
He couldn't save himself,
you know religion is a trick.
Oh, tidings of trembling and fear,
trembling and fear.
Oh, tidings of trembling and fear.
Oh, tribulation and victory,
I will not ask
you why you call me
Cruciate development of a charge
For this is a cooked up
Right here in Dallas, Popet, with God rest ye wary citizens.
Oh, yes, and that was me giving his brave combo.
And this behind me is Ivan staying in brave combo.
Amazing how that works, isn't it?
And we're just...
And we're just sort of drop that out and drop this up.
Ah, there we go.
A lovely, lovely thang.
We like to say all too often.
In 1983, an 18-year-old student at Colorado State University
alleged that a Fort Collins Catholic priest threw her down a flight of stairs
because he was upset at her tambourine playing during mass.
She quoted him as saying, quote,
You play the same way over and over again.
You're not going to play the...
You're not going to play...
You're not going to play the 515 mass anymore.
He then grabbed her by the neck and belt
and threw her out the door where she tumbled down the stairs.
When the church's youth director tried to intervene,
the priest slugged her in the face.
Weird clergy.
Members of America's largest Tibetan Buddhist sect,
just so you know, we aren't picking on just, you know, one sect.
This Tibetan Buddhist sect leader, or sect,
demanded the resignation of its leader, Osul Tenzin,
in...
a 45-year-old in 1988,
after news got out that he had contracted AIDS
and had knowingly spread it to his male sexual partners.
A church official said Tenzin had spread the disease to, quote,
many, many people.
Just how many is that many?
A National Law Journal article in 1988 revealed
there have been more than 140 reported instances in 18 states
of priests,
molesting children,
and that a report to the U.S. Catholic bishops
estimated that the church's liability in lawsuits by the victims
could reach over $1 billion over the next decade.
Sister Franziska Lesky, 57, a Roman Catholic nun,
was fined $500 in Graz, Austria, in 1988
for strangling a kitten to death with a cord
after it meowed too loudly in the convent.
A Brownsville, Texas jury awarded Steve,
Wolverton, $500,000 from the local Catholic diocese
for its negligence in refusing to stop Sister Mary Krieger
from seducing and carrying on an affair with Wolverton's wife,
a guitar player in the choir Krieger directed.
Grand Rapids, Michigan, Baptist minister,
this is my favorite one,
Baptist minister Dwight Reimer used electric shocks
to help him teach the Bible to children.
He asked for young volunteers to sit on a stool
wired to a six-volt...
...lantern battery in order to demonstrate
that sometimes, quote,
God can shock you into hearing his word.
Dr. William Pollard, an Episcopal priest
and author of Let's Talk About Theology and Nuclear Energy,
says that nuclear power is part of God's plan
and thus is essential to life.
According to Pollard, one cannot both accept
that God is the divine creator of all things in the universe
and reject nuclear energy.
And Los Angeles,
Los Angeles minister R.L. Himers Jr. asked parishioners
to pray that a U.S. Supreme Court justice,
William Brennan, would die so that an anti-abortion justice
could be appointed in his place.
Ah, yes, dear friends.
And here's the latest little piece of music
just to totally change the subject entirely.
A little piece of music from Reverend John Bartles,
Ah, yes.
A redhead Iraq till I just could wait
This Arab and right, if you know what I mean
It's really no problem, Jordan, you take it to Syria
Don't let them live here, no crap
It's only an old anyway
This is a song I sang in my weapon in Vietnam
Whoever takes those things to Kuwait's gotta be putting me out
Like cooking turkey in a bath on Thanksgiving Day
These kids in chemical warfare suits
Oughta be done right away
I like them tender, but I like them dumb
And as the odor of freshly cooked American flesh rises into the air
It should whet the appetites of armchair generals everywhere
Oh yeah, oh yeah, so
I ran and I wrecked till I just could wait
This Arab and right, if you know what I mean
This redhead no problem, Jordan, you take it to Syria
Don't let them live here, no crap
It's only an old anyway
This Arab and right, if you know what I mean
This redhead no problem, Jordan, you take it to Syria
Don't let them live here, no crap
It should whet the appetite of American flesh
This Arab and right, if you know what I mean
This redhead no problem, Jordan, you take it to Syria
Don't let them live here, no crap
It's only an old anyway
This Arab and right, if you know what I mean
This redhead no problem, Jordan, you take it to Syria
Don't let them live here, no crap
It's only an old anyway
Ooh.
And that was, once again,
Reverend John Bartles.
He's got some great stuff.
Most of it I cannot play over the radio.
Although, the other side of this,
it says, all clean except last one.
We'll see if nobody comes in to replace us tonight.
We will play that.
A tummy beast.
One afternoon, I said to Mommy,
who is this person in my tummy?
He must be small and very thin.
Or how could he have gotten in?
My mother said from where she sat,
it isn't nice to talk like that.
It's true, I cried.
I swear it, Mommy.
There is a person in my tummy.
He talks to me at night in bed.
He's always asking to be fed.
Throughout the day, he screams at me,
demanding sugar buns for tea.
He tells me it is not a sin
to go and raid the biscuit tin.
I know quite well it's awfully wrong
to guzzle food the whole day long.
But really, I can't help it, Mommy.
Not with this person in my tummy.
You horrid child, my mother cried.
Admit it right away you've lied.
You're simply trying to produce a silly, asinine excuse.
You are the greedy, guzzling brat.
And that is why you're always fat.
I tried once more.
Believe me, Mommy.
There is a person.
There is a person in my tummy.
I've had enough, my mother said.
You'd better go at once to bed.
Just then, a nicely timed event
delivered me from punishment.
Deep in my tummy, something stirred.
And then an awful noise was heard.
A snorting, grumbling, grunting sound
that made my tummy jump around.
My darling mother nearly died.
My goodness, what was that, she cried.
At once, the tummy voice,
came through.
It shouted,
Hey there, listen you.
I'm getting hungry.
I want eats.
I want lots of chucks and sweets.
Get me half a pound of nuts.
Look snappy or I'll twist your guts.
That's him, I cried.
He's in my tummy.
So now do you believe me, Mommy?
But Mommy answered nothing more.
For she had fainted on the floor.
.
Set on, set on, hooping it on and hanging it up.
A lovely trophy, a conversation piece too.
Another broken jaw, hanging from the dog, from the dog.
A blanket, a feathered plow, safe as a cow.
Well, I must have been about 16 years old
when we blew up dead birds with firecrackers.
Displaced guts, organs, blood in the air.
And it was such a fun sight to see.
Very unusual song there from an unusual band on this unusual show.
Actually, that was something we got in the mail from a band called The Sealers
in Stilesville, Indiana.
The Sealers from their Organic Orgasmic Body Buzz EP.
You never know what we're going to be getting in the mail here, dear friends.
And speaking of the mail, I think I'll play this just so you know what to do with the mail.
You're listening to the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
For free information on Bob Dobbs and the Church of the Subgenius,
send a self-addressed stamped envelope to...
Got your pencil ready?
Bob, Post Office Box 140306.
Dallas, Texas 75214.
That's Bob, P.O. Box 140306.
Stay tuned and praise Bob.
Subgenius Post Office Box, which once again is Box 140306.
In Dallas, Texas 75214.
And you can write for free information on the Church of the Subgenius.
Because, dear friends, we are going to save the universe.
Or at least the swinging love corpses are going to save the universe.
When we were born into this life
We were destined to make it right.
And it's predetermined.
And this is our fate.
We're singing this song.
So you can read later.
We are going to save the universe.
This time!
We are full grown.
We are grown up men.
We are all past.
We've paid to reason.
That is our mission.
And it is our task.
It's all for us.
Yes, you still ask.
We are going to save the universe.
This time!
Don't you worry
Don't have no fears
Don't get out of sight
Because the end is near
We can plan
Don't be smug to the side
We're in control
And we are more than fine
We are gone
Inside the universe
Inside
Well, maybe next time.
Maybe next time.
The church of the subgenius
will save the universe.
And if not us,
then the swing and love corpses,
which in some ways
might as well be the same thing,
except they don't answer as much mail.
And we're coming down
to the end of the show,
the unedited show.
I've actually done a lot of
two shows today,
but you'll hear the edited one next week.
This was the sloppy show.
Actually, I went to,
I just got back from a movie.
I went to see Dances with Wolves.
And it's real hard to get
into the proper churchly mode
after a sort of
ponderously serious movie like that.
Not really a ponderous movie,
although one's coccyx
feels like it's done a lot better.
It's a lot of pondering
because it's over three hours long.
Well, friends, here's another church
that wants to save the universe
next time.
This is not associated
with the church of the subgenius.
I'm going to read this one
out of the Puzzling Evidence News Service
from Puzzling Evidence.
Police unplug 1-800-WANT-POT.
New York, November 14th.
A Greenwich village man
who calls himself the Pope of Pot
was arrested today
on charges of murder.
The charges that he ran
a marijuana delivery service
that used a toll-free telephone number
and a dozen bicycle messengers,
police said.
Customers were able to call
1-800-WANT-POT.
It's so basic.
And a bicycle messenger
would be dispatched
from a comic book shop
with eighth of an ounce
pouches of the weed
that sold for $50,
a police spokesman,
Captain Stephen Davis, said.
Good, good.
Captain Davis.
The operation netted
about $40,000 a day.
This, um...
Let's see.
The leader of the organization,
Michael Cesar,
48 years old,
a friend of Mr. Cesar,
says he headed a group
that he dubbed
the Church of the Realized Fantasy,
which met at the loft,
the police said.
A member of the group
who asked to be identified as
Fred
described it as a, quote,
communal marijuana sex church,
unquote,
where members would smoke dope,
ask questions of the Pope,
quote,
and have sex.
He basically believed
that you should be able
to get what you want,
when you want it,
as you want it,
as long as you don't infringe
upon the rights of others,
Fred said.
Associates of Mr. Cesar
said the flamboyant preacher,
a figure,
preached that marijuana
should be legalized,
that money was evil,
and that sexual relations
should,
should be casual.
He doesn't believe
marijuana should be illegal,
Fred said.
He believes it is a sacrament
of his church.
Well, you know,
in some respects,
that church sounds very similar
to the Church of the Subgenius,
except that
we don't want your common
street drugs like pot.
I mean,
that's kid stuff.
As Bob Dobbs' son Bobby
once said,
drugs are for kids.
You know,
so grow up.
And, uh,
because,
now,
if you want to,
if you call 1-800-WANT-FROP,
you wouldn't get anybody.
Sorry.
Sold out.
Frop,
by the way,
just so you understand
what I'm saying,
is an herb,
a common herb in Tibet,
in the Himalayas,
or at least near places
where yeti,
yetis leave droppings,
where this amazing
healing herb can grow
and eventually be smuggled
on the backs of
llamas
to, uh,
Bob's special
monkery,
or lamastery,
in, uh,
Dobbstown, Malaysia.
Uh, yes.
Oh, ha.
No, I threw a towel over it
the moment it happened.
Oh, no.
They flew on their
membranous wings
through the ether
from the planet Yagov,
which we know
as the planet Pluto.
Yes, I know.
It's surrounded by
a large moon
which we call
Cheron.
The moon is actually
the departure station
for hundreds of
Yagov beings.
They're Indians
in ancient colonial times
under the leader
of their shaman,
an eskimo,
who are in dire
and dark communication
with these evil
angelic beings
from the depths
of space.
Oh, where are your
wacky improvisations?
You're just reading,
uh, material.
I am not.
I'm improvising everywhere.
Well, uh,
I'm not so sure.
Oh, look out.
We spilled some dough.
I don't believe it.
We've got a voice
stress analysis
of our, uh,
this bootleg tape recording,
uh, we'll sell you,
and, uh,
That's why I'm on
the end of this, uh,
line and line.
I'm on this acoustic
hologram
that I threw by a point.
You're just glistering
that baby's behind
with that shaft of sunlight.
I can't even talk to this guy.
Okay, you're supposed
to be up to date.
Read the script.
It's so brilliant.
I don't have a script.
I brought these notes
from my staff today,
but I threw them away.
Black market pills?
Do you have any
naked pictures of your wife?
Okay, here's one.
Oh!
Oh, no.
Oh.
Oh, no!
That stuff might
get nasty on me.
I don't even know
what's coming up
on that tape.
I knew what was
on that part.
Ranger Rita.
All right.
We're, uh,
ancient history.
Oh.
A hunk,
a hunk
of burning meat.
Yes, and you're
just a hunk
of burning listener,
huh?
Oh, now,
here's Emmett.
I guess we've got
two minutes to clear
out the station
or I'll see ya.
Oh, wait a minute.
Yes, indeedy-poof.
It's time to leave
the air once again
in a magical way.
And we're glad
because our hunk
of burning love
wants to go home.
Uh, yeah,
put the show away.
How's it going, Emmett?
The show better now.
Wonderful.
Y'all can listen to this.
Goodbye.
I predict that although
50% of the coming population
will be under 25,
70% of the voters
will be over the age of 50.
I predict
paste on bikinis
for you girls
and clamp on bikinis
for you men.
I predict a new
one-shot serum
that will control
every known disease.
I predict that the
French prostitutes in Paris
will go on a stand-up strike.
I predict public executions
will be shown on television
sponsored by your local
gas company.
I predict that future
television commercials
will be so interesting
that the viewers
will not go to the toilet
during the program.
And I predict that our
local American doctors
will go on strike
and be replaced
by African witch doctors.
I predict that human flesh
will be canned and exported
from Africa for sale
in England and on the continent.
I predict there will always
be more people,
but there will never
be more land.
I predict that population
explosion will permit
standing room only.
Every inch of our land
will be occupied.
I predict we will live
in floating cities
sustained by
anti-gravity,
huge plastic bubbles
under the sea
which draws oxygen
from the sea itself,
underground tunnels and caves,
plus the very center of Earth,
which will be a nation
unto itself.
I predict we will travel
by means of non-gravity,
a set of a personal wings,
moving platforms which float
through the air.
We will also take a pill
which makes us lighter than air.
Nothing will travel on the ground.
We will be able to travel on the ground,
freeways and streets will vanish
and be replaced by small landing fields
on the very roof of your very home.
I predict that your television set
will cover one side of your wall
and the figures there
will be three-dimensional
and almost walk out into the room
in natural color,
breathing, living,
with odors to match.
You will enjoy the bracing air
of the Northwest,
the warm enchantment of the South Seas
or the swill of the jungle.
I predict education will be given children
through the television screen.
No personal teachers,
but there will be a warden on duty
to see that 100% interest is sustained.
Later, education pills,
which will give you all of the education
that you may need.
I predict that firearms will be outlawed
and only police visible will be the eye
of the television detection cameras,
which will stun with a laser
and disarray any and all wrongdoing.
A camera eye will follow you
from the day of your birth
until the day of your death
and if you go to the right place, beyond.
Oh, my friend,
how far have you progressed
from the Stone Age?
How far have we advanced
from the ooze and the slime?
Are the present doctors
really miracle men of medicine?
What have they cured?
What have they controlled?
In the next few minutes,
you will be shown a special example.
My friend, this is not the 10th century,
but the 20th century.
I firmly suggest that if you are...