Let's go to the Gigolo Club over in Yancey.
They've got a...
Self-genius.
Power of Slack.
I say this calls for action, and now, nip it in the bud.
Ah, shut up.
Ah, yes, dear friends.
This is your prayer partner, Reverend Ivan Stang.
Welcome to Hour of Slack number 1,272.
And boy, howdy, have we got something different for you tonight.
Last July 2nd at the 13X Day Drill, there suddenly evolved an all-uber-femme live Hour of Slack panel.
Yes, an Hour of Slack featuring pretty much only female voices.
At the beginning, you'll hear this shift from all men to all sexy, naughty girl voices.
The prisoners who listen to this show in Wisconsin and Georgia should really like this one.
These girls cuss like anything.
Us boys are prim and proper models of decorum compared to them.
But nonetheless, because of the estrogenized nature of this episode,
I'm not going to chop it up and fill in the lame parts with collages or songs like I normally do.
And you know, many awkward young men might really stand to gain from the advice that these ladies,
these ewes out as they provide a concise and yet blunt lesson in what not to do to get laid.
And so, let us go into that live show, practically uncut,
except for the billion cuss words that had to be removed from the broadcast version
as opposed to the internet podcast.
The church was, in fact, the sausage fest that many would rightly suspect it to be for a long time.
Yeah.
We lied our asses off.
We lied and we said it was a sex cult and so forth.
And you know, build it and they will come, as it were.
And also it helped.
One year I published, back when the Stark Fist was published on 100 pages of paper,
I did an issue that was deliberately as gross and offensive as I could possibly make it.
All my friends in San Francisco were horrified and said,
there's never going to be any girls in the church.
Now, but they were wrong.
Because Reverend Susie the Flusie and before her even,
crazy women like, remember Sister Mary Squared?
Anyway, you know, it was like all these dames saw that disgusting magazine
and thought, oh, these boys think they're so gross.
We'll show them.
And they did indeed.
And to this day, you'll hear dirtier talk on the secret recordings of the lady subgeniuses.
And you hear of them.
Nice, polite, glad.
Yeah, that's the thing, friends.
If you know Uberfems, you know that they're going to one-up you.
If you say something disgusting, they're going to say something even worse.
If you do something disgusting, hold on.
You're going to be puking in a few minutes.
You know what?
I think that's a good idea.
I think we should all get off this stage and let the Uberfems out here and disgust them.
I mean, really, I want to hear some filthy talk from the Uberfems.
So you want to see a subgenius version of The View up here?
Yeah.
I want to see.
The subview.
The underview.
I want to see.
I want to see the.
So you want to peek under the skirt of the church?
Yes.
The literal skirt.
The literal skirt of the church.
To see the under things.
I can see a few right there.
Yes, we're the Uberfems in this radio show.
And just as we had said it, friends, we invoked the disgusting acts of the Uberfems.
Please report to the stage now.
And forward they come.
Here they come.
You have asked them, and here they come.
To show them as a pair.
So now our.
Pair of tits.
Right.
Round table discussion shifts to the panel of the Uberfems.
We can't have our booze, okay?
Oh, yes.
I can have my Uberman chair back now.
Enough male energy, eh?
Now let us.
Enough of this work.
I can have my Uberman chair back.
Release the divine Cythera to the ambient atmosphere.
Oh, God.
I have stage fright.
I don't know.
What the hell do I do?
Shit.
I'm going to drink this.
Ladies and gentlemen, the Uberfems.
I think I might just do it.
I might just fill up the table chewing.
Kick off the discussion.
You probably ought to say right now, since we're all friends here and engaging in healthful
banter, what kicks you off the most about X Day 2010 that you haven't satisfactorily
articulated yet?
There's not enough tits.
You think so?
Oh, hey, look, look.
There's some.
Right there.
There you go.
Yeah.
Ready, set, go.
You see, even as you are talking about the Uberfem, you're not going to get a tits.
I'm just articulating.
It gets better.
What else?
That's first in my list.
I have a fucking sunburn already.
Oh, that's terrible.
And do you have the stuff to put on it, the goo that you put on there?
No.
I didn't bring any.
I brought it.
Well, now let it be announced.
If anyone has the goo, Pantiera needs a little bit of it.
I thought this was chicks, but I'm seeing a lot of dicks.
Well, I'm sorry.
I'm not sorry.
I'm just trying to moderate, but I will withdraw.
Well, before you all get started on disgusting us all, if that is what your goal is to be,
I'd like to take a moment for those of you out here in the audience and the people listening on the radio
to give a little testimonial to the subgenius chicks out here and their ability to disgust people.
In that, although there are very few of them here, they have somehow convinced men that are here
that they should be drooling and lusting after mucus that flows, to lap up the mucus that flows
out of their snot cavern between their legs, just inches away from their rectums.
And yet, here you all are, yelling for more.
So, come on, girls.
Come on, girls.
Disgust me.
And in exchange for that, we're supposed to put your mouth around a giant sausage-looking thing
that squirts out yogurt that doesn't taste like yogurt at all.
It's not really yogurt.
Oh, shit, he was lying to me.
Fuck.
It's supposed to be fun, right?
Just pretend it's something else they said.
Oh, God.
Close your eyes and think about the sweetness.
No, no.
Actually, this is...
Unfortunately, the oldest one here.
I would love a certain other uber femme to come up here if someone, say, could stand
in front of the camera for a minute or stand behind the camera for a minute because I'm
looking at this beautiful, beautiful space princess who really, I mean...
Yeah, come on.
If you want to talk, boys and girls, look.
You have all your microphones here.
No, no, no.
You're going to sit right here.
You want to touch uber femme.
You can share one of them.
Your microphones are all being taken up.
No, they're not.
There's always room for the princess.
I like being at the podium better anyway.
But, you know, if you want to talk about uberfemmes throughout history,
and, I mean, princess, we.
And she's such a princess.
What a dreamboat.
She walks into the area, and she just glows, and she smiles,
and she's not at all.
Oh, she found something.
Oh.
It's a heart.
The princess is happy.
The princess gave me his heart.
Oh.
And the best thing about Wee is that she's always so sweet and so wonderful
that when someone finally pisses her off,
it's the most awesomely beautiful rage anyone's ever seen.
Aw.
Thanks, Sister Pisces.
We all just fucking love each other, you know.
We do.
It's so beautiful.
Fuck.
And love each other.
Unless you're a bitch.
And then we hate you.
But we still love you.
But we still love you, yeah.
We love you with all our hate.
Well, you know, hate and love are really just a red-cut hair away from each other.
They really are.
I mean, that's just the way it is.
If you feel anything that strongly, it's easy to flip over to the other polarity,
which I guess is kind of what this is about,
because we are, in essence, another polarity of the common, average sausage party.
I mean, don't you guys have sisters?
You know?
Cousins?
No, the Church of the Sausage.
You know?
I mean, we're trying here.
We're trying.
How about friend girls?
No friend girls?
Friend girls?
Oh.
Oh, a donation has been made for the sunburned.
Now, that is a real gentleman.
The sunburned.
Preferring the proverbial soothing gel.
Yes, yes, yes.
And that's one thing.
One thing I will say I've known about uberfemmes in general
that is a definite interesting trait of us
is that we are often very sweet and very kind and very fun,
but then we turn on a dime and give you five cents change back.
And there's a reason for that.
Just as, you know, someone like Stang would say,
everyone keeps going,
Hey, Stang.
The same people go,
Hey, we.
I want to tell you something.
You look really nice.
Hey, we.
I wanted to talk to you about this great idea I had.
And then they go to Pantyara and go,
Oh, hi, Pantyara.
How are you?
And it's,
Hi.
Hey, Pantyara.
Hey, can I show this to you?
Hey, look at this.
Oh, my God.
It's such a good idea, you guys.
You should totally do this.
Oh, that one?
No.
Yes.
I think we should reveal to the radio listeners
that we are broadcasting this naked since we're at Brushwood.
I know.
I mean.
It's true.
So they can picture that.
There are no clothes on the premises.
No clothes allowed.
Awesome.
For the radio listeners, we are all sitting here with our.
Another effing stalker is what that was.
And rubbing together.
Rubbing together.
In the goo that has been obtained.
Yes.
It's.
Slimy.
I oppose.
It's a special goo.
It's a little sticky at times.
Yeah.
Just flick it off.
It has an odd smell.
And those who are here will notice that there is a.
Very nicely placed tablecloth.
Which is concealing.
Any motions that could be done with.
Knees or feet or.
Hands.
Or.
Oh.
Oh, nevermind.
But anyway.
Anyway, you know.
That's for the.
That's.
It's hard to describe the action that is on the stage
and for the radio listeners to really understand it.
And, you know, it seems to be enjoyed in the audience,
and there's a plethora of beautiful breastises.
Oh, yes.
Beautiful breastises.
I'm an expert in observing beautiful breastises,
and there's nothing on this stage.
Ten in a row.
I'd like to say beautiful breastises blowing exposed in the breeze.
Yes, beautiful breastises blowing exposed in the breeze.
And I have an important announcement to make.
If you pay your $30, your breasts will grow.
Oh, yeah.
They've grown an entire size.
Yeah, there are some interesting female benefits.
You know, they always say have sex with a live girl.
I mean, that still applies if you're into that as a chick.
You know, it's great.
But, you know, there are other benefits besides, you know,
the pamphlets are always written, unfortunately,
it's a sausage party, you know.
It's kind of like, yeah.
Have sex with a live girl.
But, yes, a lot of interesting hormonal changes occur
when you pay your $30.
That's true.
I have to let you know, why is there nothing in the pamphlet
about once you become a subgenius woman,
you can pee on anybody, and it's, like, amazing,
and they love you, and they'll follow you with rainbows and butterflies.
That's just you pockets.
I think that's just you pockets.
I'm sorry.
I've never, you know, no.
I have to say about the breast thing,
if your breasts are already pretty big,
you probably shouldn't pay too much
because they'll be dragging on the floor.
Yes.
It hurts the nipples.
The weight of my breasts doubled the day I paid my $30.
Reverend Stang, I think anybody that has over double D breast disease
should get a 50% discount on ordnance in the church.
Right.
I think it should be $15.
You have over double D cups.
That's not fair because once I want them.
Well, when you buy them, he'll send you, no, you'll get nothing.
You lose.
No.
Sorry.
There's also a lot of nice legs on the stage and a lot of nice.
There's some booty up on the stage.
There's some big booty.
There's a lot of booty on the stage.
A lot of booty.
And then, of course, just the amazing beauty that these lovely ladies just emanate.
Booty beauty.
Beautiful booties.
And it's nice because.
Seriously, for those of us who have been around a little bit longer,
and, of course, there's people who have been much longer than I,
pretty much for a long time, you know,
the ladies' showers were always empty during X day.
What ladies' showers?
I thought we all showered together.
Oh, no, no.
As far as I can tell, none of you ever took any showers.
Oh, man.
Thanks a lot, honey.
Bye.
Wah, wah, wah.
We need a cat fight.
Come on.
Cat fight.
Rear.
I have an interesting subject to ask all of you.
Do any of you have any views on why it is that the Connie products in the Church of the Subgenius
do not sell as well as the Bob Dobbs products?
I have an answer.
Go right ahead.
Total fear.
Fear?
Fear.
Absolutely.
They fear her.
I see.
Absolutely.
They fear Connie's cunt.
Trouser wettening fear.
You know, and I think a lot of it has to do with the fact that it hasn't really been explained
how many faces.
Well, Bob has one face, right?
Right.
There's only one Bob.
We know what he looks like.
Connie has infinite faces.
And hairstyles.
And colors.
And races.
And she is.
And cunts.
And the hair is red.
And because Connie is so many different things, it's really hard for most of the general population
to actually be able to know.
To know that's Connie.
Good point.
At that moment.
I mean, I've seen Connie as some of this amazingly just gorgeous kawaii little Japanese girl.
And I saw her one time when I was in a rather bad neighborhood.
And she had on high heel boots and black booty shorts and a black tube top and a freaking
leather top hat working it.
I think that was Suzy the Flusy.
No, no, no, no, no.
Oh, it wasn't?
It wasn't Suzy the Flusy.
But.
No, I don't like.
We should get Suzy a top hat, actually.
Anyway.
She'd wear it well.
But yeah, because Connie is so many different.
I mean, she's the opposite of Bob in a lot of ways, besides just gender and equipment.
But, I mean, she has.
She can show up as so many different faces.
The Connie merchandise is that one incarnation of who actually was created by a guy.
Of course.
Who.
Who thought that that was what all the Connie's were.
It was just the Connie that came to him.
You know, that's probably part of the issue, I would say.
I would imagine so.
That's a very good point.
We should probably.
Actually, we should mention some things about while we're up here, because this has been
asked for before.
How not to make an ass of yourself in front of a female.
Actually, as a male who is trying to look for some ooze squirt or sex hurt.
Because this has been.
We've been asked a lot from how not to flirt with an uber femme.
No.
Well, we can do it from that point or what to do.
How to flirt.
Why don't we do how not to?
Because I think that's probably the more important problem.
So, what I guess we'll ask is, is think about the worst.
I mean, this has been asked for before.
I mean, just think about what's something or give us an example of how the type of behavior
that you're not even.
You're there's no chance in hell.
Don't squirt anything on a woman's back.
Yeah, that's all.
In general or on meeting?
Well, yeah, on meeting.
That's not that's not a good way to.
What is that like?
Hello.
No, even before you say hello.
We will not go home with you if you do that.
That's like the.
Even before.
The before the.
Hello.
Initial greeting.
It's just like.
And you're like, oh, sorry.
Yeah.
I must have.
That's that's right up there with like coming up behind somebody to give them a hug with
your zipper down and your junk out.
It's kind of like it's kind of like the hole in the popcorn, you know, things that that's
usually a generally a bad sign.
If you feel that you have to pull your junk out to give somebody a hug from behind, that
that's the next step in the relationship with somebody you've recently met.
Yeah.
I urge you to reconsider.
Yeah, it's not really.
It's not really.
Sadly, in general, unless you have a masterpiece of junk, generally, it's probably not best
to pull it out until we're on a first name basis.
Right.
Usually, you know, when a guy comes up with the line, hi, I'm hard.
You what?
That just doesn't work for me.
Yeah.
You need something a little more.
Right.
After that.
Do you get the.
Do you.
Of course, you're married in this situation.
So you.
Yeah.
There's a little bit of off limits for you, though.
I'm sure you still get some because.
Well, yeah.
The off limits.
There's some.
I mean, yeah.
I mean, men are human after all.
I mean, some are yetis, but most are human and they're susceptible to the usual feelings
that one would get.
I had one time where I was told that the person looked me straight in the eyes and stared
intently in them and said.
Oh, you have the most beautiful eyes.
I don't fucking know what color they are, but they're beautiful.
That's a winner.
And colorblind, right?
He was colorblind.
Now he's just drunk.
That's what I write.
It's like, yeah, I'm sorry.
That's not a good place to start.
But well, Pantiera, can you think of I know you have I've seen you subjected to quite a few
bad lines.
I can't remember them.
They they immediately fall out of my brain as soon as somebody says them.
I immediately ignore them.
But damn, I can't think.
She's chowing down on this meat, by the way.
I'm literally sucking the marrow out of these bones.
That's a hardcore.
Yeah, that's some hardcore eating pockets.
I know pockets is from almost my neck of the woods.
Actually, we're both from the sort of like southern mid-Atlantic.
I'm a little more mountain.
She's a little more Piedmont.
But we we both have the same not suffering drunken male fools a lot problem.
I've gotten I've had my share.
I, you know, actually, I write them down.
You do.
I keep track of the lines that I get.
I cherish that.
Yeah.
Well, share some really good ones.
I've had a good place.
Please share this one actually worked out because coincidentally, I am a Pisces.
I had a fine drunk fellow come up to me one day and say, Are you a Pisces?
Because I'm an Aquarius and you need my water to swim.
Oh, yeah.
That was a good one.
That's that's one.
And that makes three Pisces up here then.
Yeah, there's a lot of us actually, if I remember at some point it was brought up because I
believe Reverend Magdalene is one as well.
I'm an Aries but I'm a Magdalene.
Definitely.
You're on the cusp.
There Yeah, there are a lot of Pisces and females and I think it has to do with the
fact that that we're just crazy enough.
Yeah.
I would however like to share one more line that is sure.
I cherish it.
I'll remember it till the day I die.
I was approached by another drunken man that asked me, baby, is that a keg in your pants?
Because I would really like to tap that ass.
I think you should tell the Perry Como story.
Oh, I don't know about Perry Como.
We'll see.
Perry Como.
We want Perry Como.
Oh, Perry Como.
He's my favorite.
Come on with the Como.
Perry Como wanted certain oral favors from me as a younger youth drunk in a Florida bar,
and being that I'm classy as well, I said very loudly, F you Perry Como in the bar.
Then I finished my beer.
That's all, it's not the best story ever.
That's a pretty good story.
I like it.
How many people have had the opportunity to say,
fuck you, Perry Como, and mean it?
That's a better question.
My first question was how many people gets the chance to be asked
by Perry Como for oral sex,
and then it dawned on me that probably a lot.
He probably makes a habit out of it.
I think I was supposed to be like, oh, you're Perry Como, let me.
Sister Decadence was approached by Adam West.
Sister Decadence was approached by Adam West?
Awesome.
Yes, he wanted the special finish on his massage.
Happy ending?
He was turned down.
She doesn't work in a spa.
No, that's where the shark repellent was.
The shark repellent, yes.
She needed some happy ending repellent on his ass.
I have one line that people tend to use whenever I'm at X Day.
They're like, hey, why did you come over this way
to my house?
They're like, why are you at my tent?
Well, they don't say.
They're just like hinting to do that.
That's another way not to attract women.
Don't tell them to go somewhere alone with you
when you've known them for 20 minutes.
Don't hit them over the head with a stick and drag them
by the hair to your tent.
It doesn't work.
And some of us have really, really, really hard skulls
and it doesn't work anyway.
Not at all.
That means we will become angry.
Why would we get kicked in the balls?
They've tried to knock me out a couple of times.
It's never worked.
Do not ask a lady if she's worth it.
She wants some of this chocolate.
Referring to yourself.
No.
And please, please, under any circumstance,
do not ask us if we want to get pizza and fuck.
We do not like pizza.
As far as, you know, the X-Day situation,
one of the things that needs to be understood is that, you know,
besides that old line from the book,
we're just not that into you.
I mean, that happens.
It does happen.
But one of the things that does happen a lot, I've noticed,
is that there is a tendency towards what I call creepy stalking it.
Where, for example, like, let's say Pantiera is, like,
walking through the field, and I'll notice behind her,
like, about three feet is this guy.
And then, you know, she'll change directions,
and about three feet behind her will be this guy.
And so she comes over to talk to us.
I'm like, hey, Pantiera, what's up?
And then there's this guy.
And then she goes over to another camp, and there's Wee,
and she's like, hi, Wee, how are you doing?
And there's this guy.
And everywhere she goes, there's this guy,
and he shows up just a little bit after her.
Not a way to get laid.
No, there is only one guy that's allowed.
This brings up a really, really, really, really, really good point.
Okay?
I know when Stang and Philo were writing this material,
there was, you know, promises of sex quite a bit.
That doesn't necessarily...
The whole sex with the live girl
doesn't necessarily mean that you, personally,
get to have sex with me, personally.
It's not like a ticket where you can go up to any chick and say,
hi, tits, I get to have sex with a live girl.
Redeem it.
It's not like that.
The key on sex with a live girl is,
and it has been said that, you know, there's been statements,
well, if you can't get laid, actually, you're not trying.
There's a little finesse to it.
There is a little finesse to that.
The truth of the matter is, is that you will, at some point,
before the exes come, have sex with a live girl.
And if you don't, I understand, I'm not going to name anyone.
But if you don't, then the sex goddesses on the saucers
are giving you your own live girl.
Right.
So you don't have to...
She may not have a brain, and she may be a clone.
It won't be perfectly realistic.
It's still a girl.
It's still a...
It's still a live girl.
You will get this no matter what.
They just...
Please, please, I understand the nature,
because if you can beat off in 2.5 seconds,
I'm sure that you think that it's that easy to get a woman.
But it's not.
Just because you can do it that quickly
doesn't mean you can come up and say,
hey, let's fuck.
There's a little more to that.
It's just you won't get it.
Well, you know what, though?
Hey, let's fuck.
Let's be straight about this,
because if it comes down to it, me personally,
I somewhat prefer that,
because then we can just go and break through all the bullshit.
You're not talking to me.
You're not trying to be friendly.
You're not saying,
hey, I got some beer back at my camp,
and we got some really cool picture books.
No.
Instead, what happens is you say,
hey, I'd like to fuck you,
and I say,
probably no.
Yes.
Pockets.
I'd like to fuck you.
Okay.
See?
It works.
Woo!
Praise Bob.
Now, and again,
I would probably say no,
but then Pockets in this case said yes,
but you see,
that could be the live girl for that Yeti.
You can't just fuck any girl.
You got to find the right one.
It's a matching game.
It really is.
And here's the thing about the matching game,
boys and girls,
because here's the important part of what I was bringing up earlier.
The matching game works this way,
because some of these girls who are your match,
or who are your match,
haven't joined the church yet.
The only way you are going to get your match,
if that's the case,
before the saucers arrive,
is to encourage more tits in this church.
It's really that simple.
That's how you get your match.
And so just because you say,
Pisces, I really want to fuck the shit out of you,
and I say,
um, sorry, no,
doesn't mean that it's over.
Right?
It means that next time you have some subgenius propaganda
in your pocket on the bus,
and you see a girl that's kind of like,
Picking her nose.
I'd do her.
You can hand over some subgenius information,
or leave it nearby and let her read it,
and who knows,
you may show up next time some subgenius event occurs,
and there she will be.
There she will be,
and that could be your real live girl.
She's on the screen behind you.
It could be your true Yeti mate.
Right.
But until we get more chicks in the church,
some of you boys are going to be
whacking off in 2.5 seconds.
I'm sorry.
So I think the mission for all you Yetis out there,
for, well, I guess the next, what, two, three days,
because this is the year,
Yes, it is.
is to find as many women as you can
that are worthy of the ordainment,
and bring them in.
We need Uberfams,
and you will get laid,
if you find your match.
And again,
this is the year,
so some of you don't be totally disheartened.
As we said,
the sex goddesses will be providing you
with a real live girl, too.
Absolutely.
This is definitely the year.
This is the year.
You know why I know this is the year?
You can feel it.
I can smell it.
I've heard a lot of great sex this year.
Me too.
I mean, not just me.
Yeah.
Oh my God.
There is a good sex.
The amount you can walk,
just be, okay,
and you're not actually getting the great sex.
Look, walk very quietly through the campground
around 4 a.m. or so.
That's when the great sex seems to start.
And you can hear it from tent after tent after tent.
There is some serious grooving going on this year.
And we've said before that there must be some signal
that contacts the exes.
More sex.
You know, I'm sure that with the more sex,
I don't know,
I mean, some people were woke up,
I think a lot of people were woke up in the past couple of nights,
but that's,
if we can wake up our neighbors in the next tent with our sex,
perhaps that will be the noise that is needed
to call the exes from the heavens.
More sex.
Absolutely.
You want the exes.
We need more sex.
To have more sex,
you need more titties in the church.
Loud sex.
Good sex.
Good sex is always loud and funny.
It's always good sex.
Right.
And this is again,
this is a great thing.
This is why we need you to work to find more women for the church,
because your woman,
who you're going to have good sex with,
is out there,
and she just hasn't found Bob yet.
So it is your duty to help her find Bob.
And you know what else?
The buddy you're sitting next to you right now,
look over at him,
because his live girl is out there.
She has not joined the church yet.
Do your buddy a favor.
He needs to get some.
Start showing girls about Bob.
It's really that simple.
That's all you have to do.
Look,
he'll help you out.
He'll hand the car to a girl on his bus.
She will show up,
and you will get the best sex ever.
You do the same when you're riding the train into the city.
Go ahead.
Pass out that Bob information.
Bring more tits to this church.
Praise Bob.
Lick Connie.
Aye, aye, aye, aye, aye.
Well,
I have a little secret.
I happen to know that Susie the floozy has brought an inordinate number of Mardi Gras beads.
So there should be lots more tits showing up.
Woo!
Lots more tits going around here.
More tits.
She must have brought like 500 pounds of Mardi Gras beads.
Oh,
I see titties in the near future.
There could be more.
She said,
she said when she held up her gigantic pile,
she said,
yeah,
I brought a few.
A few.
And Susie the floozy,
and I know she had a rough drive in here.
She has been,
she got here by herself,
and she's tired.
And what a vision she is,
no matter what.
That is the truth.
She's got angels,
uh,
whacking off next to her at all points.
I,
I mean really.
That's for sure.
When she rolled in,
looking like a,
like a angel glowing in the sunlight.
She excrimeticates pure slack.
That was the angel.
She really does.
She just,
just craps out pure slack.
It's amazing.
I don't understand it.
When I,
when I grow up.
People fight to smell her poop.
When I grow up,
I want to be Susie.
I want to excrimeticate pure slack.
There's a trick to it.
We can,
we can,
yes.
Well,
she'll,
she'll take an understudy,
I'm sure.
Yeah,
I mean,
well,
call me.
Yes,
there's,
there's certain tricks that.
I'm going to ask,
uh,
well,
let's,
you want to open the field for questions?
Oh,
yeah.
Yeah.
Open the field for questions.
Okay.
Look,
Tits is,
Tits,
Tits would like to know,
wouldn't it be better to recruit other women to the cause by handing out Connie instead
of Susie?
And that's certainly a possibility.
Here's one of the things that I will digress just momentarily.
Sometimes with telling people about Bob,
you don't necessarily have to go about it the way of say pamphlet one or pamphlet two.
There's a lot of back doors and other entry ways.
And that's another thing good about.
And I,
some of us,
and I know myself and Pantiera both have had our own outreach ministries in various
ways.
And I,
and everybody does it a little different.
Pantiera was all about,
man,
you work the postal service.
Yeah.
I only got one reply though.
That was from an 80 year old man.
But I'm sure,
you know,
I,
he could have been a rich oil man and you could have married him and,
uh,
got yourself a trend spot commercial or no,
but you,
everyone,
everyone has their different ways of outreach.
And I used to do it based on what the market was.
I mean,
it's really like that's what we're talking about.
This is a church,
And so you've got a great point.
It is about the market.
For example, when I would go to science fiction conventions,
at a science fiction convention, those of you who have gone,
there is a lot of guys who are going to be jerking off that night.
I mean, there just really is.
There's a lot of girls who are completely unattainable,
and there's a lot of guys who are going to be jerking off that night.
So most of my promotion at what I would talk about, Bob,
at the science fiction conventions was from the concept of the saucers and the sex goddesses,
and that was a way to handle that.
You are exactly on point.
I encourage you to do that.
I think that's great.
Next.
Oh, come on.
No questions for all of these women sitting up here?
Not a single question?
Yes, Sting.
How is Bambi formed?
Just forget the whole thing I said earlier about the live sex girl thing.
You see, when a man loves sex,
when a man loves a woman very much,
he puts his hands in her,
and then things happen.
We're not talking about finger babies.
Oh, oh.
Oh, well.
I've had lots of those.
When a man and a woman
and then mudkips
and alcohol
they forget everything they did the night before,
and then the woman gets pregnant.
Suddenly.
That's how it was meant to be.
It was meant to be, right.
Next question.
Motomac.
A comment, what you said earlier, introducing women to the church who are coming.
As for the saying politely, how much comedy merchandise is sold?
We had a discussion about that earlier.
We actually have been through this, Motomac, yes.
If you have been paying attention.
Please take notes when the Uber fans are speaking.
Thank you.
There will be a pop quiz.
I was off track.
This does count.
Oh, okay.
This does count towards your final grade.
Thank you.
He did do extra credit there, he said, so I guess that's okay.
I mean, you know, I always curve on it anyway.
I have a question.
Yes.
Would it be easier to recruit the Sporian women?
Would it be?
Okay, okay, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I actually know about, there's a couple of us who know a lot about this,
and let me just explain something really quickly, okay.
I made the mistake years ago of fucking both Connie and Eris on the same night,
and it's a really.
That's a bad.
That's a really bad mistake.
No, yes it was.
It was.
And actually, Eris was first, so it was really, really bad.
So basically, because Connie really hates sloppy seconds.
And so here's the thing about this, is that the Discordian female
and the Eris-Connie connection, it can only be pulled off
by a true hardcore Uber femme, who really can be stupid enough,
to screw Connie and Eris in the same night.
I do have a comment on that when you are done.
Yes, okay.
I've tried several, and what I've found is that you can get a Discordian
to become a subgenius, but it takes about a year and a half.
Really?
That's not a bad incubation period.
It's not bad.
Really?
You have to plant the seed in their belly button.
You have to slowly plant the seed.
The $30 for a turnip.
The seed of doubt.
The seed of doubt grinds their gears.
It tickles their Uber femme skin.
They can't stand it.
They tickle their ovaries.
So you kind of have to talk Discord to the future subgenius.
You've got to trick them into it.
Pay your $30.
Or don't.
Whatever.
And just walk away.
Right, right, right.
Make it mysterious.
Yeah.
I mean, for me, I found both of them very close at the same time, actually.
So it was a little, I guess it was easier to convert me.
Hmm.
And this is a good question, which is a good insight into Uber femmes.
And we can ask, how did you find subgenius?
Since we're talking about how to get more women into the church.
How did, for we, for example, how did you find subgenius?
Well, I was part of a group called the Association for Consciousness Exploration
that had the Starwood Festival here for the last 19 summers.
And someone in our group was well-read enough to...
Oh, yeah.
...ask Ivan Stang to come and speak at Starwood.
And that's how I met Ivan and Bob and all of you.
Right.
Awesome.
That's sweet.
Aww.
Oh, no, no, no.
Do you need tissue?
And then you fucked.
And it was beautiful.
I think my vagina's crying.
Okay.
Well, can I say something about the woman who's the right?
Get at me.
She found Bob, but to make it official, I told her if she didn't go online right now
and pay her $30, I was going to effing kill her.
And now she's an uber-fem.
Yes.
Wow.
That's a hard-fisted approach.
Go fuck it.
That's work.
I had a crush on this boy, and he's actually wearing a skirt now, so I don't know what
the hell I was doing.
It's a kilt.
No.
That's a utility kilt.
That's not a skirt.
Are you wearing underwear underneath that kilt, by the way?
No.
No, he's not.
I dropped a quarter.
Could you pick it up for me?
Praise Bob.
Well, I had a crush on this boy for about three years.
Oh, wow.
And we got back in contact with each other, and he introduced me to Bob and to Tiny Chat
and a year ago yesterday, which coincidentally is also my vaginal ejection day, is my sub-birthday,
because that's when I got my card in the mail on my birthday.
Nice.
Awesome.
Aw.
That's so touching.
And then you fucked.
And then they fucked.
They fucked.
And how about you, Miss Pockets?
Well, I was kind of slack about it.
I found Bob back in high school.
I guess I was a big old gimme Bob.
I love Bob.
Praise Bob.
And then I went.
I had the good slack attitude.
And then I got knocked up.
I kind of forgot about Bob for a while, doing the kid thing.
And then, you know, my kid got old enough, went to school.
I had some more free time.
And I said, oh, Bob.
Praise Bob.
And, you know, I got more into it.
And so finally, you know, I went on my internets and I paid my ordainment.
Approximately how long did that take you?
To actually pay from when I found Bob?
Yeah.
Ten years.
So you were talking earlier about 1.5 being long.
That's what I'm getting at.
You know, a lot of people take that long.
And it wasn't a lack of just laziness.
That's the gestation period of a subgenius.
Yes.
And, Pantiera, what about you?
Well, I was in the same dorm as Reverend Alex, who he hasn't been here for like the past
three or four years or something.
But he, you know, he was like the young superstar sort of, I don't know.
But everybody liked him, I guess, at that point.
He was popular.
Yes.
And so he invited me.
While we were living in the dorm together, he introduced me to Reverend Alex.
And I was like, I'm going to go to the church.
And the first subgenius book I ever read was Revelation X, which is an excellent indoctrination
book, even better than the original book of the subgenius.
I concur.
Yes.
It's excellent.
I was obsessed with it.
And then he took me to X Day.
And we never did anything together.
But I've met others.
You found Bob together, dear.
Yes.
That's it.
Yeah, well, that doesn't mean anything.
My story is so lame.
I'm sorry.
Okay, like, we'll break this down.
And this is how it happened.
There's this dude, right?
And I had a relationship with him.
It wasn't a relationship as in, like, lovey relationship.
It was a relationship as I go over to his house, get fucked up, and we have sex.
And that was all it was.
And this went on for a couple of months.
We were happy.
No problem.
One day, he wouldn't have sex because he couldn't stop talking about some stupid fucker named
Bob Doves.
And I was like...
That's kind of a good thing.
I'm an oxymoron, but fuck you.
And I was like, what the fuck are you talking about?
Look, you're cutting into the booty time.
Let's get on and have sex.
And he was like, no, no, no, I have to show you this website.
I have to do this.
And at that point, I was like, fine, I'll fucking pay it.
I paid the membership.
And then later, I started hanging out on IRC and things like that.
And the dude who introduced me to him, I haven't seen him since the one time he came to XC.
He's a fucking blonde.
So I don't know.
Surprised.
Surprised, yeah.
And then his loss.
He got married in a minivan and forgot about Bob.
I think it might have been like he became a baby daddy or something.
I don't know.
Don't let becoming a baby daddy or a baby mama turn you away from the church.
Just get a babysitter.
Right.
Don't slip into normality once you've paid the $30, because then you won't get taken
up into the saucers, even though you've paid your $30, because Bob can smell the pinkness
that's rubbed off on you.
This is true.
I am living proof that you can become a baby mama and still be a subgenius woman.
Exactly.
And a hot baby mama.
Damn straight.
Hot damn baby mama.
MILF.
That's why I married you.
This is true.
You need to teach your children about slack.
Teach your children about slack, and then they will grow up to be future females.
And then they will be like, I'm not a baby.
That is true.
I need to be very, very bold and very round.
Wait till you see me in my 20th birthday.
Look what I did.
Look what I did to my Allison, my royal aunt, my queen mata, my princess m 8 sak prey,
I loved doing baby rowing.
I loved photographs.
I loved telling my grandchildren.
No!
I hate Bob.
That's the point.
But they'll get over it.
After they're about in their 20s, they'll realize that you're right,
and they'll forsake Jesus, and they'll accept Bob into their urethras.
Do we have any other questions?
Come on.
Any more questions?
Come on, you have a question.
We are women and have vaginas, and we can do whatever we want.
That's exactly right.
Praise Bob.
Hail Connie.
Hey, we have a question.
Yes.
What list?
Remember you were taking notes earlier for things not to do to get laid?
Okay, another thing not to do to get laid is make us repeat ourselves.
We don't like it.
That's not how you get laid.
That's how you get fucked.
Yes.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's recorded.
Don't worry about it.
Ask for help.
Yeah, that's an interesting one.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, you know, actually, I'm not going to say much about that, because I got to tell
you something.
Uber femme women are the most stubbornest fucking bitches on this goddamn planet.
Yeah, we are.
Woo!
Amen.
You said that right.
We are ornery, and we are stubborn, and we are just difficult.
We are ornery to the 15th power.
But we're kind of, but I don't know.
Especially next time.
I think we're kind of worth it.
Because, you know, we're on our guard.
We, there's, it's like a ratio of one.
Woman to four men.
Right.
And we have to be on our guard, and we're getting sun poisoning, and.
Or melanoma.
Yeah.
And so, you know.
And probably a little bit hungover, you know, and.
Yeah.
I love that we laugh over cancer.
Praise Bob.
Well, I mean, and we are ornery, we are difficult.
And yes, but I do think most of the time when you, when you find the right Uber femme, you'll
find it's worth it.
I'm staying in.
We are an incredible example of that coupling, actually.
Yeah.
Honestly, of a lot of, there's a, there's several couples I know like that have this trait, but
it's very strong in them in the sense of we is the only person who can take stank shit
and stings.
Probably the only person who can take we shit.
You said that perfectly.
Absolutely right.
You see, here's a big clue.
Here's a clue in relationships that I will share with you.
The number one rule of, of, of subgenius relationships.
It probably applies to pinks, but I don't know.
Cause I don't, I try not to do anything with them is.
Everyone is crazy.
Everyone, everyone's bat shit.
The clue and the key, the thing that you have to do is find the compatible crazy to your crazy.
The problem is, is that since everyone's crazy, that's a long, hard road.
And how.
Okay.
And Dr. How.
Dr. How.
I like Dr. How's brain.
I think he has an incredibly sexy brain.
And, and that's, you know, it's just.
It protrudes right through your brain.
It's like a little bit of a trim his skull.
It's, it's, it's, it's incredibly hot.
It's got nice curves.
We want to lick your brain.
I mean, I want, I, I wish you could like take the brain out and have my brain, like
get it on with just his brain.
Brain babies.
I mean, that would rock.
She wants to have Snoo Snoo with Dr. How's brain.
Snoo Snoo.
Me want Snoo Snoo.
Well, the brain is the largest sex organ.
I mean, I want to have a little bit of a sex organ on the body.
When the saucers come, we shall come as well.
Yes.
Yes, we shall.
That is, that is, that is one of the things that you have to understand.
So, you know, I mean, that's the advantage of being naked at 7 a.m. if you're interested.
It's cleaner.
If we get naked, do we get on the ship sooner?
You don't have to experience this.
You don't have to experience the clothing removal part.
And also the mess that happens right when the, the mess.
I understand.
Yeah.
The mess.
I expected the mess.
If you're naked, it's, it's an easier step because when they bring you up, they will
just sort of hose off the mess and they don't have to take the clothes off first.
So yes, in theory, a few seconds faster because your clothing are, you don't have any clothing
to remove, but they can just hose off the mess.
That's love.
I mean.
I also feel that the women with over double D boobies should get like the best saucer,
kind of like first class accommodations.
What about the men with double D boobies?
Maybe leather seats, a little more leg room.
A nicer, a nicer balcony.
Yeah.
Here's the catch.
Cause I'm in this line.
Once you get on the saucer, your breasts will expand to like triple J's.
So we'll all be happy.
Oh, praise the Uber fans.
Unless you don't want them.
Well, you know, and that's the thing though, is that that's part of the thing that people
forget about the sex goddesses is they are doing their, they have a list.
I mean, it's like, it's like going to the best Chinese restaurant ever, except for on
the menu is all the augmentations.
The augmentations.
And the changes.
And there's no MSG.
It's great.
You can say, look, you know, I've lived my whole life in my left tit sags a little bit
more than my right.
And it's really gotten on my nerves.
I don't care if you're 80.
Once you get on that saucer, you will have the perky is most beautiful, roundest, hugest
tits on the face of this planet.
You'll have better tits than we'll be on this planet even.
You will no longer have to tuck them into your socks.
Well, let's talk about that for a second too.
We're going to talk about that in a second.
One of the things about sex gods and sex goddesses is that the sex goddesses come with a variety
of attachments.
These sex goddesses have more attachments than the standard electro looks that your
grandmother had back in 1940.
These sex goddesses have the capability to morph and change into anything that you could
possibly want.
So if for some reason you really want to fuck Milton Berle, the sex goddesses will do that
for you.
You know, and some of you, some of you may have heard of the sex goddesses.
They have had some concerns that they are aliens.
They might not know what to do.
You know it's okay.
You can bring some porn, show them, but you don't really need to worry about it.
They know what to do.
They do.
They know.
They're ready.
Praise Bob in the hands of our-
And you can get them with the handles built into the head so you can kind of just
turn them.
Mind I add that gender is a pink social construction.
So whether you call them sex gods or sex goddesses, it doesn't matter.
They're the same damn thing.
Right.
They are.
It's all about the catch.
And the great thing about that is, is that if you happen to be a boy who likes other,
who wants to fuck Milton Berle, you can fuck Milton Berle.
If you have to be a female who wants to fuck Wilford Brimley, you can fuck Wilford Brimley.
It's okay.
I'd really prefer that Perry Cuomo didn't come on the ships though.
I don't think I'd ever think about that.
No Perry Cuomo on the ships.
No, no, no.
I think we can, we can arrange for that.
That is one creepy old man.
It can be arranged most definitely.
But hey, if you, if you want to be a woman, you can be a man.
If you want to fuck creepy old men, you can do it.
I mean on the, on the.
You can do it now.
I mean.
Yeah, you could.
Yeah.
Go for it.
I don't know.
I've walked around and I've seen plenty of creepy old men.
I mean, look ladies, if you want to fuck a creepy old men, look, I can, I'll set you
up.
Look, just, just come and talk to me.
The free scale men will be delighted.
I mean, come on.
Do we have like a PA here?
Can we call all creepy old men to the stage?
Let, let the ladies pick them out.
No, no.
What a shame.
Wah, wah, wah.
That's fair.
And we all went to lecherous you.
And so, yeah, I mean, there's, again, we have that, those issues.
I'm going to give, we're going to have Dr. Howell come up here very shortly.
He is welcome to come up here at the moment if he would like, if it, unless there's.
Oh no, never.
He would never ban you, Dr. Howell.
You were just put in the penis section for about 45 minutes.
Yeah.
You know.
Your restriction was, you know, you were just put in the penis section for about 45
minutes.
You're welcome back.
Yes, the, the, the, the penis ban has been lifted.
I can't even say that with a straight face because that's such BS.
No, no.
The next day we banned penises.
Oh, no.
No, no.
No.
Just kidding.
Then we'd have to get vibrate.
Ban penises?
Who said that?
For 45 minutes.
This is another Uber, quick Uberfim story.
Oh, okay.
Your, your town of home.
I'm from, I'm from, I'm from, I'm from, I'm from, I'm from, I'm from, I'm from, I'm from,
The airport there.
My town?
Yes.
Oh, okay.
I was going through that airport to go to Atlanta, Georgia for Dragon Con years back.
And I've told this, some people have heard this story.
This was a very interesting situation that I had.
I was going to Drag Con and I had a number of sex toys in my carry-on.
And one was, for example, a little white bumpy, you know, little, you know, palm-sized
pocket rocket.
And the other one was a very well-endowed purple alien cock with a vibrator in it.
And I mean, so I knew my problem was going to happen when I got my boarding pass.
And right on the boarding pass were three red X's.
And I went, that's got to mean something not good at this point.
I hate red X's.
I get to the gate, the security gate, and they pull me aside.
And they're like, we need to go through your stuff.
And I'm like, all right.
So the guy goes through it, and he gets to the sex toys.
And he stops, and he goes, you're going to have to turn them on and prove they work.
And I'm like, you want to use it?
What?
You want a demonstration, dude?
Come on.
And he's like, no, no, no, no, no, just turn it.
And this is this old dude, and he's really embarrassed.
He says, just turn them on and make sure they're not bombs.
Okay, that's all right.
So I turn them.
And they're not bombs, and we're fine.
So then he has to go through this series of screening questions.
And the first screening question, you know, what's your name?
Where are you from?
You know, that kind of thing.
These are typical security screens.
You know, where are you going to?
I'm going to Atlanta.
Where are you going for?
I'm going for a convention.
And he looks down at the sex toys, and he goes, what kind of convention?
And I said, it's a science fiction convention.
And he points at the giant purple dildo and says, well, that would explain that.
Well done.
The main Connie-type panelists there were Reverend Enshrina from Ministry of Slack,
Priestess Pisces, Reverend Pockets, also Ministry of Slack,
Princess We Are Doe, Queen of All the UFOs, and Popess Pantera Ibakovich.
Dr. Legume, Dr. Howell, Pope Black, and myself were also heard from the Peanuts gallery at the beginning.
I told you before.
I'm going to tell you again.
There's something that seems to be a misunderstanding with you men.
Connie's a redhead.
Connie's a blonde.
Connie's a cute melee princess from Vietnam.
Connie's a deep, deep, deep southern bell.
Connie's a gangsta bitch who will shoot your ass straight to hell.
But there's no Connie.
There is no Connie.
Connie's a Norwegian hooker.
Connie's your neighbor's daughter and she's quite a looker.
Connie drives a red pickup truck with a rebel flag.
Connie's been sleeping with your dad.
Connie fucked a two-ball thirty horsepower, already killed.
players. Connie's got her hair in those blonde whiskey layers and there's no Connie though.
See, there is no Connie. Not at all. She's Connie. She's Connie too. I'm Connie. But there is no Connie.
There is no Connie.
Connie wakes you up on Saturday morning with a blowjob. Connie likes to be bent over and bark like a dog.
Connie will put a strap on on and show you what's more. But there's no Connie.
There is no Connie.
In the background, we're listening to an improvisational jam by Six Fisted Tales of Connie, the band that forms only at the X Day Drills, in this case featuring Priestess Pisces and Dr. Drummond on vocals.
Dr. Drummond on sax, Reverend Angry Larry and Reverend Suds Pasha on guitar. I think Reverend Phil on drums and no doubt others involved there, but I'd have to look at the videotapes and the answers.
And where on the record they aren't even labeled yet.
I don't think they're labeled yet.
This has been The Hour of Slack from the church of The Subgenius. You can learn pretty much everything you need to know about that and Bob & Connie Dobbs at subgenius.com
For those in prominent or otherwise free of the internet.
It's post office, 181-417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
In combination with an expensive erfolg in King County, inching generic somber viewpoint.
We have a$$%&d& long go ES8 eby 8 1 8 7% in the home area, it's Bill gettinCoom straight away with three new songs for Halloween, helps & fiction.
York City on October 9th, a DeVival in Detroit on November 13th, and one in Little Rock on
November 20th.
Again, that's subgenius.com.