Actually, live and direct, our Slack fans, we actually have the Reverend is live and direct here in the house.
So we're going to Slackers and Slackites, we will be getting a sermon live and direct.
Slackites?
Yeah, Slackites.
Okay.
Those are the ones that hang from the ceiling.
I don't listen to the radio.
I read books.
Don't be that guy that reads books.
Listen to WCFB Cleveland 89.3 FM.
From PR News in Washington, I'm the nation's drug czar.
President Trump said that says the president is justifying false controversy over his fresh claim that his president didn't call families and nearby oil fields.
President Trump said PR report.
President Trump suggesting that he was killed while he was nine years old.
In southern Afghanistan in Afghanistan.
I mean, you could ask, did he call him as Bob Williams?
No one could ask you my obrums.
Trump said on Monday he was nine years old.
I guess I write letters and I also guess I call.
PR's reports.
Last month.
Reporting bad PR news.
On Wall Street, 22-972-1516-23.
I think 23 is only a number, but it's a number, you know, and so I think it's not the number.
Hugh Johnson.
Didn't stay that high very long.
At last checked.
U.S.-backed militias in Syria say this is PR news from Washington and called it a self-declared caliphate.
Kenya's deputy president says.
The essence of all this.
Kenyan deputy president says that, quote.
Kenya is taking part in an international effort to help Washington as that city attempts to recover from Saturday's PR news in Washington.
You saw me crying.
And the.
Self-genius.
Power of.
Squash.
The tears I shed were tears of.
And you'll surely find the way.
Subtitles by the Amara.org community
Once upon a time in an ordinary town, a rather ordinary man named Broderick returned home from his ordinary job and stared blankly into his refrigerator.
Broderick decided it would be nice to heat up a Swanson's frozen turkey dinner and spend the rest of his evening binge viewing season.
Two of Duck Dynasty.
While he was waiting on his delicious turkey dinner, Broderick drank three cans of malt liquor and took ten hits of Hindu Kush from his beautiful red bomb.
Then he got up to take a piss.
But when he walked through the kitchen, he found a tiny little black caterpillar that seemed lost.
He picked it up with a tissue and was going to flush it down the toilet.
But in a moment of drug-induced compassion, Broderick decided to release the caterpillar into his backyard, where it would have a chance at a second life.
He opened the screen door, climbed down the rickety wooden steps, and set the little caterpillar down in the soft green grass.
But when it didn't move, Broderick realized it wasn't a caterpillar at all.
It was just a silly old clump of lint from an old sweater.
Broderick chuckled to himself and said,
Gosh, I must be very, very stoned.
I must remember to buy more of that wonderful marijuana from the nice man at the Department of Motor Vehicles.
Broderick went back inside to the bathroom, sat down on the toilet, and began reading a magazine.
While he was passing wind, he felt something damp brushing against his nether regions.
And before he could react, a long black tentacle sprang up from between his legs.
It wrapped itself around his testicles and began pulling ferociously at his delicate genitalia.
A strange razor-sharp cartilage emerged and began sawing at the base of his spotum, and blood sprayed out in all directions.
The strange tentacle also had an ingenious noise cancellation device,
which muffled Broderick's screams as it ripped his legs from their sockets and spun them in all directions around the bathroom
before tossing them into a quivering pile of veins and sinew in the mildew-encrusted bathtub.
When Broderick woke up at the hospital,
all of his family and friends were there, and everyone had a nice time recounting the day's events.
But Broderick's mom had brought him a surprise.
Her eyes turned towards the hospital tray, and that's when Broderick saw it.
They remembered to bring his Swanson turkey dinner, with apple cobbler for dessert.
This was going to be the best Labor Day weekend ever.
And the best day ever.
And now, my friends, we have a very special guest vocalist.
A living legend from the beginnings of rhythm and blues.
Ladies and gentlemen, the one and only...
Bob!
He's gonna get me!
Honey, honey, who's gonna get you?
The President!
I saw him!
He's gonna get me!
The bomb dropped by the US President took out the entire city of Toronto,
and Fallout is expected to kill thousands more in the coming days.
Guess that's all the Whites can hope for these days.
Oh, for f***'s sake, White!
He's running around eating our pets and terrorizing our kids!
Okay, good. That's right.
So best thing is just lock up your garbage, and see if we can get the President to go away.
What are you doing, Bob?
Ah!
Have you been putting food out for the President?
Bob, come on.
You have to know it's not safe to have him here.
Bob, if Canada finds out the President is hiding here, they are going to nuke us!
What?
I think we have to assume that the President has...
eaten them.
Why are you here talking to me instead of trying to find the President?
Don't worry, we're close.
He's out in the woods somewhere.
Hackman Fears!
Oh yeah, that's better.
Can we go, please?
I've got a Hackman Fears!
Hackman Fears!
I'm going out of my mind!
Going out of my mind!
Here it is!
I've got a Hack...
Bob, for the love of Pete, our country is about to go to war!
I'm past being grown up.
I'm old and withered.
I am dead.
They wave ten pounds of wieners at me for the sake of the President.
But for no reason at all, they ask me if I'd like to go on a wiener fry.
I tell them no.
I've got you, Kanda!
Did you eat your parents?
Rip, rip, rip, rip, rip them!
I've got pills for you guys, too!
My father ate that!
Dance, dogs, home, out!
Scientists kill millions of free-roaming cats annually.
Cats face a host of hazards ranging from accidents to poisoning to disease.
Few cats survive, even if they appear to have escaped.
Come and do it. I am waiting.
I'm not going to take it anymore!
I'm mad as hell and I'm not going to take it anymore!
But you want to know something?
I think you're the freak.
I think you're the one that's different.
I can release a destructive power in a human being
that would make the split atom seem like a blessing.
But you're the one that's different.
To put it country simple,
Earth has a lot of things other folks might want,
like the whole planet.
And maybe these folks would like a few changes made.
Ow! I feel good!
Shazam!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Wipeout!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Subtitles by the Amara.org community
America! America!
Don't share to me!
You ask me why I love her?
We don't have any time.
I'll explain.
Have you drifted on a cold fog drifting over Kansas, sir?
Bayoued over San Francisco Bay?
Have you heard the bellow of a Bob White calling
in the diesel in the Appalachia Mines?
Look with awe and wonder drifting way up high
where men who braved a hard new world
first stepped on the diesel in the city dock?
Do you think of them when you stroll along a
rock?
Ray-eye.
Have you seen the mighty Peet?
Have you seen an eagle roll along Missouri's shore?
Have you felt it rage along the shore?
Is the word why a Mary?
From Alaska's Everglades to Maine,
my heart runs out.
My pulse risest at the might for Domain.
You ask me why I love her?
I've a million Appalachia Mines.
My beautiful Appalachia Mines.
Beneath God's wide-hold fog sky.
And found my good from shining sea to sea.
Ah!
Dear friends, and thank you for that lovely collage there.
Fernanda Nandy, Lee Murr, and John Wayne.
That, and also the titles, and also for,
oh, that longer collage, Media Barrage,
there was by,
Cool Hand Chris.
I have no idea what the source material was,
although it was just called Track One.
But what you want to know about, I know,
is that little story about Broderick and the Magic Caterpillar.
And that's from a brand new Rudy Schwartz project album
called Postal Code for Ham that just came out.
And that song had yours truly on vocals.
But now we have this new song by the El Queso All-Stars.
And it's called Practice What You Preach.
Violence is bad
And if you try to prove me wrong
I'll kick your ass
So you just better love your neighbor
Don't drive fast
When you're cruising in your car
But let me pass
Come on now, do a guy a favor
I don't take my homemade remedies
Cause they're no good for me
But I'll force them down the throat
Of every person I see
I don't practice what I preach
Because I'm not a man of my word
I'm not the kind of man I'm preaching to
And the lessons that I teach weren't meant to be
To a guy like me, cause they're for you
You can say that I'm a hypocrite
And all your stupid friends will think it's true
But I don't practice what I preach
Because I'm not the kind of man I'm preaching to
I don't practice what I preach
Cause I don't listen to music
And listen to ministry
Kinda get the ш me
Don't you hear this man?
Nothing goes up to the sky
But one life will rise another day
I come out hitting Ted Mechord cross Animal Friends
And it's without the'll of me
I just need to do dei—
I don't practice what I preach because I'm not the kind of man I'm preaching to.
And the lessons that I teach weren't meant to reach a guy like me, because they're for you.
You can say that I'm a hypocrite, and all your stupid friends will think it's true.
But I don't practice what I preach because I'm not the kind of man I'm preaching to.
And I think you're trying too hard at not trying hard enough.
The slack you lack will kick your ass because you're acting tough.
I know I leave you questions that you just don't understand.
But you can buy the answers, thirty-five bucks cash in hand.
I don't practice what I preach because I'm not the kind of man I'm preaching to.
And the lessons that I teach weren't meant to reach a guy like me, because they're for you.
You can say that I'm a hypocrite, and all your stupid friends will think it's true.
But I don't practice what I preach because I'm not the kind of man I'm preaching to.
And I'm preaching to.
And friends, that was the El Queso All-Stars.
With a new song, Practice What I Preach.
And this show is being broadcast and recorded on Sunday, July 4th.
At WCSB in Cleveland.
Four days before Thursday, July 5th.
At 7 a.m. X-Day, when the world will end for the normals.
And begin for the subgeniuses.
We just got back to Cleveland from Texas with a new doggie.
And we're about to drive five hours to the Wisteria Campground in Southern Ohio.
Which is going to make little Buddy.
Think we're homeless gypsies.
And then, suddenly, we'll be aboard my planet-sized escape and pleasure saucer built for countless.
And that little hell dog will really be confused.
Although, you know, that reminds me.
I'd better buy him a subgenius ordainment kit immediately.
Or he'll be left behind.
Like most of my neighbors and countrymen.
Friends, you should think about your priorities.
And your pets, too.
My fellow subgeniuses.
Otherwise, you'll be rising up to the saucers at 7 a.m.
Calling to your poor little pup, Spot.
Come, Spot, come.
But Spot will be stuck on the ground.
Because if he doesn't have that subgenius minister's card, Spot can't come with you.
But Buddy and y'all don't need to worry.
I'll beam up the Wisteria Campground.
The WCSB studios.
My old slacker mansion.
All of Stang Ranch.
Plus various museums and national and state parks.
Because to me, my friends,
X-Day isn't about destruction so much as preservation.
To my slack-filled heart, it's an opportunity to save everything cool from the humans.
Such as the subgeniuses.
And I'll let them do most of the killing and torturing while I'm gone.
While I go down my list.
Beaming up wonders of nature.
Majestic cathedrals.
And antique toy warehouses.
And now let's get back to this unusual collage.
By the cool, cool hand, Chris.
Praise Bob.
Oh, this music in the background, by the way, is by Reverend Nicholas McNutt.
It's called a sonata or tribute to John Lear.
And McNutt, he might be related to me.
Sort of.
Okay.
Alright.
Three, two, and one.
Now to continue with the tape recording.
These guys need to turn those frowns upside down.
And I got just the thing for that.
We call it...
Bob.
How much for your wife?
that I'm answering your question about the
Boy, we're all doomed.
Difficult part.
Ah!
Daddy!
Get some more money for you tomorrow.
Oh my god.
That looks like a second plane.
We do not forgive.
We do not forget.
Get back to work, you slacker.
Get all the freaking cops away from the building.
What's wrong?
That's it.
One day.
Gotta go.
Bitch, remove yourselves from the location.
I'm a such person.
Remove yourselves from the location at this time.
We got another tower collapse.
Look at me.
I'll help you if you want me to.
Don't be afraid.
I'm blind, but I can see through your soul.
And I can tell you're good.
Don't be afraid.
You never did know when to quit, did you?
Can you take a hint?
I want you to get out and leave me alone.
I don't want you around, do you hear?
They hate you.
They hate you when you...
question them.
They hate you when you expose them.
They hate you when you speak out.
They hate you when you resist.
They hate you when you stand together.
They hate you when you fight back.
I don't know who you are, where you're from, or what you want.
But if you threaten my freedom,
I'll kill you.
Access denied.
Why is it so important that you want to contact the governments of our Earth?
Because of death.
Because all you of Earth are idiots.
You big frothy frog-toe bucky-peeper-chick,
slack-jaw-slobber-slackin'-Bobby-banana-boat-foot-dragon-fluzy,
rake-tooth-gumpy-jump-toe-jack-jockin'-jack-mackler,
chip-tooth-chalk-chafin'-onion-toe-slew-foot-crack-toe-chain-chucker,
waffle-grid-iron-foot-claw-and-half-tooth-Nelly-Nelson,
and the flying-cartanian-twin-lookin'-fruit-lip-hanging-fruit-boot-bowler-head-three-pong-pin-head,
swashbucklin'-hippie-corduroy-codpiece-canker-canny-bake,
chisel-tooth-ear-eye-elbow-chisel-neck-cookie-head,
drill-cake-bakin'-cock-toe-crevice-creepin'-cracker-croaker,
double-belly-roll-bagel-bake-knock-knee-double-joint-jelly-eyed-steam-iron-toasted-head-brick-jaw,
coleslaw,
mommy-playin'-kickball-for-croaker-head-motherfucker-you,
and the
We have members throughout society, and all stratas of it worldwide.
Yet we have no leadership.
It's one voice. It's not individual voices.
That's why we don't show our faces. That's why we don't give our names.
We're speaking as one, and it's a collective.
We're given this gift, don't you know? The ability to understand.
Yet no one wants to understand.
We're given the ability to read.
I mean, read Nietzsche.
Read Thomas Mann. Read Spengler.
Joyce. Rimbaud.
Everything's out of whack.
People just worry about money now and deny their inner self.
Money. Money.
They walk through the night crowd protected by money, lulled by money, dulled by money.
No least single object anywhere that is not money.
Money. Money everywhere and still not enough.
And then no money, or little money, or less money, or more money.
But money. Always money.
And if you have money or you don't have money, it's the money that counts.
And money matters.
Money makes money. But what makes money make money?
Keep your mouth shut!
Easy, easy, Reverend!
That whole game, that whole game, somewhere.
And the movies, the movies ain't doing but program your thing.
They say, put them all on dope.
And all the movies start glamorizing drugs.
That's what Hollywood is about. Hollywood ain't about a trick.
Glamorize drugs. The French Connection Academy Award winning.
And how many have seen a movie called Midnight Express?
About a white bar over there.
And a turkey smuggling drugs.
And they caught him.
And the movie made the white drug smuggling the hero.
And the Turks who caught him made him the pig.
Help you out, champ.
Yes.
I just don't want to grow anymore.
I don't want to grow anymore.
Most illogical.
Blast him!
I saw him! He's gonna get me!
The bomb dropped by the U.S. President took out the entire city of Toronto.
And Fallout is expected to kill thousands more in the coming days.
Guess that's all the whites can hope for these days.
Oh, for f*** sake, white!
He's running around eating our pets and terrorizing our kids!
Okay, good. That's right.
So best thing is just lock up your garbage.
And see if we can get the President to go away.
Bob, for the love of Pete, our country is about to go to war!
You wanna know where there's a war?
There's a war on Christmas!
Nobody cares about that!
Cause guess who loves Christmas?
Bob?
BLEAAAGH!
I am your father.
Suspicious auditory stimulus detected.
Heaven will never be an extension of your body!
Your body will always belong to someone else.
The moon ripens and turns red.
It rots and is swallowed by the darkness.
They call this living.
There must be kind durante this time.
But the air, this land obviamente, has something to hold on.
Some values sự 발생 from time overseas are not a matter of public expression
Shoot compilator for real time measurement,
We are sailors on the deep In the storm's raging power
And the captain is asleep See us through the sinking hour
We are pilots in the blue Losing contact with the tower
No horizon lining you Talk us through the sinking hour
And the hammer striking louder
And the hammer striking louder And the hammer striking louder
As we face the sinking hour
We are sculptors of the storm We are sailors on the deep
And the captain is asleep See us through the sinking hour
Only con-de-sci-te
And the hammer striking louder
And the hammer striking louder As we face the sinking hour
We are sculptors of the storm We are sailors on the deep
We are merchants moving minds
Towards life
And it's now or never
One more time
Walk with me
The sinking hour
And the hammer striking louder
As we pass
The sinking hour
And the hammer striking louder
It's Walkenhorst and Porter.
Two of the Rainmakers.
Bob Walkenhorst, promise Bob.
And Jeff Porter.
I think that's his name.
Just occurred to me.
I knew another Jeff Porter.
Very different.
Yeah, Walkenhorst and Porter.
It's kind of a duo solo album.
And Friends.
if you have a birthday coming up,
I have a birthday wish for you.
Thinking of you on this most marvelous of days,
this kingly prince of a day,
this shining luck goddess of a day,
your birthday.
From now on, you can look forward to your years
becoming subjectively shorter and shorter
until they're like the day pages
falling magically off a calendar
in an old movie transition gimmick.
Months being ripped away every second or two.
Every birthday will increasingly feel
like it came too soon after the previous one.
Yes, you have much to look forward to,
but it'll gradually become harder and harder to appreciate
because it'll seem to be going by so fast.
You'll see.
If you're a king,
you're lucky.
This has been Reverend Stang's personal
happy birthday to you.
Although I originally wrote it for Dr. Argus Fox.
And while waiting for the lonesome cowboy
to call in again,
I'm looking at this cool newspaper
I just got in the mail from Dobbstown, Malaysia,
the Dobbstown Nanoheliograph 21X Day edition,
a special edition.
And the headline on it says,
subgenius ritual reaches majority.
X day, now old enough to vote.
Buy liquor, firearms.
21-year-old gathering obtains adulthood.
Because yes, friends,
in just a matter of four sleeps,
it's gonna come.
Finally, well, it'll be July 5th,
and it'll be seven in the morning.
And maybe this is 1998.
Maybe it's not.
Maybe it is.
We'll see.
And we'll see if this is Dave.
Is it Dave?
Dave?
It is.
It is Dave.
Regimondo.
How the bleeding hells are you?
I got a little funny place in my back
from being too funny while moving stuff around,
packing the van for X day.
My back is killing me today also.
Extinction day.
I just thought of that.
X day.
Extinction day.
I never made that connection.
Because I'm usually not thinking about,
I usually am not thinking about all the killing.
I'm thinking about all the getting,
the acquiring,
the acquiring.
Well, you're also so close to the object at hand
that you, you know,
you can hardly force any enamels down there
in the first place
if you're like one of these big ceramic steelers
in Spokane or Washington or something.
But the main thing is
you're constantly out there reminding everybody
that, you know,
it could be extinction day indeed.
Well,
either way,
even if it's not the aliens
that give us the power to
change,
change the situation,
there's going to be,
I mean,
the whole human race
is an extinction event in progress.
Yeah, you got that right.
But you know,
extinction events are just God's way
of wiping
his fundament.
Getting everything cleaned up
to make a new,
to, you know,
to rear back and pass another miracle.
But in my estimation,
it appears to me,
what if there is,
there is no God to wipe the poopy whistle
from the area?
Then it's up to us.
Then we got to build our own ship.
That's what I agree with also.
It doesn't mean we're going to do it.
It just means it is up to us.
No matter if there is a God or there isn't.
Or,
wait a minute,
I take that all back.
Right, right.
It doesn't,
it doesn't,
it don't matter none.
It just don't matter none.
It,
it doesn't matter to me.
Oh, are you doing Moronica Oensky?
I mean,
Moronica Valvolino?
Oh, no,
I was doing,
Moronica Trump.
I was doing a,
a forgotten Devo song actually.
But,
did you remember Moronica Trump
walking down to meet the sick and children
of the occupants of the Southwestern zones down there?
Yeah,
wearing that,
that callous outfit.
Well,
that just pleases the heck out
of all the stupid rednecks
and racists
and peckerwoods
and numbskulls.
They love that
because they know
it irritates the smarts
and the smart people.
And that's all they're,
that's really all they care about
is how does it make them feel?
It makes them feel good.
It's not about what,
you know,
the country or,
or,
or certainly not truth,
justice of the American way.
It's all about what makes them feel good.
And seeing a,
a racist cop mocking a child
who's,
who thinks his parents may be dead,
or abandoned him
while sitting in prison,
in a child prison.
That's the kind of thing
that makes those dumbasses so happy
because they know it irritates us, Dave.
And just think of those self-same positioning people
that like when they were talking about waterboarding,
that was an instrument of torture
that was used in the days of Torquemada
in the Spanish.
Anybody who knows anything about it
agrees it's torture.
My dad,
had to go through some training in the Navy
that involved waterboarding a guy
that was training, you know.
And he,
he was,
he considered it absolutely to be torture.
And of course,
that's what John McCain
and anybody who's been tortured says.
And then also think,
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
I mean, it's just,
but,
hey.
And then think of even our beloved Obama liberal boyfriend
and even in those days,
well,
let's go kill,
kill Osama bin Laden,
who's probably been,
already been dead for five years.
Or kill somebody right in his own home
without abrogation or adjunction
by a legal person or something.
War is hell, baby.
War is hell.
Or hack, I'm sorry.
I wouldn't want to.
Oh, yeah, it's peace.
It's hack.
War is hack.
Peace hack.
Oh, wait.
I know.
I'm so confused now.
Truth and lies are the same now.
That's what they,
both sides keep saying.
I don't trust anybody.
Why should you?
Well, I trust,
I trust Bob to rip me off.
Oh, Bob Dobbs,
to rip me off.
That's one thing you can count on.
But it,
but it,
somehow I'll feel like it's okay
when Bob does it.
As long as the third nostril is opened wide,
and this is opened wide,
then...
Well, think about it though, Dave.
A year ago,
well, we were making satirical jokes
about the patriot camps.
But it'll be okay,
Reverend Pease said.
They'll have snacks.
And we laughed,
because we thought that was a little,
not really going to happen.
It was just funny to think that
they could possibly really kind of get that extreme.
And then they did!
Oh, yeah.
Then they did!
The Trump stops became real.
I mean, the worst fantasies
by sick humor satirists
have become real.
And everything's upside down
and flip-flop.
The right-wingers love the commies
and hate the freedom of the press.
What the hell?
There's only one amendment in their constitution.
That's the Second Amendment.
They constantly threaten you on the air
on these,
these AM talk shows
that threaten,
constantly threaten to kill you.
Especially if you have any socialist leanings
of which they don't even know
what that word means.
I mean, who does?
I mean,
communards must think
unlike, I suppose,
a little bit.
But,
um, man,
it tickles my fancy.
It irritates my torus,
my urethra,
and it makes me just
all go banana hog wild
just thinking about it.
Well, in that little country
only about 100 miles north of us,
they completely legalized
recreational marijuana
across,
the whole country.
As well as medical, yes.
I think that,
I think that may
shift some demographics.
I'm hanging on to my passport.
I was just thinking that today,
you know,
get a big boat
and it's only 52 miles
across the lake.
Go over to Port Stanley
or one of those places like that.
And apply for asylum.
Yeah.
Where they'll laugh at you.
Well, because it is a joke,
but they won't really laugh at you.
They'll actually give you asylum.
Because you're supposed to.
Well, it doesn't mean anything.
Of course not.
Today is Canada Day.
Did you know that?
Huh?
What?
Today is Canada Day.
It's like their 4th of July.
Oh, I did not know that.
You know, 1876,
all these three huge macro provinces
all decided to get together
and have more freedom
from the queen
or the aristocracy,
whoever it was.
And that's why
they all,
they all smoked
the humbling nomadic
herbal rest.
Because they were atrophying
in a scumbag.
At least the last time
I checked it,
I didn't really want to,
but I was forced to.
I've been having to
check a thing
and put
antibacterial ointments
on it.
Is it your thing
or is it your dog's thing?
No, it's mine this time.
I have to protect it
because I'm about to go
go out in the woods,
you know,
for a couple of days,
not for two weeks or anything,
but, you know,
because X Day's starting,
like, well,
I'm going to drive out there Tuesday
into the tick-infested,
beautiful, diverse forest
and use lots of bug repellent
of all kinds.
And then I'm going to be boarded.
I'm going to be boarding
the escape vessels
because of my faith in Bob
or Bob will completely
screw us again,
laugh at us,
go, X Day could happen
any minute, you fools.
Why do you cling to your ritual?
And then we'll have Starwood
and I'll end up being out there
at that festival ground
for two weeks solid.
Dressed up like Harry Potter
and all that stuff like that
with a big, with a cloak
and a pointy hat
and everything.
No, no, no.
I dress up like a subgenius
with a doctor's surgical outfit
and a big chainsaw
golf club combination.
That's the doctor look.
That's being a good subgenius
dressing up like a,
like a little Bobby.
Awful artists and drug addicts
were as similar or were as honest
as the air stuff in a crowd
that we might have to deal with
some days.
It's just too much to contemplate.
They got it from the left.
They got it from the right.
They got it from the top and bottom.
We feel like we're boxed up
into a Transylvanian little hole
or some decipherable
recreational room
and we can never, never escape.
I saw a little funny
two panel drawing,
a cartoon,
a two panel cartoon
by a subgenius
that I don't know on Facebook.
It said,
here's a genius
and the genius is a little,
little stick figure
and he's having a,
there's a problem on one side.
The genius looks at the problem,
solves the problem
and fixes the problem.
And that goes,
here's the subgenius.
The problem comes at the subgenius
and the subgenius makes a joke
and it has a funny,
it doesn't solve the problem
but he makes a joke about it
and it shows this,
the subgenius stick figure face
is laughing
but it has tears coming,
from its eyes.
Has this sad expression of
joyous sadness and pain
and irony.
And I thought,
that's pretty poignant there.
The genius solves the problem
and the subgenius
makes a funny joke about it
but it doesn't go away.
Either way,
it doesn't go away.
The subflamorals
or whatever you want to call them,
they're always joking.
It doesn't matter if anybody's,
dying or not
or if things have reached
the most sorrowful ending
they could possibly iterate.
They just like to ride the bus
and point at different people outside.
Just like Ken Kesey,
remember the magic warthog
in there?
Or that was the guy with the frogs.
That's funny you should mention Ken Kesey.
I was reading up on him
because I can't help but identify
with,
him and the Merry Pranksters
to a certain extent.
You know,
you write a book
and suddenly there's this weird club.
Anyway,
what I got to thinking,
well,
I've been worried about
being sick and dying lately
since I've got a Medicare card in my pocket now.
I'm about to turn 65.
I thought,
but hey,
you know,
I outlived Ken Kesey.
I think he died in his 50s.
So I looked it up.
I was wrong.
He died when he was a year older than I am now.
And he died of,
of a,
well,
he had been diagnosed with diabetes
about a year earlier,
which is something I'm planning to do.
And then he had,
there was,
he had to have a liver operation.
They found something on his liver.
They were just going to remove a spot from his,
just the onions,
I guess.
And he didn't survive the liver operation.
He died,
died rather suddenly.
Well,
you know,
that wasn't supposed to happen,
but again,
I was thinking,
what else do I have in common with old Reverend Ken Kesey,
who was by the way,
a,
a subgenius minister whose subgenius name was Reverend Hardly Visible.
Cause he had,
he had done.
That's a good name for somebody who wanted lots of visibility in this
earth while existence of personality plus.
Well, no, he did.
He did it for,
he did for a few years,
but after his second pot bust,
he settled down and just kind of hung out on his farm and
wrote occasionally for hippie magazines.
And I can identify with that too.
Well, you're a hypnotist,
so you should take at least a modicum of sanity with a grain of salt.
Modicum of sanity,
a grain of salt,
a loaf of fro,
a jug of mind and a bag of toothpaste and pee some friendly orphans with no
teeth.
And,
uh,
I don't know.
I think I might've crossed some sort of limits there.
Yeah,
man.
You crossed the Lummox with the ox.
You crossed the Lummox with a hound dog.
You get a lum dog.
Yeah.
Lum dog.
Well, that's ridiculous.
There is,
whoops,
I'm sorry.
Well, you know,
princess,
we isn't here tonight because we don't know what'll happen when we,
if we leave young buddy alone in the Cleveland house.
We just don't know.
There's not much he can tear up because it's almost completely empty,
but I'm sure he'll find something.
So we're,
uh,
yeah,
we're,
we're one of us has to dog sit constantly until we train that little fellow better or until the world ends on July 5th,
1998.
You either learn to relax real quickly or you could,
we could just leave the planet and let it blow it all to hell.
They're going to whether we leave or not.
That's the problem.
And even if they don't,
it'll blow itself some way.
But as George Carlin pointed out,
the planet will be fine.
It's us that are screwed.
The planet will bounce back.
Something like a dodo will eventually appear on some island again.
And something like a human being will appear a million years from now again.
And something like a human would,
what might something like a human be not,
not in that lesson of ranking and so forth,
but human,
what kind of human would it produce?
Not a human being.
Well,
you like to think that they would discover the ruins of our cities and,
uh,
and figure out what we'd done wrong and then try to learn from our mistakes.
But the problem is we haven't been around long.
Even with our giant buildings,
we haven't been around long enough to leave a permanent mark.
Every city in,
Oh yeah,
yeah.
But it'll,
it doesn't take nature very long to just devour it all again.
The reason I bring that up is it's been pointed out that there could have been an Atlantis quote unquote.
Uh,
and in fact there have been.
South America,
it turns out is full of completely buried cities with huge pyramids,
not the famous ones that have been dug out,
but a whole lot of them that have only been recently discovered.
In fact,
people laughed at the,
at the archeologists who said that there were buried more buried cities and there've been,
you know,
those guys,
those cities were around for thousands of years.
Well,
just think of Cahokia.
Then they disappeared.
You know,
they,
those cities disappeared long before the Europeans got here.
Think of Cahokia and East St. Louis,
city of over 2 million people just appeared as far as historians are concerned to,
to just wiped off the map not long after Columbus landed,
which turned out not to be true at all.
And then what,
what was I saying again?
Oh man.
Well,
it doesn't take long for a society to collapse.
We're going to put them all in Cahokia until somebody said,
you know,
this pyramid here looks really obvious.
You can't hide this.
You can't tear it down.
And they started this movement and they turned into a national resource.
Well,
you know,
it won't be one for long.
It'll,
it'll be a,
a Mr.
Moneybags resource and they will put a mall there.
The Trump administration is trying to make sure they can put malls right in the middle
of Grand Staircase Escalante,
the last barely,
the,
the almost the least explored remaining part of the United States.
And they want to make sure that it can be explored by highway with Burger King's lining
the highway.
Yep.
And,
and,
you know,
a tram to the bottom of the Grand Canyon.
And it won't be so grand when they fill it up with plastic cups and plastic water bottles.
But,
uh,
I won't be around to see that cause I'll either die first,
I hope,
or I'll be on my escape vessel laughing,
you know,
toasting the old earth.
And,
uh,
toasting the people.
The old,
old earth is toasted.
And toasting the non-subgeniuses on it.
Perhaps you might be.
Of course,
they're going to toast anyway.
It's getting hotter.
Yep.
They're going to be as red as reptiles.
Well,
it's getting hotter in some places and colder in other places.
I don't know what places it's getting colder in.
Oh,
it's getting colder in the Northern US.
It's getting colder in,
I,
it was 70 degrees in Stang Ranch this morning.
And 90 here in Cleveland.
How does that happen?
Changing weather patterns.
Uh,
global warming doesn't mean everything gets hotter.
It means there's kind of an overall heating.
But when the wind patterns and the ocean patterns change,
that can cause glaciation.
So go figure.
You just don't like me when I think some people know how to manipulate the weather.
Well,
I don't think they manipulate the weather for profit.
No,
I don't think they do.
I don't think that they can.
And I don't think,
I think it's going to take a long,
long time to manipulate it back to normal.
You can't just wave a wand and make gases come and go in vast unthinkable quantities.
Well,
just think of what,
like it almost melted almost all the way up to the North Pole this year.
Oh,
yeah.
Yeah,
I know.
Oh,
I,
oh,
I know much worse things than you do,
Dave.
Much,
much worse.
I don't like to go on and on about it,
but,
uh,
I think the oceans are all going to be dead.
Look,
again,
it'll take,
take a little longer than I won't be around for it.
But I just found out I got another grandkid on the way.
And he or she is going to have to see that stuff.
They're going to have to read,
they're going to have to pick up a paper and go,
well,
the last gorilla has,
dog.
You can see it sometimes without trying.
I remember there was a fish and chip shop I used to go to that had a thing on the wall
that showed that there were a thousand different varieties of Great Lakes fish.
I mean,
you can just live on fish.
And now there's what?
There's two,
there's walleye,
or there's three.
There's perch,
walleye,
pike,
and zebra mussels.
They are delicious.
Oh,
and they're trying to bring back the Lake Erie oysters,
but they're having problems.
The water is so polluted that even if they reproduce and everything,
what difference will it make?
What difference is it going to make?
My God.
Think of the floating massive debris of plastic in the middle of the Pacific Ocean.
I never thought I would see anything like that.
Now my grandfather's going to have to see it.
I mean,
my grandchildren.
From heaven,
because he's in outer space now.
Heaven is a big cloud.
I'm a spaceman now,
but my grandchildren are not spacemen,
I swear.
I promise to.
Oh,
they'll find a way to build condos on that floating pile of trash.
It's just that there won't be anybody to live in them because there won't be any fish or rain or crops or,
you know,
because the rain will be all acetic and,
and,
and there are no more family farms.
But wait a minute,
come on,
man,
if you're going to vote negative,
let's go out and vote.
Because when you don't vote,
that meant you voted for the person that won,
which means you voted for Trump.
If you,
if you,
listener,
if you're an American and didn't vote in that election because you wanted to teach someone a lesson because it's really all about you and how it makes you feel,
you voted for Trump.
It made more sense to you as it my case,
but I still,
I never mind.
Well,
Dave,
believe it or not,
the show is coming towards an end.
Casi abierto,
meaning almost closed.
Open.
That's right,
abierto.
And so that means we have to say it's the hour of slack from the Church of the Subgenius.
And you can learn more by subgenius.com.
It'll make you so calm at subgenius.com.
And we have two post office boxes.
The Cleveland one is still good for the next few months.
But I'm not going to give that.
Okay,
Dave,
thank you.
Thank you.
And good night and thank you for the luxurious appetite.
We'll see you on the saucers.
I believe.
I may be.
Rob said,
Oh,
I may not.
I hope.
Well,
keep in touch,
but not touchy feely.
No means no,
Dave.
Right.
You're supposed to say keep in touch,
but not too much.
Know what I mean?
He's supposed to wink.
He's supposed to get real flatulent,
real loud and real gumpy and stuff like that.
And then I guess they arrest you and take you to one of them camps.
Right.
But there'll be snacks.
Okay.
Time for PR news.
Snacks.
From PR news in Washington,
I'm fighting terrorism and attacking the U.S.
Authorities should be considered armed and dangerous.
NFL Commissioner Roger Goodell should stand during the national anthem.
It's,
uh,
and it's also,
On Wall Street,
Secretary of State Ray Tiller says this is heartbreaking PR news.
Someone will be held accountable.
Where'd you two take this elevator from, Shangri-La?
I was supposed to be a boy named Thomas.
Whee!
I'll get him.
But no talking behind my back.
This is so rich.
It was a stone groove, my man.
I have a brother who's a drug addict.
I'm very proud of him.
Thank you for representing me, man.
We are connected!
Mac Douze Vs.
Fox News away!
All characteristics and assumptions introduced in thisnel.
I'm very proud of you.
for a revolution.
A revolution.
I ain't gonna be your punching bag.
Stones and sticks,
bones and bricks,
hear the sound of something breaking.
Wrong look,
right hook,
with your bad combination.
I ain't gonna be your punching bag.
Ain't going down,
bound and gagged.
I ain't gonna be your punching bag.
I'm in deep water here,
hear the sound of something sinking.
Faith and hope ought to get me afloat.
What was I thinking?
I ain't gonna be your punching bag.
Ain't going down, bound and gagged.
Boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, a ton of bricks, a ton of feather.
Boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, the room's in the living room,
I can't sweep it together.
Boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, the room's in the living room,
Boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, the room's in the living room,
Where's my coat?
Where's my hat?
Where's my shredded dignity?
Where's my gloves?
My lost love?
You pounded it out of me.
I ain't gonna be your punching bag.
Ain't going down, bound and gagged.
All right, but how's the ball almost there?
Yeah, it's nice and high out, right down, you say?
Yeah!
Oh, yes, dear friends.
That was Bob Walkenhorst from an early solo album called The Beginner.
Punching Bag from The Beginner by Bob Walkenhorst.
And now this.
From PR News in Washington, I'm expected to top the agenda.
President Donald Trump is accused of involvement in the 2012 attack on an American consulate in a U.S. court.
Trump is the second person brought to the U.S. to face charges for PR's reports.
Faces three charges, including his alleged PR news, Washington.
Trump is due to touch down in Tocan and south of the Philippines on Sunday, where he'll be welcomed by Japanese PR News instead.
One key factor is a state's members with Indians who admit the palisade from this direct stemson.
A Libyan man reports movie producer Harstein is incredible.
Incredible for the cultural agency's founding ideals.
New York City police believe this is PR.
That's right.
I mean, I mean, so.