At last I have control of your radio tubes!
Uh, and I do too!
Good! This is Ren Hoak!
And this is Stimson J. Cat of the Ren and Stimpy Show!
And you're listening to the Hour of Slack!
Keep listening, you idiots!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Else I shall kill you!
Shane, look out!
The Self-Genius Hour of Slack!
If anything is excellent or praiseworthy,
we should find something else to do instead.
Now you're starting to get odd.
That's right. Watch it.
Oh!
The problem is, it's special.
Hard of thinking of us.
I cannot.
You really tolerate it well.
And what happens is an old pan,
a pair of neon and old pizelle,
it thins skinless serrates,
and the back of it now comes critched.
In fact, in there, in a gay spunner,
to live in a sea of pus.
The openings of this show, down there,
were by, all of them,
Fernanda Nande, Lee Murr.
More, of course, from him.
My friend, the Pope of all Europe!
Pope Dave Lee Black!
An exile from his own country in America!
Well, I'll tell you more about the conspiracy.
It is Pope Dave Lee Black!
Praise Bob!
Hi-ya!
Hallelujah!
Now, before I get started,
I've noticed that most of you are standing in the back.
I think you need to come up here a little bit.
Come on, come on to the front.
Come on to the front!
Come on, don't stand in the back.
Step up, step up!
Step on up!
Don't be afraid.
Don't be afraid of this man,
this smiley man with a pipe in his mouth.
Come on, don't smile!
Okay.
Now, I want everybody...
He's not real! He's not real!
I want everybody to bow your hands.
Bow your hands in a moment of...
A moment of truly sacred...
Noise!
No!
Praise Bob!
No one wants to...
Woo!
Now, I know most of you have been wondering,
what is this church of the subgenius?
What are you?
We're a...
Well, just to make it a little bit simple,
we are a sex, drugs, and rock and roll,
end of the world, UFO religion,
and the world's only true religion.
Praise Bob!
Pray, on the cross.
Follow.
on the cross.
Point to Bob now! Point to Bob now!
Point to Bob and the holy photo opportunity!
I'm going to prove to you this is the only world's true only religion.
There were maniacs who flew planes into buildings in New York on the 11th of September.
And they flew these planes into these buildings with a promise they would go to heaven
and they would receive each 42 virgins.
Not in the Church of the Sub-Genghis, my friends!
No! You don't have to fly a plane into a building to get virgins!
Hell, who wants virgins?
The Church of the Sub-Genghis for $30?
You don't have to fly a plane and you get professionals!
Not virgins, but professionals!
Now, this is true.
There are other virgins.
There are other popes in Europe.
But I am the only pope in Europe that passes out condoms.
It's true.
That other pope won't even wear a condom!
As a matter of fact, I'll give you one.
I'm not the only pope in the world that passes out condoms.
I'm the only pope in the world that passes out used condoms.
I'm the only pope in the world that eats used condoms!
A-ha!
Illuminatus...
Electrus...
The plan was fixed. All we needed was guitar.
Then around the bend, an old friend fell down from the sky.
We helped him on our voyage to the happiest vie.
Then we racked our brains too far.
The thing that we would advertise
Illuminatus, Illectus, Immaculatus
Illuminata, Electra, Immaculata
Immaculata, Electrus, Illuminata
Illuminatus, Electrus, Immaculatus
Illumin, Illumina, Illuminatus
Illumina, Illectra, Electrus
Illumina, Immaculatus
Illuminata, Illumina, Illumina
That's our story, simple as can be
Though the planet's torched with dangers
And never guarantees
We might be eaten by dragons on the way
But we might be eaten by dragons on the way
But we might prove indigestible, perhaps you'll agree
Illuminatus, Illectus, Immaculatus
Illuminata, Electra, Immaculata
Immaculata, Electrus, Illuminata
Illuminatus, Electrus, Immaculatus
Illumin, Illumina, Illuminatus
Illuminata, Electra, Electrus
Illuminata, Immaculata
Immaculatus
Illuminata
Illuminata, Lake scheda
Illuminata, Beltrass
Illuminata, Herculean
Illumina, Illuminata
Illuminata, Lux悪
Illuminata, Yi ya
Illuminata, Dron
Illuminata, Dracutia
Illuminata, Nyscrath
Illuminata, tama
Illuminata, The Elephant
bang woo
bill smoking
yay
you live in
Raleigh North Carolina
what's your
what suddenly
the economy
gets a boost
fuck
now I've been
getting that look
a lot lately
because I started
smoking again
and performing
abortions
so you know
I mean
everywhere I turn
these
sometimes I can
hardly get out of bed
but I just love
smoking folks
I'm sorry
I went nine months
without them
and man
what can I tell you
the hook is fucking
deep man
I'm telling you
they just dropped
the bait
back in the water
boom
plop
they weighed me
you know
hung me up
caught a big one
but I have this
theory
actually it's a hope
that if that scenario
is at all true
when you die
and you go to heaven
and St. Peter
meets you at the gate
if that's at all true
I believe the first thing
he's going to ask you is
you got a light
you mean y'all smoke here
yeah that's why it's heaven
these aren't clouds
this is cigarette smoke buddy
hell is non-smoking
you want to look down
at them for a minute
alright
I can't believe it's not smoke
I don't know what they do
to their bodies
it smells like an ashtray
I'm trying to eat my food
why would they want to do that
to themselves
do you know how stupid that is
god how hellish
no shit
light up
come on in
Hendrix is on harp tonight
let me stand next to your fire
yeah
and no one beats Hendrix man
fuck Eddie Van Halen
fuck Steve Vai
no one beats fuck
Hendrix was an alien
okay
the ship landed
they said Jimmy
show them how it's done
we'll pick you up in 28 years
and you know what Jimmy said
alright
he plays his cock
did y'all know that
they just strung his cock
he played it with his teeth
does that make him gay
I love people who are dead
for some reason
all my heroes are dead
Keith Richards
you know that's right
for instance
ah
what do you say we do some comedy
I always like to put some comedy
in my shows
here's an impression of
Keith Richards
some people are
start talking to him
it's so real
Keith
boy Keith went over the edge
years ago
went over the fucking edge
right now
right now everyone thought
that's it
Keith's gone
and then they looked over the edge
and there was a fucking ledge
and he had hit and landed on it
there's a ledge beyond the edge
Keith was like
I hit a fucking ledge
I'm alright
throw down me guitar
got a song
there's a ledge beyond the edge
Keith landed on it
so shake it
I literally
worried about this
People commit to just
wonderful's
or even better
ill call it
it's so true
this guy continues to become
a mind who wasn't
always motions
honorary subgenius minister one month before learning that he had just died.
Go!
Lemur!
Good!
Am I the only one here who feels that tremor in the force?
Or did somebody just cut a fart?
Did someone just bite a tooth?
Did I just hear the moan of the trouser ghost?
Or did the pipe just take a puff of Bob?
You see, friends, our guru Bob Dogs does not smoke the pipe.
The pipe smokes Bob!
And if that pipe ever stops smoking, that's when we're in real trouble.
Because, you know, here's what it really is all about.
This is the truth.
If you're new to this subgenius thing,
and don't know and really came here for an explanation,
sorry.
But I can tell you it's like this.
This is the true subgenius in slap.
Look at that Bob.
He's so stupid looking.
I could sit here looking at how stupid looking he is
for the rest of my life.
Look how stupid looking he is, sitting there looking at me.
That's what the church of the subgenius is all about.
Well, some days.
Some days, friends, it's...
But see, it's not about the intelligence.
It's about sense, common sense, sense of humor.
The subgenius, as Dr. Onan Kanabite said,
is pre-targeted.
Pre-targeted.
You know, we'd rather be stupid than their idea of smart.
We'd rather be stupid than their smart.
That's what J.R. Bob Dobbs said to Onan.
Friends, we get to see the world through rose-colored glasses
and Bob holds them up for us.
We pay for a subscription to what we really think.
And, you know, you might say,
well, that's why they call it subgenius.
But really, friends,
are the normals.
Are the normals that much smarter than us?
Have you watched TV lately?
Do we have to?
You know, the less you watch it,
the more retarded it seems when you do watch it.
I don't have cable, deliberately.
But when I go to a hotel,
I turn the cable TV on,
and then I'm locked in,
and I sit there switching channels for five hours,
going, thank God I don't have this cable stuff.
Because I can't stop.
But, you know, it's gotten to the point
where they're so sophisticated,
the television producers and makers,
that, you know, they've taken it, like, conceptually.
They go ahead, they gloat brazenly
at what cows we are to watch their dumb crap.
This reality TV stuff.
Actually, I'm surprised it took him so long to start doing this,
because it's actually not a TV show.
It's not a bad idea.
The average dumb-ass normal human being
is more entertaining
than a lot of what they were scripting and putting on.
And if, you know, they are following people around
with cameras as they act stupid
or they endanger themselves,
that's fine, you know, that's no problem.
But it's almost as if,
it's like you watch Jerry Springer
or so many of these shows,
and you're going, God, this is so stupid.
People must be really dumb to watch this.
You don't change the channel, though.
And it's as if,
and they're just so upfront about it.
The television itself tells you how bad it is.
They make fun of how bad they are
and how dumb you are to watch them.
It's as if they're saying,
break free of the Matrix after this message.
I wasn't going to bring this up.
I saw it.
Sometimes they're inadvertently dumb.
I saw an ad for Yoplait yogurt
that they were saying,
I guess it's like every time you buy the yogurt,
they give a little bit of money to breast cancer.
And the announcer actually said,
together we can lick breast cancer.
And, you know, the Anna Nicole Smith show
and my cousin, by the way.
You know, you watch that stuff,
and you go, maybe everybody's doing that.
Maybe everybody's looking at the TV saying,
man, I can't believe how stupid this is.
People watch this stuff?
Cool.
Yoplait must be stupid.
I could sit here forever looking at how stupid
people must be to be watching this stuff.
And I'm guilty of it, too.
But the ultimate reality TV show, friends,
started this Wednesday.
It's a great follow-up to that miniseries from 91.
You know, they've got some new special effects.
They've improved all the graphics and things.
Reality TV.
They've certainly taken it all the way, I guess.
Viewed paleoanthropologically,
television paints quite a visible picture of its very self.
Incredible levels of talent dedicated to the giant alibi for pinkness
and the dope rating of the language itself, friends.
Changing words to mean less and less instead of more.
And oddly enough, using more words to do it.
And the news, my God, man.
I swore off the news totally for three years.
But of course, on September 11th,
I had to start tuning in again.
The news is either evil or it is a sin.
We don't know which yet.
But we know that, well, maybe even if the revolution was televised,
television will not be revolutionized.
And it is.
And it is addictive.
And even I, you know, I try to fight back.
But, you know, we're all slackers.
As the great slacker princess, we said once,
I have feist in me.
I have feist.
But it just can't be sourced properly.
In order to fight, friends, the subgenius must have slack.
True slack, though.
And everybody knows that.
You know, I don't have to explain that.
And I'm with everybody who's anybody.
But not if it's for everybody, because I'm cool.
You know, I'm not, I'm only into it if it's only for everybody who's anybody.
I'm too independent to follow the big crowd.
I follow the small crowd.
Good.
Real independent thinker.
And everybody knows that everybody who's anybody already knew that,
except for the nobodies.
Nobody who's anybody doesn't know that.
I'm nobody's fool.
Not nobody who's anybody, anyway.
I'm not the brightest crayon in the box.
Everyone says I'm dumber than a bag of rocks.
I barely even know how to put on my own pants.
But I'm a genius in France.
Genius in France.
I may not be the sharpest hunk of cheese.
I got a negative number on my SATs.
I'm not good looking.
And I don't know how to dance.
But nevertheless, in spite of the evidence, I am so widely considered to be a
genius in France.
Genius in France.
People say I'm a geek, a moronic little freak, an annoying pipsqueak with an unfortunate physique.
If I was any dumber, they'd have to water me twice a week.
But when the mademoiselles see me, they all swoon and shriek.
They dig my mystique.
They think I'm c'est magnifique.
When I'm in Paris, I'm the chicest of the chic.
They love my body odor and my bad toupee.
They love my stripy shirt and my stupid beret.
And when I'm sipping on a Perrier in some café down in Saint-Tropez,
it's hard to keep the fans at bay.
They say, sign my Poodle, Sibu play.
Sign my Poodle, Sibu play.
Poodle, Poodle.
Folks in my hometown think I'm a fool.
Got too much chlorine in my gene pool.
A few peas short of a casserole.
A few buttons missing on my remote control.
A few fries short of a heavy meal.
I couldn't pour water out of a booth.
With instructions on the heel.
Instructions on the heel.
But when I'm in Reuvence, I get free croissants.
Yeah, I'm the guy every French lady wants.
And if you ask them why, you're bound to get this response.
He's a genius in France, genius in France.
Genius in France.
I'm not the brightest bulb on the Christmas tree.
But the folks in France, they don't seem to agree.
They say, bonjour mon chien.
Would you take ze picture with me?
I say oui, oui.
That's right.
Oui, oui.
He says oui, oui.
I'm done.
Now I'm gonna make a big splash.
I may look a little dumber than a box of hair.
But those Frenchies don't seem to care.
Don't know why I'm on France, but they love me there.
I'm a genius in France.
Gonna make a big splash when I show up in Cannes.
Gonna make those Frenchies scream.
Use a man, use a man, use a man!
Like a fine red wah!
I got that shit to say wah!
I got that shit to say wah-wah-wah-wah-wah!
Hoo-wee-oo!
Wah-wah-wah-wah-wah!
Bow-dee-dee-bow-dee-bow-dee-bow-bow-dee-dee-bow-dee-bow-dee-bow-bow-dee-bow!
I'm a taco short of a combo plate
But by some twist of fate all the frogs think I'm great
Oh, the men all faint and the women scream
They like me more than heavy cream
When I'm in Versailles, I'm a popular guy
My oh my, I'm as French as apple pie
Apple pie!
They think I'm awful
Fully witty
A riot and a half
When I tell a stupid joke they laugh
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha
And laugh
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha
People and friends have lots of attitude
They're snotty and rude, they like disgusting food
But when they see me they just come unglued
They think that I am one happening dude
Bow-bow-bow-bow-bow-bow-bow-bow-bow
I'm about as sharp as a bowling ball
But they like me better
Than Charles de Gaulle
Andre knew it's very true
The room temperature's higher than my IQ
But they love me more than Gerard Depardieu
How did this happen?
I don't have a clue
I'm not the greatest tractor on the farm
I don't have any skills or grace or charm
And most people look at me
Like I'm all covered with ants
But I'm a genius in France
Genius in France
And I'm never going back
I'm never going back
I'm never, never, never, never going back home again
I'm tearing up my return flight ticket
Gonna tell the folks back home
Where they can't stick it
Cause I'm never going back
I'm never going back
The girls back home never gave me a chance
But I've shown off goddamn frogs and some kind of trance
And I'm aware that it's a most improbable circumstance
But great googly moogly
I'm a genius in France
Every Frenchie that I meet
Just can't wait to kiss my feet
Get in line, fuck her up, too sweet
Poundity, poundity, poundity
I'm getting even more famous by the hour
I'm stuffed with pastries and drunk with power
Now they're putting up my statue by the Eiffel Tower
A little more to the left, boys
A little more to the left
I'm the biggest dork there is alive
My mom picked out my clothes for me
Till I was thirty-five
And I forgot to mention
I'm not even welcome at the Star Trek convention
But the Frenchies think that my poop don't stink
I'm a genius in France
Say, would you pass the Grey Poupon?
Merci beaucoup
Weird Al Yankovic, of course, from the album Hoodle Hat
I think that I ought to begin by saying that our subject today concerns silly
Oh, let's take an example
Probably the silliest personal emergency that can come to a man
is his silly wedding.
Oh!
Rather than keep you in suspense any longer,
the ladies will have to leave the room.
Thank you.
Are you all right?
I'll say that we are guilty,
but also look silly.
No, no.
Oh.
Oh, yes.
24 and a half.
9 and 3 quarters.
13 and a quarter.
24 and a quarter.
42.
42 and a quarter.
39.
43.
Well, I guess I'm in the way here.
So I see.
Good night.
Did it.
And now,
a puzzling evidence
and glass madness
about 20 years ago.
What you gonna sing about
at five o'clock
in the morning?
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh.
Yeehaw.
Talking about Bob Dobbs
and the church,
everything in a whole big mess
on the floor.
Just back.
A disorganized first church,
a disorganized mess on the floor.
You're a little intimidated.
I'm joining any kind of church.
You can call a church
anything you want.
Foundation or a club
or just something to look at.
We call it Church of the
fill-in-the-blank.
And Bob Dobbs
is the biggest blank
to fill in you'll ever see.
And that's all it is.
Friends and neighbors,
out there listening tonight,
we hope that you're putting
your hands on the radio
and getting the full impact
of this message
that's coming down to you.
Face at the very fact
of your eyes
moving across the page
at this very moment
as you try to read your radio
is inevitably
and subatomically decreed.
Your brain is working
without your control.
You are locked into the machinations
of a cosmic puppeteer
who worked your strings
so skillfully
you never knew they were there
until now.
Feels good, doesn't it?
Oh, it feels so very good
when I've got the strings
pulled tight.
Oh!
But we can show you
where the strings
are attached.
And how to sync up
with a puppeteer.
Will this say
life after death,
reincarnality,
psychic powers,
immortality,
invisibility,
nirvana,
communications,
higher challenges,
slack, slack, slack,
so on.
They may be pink,
but their money is green.
So I walked into the
air conditioning.
I walked into the jaws
of corporate sellout city today.
You did?
Did you?
Yeah, I bent over and said,
let me in the club.
You didn't say
put it in here,
but don't be gentle?
I said, you put it
wherever you want.
Just let me in the club.
He doesn't even want it.
Dome.
When they release the gas,
let me in the dome.
Lube or no lube,
don't matter to me,
but you let me in,
you got your way.
That's why you got into it,
man.
You don't like the lube.
You like it rough.
So we'll see if I get
called back in
to the sacred orb
for round two.
Are you going to have to kiss?
Round two will be
a showdown
between three people,
like good,
the bad,
and the ugly.
Remember the good,
the bad,
and the ugly?
At the end,
it was three people,
not a shootout
between two people.
But a shootout
between three people.
Job interviews
are more and more
like American Idol.
This was definitely
They are definitely
all videotaped
from the time
you walk in the door.
They want to make sure
there are no stains
down there,
and you know
where I'm talking about,
too.
The finger pad.
Well, you did great
in the bathing suit contest.
I did really good in that.
You had to wear
five pairs of socks
on that thing,
though,
to get any kind
of substantial formate.
Oh, they all do that.
That's understood.
I did really good
with the Motown song.
They do sometimes
take off that
ten-point slide
for too many songs.
The Motown song was good.
The R&B song was all right.
What did you do?
Did you do
Stop the Name of Love?
The Elvis song, though,
was a little tough
because I picked a hard one.
Which air...
I picked the
American Trilogy.
Which air guitar
ten did you pick?
Or did they assign one?
No, no.
That's coming up
in round two.
Oh.
They're saving that
for the big round.
There's a lot
of people
who have eye injuries
and those things.
Man, make sure
that EMS is on call.
And make sure
you're getting plenty
of food and water.
And make sure
your vacation time
is clearly marked here
on the digital cock.
I mean clock.
I'm sorry.
Rocking.
It's only rocking rocks.
Boy, talk about Freudian.
I know.
Man.
That guy kind of
climbed in my head
and now I can't.
I just, I don't know.
That was pretty Freudian.
I'm still thinking
about little kids.
Everyone.
The one listening
is listening.
Look, Chaz,
the one listener
is there.
Oh, cool.
He's calling again.
And his twin brother
on the other line.
It's okay.
You can call now
and you can express
yourself freely
because, damn it,
we liberated this zone
for your protection
and flavor.
Just relax.
Release.
And just let it go.
Enjoy.
It's for your own good, man.
It's good
for your own good.
Push.
Like you're trying
to get one out.
It'll go in easier.
Come on.
Remember what Mommy
did so many years ago
when she pooped
a watermelon
and called it you.
And, friends,
of course,
that was ESO Radio,
Swamp Radio
from WCSB Cleveland
with Professor Chaz Smith,
the host,
Lonesome Cowboy Dave,
Princess Wee,
and Yee.
And now,
Lamer.
Hey, you guys want to keep it down?
There's more than enough
flame to go around.
It doesn't have to be
an entity.
Delicious frozen custard.
It doesn't have to be a custard.
It doesn't have to be an entity.
It doesn't have to have
fibulations because
its heart beats.
7th Cavalry caramel topping
You can hear the sound
of the pounding heart
of the show
from under the floorboards.
Has the pain ended?
Oh, God, look at that EEG.
It's incredible that it could be in a coma for this long,
yet still it goes on and on like the vegetable it is
and doesn't die.
Although when you purchase all three,
it's only $16.98 per stew.
They try to clean up the song and make it feel good about itself.
They thought maybe then it would be ready for death.
Maybe just a sense of bitterness was keeping it from dying.
The other members of the team kept ranting about other things
while the song pulsated along behind them,
unbeknownst to their very actions.
You know, go ahead, try to kill it, Hal.
Try to kill the song right now.
Take this gun and shoot the song.
Just try to kill it.
Don't cripple this song, Hal.
No, let it glide along.
You can't slow it down.
Hold on, we're trying to pull you up right next to our little spacecraft.
They cut off three of its legs, but look at it.
It's still chopping along.
There you are. You're climbed on.
You're on, you're on. You're in, you're in.
Dr. Philodrum, Dr. Hal and Puzzling Evidence
on the KPFA Puzzling Evidence Show.
By the way, this music or sound in the background is from Negative Land,
whose show precedes the Puzzling Evidence Show on KPFA Berkeley.
For the vivid subgenius imagination is in a churning turmoil of constant growth,
and it can make the wait blast.
When starving, or contemplating unpaid bills,
the subgenius eats his imagination for breakfast and lunches on his own soul.
It invents more possibility of future pain and joy,
letting us see their immense range and depth,
and that they are subjective.
We then realize that duration is dependent upon mood.
Could we control our own rates?
We could shorten apparent pain time to zero and apparent slack time infinitely.
Meanwhile, the subgenius must bravely face the bars of his cage.
Patience is the only form of time control,
at least until the time of now.
Now, go for a walk and keep walking,
until you stub your toe, get bugged,
or until your feet really hurt.
This will remind you that what you have been reading is valid,
only idea your head and just a bunch of philosophical crap to begin with.
There's no sense in getting permanently cosmic-headed,
even if you could and most yogis are only faking it to themselves.
You still have to eat, and your shit still stinks.
There is such a thing as getting too high, and death is a waste,
though that is the only reason you should be afraid of it.
Religious yahoos can keep blabbering glib crap forever,
us included, and it's a good flushing out of the brain-pen,
but that's all it is.
The rest is between you and Bob.
Good luck, suckers.
Time control outtakes from the subgenius book,
Revelation X, read by the author.
The book is available for purchase at www.theblogspot.com
One of the most spectacular kinds of automobile accidents
is the one in which a car not only gets banged up,
but bursts into flames.
One makes it really horrible...
...is the idea that a driver and his passenger, stunned by the accident,
may be trapped inside the burning car.
The National Safety Council says that, proportionately for most of us,
this type of spectacular smash-up...
...is very dangerous.
...is very rare.
The thing that stuns people inside a car...
...will make you help.
Artemia Salina did it.
And now...
Les Murs.
The American Heart Association
has a lot to learn about dirt.
That dirt, McCain.
I want you to look around.
And you tell me who'll pick dirt.
That dirt.
But...
If the Marshal's dirt was the dirt,
why Paul never throw that...
...that dirt in the dirt?
I don't know.
He's got too much dirt.
Because I don't believe in principles?
But it's important dirt.
Very, very important.
Who is it?
The American Heart Association.
Still awake, son?
Can't seem to get to sleep.
Well, maybe you can sleep if you think of something pleasant.
Not Michael or me!
Maybe.
Mark, I told you before.
You had no right to get away.
I'm sorry, Paul.
One thing is sure.
We're not your friend.
Mark, wait!
I'd be glad to.
Well, I guess I take the prize for stupidity.
I know.
I know the one you mean.
Don't you have at least 15 friends?
No, it's easy.
The problem is you get too many people.
We would have to arrange a friend stock.
Like 60.
You would have to have a friend stock.
We'd have to have like more than 15.
We might have to have 16 friends.
We can rent some friends.
I know there's this place called Rent-A-Friend now where you can go in and you can rent somebody.
Rent-A-Friend?
Is that like where you can get a Russian bride or something?
They'll act like they've known you for a long time.
You'd give them like a bio sheet and they'll memorize your bio sheet.
And then like when they walk around with you, you know, they'll...
They'll always be laughing at your jokes no matter how lame.
I wouldn't show just anyone my bio sheet.
You know, you don't have to pay them too much.
It's really...
You notice this scene looks a lot like the one in 2002 where the guy touches the monolith.
You pay their expenses and give them money.
I was enjoying the special effects but they just somehow didn't look very convincing.
But did you notice that when you have your Rent-A-Friend that they never say anything bad?
Yes.
Well, that's their job, you see.
They never ever say anything bad.
I mean a good friend, a real friend...
Motion picture in the scene.
They'll tell you a bad news every now and then.
So when you rent one, it sort of like breaks down after a while.
And people can say, you know, people will notice,
Hey, I think that's Hal's Rent-A-Friend because he never says anything bad about Hal.
But there are natural culling factors which would remove me and him from any suspicion.
That boy needs therapy.
Psychosomatic.
You're psychosomatic.
That boy needs therapy.
Gonna lie down on the couch.
What does that mean?
You're a nut.
You're crazy in the coconut.
What does that mean?
That boy needs therapy.
I'm gonna kill you.
The Branniga Zoo blitz half of Chief.
Now when I count three.
That boy needs therapy.
He was white as a sheet.
And he also made false teeth.
Frontier Surveillance
Can you think of anything that talks other than a person?
Uh-oh, uh-oh, uh-oh.
A bird?
Yeah.
Sometimes a parrot talks to me.
And sometimes...
Sometimes...
The laundry talks to me.
And sometimes...
A little teeny piece of house will talk to me.
A little...
Wax...
A statue of a person this big...
Talks to me.
And we go dancing.
In a club in my own mind.
And I used to have friends.
And they used to be on the air with me.
But now they just sit around and drink little energy drinks.
And draw little smiley faces.
At times.
Yeah.
I still think the show's funny.
They do talk about phantom planets that are actually planets in another dimension
that we can't see or anything like that.
Oh, come on.
The only thing that...
The only way we could tell they exist...
That doesn't sound like Starbucks coffee.
The only messenger particles that could carry between the two dimensions would be gravity.
So would this explain dark matter and that stuff running out of Dave's...
Yeah, they're trying to explain all kinds of stuff like that.
Gravity waged.
Now, see...
Now, I'm confused again.
Gravity's particles?
I thought gravity was waged or maybe wave particles.
The graviton.
There's actually...
Have you ever heard about the graviton?
No, I have not heard of graviton.
It's all a bunch of fairy tale stuff.
What are these?
I find these to be odd.
I don't believe it unless I see it.
Fairy tales and children's stories.
I can prove the world's flat.
The moon is made of green cheese and the world is no more.
It's flat.
If the world was curved in puddles...
Would have a curve to it.
Right?
They're flat.
If the world was round stank, we'd be able to dance all the way to the other side and back and never know the difference.
What do you think, Wee?
Well, the horizon is straight.
It's not curved.
It's straight.
So it must be flat.
Flat.
Flat as it can be.
Man, flat as your skull.
Sometimes it seems to go up and down and kind of curves at the sides.
Up?
Or it's like...
There's something really wrong.
Stang, if the world was round, you couldn't go bowling.
The balls would go on infinitely and return back into your hand from the opposite direction.
That happens below the equator, right?
I don't know about blowing the equator or any of these other strange things you allude to,
but I know one thing.
If the world was truly round, you'd not be standing where you are right now.
All ready?
This lecture is about Guadalupe.
Guatemala.
Uh, he, the, uh, Guatemala is far more, uh, powerful than the CIA.
Uh.
Before beginning the lecture, one point I should make is that when people think of this Guatemala,
they think of lawyers, they are going to be front and center because
the Lord, the Lord and the Son of God, will not stand there and do things.
I, uh, do.
Uh.
It's difficult to give a lecture and not avoid Guatemala's
Obamacare.
Oh, my God.
Oh my God.
If you look down, you see a Guatemala, Leon.
What's that?
You know what a turtle is?
Of course.
Same thing.
A little bit there by Reverend Jarto.
Uh, friends, you know, this show, it's not just you.
This show makes me feel weird, too.
In fact, I'm feeling kind of sick.
Do you need to go to the hospital?
I need to go to the hospital now.
Hey, can I take you to the hospital now?
Yeah, take me to the hospital, please.
I think you need to go to the hospital.
Yes, you do.
It's weird.
Go to the hospital.
Go!
Get up and go now.
Get up and go.
Or you just stand up and walk over to the hospital.
Yeah, just go.
Just get the hell out and go to the hospital.
But I feel better now.
I don't think my heart is beating too fast, and that rash is imploring my mind as bad as it was.
That's okay.
The hospital is waiting.
They've staffed up for you.
They've added on new doctors and new nurses and a whole army of volunteers ready to meet you.
I know that your needs are waiting at the hospital.
But I don't want to go to the hospital anymore.
I don't want to need my insurance.
That's okay.
The hospital is free now.
You go to the hospital.
It doesn't cost any money.
You just walk in.
They'll start doing the tests.
They don't even...
You don't have to sign any papers anymore.
You don't have to wait in the waiting room.
They did away with the waiting room because there's no waiting.
You just walk in.
You just can't have a camera guy with you.
And there's a whole hospital dedicated just to you.
A whole staff...
Just for me?
Yeah, just for you.
It has a whole staff of doctors and nurses, lawyers, and all those other kind of people that are at hospitals to take care of you without any overlap.
Without any focus on any other patients besides you.
You are it.
Yee-haw!
I'm King String.
I make a living.
Take a home-made electric chair at home in your own house.
Everybody is dropping out, man.
Everybody's dropping out.
Blau and red.
You can't fight the machine no more.
And their tuning out and turning out.
That's right.
And toning out.
Did you ever try and make a home-made electric chair in your own home?
Like you make the chair with the straps you get, like one of mom's aluminum pie panes you put on your head.
And then you get the battery charges and attach them to your...
and did you stick your feet in the water
and you're good to go somewhere?
We killed the neighbor's kid's bunny that way.
You put him in a chair?
You gave him the chair?
A little fake chair and a car battery.
Did you guys go through a series of appeals
or anything like that?
No, no.
No, you just...
It was just cruel Pobucker kids.
Not even a trial for the bunny.
You didn't even try him or anything
or charge him or anything?
No, it was just cruelty to animals.
That's what kids did in Fort Worth in the day.
See, when we would...
In the 50s.
The 1850s.
Yeah, the 1850s.
Who else was there to torture besides animals?
You were a kid.
We have a real police force here
and they have enough M16 toting criminals
to deal with and without scooping up sub-dini's
without table manners.
Sidewalk lawyer G.G. Gordon had his hands full
just trying to get us out in one piece
because of that little dinner.
Those jokers have got to go.
Can't you burn their houses down
like you did your buddy D. Burns suggested?
Maybe they'll...
Then they'll see
Stemo comes out here
with the same fake accent they all use,
all of you use,
and slays no one.
J.N.R. spouts that his lower extremities are aflame,
that he wishes and asks that a member of the court
at both the state and federal levels,
not to mention God,
to perform an evil, defiled sex act on him
just that he may hear the same washed-out sound effect
of an explosion.
that we all heard.
Ha ha ha!
I was mortally embarrassed to play that Midwestern drivel,
but in the interest of salvaging some sort of a show from the muck,
I bore on.
Kids, I'm afraid I've...
I've lost the most precious thing there is to me,
my personal slag.
Our children gather around,
you know, the older girls.
Look up closer,
the ones who are starting to sprout.
Are you missing your slag, brother?
Have you no slag?
Well, praise Don.
Don brings slag.
To the slagless,
if you down in your mine or your quarry
have not enough slag,
why, R.L. Don Glodds
will bring you slag.
Smooth.
And he will teach you the story
Sweet.
of the MS,
from outer space,
who will come down to Earth
and save all those who spent their $31.
Oh, yes.
Praise Don.
Don will let you play with your thermometer in the rain,
unlike Bob Dobbs,
who'll let you stand in hackneyed and short.
He's the kind of man who visits block...
What was in that stuff?
Is that stuff, or is it just something else?
Oh, that's that stuff.
J.R.
Bob Dobbs told you, ain't it?
He ate it?
Yeah, he ate it.
He can't, he can't step, step thinking
and then he downed it.
All the time.
It just goes like Bob.
It gets into your brain
and then it just scrambles everything up.
Thank God we're into Don now
and forgot that evil slackmeister Bob.
Trying to heal, you know,
those who've, those who've been brainwashed
by the Bob cult.
Those who eat their...
Or recovered.
Recovering.
Those poor people.
Recovering cult addicts.
That was about his mother, I think.
His sainted mother.
His sainted gray-haired granny.
Well, you know,
there's no replacing
his gray-haired granny
and his blue-haired brother,
brown-haired idiot,
his pet idiot.
And his pet idiot.
He had a pet idiot.
Can you believe that they allowed him
to keep a pet idiot?
How are you?
Actually, to tell the truth, Chaz,
I've been doing X-Day shows
for Hour of Slack
ahead of time.
They're all done.
So it's like,
anything we say about X-Day now
would be used on next year's show.
I can't stand the pleasure.
Assuming that the world was still here
and that our cult is, in fact,
just a sad, pathetic joke.
Well, that's true.
Struggling tadpole out of the water.
Well, we...
Never to grow...
Never, ever to lose its tail
and grow legs.
Well, now,
Reverend Stang,
is it not true
that you gave
in the year 1980 itself
on itself here
on my congressional rectus?
That's right.
It says here that you...
We tried to destroy the world.
You tried.
Well, you actually succeeded
in destroying some parts of the world.
Isn't that true, Senator Klebock?
That was absolutely true,
Senator Hedwig.
That was the federal building
in Waco, Texas.
Well, it says here,
there's the Fezziwig building
of the Imperial Literacy Towers,
a place that doesn't really exist
except for in your warped mind.
Well, look, look.
Almost every religion
has an end-of-the-world prediction.
Sir, are you...
Fizzles are...
You know, they try to end the world
in their immediate vicinity.
I cannot...
We've got a virus this time, though,
that we think is going to work.
It's going to take a while,
so, you know,
the July 5th thing
becomes sort of more of a symbolic...
If my ears aren't burning now,
I don't know so when my ears
will ever burn again.
You have said not only you've promised
to hook the virus upon this land...
It's done.
...to visitate the pestilences and so forth.
You've not only included yourself
in this plan,
but you call yourself a religion?
What?
I almost swore.
In the name of the Lord,
I can't...
What kind of religion
would you call that?
Well, an above-average,
well, below-genius religion, sir.
Your Honor.
It's not...
Just another...
Just another end-of-the-world
UFO sex weirdness.
Well, these moon pants you've marked there,
they contain spent plutonium,
much like the weapons
we're using in Osaka, Japan.
Sir, how can you be so cold-blooded?
I know you have some lizard blood in you,
but how can you be so cold-blooded?
Who let the rooster in?
Yeah.
Well, the plutonium in the moon pants
prevents...
prevents normals
from being born to sub-genius couples
who wear the moon pants.
That's weird.
Well, I...
I never saw a rooster in my studio.
If my ankles are not covered with sweat
and turning green right now, sir,
I do not know if they ever shall.
Now you've got the music to this.
You've got the music to this.
You seem to think you're some kind of big dude.
You've got all...
You know where you get those ideas.
You know you're nothing but a shield for the needy.
But you want you to live happy, Phil.
But everybody wants to start something happy.
And the thing that's watching through you
is this Catholic selection.
It's a sin.
It's a downright disgrace.
You never thought I'd find out the big secret.
Now you've got the music to this.
You've got the music to this.
The geeks and the boys know all about it
You gotta get out of town, you gotta take a platter with it
Doesn't look like you draw a lot of water with
You don't have any say in the matter with it
Looking for someone to throw the book at with truth
Think the world's nice and queer, but it's a shame, it's a sin
It's a downright disgrace
You never thought I'd find out the big secret
Now you've got the music to face
You've got the music to
Music
You've got to face the music
Face the music
You've got to face the music this time
Music
The Pink Boys
With Dr. X on vocals
May he rest in peace
The Pink Boys
With Dr. X on vocals
You are listening to the Hour of Slack from the Church of the Subgenius, www.subgenius.com.
Praise Bob and praise the doctors.
This is Reverend Ivan Stang and you can reach me at Post Office Box 181417, Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
Ah, yes.
I am the purser of Dumpstown.
Thank you.