Friends, this is one of the greatest hours of slack you will ever hear, because I did not edit it.
I had a hard week around tax time, and I was whining on the Scrub Genius forum about that,
and having to whip out another show, number 1,305 this time.
And who should pop up with a complete one-hour best-of subgenius classics media barrage of his own design to help me out but Reverend Frodus Sudds Peshaw of Monkey Hive fame,
who will be at X Day 14, by the way.
Reverend Sudds made this collage years ago from the CDs and DVDs in our catalog.
Never expecting anyone to hear it.
But this week, it's time came.
It's a wonderful pastiche of favorite subgenius classics from the past, but it's his favorites and his mix of them.
To me, it's an almost tear-jerkingly good collection and a reminder of why we did all this for all these 30 years.
And he even cut out the cuss words for the radio version.
Friends.
That is what I call a gift of slack for me personally.
There are hundreds of tracks involved, and at the end, I will attempt to give credits as fast as I can,
which will be quite a trick because of the sheer number of subgenius artists you're about to hear.
And so thanks to Reverend Sudds Peshaw and the 500 or so subgeniuses whose work he collaged together.
And so on.
And so on with the shows.
What the hell do you think you're doing?
Dragging your butt through the day, selling body and soul to a bunch of bland normals?
Acting stupid so they'll think you're one of them?
Tired of getting all of the guilt but none of the sex?
There is a simple answer, dear friend.
A glowing beacon of slack amidst the turmoil and darkness.
It's J.R. Bob Dobbs.
The Living God.
The Slack Master.
And his Church of the Subgenius.
Bob brings a new destiny for the abnormal.
For Bob comes to justify our sins.
To unmask the conspiracy and to get us back.
The slack they stole away.
It's us versus them.
Are you gonna fry in hell on earth alongside the pink boys?
Or will you pull the wool over your own eyes and accept Bob into your mind?
Repent.
Quit your job.
Slack off.
And praise Bob.
Church of the Subgenius.
Eternal salvation or triple your money back.
Finally tonight, have you ever wondered about your neighbors?
Maybe wondered about the weird thumps and bumps or chants emanating from their apartment?
Well, they may be followers of Bob.
You know those late night commercials that promise everything from electric massage recliners and instant weight loss to do-it-yourself bathroom renovations?
Well, here's a deal you might not want to miss.
Salvation or triple your money back.
Bob Dobbs came to town to sit you.
Free.
You got no business being sick.
You got no business being embodied.
You got no business living out of sin.
You got no business living without slack.
Because Bob came to town to set you free.
Bob Dobbs.
Oh Bob.
Turn on.
Tune in.
At the start of the show.
Home detyghe.
Dead.
The roll-up, dear friends.
That fateful day, July 5th, 1998.
Next days a-coming.
And the pigs are bumming.
I wouldn't.
Who would want War.
By default, my sillyudes are gesture.
Littleoncé talks about the world I care about.
They're coming!
And the pigs are bumming!
Sure, when the rupture hits,
we'll all be in our first-class window seats on the pleasure saucers
watching the little pink boys fry.
Turn on.
Tune in.
And...
You certainly don't want to trick these people.
X days are coming!
And the pigs are bumming!
Sure, J.R. Bob Dobbs is my savior.
And of course I want more slack.
And I'm smoking prop nonstop.
But what I really want...
Oh, yeah, that's it.
Those lovely alien nympho mutants.
Oh!
Non-stop orgies on the pleasure saucers.
Oh, yeah.
Oh!
Oh, I love to be naked.
More.
Oh, fuck!
Oh!
Turn on.
Tune in.
Turn off.
And break a nail.
mort những increcial
Oh!
X days are coming.
Sub été.
And the pigs are bumming.
I said, X days are coming.
And them little pigs are bumming!
Oh, rad Dylan.
Sub spins!
Those conspiracy Duke Pinkboy normals are gonna fry!
They won't even know what hit them.
That old stark fist is gonna come down hard.
But nothing's guaranteed, dear friends.
I'm a card-carrying member of the Church of the Subgenius.
I'm the almighty king of slap!
But when X-Day comes around,
the only thing I have is my unshakable faith in Bob!
X-Days are coming!
And the pigs are bumming!
Don't you wanna be saved?
X-Days are coming!
And the pigs are bumming!
Listen to me, mister, it's salvation I'm talking about!
Bob...
Alive!
Bob?
Alarm Santa Fe parents met again with elementary school officials last night
to discuss the growing presence of Bob in the schools.
Bob, the deity of the Dallas-based Church of the Subgenius,
is a comic book character who communicates with aliens and worships money.
Parents and teachers complain that the Bob stickers and pamphlets,
which have turned up in school laboratories with increasing frequency,
encourage troublemakers and weird behavior.
Bob!
Bobby!
Ian il Gare disappointment
while theiar
Ian il Gare
Ian!
Paul!
Ian il Gare
Oma-
This is the first industrial church.
We're not a tax write-off scam.
We are an incorporated profit-making foundation.
We'll- We're profits
and we
We want profits.
Let me tell you the story of J.R. Bob Knauss.
Bread of man and yet he, he walked with the gods.
He wore a silly grin and he smoked a stupid pipe.
He fought the conspiracy every day of his life.
He worked the stench of many a man.
Fathered many children with his mighty glance.
He founded the religion in which we all believe.
Brought us all the slack that everybody needs.
Bob was the greatest salesman.
The world had ever seen.
He could sell the farts after he ate all the beans.
He could sell a pile of to a lonely fly.
All of us who knew him figured he would never die.
Bob Knauss, Bob Knauss.
He was a real man.
A real man and brave.
Bob Knauss, Bob Knauss.
Is lying dead in his grave.
Without Bob what are we gonna do?
With a man from Planet X go marching through.
An armed little racist stuck in jail.
With only Bob who raised the veil.
But now he's dead.
So.
So we're doomed.
What to do?
We're doomed.
He founded the city known as Doptown.
Deep within Malaysia it was rarely found.
There he studied forbidden science until that fateful day.
When he came unto his flock in the city by the bay.
Few had ever seen him.
Few had ever dared.
Most had no occasion.
Others just plain scared.
The rurits came to Frisco for the event of the age.
When the holiest smiling one would step out on the stage.
It seemed.
He looked to the left and he looked to the right.
And they stepped out with confidence into his eyes.
But the rurits had no way of getting out.
With all the cheering fans as he strode up to the light.
It seemed.
When a great assassin's bullets shot him to his throat.
Oh my god.
Bob dogs.
The crowd saw their savior had come.
Was greeted by the fire of a gun.
Without Bob we have no gain of fear.
As we swiftly approach that fatal year.
For in 1998 he would have set the record straight.
But now he's dead so we're due no adieu.
Bob dogs.
Well this has been the story of J.R.
Some called him messiah.
Others called him fraud.
I hope that before 98 that the word gets out.
That Bob dogs was the only guy we couldn't do without.
The end times are upon us.
And things don't look so good.
But we'll never forget.
Bob dogs had the answer but was seldom understood.
We're in a heap of trouble.
Our books are in the red.
There is no joy in Mudville.
Now that Bob is dead.
So we pray to Biden and Jesus to do battle for Bob's soul.
To poop dog and a pee dog for strengthening our whole.
We pray to he who needs no name that we may need no slack.
We pray to Wotan please send our Bobby back.
Bob dogs.
All our lives are worth shit without you.
Oh dear what will we do?
What will happen?
The truth is I think rather Conference call no
How involving are we?
Yeah.
Let's just for kicks
If it were not in his grave
All these subgenial would be saved
But it is, so our chances are nicks
There may be some people here
Well, I know there's some people here
Who don't know a damn thing about church and subgenius
In fact, I overheard somebody saying
Well, I think it's like a comedy thing
And it's funny religion
Well, yeah, that too
But why not both?
It really is a real mind-controlled cult
And if you don't believe me
You'll find out what I'm talking about
Later on tonight
The subliminals that are playing right now
Have fulfilled their mission
You'll see
What is all this I hear about this youth cult
This church of the subgenius?
Gee, I don't know
Well, how about
What about you, sir?
What?
Well, what about you?
It's about Bob, you know?
It's Bob
That's it
Bob is great
Starts with a B
Father, what is it, man?
I knew it when I came in here, man
Ends with a B
No, don't tell me
I'm through
Ten seconds, Bob
Bob!
Oh Bob!
Wow, Bob!
Very nice!
Very nice?
Brian, everybody besides you said you're Harold Bregue
Can you abused a JBL gentleman?
What did you do to the rabbit, Bob?
See you tonight
Suddenly Bregue
So excited
Oh, right
Yeah
The night is cool
Oh
Brigho
Yeah
Bob!
It isn't that far out in Salt and Right on, Bob.
Boy, I'm sweatin' like a whore at church, baby.
And this is the church to be in.
Bob.
Who's Bob?
What's ?
You don't know that? I can't tell ya.
Bob.
So, friends, uh, I have not yet answered the question,
what is the church of the subgenius?
And it's a difficult question to answer because, basically,
it is an answer that didn't wait around for a question.
Bob is THE answer!
But, no, actually, Bob is not the answer.
But neither is anything else, friends.
That is the great freedom that our religion gives you.
There, you ain't gonna find an answer, but you can find some helpful hints
and some coincidences that can drive you halfway crazy.
J.R.R. Bob Dobbs is a mystery
enfolded by an enigma,
bound by a puzzle,
wrapped in a strip of bacon,
surrounded by creamy nougat and a rich milk chocolate coating,
held together with a toothpick,
served on a greasy paper napkin.
An indigestible canopy for the new age.
Born to humble parents somewhere in the Midwest,
the child, Bob, experienced a traumatic, close encounter with a UFO at the age of three.
Soon thereafter, he began to exhibit strange,
strange powers of persuasion.
By age six, he had made his first million,
almost by accident.
In college, he met and married his first and still his primary wife, Connie,
who is now revered by female subgenie as the blessed anti-virgin.
With Connie's encouragement,
the young Dobbs became a salesman of legendary, almost frightening abilities,
known to his peers as the man who could sell anything.
He worked his way up to the very top of the conspiracy ladder
and might have stayed there.
But, late one night in 1953,
while working on an amateur television of his own design,
an event occurred which was to become a milestone on man's mind path to slack.
He was suddenly seized up in the spirit,
by the hand of Jehovah One itself,
the cosmic puppeteer of the Old Testament,
the wrathful alien space god from some corporate sin galaxy.
In this timeless moment,
which we call the divine immaculation of the Bob,
Dobbs received the first of countless brain-curdling pronouncements
which formed the sacred pre-scriptures of the church.
He was shown a vision,
a world where all humanity was equally wealthy,
rich beyond imagination,
but without working.
This experience, combined with his UFO-given sales magic,
led him inevitably into the religion field.
He quickly discovered the golden rule embodied in his classic saying,
they'll pay to know what they really think.
From then on there's no stopping the Bob as it spreads from town to town.
Sex, sex, sex, 30, 30, s-s-s-sex, sex, pay $30 and get six sex free.
Right.
It's not that we love Bob so much,
it's that we love the idea of everybody else going to hell,
and that is what religion is all about!
How many, how many Buddhists do you know,
who you know that that nice Buddhist is thinking to himself,
I've got less ego than anybody else here?
Science does not remove the terror of the gods.
We can't do much about those evil gods
from the other side of the cosmos,
who fly through the air and through the nebulous darkness of space.
Space, my friends,
the infinite inky clouds of nebulae,
they fly on their membranous leathery wings,
holding in their coiling tentacles shiny steel cylinders,
each one containing what was once a human body,
a human soul,
what was once a member of the church of the subgenius.
But enough of this.
You don't want to hear about this.
You will learn about this.
Take me off to space,
take me off to space,
come on down you saucer man,
and take me off to space,
take me off to space,
come on down you saucer man,
and take me off to space.
Thick needles in my belly
take samples of my skin.
I don't care as long as I can live with saucer man.
I know that you don't take requests,
but I'm a special case.
Come on down you saucer man,
and take me off to space.
Take me off to space,
take me off to space,
come on down you saucer man,
and take me off to space,
take me off to space,
come on down you saucer man,
and take me off to space.
Hey cow mutilators,
let me join your crew.
Give me a knife,
you bet your life I'll cut up cows for you.
I don't care if you're some kind of ghastly fiend without a face.
So come on down you saucer man,
and take me off to space.
Oh take me off to space,
take me off to space,
come on down you saucer man,
and take me off to space.
Take me off to space,
take me off to space,
come on down you saucer man,
and take me off to space.
Come down you tiny robots,
with your little nipper claws.
You pale and bug-eyed aliens,
with white and clammy paws.
Life is just a sucker,
a sucker's dream,
and Biff is a disgrace,
so
come on down you saucer man,
and take me off to space.
Take me off to space,
take me off to space,
come on down you saucer man,
and take me off to space.
Take me off to space,
take me off to space,
come on down you saucer man,
and take me off to space.
Yeah!
Here's more money, Bob.
Now, at last, the step-by-step process is revealed.
This is it.
The only faith that promises action, thrills, success in sex and business.
Y'all are out to put down outrageous cult groups.
What does this mean?
No, no, this is an outrageous cult group.
Praise Bob.
Help me somebody.
Now, children, many people have asked me,
Reverend Sternow, how did you become a subgenius?
How did you find Bob?
Well, I'd like to tell you about that tonight, children.
And a happy tale it is in the telling, too.
For it was in the winter of 1965.
Ironically, I was walking down the streets of Dallas, Texas.
Children, I was depressed.
Say, oh, no.
Children.
I was dejected.
Say, my God.
My God.
Children, I had not f***ed the exit wound of a recently assassinated U.S. president in weeks.
Say, holy s***.
Holy s***.
Children, I was down to my last two cc's of faith s***.
Fat sperm antidote pudding.
Say, oh, no, Sternow.
Sternow.
Children, I had not launched the bleeding head of Arnold Palmer in six months.
Man, oh.
God, Sternow.
Sternow.
Children, I was at the end of my rope.
It came to me that the only solution to my problems was suicide.
And I didn't even have the money for a Saturday night special.
I was walking to the pawn shop, praying to Bob that I had enough money to buy a Wednesday
or a Thursday night special to blow my f***ing brains out.
Brains out.
And I had to glance down into a mud puddle, children.
And there in that mud puddle, covered with mud, was a pamphlet.
And there, children, in blazes on the cover of that pamphlet, was Bob's mighty face beating
up at me.
His enigmatic smile seemed to say, here, model is this cheesy ad in 1953.
I know exactly how that smile will look when Reverend Sternow needs it in 1965.
Well, I picked up that pamphlet, children.
And I read it.
And what it said in essence was, get in on the ground floor of a lucrative new cult now
while raising your load.
Well, I was one of the few people to do that, children.
And now there are thousands, nay, millions of zombie-eyed, panhandling teenage followers
standing on street corners in cities the world over, selling that self-saved pamphlet instead
of me the money.
With a fourth-feet considerable slack, as you might have guessed.
So.
If you.
Are what they call different.
If you think we're entering a new dark age, if you view the entire universe as one vast,
morbid, cosmic joke, if you are searching for an inherently bogus religion that will
condone superior degeneracy and tell you that you are above everyone else, and most important
of all, children.
I'm done.
If you can help us with a donation, a national donation, the Church of the Subgenius may just
provide you with the slack you've been lacking.
Praise Bob.
Slack, what is it?
Well, if you have to ask, you will never know.
You were born with original slack, an infinite supply of it.
But the conspiracy has most of it now.
They don't even know what it is, but that hasn't stopped them from stealing it away.
How do you think you ended up a slave to their so-called?
Work?
Let's bring it to vertical one more time.
I get to be another dumb American mime.
Miles and miles and miles ago, to get to work with other conspiracy heads that treat me
like a jerk.
Paper pushing, collating, checking the mail.
What the hell's going on here?
Pink belly, pink belly, pink belly, pink belly.
Paper pushing, collating, checking the mail.
Peter Cushing, SoulCrate, the stupid emails.
Don't know how they expect me to meet all these deadlines, but I don't want to resort
to the Scarlet Red Line.
So I'm going to go to the
work, but what am I going to buy with all of this stuff daily?
I guess I just got to.
What the hell's going on here?
Pink belly, pink belly, pink belly, pink belly.
Paper pushing, collating, checking the mail.
What the hell's going on here?
The oblivion of work is often interrupted by work.
I believe that the work on the internet is the same as the work on TV.
But my favorite grace, which seems to never abate
As a blade awaits a whole other day
When the space freight of the potential multiple may
Derive from this world I hate
And on that day I'm gonna party
Like it's 1998
No more peep nosing or whoring
All we'll be doing is soaring throughout the doors of perception
Running past the waves of deception
Oh, what a reception into the arms of the goddesses
It's beyond description
What the hell's going on here?
Party like it's 1998
Don't finally expect me to meet all these deadlines
But I don't want to
So what's all this call with red lines?
So I comply with all this stuff daily, I guess
I just gotta
What the hell's going on here?
Work
Conspiracy
Normal
Pink
Anti-slack
Oh, I could tell you
I really use an ex day
What the hell's going on here?
Threat
Springing to vertical one more time
I get to be another dumb American mime
Miles and miles and miles ago
To get to work with other conspiracy heads
They treat me like a jerk
What the hell's going on here?
Take Valley, take Valley
People pushing, collating, checking the mail
Peter Cushing's soul craving the stupid emails
Don't know how they expect me to meet all these deadlines
But I don't want to resort to the score with red lines
So I comply with all this stuff daily, I guess
What the hell's going on here?
I just gotta
Work
Slut
Door
Store
Four
Core
Back
For more
What the hell's going on here?
Often
I feel like a ghost
Insubstantial
Drifting
Evanescent
Amidst waves of dumb circumstance
Living dead
Glimpses of life
But distant
As behind a thick wall of glass
The oblivion of work
Is often
Interrupted
By work
feature clips
Dad camping
visit day co.z
pally
plan
preview
Covers and Gang
P hardness
My favorite
math
rock
to anyone who can prove that Bob Dobbs is just a piece of clip art.
Look around you.
Look at what they've done to the things that you love.
They took Elvis Presley.
They turned him pink.
They made him into a fat monster.
People say to us, people worry that the Church of the Subgenius
is an anti-American church.
A subversive church.
Children, we are the first real Americans.
We know what America is before they took it away from us
and tried to sell it back to us for a profit.
You know, my friend, while you're alive,
you gotta shout and make a lot of noise
because when you die, you shut up like hell.
If you have never heard of the Church of the Subgenius,
do not look to us for enlightenment.
Even the believers in this self-proclaimed totally bogus religion
say,
it defies description.
We realize that if Jim Jones could talk 900 people into killing themselves,
we could talk 900 people into sending us a dollar.
Everybody out there is so crazy about Bob.
Eternal salvation.
Jim, pull your money back.
All of the religions will be having a heart attack.
A pipe full of frog equals what?
A lot of slack.
No matter how you kill him, he always keeps coming back.
Bob.
I'm talking about dobs.
Repent, quit your job, and slack off.
Get ready to blast off.
When Ed's name comes and all the geeks are on the run from Bob.
Bob.
Pull the wool over your own eyes.
Start to realize what till now has been disguised.
Keep looking to the skies at the saucers flying by.
And maybe by and by you will see the light at the end of the pipe that leads to Bob Dobbs.
Bob Dobbs.
Talking about the salesman.
Do the gods.
He's still in check of the coffin lid.
On a conspiracy of normality.
Oh, who could it be but Bob?
Oh, a whole group of burglars.
And then say Someone Have Badcountry in Time.
Two years later, he's like you.
Crazy about Bob.
Crazy about Bob?
Disgusting.
Quips.
Gross.
Garph.
There is no difference between truth and lies
The race became the beggar and the fool became the wise
Cause it's a way out, far out, psychedelic freak out
Took a hit of Bob, I'm startin' to freak out
Geek out, my friends are gonna leak out
Look out everyone, here he comes, it's Bob
Everybody out there is so crazy about Bob.
I got one thing to say, and it won't take long.
But Bob Dobbs done been here, took a good shit, and gone.
The Church of the Subgenius is basically a religion for mutants, misfits, sinners, disbelievers,
or people who believe anything, and particularly for people with a really sick sense of humor.
You think I'm crazy, right?
Media is the key to power.
Good job, bitch.
When you first look at it, some people go, oh, I get it.
This is a takeoff on weird cults and conspiracies and kooks in general.
Then they look a little bit deeper, and if they're really an attuned sort of person,
then they realize, oh, I get it.
This really is a weird cult with cosmic wisdom and dogma that I've been needing all my life.
And that's usually when they write their first check.
Now at this very moment, the veils of secrecy can be torn aside.
We, the persecuted, may now dare to raise our heads high and declare,
behold us, for we are the subgeniuses.
Subgeniuses.
When the trumpet call makes sound
Brother and sister band
While we blow the world away
We shall have paradise
Sardinia of the world, unite
Alien sex every night
Sardinia of the world, Sardinia of the world
Sardinia of the world, unite
J.R. Bob Dove
Let us not forget
That the only reason we are here for even a second
Is because of that man Bob
You have slacked by his stripes
By his stripes you have money
By his stripes you have sex
By his lucky strikes you have cigarettes
By Bob's lucky strikes you are here today
So praise Bob, praise Bob, praise Bob
If you see Bob on the highway
Suck his
If you see Bob on the street
If you see Bob
Suck his
Or if you're being ruptured after those
You better suck Bob's
And let that be Bob's award
Praise Bob and hail Bob
The choice is clear, cunt
But even though Bob is a trip with suitcases
There ain't gonna be a whole lot of room
For any carry-on baggage
So if you've got any really foul
Psychic luck
Or any luggage
You're gonna have to get rid of it before boarding
You gotta do a final inventory on your own psyche, seekers
Take it away
Cause do you have what it takes to dare to be slack?
Yeah
Do it
I fear the day I meet Bob Dobbs
I've actually had nightmares about that
Real nightmares
And he owes me money
Well I used to be a sinner
Cause I truly did believe
That the Virgin Mary, Jesus
And me were thick as thieves
And I used to give my daughter
A hell of evangelistic snot
But then the light had shone upon me
And I found J.R. Bob Dobbs
And now my wallet belongs to Bob
Yes, my wallet belongs to Bob
Well my heart is for my honey
And my brain is for my love
And my soul is for my job
But my wallet belongs to Bob
Well Bobby goes to profit
Every chance that he can get
He can outperform the biggest
Without even breaking sweat
So I gave him all my money
Reverend Stanks said it was right
And for only twenty dollars
He did save my soul tonight
And now my wallet belongs to Bob Dobbs
Bruce Carter Gracie
I don't quite get what they're saying
But the big change is
That I got my partner
pseudonymly Bob
Now I'm like Bobby
Well Bobby's got a sweetie
And Connie is her name
And her ways to put the sacred
The secret whore of Babylon, Deshaies
She reaches in Bob's pocket, feels around for something hard
Then pulls her hand out, holding on to his mighty credit card
And now my wallet belongs to Bob
Yes, my wallet belongs to Bob
And I never have to fear, cause I know Connie's on the job
And my wallet belongs to Bob
Well, you may have your lady and your horny green man too
Their existential energy may be what's right for you
But someday you'll grow weary of those paganistic cuffs
And give away your money to the one that gets results
And then your wallet belongs to Bob
Yes, your wallet will be for Bob
And you will be subgenius, not another stupid slob
And your wallet will be for Bob
Well, I believe I am much calmer
Got the bleeding head of Arnold Palmer
Sittin' on the dashboard of my car
I'm a poor, poor, poor
Praise Bob
Wee-haw!
Praise Bob!
Money back!
You can't be mentally ill and self-righteous at the same time
And yet, here I am!
These are people who are seriously suffering from a major problem
Bob, are you here?
Oh, it feels good
Hallelujah! Take place the Lord!
I know the word hell
Yeah, ain't it groovy?
I know what I mean!
Making sense so far?
Well, don't worry about it, kids
I don't understand a word of it either
This church started in Dallas, Texas
Which is often called the Buckle on the Bible Belt
All we're trying to do is unbuckle the Bible Belt
He does not really care about your sins
He comes rather to justify your sins
To rationalize your sins, my friend
He brings not forgiveness, but an excuse
The Church of the Subgenius is nonsense
I mean, it's triviality
It has no significance for anything that anybody's gonna care about for any length of time
Bob is a very special kind of religious leader
Bob is a short-duration personal savior
Yes, children, Bob wants you to take him into your heart and into your mind
Bob wants you to take him into your checkbook
But after you've taken him into those sacred places
Bob wants you to think about him, consider him, and then...
Cast him out!
Short-duration personal saviors
It solves a key problem that kept cropping up in earlier faiths
Turns out it only takes five or six generations
Before the memory of a great spiritual leader like Muhammad...
Or Jesus of Nazareth...
Is totally corrupted by the people who are retelling the story
All of whom have their own motives
Five or six generations, that's only a hundred years
And up till now, that's been the maximum useful life of a religion
After that, a sexual paranoid like Paul
Or a megalomaniac like the Pope, King James, or the Ayatollah take control
At that point, the religion is virtually used up
The mass repression completely outweighs the Church's other virtues
But with a short-duration personal savior
Blind faith in an exalted person or object doesn't have to last even one generation
It doesn't even have to last an hour
Which makes the crucial difference in long-term performance and maintenance
F*** the New Age! No blood for snake oil!
It was like the end of the world
There was destruction everywhere
People scrambled around in hysterical panic
Cars and buses and taxis were slamming into each other by the second
Mass confusion reigned like never before
And the cause of all this?
Bob?
The end of the world
You're not Jesus
You're Bob
Yes, Bob!
If you feel it in your eyes, it's in your device
Such was God on his side, Dan Price
We got the hype, we got the tools, and we wrote all the rules
Say when the candle was playing, let me tell you now where you stand
Star-Cruiser, this is the night, it's such a glorious sight
We'll jump your face in the dirt and show you what you really want
Scuttle-eye to the end of the line, cause it's our time
This ain't no game, so you better run, run, run
I'm on my high horse and I'm gonna ride, ride, ride
I'm on soarers, fakers, punks, fly, fly, fly
I pay my dues to the man with the pipe
So we own all the guns, we're gonna watch his planet blow tonight
So cry, baby, cry, tears won't change the story
Scream, baby, scream, cause it won't change a thing
Pray, baby, pray to the gods who will not answer
Cause today is his day, he's coming to pierce the pain
I'm a monster without fight
J.R. Bob Dobs, monster of the fight
Do you journal salvation or dribble your money back?
I will make your wallet safe and soar
Put it under Bob's control
All the inspires while you wait
Operators are standing by
From then on there's no stopping the pop
As it spreads from town to town
I'm getting through, ain't through, ain't nothing that you can do
Make all the queens start shaking in their boots
Make the customer receive what I view
You can't hold me or control me
All the bobbies wanna be me
Until the sources come down and burn your tail to the ground
There's no path to go, collect you hundred bleeding souls
Survive till my fifth in the moon
So we eat, shout, and breathe corn
And then it's time to settle the score
It ain't about the battle, it's about the war
So go read Revelation, excuse that dirty score
I got more, verses than a damn bible
Play the lack of recital
It's just me and Black Screw on the edge of the aisle
So cry, baby, cry, tears won't change the story
Scream, baby, scream, cause it won't change a thing
Just a fight or a sin, or with a family congrats
There ain't no asking why, it's time to slap your butt
It's our money, your wealth, our power
J.R. Bob Dogg's Master of Swag
My life's just the same as mine
Eternal salvation or triple your money back
Don't think no more, let's save your soul
Put it under Bob's control
Cause I'm only good through next day
July 5th, 1998
For Christ's sake, Mr. What You F***ing
Maybe I can tell you what I'm talking about
I'm not talking about my life right now
July 5th is coming, there's no time to wait
Serve a World Cup golfer's head on a plate
I'm not talking about my life right now
I got to go to bed from the rings of Bob's pipe
And if you don't, within the next 30 minutes
We're going to be helping a furry squid
Damn! Some parts of the universe, this thing would be considered funny!
Woo!
Repent, quit your job, slack off, and
Bring Bob!
I see visions of counting
Of course I do
I am a vision of counting
Woo hoo!
I have that could feed a small South American nation.
I have ovaries of steel and a built like a brick house.
My uterus could nurture a full-grown yeti.
I am a sweetie.
I'm a slut.
I'm an angel.
I'm a devil.
I am F-A-T fat and P-H-A-T fat.
I'm the succubus and the innocent.
I am a vision of Connie herself.
And you know what?
So is every sweet, likable, lovable,
sexy uber-femme in this church.
The secret of X-Day.
Am I evil?
I don't know, my son.
All my life I've been a little man.
Happy little fella.
But in the dressing room, I don't understand.
Do you ever hear of X-Day?
No.
You mean, yes, yes, a chance to grow to normal size.
Please, please, please let him do it.
Yes.
Just what does this X-Day look like?
Uh, uh, a rag.
I had grown.
I was growing.
You've grown, but not so much that I can't handle you.
I was normal.
Normal.
You look good to me.
I do?
Well, I always did go for big men.
Big?
Yeah.
I was vaguely disturbed.
I'm afraid of you, John.
You're too big now.
Yes.
I'd grown at least six inches.
Now I was a freak again.
I was a freak again.
I cut my finger on a soup can lid
I got an infection and it spread to my d***
It swelled up to the size of a human head
And then a mouth opened on it
And this is what it said
Kill the pink boys, quit your job
Mock the world and praise Bob Dobbs
We'll build a ship and take a trip
Go on, go get a pen, write the coordinates
Three and a half months in my garage
Tearing parts off of old used cars
My groin at this point was unusually large
And went occasionally home while smoking cigars
The project was finished, the ship would hold twenty
The power source was anything a crew would think was funny
We didn't need the slack list, they're hapless
Our mouth proved its worth in escaping the stark fist
On our way to Planet X for sex, direct snacks
So Barry's quitting every pot of money
Shredded the shit out of my face
Shot a corny d***
All-horse hour of bonanza
It's like a world without Tony Danza
Orphanza, the pink s*** that hits the charts
In a world of dead art
Simultaneous lobotomy and sodomy
We take a moment and we pause to reflect
On the pinks that we killed and the planet that they wrecked
Then we laugh like banshees
And howl like comanches
Do a victory dance
In our underoos and panties
Our fantasy is a reality
Earth's tarnished in dust
It's Planet X or bust for us
Bob's pipe is lit
Space and time shift
General, that's all
That causes a slack rift
A three-dimensional split
Severs forever subgeni from pink s***
Blocked in a circle
And steadily exhaled in the smoke
I can see why the pink boys failed
To pay a naze has caused destruction
Second hole of slackless suction
Pay-per-view alien abduction
Functioning on soulless slack
The money should be painted black
The meat from space that store your balls
Will soon come back and take it all
Return to the past
Return to slack
Return to Bob
Repent, slack off, and quit your job
Or slurp the beastly knob
Connery
Lick the throbbing vein of slavery
Now you're sleeping like a baby
But Bob woke me up and said
Get out of Dodge
There's a guy who's f***ing dropped a UFO in his garage
I ate some bad ham and I got really sickened
In a puddle of my puke where the puke was most sick
A mouse did appear and it beckoned me near
And it whispered the following words into my ear
It said, kill the pink boys
Quit your job and get out of here
Mock the world and praise Bob Dobbs
You'll build a ship and take a trip
Go on, go get a pen, write the coordinates
Six and a half months, hold up alone
Circuit boards, duct tape, and turkey bones
The ship appeared more than disaster prone
But the vomit assured me that far weirder ships had flown
The project was finished, the ship would hold twenty
The power source was anything the crew would think was funny
We didn't need the slackless, they're hapless
Our mirth proved its worth in escaping the star-fixed
On our way to Planet X we're setting off
The next that wrecks next
A prairie squid and every pot of money shot at Connie
The all-hoss hour of Bonanza
It's like a world without Tony Danza
We're fans of a pink sh** that hates the charts
In a world of dead art, simultaneous lobotomy and sodomy
We take a moment and we pause to reflect
On the pinks that we killed and the planet that they wrecked
Then we laugh like banshees and howl like Comanches
Do a victory dance in our underoos and panties
Our fantasy is a reality
Earth turns to dust, it's Planet X or Buster Bust
We're the one and only
Embrace the yay blood that flows in your veins
And when the frog pipe clouds bring slack like rain
Let Bob control
What's left of your brain
Oh yes and all your money to the Reverend Heidenstein
Embrace the yay blood that flows in your veins
And when the frog pipe clouds bring slack like rain
Let Bob control
What's left of your brain
Oh yes and all your money to the Reverend Heidenstein
Embrace the yay blood that flows in your veins
And when the frog pipe clouds bring slack like rain
Let Bob control
What's left of your brain
Oh yes and all your money to the Reverend Heidenstein
Friends, question authority
WHY?
Now look, when everybody does that kind of defeats the purpose, doesn't it?
Jesus, how can you get rebellion going with a crowd like this?
BOO!
I'm not a rebel, I'm a rebel
I'm a rebel, I'm a rebel
I'm a rebel
You will emerge from trance on the tone remembering everything except your instructions for the omega contingency plan
Turn this thing off so you can get these four letter words
These damn monkeys won't stop
Don't grit
Okay grunt
Ahhhhhhh
Friends what you have been listening to was all remixed and recolaged by the Great Reverend Frotis Suds Pasha of Monkeyhive
who will see you at X Day on the saucers.
What we've been listening to,
if I can do this quick enough from the beginning,
yours truly, Reverend Ivan Stang and Mark Mothersbaugh,
commercial soundtrack of the Subgenius commercial.
Channel 4 Dallas 1980 Bob intro, CNN Subgenius report.
Bill T. Miller, the king of slack, song X Days of Comin'.
Sontar's fake news report from the Arise video.
Yours truly, in 1981 on What's Up America Showtime,
Dr. Ahmed Fishmonger with Bleepo Abernathy,
Donna Cossey and Peggy Kennedy doing Ballad of Bob Dobbs.
Me preaching somewhere with Mark Mothersbaugh's
Babacato in the background.
Sontar did the fake news report from the Arise video.
The El Queso All-Stars did that Bob song
that came just before Reverend Susie the Floozy
at the Club No Divival in Dallas 1992.
Reverend Stevie Hambone was in there.
Me at the Stark Club and Smart Club in Cleveland.
Paul Mavridis on Bob, the indigestible canape of Bob.
Dr. Howell's Arise narration with the history of Bob.
Arise cuts by Puzzling Evidence.
Yours truly at Starwood.
Dr. Howell at the Night of Slack Divival in 1984
with added music by Negative Land.
I think.
Reverend Orton Nenslow and Dr. Ahmed Fishmonger.
Take Me Off to Space, that fabulous song,
which I think had Donna Cossey and Peggy Kennedy in it.
Reverend Bleepo Abernathy and myself
from Book of the Subgenius, the Sub-G Intro Barrage.
Pope Sternodox's sermon at the Club No Divival 1992.
Dr. Howell on Slack from Arise, a script by yours truly.
The song Pink Belly was by Reverend Norrell Preff.
You heard Pope David N. Meyer at the 1984 Night of Slack
about the first real Americans.
Me preaching at Starwood, some news report.
The Great Groovy Neptune.
Did that song crazy about Bob.
There was some me at 6X Day,
old 1980s NPR interview with Reverend Velveteen Sly's music in the background.
Dr. Howell with music by D.K. Jones from Arise.
Lonesome Cowboy Dave's band at a Cleveland Divival
doing Subgenius Anthem.
Me at Club No, put that up by his stripes.
You are here.
Susie the Flusie at Club No Divival Dallas 1992.
Sister Melodious Chops with Princess Wee and M.A. Cummins,
also known as Victoria Ganger and Revelry with that song.
My Wallet Belongs to Bob, recorded live at a Cleveland Smart Word Divival.
A collage by Stang, Lee Murr.
Puzzling Evidence.
Some stupid British show.
Book of the Subgenius promo flexi-disc.
Pope David Meyer at the New York City Divival of 1983.
The MIT Computer Lab expert Michael Travers from Arise.
More collages by me and Puzzling Evidence.
Monkey Hive did that kick-ass Bob song near the end.
Priestess Pisces did the Uber Femme rant with Monkey Hive
live at X-Day Drill 2000-something.
Lee Murr or Neil Norrell Prep did the Secret of X-Day collage.
The El Queso All-Stars with their classic Planet X or Bust.
A little bit of me at Starwood.
Arise outro.
X-Day moments from Jesus Devil Aqua.
Pastor Craig roll after his collarbone was broken.
And the Blood Wrestling.
All done and remixed by Reverend Frodo Shaw.
Oh, my God.
For more information or a text log of this show
or to download the original cuss-filled, uncensored,
one-hour, 20-minute original version of this remix,
see subgenius.com and look for the radio tab.
Praise Suds and praise Bob.