Hey! Who's that?
Bob?
Totally lacking in sympathy or imagination.
The modern racketeer.
Psychologists say that such character can frequently be traced back to-
The self-genius!
Power of SWAT!
Hey.
Weeeeeeeeeee
Weave-a him away!
In the White House, the mighty White House, the liar tweets tonight.
In the West wing, the self-obsessed wing, the liar tweets tonight.
Ha, ha, ha.
Hush, you doctors. Hush, reporters.
Hush, you doctors.
You science nerds
Look, my ratings are through the roof
When I just say happy words
Everyone can get a test
It's just the flu
It's a hoax like all the rest
A left-wing coup
We've got lots of pee-pee
The cupboard's bare
It's Obama's fault, you see
The buck stops there
In the country, the quiet country
No nurses sleep tonight
But in the White House
The of shite house
The liar tweets tonight
Ha! Ha!
Believe me, believe me
Believe me
Pretty sure you'll believe
The lies of the Pope
Say believe me
NietzscheامNoise
Oh月
Space
Komm transition
Have factкам
This is the darkness
These are the days
When the shadows
hidden human hearts
step out of the haze
And stand like blots of ink
in the bright of the day
And the light
can't chase them away
This is the darkness
Where is the sun?
You've traded your god of light
for one with a gun
Empathy, justice, and mercy
only for
once
He deems to be the chosen
This is the darkness
This is the place
This is the lake
This is the embodiment
of all we have made
Greed personified
He'd in a suit and a tie
A corpse searching for
his bride
A scrolling mirror
But what of all these elves?
Heh heh heh at least
Got free plans
Yeah I won't.
will bend the truth to fit your fears and absolutes and it will leech into your soul
pollute your mind
this is the darkness where is the light
it must still be up there somewhere but you might be right
it might be days weeks and months of this long polar night
but i believe there's more of us than them and prodigals return again and scales can fall from
clouded eyes and moons can set and suns can rise and swords be hammered into plows and all that
crap but this is now
this is now
and this is the darkness
this is the darkness
so
i'm alec baldwin
and you're
listening to here's
the thing
i'm alec baldwin
and here's
the thing
i'm alec baldwin
and here's
the thing
i'm alec baldwin
and here's
the thing
alec baldwin
and the thing
get back on mic anytime
at least
overnight
Oh, thanks, Dr. Falk.
I almost forgot.
That last song was Bob Walkenhorst's
This Is the Darkness.
Brand new from his Patreon page.
Although he said this hit was for free
so I can play it on the radio.
Pretty damn somber.
And old Bob is starting to sound
even more scratchier voiced than I am.
Although I like to think he's just taking advantage
of the high pollen count,
which is also affecting my voice.
We're only about a month apart in age.
But the cheery song before that,
The Liar Tweets Tonight,
was by Roy Zimmerman.
And on the same basic subject.
Uh, yeah.
Some of us miss our country.
Okay, so I'm going to do something different this episode.
Actually, I probably did it before, but in 1984.
What happened is I pulled out my CD
of the first two Oingo Boingo albums,
which were among my absolute faves in the 1980s
for reasons that'll soon be obvious
if you're unfamiliar with this band.
Oingo Boingo, which later turned into
the movie composer known as Danny Elfman.
Anyway, I hadn't listened to Oingo Boingo in years,
and I was surprised to discover
that I still remembered every single lyric.
And I was not surprised
when all those songs suddenly turned into
an immense brain worm
that's been tormenting me
and Princess We as well
for days.
And of course, like Cove Fef 19,
the only way to cure myself,
if this brain worm is to give it to you,
dear listener.
Oh, sorry, I should have covered my mouth
or worn my new Dobbshead face mask,
which we have now.
So anyway, I wanted to do this mostly Oingo Boingo show,
but the big decision was,
do I arrange it so it starts with the light
and hopeful stuff
and ends with the scary and dark stuff
or the other way around?
And I decided on the other way around
and on a positive note.
Let's not increase
the suicide statistics among subgeniuses.
This song, Perfect System,
it's about where we were heading
before all the crap hit the fan.
And society may well head that way even faster
once the virus kills off one type of dumbass,
but leaves the other type of dumbass alive.
The kind of dumbass that's fine
with perpetual mask wearing,
complicated rules,
enforced manners,
and isolation from the others
except by Facebook.
Forever.
I'm in love with you, I know.
And I know that you love me too.
I'm in love with everyone too.
We're all comrades now, you know.
We're all brothers under the skin.
We've got a few adjustments now.
Living in a perfect system.
The adjustment's simple, there's really no pain.
You'll hardly notice anything.
Nothing has changed.
Living in a programmed life.
Nothing really has ups and downs.
There's no need for fighting now.
There's no reason to worry.
In a perfect system,
there's no confrontation.
Unnecessary friction
to repeat our concentration.
We've simply done away with
unnecessary friction.
Unnecessary friction.
I live in a system.
I get enough nutrition.
By eating protein biscuits.
Recommended by the system.
It's routine regulation.
I had an operation.
And what was it above.
Let me give you a little taste.
I've already had enough.
I can show off my strength.
My finance is amazing.
To prove my stickiness,
Everyone too
I can tell by the look in your blank little eyes
That you agree, but you might have been surprised
Living in a programmed life
All the really house ups and the one runs
Don't need my fighting now
I believe in two-way or round one
I had an operation
With a red bush reaction
They tapped it with my brain some
It helped me see the reason
For living in the system
We're all brothers in a perfect world
In a perfect world there's uniformity
In a perfect world there's continuity
We're all brothers in a perfect world
There's no need for spontaneity
Perfect system
We're all brothers to the end
Brothers to the end
I know
And I know that you love me too
Brothers to the end
I know
I'm in love with everyone too
Brothers to the end
I know
We're all comrades in the buskier world
Brothers to the end
I know
Living in a perfect system
Brothers to the end
To the end. To the bitter end.
I kind of want that operation he's talking about.
Do you suppose some of these songs might be meant in,
I don't know, in an ironic way?
Boy, just thinking about that makes my head hurt.
I'm gonna go to Trump's stop and have one of those doctor prisoners give me that operation that makes me as intelligent as the president.
I bet I'd probably sleep better.
And I hear they have snacks.
I'm sure they wouldn't lie about that.
I'm pretty sure that everything the government promised us is coming and it'll be just like they said it'll be.
There we go!
This tires me out.
Well then, I guess it was time for some dr주고.
I really am in love with his initial lead because he had so many say.
And I was asking that, too.
You're not home yet
What you see
Is what you get
Don't relax
You're not home yet
Put your life into my hands
Look around, you'll understand
It's the 80s, idiot
What you see is what you get
It's the 80s, little fool
Don't forget the golden rule
What you see is what you get
What the hell do you expect?
Pretty red roses
White puppy noses
Man with rubber holes
And his is more like it
Ah, what you see
Is not always what you get
A lesson we must not forget
One never knows what to expect
So close your eyes and watch you get
Oh, oh, oh, oh
Is what you see
Is what you get
Open up your eyes and look around
Wow
Don't close your eyes
And just say wow, wow, wow
You've got to be thankful you're alive
And how much longer can you survive?
Underneath the mask there's something ruined
Underneath the ground there's something we will bang
And everything is gone
Put your life right into my hands
The man who you hate
Because what you bar under me
Is our life
I believe you know
The way you die
They didn't bring it
Anyway, hoje
You're gonna die
Be careful
I have some stuff on the table
Hold on realize
That you are around
I'm trying to find
omaniac
I burger
Pretty red roses
White puppy noses
Men in the thwopper hoses
It's what I like it
We're doing the streets
All of our friends
Bust you around
And make you like them
What a comforting song
Don't you agree?
Yeah, Oingo Boingo
Specialized in that
It's funny
It was announced that among the many musical combos
Danny Elfman was scheduled
To perform at the now cancelled
Bonnaroo
Or Hullabaloo
Or Woodstock
Or Coachella
One of those things
And all these kids were going
What's he gonna do?
Play the score of Batman
As if Oingo Boingo
Had never
Ever existed
Well, there you go
I'm old
And tonight I'm playing oldies
That might have well have been recorded
Tomorrow
This upcoming song
Addresses the paranoia
That so many of us feel
Especially those who are cooped up
And surveilled
And feel like they're being watched all the time
I don't have to worry about that
Because for the last five years
I've been hacking and digging out escape routes
Through the deep woods
Surrounding our compound here
So when the black helicopters come for me
They'll never catch me
Until I get to the highway
Or unless they have dogs
Or infrared
Or armed sniffing drones
So yeah
I have nothing to worry about
Doing this anti-establishment show
From a cult compound
In Texas
Kind of near Waco
What, me worry?
But at home
There's nothing
Some are knocking on my door
Hard
I think they're looking for me
Yeah yeah
But tonight ain't nobody home
I make a sound don't even move
No given nothing to see
I think they're looking for me
I get to run, I get to run, I get to run, I get to run, I get to run
There's someone calling in my yard
There's someone creeping on my roof
There's someone tapping my phone
I feel it deep in my bones
They want to throw my intuition
They want to find out what I know
Why don't they leave me all around?
I get to run, I get to run, I get to run
Might need a catcher, but I can't show them
Can't be too careful, I take precautions
They're very clever, I get to run
Faceless surgeons, armed with razors
Cut out our impurities
Imagine they die
There's someone knocking on my door
I need them looking for me
I couldn't get nobody home
I'll make a sound, I'll even know who
Don't give them nothing to see
I need them looking for me
I get to run, I get to run, I get to run
Might need a catcher, but I can't show them
Can't be too careful, I take precautions
They're very clever, I get to run
Faceless surgeons, armed with razors
Cut out our imaginations
It's a strange thing, deadly
Razor, Razors cut with such precision
Prodded here with eye detection
Razors never lie
It's all right
I'll do all
I think they're looking for me.
There's those lobotomy surgeons again mentioned in that song.
Back in the days of Oingo Boingo, the 80s,
we were worried about chemical and surgical lobotomies.
In the end, the invention of social media took care of all of that.
The prisoners are happiest when they build their own cages.
And seriously, do you think they're looking for you?
You wish. They don't consider you important.
And besides, you're throwing yourself at them every hour
that you work at your 24-7 non-paying database entry job for Facebook.
Thank you, Oman.
Late at night, my wife and I have been dancing frenetically to these old songs.
It's good exercise and it baffles the dogs,
but I wish y'all could see my air vocals.
I also do air guitar drums and keyboard when appropriate,
but I'm most proud of my air facial expressions and air vocals
with Danny Elfman's remarkably theatrical and melodramatic singing style.
It's great rubber face exercise.
I'm proud of my own clownishly overdrawn,
dramatic facial and bodily poses.
I studied under Jimi Hendrix and other masters,
so I realize I can't sing for hooey, but I look great faking it,
at least in my own mind.
And according to new agers, that's all that counts.
Now, during this strange year of the new abnormal,
a lot of my friends, the older ones, the ones who can still work at home,
which is a privileged bunch these days,
are finally starting to go nuts with this sheltering in thing.
On the other hand, some are all like,
hey, I could get used to this.
I hate people anyway and feel horribly awkward in any social situation.
Me, I'm an old hand at being a hermit,
except when I have to pretend to be a normal person
in order to get things done and, you know, make a living.
The distance, we share contexto,
and I'm all about интерplay.
In the hood of my old car,
Come and get me out of here
This is my private place
Everything is neat and clean
The skeletons are hidden in the closet
This is my private place
Come and get me out of here
This is my private life
Come and get me
These are my private things
They're there against the wall
The dirty pictures, religious objects
These are my private things
Come and get them out of here
This is my private bed
This is where I lie at night
Staring at a light bulb
Hanging on the ceiling
Waiting for dreams to come
And get me out of here
In my humble room at night
I often wonder what goes on out there
What makes them run so scared
I hold and stare
At the people I love
At the people passing by
But they can't see me through my window shades
Looks like I'm not even there
This is my private life
There's something dangerous I like
And all my problems are in trouble
What I really want to know
Has it always been this way?
It is I the cause of everything
I am playlist of thoughts
This is my private life
The world has beenobile
Go get rid of the dangers
You've been talking all day
This is my private life
That you think you could fluidily
Dissensions
Candles, rings
Mi-mi-mi-mi-mi-mi-mi-mi
I'm stuck in my mind
As I see all this
smirking
See you
This is my private life.
This is my private life This is my private life
Islands in the sea
Not so much like me
They don't doubt that change
No emotion, no emotion
Islands are the land
High like desert sand
Islands in the city
All alone in such a city
Smiles of rain
Just like the face of
When will it change
Islands in the sea
The world's come over me
We are both surrounded by water
And the wind is blowing
The water's in order
Keep them in sorry
And the fear is free
Anything at all
To break the flow of velocity
Smiles of rain
Just like the face of
When will it change
Oh I'm just so
People lips
I grew apart
People in my life
I was just broken
I'm in no Chap deіт
I can feel the sea
Ah, so much like me
Things don't ever change
No emotions, no emotions
I live on the land
Dry like desert sand
I live in the city
All alone in such a city
Forever
I live in the city
Let me
Run
Through the sea
Let me
Run
Through the sea
Let me
Run
Through the sea
Pretty grim, huh?
I'm personally not all that isolated, as I have a solid and nearby family and a large network of friends that I actually know well and like very much.
So, see, I have a safety net. Heck, I've got nothing to fear. Nothing at all.
So, I'm not alone.
Hey neighbor, let me give you some advice.
The Russians are about to pulverize us.
In our sleep tonight, that is if the crazy Arabs or the rights don't get us first.
And the fire will rain down from the sky.
The fire will rain down from the sky.
People die, people die, people die, people die.
But go ahead and sleep tight.
Then you barely remember what the wise man said
There's nothing to fear
There's nothing to fear about fear itself
THERE'S NOTHING TO FEAR
There's nothing to fear
There's nothing to talk now
There's nothing to keep
Lol
Hey little girl, won't you come this way?
Won't you let me buy you candy?
Or perhaps a chocolate shake?
Or perhaps a nice cocaine?
Or perhaps a little kiss?
Or perhaps a ride in my big car?
Don't be afraid
Won't you make an old man happy?
Let me show you paradise
Don't ask your mother for advice
There's nothing to fear
But fair itself
But fear itself
There's something to fear
There's nothing to fear
Temperature's starting to drop now
Temperature's starting to drop
If they don't hear the end with junkie
Or with a zombie on the street
If they don't turn you into a yolkan or a grinning Jesus' spring
If they don't take away your brains and turn your body inside out
If they don't take away your passion with a color to be set
They will take away your heart and soul
Remember what the wise man said
There's nothing to fare
There's nothing to fare but fare itself
There's nothing to fear
Temperature's taking a drop now
That's one of my favorite songs of all time.
Man, that horn section is something else.
Steve Bartek has apparently been the silent partner genius
behind the orchestration of Danny Elfman's compositions all this time.
And also, the guitar player.
So, okay, this one coming up is a good anthem for junior scientists in these end times.
Actually, you know, ends are only beginnings,
although that's a moot point for everyone but junior scientists.
For all I know, this song is really about a romantic breakup,
but I like to think of it as an expression of profound sadness
at the impending collapse of a once great ecosystem
and yet another era of the world.
Yes, at times, a few once great societies.
whoop whoop whoop
Everyone says
Whoop whoop whoop whoop
We've come such a long, long way
We're civilized
Isn't that nice?
We've gotten so smart
We know how to blow the whole world apart
When it comes to the simple things
Like living together
Ha!
Why'd we have to come all this way?
Is anything easier to understand?
Our life is better than written commands
We've been bullied enough
But we know better
Is anything we can all just say together?
Stop wasting all my time!
Why'd we come all this way?
Why'd we have to come all this way?
We couldn't quit while we were way ahead
Why'd it have to end up like this?
We should've just stayed at home instead
The road was long and the journey was hard
And I even dreamed that we'd come so far
Oh, how time, we swung on my time
Why'd it come all this way?
We should've just stayed at home instead
Why'd it have to end up like this?
Why'd it come all this way?
Why did we come all this way?
I do really good air vocals and expressions to this one.
Have you seen my girlfriend?
She lives in a pig pen.
I can't seem to find her.
Perhaps she is hiding underneath a plate of scraps.
Let's take the holy off.
Have you seen my new house?
Looks just like a dog house.
Someone saw it walking straight into the ocean.
Thought it was an ivory boat.
Let's take the holy off.
Maybe...
It's just a bad dream and a way to assume
I don't think I'll be so lucky.
Maybe...
It's just one of those strange days
When nothing's right.
No, nothing seems right at all.
When I threw a paper on a bathroom wall
But I can't remember who I wanted to call
Operator, can you help me?
The leftovers?
It's amazing how many good things
And, how was it that I fell in love together?
Rather hard than dying?
We said that we've just broken up?
Then I started to yell out my name?
Let's take the whole day off
Let's take the whole day
Have you seen my girlfriend?
They matter
Ahh
Ahhh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
I think you're better, better, better off
stuck up there without your head.
They say you're stupid, that you're too young to wow.
They say you're the swine of anything
that you can think of.
Hey, jump down this road.
If they say you're that, you don't, if they say.
You're right now.
You don't, if they say.
Turn around.
Hit the ground.
You don't, if they say.
Fight to pick a witty.
What's that doing?
You don't, if they say.
Then it's over, baby.
Take your head, now.
There's something inside your head.
All
No matter
Oh yes dear friends
before I end the show with the
ultimate Oingo Boingo
subgenius anthem
let me first explain
I'm not personal friends with Danny Elfman
of Oingo Boingo
we've never met although we have friends
in common and I have a picture
of him as the devil
in forbidden zone
personally autographed to me
personally
he was given a copy of Book of the
Subgenius by Dr. G. Gordon Gordon
under pleasurable
circumstances a long time
ago so he apparently remembers us
well so it's mutual
anyway this is Hour of Slack
number one thousand
seven hundred and
seventy six
seventeen seventy six huh
you'd think I'd
have some kind of pertinent
numerology quip about that
but what's way more important
is subgenius.com
where you can learn
about everything old but also
available
it offers pathways to the newer
subgenius things too
for instance check out
freethinkradio.com
which carries all of the other subgenius
shows and this one
and triologiesoaps.com
which can get you clean
with Dobbs Head Soap and some of the
ten million authorized
and unauthorized subgenius
Facebook pages and what
not and so on but now
friends a real anthem
a feel good anthem
for subgenie
from like
nineteen eighty
boingo boingo
music
music music
music rock
music
music music
On the outside looking in
I'm on the outside
I never was a punk
I never shot junk
I never even tried
Counterculture passed me right by
Don't talk to debutantes
Don't eat in restaurants
The patrons sit and stare
The winners make wisecracks behind my back
The teachers stay in school
They front me by the rule
They said I have no motivation
Raise your brains and dedication
I just see a missile to the right
I'm on the outside
I'm on the outside now
This is where it all begins
On the outside looking in
Looking in
At you
I'm just a alien through and through
Trying to make believe I'm you
Trying to fit
Just a stranger on the outside looking in
At you
The pistol makes me sick
I wear the wrong collected clothes
I see the wrong things, you know I can't dance, my feet are much too wide
Who thinks you set the trends? You wear your head as right
Your girls are out of sight, your house is modern, really kitsch
You get so macho when you're with your bitch
I see them go to work, I see them go to sleep
I see them on TV, I see them laugh and cry
I'm on the outside, I'm on the outside, I'm on the outside
I'm on the outside now, this is where it all begins
I'm on the outside looking in, looking in
Looking in
And you, I'm just an alien through and through
Trying to make believe I'm you, trying to fix
Just a stranger on the outside looking in
I'm on the outside, I'm on the outside now
I'm on the outside now
I'm on the outside