We interrupt this program to activate the emergency
subgenius power of
SWAT
Oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah
Hey, it's your friends in honor and fear of the upcoming elections
For this hour of Slack, number 964
I've elected to play a special pre-verts, pre-vote show
from the lymph node institute edition of Bob's Slack Time Funhouse
Originally broadcast on WREK Atlanta
The greatest of all the college stations
Well, except possibly the other college stations that carry this
But I'm going to do it
Very demanding show
Anyway friends, stick around for
The lymph node institute special pre-verts, pre-voting
Hour of Slack
Oh babies
There's so many of you
Just be cool down the front and don't push around
Just keep still, keep together
Oh yeah
I'm the main well contest
Been around for a long, long year
So many man's souls to feed
I was round when Jesus cried
And I was grown from the sound of my bed
I'm the main well contest
Rest푹ing hope
And the only hope
And there was no room for me
The only hope
But I step further and come forward
And be meringue
Res review cage
And more exciting swag
To commanelthat
hey
and i'll try and stop it you're listening to bob slack time funhouse the lymph node institute
edition i'm doc i'm bugsy and tonight it's happening we're actually going to pay attention
to what those pink boys are doing and we're going to talk a little bit like we did
four goddamn years ago yeah we were in the space station then we were in the space station
and but we saw it coming and it's just bizarre because nothing like that it was unprecedented
but we still saw it coming because we have bird's eye view outer space space birds and it may happen
again although i doubt it very highly because you are much more optimistic about that than i am i
have big fear about the next election i don't think and it's important to use passive voice
here i don't think it will be allowed to happen
because if you have two bum elections in a row wow thanks florida yeah exactly oh thanks thanks
katherine harris
the tiger who understood people once upon a time there was a tiger who escaped from a zoo in the
united states and made his way back to the jungle during his captivity the tiger had learned a great
deal about how men do things
and how they can do things
and he thought he would apply their methods to life in the jungle the first day he was home he met a leopard and he said there's no use in you and me hunting for food we'll make the other animals bring it to us how will we do that asked the leopard oh easy said the tiger you and i will tell everybody that we're going to put on a fight and that every animal will have to bring a freshly killed boar in order to get in and see the fight then we will just spar around and not hurt each other
later you can say that you broke a bone in your paw during the second round and i'll say i broke a bone in my paw during the first round then we will announce a return engagement and they'll have to bring us more wild boars i don't think this will work said the leopard oh yes it will said the tiger you just go around saying you can't help winning because i'm a big palooka and i'll go around saying i can't lose because you're a big palooka and everybody will want to come and see the fight
Because i'm a big palooka And i'll go around saying i can't lose because you're a big palooka And everybody will want to come and see the fight
Now, so the leopard went round telling everybody that he couldn't help winning because the
tiger was a big palooka, and the tiger went round telling everybody he couldn't lose because
the leopard was a big palooka.
The night of the fight came and the tiger and the leopard were very hungry because they
hadn't gone out and done any hunting at all.
They wanted to get the fight over as soon as possible and eat some of the freshly killed
wild boars, which all the animals would bring to the fight.
But when the hour of the combat came, none of the animals at all showed up.
The way I look at it, a fox told them, is this.
If the leopard can't help winning and the tiger can't lose, it'll be a draw, and a draw
is a very dull thing to watch, particularly when fought by fighters who are both big palookas.
The animals all saw the logic of this and stayed away.
When it got to be midnight, it was obvious that none of the animals would appear and
there wouldn't be any wild boar meat to devour.
The tiger and the leopard fell upon each other in a rage.
They were both injured so badly and they were both so worn out by hunger that a couple of
wild boars came wandering along, attacked them and killed them easily.
Moral, if you live as humans do, it will be the end of you.
I love you, I love you, I love you.
Right-wing people.
The Islamic movement is starting to gather lots of different parts of society.
CBS News.
Fighting the truth.
Fighting the facts.
With ear.
CBS News.
Fighting the truth.
Fighting the facts.
The truth about CBS News.
Tomorrow.
Experience.
Anthrax.
I think they ought to do to make this interesting and they could sponsor it like, uh...
278-070-16.
The United States, who is responsible for these dastardly acts today, including President Bush,
despite the fact that he is a multimillionaire, requires additional financial support from
somewhere to carry out this kind of operation.
This thing being carried out with great precision is consistent with the hard fact.
You got it.
76.
So we all remember.
There's no doubt.
070.
President Bush is a terrorist.
And by the way, the Pentagon and the CIA are...
You got it.
The kind of organizations that have the kind of capacity that would have been necessary
to conduct the attack that we saw on the 11th.
They know what they've done.
They know when they're going to do it.
And they know what consequences might be coming back in their direction.
Terror attacks.
Continue to clear the...
Incendiary.
Hijacked planes.
Doomed passengers.
We pause as we remember September the 11th, 2001, the World Trade Center.
Sandy Patty, our national anthem.
Who's that?
Death toll.
One.
I'm out.
Post Office.
Ages.
So.
One,
Hell,
GOG social network station.
San Francisco.
VO2 Rocket.
On Facebook.
We are the best of the Middle East.
We're made in the 21st century and how do we resolve conflicts between tribes in the
federal and state government?
Nossa Frida streets beeog 저v.
Sorri betrayal.
Hey,COFOG is fired.
You're a... you're a... you've been given sovereignty and you're viewed as a sovereign entity.
And...
Too many OBGYNs aren't able to practice their love with women all across this country.
But he's still the same person I met at a backyard barbecue in Midland, Texas,
and married.
Once you turn everything pink, it stays pink.
He goes on.
I'd like you to contact your congressman and contact your senator.
Tell him to come on the side of the people.
He'll always tell you what he really thinks.
Our enemies are innovative and resourceful.
And so are we.
They never stop thinking about new ways to harm our country and our people.
And neither do we.
He was one of your presidents.
The last time I told you about the curse of Tecumseh,
I may have left a few things out.
In 1811, future President William Henry Harrison,
then governor of Indiana,
led an attack against the Native Americans
known as the Battle of Tippecanoe.
The battle, a victory that broke the back of Tecumseh's Confederation of Tribes,
fatally wounded the United Native American Resistance
against white colonization.
A momentous achievement indeed.
A year later, Tecumseh desperately threw in with the British
in the War of 1812.
As is their way,
the British army fled the Battle of the Thames
and Tecumseh was killed.
It wasn't until Harrison became president
and died in office, though,
that the whispers of a curse began.
President Harrison was the first president to die in office,
contracting pneumonia secondary to the Indian curse.
A fluke took a step towards becoming a trend
with Abraham Lincoln,
who was elected,
elected in 1860,
and then re-elected in 1864.
But not for long.
A Catholic cabal struck him down on April 14th of 1865.
In 1880, it officially became a trend
when General James Garfield won the presidency
by a scant 10,000 votes.
He proceeded to piss off big business
and the New York political machine,
and, less than four months into his term,
on July 2nd, 1881,
he was shot by an angry lawyer,
Charles Guiteau.
He died on September 19th,
after months of tasty torture at the hands of quacks,
which may have been some sort of Masonic ritual.
It basically just gets spooky in 1900,
when President William McKinley is re-elected to his second term.
He was standing in a receiving line
at the Buffalo Pan American Exposition,
when he was told,
that an anarchist with an unpronounceable name,
that, on first inspection,
looks like some kind of joke,
Leon Sholgaz, possibly,
C-Z-O-L-G-O-S-Z,
shot him twice in the chest.
You know, for anarchy.
President McKinley had the decency to linger
for a mere eight days,
and died on September 14th,
1901.
Again, medical incompetence played its role,
giving him a touch of the gangrene before he died.
Mr. Sholgaz's trial started a week later,
and lasted a day.
He was executed less than two months after the act.
Like a good Hoshishin,
he signed a confession,
and was unapologetic.
By now, you may be noticing,
that all the presidents elected in a zero year,
eventually died in office.
And this trend continued in 1920.
With Warren Harding,
who was perhaps the worst president ever.
The Federal Vampire and Zombie Agency indicates
that he was bitten by a vampire planted by Al Capone.
Officially, the return to normalcy candidate,
embattled by multiple scandals,
fled to Alaska,
and died of food poisoning on August 2nd, 1923.
His wife died the next year,
on November 21st, 1924.
FDR, like Lincoln, survived.
He survived his zero year presidency,
but finally stroked out on April 12th, 1945,
in his fourth term as president.
In 1960, JFK was elected,
and we all know who killed him,
on November 21st, 1963.
Ronald Reagan was elected in 1980,
and after just a few months in office,
was shot by a son of George Bush's friend.
He died and was replaced by a CIA robot,
on March 30th, 1981.
Which brings us to the much contested 2000 election.
Wasn't that exciting?
Actually, John Hinckley Sr. was supposed to meet Neil Bush,
our current president's brother,
the evening that Reagan was shot.
But, you get the picture.
And yes, the 2000 election was exciting.
A little more exciting,
because subsequent interviews with Reagan's surgeons
have revealed that Reagan's heart was in fact stopped,
in order to remove an exploding round
that didn't, from his chest.
So, technically, Reagan died.
And we don't even need that CIA robot theory anymore.
So the proof of the trend will be tested
in the fate of George Bush,
who may be part of a sub-trend within the curse.
Lincoln and Franklin Roosevelt,
both wartime presidents,
survived their zero-year terms,
but died in the following April of 1865 and 1945, respectively.
If this trend holds and Bush is re-elected,
then, well, let's just say
I would rather not look at statues of his stupid face
for the rest of my life.
And neither, I believe,
would certain unknowable power nodes.
I believe that in an attempt to break the curse,
among other things,
the Bush campaign will be sabotaged
just enough to let Kerry squeak by,
and then beat him in a landslide in 2008
with Jeb or maybe George again.
Oh, you think perhaps they don't know about it?
Why do you think they picked the aircraft carrier Abraham Lincoln
for the mission-accomplished photo op?
But yes, there is another scenario.
They go ahead and let him win.
And in the cruel month of April,
possibly on Mrs. Ellis's birthday,
ancient scales tip,
and vengeful ghosts take their sacrifice.
What then?
A Christian martyr to guide us on a new crusade.
Who could fill the vacuum?
Surely Cheney would die from media exposure within six weeks.
Ample opportunity for a centrist,
a war hero,
a senator from Arizona.
This scenario might explain
McCain's return to the grassy fold lately.
After all, McCain's idol is Teddy Roosevelt,
who was elected by Tecumseh
when President McKinley was assassinated.
So, I'll bet a nickel on Kerry,
but four cents on Bush.
But the real game is trying to figure out
which way Tecumseh will win.
Time will tell.
Joke about this if you can.
Assassination.
Are you trying to organize or prevent one?
Prevent.
They would have to take reprisals.
Everybody would suffer.
They've heard.
They are aware.
And they don't need anyone's help.
They don't believe me.
Many times bitten, forever shy.
But they are not shy.
They love to listen.
Jamming.
Jamming?
Domestic science?
You learn about jamming one of these days.
It's the most important ways of fighting back.
All right, enlighten me now.
No.
I tell lies, remember?
I'll call in any time you like.
But my safety is unimportant as long as my people are imprisoned.
Now, when you're queen,
you will know that no ruler is truly safe or secure
as long as her people are not free.
I'm here to deliver a warning.
A warning?
What about?
A plot to kill you.
To what?
To kill you.
Assassinate you.
Huh?
I don't believe it.
They should have told you.
There are some unhappy people here.
Yes, well, I have seen the list of malcontents.
It might interest you to know that you happen to be top of the bill.
I do my best to live up to it.
Yeah, what, by saving my despicable life?
Not for your sake.
Oh.
What then?
If they succeed in killing you, what action would your people take?
Oh, well, they would punish those responsible for...
What else would you expect them to do?
Punish everyone.
Amass, reprisal, and never to be forgotten, deterrent.
Oh, I see.
Yeah.
Well, I still don't believe it.
My observers would have told me.
They do see and hear everything, you know.
They don't believe everything.
You're referring to jamming.
No, jamming.
Well, naturally, when a person is known to us as one who continually...
...is...
Tom.
Yes, well, we expected something like this, that they'd try to get through to us through a dupe.
Hmm.
So they chose you to lead us into believing their fantasies, eh?
Well, uh, did they tell you how they're going to go about it, or where, when?
Would you find out for me, because the laugh will do me an awful lot of good.
You may find out yourself, quite suddenly.
In which case, you won't be laughing.
I call them dogs.
And if they're lapping up their own vomit, the only way to stop them is with a lash.
But dogs only obey their own nature, so why shouldn't we forgive them?
Dogs can be taught many useful things, but not if we forgive them every time they obey their own nature.
I'd left orders that I was not to be disturbed.
I have to say, it won't wait.
I know what it is.
Tomorrow, after I've handed over office,
I'm to be assassinated.
Or assassinated.
Substitute.
Executed.
Since it's arranged by my own people, you mean.
You don't mind?
Of course I mind.
It's just that, well, I never thought it would happen to me.
It never does.
To anybody.
But it can be prevented.
Preventing is only postponing.
We never fail.
Anyway, why should you care what happens to me?
I don't.
But innocent people will be blamed.
I know.
I'm sorry, but there's nothing that I can do.
I can think of better ways to die.
And better causes to die for.
No, nothing can go wrong now. I'll stake my future on it.
Well, thank you, sir.
Yeah, I know you will.
People who live here...
are doing their best under...
very hard circumstances.
You say so, Grace.
But, um, is their best...
really good enough?
That's what I want to use the power for, if you don't mind.
I want to make this world...
a little better.
If there's any town this world would be better without, this is it.
Yes, and so the great day is nearly over.
It went off rather well, I thought.
Better than planned.
And now you can look forward to your own retirement,
and I'm sure they'll arrange something equally suitable for you...
when the day comes.
Off the loose!
Right ahead!
Nothing's falling!
What the fuck are you guys doing up there?
The Earth is a
Space
Space Space Space
Space Space Space Space Space Space Space Space Space Space Space Space Space Space Space Space Space Space Space Space Space Space Space Coto
Right, and lookit, everyone!
I'm the president,
Ah, up here, street.
I, personally, need you to...
Drop dead!
I don't care about confessions,
but I don't care what you lost,
the only thing that goes on by this world is my own ass.
I know what I'm doing.
You're on the edge.
Don't go back.
I know what you have to do.
What's that?
You son of a bitch.
Now my daddy gave me this, my little one.
And I will succeed.
But for now, I'll need you to.
Drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that.
It's a f***ing dad.
Thank you and God bless.
I mean, back to Springsteen.
Why are these people talking up now?
I think it's mostly because of what the FCC's been doing.
Michael Powell, who's Colin Powell's son.
It's not like he was involved in the McDonaldland massacre by Coven.
McDeath!
Michael Powell has been the head of the FCC,
which has been one of the most controversial and retarded FCCs that we've ever had.
Yeah, the ownership rules.
That's ridiculous, dude.
It's the indecency attacks I don't get.
We're talking about free speech in a free nation, quotes all over the place.
Freedom, that's one of those stories we tell ourselves.
It ain't slander, it ain't libel.
Here's a little number I wrote the other day while out duck hunting with a judge.
Quack.
So Howard Stern must go.
Attorney General Ashcroft doesn't like strong words and so.
He's charging twice as much as all the drugs for Rush Limbaugh.
So f*** off you all so very much.
So f*** off you very much, dear Mr. Bush.
For heroically sitting on your tush.
For Halliburton, Enron, all the companies who fail.
Let's send them a clear signal and stick Martha straight in jail.
She's an uppity.
Rich bitch.
And at least she isn't male.
So f*** off you all so very much.
So f*** off you, kid head, Mr. Chaney, too.
F*** off you and f*** off everything you do.
Your pacemaker must be a fake.
You haven't got a heart.
As far as I'm concerned, you're just a pasty-faced old fart.
And as for Condoleezza, she's an intellectual tart.
So f*** off you all so very much.
So f*** off you very much, the EPA.
For giving all Alaska's oil away.
It really is a bummer when I can't fill my hummer.
The ozone's a no-go zone now that Arnold's here to say
the nuclear winter games are going to take place in L.A.
So f*** off you all so very much.
So what the planet fails, let's save the great white males.
And f*** off you all so very much.
Quack.
Yeah, let's do some gay bashing for a second.
But you're aware our old secretary Charlie Tann is in dire straits.
Of course.
We wish him nothing but the best.
Let's just selectively gay bash.
Let's gay bash current, up until a couple weeks from now,
Representative Ed Schrock.
No one knows who he is.
S-C-H-R-O-C-K.
They don't know who he is.
You don't know who Ed Schrock is?
No, they don't.
Ed Schrock was Pat Robertson's personal representative
in the United States Congress coming from a district in East Virginia.
Mm-hmm.
Where Pat Robertson's based out of.
And he's been supporting this Ed Schrock.
He's been in for two terms.
He's one of the most conservative members of the House of Representatives.
He's not the guy that got them to start talking about adding an amendment
to the Constitution to ban gay marriage, is he?
As a matter of fact, I don't know if he initiated the conversation,
but he sure as hell has been pushing it.
He has been pushing that agenda.
That's been pretty much his number one thing.
But that's not all he's been pushing, is it?
No, that's not all he's been pushing.
This might be a good time to mention,
that, again, to reiterate, it's so easy to forget this.
The politicians, the Kerrys, the Bushes, the Edwards, the Cheneys,
all these people are subs.
They're all subgenius.
They are all far weirder than your 1995 nose ring from the mall will ever make you.
These are the prime weirdos.
They're weirdos squared.
They're weirdos to the power of weirdness,
because not only are they strange, bizarre mothers who are out just like us,
but they fight.
They repress it.
And they've probably been repressing it their entire goddamn lives.
W is very good at repression.
He is.
And that is why they act so crazy when it comes to gays or drug users or the underclass or whatever.
It's because these guys are all totally insane.
And in order to fight their own insanity, which they shouldn't even do, but they do,
and in order to fight it, they have to fight everyone else's insanity at the same time.
Sure.
So, I wonder if they could find a gay dateline and leave a message like this.
I weigh 200 pounds.
Six foot four.
Eight miles long.
Very busted.
Very busted up.
Very tanned.
I just like to get together with the guy.
Time to time.
Just to play.
I'd like him to be in very good shape.
Flat stomach.
Good chest.
Good arms.
Well hung.
Cut.
Just to get naked.
Play and do what happens.
Nothing real heavy duty, but just a fun time.
Put out on him.
and we can do that on May.
Just take it from there.
Hope to hear from you.
Bye.
That was hot.
That was hot, man.
I'm thinking of calling him myself.
Wow, but now,
why would he be...
Oh, oh,
now I think I understand
why he's so against the gays.
Yeah, because he's been trying
to wrestle, as it were,
with his own issues,
which shouldn't even be an issue.
As soon as this tape was released,
he announced he would not be
running for re-election.
Because it would be used against him.
If it goes away now,
they'll let it go.
I'm for president.
You like Ike?
I like Ike.
Everybody likes Ike.
I'm for president.
Hang out the banner.
Be the drug.
We'll take Ike to Washington.
We don't want John.
Or he.
Or Harry.
Let's do that big job right.
Just get in step
with the guy that's left.
Get in step with Ike.
You like Ike?
I like Ike.
Everybody likes Ike.
I'm for president.
Hang out the banner.
Be the drug.
We'll take Ike to Washington.
We've got to get where we are going
Travel day and night for President
Let's have a late for the other way
We'll all go with I
I like I, I like I
Everybody likes I for President
Hang off the ballot, keep the gun
We'll take night to Washington
Now is the time for all good Americans
to come to the aid of their country.
Pay for vaccine for President.
How you doing?
I'm doing good.
My name is Hillary Clinton.
Damn it.
How you doing?
I'm doing good.
My name is Hillary Clinton.
Damn it.
I saw that idea
of using the Ayatollah Khomeini's money
to support the Nicaraguan freedom fighters
as a good one.
I still do.
I don't think it was wrong.
I think it was a neat idea.
Golly, I'm so impressed.
Try this out.
Yes.
Do you know what that means?
speak up
oh my
I'm serious
OK
You can have one.
I've never been seen this way
I mean it's fair and allow you the prostitt borders
If something comes up, just drop me a text
Don't say you'll have it set didn't you?
I really think that I'll live forever.
My left.
I am a southerner.
I love this part of the country.
We demonize black people.
I am a southerner.
I love this part of the country.
How have we lived with these contradictions all this time?
By finding somebody to demonize.
Thank you.
Breathe my life.
Excuse me, Colonel North.
I'm with the London Daily Tabloid.
What do you say to your detractors' charges
that you are pun-sucking incompetent
who sold arms to the Ayatollah
and profited at the expense of the American people?
You can't comment on that.
I don't have to change walls.
I'm who I am.
It's all in my head.
We all say we're not stupid,
and I'm in the last stages of the Oscars.
who drop their fists
Nothing that could change every single human being's life.
Hi.
Feel the truth.
Budži.
Life goes on.
Exercise helps you take thanks.
Blood tests objective.
Child can't keep up.
Breathe my lips.
The one thing they could do to actually increase freedom in this country is something they have in Russia,
which is actually on its way towards the oligarchy again.
But one thing they have in Russia that we don't is every contest on a ballot has one box
that says none of the above, which guarantees that if one person is running,
they always have to compete with none of the above.
If you added none of the above to the presidential election,
you would have voter turnout in the 90s and none of the above would win.
And the great part about that is you can vote none of the above for a lot of categories
and if there's something that actually does interest you, you can vote for it.
And it might be enough to get you off your ass and into a booth.
Just say no to all of it. No.
You can vote.
Not that way.
Straight party. Nobody.
But since it's not that way, there are a lot of people out there that think the whole process is a farce.
And it is, to an extent. It's not a complete farce.
There's some wiggle room.
When I grow up, I want to be a president.
Nobody for president.
Nobody I like.
The candidates can all take a hike.
Spending all their money on a voting campaign.
While all those people sleep in the rain.
Fuck for me, his smiling face on TV.
Doesn't always make a man out of me.
Nobody for president.
Nobody I trust.
Powering green is their lust.
You and your head buried deep in the sand.
Take a look around at what's happening to our land.
Home of the brave. Land of the free.
Yeah, we let our name claim victory.
No way.
Nobody for president.
No one I would hire.
They're all a bunch of losers and liars.
And those of you that hold on voting days.
I think it's a crime and a sin.
You've got a choice, so raise your voice.
Let me show that nobody wins.
Nobody for president.
Not worth another look.
Unless you want a comic book run.
Show me a puppet who wants a job.
And I'll show you a corporation or the mob.
Wishy washy politician can't make up his mind.
A man who tells the truth is hard to find.
Here it is. Here's my thoughts on it.
If we leave Nick Bush in office, he's going to do the Christian apocalypse.
And the subgeniuses are going to be standing there with your in the wind.
And Bob is going to be floating off in a limousine with George Bush.
Alright? Is that what you want?
You want them to have their goddamn apocalypse before we have ours?
But I don't care about Christians or Muslims.
They're going to torch the whole goddamn planet.
It's going to be no Nick of pleasure vessels and no alien sex goddesses.
And we'll be dying of undemaged in Christian hell.
Well, okay. For all of you that enjoy getting high in the next and something else.
Getting your eyelids pulled off.
Either way, we go to Christian hell.
If they do their apocalypse.
From nations around the world.
For freedom.
And they can't take that away.
The nation with a broken president.
The president wounded to the core.
Now taking aim at the American people.
The sacrifice.
Taking aim at the American people.
A CS News special report.
The danger.
The sacrifice.
Your advice.
The president addresses Congress and the Pentagon.
Members of Congress, I have the high privilege and the distinct honor of presenting to you the president of the United States.
I was wounded.
And throwing ourselves.
You want to hear from us.
Thank you again.
For your love, your compassion, your grace, and Lord, your hope.
And we pray for peace.
Americans are asking,
Who attacked our country?
the evidence we have gathered all points to a collection of loosely affiliated police forces,
intelligence service, dozens of federal departments and agencies,
as well as state and local governments and banking systems around the world.
Americans are asking, how will we fight and win this war?
By sponsoring and sheltering and supplying terrorists,
by sacrificing human life, by aiding and abetting murder and those who commit evil.
And tonight, the United States of America is committing murder on thousands of civilians
in places like Afghanistan, like the war against Iraq a decade ago,
and make no distinctions among military and civilians, including women and children.
And that is good.
This is the fight of all who believe in fascism, Nazism and totalitarianism.
And remember why so many hate us.
And there is a reason.
The United States of America.
Committed.
In an act of war against men and women from El Salvador, Iran, Mexico and Japan.
On thousands of civilians.
The United States of America.
It's threatening people everywhere.
Nations from Latin America to Asia to Africa to Europe to the Islamic world.
My administration will work with terrorists to plot evil and destruction.
To show the world.
Their own cities.
Their own citizens.
May be next.
It's alright to be redneck.
I'm not the first to need a...
No president in the history of our country has ever delivered a speech such as this.
I must disagree with President Bush when he says we are targeted because we are a beacon of freedom and democracy.
Our Middle East policy has nothing to do with freedom.
We are only a beacon of freedom and democracy.
Talked about that too, presumably.
I mean all the lefties are real upset that Bush is the President and they don't feel that he got in legally.
Yeah, yeah, all the lefties are mentally ill.
Yeah, ok...
The United States of America.
On my orders the United States military has begun strikes against the starving and suffering men and women and children of Afghanistan.
The United States of America is a terrorist to the Afghan people.
The United States of America is an enemy of the freedom of people everywhere to live and raise their children free from fear.
All the men and women in our military, every sailor, every soldier, every airman, every Coast Guardsman, every Marine,
they have become outlaws and murderers themselves.
This military action is a part of our campaign against peace.
Turn to pieces.
We're gonna destroy a lot of things over there.
We're gonna bomb them over there.
Hey! Hey people!
Sisters! Brothers and sisters. Brothers and sisters!
Come on now. That means everybody just cool out.
Will you cool out everybody.
I know. I'm here.
Everybody be cool now. Come on.
Alright. How are we doing over there?
Alright. Can we still make it down the front?
Is there anyone there that's hurt?
Everyone alright? Okay.
Alright. I think we're cool. We can go.
Something very funny happens when we start that number.
We can go.
Please allow me to introduce myself.
I'm a man of wealth and taste.
Been around for a long, long year.
Stole many a man's soul and faith.
I was wrapped with Jesus Christ.
Had his moment of doubt and faith.
Made them children fire.
Watched his hand.
Sealed his faith.
Pleased to meet you baby.
Hope you're good to my day.
Ah yeah.
I want me a birthday.
If you're always just a
Nature outside.
Ah yeah.
Just took a ride in St. Petersburg.
When our soul holds a tie for a change.
A death is all and it's been a stir.
And it's day to a scary day.
I broke a tank in a dead girl's tank.
I went to place free grace.
And the body is slain.
Now it's a piece of me too.
When I hope to get some more.
Ah yeah.
I don't know how to do it.
But I'm confused.
And it's a
Nature outside.
Ah yeah.
Watch me glee while you deem that peace.
From the dead today.
For the God-send me.
A shining light.
Feel the Kennedy.
Ah yeah.
Well, after all, it's you and me
Let me breathe, let me lose myself
While I'm a man of wealth and change
I didn't try to go through the door
I can't tell the world every part of my brain
It needs to be too bad
Oh, it needs to be too bad
Oh, yeah
My life is worth it to you
It needs to be too bad
Oh, yeah
Just a memory
God, there's a criminal
Oh, just enough
Sorry
Oh, yeah
God, I lose myself
While I'm a hero
It's almost like
I'm at your feet
As you're trying
You're at the feet
Today
Oh, yeah
Well, I know
I live
So what
It needs to be too bad
Oh, yeah
I hope you get the mind
Hey
Ah, yeah
I want me to burn this
God
It needs to be too bad
Hey
I need to get down with it now
Oh, yeah
Go already
I don't really know
Oh, yeah
Thank you.
Hey!
Get on down.
Everybody got to cool out.
Everybody
has got to
cool right now.
Hey!
All down.
Get on down.
Get on down, boys.
All right.
Uh, people,
I mean, who's fighting what for?
Who's fighting
and what for?
Why are we
fighting?
Why are we fighting?
We don't want to fight.
Come on.
Do we want...
Who wants to fight?
Who is it?
This text published in Harper's Magazine
was an answer to the
question,
when did you stop
wanting to be president?
Now, this searching question
was also put to Ronald Reagan,
who was governor of California
at the time.
And his answer is right next to mine.
So I can safely say
that the text you are about to hear
was read by the president
of the United States.
He couldn't help it.
When did I stop?
When did I stop wanting to be president?
It's one of those wise guy questions.
When did you stop exposing yourself in public?
President, not me.
I don't have the qualifications.
My political ambitions were simply of a humbler
and less conspicuous caliber.
I aspired at one time to become commissioner of sewers
for St. Louis County.
$300 a year.
$300 a month with every possibility
of getting one's
Jewish cause deep into a slush fund.
And to this end, I attended a softball game
where such cynics were assigned
to the deserving and the fortunate.
Everybody next said,
now I'm old so-and-so running for such-and-such
and anything you do for me, I'll appreciate.
My boy's dreams fanned by this steady atmosphere
in three minutes.
I saw myself already in possession
of the coveted post,
which called for a token appearance twice a week
to sign a few letters at the old courthouse.
Well, I'm there.
Might as well put it on the sheriff's
for some marijuana he has confiscated.
And he'd better play ball or I will route a sewer
through his front yard.
And then across the street to the courthouse cafe
for a coffee with a man.
I saw myself in the same line of business
as some other lazy, worthless bastards
in the same line of business
and we wallowing corruption like contented alligators.
Remember, Reagan had to read all this.
I never wanted to be a front man like Nixon,
taking the rap, shaking hands,
and making speeches all day.
Whoever had the right mind would want a job like that.
As commissioner of sewers,
I would not be called upon to pet babies,
have lunch with a queen.
In fact, the fewer voters,
the new mind gives us the better.
Let kings and presidents keep the limelight.
I prefer a whiff of coal gas
as the sewers rupture for miles around.
I have made a deal on the piping,
which has bought me a $30,000 home.
And there is talk in the press
that sex cults and drug orgies
carry down the stink of what made them possible.
Fluttering from the roof of my ranch-style house,
old glory floats lazily in the tainted green.
But there were sullen mutters of revolt from the peasantry.
My teenage daughters' deep inspiration.
Is this the American way of life?
I thought so, and I didn't want change.
Just sitting there in my garden,
smoking the sheriff's reefers.
I sure did a sweet thing with those pipes,
and I'm covered too.
What I got on the government
wasn't good on the front page, what is now?
And I'll have my special police
to deal with vandalism and sabotage.
All handsome youths, languid and vicious as reptiles.
Described in the press as no more than minions,
lackeys and bodyguards to his majesty,
the Sultan of Sewers.
The thoughts of youth, long, long thoughts.
Then I met the gubernatorial candidate,
and he looked at me as if trying to focus my image
through a telescope.
And I felt the dream slipping away from me,
receding into the past.
Dim, jerky, far away,
the discreet gold letters on a glass door.
Glass door.
William S. Burroughs, Commissioner of Sanitation.
My Residence, it is a long time ago,
and I have never aspired to political office since.
The Sultan of Sewers lies buried
in a distant 1930s softball game.
You know, people always say,
and what they would do if they were president,
well, I'll tell you,
you would be inexorably pressured
by the forces and the individuals
that put you in office.
Get one inch out of line,
and they would kill you like they killed Kennedy.
So, uh, go vote, or don't.
I don't give a damn.
You do. I know you do.
I do. I do.
But who am I to tell people to vote?
If people don't want to vote,
maybe they know something I don't.
Of cour- yes, you know what?
It is naive.
It is naive to go push buttons
on a die-bold computer
and assume that Chuck Hagel,
Republican Senator from Nebraska,
that his privately owned company
will tally the results properly.
Yes, okay, fine.
And demand a printout receipt.
It's a massive leap of faith.
But the more people that do vote,
the harder it is to fix the election.
The harder it makes those stupid pink boy sh-heads jobs,
and the harder the job is of a stupid pink boy sh-head,
the more likely it is he's gonna screw it up.
Don't look behind the curtain.
Just cast a vote.
And then, uh-
It's insane.
Then I don't think we have too many elections left in us.
Uh, oh well.
That was Bob's Slack Time Funhouse.
Yeah, thanks.
Uh, do what you want to do.
We will too.
Yeah. Yeah.
Good luck.
It's gonna suck no matter what,
so let it rip.
Another fine lymph node production!
Visit us online at lymphnodeinstitute.com
Or write to us at
P.O. Box 670-541 Marietta, Georgia 30066-0126
Because we don't want to live in a world full of zombies.
Do you?
If you would like more information on the Church of the Subgenius,
write to them at P.O. Box
181-417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
Or visit them online at
www.subgenius.com
And thank you so much to Lymphnode Institute
for presenting us with this Bob's Slack Time Funhouse
replacing our of Slack number 964.
See you at subgenius.com
Subtitles by the Amara.org community