Wisdom and tune in again next Sunday at 10 o'clock, and now it's time for the hour of slack.
Yes, dear friends.
Hey.
Hey, you over there.
Want to buy some show?
Yeah, we got some good show.
Hey, what's the matter?
What's the matter, man?
Aren't you into show?
Well, once again, we're here in mono.
Oh, no, we're not.
If I jiggle this little knob.
Stereo.
Well, I wish I could say hello to the young lady who was downstairs as I was coming in here.
She was doing business out on Fitzhugh.
I mean, I don't know what she was selling, but she walked up to me like she wanted to sell me something.
But I told her I was in a hurry.
It's.
Too bad.
But.
Oh, yes, dear friends.
It's.
Like I say, we got some show.
Got some show.
If you want it, you can call up here, but we won't put you on the air.
We can't.
It's 823-7490.
I know.
And once again, they've changed the buttons around on everything here, but I bet that if I push this one, we won't explode immediately.
Copyright 1986 by the Subgenius Foundation and the participants.
This is Doug Smith, radio operator.
I'm going to bring you a piece of that green cheese for sure.
I have some magic!
No trouble.
Hear me?
Recording?
Everything's going fine.
No trouble.
And now you are ready for the final 200,000 mile voyage to the moon.
Stop right there.
Intensifying our prospects' desires, and that's when the wheels of action begin to move.
Sorry for jumping in, doctors.
Go on.
Dr. Dobbs is known worldwide as a foremost spokesman for Christian and family values.
He has a plan to attend this rare personal appearance of Dr. Dobbs.
He's the second in the past four years.
And he's the first in the past 20 years.
And he's the second in the past 20 years.
Even if you never intend to write your name again, one sure way to impress folks is to stay a little bit over their heads, because it was better than looking stupid.
It's natural that we followed the circle around and around and around, helping to create a nice round world of confusion and misunderstanding.
Resist the temptation to feed your ego.
Well, we take our initiates and we string a little tendon between the two.
And we drag them three times around the radio station before beginning.
And then we dip them in the sacred waters of S.L.A.R.C.
And what exactly does this do for them?
Well, it causes them to forget everything they've learned, and it prepares their mind for the slate-like impression, the imprinting of the true subgenius.
Welcome, dear friends, to the subgenius hour of S.L.A.R.C.
S.L.A.R.C.
The message is now part of and registered in your subconscious mind.
Every time you say, see, hear, or think.
That's your key phrase.
It will trigger the entire message without your being aware of it.
Repent. Quit your job. Slack off.
Driven to the brink of false sanity by the conspiracy's false reality?
The puncture of a crumbling world.
Then this may be for you.
Eternal salvation.
To triple your money back.
The Church of the Subgenius.
Bring you another 33 minutes of condensed, eraglic functions.
Ah, yes.
This is some swinging music.
Thanks, Reverend Byron Werner, for this.
Great album.
Space Age.
Bachelor Pad.
Friends, tonight, for various different reasons, as always, you should listen in headphones
because the special interactive holophonic stereo whip-around effects, which will permeate
about half the background.
Oop.
Excuse me.
You never know how many tape decks I may have running on this one, Robert.
What?
Oh.
Well, we're cool here, friends.
That's all.
As I was saying, we've got, uh, there's certain dangers inherent in listening to the Subgenius
Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
Uh, this music, uh, not necessarily included.
I'm listening to that swinging.
Hoo.
Yeah.
Um, anyway, we, we create special effects with an Ultimac Color Tone Brainwave Synthesizer.
You may have been reading about those lately.
They're illegal.
Uh, they trigger a total physical separation.
They trigger a total physical separation by stem cleavage of the left and right brains.
Um, that's cerebral mitosis to you science fans.
Creating a forebrain-hindbrain sync lock, if you can dig on that.
And that's the whole reason for this show to exist.
This is a brain disconnection show, which operates on a simple, new, break-thinking principle
by which your brainwave patterns are gradually forced into resynchronization with this tape's
underlying messages.
And...
instructions.
So...
What?
Oh!
Oh, no, not again.
Oh.
A bug of noise whizzing past your ears.
So, okay, that's what we do.
Let's take the old cotton wad that comes with this station and clean it out.
And cautiously...
You did get a cotton wad with your station?
I think it's almost the first of the month.
They come every first of the month when they put acid down the hall of the station to
make sure they kill it.
Diversionary platforms which might be producing that.
Discourse.
That kind of trash.
And there's only one a day, so be very careful where you use that cotton wad.
Salt and mortar.
And now, the noble subgenius knight comes up over the hill and gets ready to slay the
ugly dragon of the conspiracy.
See, there it is with the longy eyes.
So easy this time.
Yeah, you can always tell which one is the right side, which one is the left side of
the screen.
Practice makes skillful.
Oh, no.
Ugly truth.
Well, I guess I'm going to have to spend the day out in Las Colinas today sweeping floors
in a beautiful recording studio to pay the bills.
Working for Bob.
That's right.
But there he is now.
What Bob was.
Which one's the real Bob?
Which one's the conspiracy Bob?
He's been shot.
How many times have these callers given up attempting to get on non-radio?
Well, Bob was shot again by them.
The Californians.
And we don't know what exactly he wants to do now.
Here's a film of that shooting now.
Bob, as played by Bob, appears behind the doctors on stage.
Gary Capofram begins shooting.
All right.
God.
If I can.
I'll let.
Shooting.
He's shooting this.
There.
No.
Okay.
Just about.
Light rays of power.
There.
Oh, friends.
It's more of those air pirates trying to get into the show.
All these other shows trying to horn in on the original true hour of slack,
which hasn't existed for nearly as long as some of those other shows.
But as I was saying, friends, some other warnings,
along with the earplugs that you should have received when you turn the show in.
Each subgenius show, by the way, is one note in one great vast Doctors for Bob song.
That's Doctors for Bob are a subgenius band.
And this show is a note in their song.
And the crescendo of that song will come at the end of creation.
So do not over medicate yourself with this show.
You should, however, listen more than once.
These are complex shows, more carefully orchestrated and more scientifically accurate than any previous form of art or expression in all of mankind's history.
Do not operate heavy, heavy machinery while under the influence of these shows.
Car listening is legal.
But not.
Recommended for first time users.
Do not in any way attempt to dance to these tapes or shows.
The demons you see during the initial hallucination sequences are not real.
If you become frightened, try not to give up the scene.
No scene on the show lasts any longer than a minute or so.
So don't panic during the hell scenes and a surface from the show slowly at the end of the hour,
because coming out of the show is sort of a total rebirth experience.
If you can do it successfully, that is.
If you have trouble.
Re-entering the earth plane after this show, focus on Bob and chant his name and then try to remember your own name and chant that for a while and don't eat for a couple of days after the show.
So I think this is going to be.
I love this music.
It's like cartoon music.
Well, anyway, I'm as usual, prepared an elaborate subgenius show tonight with all of our tapes and then decided to throw them out.
And instead went through my record collection and pulled out.
Songs by other subgeniuses of different cultures to vastly different cultures.
Songs against the conspiracy, and that's what the Church of the Subgenius is all about.
Fighting the conspiracy.
And I'm not going to try to define the conspiracy for you.
You either know what we're talking about and know it's the truth or else.
You're doomed and may fry forever in some before life or afterlife.
But we'll we'll depress you first with the protest songs by ethnic subgeni.
And then we'll try to build your mood back up into some semblance of sanity.
But first, a word from our sponsor.
Don't worry about all that.
Lying was.
Has this ever happened to you?
Why, I should have been there, Ted.
It was great.
There was free booze.
Great music.
One of the best.
One of the best parties I ever went to.
And where were you that night?
Oh, I just kind of stayed home and watched TV.
I guess I should have gone, huh?
Didn't you feel stupid?
Didn't you wish you could go back to that night, that party?
Well, maybe now there's a way to learn how to do that very thing.
Introducing Bob's School of Time Control.
At Bob's, you'll learn how to speed time, slow time, and make time run backwards.
Backwards.
But most importantly, you'll be learning how to make time work for you.
How, you may ask?
Well, just ask this man here, an actual graduate of Bob's School of Time Control.
One day, my dog ran out in front of a truck.
Blango.
My dog was dead.
Was I sad till I met Bob.
Bob showed me how I could go back, get the registration number for the car, do a slip
job on the brakes, and wouldn't you know it, that truck went off into a ditch and burst
into flames just exactly a block before he could hit old Booger.
Ain't that right, fella?
Yes, just imagine the horrible things that could be undone tomorrow if you had only gone
to Bob's School of Time Control.
Julia Albalan, Mary Tabby, Amy
Walsher.
Hi.
We had a first cousin called Arthur McBride
He and I took a stroll down by the seaside
A-seeking good fortune and what might betide
T'was just as the day was a-dawnin'
Then after restin' we both took a tramp
We met Sergeant Harper and Corporal Cramp
Besides the wee drummer who beat up for camp
With his rowdy dow-dow in the morning
He says, my young fellows, if you will enlist
A guinea you quickly shall have in your fist
Besides a crown for to kick off the dust
And drink the king's health in the morning
Had we been such fools as to take the advance
The wee bit of morn'
Had to run chance
Do you think you'd know scruple to send us to France
Where we would be killed in the morning?
He says, my young fellows, if I hear but one word
I instantly now will outwit my sword
And into your bodies as strength will abhor
So now, my gay devils, take warning!
But Arthur McBride said,
Your lord and I, we took him the odds
We gave them no chance for to launch out their swords
Our wacky chaleleys came over their heads
And paid them right smart in the morning
As for the wee drummer, we rifled his pouch
And we made a football of his rowdy dow-dow
And into the ocean
To rock and to roll, and bad at the tea is returning.
As for the old rapier that hung by his side,
We flung it as far as we could in the tide,
Till the devil wiped its shoes as Adam and Bride,
To temper your steel in the morning.
¶¶
Oh, yes, dear friends, that was a group,
an iron.
An Irish traditional group called Planksteep.
Some listeners to this station may even have heard of them.
They blew my mind at one time in Ireland.
Yeah, whew.
That was some of my racial memory going on there,
but we've got lots of others.
I wanted to, I cut in to say that somebody was trying to call,
and if this, I can't answer the phone when I'm talking or cueing tapes,
and, I mean, we can't put you on anyway,
all we can do is kind of deliver a slight amount of healing or slack or hate or something,
as per this church.
But whoever called can hang up and call back again,
because right now your call is locked in Jeff's office down the hall,
and we can't get in there.
Your conversation is tied up in a room in this poor station.
Well, anyway, friends, do you remember the last poets?
Song!
Up, down, on the corner, uptown.
I turned around and hear the sound of voices talking about who's gonna die next.
Cause the white man's got a God complex.
Silent niggas scream for help.
Ah, help me, help me.
Nigga, make your own help.
Shit, you need it.
I turn around and hear the sound of jukeboxes playing in bars.
Pimps popped outside in big pretty Cadillac cars.
Cleaned it in a broke dick dog.
Sitting in a big fine hog.
Dressed very fine in a mohair silk vine.
But Jim Dale died next.
Cause the white man's got a God complex.
Hey, brother, what's your sport?
My man, I got just the thing for you.
Only cost ten and two.
What you gonna do, baby?
I got black ones, brown ones, red ones, yellow ones.
I even got a white one.
If you wanna buy some.
Yeah, that's right.
Two fifty-eight.
Play it straight.
I got it all worked out.
You know what I'm talking about.
Been reading my dream book.
Ain't no way in the world a kid gonna get took.
Nigga, what you mean?
I didn't hit.
Nigga, you full of shit.
Lick dice.
Uh, now seven.
Come on, be nice and hit eleven.
Well, what do you know?
It's little Joe.
Hey, my man got twenty dollars.
Say, little Joe don't blow.
Ha, baby needs a pair.
Yes, you.
Ah, Papa's got the funky blues.
Ah, Mama plays the crossword in the news.
Oh, snake guys.
Sorry, nigga, you lose.
The line forms to the real lady.
And I don't care if you never cash your welfare checks.
Cause the white man's got a God complex.
But I got ten babies.
I ain't got no man.
I ain't got no choice but to hold out my hand and feed my young ones the best way I can.
Hey, man.
What you mean?
Ain't no doubles on blackjack.
Pup, you better change that rule.
Cause I ain't no fool.
You better be cool, Jim, or you'll die next.
Cause the white man's got a God complex.
Hey, my man, uh, I wanna cop a nickel bag.
You say, oh, you got a skag.
Wow, that's a drag.
Cause, uh, I don't wanna cop no dope is death.
Next.
Cause the white man's got a God complex.
Hey, baby.
You better get out tonight.
Well, there's one over at Slick's for faggots and tricks.
There's one around graveyard side of town that'll cost you a pound.
But if you go and know what I know, you better pack your piece at least or you'll die next.
Cause the white man's got a God complex.
Mr. Stein, I done paid enough rent for this pad to be mine.
But you just wanna cheat me cause I ain't your kind.
Damn, can't you see the place is falling down?
No.
You can't dig it.
Cause you ain't never around.
Damn, I'm so poor.
I don't know what the hell I'mma do anymore.
Not from this day to the next.
Cause the white man's got a God complex.
I'm making guns.
I'm God.
I'm making bombs.
I'm making gas.
I'm God.
I'm making freak machines.
Life control pills.
I'm God.
Kill Indians who discovered him.
Kill Japanese with A-bomb.
I'm God.
Kill and still kill black people.
A slave in the earth.
I'm God.
No way to the moon.
Fell back with his dog.
Don't you blame me for your problems.
I'm not your Indian anymore.
You belong to white man.
We are high, high, high, we are high, high, high.
B.I.A., don't you blame me for your problems.
I'm not your Indian anymore.
You belong to us and we are high, high, high, we are high, high, high.
B.I.A., you can't change me, don't you try.
We don't want your white man rules no more.
We can live our own way.
We are high, high, high, we are high, high, high.
B.I.A., don't you blame me for your problems.
I'm not your Indian anymore.
You belong to us and we are high, high, high, we are high, high, high.
B.I.A., you can't change me, don't you try.
We don't want your white man rules no more.
We can live our own way.
We are high, high, high, we are high, high, high.
B.I.A., don't you blame me for your problems.
I'm not your Indian anymore.
You belong to us and we are high, high, high, we are high, high, high.
B.I.A., you can't change me, don't you try.
We don't want your white man rules no more.
We can live our own way.
We are high, high, high, we are high, high, high.
B.I.A.
Boy, folks, this is a tough one.
My headphones are all tangled up in the telephone.
I shouldn't have given anybody the number.
We can't put you on.
I can barely handle this engineering stuff.
So...
Don't call unless you really need a healing.
But we do appreciate hearing from you.
Oh, by the...
Well, I'm going to get on with this before we go into the subgenius news.
This is the next ethnic minority group to be represented.
The Mutants.
Captain Beefheart.
Oh, that I just played was Floyd Westerman.
He's a sort of...
He's a Lakota Sioux folk singer from...
I think he's from Rosebud Reservation.
And if there's...
Now, here's somebody who can call in.
Anybody from Rosebud Reservation in South Dakota, call up.
Because if I know you're out there, I'll play some...
I've got all kinds of stuff from the Crow Dog record,
UEP stuff, various ceremonial deals, and some fancy dance music.
So I used to live out there, believe it or not.
Yeah, I've been to all these places these records are from,
and that's why I have them.
And I'm afraid I've been here, too.
¶¶
Sky's showin'
Bein'
Flower growin'
Boyin'
Girl glowin'
Factory no place for me
Boss man, leave me be
guitar solo
Factory no place for me
Boss man, leave me be
Mind inside I'm goin'
Rufflin' bonus showin'
One thing sure I know it
Get a hold of where I'm goin'
Factory no place for me
Boss man, leave me be
guitar solo
GTM
oh
pop
jam
fare
really
advantage
aboot
my
job
Just left school, nice and clean
Power tool, man machine
Steady job, nine to five
Wonder if I'm still alive
I'm completely bored
Nationally insured
Life is not so hard
When they stamp your card
Nine to five pollution blues
Only got my soul to lose
Wish I didn't have to choose
Standing in a dead man's shoes
My armpits smell, my breath is bad
I look like hell, I feel so sad
Rotten fruit between my toes
In my suit I decompose
Standing on my own
My flesh comes off the bone
My blood takes away
Tells me that I'm saved
Nine to five pollution blues
Only got my soul to lose
Wish I didn't have to choose
Standing in a dead man's shoes
I didn't
Soon beyond when I die
Another moment you'll survive
See no future, no escape
Mother nature changing shape
The day that I was born
A number of four
Said I'd rise
And must be utilized
Nine to five pollution blues
Only got my soul to lose
Wish I didn't have to choose
Standing in a dead man's shoe
In a dead man's shoe
This is KNON 90.9
in Dallas, Texas.
You say you're looking for excitement.
I'm not.
Look, isn't this opportunity a real nice place to raise the kids?
Well, explore no more.
We're there already.
Let's visit the world of the future.
World of the future.
Yes, this bustling world of a thousand moods reflects the dreams of its ambitious inhabitants,
dreams already realized of man's triumph over nature,
where humans no longer suffer self-inflicted pains,
where one is made to enjoy life.
All the signs point to serious health damage.
There are no winners in a nuclear war.
The minute you have another war,
there's not going to be much.
There's only one world left, I don't know.
But you're going to blow one another to pieces.
And in these times when the world is breathing,
all the others find a home.
There's not going to be anything left for the kids.
I mean, there's not going to be a world left.
And we're all going to end up digging our own holes.
As soon as we dig them, they're going to fall in on us.
I don't think anybody would know what to do.
Even the Australian president.
The only true religion is guns.
The guns will create your own reality.
Not a gun, I can create my own reality.
What is the church's priorities?
What's important to you guys?
Mainly the quest for slack.
The casting out of false prophets.
And controlling time.
Those are our three main goals, I guess.
Slack.
Slack is something we all need.
And I know that lots of people out there
listening right now are feeling
a terrible shortage of slack.
A shortage that can be...
Slack is something you can't get enough of.
That's right. That's right. And we can help them to get slack, George.
That's right. And we can help them to get slack, George.
Man, the world is filled with a bunch of
kooky ideas and concepts about the Bible.
And I can't believe the weird things
that people get in their heads and start...
Ashley Bob just uses me as an instrument of death.
That's what I like about the Word of God.
There's nothing fakey about this thing, man.
You talk about telling it like it is.
See, it hangs the dirty wash right out the front bay window.
For everybody to see.
Aw fridge, Hey wanna know they got the spirit of fire
for entire, whole entire, whole entire day
It's production stamp
about the word Trump and Trump and Trump
and what it's a hell like some facts things going on.
The following program is transcribed in Spanish for our Latin listening audience.
A big house and a cheap education?
Do you want to change your luck or take advantage of your business?
Friends, you can have those things and much, much more easily.
I'm going to explain.
Do you know JR Bob Dogs?
Are you informed with the Church of the Subgenius?
I thought not.
Only Bob! He's the same Bob!
And Bob does not change!
And Bob does not stop changing!
He come on down!
Yes?
These humans will not wake up.
Only the return of Jesus or intervention by some cosmic superintelligence can save us now.
And only Bob can bring about either one properly.
But if you don't want to boil your brains,
and you don't want to be a man,
or if you want to be a man,
then you've got to be a zombie business corridors of empty pinkness or grinding poverty.
If you don't want to feel the meat cook off your bones in a nuclear oven that was once your hometown,
you'd better drop your mental candy bars and step out under the blinding light of the sun
and make witness to what you really are.
Yes, you'd better be ready to jump.
Probably econocataclism.
Those of you who know how to climb up a conspiracy job tree
had better know how to climb back down again.
You're going to be stuck.
up there when the heat rises.
Look around you.
The signs
are everywhere.
The American social
patterns have already gone
way too far.
The family is all broken
apart. Morals
have degenerated into a
venereal TV swamp.
Drug abuse
and perverted
sex are taught
in schools just
like the Roman Empire before it fell.
Collapse is nearly total now.
It may become
in the final few years
we'll mutilate our children
beyond our wildest
nightmares.
Yes, it's everywhere.
The money changers,
the beast, the masters
of pink, purveyors
of all that is sheepish and soft
in the world, they're just setting
us up for a massive
white
wee resurgence, which in turn
allows the great witch burning.
Look, there, we already have demon
infiltrated normalcy
shock troops
going by the hellishly ironic
name of moral majority.
Good God,
are these supposed to be Christians?
They've got Jesus
and the devil all mixed up.
Make
no mistake,
some genius foundation is with
Jesus, the fighting
Jesus, not some
long-haired mush mouth.
We're with Brother Roloff
and free enterprise in America.
We're no communist tools of
Satan.
Who are they winning souls for,
Satan or Jesus?
Beware of false prophets.
That is the main warning that
Bob is getting out. You're going to be
seeing more and more of these people,
who claim to be Jesus, come again, for instance.
We know of ten people right off hand
here in the United States that claim to be
Jesus right now, and they all
have tremendous number of followers.
Now, we believe that there can't be more than one
Jesus at any one time,
so even if one of them was the real one,
there's nine of them that aren't.
All we want people to know is that there's a lot
of people out there that are going to try to get you
to believe what they want you to believe.
You think we're trying to get money out of you.
You ought to see how some of these guys with the
new Messiah,
they're trying to get all your worldly goods.
Sure.
If you send us enough money, we'll send you the whole
church, and you can deal with it instead of us.
Okay, well,
after I do that, what are you going to do for me?
Slack.
Quite enough of that
depressing fare.
Hello, and welcome to Happyland.
The people here in Happyland are very
calm.
And the drugs are very effective.
Nonsense may be heard over
our PA system, and as we
walk toward Happyland's gates,
let us remind you of no pushing,
no sharp objects, and no writing
to your favorite home. Thank you.
This is a crook
at her first night.
I feel to wear it.
There's nothing less graceful than an
angry spud.
This is some rare Devo.
Bootleg Devo.
Naughtyajev novikievskoy,
Oh, trouble's coming.
No one's going
You are not fighting
here
There's a curfew
to war
Laughing
lying
mad
Laughing
rational
No more
grumbling
Edwards
Thank you.
Well, as some of, as a few sub-geni know,
old Mark Mothersbaugh, Reverend Mark Mothersbaugh of Devo,
is also a born-again sub-genius.
And it's funny how the circle comes and goes.
That song was probably being done about the same time as we wrote our pamphlet.
And a couple of months ago, when we were doing our devivals,
Buck and I were out with Doctors for Bob and the Pope of New York
and the band Dare Not Speak Its Name doing sub-genius revivals
up and down the Pink Coast, the West Coast, Seattle, San Francisco, and L.A.
And there we met.
And all kinds of strange weirdos.
And Nina Hagen.
Oh, yeah, Buck saw Nina Hagen and thought it was just a punkette
dressed up as Nina Hagen.
And went up and said, you look like Nina Hagen.
And she said, my name is no name.
So she said, yes, I know Nina very well.
So let's see.
Anyway, what I was getting to is Mark introduced me to a young lady named Nancy Ferguson,
a younger generation of rock and roller.
I mean, real younger.
This is a song called Drop Me Off at the Galleria by Visiting Kids.
This song, I think, illustrates what's wrong with the world today.
It's done by a group of, well, Nancy's probably in her 20s,
but the rest of the singers are little bitty kiddos.
They're like 10 to 12 years old, something like that.
Yeah.
This is Visiting Kids.
And after that, we'll play the Wallman's version of The Shopping Mall Life,
followed by Negative Land's version of The Shopping Mall Life.
What a life, friends.
He was 14, a little older than 13.
He was in eighth grade, and he made me go crazy.
After school, he asked me if it was cool
if he could take me to go shopping.
His mom drove a K-car.
It was far, I thought.
I started to blink a lot and sweat a lot, and I said,
Drop me off.
Drop me off at the Galleria.
I couldn't stand this guy or his mother.
Oh, brother.
Drop me off at the Galleria.
Drop me off on the San Diego freeway.
Oh, drop me off.
Drop me off at the Galleria.
After school, he asked me if it was cool
if he could take me to go shopping.
His mom drove a K-car.
It was far, he thought.
I started to blink a lot and sweat a lot, and I said,
Drop me off at the Galleria.
I couldn't stand this guy or his mother.
Oh, brother.
Drop me off at the Galleria.
Drop me off on the San Diego freeway.
Oh, drop me off.
I just got a guy in his car.
He was funny clothes.
He was freckles.
I want to go to the Galleria.
Maybe see a movie or something.
Buy new clothes.
I just want to be drunk.
Please drop me off at the Galleria.
Drop me off.
Drop me off at the Galleria.
Drop my off.
Drop me off.
on any other radio station around here because that's not on a record.
Most of the stuff we play, there isn't on records.
Like this next one by the Wall Men.
This is the other side of the shopping mall world that has created the...
Anyway, this is the Wall Men.
Yeah, the Wall Men.
They're a lot like Doctors for Wotan,
one of the first Doctors for Bob copy bands in the subgenius church.
These guys are from Syracuse, New York,
and they're depressed because they're the people who are working in the malls.
Here we go.
Because you have been faithful in prayer,
faithful in the reading of the word,
and because you have not forsaken the house of God,
you have overcome the tempter and gained the crown of eternal life.
For this I say, well done, thou good and faithful servant.
Enter thou into the joys of thy Lord.
Praise God.
I made it.
I finally made it.
Did you hear?
Glory to God.
Oh, I thank you, Lord, for thy mercy.
I thank you, Lord.
Blessed be thy name.
Oh, I love you, Jesus.
I thank you, Lord.
Hallelujah.
Glory to God.
I made it.
Hallelujah.
Praise God.
All right, see, folks, it works out okay for some people.
But then there's others.
This is Doctors for Bob's version of Hell.
This song introduces a new genre in country and western music.
We call it Gosp Hell.
It's gospel music for people who know they're going to hell anyway.
It's a little thing called Legs of Fire.
Let's roll.
Okay.
Well, I thought I could get away with saunter on our wedding day.
Preacher man said, boy, better put away your song.
But I said, I don't.
Cotton to no God's county law.
But that song was stolen.
At least that's what they said.
So I wrapped up in asbestos from my waist up to my head.
I wrapped up in asbestos that I got from Greg's.
I only wish I had enough to cover up my legs.
So I've been sinning, sinning, sinning.
But I ain't no liar.
I'm burning, burning, burning.
I got legs, I got legs, I got legs of fire.
Oh, my head's dry and cool.
So's my arms and tool.
My torso, even more so.
But I ain't no liar.
Now I'm burning, burning, burning.
I got legs, I got legs, I got legs of fire.
Well, I was selling heroin at the elementary school.
Preacher man said, boy, you know that isn't cool.
The good Lord come to me and said my time was up.
When I asked why God, he said because that horse was cut.
They were shooting up in the bathroom.
Yes, you know it's true.
But they were not getting off until my soul was through.
Oh, I've been sinning, sinning, sinning.
But I ain't no liar.
Now I'm burning, burning, burning.
I got legs, I got legs, I got legs of fire.
Oh, my brain ain't in no flame.
And my shoulder ain't in pain.
But my toes.
Need a hose.
But I ain't no liar.
Now I'm burning, burning, burning.
I got legs, I got legs, I got legs of fire.
Well, I was stealing cars for God to try to get in well.
But when my judgment came, he said you'll have to go to hell.
It's true I gave my son, he said, to pay for all your sins.
But when you brought me that limo, Jane, or the door was dented in.
Oh, I've been sinning, sinning, sinning.
But I ain't no liar.
Now I'm burning, burning, burning.
I got legs, I got legs, I got legs of fire.
Oh, my head ain't on the line.
And my arm is doing fine.
But my knees are trying please.
But I ain't no liar.
Now I'm burning, burning, burning.
I got legs, I got legs, I got legs of fire.
Well, I was bashing grandma's head with a railroad tie.
Good Lord, come to me.
And said, why did you lie?
When I said, what lie?
God, he said, you must confess.
That ain't your grandma's head at all.
It's just a bloody mess.
Oh, I've been sinning, sinning, sinning.
But I ain't no liar.
Now I'm burning, burning, burning.
I got legs, I got legs, I got legs of fire.
Yeah.
That's too bad that I don't own that mystery.
They call it a download, guys.
No, I'll change it toion top.
At first, stop wanting to listen to it.
Leave it to yourself.
No shame, this is your promo.
We need to be happy with our money.
I don't know how I'm ever going to get it why
I get it wrong.
But I earned $300.
Did you know that I never bought a Poker Robo?
It's a crack pot.
After all, it should be every person's choice to curse God and die if that is what they wish.
We all have the right to spit in the eye of the collective gods, did we not create them?
Where indeed would Yahweh own be without the human race to torment and pester?
I'll put it to you, the old chiseler would be pretty damn bored with it all
if there was nothing more entertaining than sherbins and seraphims and numby-pumby flaming angels
sitting around up there on damp clouds and arcing and trumpeting all 24 hours a bloody day
and you can fuck all that.
Uh, what did you say, Bob?
I said good Lord, what's to lose?
A little time?
Hurt your ego a little bit, baby?
You've probably got time you're wasting on Mickey Mouse stuff now, so that's no big deal.
So why not?
Why not make a new beginning in your life and see what'll happen?
I don't know.
You don't know.
And you will never know.
You have signed the application.
You do have the kit.
None of those things are important.
But there is a point in your life when you've got to just stop talking about it
and you've got to stop worrying about what your friends and neighbors and relatives
and uncles and aunts and sisters and brothers and everybody else is going to say about it.
Because nobody else is going to pay your bills for you.
Why not?
You don't know.
And you will never know.
And who knows?
Just maybe.
You could air one of the biggest...
I don't know.
But even more important, you don't know.
And you will never know.
You will never know.
Just maybe.
You're in for a new and exciting experience.
You have signed the application.
Well, have you got your pipe through the mail?
Or are you going to write in and get your pipe?
I'm still waiting for the cast.
The cast?
Well, the cast is all here, unfortunately.
They'll be outside your house to sing a song about 8 o'clock this morning.
Actually, we're expecting Vic Moore.
Oh, well, friends, that was that last little piece you heard there.
On the...
Ooh.
Good thing I punched the tabs out of that cassette.
I would have erased it.
That was put together by Puzzling Evidence.
The original Puzzling Evidence.
Not the Puzzling Evidence that you'll...
That David Byrne's group will sing about in the song they...
In the movie they filmed around here.
They got that Puzzling Evidence from our Puzzling Evidence.
But, uh...
Let's see.
What have we?
Slim Whitman.
No.
It ain't Slim Whitman.
It's...
Ooh.
Wow.
Listen to that, friends.
It's negative land.
Yeah.
Let's get 10-4 first.
I guess I'm gonna have to start jamming mobile.
Is that what you're trying to tell me?
I guess I should start jamming you guys.
All right, people.
It's almost time for us to be 10-8.
In just a few moments,
we're gonna be 10-8,
and I'm...
I'm going to tell you the story of 180 and the letter G.
All right, people.
It's almost time for us to be...
We're almost to that moment right now, people.
In just a few moments, we're gonna be 10-8.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
Hmm.
I am a man
A man with four fingers
A man with four fingers on my hand
I am a man
A man with four fingers
Oh, yes, dear friends.
I'll tell you what.
I promise I'm gonna play
the negative land and special effects editing
song that I'm gonna be playing.
I'm gonna play the negative land and special effects editing song that I'm gonna be playing.
sound effects show, an incredible
narrated show
next week.
We'll go heavy on sound effects,
so be ready with
your tape decks and your headphones.
This
Negative Land album is literally
just unbelievable.
Anyway, and it was unbelievable
today. It's the reason we've got
such a disorganized show, because
this is a disorganized religion, and we were
mailing out the new
subgenius pamphlets
today. Oh, yes,
it's beautiful. You should have seen
the warehouse. This is pamphlet number two,
and all you members in Dallas, you $20
subgenius members, you believers
and bobbies and gimme bobs and so
forth will get this pamphlet soon,
because you should have seen the warehouse today.
We had all the zombies wired
up.
65 zombies, Smith's
zombies. They're all named Smith, every one of them.
Not me. I'm Reverend Stang.
But these were the other
Smiths, the clone
Smiths. They were all wired and yoked in
sequence, having to hand sort
49,000 pamphlets by zip
code. These subgenius
church pamphlets are to be airdropped
into foreign countries where
there's no slack.
For instance,
Galapagos sea turtles are used
to carry the pamphlets strapped to their
back into
the shores of Red China.
Whales
have been force-fed pamphlets.
I mean, these zombies are hard at work.
We force-feed the pamphlets to these
whales, which then swim to Russia
and South Africa and other
slackless places and beach
themselves. They actually commit suicide
for Bob by beaching themselves
and disengorging
those hundreds and thousands,
49,000 subgenius
pamphlets, so that those
red commies can read about
the world of slack and revolt against
their masters, and so that
all the slackless
people in all the slackless lands
where there's too many of
those who don't
have enough. And you know, too much is always
better than not enough. Bob said that.
Bob always says that.
A man with no fingers
on my hand
I am a man
A man
with no fingers
A dad
Well, that
doesn't count my ring finger, my middle
finger, my index finger,
or my...
Ah, yes.
Dear friends, if you want to write for information
to the Church of the Subgenius, that's
P.O. Box 140306
Dallas,
Texas, 75214.
And we need those
dispensations from you, those love
offerings. Once again,
that's Church of the Subgenius, P.O. Box
140306.
Dallas, Texas,
75214.
Write for information
about all the books and pamphlets.
We're not kidding about these pamphlets and tapes.
We sell the tapes. We can tell
you where we got the
songs we play because you can't
get them in stores. And this one
right here, as a matter of fact...
You hear this?
This is...
This was
performed by Mark
Mothersbaugh.
Believe it or not, we've been playing it all this time
and you thought it was just some subgenius.
Ha ha.
America
you invite the
red man to sit
at your table
and be your guest
to justify
the guilt that
you are feeling.
Now you tell us that
you like us the best
and a black
man
waiting on the sidelines
for the chance
to get into your game
to show
you that
he's just as good as you are
to prove to you
that he can be
the same
and the triangle
that you have created
is the triangle that you have created
and the triangle that you have created
keeps you by yourself
and keeps you paranoid
for the red, white
and blue that you keep flying
and black that you avoid
cause the red man
was here so long before you
while the black man
was a slave you brought ashore
and the red man
was killed to free the boy
from the frontier
while the black man was killed
for sporting nothing boy
and you wonder why
the red man won't be like you
you should wonder why
the black man wants to be
and you came to this land
because you wanted freedom
but that you have forgotten
now that you are free.