Do not stand at my grave and weep.
I am not there.
I do not sleep.
I am a thousand winds that blow.
I am the diamond glints on snow.
I am the sunlight on ripened grain.
I am the gentle autumn rain.
When you awaken in the morning's hush,
I am the swift, uplifting rush of quiet birds' encircled flood.
I am the soft stars that shine at night.
Do not stand at my grave and cry.
I am the self-genius, power of sweat.
God did not sweat.
Thank you.
For you
Not me
More beautiful than ever
You know
I don't know about you
But I think it's pretty hard
Keeping up with the Kardashians
It's really tough
And Jersey Shore? Man
I can't even take my clothes off no more
It's so goddamn beautiful out there
Everybody's so full of ideas
And wonderful values
Trying to bring the world forward
Like Glenn fucking Beck
And Snooki
She's too beautiful to go to jail
What a piece of fucking hard-fucked piece
Subhuman shit
You know what I'm saying?
I said do you know what I'm saying?
It's getting hot in here
So take off all your clothes
I'm getting so hot
I'm gonna take my clothes off
It's a beautiful, beautiful world
For you, for you, for you
Well, but not for me
Thank you guys, thank you, folks
Jerry Casale, everybody!
Jerry Casale!
All hail Devo!
I saw juice at dinner time swimming in the stew
Jesus is everywhere
I saw juice in the morning in the burning bush
I saw juice in the afternoon too
I saw juice at dinner, swimming in the stew
Jesus is everywhere
And in this film, the guy is talking about how...
Are they Abraham's descendants? So am I.
Are they servants of Christ?
I am out of my mind to talk like this. I am more.
I have worked much harder, been in prison more frequently, been flogged more severely,
and been exposed to death again and again.
Five times I received from the Jews the forty lashes minus one.
Three times I was beaten with rods.
Once I was stoned.
Three times I was shipwrecked.
I spent a night and a day in the open sea.
I have been constantly on the move.
Once I was stoned.
I have been in danger from rivers, in danger from bandits,
in danger from my own countrymen,
in danger from Gentiles,
in danger in the city,
in danger in the country,
in danger at sea,
and in danger from false brothers.
I have labored and toiled and have often gone without sleep.
I have known hunger and thirst and have often gone without food.
I have been cold and naked.
Who is weak and I do not feel weak?
Who is led into sin and I do not inwardly burn?
If I must boast, I will boast of the things that show my weakness.
The God and Father of the Lord Jesus, who is to be praised forever,
knows that I am not lying.
In Damascus, the governor under King Aretas had the city of the Damascenes guarded in order to arrest me.
But I was lowered in a basket from a window in the wall and slipped through his hands.
I must go on boasting.
Although there is nothing to be gained, I will go on to visions and revelations from the Lord.
I know a man in Christ who fourteen years ago was caught up to the third heaven.
He said, give me a Pepsi.
I said, give me a Pepsi and a bowl.
Whether it was in the body or out of the body, I do not know.
God knows.
She says, well, he is some kind of a nut.
So she poured a bowl of Pepsi and put it in front of him.
He took a dead bird out of his pocket and put it in the bowl.
And I know that this man, whether in the body or apart from the body, I do not know, but God knows, was caught up to paradise.
Then he started singing the little song, Come Alive.
He heard inexpressible things, things that man is not permitted to tell.
I will boast about a man like him.
I will not boast about myself, except about my weaknesses.
Even if I should choose to boast, I would not be a fool because I would be speaking the truth.
But I refrain, so no one will think more of me than is warranted by what I do or say.
To keep me from becoming conceited because of these surpassingly great revelations, there was given me a thorn in my flesh, a messenger of Satan to torment me.
Compares is to move
As time goes on, chief whitewhale moon gioves in
I will boast all the more gladly about my weaknesses, so that Christ's power may rest on me.
That is why, for Christ's sake, I delight in weaknesses, in insults, in hardships, in persecutions, in difficulties.
For when I am weak, then I am strong.
I have made a fool of myself, but you drove me to it.
I ought to have been commended by you, for I am not in the least inferior to the super-apostles, even though I am nothing.
Forgive me this wrong.
Now I am ready to visit you for the third time, and I will not be a burden to you, because what I want is not your possessions, but you.
And now we have a very special guest.
Devo Dan.
Known for albums including Everything Must Go, Total Devo,
Pretzels Now,
For the Future,
But most of all, for the acclaimed Are We Not Dan, We Are Gaucho.
He took a 20-year Hawaiian vacation, but is back in the game.
Here to sing his 1978 hit, Hey Homo.
They tell us that we lost our tails
Evolving up from little snails
I'd say it's all just within sense
Are we not men?
We are the old
Please take me along when you slip on down
We're pinheads
Now we are not home
We're pinheads now
We are not home
Are we not men?
We are the old
Please take me along when you slip on down
So long as you do bump on down
Are we not you?
Are we not we?
Are we not men?
Are we not the old?
Are we not to be Para bolos?
Are we not our houses for predominant pox?
Are we not men?
God made man
Mm, mm, mm
Can use the monkey to do it now
Monkey man all
In business suit
Teachers and critics all dance the boot
Say it again
Monkey man all
In business suit
Teachers and critics all dance the boot
Monkey man all
In business suit
Teachers and critics all dance the boot
We are Devo
D-E-V-O
All right Cleveland, Devo Dan loves you. Peace out.
Thanks Devo Dan.
The fire will
T- communities
Coercions
Empress
The
FYI
Hmm
The
One, two, three, four
Devo, Devo, Devo, Devo, Devo
Devo, Devo, every night and day
Devo is the one and only way
Devo, Devo, Devo, Devo, Devo
Devo, Devo, every night and day
Devo is the one and only way
Devo, Devo, Devo, Devo, Devo
Devo, Devo, Devo, Devo, Devo, Devo
Devo, Devo, Devo, Devo, Devo, Devo, Devo
Devo, Devo!
Devo!
Another day and someone listened to me
It's time for us to join in the fight
It's time for the two babies grown to be cowboys
You let the bed bugs bite
You better put all your eggs in one basket
You better catch your tickets before they hatch
You better sell some wine before it's time
You better find yourself an inch too scrunch
You better squeeze all the Charmin you can
While Mr. Whipple's not around
Stick your head in a microwave and get yourself a tan
Talk with your mouth full
Bite the hell that feeds you
Bite of more than you can chew
What can you do?
Dare to be stupid
Take some wooden ankles
Look for Mr. Goodbar
Get a mojo working out
I'll show you how
Dare to be stupid
You can turn the other cheek
You can just give up the shift
You can eat a bunch of sushi
Then forget to leave a tip
Dare to be stupid
Come on and dare to be stupid
It's so easy to do
Dare to be stupid
We're all waiting for you
Let's go!
It's time to make a mountain out of a boy
Is it good? I have a volunteer
There's no more time for crying
Oh, it's still a pill
Now it's time for crying in your fear
Settle down
Raise your family towards our PTA
Buy some kids a bowl of Cheetos and a Chevrolet
You party till you're broke and they drive you away
It's okay
Dare to be stupid
It's like spitting on a fish
It's like walking up a tree
It's like I say you gotta buy one if you wanna get one free
Dare to be stupid
It's so easy to do
We're all waiting for you
Dare to be stupid
Run your candle at both ends
Put the gift horse in the mouth
Bash potatoes can be your friend
You can be a coffee and tea
But you can sit around the house and watch the lemurs and beavers
The future's up to you
So what you gonna do?
Dare to be stupid
What did I say?
Tell me what did I say?
Dare to be stupid
It's alright
You can be stupid all night
Dare to be stupid
Diet tour in the crowd
Wow
Dare to be stupid
Shout it out loud
I can't hear you
Dare to be stupid
Okay, I can hear you now
Let's go
Dare to be stupid
You know, you were talking about the next step in human evolution, or so-called human
evolution.
Oh, that was a little paid cent.
Along the time continuum from our friends in the far ahead.
Well, you know, I came across an idea of my own there, and I wiped it off, and I said,
what about the next step in evolution being that of schizophrenicus rationalis?
How does that start here?
Well, there's a good reason to think that there's not going to be any more evolution,
so whoop it up.
Well, we've got to pretend like there's a future.
I mean, what's the point?
I ain't saying there's no future.
I'm saying there is no more evolution, that is, no more extrasomatic forces that cause
evolution.
So we've hit the ceiling, as it were.
Not necessarily, but we're going to have to take charge of it ourselves now.
Why?
What do you mean?
Well, because your evolution, your natural selection, if you are...
A good Darwinian is a result of what happens to you.
But if you are one of these so-called intelligent beings, you're controlling what happens to you.
That's what the Nazis...
That's your monkey and your evolution.
That's what the Nazis tried to do, wasn't it?
They tried to take matters into their own hands and shape the genetic pool themselves.
Well, that was one slight aspect of it.
If it had turned out that breeding for their so-called Aryans, which, of course, don't
actually exist in genetics...
Yeah.
If that had been for...
If that had been for survival characteristics, then they might have indeed improved the race.
But unfortunately, that was not really their intention.
It was not evolutionary.
It was a type of fuzzy thinking, I guess.
Well, I wouldn't call it fuzzy, but they believed some strange things.
For example, most of your top-flight Nazis believed that giant chunks of ice were flying
through space and were going to hit the Earth and cause the doom of everything.
Really?
Yes.
It was called the...
Well, I forget the German, but it was called the World Ice Theory.
And the top SS men believed in it, even though this was scientifically thought to be absurd.
No one dared complain about it.
So they embraced the...
It was one of the ritual beliefs that was fostered by Heinrich Himmler and his pan-Germanism.
Does that relate to Velikovsky or anything?
It's even more absurd than Velikovsky.
Yeah.
But, of course, your unstable political minds are always susceptible to these cosmic mish-mashes
of nonsense and non-secretaries.
But they like destructionism.
No, they like fundamentalist Christians.
And other misguided souls like to live in a tiny, cozy, neat, orderly universe that they
can comprehend instead of the large, unfathomable, and frightening evolutionary universe that
we actually are forced to inhabit.
Yeah, the rationality just breaks down when you try to apply it to the universe.
It just doesn't work like that.
We're surrounded by things that just don't make sense.
Well, I don't know about that.
I'd rather choose to suppose that...
How do you explain mass murders and earthquakes killing...
That's the fact that we don't make sense.
The universe makes perfect sense.
We're the nonsensical particle in the equation.
And yet, without a position outside the spectrum of logic and truth, how could we observe it at all?
Otherwise, it would be a case of not being able to see the forest for the trees or the flowers for the bees
in this great land of ours, from sea to shining...
And so, once again, fat triumphs over thin, tall triumphs over short.
And big triumphs over little.
In the coming order, everyone will wear special shiny shoes.
And on each shoe will be a portrait of the Fuhrer, J.R. Bob Dobbs.
And so Hal became crazed with radio power.
And soon he had Dobbs' image all over every color.
No one ever wanted me, Sprawl and I.
Even Frank Bent was bent for the will of Uncle Thread.
We were stabbed in the back by the politicians.
It is our destiny.
Don't worry.
I've never been turned, but we've got to go along with him for now.
We will exterminate the inferior orders so that the true, big, Aryan race can subtract the inferior orders upon the face of this planet.
Well, get out, or I'll shoot out the car from underneath.
It is every subjeudicist's duty to exterminate these vermin.
They say we are prejudiced against minorities, but I say we, we, we are the minorities.
And so we witness the self-immolation of an entire religious group.
My soldiers, I salute you.
It's time!
I want you to go out and kill for old subgenius tech!
I want you to give them a prison they won't forget!
Hey!
Hello, you're on the air!
Hello you're on the air!
I'm talking to you from inside, Bob.
I...
Oh, no!
You see I'm trying to give a speech here.
Get this man off the reviewing stand.
There he goes.
The old sidebooster!
Well, you're going to have to hang up.
We were trying to rescue him.
Uh-oh.
Frank Bent is here.
He's been frustrated. He's being carried away now by the security forces.
This is my last territorial demand in Europe.
Yes, Hal has lost his show mind.
Absorbed with power, he struts down...
The greatest of genius, life, will last for a thousand years.
Why, your radio personality so decreed.
Lost in power, he struts down Shattuck Avenue.
People call emergency services.
There's nothing the Berkeley police can do.
Out of my way!
But for you, caller, it's just another pretty night.
Sieg Freud on KPFA.
Unlike you humans, we are so great.
We cut to time, dancing right.
We touch all fire, we go solid, alright.
My cops is out, and we're dancing right.
My cops is out, and we're under the right.
We see you're human, and we're human.
We're dancing right.
Life's not a child's mandatory right.
And your voice from the sky is falling.
These robots that keep us going around and around and around.
These robots that keep us going around.
About no thing that is awkward.
We used our tables, see you right in your day.
A lot of time, dancing right.
My cops is out, and we're all right, right.
What counts is late, don't care.
The Birkin abyco song.
ggi your future Let's make things great.
Why can't it play too hard we're totally in line?
The Only Ghostanteast Chorus everybody watch the second takeaways.
Ah, I miss you so, me too, I miss you so.
We see your future.
The Ice compiler's gone.
The Ele alrededor, you know me.
If your blood's like a sky is falling
Feel the fire to keep us both
On the sky
And your blood's like a sky is falling
Feel the fire to keep us both around
New robots to keep us rolling around
And our vote on the sky is falling
Poppy with the khaki sweatband
Bold goat pot-bellied barnyard
The only he noticed
The old fart was smart
The old gold cloth Madonna
Dancing to the fiddle and saw
He ran down behind the knoll
And slipped on his wooden fish head
The mouth worked and snapped
All the bees back to the bungalow
Mama was flattening lard
With her red enamel rolling pin
When the fish head broke the window
Rubber eye erect and precisely detailed
Mama was flattening lard
Air holes from which breath should come
Is now closely fit
With the chatter of the old fart inside
An assortment of observations took place
Mama licked her lips like a cat
Pecked the ground like a rooster
Pivoted like a duck
Her stockings down caught dust and dough balls
She cracked her mouth, glazed, caught one eyelash
Rubbed her hands on her gorgeous gingham
Her hand grasped sticky dough balls
And her cheeky metal intricate latchwork
Opened to the room
Uh, smell, cold
Mixed with bologna
Rubber bands crumpled
Wax paper bonnets
Fat goose legs and special jellies
Ignited by the warmth of the room
The old fart smelled this
Through his important breather holes
Cleverly he dialed from within
From the outside we observed
That the nose of the wooden mask
Was the nose of the wooden mask
Where the holes had just been a moment ago
Was now smooth, amazingly blended
Camouflaged in with a very intricate
Rainbow trout replica
The old fart inside was now breathing freely
From his perfume bottle atomizer air bulb invention
His excited eyes from within the dark interior
Glazed, watered in appreciation
Of his thoughtful preparation
Oh my lover, that's so heavy
That's the people just waiting
Counter sachs appear
Ohскийcasting
bride
photon
A Short Campos
Time Well錢
Home this
Bad
I don't live in a fairytale world
With kings and queens and unattainable dreams
Where the bad guys lose and the good guys win
And there's always a price they forever receive
I've looked around and I've gotten to know
That life isn't life, a reality show
Cause I'm a realist, baby
And Romeo, he ain't no realist
It takes a logical mind to escape the traps
This is a realist show
Laid out by society and those who take charge
Villains are heralded and heroes can fall
While teens buy identities down at the mall
Will the stories of this generation be written in blood?
Trapped forever in a screen of false information
God, I hope not
But I'm a realist, baby
And Romeo, he ain't no realist
Cause I'm a realist, baby
Let's go
Outmouth heard here
Outmassador
Outmampoo
Outm (#
Outm bathtacht
So sh holy-
Alright, we rope here
Don't give in and a스
So you know it was Prime, Sir
So I'll show my face
I'll show my face
You first I'm next
Outro Music
Why?
Not everybody's always on the right
But not because nobody's down
Here we go
Thank you, I think I messed something up, but we have t-shirts for sale over there. We need to sell at least five more to get home. And I guess that's it. Thanks guys.
Praise Fart Barf. And now, internet listening friends, we're going to let this show go on over an hour again with a song that we can't include on the normal radio copies.
Only the internet version, because it's too naughty to work if bleeped.
Here then, for our non-broadcast listeners only, or mostly, Nervous Energy's incredibly great song, Holy Shit.
。
.
Escape from this everyday hell
Perhaps a position
To make it seem like my life is well
But no religion will suit me
They all seem so damn untrue
They all have a skewed perspective
So what do I do?
Start something brand new
Holy shit
It's holy shit
We'll watch Michael Keaton movies, Mr. Mom
And listen to Rush all day
Don't worry about obscenities
Cause you can say what you wanna say
Fuck
Shit
Holy shit
Ass
Bitch
Cunt
Brendan Fraser
Holy shit
It's holy shit
We'll have lasagna for dinner
We won't judge if you ask for more
Put on a Falco record
Because the world is your dance floor
Holy shit
It's holy shit
You thank god you don't wear 對了
You can Peters, Lekhito, 都 Korea At The New
You may pay to the tentar