Bob, Bob, love you.
Light your prop eyes up and test it back.
Well, welcome to the hour of slack.
Praise Bob, Bob, and Connie's rack.
Yes, welcome to the hour of slack.
All bow before the great metal lord.
Worshippers? This ought to liven up my endless tragic voyage.
We're all here tonight to praise Bob.
He's kind of shown us that Devo works in parallel ways with other pockets of humans on this planet.
Where we thought we were alone, we know there are now other human forms that believe in God.
And we know that Bob is a conscious mutation.
As he knows, Bob is merely an enema for a constipated society.
These people here are here to help a constipated society blow it out their ass.
Have you ever met Bob?
Well, like I said, Bob would appear in my bedroom and chase me around, making me do jumping jacks.
He's got food.
I know what you do.
Cause I do it too.
Intelligence.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Am I as smart as I think?
Probably not.
That's good.
Daily disease cannot feel pain.
He said that just because I make a speech, that's because I have money.
I'm glass..
Well, you were right.
It's the best I have ever heard.
I can see that through words.
held on August 10th in Cleveland.
The third annual one organized by several old subgeniuses and fellow Devo fans.
Reverend Toth Wilder, Reverend Scott Orsi, the good Blinker Boy at AOL.com,
and help from Steve Sinek.
Friends, it's just been great.
Because I love the Devos.
We have a lot in common, the church and the Devos.
We're both owned by Bob.
We were both controlled by Bob completely for quite a long time.
And we both share a philosophy.
We don't always have the same kind of music, but sometimes we do.
We always have the philosophy.
A special philosophy, a little different, depending on which cult you're talking about.
But it is a philosophy for the different.
You know, in pamphlet number one...
What the hell?
There's Herb Alpert here in the background.
Friends, did you know that Herb Alpert was the guy who signed Devo to their very first big-time record deal?
Anyway, friends, the Church of the Subgenius has called itself the Spaz Church of Macho Irony.
And it's a church of macho irony.
And as I enjoyed the various cover bands covering Devo,
and the new and old and rare Devo materials that were dredged up for each of these conventions,
I got to thinking and pondering about the spazfulness of the great spaz bands.
And the ones I was thinking of primarily are ones from the 80s.
Elvis Costello, who I actually used to sort of resemble back in the day.
And Talking Heads.
I never was that into Talking Heads.
But they were a great spaz band, I suppose.
And David Byrne is a deuce-paying subgenius twice over, just as are several members of Devo.
Ah, friends.
But, you know, some people...
And of course, there's spaz bands today.
And we'll be playing a lot of that.
But, you know, some might say that the spaz, the spaziness and spazitude,
of the weirdos shows no dignity.
That it is somehow silly and unmanly.
But, nay, my friends, nay!
I say the ability to spaz is our treasure.
And the inability to spaz is the curse of the blockhead and the pink.
Because think, is not the sexual orgasm coming?
The ultimate?
Spaz attack?
The spaz of sex, friends.
The spaz of letting your own mutant abnormality out.
Do you really care what the others think?
Well, sure you do.
But, why let on?
Friends, as Bob Dobbs said very recently to his young ward, Dr. Onan Canabite,
Bob said,
I'd rather have the right people laughing at me than have the wrong people laughing with me.
Friends, you think about that as you spaz out in this, uh...
Friends, you just wait. You just wait.
You just wait.
Is there anything religion can do to help me?
Find my friend?
Well, we could join together in prayer.
Uh-huh. But is there anything useful we can do?
No.
Oh, man.
Whoa.
We can't just efic spiritedly fight before the Εfos out of the way.
Whose turn is it?
Well, of course, mine.
I'm ready to see what I've got.
Now, while the runner goes to work
You've got both hands
You've got beret in hands
Take me for no man
Okay, relax
And assume the position
Going to dog is a mission
One, two, and three, time to date
Always do what your mama don't say
Run some teeth with the follow way
One, two, and three, time to date
You've got both hands
You've got beret in hands
You've got both right hand
You've got both left hand
While the left hand is left
While the runner goes to work
I said the left hand is in the hole
You've got both hands
You've got beret in hands
We got beret and hat and
Play great ball, no man
Okay, relax
And assume the position
Going to dog is a mission
Watch your head, do you touch the thing
Always do what your mama let's say
Bust the teeth with the ball away
Watch your head, do you touch the thing
Always do what your mama let's say
Bust the teeth with the ball away
Watch your head, do you touch the thing
A lovely, lovely rendition of Devo's Praying Hands
Performed by Occupant
Who has covered a number of Devo songs
Which we'll hear this hour
Just
Just absolutely
Just absolutely amazingly
Occupant
You can learn more about Occupant at
www.mp3.com
Or you could even write to
Dr. Onan Kanabait
Onan at subgenius.com
And now
Through subversive measures
Devo passes on the word of Bob
By uh
By uh we
If you take a look at our last album cover
His name's been airbrushed
Into the rubber hairlines
Of each of the band members
Right next to the word sex
Do Bob and sex go hand in hand?
Well Bob is a kind of total all-consuming sex
We're like explosions
That leave you feeling good
We're like IBM
We play it slow
Up above
Nothing has to stop and go
There's nothing but the up and go
There's nothing like some men and dough
There's nothing more than what you know
Yes
I guess the only slack that I get any more
Is worshiping at the holy temple of the yoni
Tell us about that
What's that?
Uh huh
Don't come to church
I'm sure your audience knows what the holy temple of the yoni is.
Can you tell us?
It's the female delta.
Female delta?
And that's where you are sitting?
It's penis fuck pussy.
Oh.
Pussy surround penis.
Oh, I see.
Mark Mothersbaugh on Bob.
The planet has been suppressed, but now it can be told.
Every man, woman, and mutant on this planet shall know the truth about de-evolution.
P THE Miranda
Pika boo!
Promo
Thank you.
A Bruiser Mix
by
Bruiser
Whoever that is.
It came with the
devotional
special memorial CD.
It came with the
devotional special memorial CD.
but you know
I don't look forward
to going back
to the
thy platypus
Just talk about
the de-evolutionization
of man and stuff man.
The other week I was over at my Aunt May Biel's house.
Me and my cousin Bubba were talking about third world politics and the effect on the micro farm workers of the southern United States.
And all of a sudden it hit me.
Mark Mother's ball was right.
Man was devolving.
And turning back into the most simple of primates.
This would explain daytime TV.
Jerry Springer being so popular.
Why the hell were you not on a fucking record label?
But right when I was about to tell Bubba about this.
He turned on Jerry Springer.
And as I watched that 13 year old.
prostitute straddle the Pope.
I couldn't think anything but.
What a damn fine country we are.
God bless fucking America.
Devolutionization.
By a group called the Cryogenic Strawberries.
An unusual group.
I think they're on mp3.com too.
Or somewhere out there.
Do a little search.
Cryogenic Strawberries.
And now...
Occupant.
Today, what does it take to do the super thing?
I'll tell you what it takes, a very simple thing
Iron nerves, like the pilot of a jumbo jet
Or a girl, on the go who hasn't got there yet
Magnetic trumpets blowing, synthetic saxophones
The evidence kept growing from below
Hidden motivations, buried in the past
Still give us strength for the super thing
The Red Alarm
A rude surprise every time it rings
It means it's time to go beyond the normal thing
Pay attention and be prepared to do it right
The super thing, the thing that makes you bigger than life
Magnetic trumpets blowing, synthetic saxophones
The evidence kept growing from below
Hidden motivations, buried in the past
Still give us strength
Iron nerves, like the pilot of a jumbo jet
Magnetic trumpets blowing, synthetic saxophones
Still give us strength for the super thing
Iron nerves, like the pilot of a jumbo jet
Magnetic trumpets blowing, synthetic saxophones
The evidence kept growing from below
Hidden motivations, buried in the past
Still give us strength for the super thing
The realument of the super thing
Ready starts tomorrow
Here's us, the delinquent
Good luck その地くそ俺たちが
Pleasure pain
Sensations unfamiliar
Can make you sick
It's a superhuman thing
And it does the trick
Magnetic drops are flowing
Synthetic saxophone
The evidence kept growing
From below
In motivation
Buried in the past
Still give us strength
Super, super thing
The super, super thing
That get my bottom
People gonna think you're a spy
Whales by the Elastic Band, a classic song of great spazitude.
And before that, some ESO Swamp Radio from WCSB Cleveland, Chaz Smith and Lonesome Cowboy Dave and yours truly, Reverend Ivan Stang,
talking about the feast of spazism.
Speaking of which, upcoming are some amazing, well, here's an example.
It's not a Devo song, although Little Theodore later on in the show will cover through being cool.
Here's Little Theodore with I Don't Care.
I don't care about the economy. It has no effect on me.
Well, I need to be happy.
There's a woman, a screw, and a place to pee.
I don't care about the government.
I think it's about time it went.
Nasty politicians I resent.
Just like me, they're all hell-bent.
I don't want to hear about big stars.
They should all be behind bars.
Maybe we can ship them off to Mars.
Or take off their clothes and expose them.
I don't want no more of the press.
They're responsible for our mess.
If we knew what was best, we'd live our own lives and skip the rest.
Ha ha ha.
Little Theodore, dear friends, and you can contact Little Theodore at
little Theodore at yahoo.com
or write to 3277 Raleigh Street, Denver, Colorado 80212.
Or on www.grantrproductions.com
slash pages slash fiodor dot html.
Fiodor, by the way, is spelled F-Y-O-D-O-R.
And now, the Hot Foot Quartet.
¶¶
He had a job and he brought home the bacon so that nobody knew.
Mongoloid, Mongoloid.
Mongoloid, he was a Mongoloid, happier than you and me.
Mongoloid, he was a Mongoloid, one from a song too many.
Mongoloid, he was a Mongoloid and his friends were unaware.
Mongoloid, he was a Mongoloid and nobody even cared.
And he wore a hat and he had a job and he brought home the bacon so that nobody knew.
Mongoloid, Mongoloid.
The Hockfoot Quartet, friends, and now Occupant.
Occupant.
Left home with a friend of mine, gone two years and I don't know why.
Now I'm happy all the time, I can't think, I'm feeling fine.
Girl put me in a situation, going through soft computations.
I'm going under
Down under where the lights glow
To a place where all the mutants go
Doing things I'll never get before
Inside I'm coming back for more
Little girl with a boring lips
Never knew it could be like this
You put me in a situation
I'm going through a dark car
You see something down under where the lights glow
To a place where all the mutants go
Doing things I'll never get before
Inside I'm coming back for more
Little girl with a boring lips
Never knew it could be like this
You put me in a situation
I'm going through a dark car
You see something down under where the lights glow
To a place where all the mutants go
Doing things I'll never get before
Inside I'm coming back for more
Little girl with a boring lips
Never knew it could be like this
You put me in a situation
I'm going through a dark car
You see something down under where the lights glow
To a place where all the mutants go
Doing things I'll never get before
Inside I'm coming back for more
Little girl with a boring lips
You see something down under where the lights glow
To a place where all the mutants go
Doing things I'll never get before
Inside I'm coming back for more
Little girl with a boring lips
Never knew it could be like this
You put me in a situation
I'm going through a dark car
Doing things I'll never get before
Little girl with a boring lips
Inside I'm coming back for more
Doing things I'll never get before
Go-Go-Go-Go-Go down
Occupant
at www.mp3.com
slash
Occupant
There's more, more, more
more, more, more, more
such as this song by
well, this came from the
devotional CD
for more information on the devotional
here's their
well, a website that will help you
that's
hometown.aol.com
slash
Blinkerboy
but Blinkerboy isn't spelled with vowels
exactly, it's spelled this way
slash
B-L-N-K-R
B-O-Y
Blinkerboy
and they
on their CD, I found this
piece
by Beall and Elvin
the Sewer Rat
They took us in
we watched our tails
We've only got
a little sense
I said
it's all
just wind and sails
Are we not men?
We are demons
We're pizza
We are the whole
Don't go away
Are we not men?
We are demons
We are even
Are we not men?
From even though
In business suits
Teachers and critics
Are fans of the law
Are we not men?
We are even
I say it's all just wind and sand
Wooden hands all just go on
Pictures and dreams are fits of love
Are we not men?
We are even
But let's leave things of this world behind
And walk now down the path of Bob for this brief minute of slack from the Church of the Subgenius
And we find then the family falling apart
Oh, they wail and gnash their teeth, our rival churches do,
about how the children are getting exposed to too much this and too much that.
What they ain't being exposed to is a little bit of mom and dad.
Forget the pornography, I don't care.
It makes me mad, my friend, the hypocrisy.
Now, I have nothing against hypocrisy.
Every religion must have its fair share of hypocrisy.
As Bob Dobbs once said, I don't practice what I preach
because I'm not the kind of man I'm preaching to.
But that preacher can get up there on TV and oh, he's so glad to keep you normal,
keep you working so hard you don't even know your own wifey anymore.
And your kids, you don't know your kids any better than your employees.
So, friend, let there be slack.
Salutations.
Today I feel a sense of urgency as I speak to you for Devo Incorporated.
There is a direct connection between Devo's work in the music field
and a message from my wife.
There is a big wiggly world around us.
You may not be aware of this, but we are in the middle of World War III.
It is not nuclear bombs that we must fear.
The weapon is the human mind or lack of it on this planet.
That will determine our fate.
Capital punishment for airline passengers who attempt to save money.
Spud men and gas lines who forgot that guns don't argue.
And tourists attempting to catch some rays at Three Mile Island.
Add up to a major attack of corkscrews in the brain.
We must fight back.
We must know what we want.
We must want what we need.
And what we need is duty now for the future.
You may not have eternal peace.
And między Medo-
D27
The 1500th networks,
Wild num-
b
Just stop.
Bye.
We helped with the RU experience video.
And now, more Occupant.
See you next time.
Bye.
Bye, bye.
Bender!
It's a miracle!
Ah!
This is by a wide margin the least likely thing that has ever happened.