again it's been a week for you for for me it's just been well i did i did last week's show and
then i had dinner and now we're back yes well no that's not the right tape deck actually there
here welcome potential initiates and remain with us for the next 30 minutes
welcome to the subgenius radio ministry
the subgenius hour of slack that you are about to listen to is is this one number uh what number
is this now dear friends it's uh
you
480 yes hour of slack number 480 we don't date them because they uh they get played at different
dates in different places especially when they're late like this particular batch you know it's so
but you know we're subgeniuses here we we like to procrastinate we're procrastinationals
my friends and uh we have been known to put things off until they had to be done all at
once at the very last minute and you know we love it that way yes it's a it's a challenge
uh either that or we're just well not very organized but i'm not gonna i'm not gonna take
up your time with that i don't have any uh special new subgenius news uh this time i don't think uh
but because it's gonna be a month later that from now that you'll hear any of this and
that's okay it's okay it's okay it's okay stang take it easy man
we've got lots of tape what have we here tonight we've got uh old father joe mama
ranting at the philadelphia d bible a couple of months ago we've and dr legume probably
we've got uh the cleveland d bible live lonesome cowboy dave and chaz uh einstein secret orchestra
eso radio brain rot theater on stage and we've got reverend suzy the floozy fleeing from religion
uh and we just never know what just a little while ago i went out to run an errand it's sunday
night where i am right now and i thought well gosh i'll turn on that radio station that i used
to produce this show on and see what's on here in dallas in what used to be the hour of slack
time slot and friends it was preachers but it wasn't like a subgenius
preachers because it didn't have zoog's riff music in the background i'd say that's the the most
immediately noticeable thing about it and also that it would they were preaching a doctrine of
hate my friends hate hatred uh and and uh and they weren't kidding except that they they dressed it
in the the guise of love of course love of them and hate of us whereas friends we don't even bother
to see it up like that we ain't trying to dress it up we'll just tell you right out right that's
what this religion is all about it's about hate it empowers us to hate fame them others any of
them others all of them the humans you know those lowly monkey people the humans the silly
ten-fingered things uh and uh just to uh celebrate that aspect of dallas the fact that they
they don't want to hear
reverend stang preaching in dallas no more doesn't empower low and moderate income people
that's right people people yeah people so uh it's sure as hell don't uh but um
we did do a bookstore signing here in dallas at the borders it was a nice crowd nice subgenius
crowd about 150 people and people yeah people but they were uh it was the cross section that
we like to see it wasn't a bunch of people it was a bunch of people that were like
people in black youngsters there was plenty of them uh tattooed with dobbs tattoos on their
bodies and and special black leather jackets that had jim morrison on one side bob dobbs on the other
um and there's little old ladies they're perplexed and confused looking little old ladies but they
were trying they were trying to regain their slack and you know old biker fellers and and
wimpy geeky be spectacled
nerds like me only without the uh well the showbiz hairdo you see and so we may play a little bit of
that but mainly i just wanted this this young feller came up to me and handed me a cd that was
composed of uh uh music shot we can call it music i guess by dallas area bands texas in general but
mostly oh there they are working
in the background chanting and working will you can you guys hold it down over there uh
can you hold it down over there not you will that's okay talking to the guy with the hammer
there uh anyway he gave me this cd it's a texas mostly dallas bands that no radio station around
here is gonna play in a million years so to commemorate our shared dallasness here's a cut
from the subgenius cut that was on there not this in the background what you're hearing in the
background is uh joe newman uh rudy schwartz project but coming up here we've got this this
band called the leper chunks isn't that a cute band name the leper chunks uh and this young
fellow mike wilson wilson handed me this uh cd and this tune coming up here friends is called
bull dada bull dada the latest exploration into the world of advanced surrealistic morealism in
which the mind is filled with dirt and lugs which trickle like mutilated centipedes down the sides
of the now empty cranium to find shelter and rest inside the now sightless eye sockets
this at the same time he was tackled to pay shop people ofなんто who
catching away
yo
Charlie don't search, neither do I
Worship me and Dad
Bring it in the heart
Because they take that
Dad, where's the muncher?
It's a joke
My eyes closed, I see
Bobs of yellow moving around in blackness
Who's a crazy life is able to find
At the sun of the dark
I don't care if it's a merchandise
It's a single wire
I don't care if it's a urinal
I don't care if it's a lettering
There is no logic in this emotion
Don't you hear me yet?
I'm just a single line
And I don't sense
So worship me and son
Worship me and son
Hold on a minute
I'm gonna turn down the volume
You're just a serendipitous
Following the blues
Always running your own course
I'm stating a radio
Standing everyday
Thelear
Pod의
One's theTO\'Deanie
You're fy googoy
In the sky
But never should I
My ears are open
I cannot turn
Let me other way
Oh, dear friends, that was indeed some bulldada from the leper chunks.
Yeah, man, leper chunks rule.
Or something like that.
And we can find that CD, which is called We're From Texas, Volume 2, at P.O. Box 800-88...
Wait a minute.
8-uh-oh.
No, 800-867.
That's Box 800-867, Dallas, Texas, 75380.
Hmm.
What could it mean?
Well, let's not dwell upon things like that.
Let's not even think about it.
Or should we?
I wonder if those paranoid people are after me again.
No, no, no, probably not.
Well, let's go to this lovely devival.
This is Father Joe Mama.
You can't go wrong with Papa Joe.
One of the great all-time subgenius preachers, I think.
If you don't mind.
I'm sorry for my saying so.
This recording is cut off.
We're missing the very beginning of the rant.
My recording is non-existent, but we got this one from the great Bob Payne.
The pain of Bob.
And so...
Yeah.
We're not even aware we're making it.
But hey, you gotta bend a little to get along, right?
You can't always get everything just the way you want it, right?
Right.
Well, allow me to respond to that.
That common misconception with one word.
Corrupt.
You've heard about corrupt.
It means lacking in moral integrity.
To taint, to infect, to spoil.
To change the original form or intent.
In other words, to compromise.
Now, most of us don't like the word corrupt.
It sounds too dirty, too sleazy.
We'd rather think of ourselves as compromising.
That sounds more respectable, doesn't it?
But is there really any difference?
Allow me to tell you a little story about a fine Christian woman.
She was a widow going through some hard times.
She was still beautiful, mind you.
But her husband had jumped to his death after the stock market crash.
We heard her family without very much money.
They had lived very lavishly before.
But now they were struggling.
Her only daughter was sick.
And her mother and parents were getting old and feeble.
Still, she was a very proud woman.
Because she still had her integrity.
Until one day.
Yes, a wealthy old man came and visited her.
He asked the beautiful woman if she would perform sex with him.
Well, she flatly refused.
Angry at the suggestion.
But then he offered to marry her.
Take care of the little girl.
Rest in peace.
Restore the family fortune.
And also assist in the parents ever getting older.
At this point, she knew the old man was a lecher.
But she figured marriage was a fair compromise.
So she agreed.
At this point, the man then offered another compromise.
He said, why not just skip the marriage and have sex for a hundred bucks?
Well, she was furious.
I mean, what did he think she was?
Some kind of hoe?
Why, yes, the man replied.
We've already established that.
Now we're negotiating price.
You see, the man was right.
She was always corrupt.
She was just living in denial.
She wasn't a bad woman.
She had many good qualities.
But she had one fatal flaw.
She was willing to compromise her principles.
Now how many of us are in that same situation?
I don't mean widowed with a sick kid or older parents.
I mean willing to compromise our principles in order to get ahead.
Oh, dear friends, after all the reward is big enough, it's not easy resisting giving in just once.
The problem, of course, is that it never is just once.
It's only the beginning of a long line of compromises.
It's always that first little compromise that's the hardest.
But from there on out, it's downhill all the way.
Even religion is an example.
It's the only way to get exempt from the temptation and powers of corruption.
No!
Have you ever heard of a secret church, friends?
No, no.
Well, a secret church then, allow me to enlighten those of you who are unfamiliar with it,
is a non-denominational church that was built with compromise.
Every principle that might offend or scare newcomers off is compromised away.
There's no loud English.
There's no angry servants.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
There's no insistence on time.
You can keep your money.
Oh, we don't want your money.
Oh, no, no, no.
There's no talk about the horrors of hell.
Just the pleasures of heaven.
In fact, there's no controversy at all.
Just touchy-feely stuff to make you feel good and come back and get an ex of it.
These so-called secret churches, friends, are the fastest growing churches in America today.
Many of them are mega churches.
Churches that hold hundreds, if not thousands, of customers.
I won't call them believers because they don't have anything to believe in.
They've compromised all their beliefs away.
Yes, and the reason is because their church wasn't built on a rock.
No, friends.
It was built on the shifting sands of compromise.
Alas, it's not just the secret churches that are built on these changing foundations.
Religions across the globe are compromising away their most fundamental beliefs.
You know what I'm talking about.
It starts out small.
Some Jew starts eating pork.
And then some Catholic has an abortion.
The next thing you know, the Episcopalians want to marry the homosexuals together.
And then the, what is it, the Hindus start forbidding their wives from throwing themselves on the funeral fires.
I mean, what's the point of even having a religion if you're not going to play by the rules?
The rules!
Do you think God doesn't know when you're cheating on Him?
Do you think He's just going to turn a blind omnipotent eye on your sin?
No sir.
No sir, He knows.
And if you betray Him, then why should He betray you?
Oh, it's your choice, alright.
But stop and consider this.
Who is going to suffer more?
God or you?
You.
We.
We consider.
And that's why we, the church and the subgenius, are dedicated to not compromising.
That's why we, Bob's chosen few, have decided forever, never, to get in and become mainstream.
If you want mainstream, you can just go join any one of those other milquetoast churches that litter the landscape and refuse to pay taxes.
But don't come whining to us with your,
Gee, Bob, can't you tone it down just a little bit, attitude, because we're not interested
in winning the Nielsen ratings.
We don't care if you're disgusted by Jaina launching decapitated hits across the audience
with some bloody nine-iron.
We don't care if you're nauseated by the ear-shattering anti-fascist
ideas, or your little squeaky left heart is all gone.
We don't care.
And we damn sure don't care if you're offended by my hate raps, because in short, we don't
care about you.
We don't care about you.
In fact, we're probably the only church of the so-called me generation, and probably
the only product for that matter, of the me generation, that does not care about you.
Yeah!
Because we care about Bob.
Praise Bob!
And if you don't like it,
then you can just go to hell!
Yeah!
Yes!
Because that's where Bob sins.
Those who compromise his church.
And in the word of Bob, praise Bob!
Praise Bob!
Oh man!
Yeah!
Those who pawn service can hear,
but they're the helping selves.
And when the tax man comes to the door,
the best will help him, so yeah!
It ain't me, it ain't me, I ain't no villainous son.
It ain't me, it ain't me, I ain't no fortunate one.
Yeah!
Some folks can hear it in the stars,
but their eyes, they miss the insightful law.
Res lanes get powdered if I step one step further.
Be want last, be want more, more, more, more.
Yeah, it ain't me, it ain't me, I ain't no villainous son.
Yeah, it ain't me, it ain't me, I ain't no fortunate one.
It ain't me, it ain't me, I am the first son.
I am the first son.
I don't know if they're in Dallas, but yeah, us, us, us, man.
Point one check complete. Radiation normal. No leakage.
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you so much.
I'm glad to know that we're not leaking again.
We had a terrible one last time.
Big nasty leak.
A leak in the mouth, probably, is what you might call it.
But let's...
Man, I'm beat from doing shows all day.
Not this show.
I did the last two.
Two weeks worth of shows today.
It's just the way we have to do things around here.
What's this? Oh, that's background music.
It's Cleve Duncan's background music in the background right now.
But I think we're going to whip over to Sister Susie the Floozy's subgenius show
from WREK in Atlanta.
Praise WREK and the lovely Sister Susie the Floozy.
Who has the very best background music choices in the world, I think.
Oh, welcome, welcome, seekers of slack.
Oh, welcome to Bob's Slack Time Funhouse here on WREK Atlanta.
Oh, I'm the breathless Reverend Susie the Floozy,
and welcome to our 31st show this year.
Oh, I'm your friendly neighborhood flock teaser,
the Reverend Susie the Floozy,
and, oh, I'm still on a highly spiritual roll
from the devastating...
...released at the Big Divival.
Oh, two weeks ago at Dragon Con,
and then the stellar stream of subgenius consciousness radio show
the following night.
Woo!
Being at ground zero for those vortex-stretching rituals
has served to recharge and reaffirm my ministry to you,
dear seekers of slack.
Oh, I've been losing sight of the fact
that this is, after all, a church here.
So let's all hop in the car,
and I'll try to remember where the inseminary is.
The old church had us,
and my dear억ed cousin,
my collar-stone darling,
my rosettita at the time
for yes Patino.
Now, all long Ob Hour!
We had
I like Sundays.
I sure wish Mommy and Daddy did.
You know, I've seen some men walking around today
with their hair so long,
they must think they're women.
Now, we all know our bodies
are the temple of the Lord.
So I ask you, would the Lord Jesus Christ want to live in a long-haired temple?
No, he would want a clean-cut temple.
And the congregation said, Amen.
Therefore, let the true men of God resolve to wear their hair above their ears.
Amen.
And let us all be standing as our featured quartet sings the song of encouragement.
A rich young ruler came one day
To ask about the narrow way
But his hair was long
And he couldn't be saved
No, he couldn't be saved
So the preacher looked at him through tears
And said, Your problem's on your ears
If your hair's too long
There's sin in your own hair
If your hair's on your ears
Get a cup today
And make an is not a happy good start
You'll live a life of fear and dread
There's a tangled mess upon your head
If your hair's too long
There's sin in your own hair
Take the kid out
My friend, my friend
If you would enter there
You'll not go there with your long hair
If your hair's too long
There's sin in your heart
You'll be left behind with those out there
Who wear their hair upon their ears
If your hair's too long
There's sin in your heart
If your hair's on your ears
Get it done today
Make a new start
A happy, glad start
A more meaningful life
With fear and dread
With a tangled nest
And a new life
Upon your head
If your hair's too long
There's sin in your heart
Ah
Man
Thank you, Brother Blowforth,
for another inspired
message.
And now, for this week's
verse of meditation,
the dog returns back
to its own vomit
and the sow is washed only
to wallow in the mire.
We're glad to have each
and every one of you
at our service today,
especially the young folks.
There's going to be
a youth meeting tonight
after the assembly
and all you youth
need to be there.
We're going to serve
macaroni and cheese,
fish sticks,
and banana pudding.
Brother Blowforth
will speak on dating
and mating.
Is it fun or frustrating?
Should be real good.
Don't forget,
what happens on
Tuesday night,
Pew Packers.
That's right,
That's where we go
visit the sick,
afflicted,
and the backslid.
I'm a Pew Packer.
He's a Pew Packer.
She's a Pew Packer.
We're all Pew Packers.
Wouldn't you like
to be a Pew Packer, too?
Now, as you're dismissed,
shake the hand
of your neighbor
before you leave your pew.
Margaret!
Oh, Mary,
hear from the bird.
Whoa, whoa.
This is our cue to run.
This is one of those,
ah, repressive pink churches.
Oh, I've read about them
in the pamphlets,
but it's,
it's even worse
than I thought.
Oh, let's,
let's run down the street here
and see what we can find.
Hey,
I never heard
of the first church
of Bob's Your Dad.
I wonder what kind
of place this is.
Hmm,
let's walk in
and see.
Daddy started out
in San Francisco
tootin' on his trumpet
loud and loud.
He drank out a can Xbox
od un pouco
with a 53 cart
and had a high potassium
kiloblast guy
at the hospital
where he had a
headspace
© BF-WATCH TV 2021
Distant Galaxy Space Age Bachelor Pad music.
By the way, you know that term Space Age Bachelor Pad?
For this sort of thing that you hear in the background.
That was coined by an early subgenius apostle,
one of the original 13 apostles,
a Saint Byron Werner.
A Werner.
Yes, Saint Byron Werner.
Remember that name?
He's the god of Space Age Bachelor Pad music, really.
And Pope Irwin Chusett up there at WFMU in New Jersey
also is one of those self-same popes.
But for now, you know, I don't know where we're going with this show.
It's just lost its center or something.
And since it has, we might as well.
Well, why not?
We'll go to that Cleveland revival with that strange live presentation
of ESO radio on stage.
And interrupted by yours truly quite frequently, I'm afraid.
This is, well, I believe the intros are right up here at the front, friend.
We like them that way.
Oh, we're doctors.
Hey, Chaz, everybody always wanted,
well, they hear you guys on the radio all the time,
and they always want to know what you look like.
And Chaz Smith is over here playing violin.
Let's have a big hand for Chaz and his new look.
Yeah!
And this is the keyboard player.
His wife, Morgana.
Todd Bassoon.
And his trained baboon.
And Dave Guitaro.
Oh.
But we're not in the room.
It's the normal conspiracy, Ivan.
It's the corrupting, eating worms, Dave.
They're behind it.
But some of them are kind of cute.
The fuzzy ones.
Yeah, I like them fuzzy normals.
Oh, I like them in a pair of socks.
They almost pass for an abnormal, you know.
Hey, look, I mean,
wait a minute, I thought I was coming to like a church revival.
It was going to be preaching or something, right?
Yeah.
They were going to be doing some, some, but then I went to this thing and well, hell,
they had this underwear tacked on top of the walls.
And there were these people with, with these chains around their neck that were getting
signals from the radio broadcast out of the plate and lonesome cowboy Dave's head.
And they just appeared to be saying that they had a script that they were reading that floated
in the air in front of their faces that nobody else could see.
And they kept talking about this Bob thing, but it was just, it seemed like a rip off.
I mean, the.
I think for America, I never.
Pray for America to end tonight.
Hey, it's like.
Sit down and.
Bring your feet.
Stay your feet.
It's Dave the boo.
Pray.
Pray for America to end.
Pray, dear friends.
The lot would have.
I would have known to be.
So.
Remember, nothing more than.
The psychic.
Implants of fundamentalist Christian counselors.
A lot of the great majority of these people are under psychiatric counseling and the counselors
are very often fundamentalist Christians who reinforce their belief in possession.
Are you hurting today?
Is there a need in your life?
I need helpful people to Prosper.
Disgraceful assault.
I need people to look from the perspective of, you know.
I need people to look from the perspective of kindness, forgiveness, detachment, momento and
Peterоче will just be giving out the Bible that went to God began to she real.
You understand?
That's just the law.
Its already validity say no, you've seen it.
Just follow the code.
That because we don't revolve.
Speaker 7 Yeah.
I don't deserve this phone abuse, so please stay a while.
I work in the graveyard.
Work in the graveyard.
I work until the dawn of day.
I work for the CIA.
I work in the graveyard.
I work until the dawn of day.
I work.
Hey, Barbariba,
Hey, Barbariba Yes, my baby
My superpower
Will be your graveyard.
Hey baby, you better go.
Look in the graveyard.
Yes, my baby.
Now mama's on the bottom and papa's on the top.
Baby's in the crane, she sure has poured it to her pop.
Hey baby, you better go.
Now these women, we are in it.
We are the space of the moon and the space of the sky.
Oh my lord.
We are the space of the moon and the sky.
It was grace that taught my heart to...
Oh yes, that's a proper churchly setting for us, isn't it, seekers?
Oh, and looking out across my radio pulpit here,
I can see by that constipated look in your eyes that you're truly getting the spirit.
We are a scattered flock, to say the least,
but someone even more badly in need of guidance is coming to our realm,
a poor shepherd who has been out of flock fleecing circulation for quite a while.
I'd like to take this opportunity to invite our dear brother, Jim Baker,
to explain to you what it's like to be a shepherd.
I'd like to accept my warm invitation to come nestle in the bosom of our subgenius church here.
Oh, I talked it over with my funhouse co-pilot, the Reverend Microphone,
and he's all for it, too.
Brother Baker, we like the cut of your jib.
All that drinking and whoring and stealing was a perfect training for our faith,
even if you didn't take it far enough for my taste.
And your expertise in financial wheedling is just what we need to finance our subgenius,
and I'm sure you'll be able to do that.
I'm sure you'll be able to do that.
But wait, that's not all.
Oh, not only are we throwing in this nifty, inflatable Jessica Hahn love doll,
we offer up our own warbling little goddess, Ms. Marvel,
as your all-new improved Tammy Faye.
Oh, and we've got one of your air-conditioned dog houses
out in back of the station here for your honeymoon cottage.
So give us a call, Jimbo, and get in tight with Bob.
After all, this is a good time to get some air.
The church is where the action is.
Amazing grace
How sweet the sound
That a man so rich like me
Some fellas listen to the tenors
Other fellas listen to the bass
I always listen for the star notes
And amazing grace
Amazing grace
Believe me
Oh, and it certainly paid off big for you, didn't it?
Another reason to complain
Oh, yes.
Oh, beloved Ms. Marvel.
But right now, seekers,
we're going to try a little experiment here.
We've got a genuine exorcist here today,
a specialist in casting out what he calls the Jezebel spirit.
And, hey, it's not like there's a shortage of materials
to work with.
Here with me,
because I got a metric ton of Jezebel spirit
in a one-pound bag just busting to get out.
You about ready, Earl?
Hook up the exorcismotron.
Do you have a voice?
Yes, I hear voices all the time.
You do? Do you offer that?
Oh, honey, I'm reaped.
Possessed and possessed again and again.
You ought to believe I'm born again.
Honey, I was born right a Yeti the first time.
Okay, are you ready to deliver?
I'm ready.
Deliver me, baby.
Put your head under there.
If you can.
This is your lucky round.
Come on.
You have a Jezebel spirit within you.
Yeah, yeah, come on.
I got a Jezebel spirit.
Here it is.
You're the expert.
I ought to be tingling or something by now.
What's the deal here?
You have a spirit of destruction.
Yeah, it's a spirit of destruction.
Come on.
Come on, if you're any good.
Ha, ha, ha.
Ah.
At this point, I think we'd just better give up.
This obviously isn't working.
If this guy had any inside straight at all,
I'd be a smoldering pile of ruins.
Well, it helps me see which side my fate is in.
I guess my head is in the way,
so I better stop it.
I have to be there by the time I strike one.
Oh, if it's someone I know,
I'll Independently smoke them.
One more time.
Number of years my stay.
And the Russian government
olsun.
Stop it.
be no need for us to destroy the world
in 1998.
Oh, but the odds of that ever happening
are beyond being merely astronomical.
These fundamentalists
never learn, do they?
Boy,
fundamental
is right. You take out
the fun,
then you take out the mental,
and all you're
left with is the duh.
The carrot,
they dangle in front of you
as the promise of inheriting the kingdom of God.
Well, I'm not sticking around
waiting for that old fart to die.
I'm blazing my own spiritual
path, and it leads into the rumpus
room of eternal slack with Bob.
Oh, but
what about Satan, you might say?
Oh, Satan's just a
middle management schmo. He's nothing
but a short-sleeved shirt clip-on
Ty Hardy's assistant manager
when you get down to it.
Oh,
and Jesus,
on 285 yesterday,
I saw painted on an overpass
pillar a message.
Benny Poole hates Jesus
for no reason.
Hey, hey, Earl, what's this fade-out?
Come on, come on, punch it up. Hey,
come on, I still got a lot of Jezebel spirit
to exercise here. Come on
before I kick ya.
Okay.
Well, yeah, the message said
Benny Poole
hates Jesus for no
reason.
Well, hey, I can guess the reason
this poor young man feels disenfranchised
from the faith forced on him.
It's because their Jesus just ain't
two-fisted enough for this hopped-up,
attention-deficit Arnold Schwarzenegger
generation.
Oh, the Jesus they give him is a
turn-the-other-cheek crybaby who wants
to take the blame.
He wants to make your sins
his, and then die for them,
to cleanse you of them, to take your sins
and your slack away.
Bob, on the other hand, is here to justify
your sins. He recognizes your sins
as your own unique spiritual baggage,
and he don't mess
with them. Your sins
are yours and yours alone.
They are your own business,
and Bob respects that.
He's not gonna take your sins away.
No, far from it.
Bob's gonna help you get more
sins.
Now, what could be better than that?
Oh, so I
suggest you just assume the
position seekers.
...
Yes, we have praying hands, dear friends.
And we have self-addressed envelope for dressing hands.
And I'd like you to use your hands to take down the sacred post office box number of the Church of the Subgenius.
Yes.
You just write that little postcard or self-addressed envelope to Bob.
That's right, Bob.
At post office box 140306.
That's box 140306.
Dallas.
The Texas 75214.
Yes.
Go ahead.
What's the matter?
Are you afraid?
Go ahead.
Write for that free information from the church at P.O. Box 140306.
Dallas, Texas 75214.
Or you can try our brand new e-mail address at i.stang at metronet.com.
i.stang at metronet.com.
With those little periods right where we said to put them.
Hey, hey.
Well, let's go back and see what's happening with Lone Star.
Awesome.
Cowboy and Chaz and Michelle and Baboon.
There's these creatures that live inside certain microphones.
They don't like the church.
We are subgenius, boys and girls.
We cannot figure everything out.
You know this, Lone?
Now, this damn long tube has been creeping closer and closer to me all evening.
Yours will be able to do that someday.
I wish mine could.
Good night.
talk about Jesus
Jingle bells, jingle all ye sirs
Hey, talk about Jesus.
Thank you.
By Jesus.
No.
And now,
strangely enough,
a song.
By Dr. Legume,
Kid Ginzu,
and
Itch.
This recording reminds me of the old,
the old time subgenius bands.
It's like Doctors for Wotan or something.
It really does sound just like old,
old Doctors.
But it's kind of young Doctors.
Kind of young,
kind of wow, kind of now Doctors.
If they don't start singing pretty quick,
I'm going to just clip it.
I'm getting
You can'tNY
John
That's very
You're doing
We're getting
or
This train is bound for downtown, this train
This train is bound for downtown
Gonna run deep in this town
This train is bound for downtown, this train
Why do you think they call it subgenius, my friends?
This train, this train
This train don't carry no executives, this train
Got no ad fund executives, this train
This train don't cost no gold, no change
This train
This has got to be one of the all-time great
All-time great guitar solos there
This train don't go to Planet X, this train
This train don't go to Planet X
Cause they're just a couple of hands that will crack
This train don't go to Planet X, this train
Man, what a soulful rendition
Ah, friends