What is it?
What's the matter?
I just had a terrible dream.
What?
It was blood and fire and thunder
and something awful was moving in the middle of it.
I could hear it roar and bellow.
The Self Genius Hour of Sight.
If I were to allow that to continue,
he would blow every circuit in his body.
That is correct, sir.
The birds!
He rises!
Who's there?
He's there.
It turned out the story about the raccoon wasn't true either.
However, some things that were more,
much more horrible than raccoon.
Well, just today, on the way down here,
we saw a deer fleeing with unnatural celerity,
an unusual amount of terror.
I've never seen an animal run with such terror.
Right across the road.
And I've seen a lot of deer running.
Full grown doe.
Yeah.
Well, clearly there was some reason to be running
from that dark part of the woods.
Friends, I'm afraid we must start this hour of slack out
on a rather somber note.
Then we'll get back to the fun and the giggles and laughs
and gags and so forth.
But right now, this is a moment for reflection
and consideration.
Uh...
To begin with,
not that anybody is going to miss him.
And we can go ahead and say this now.
The body, or rather the remains,
oddly, there was no body,
but there was a wrist bracelet.
There was no body because there was no murder.
And if it was done by an animal, it's not a murder.
And we're closing in on the culprit.
But anyway, we've ID'd the male.
And that was indeed the guy known as Reverend Bastion.
I forget his real name.
Mike Aston or something like that.
As I said, nobody's going to miss him,
but we still don't know who the female was with him
or if there was a child.
There was another thing found a little bit further into the woods,
which was bloody burst condoms.
Burst, I tell you.
Do you understand what I'm telling you?
What I'm trying to say?
Yes.
All this while I'm waiting,
waiting in the water,
trying to do the baptism.
Yes, all this happened.
Well, I'm sorry about that,
but we could have called the cops.
No, we can't have police here.
I think everyone is a realist enough to know
that this is no place for the police.
As my former show partner, Chicken John, once said,
if you have an emergency, a crisis, something wrong,
and you call the cops,
now you've got something wrong and cops.
Well, so we're trying to avoid that.
We're trying to avoid that sort of thing,
but I got the results back from the university
on the various claws, shells, bits of flesh, and so forth.
Expensive.
It's really confusing.
The detached beak we found was, in fact, from a prairie squid,
not an arboreal squid,
so it probably had been used for sex,
but we weren't able to scrape any human DNA,
off of the beak.
Of course, you wouldn't if the squid was de-beaked properly,
which indicates maybe not an animal culprit.
On the other hand, we also found,
and this pains me to have to tell you this,
but a face-fucking bat with its wings torn off,
possibly so that it couldn't fly away.
Did you bring that to show the people here?
No.
The university didn't send that back, but they did.
I've been using my trusty microscope here
to make some examinations myself,
and also in the woods near the scene of the crime or accident or whatever,
you don't want to get too close,
and this is sealed up in a medical bag,
but this horrible kind of bloody-looking encrusted filth and dirt encrusted thing.
I know what that is.
You know what?
Yeah.
Yes.
Go ahead and explain.
What this is is what is called a tampion.
It's a kind of a plug which a bear puts in its anus during hibernation
to keep ants from getting in.
Somebody needs to get a photograph of this.
Does anyone here have a camera?
You can post it on...
A small camera or a phone that would get a picture of this.
I guess we could put it by the microscope to show its scientific...
And by the Geiger counter to show its strange level of...
Radioactivity.
Try to get the Geiger counter.
Ivan Stang, martyr to science.
There we go.
Okay, thank you.
Thank you.
Now you guys are the official photographers of X-Day, and I can quit.
We are exploring a little-known realm of strangeness here.
So tonight, friends, I would be very careful going out into the woods.
I know that's one thing.
One thing I don't have to worry about.
Subgeniuses entering the forest or even leaving their chairs or cars.
Did you have something to add?
Sistar has something to read into the record at this time.
I had an experience this morning in the big house.
An experience?
Which reminded me of a movie.
I don't know if you've ever seen The Conversation.
I have seen it.
Francis Ford Coppola movie.
Well, when I did my...
I did my duty unto Bob, and I was about to cast its remains to the earth, I thought for a moment that I'd seen blood.
And it occurred to me that perhaps someone had buried parts of the body.
But how did they get the body out of the clothes?
Well, I guess you could take the body out of the clothes and then put the clothes back together.
I don't know.
See, that points to someone like Philo or Legume.
It does.
That's the prankster.
Because that's the kind of thing a criminal mind would think of.
But, you know, I was put to mind in the conversation there.
And then when I looked again, it was perfectly clean.
Well, that sounds like what happens at your condo all the time with the ghost and the absent-minded old man in there.
They probably came on my skin.
Well, I don't want to go there.
Well, the ghosts do.
Maybe.
Oh, the other thing was we found a bunch of golf clubs all bent up.
If anybody needs a set of broken and bent golf clubs, there was a big mess of those found in the woods.
Twisted by some unimaginable force.
The monster, the murderer, whatever it is.
The irate golfer, whatever it is.
They didn't just kill the victims.
The bloody condoms.
And the...
And, of course, the tampion.
This is a huge tampion, which indicates the presence of rape bears, which were thought to have been wiped out since the unfortunate accidents last year at the campground.
For the last seven years, actually, I'm afraid to say.
And it may be that the seven-year cycle of the rape bear has started again.
And you don't want to be the subgenius that gets pulled into the rape bear's den for hibernation.
I remember those.
I don't even want to think about how he keeps the victim alive.
Those illustrations that Pantiara drew I've seen online.
Anyway, no, we hope everyone has a fine X-Day.
Yeah, yeah.
Don't let any of these horrible...
Magic, mystery, merriment, and mirth.
Frightening things bring you down or anything.
That's right.
You know, if you decide to, quote, drop, as the kids say.
Yes, don't let the unimaginable horror...
Or crimp the edges of the party.
No, no.
No.
And if you feel like you're starting to have a bad trip, go talk to Andrew the Impaled.
He has a surefire cure for that.
Seriously.
He does, does he?
Well, that's interesting news also.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, he's got a great treatment for bad trips.
What is the first phrase?
It's something like...
The first law of immorality.
Impalement.
Dude, you better calm down, because it's going to be like this forever.
Something like that.
Really, the least handy phrases you want to hear when you're having a horrible, bad, ego-shaking acid trip.
Some of us, life itself is like that.
Yeah.
It's like...
You know what happened?
Hausner, your show started now.
It did start.
See, that's it right there.
Jeez.
What do we do now?
It's starting.
No, it's already started.
It's actually here now.
Oh, this one's really going to...
Oh, the show is here.
This one's going to be a firecracker.
This one's going to be a huge explosion.
This one's going to be...
This one's going to take the seat of your pants and just blow them right off.
This one's really going to take the cake.
I mean...
Don't sit on it.
Well, no.
You have to realize this one's really going to...
No, it's onions.
This one's going to have its way with you.
Well, me?
Oh, uh...
So, Dr. Howell has triumphantly returned to the show.
I would love to listen to all the apocryphal stories of what happened.
What happened to Old Sequa?
Did Sequa live, or did you guys cook him down?
Old Sequa was not harmed remotely.
That's ridiculous.
But what did happen...
That's the most important thing, that everyone, regardless of whether the exes came or not,
they had to know what happened to Sequa.
Well, there was some talk that some monstrous monster had killed him, you know, but this was all BS.
However, there was a monster...
As opposed to your lovable little funny kind of fuzzy monster, right?
There was a monstrous monster, and it did stalk the woods, and it turned a little dog named Snuckles into a horrible...
pile of protoplasm and goo, and then, allegedly, it killed this nasty subgenius whose pants and roundabout were found,
and Stang handled this investigation.
I was there in an advisory capacity, and he made videos.
Some might say too many videos of the sorry...
You can...
Well, you know my tribe.
You can never have too much.
The problem is going through the too much once you've...
Well, um...
And then the whole story is being told on special Stang radio, and I might have blown the whole thing,
but no, I didn't, because I didn't say what that monster turned out to be.
Ah, well, that's very...
That was very nice of you not to reveal the...
Who that monster turned out to be.
I agree.
Ah!
It's church.
They're stored behind the doorway.
Who's that?
It's A.D.
Oh, yeah.
Anyway, after we blither-blather here for a while with the entertaining hour of Slack show,
we'll do Ask Dr. Hal, and then from 5 to 6, the end of the Bulldada auction,
from 7 to 8, the Bobby Awards, and you won't want to miss that,
because there's more awards than there are subgenius.
Yes, the coveted Bobby Awards.
And finally at 8, the costume ball, which I'm really excited about.
And tonight, the Mutant Mountain Boys, Andrew the Impaled,
and the Burning.
The Burning.
By Stephen King, America's most popular author.
One thing we know, this thing fears fire.
Yes, most creatures fear fire.
During the... when night falls.
And the burning.
Ha, ha, ha.
Stangor here.
Now you hear how Stangor tricked little weak glasses man Stang
into hunting monster in woods.
Stangor even tricked him into tricking all other soft, fat, white subgenius boys and girls
into hunting monster in woods, too.
Wearing silly fake hunter armor.
Ha, ha.
Stangor played your world and world of Bob Pipe Man like gay.
Like silly gay.
Ha, ha, ha.
Tinky.
Hi.
This was just turned in, Reverend Stang.
It's a gift from...
Let's see, the woods are full of Amish ripe bear.
And the Temple of Mass Consumption has proof.
Found in a local cemetery about an hour ago.
And is it in this bag?
Apparently.
So, I just...
I've learned not to just reach into it.
Reach into some bag that came from a cemetery.
Right.
Yeah.
I've, uh...
But what...
At each day, you don't just grab anything.
What appears to be...
Oh my God.
Well, a...
A fossilized or petrified, uh...
What is it?
It looks like a...
Did it come with a note?
Uh...
Oh my God.
The cellular structure.
I've never seen anything like it.
The cellular...
The cell walls seem to have forked tails.
Each individual...
Each individual cell.
Look at this, Professor Mandy.
They...
They're wiggling little forked tails of each...
And yet the...
They're so motile.
And yet they're...
They...
They have features of both plant cells and animal cells.
Like...
I can't...
Like that primitive organism...
This is new to science.
The Euglena.
It is from McDonald's.
Well, the bag is from McDonald's.
It smells like that stuff Bob smoked.
Hmm.
Could he have been smoking?
This sausage like thing?
But it's unsmoked.
Uh...
This...
Corn dog of the gods.
Recently found.
It's...
It's like an anal probe or something.
Or could be.
Well, some people have stuff like that on their minds all the time.
And this was found in a cemetery.
And what were you doing lurking around a cemetery in the middle of the night?
Uh...
Where ghouls leave anal probes lying around.
Temple mass conception.
Mm-hmm.
No one is beyond suspicion.
But...
But thank you for your submission.
Have you ever seen the movie The Thing?
Well, it's like that.
The Thing.
Oh yeah.
Just, uh...
You have a great work ethic.
You know, I've always appreciated...
We'll do the job.
When you attend yourself to a problem, be it, you know, painting or drawing or memorizing a thing or answering a question, you...
You just...
You know, you don't...
You don't stop before it's done.
Or eating a hamburger.
You're getting that right.
Or if I'm demonstrating...
You're gonna answer a question, you gotta answer the hell out of that.
Oh, my God.
You're not eating that specimen.
Oh, no, I see...
No, no, this isn't gonna happen.
He's not eating the dildo.
Oh, my God.
Wait a minute.
He's eating the dildo.
No.
It's like that scene in, uh...
What was it?
Pulled Porky?
Actually, it's pretty good.
Disgustipating.
Well, I'm gonna...
I'm not just gonna eat this dildo found in a graveyard.
I'm gonna eat the hell out of it, baby.
Get out of this dildo found in a graveyard.
All right, all right.
Uh, I guess...
How many dildos does it take to...
What can I say?
... find your way through the graveyard on a...
... hungry, hungry night?
You know, there was an...
... an interesting, um, medieval monograph published, uh, as I remember, called, um,
uh, De...
De mortuis...
De mortuis?
... masticatorum in tumulus.
That is to say, of the chewing of the dead in their graves.
Wow.
It is reported in, uh...
Like a ghoul gate.
Well, uh, Timorous...
To break it all down, Timorous Soul...
... the devils passing by a graveyard have been disturbed by hearing, coming faintly
from underground, the munching and chewing of the dead in their graves.
Uh...
And indeed, when several of these were opened by the magistrate, they found that the debtors
inside had et their linen.
They'd eaten their lemons?
Linen.
Oh, their linen.
You wrap a corpse, or you used to, up in linen, and you bind the jaw so it doesn't drop alarmingly
on its breast.
Like the ghost of Jacob Marley.
Ahhhh.
You put two coins on the eyes and a penny under the tongue to pay the ferry, the, uh,
the ferry boatman, um, Charon, and, uh...
I missed the boat, but I caught the ferry.
And then you, uh, well, as...
Then you chew the linens.
Well, if they're dead, how do they chew them, or were they not dead?
Exactly.
They may be dead, but they're still a-chewin'.
That means they weren't dead.
Uh, that's my point, uh, to people who want to chew and consume mysterious things.
I mean, there's objects found in graveyards, um, well, uh...
Isn't that why some graves have little bells?
Sloppy seconds.
The bell is so if they wake up and find that they accidentally got buried but are still
alive, they can ring the little bell and supposedly, technically, someone will come and dig them
up and let them out.
But with today's scientific methods of hygienic embalming, no one comes back.
Even if you were in a cataleptic state that mimicked death by the time you were born,
by the time the mortician finishes, uh, with you, there's a guarantee, unlike in previous
ages, that you will be gone.
And not able to experience the indignity of waking up entombed.
But perhaps your life itself was an example of, uh, being confined and entombed when you
only wished to be free, to live instead of, uh, a living death.
Friend, are you entombed in your 24-7 brain?
Three weeks ago I enjoyed a 9 year long detailed meeting with my little brother,
It was traditional, fine data entry job for Facebook.
Sorry.
Bury him with a cell phone, but how long can the battery last?
Anyway, they don't need it because the, uh, uh, mortician has been there with his trocar
and his, uh, procedure.
Trocar, don't bother me!
Trocar....
Trocar...
Because they stick a butt plug in the ear of our Lord to keep embarrassing sounds from coming out.
Hot.
Yeah, Reverend Sifu was passing out butt plugs for corpses as gifts one X day.
No.
Yeah, because he works as an undertaker.
And he had had a very busy year as a New York City mortician.
In a New York state of mind.
Right after September 11, 2001.
Oh, gracious.
His job was to put remains into shoe boxes.
They were 9-11 butt plugs?
They were 9-11-ated.
Well, they didn't need them for most of them.
They would fit into a shoe box.
Oh, gracious.
That's about how much space human remains take up when there's no water at all.
Right, it's quite portable.
Squished out.
But my point is,
if you wake up in the morning,
if you wake up dead,
you won't be able to fart because of that plastic plug.
And they're a one-size-fits-all, by the way.
They've graduated rings.
Actually, dead people fart all the time.
That's why they have to use the plug.
Because, you know, you go to an open casket situation,
and there's poor old Aunt May laying there.
Just farting away.
Suddenly,
the most horrible smell fills the whole church.
Yes, dead farts are worse than the farts of living.
And the most horrible smell is the farts of living.
Yeah, Dr. Dark suggests we seek a police whistle up there.
You know, after the indignity has already occurred,
if you've simply added an audio dimension to an unfortunate experience,
it's already distinguished by a hideous, moist sound effect.
Fart.
Reverend Angry Larry,
you've been involved with the investigation into the mysterious happenstances around the
campground lately, haven't you?
Let's let him have this mic for a minute.
I wondered if you, did you see the tampion of a right bear?
They apparently have, their seven-year cycle has started anew.
And that's a feral.
It's a fresh, you can see by it's kind of bloody.
We've all watched that now.
A fresh tampion from a right bear.
A tampion would be bloody.
But not a tampon.
This is different.
This is what the bear makes and inserts into his rectum to, during hibernation to keep
the ants out.
Rectum in propter sese.
Yeah.
And this is not, obviously not a black bear.
Actually, that's interesting because the word rectum or rectus were not used in the
Latin.
Yeah.
But when you think about modern day?
Rectum means the rat.
Rectum Gadish.
And you must use them for something.
These Mahi Huang beck estas cutthroat oriented beds.
Yeah.
And that's from 1688 is которое that by now, up until 3000, back in the history of mankind.
Which is, adventures in space緩 Till, theyそして, Mein Land.
But those times, these the kind of black bears, as probable forethought, poor off rackets
Cuz this mind这小!
What a in the mythos anthing of subsistence.
So I don't swear to it, and water.
What is going on here?
So like nonhanded
a sie-
I just wondered if you had any, had observed any other strange phenomena or heard.
No, not just yet.
But I'm on it.
Okay.
I'm on it.
We've got our eyes open.
You look a little sleepy.
You don't look like you're on it.
The reason I ask, you look like you're about half asleep.
Well, you should have been out with us.
We've got a Geiger counter here.
Turn it on.
Did you try it on that?
Good God.
It's him.
Of course it's me.
Sorry, he's radioactive anyway.
Yes, of course it is.
Look at that.
It pegged.
As soon as I turned it on, it pegged.
Are you sure you have that adjusted right?
I'm turning it over here at you.
Look at that.
It goes down to nothing.
Don't point that thing at me, Daddy.
No, it doesn't shoot rays.
It senses rays.
It's a sensory instrument.
Oh, my goodness.
Is it properly calibrated?
You've spent a lot of, huh?
How should I know?
Properly calibrated, of course.
Are you kidding?
It's been appropriately calibrated by calibrationists.
You know?
Equipment.
You've spent a little bit too long around.
There's aliens.
There's amino acids.
Somebody has to.
There must be a Bureau of Standards.
Yes.
So what happened to the amino acids?
Their ship broke down.
They suffered vehicular attrition.
Yes.
Okay, this is turned to zero.
Thank you.
If I turn it to times 100, let's see how much residual radioactivity is in this room.
Go to sleep.
Nothing.
It's clean.
There's no radiation in here.
So maybe.
Maybe it's not functioning.
Turned a circuit check.
Oh, yeah.
It works fine.
Look at the fiddling with that Geiger counter.
The new toy of the subgeniuses.
I don't know what it read when you pointed it at me, but I mean.
It was pegged.
It pegged.
It went all the way.
Yes, it does.
Now that Doc Howell is touching it, it is.
At X1, we get a radiation which is off the dial.
Oh, that's my own personal journal.
That wouldn't be radioactive.
Let me just move it over.
You holding on to it is.
Well, this says everything's radioactive.
Well, assuming this thing, this monster, whatever that's right in the campground is the usual kind of monster.
We're guessing it might be radioactive.
Hey, wait a minute.
And therefore, we can track it, hopefully.
But yet, I'm very radioactive.
So am I under suspicion?
You are.
Everyone here is under suspicion.
Right, but I'm part of the investigation.
Right.
And I'm not the butler.
Well, this is the church.
I did not do it.
Well, this is the church of the subgenius.
Well, I mean, I was the one to discover the body or the remains, whatever you call it.
We'll use it in time.
We'll not auction this Geiger counter at the Bulldada auction.
We now cut ahead to the subgenius costume ball in progress at the main stage at the edge of the woods.
The costume theme happened by coincidence to be Warriors for Bob.
So many attendees were wearing faux armor, squirt guns, and Nerf weapons.
Well, I just hope something doesn't happen to ruin the fun.
We've had so many weird incidents.
You guys getting your car raped with you in it.
That poor dog.
Weird noises in the woods.
That dog.
Snuggles.
That bastard, revered bastard.
Just, you know, even he didn't deserve that.
Nothing.
I mean, everybody's having so much fun.
I just hope that we don't have a repeat of one of those unpleasantries.
Wisteria is still denying knowledge of anything, right?
Yeah, Wisteria says it's, you know, they said all of it's lies and rumors and subgenius silly stuff.
But they look scared.
They look real scared.
They know something's going on.
They know there's something going on.
They just don't want it getting out.
You know, the town's folks would blame them.
Maybe for whatever.
Well, it could discourage people from coming to the festival next week.
Yeah, that's true.
But our fuckers would be like...
Those superstitious pagans will be...
They don't like monsters, man.
They don't like monsters.
They don't even like toy devils.
They get easily bummed out.
And, you know, if they find out that all this horrible stuff is associated with the subgeniuses,
I think what it would do to our reputation.
I don't.
No.
Our reputation's always been so great among all of the pagans.
They really get our sense of humor.
They love it when the bobs come.
Yeah, right.
Oh, I know they love when the bobs come.
They're so respectful, too.
Tolerant.
Well, they all have open minds.
They know what it's like to be persecuted, all right.
Yeah.
I don't want to unnecessarily scare people, you know, right in the middle of this rock and roll party.
Oh, man.
You know, there have been some more noises and screams and bloody, scraped-up trees.
There have.
Yeah.
You heard about the tampion.
Yes.
It was from no black bear.
That was not...
It was a seven-year tampion.
You know what that means.
I do.
Those kind of bears.
Very aggressive.
Mm.
Well...
This infernal noise could wake the dead or old sequoia, for that matter,
if you think about it.
And its offspring.
Now that that ring has been taken away out of its domain.
Did you hear about that?
I did not.
Baby bear got in the pond the first day here.
And what initially looked like a large, fat, hippie silver ring slid onto her foot.
She picked it up with her toe.
And it had hieroglyphs, engravings on it.
It looked new at first, but...
That's when that...
That brown stuff started forming on everyone's skin, right?
Right.
Not everyone.
It performed on...
I didn't get any of it.
But then I never see the UFOs when everybody else...
Something in the jeans.
Later tonight we will set Bob on fire for screwing us over again.
This mask makes it hard for me to talk.
Oh, there.
That's much better.
Well, friends, you're going to love the Mutant Mountain Boys if you haven't seen them before.
They're the greatest thing this side of heaven.
And they'll help us swash the butt hurt that we got from, well, you know, the usual.
I hate saying that.
My phone is doing something.
I was trying to get it to work.
I was trying to...
I was just mentioning to Potter and Petal that I really hope that the festivities and
fun here wouldn't be disrupted like so many other events have at X-Day this week.
What with the little dog and the mangled and the, you know, that guy and the other animals.
And, well, I just hope everybody can keep their heads together.
Don't be worried.
Don't be scared.
That's the important thing.
Wisteria is a safe place.
There's no cover-up.
Everything's fine.
No trouble.
And I think that, uh, I think the Mutant Mountain Boys...
Hold on.
My phone is...
It's...
It's Philo.
What?
Dr. Drummond?
No, I'm at the stage.
Where are you?
What?
I'm at the stage.
So, you...
You...
Man, this could...
People could get hurt.
I don't know.
Most of these people have never been off the road, much less down the woods.
Jesus Christ.
Oh, okay, I won't...
I won't come alone.
I'll see if I can get some people to go with me.
We gotta hurry.
Friends, there's...
Something has come up down at the Hickory Grove.
Dr. Drummond says that the thing has...
Is on its way just out of there, and it may be possible...
...that if we go...
fast enough we can pursue it. Now we have weapons, sort of, some of these, I mean, I
guess they're Nerf swords and stuff, but, you know, pick up any pitchforks, torches,
flashlights, we're going to need them. It gets really dark in there. And I guess I'll,
maybe we can intimidate the thing or Dr. Legume or whatever it is. Come on, who's with me?
This is our last stand. What are we, just some kind of pink boys that sit around watching TV
and playing video games, downloading crap off the internet? This is our chance to prove
to Wisteria and the world that we can kick ass for real, man. It would be cool. Don't be a pussy.
Well, it's okay, Teeters. You don't have to be ashamed, poor crippled thing. But come on,
don't be like Teeters.
Follow me!
We're going on an adventure!
This is some geniuses following me right now!
Good God!
Get off your butt and off the stage!
Somebody, Philo's in trouble, man! Don't you care about Philo? Doesn't anyone care
about Dr. Drummond?
Look, not one person raised his hand.
Can you believe that?
Oh, no, no, it's this way. The yellow trail. Follow me! Follow me!
Down the yellow trail!
Follow the stairs!
Take these harpoons and lances, melt them down. Forge me new weapons that will strike deep
and hold fast. But do not douse them in water. They must have a proper baptism. What say ye,
all ye men? Will you give as much blood as shall be needed to temper the steel?
No!
To my anger now add your own. You be the cogs that fit my wheel, the gunpowder that
takes my torch. Pledge yourselves heart, soul, body, life and lungs. As I pledge myself,
I pledge my life and soul to the Lord.
Eager to protect their quaint little town.
Ross, getting groovy with his gargantuan greatsword. Barry, blowing haunting howls with his hunting
horn.
Susie, slicing up lizard scum with her longsword.
And Aaron, letting arrows fly with his beautiful bow.
Saltaire and
Rose!
Let the wind blow your way north and south.
Oh, damn it, whale!
Don't urinate down here just because it says it's the yellow trail.
There are candiru frogs, so don't stop.
If you need to do your business, do it now.
That's all I'm saying.
Just a little bit further.
Come on, Matt.
Now, wait a minute.
Maybe we should split up.
Yeah, sure.
That's what they always do in the...
What the hell?
For God's sake, turn around!
Please turn around!
Don't go!
What is it?
Is Philo okay?
Oh, that chicken shit.
Come on.
Philo's gone.
It's getting dark.
Hey, man.
It's awesome.
It's awfully quiet all of a sudden.
Too quiet.
Careful, Doctor.
We don't know what's in this place.
Look, it's like Blair Witch Project or something.
I'm inocuous hobos leaving.
Yeah, it's like some primitive thing has been out here.
What the?
Holy shit.
Oh, my God.
Oh, God.
I just felt a chill go up my back.
Oh, no.
There's a place.
That used to be...
A human...
What is that?
It's not guts.
It looks almost gelatinous.
Like a...
A pipe!
Hey, run!
Here, use my flashlight.
Give us more light here.
Now, friends, this is a...
Somebody keep your eyes out in the woods.
We're all looking down.
This thing could be...
Yeah, that's it.
Now, but...
That's a crime scene.
We probably shouldn't touch the evidence, but we can't call the cops.
Take the picture while you have the...
What are those metal things?
They always show up in your stomach.
Cotter pins.
We can determine later.
Are those cotter pins?
Cotter...
Welcome back, cotter pins.
Could that be just plain jello?
Not guts?
Well, I...
And that pipe...
Cotter pins in the gelatin.
What is this?
Good Lord.
Oh, my God.
Beautiful.
Okay.
I don't know if everybody's read their prescriptures, but the cotter pins and jello...
That means Bob's been here.
From where I'm standing...
I can see the personalized label inside that shoe.
Will you look at it, please?
That was sewn in.
That's not added in with Photoshop.
Feel it.
Look at it.
That is an actual personalized label that says Connie.
On this red high-heeled shoe.
One red high-heeled shoe.
One broken pipe and pipe stem.
Maybe we better take these for evidence.
No, no, no.
We should leave.
We should...
What the...
Is this...
This was a person?
Oh, God.
Oh, Jesus.
Oh, my God.
Look.
Arnold Palmer.
The bleeding head of Arnold Palmer.
The hideous...
All hail the bleeding head of Arnold Palmer!
Bleeding head good!
Healed head bad!
It goes on and on.
Wait.
Wait a minute.
Don't do that with your bare hands.
...far from this place.
Didn't you watch the...
I think it's a rubber one.
I don't think this is...
Tip it up a little bit.
This is one of Bob's collectibles.
There's something in it.
Is that a noise?
I think it's just...
It's not a...
It's...
Friends, it couldn't be the real bleeding head of Arnold Palmer.
No, no.
Or we'd be dead.
Does anybody have that Geiger counter?
I left it back at the...
I did not bring it.
Oh, my God.
Whatever the...
Wait a minute.
Did you ever...
Do you know what this implies?
What?
We've been chasing old Sequa or a ripe bear or Dr. Legume or whatever.
There have been a million theories.
But they've all been...
Crazy red herrings.
It must have been Bob that raped the car of Potter and Petal Nostril.
That took that little expensive annoying puppy dog Snuckles and imploded him or turned him inside out somehow.
It must...
It was...
It surely has been J.R. Bob Dobbs himself on some mad ex-day-related spree out here.
Probably with the consent of Snuckles.
And Connie.
Connie must have been...
But why one shoe?
Maybe that's part of some prophecy somewhere.
Would someone who's not carrying a camera or a flashlight...
See if you can pick up that shoe and put it in a lead-lined vault with that pipe.
This is...
We've got to...
We've got to rethink everything now, friends.
I just don't know...
I just...
How could he do this to us?
How could...
How could Bob...
First off, what happened to the damn exes?
And why is he trying to frame us?
We could get in serious trouble.
It could be the end of ex-days if word of this got out by Jove.
Jekyll and Cotter pins aren't too...
Too severe.
What's with the Cotter pins?
Yeah, Cotter pins.
When you see Cotter pins in Jello, that means Bob was here.
There's no other...
The last time he showed up in an ex-day was the...
Ding-dong.
The one...
The conspiracy called 1998.
Could we make our way back to the...
Yeah, yeah, I guess so.
We need to let the other people know that it was...
That's real.
For good...
For better or for worse, I mean, what can we say?
We can't call Bob...
Bob a murderer...
Any more than we are murderers for killing chickens.
Right.
Is Colonel Sanders a murderer?
How can we say Bob is a murderer?
Yes, well, it's a matter of...
Just because he killed a couple...
They were just Bobbies that he killed, okay?
They were asking for it.
The important thing is to keep this, you know...
What happens at Wisteria stays at Wisteria, you know?
I think that's what they say.
The Howells are not what they seem.
Man, I can't believe this.
Fuck.
Holy Jesus, fuck, fucking, fucking, fuck.
Fuckity-fuck-fuck.
I don't know.
I don't want to be taken aback by this stressful situation like this.
försö
you
I need a mic. I need to be able to tell people what happened. Let me put down this stupid
plastic helmet and silly plastic sword. Those things were no use at all. I don't know where
to begin. Friends, no, I can't. I'm sorry, but I can't guarantee. You did sign that waiver,
right? The liability waiver. I trust everybody did. Philo was, my God, could that have been
Philo? That shell? It was literally just a shell. It looked like his skin looked like
corrugated cardboard.
Covered with blood. We don't, we, no telling who it is. Now, first off, don't panic. Don't
panic. But, friends, what we found, first of all, cotter pins and Jell-O. A pile of
Jell-O. We thought it was guts at first. Simple cherry Jell-O with fruit in it and cotter pins.
Several different sizes of cotter pins. Absolute proof that J.R.
Bob Dobbs was here and is the killer.
To be enraged with a dumb brute that acted out of blind instinct is blasphemous.
Speak not to me, you blasphemy man. I'd strike the sun if it insulted me. Look here, Starbuck.
All right, I'm going to go.
All visible objects are but as pasteboard masks. Some inscrutable yet reasoning thing
puts forth the molding of their features. The white whale tasks me. He heaps me. Yet
he is but a mask. Just the thing behind the mask I chiefly hate. The malignant thing that
has plagued and frightened man since time began.
The thing that molds and mutilates our race. Not killing us outright, but letting us live
on with half a heart and half a lung.
Keep us, keep us all.
I don't know what to make of this. I don't know whether to be glad somehow that Bob is
taking action. But I tell you, the last time we found cotter pins and Jell-O in a subgenius
exhibit.
The campground was in the next day of the what the year the pinks called 1998. We found
also this broken pipe.
What happens when Bob breaks his pipe?
A broken pipe. Connie, Connie's presence and she's not always a good influence on Bob.
And then this.
What's inside it?
The A, not the, but A.
The A, bleeding head of Arnold Palmer.
But something's inside it.
Some kind of stuffing.
Well, I think it's just, it's stuffed with paper because it's made of rubber, Pisces.
That's not a real shrunken human head.
But the bleeding head of Arnold Palmer replicas are exceedingly rare. We know of only four
on this continent. This is the fifth one. More evidence that Bob is running around here
doing God only knows what.
Certainly, Bob himself probably isn't in control.
He never really is.
On the other hand, since it's Bob, there's nothing we or anyone else can ever do about
it.
And he has basically by being Bob escaped.
I mean, we could go tearing through the woods looking for him.
If it was old sequel or a right bear or man bear pig or something, that'd be a cinch.
We've got all these great weapons here.
We'd be able to take them down.
But my God, you can't hunt Bob.
But unless he wants to be hunted, you can't catch Bob unless he wants to be caught.
And since we're not running through the woods right now, I'd say that indicates that not
only did Bob escape, but he has already won simply by virtue of being Bob.
And whether his acts are good or evil, that matters very little in the long run.
There are some things man was not meant to know.
God in his infinite forgetfulness.
Oh, God.
Managed to cause all sorts of strange things to accidentally happen, including J.R. Bob
Dobbs himself.
And for that matter, us.
So friends, I guess it's whatever's going to happen next is up to Bob.
But we can send him a message with when we go to the great burning tonight, friends,
we can send a message to Bob that although he may break his own laws.
He also must obey.
His own laws.
Well, he doesn't have to, but we can pretend he has to take out our frustrations on it
by throwing things at that dummy of him and and laughing as he burns up.
Praise Bob.
And who knows, by expert performances, we may draw Bob in from the outer darkness.
He may come to visit us if we make this a congenial enough spot for him.
Oh, yeah.
You go up and meet Bob after in the mood he's in.
Dr. Howell.
Oh, go ahead.
Go.
Go communicate with it, Professor.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Go communicate with Bob.
Why don't you?
Well, he's a reasonably intelligent life form.
Sure.
We ought to be able to as members of a similar species.
Anyway, there's nothing we can do about it but live in fear or hope.
It's up to each individual subgenius which path to choose.
Which shall it be?
The red pill, the blue pill or that polka dot pill that they the guy didn't even want
you to notice.
Meanwhile, we must let this festival go on.
Try to enjoy the rest of X Day, friends, despite the murders and the failure of the
world to end.
Well, that was, we were going to be murdering half the planet at least.
So what the hell are we worried about a couple of Bobbies laying out dead in the woods?
Have fun.
Small sacrifice by comparison.
Praise Bob.
Yeah.
That's how I read it.
You know, it's just a very interesting story.
Yeah, well, we'll be right back.
You know, we've had to talk for days about it.
Oh, yeah.
That's right.
Yeah.
this boiling blood and smoking brow.
Why palsy the arm and the oar,
the iron and the lance?
I feel old, Starbuck, and bowed,
as though I were Adam,
staggering under the vile centuries since paradise.
What is it?
What nameless, inscrutable, unearthly thing
commands me against all human lovings and longings
to keep pushing and crowding and jamming myself on all the time,
making me do what in my own natural heart
I dare not dream of doing?
Is Ahab Ahab?
Is it I, God, or who?
Who that lifts this arm?
But if the great sun cannot move
except by God's invisible power,
how can my small heart beat,
my brain think thoughts,
unless God does that beating,
does that thinking,
does that living,
and not I?
By heavens, man,
we are turned right,
round and round in this world,
like yonder windless,
and fate is the hand spike.
And all the time,
that smiling sky
and this unsounded sea.
Look ye into its deeps
and see the everlasting slaughter that goes on.
Who put it into its creatures to chase and fang one another?
Where do murderers go, man?
Who's to doom when the judge himself is dragged before the bar?
No, please, everyone.
Don't worry.
This is not really J.R. Bob Dobbs.
And if it was,
it would be because he wanted us to do this.
He does smell like kerosene or something.
Yes, he does.
I can't believe I'm...
I can't believe I'm giving you盾
Neither did I want
I was build to goay support going way over from the road.
I guess that magic fire water really worked.
His shoes are twitching.
How can he play?
What have we done?
His face was the first thing to go.
Of course.
Well, Bob did give us one thing today.
He gave us warmth.
Thanks for the warmth, Bob.
If you look close.
Oh, yeah, his heart, his soul is glowing.
I hear him talking.
I hear him trying to communicate.
Now this is altogether too creepy.
Behind his face, there is an icon, the sacred icon.
He'd burn his face.
Oh, my.
But the symbol of his face survived.
He has been cleansed by fire.
It's been purified.
You can't see the icon.
The icon has appeared.
Bob's face is gone and the icon has appeared.
Milagro.
Come see this miracle of subgenius proportions.
I'm sure there's no danger of explosion.
There's no way that Bob would be so fiendish in this weird fit of his
as to give him a chance.
This is the first time I'm in a range.
I'm going to use this whole complicated thing to draw us here to be close enough to a small,
dirty nuke in his glowing red heart.
Well, you left the Geiger counter.
Yeah, I did.
Why?
I shouldn't.
What is that blue flame coming out of there?
That's a strange river of actinic fire there.
That's probably where the alcoholic beverage is.
Reverend Fid Chooley went and lit a cigarette off of Bob.
That's pretty disrespectful, Reverend Chooley.
Well, now he can't.
He's getting off better than he deserves anyway.
I mean, really, this is a slap on the wrist compared to what...
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Sure.
Slap on the wrist.
Not even that.
I'm trying to smoke Bob, but I can't get close enough to actually light the thing.
You're lighting it off the shoe, I see.
The sacred shoe.
Well, at least you get to smoke Bob's shoe.
Again, this isn't really Bob.
That's probably 808's shoe.
Wait, wait.
That's not really Bob?
No.
No?
I don't think so.
Well, you know, I was hoping I'd meet Bob here.
He keeps...
His secretary keeps sending me these very nice letters for...
You want to meet Bob here?
Do you realize what he did to some of the people here and their pets and their cars?
Well, that's kind of why I wanted to meet him.
I had a couple of grievances I wanted to address.
Yeah, that's a great idea.
No complain to Bob.
Well, that'll happen if Bob wants to hear it.
I'm not going to hear your complaint.
So keep your hopes up, man.
Oh, that's right.
Never let your...
Yeah, if he wants it to happen, it'll happen.
I should never let go of my grudges because...
Cling to your grudges!
Right.
Hold onto your hate and your perversions.
Because the moment you let go of your grudge, that could be when Bob comes and then...
You had your chance to kill him.
Right.
And save the world, but no.
It's snowing.
It's snowing Bob particles.
Bob.
Snowing flaming bits.
They're flying up from the fire and snowing down on us.
Dobbs ash.
It's a good way to spread the poison around.
Indeed.
Wow, watching a person burn like that makes me hungry.
It's like one of my old...
I think it's time for another Slim Jim.
...not to learn from.
From hell's hot isopathy, for hate's sake,
I spit my life out.
I've lost breath at thee.
Oh, dammit, whale.
I should be ashamed.
I'm carrying the gun now.
I've got to come back after I get a brief wh
Maybe he's left majors?
Will you be my舒?
Oh, no.
I only am escaped alone to tell thee.
To be continued...
For more information, see www.subgenius.com.
Praise Bob!
Friends, we're glad you listened to this show,
and we're even more glad that some listeners have donated enough to help us keep on going for another couple of months.
Not just this show, but subgenius.com and all the other archive sites.
But if you truly love Bob,
and want some of that slack back to rebound to you,
you should go to subgenius.com, front page, or especially the radio page,
or the catalog store pages,
and help out financially as best you can.
Now, we know what it's like to be on the brink of total poverty,
and we don't want any subgeniuses to make their own situations worse.
But some of you still have jobs.
Even five bucks makes a big difference,
even if it's only...
Only once a month,
from enough of you.
50 bucks makes an even bigger difference.
All we're saying is that
blow jobs could go the way of Steve jobs if you don't pay Dobbs.
We also take checks and money orders to
subgenius.com
P.O. Box,
181-417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio,
44,
Thanks for anything you can do to help Let There Be Slack!