Con radio, we are receiving flash traffic, emergency action message, recommend alert one, recommend alert one.
Alert one, alert one.
Con radio, receiving emergency action message, recommend alert one, recommend alert one.
Alert one, okay.
Alert one, incoming emergency action message.
Alert one, it's authorized.
Alert one, incoming EAM.
You can watch.
Test, test.
Radio, radio antenna.
Radio antenna.
Where's the BLF antenna?
Aye, sir.
That's it.
It's working.
I'm here, too.
Just because I rocked doesn't mean I made a stone.
I feel your fear.
It's coming through like static on my heart radio.
I'm here, too.
I can do anything.
Excuse me.
Just in case.
But like, I'm just going to do this.
Believe me.
There's a massive yearly много period on principle.
Yes, Parral Works ERAO.
Are we getting somewhere here taking a shot at animal role?
I'd really appreciate produced by Adam Gilroy, the village head of the United States,
Under the Why Are You There.
But if that was chocolate and ice cream, you got a permission to spin a jar.
Come on, I've already given you a jar.
She'd still gottan some average baseball cap.
loud voice.
Call now for fat body that will be yours forever.
Call now for a lean, fat-free major credit card.
By far the most common bird in the swamp is the white blackbirds, but the forests are
full of hawks, warblers, and cutlers, blacklers, and cutlers.
Hello there.
All of you have heard of mail order obscenity for your entire family.
I'd like to begin with a flood tide of second-class filth in a depraved manner.
An illustrated, detailed course in pornographic perversion, threatening to pervert an entire
generation of our wild, flagrant Harvard sociologists.
The United States Supreme Court has described it as,
dirt for dirt's sake.
We describe it as dirt for money's sake.
The Self-Genius Hour of Slavery.
In the past few years, this depraved filth has become increasingly worse, not only in
content, but in volume, for one reason.
It is big business, profitable business, for the mercenary perverts.
I swore I would never sing again.
Through this material, today's sadists, masochists, psychiatrists, sociologists, and psychologists,
the military chaplains association of the United States, and every other kind of deviant
can be stimulated to acht for which he has no legitimate outlet.
This moral decay weakens our resistance to the onslaught of the communist masters of
law.
A bizarre but evil misfit pervert cults.
Highly colorful contaminated hardcore human buttocks in a perverted manner.
And thus the grotesque rubber cigarette for the participant until his utter depravity is complete.
Remember, support the obscenity racketeers by writing to Cincinnati, Ohio.
Hey, I got a question for you.
This is insane.
Well, that's the power of cult.
Power of cult.
Wow.
See, we want to expose ourselves, create a limited life, and...
People are horrible and...
Crazy.
I would tend to agree with you.
Hmm.
It's nothing.
Maybe fear is just F-E-A-R.
But first, here's a mighty swell gang.
You'll want to spread the news around that you're collecting those slick new friends.
Because that's the only way they'll trade duplicates with them.
And you won't want to miss out on that fun.
You want to be sure you'll round out your collection of all 18 different friends.
Like Smitty and K.O. and Herbie, of course.
And the best part is, you don't have to ask Mom.
Remember, that's P.P.
P.P.
Hi, this is Dr. J.
Are you tired?
Do you sometimes feel?
Now you've got it.
Why go through life when you can use anyone, anyone, and get anyone, and get anyone, to do anyone, and feel powerless again?
You'll be able to use calm.
Greatest weapon on some people.
Anyone.
Any place.
Anytime.
Imagine if you were able to predict and control calm.
Perhaps you wanted to make a good impression.
So.
Feel powerless again.
Psych.
While that seems as if it would be so, sometimes it can be hard.
We feel good when we were unaware of the process.
Pleasurable stimuli.
Have a stomachache.
Unconscious victims.
Repeat exposure.
You will actually grow.
How annoying it is.
Someone has one hand in his pocket.
You put your hand in his pocket.
Why?
But wait a minute.
Why'd you do it?
So.
Heightened arousal.
Unstoppable overall strategy.
Arousal is high.
Excitement aroused.
Arousal arousal.
Arousal was high.
Flexibility.
Your own beauty is limited.
A pack of lies.
Conundrum.
What does all this mean?
You think.
Long.
Boring.
And finally.
Set yourself up as better than the rest.
Simplicity.
Your ideas are muddled.
Finally.
But how small you are.
Feel unimportant?
Once there was a boy down south.
Always had snot running across his mouth.
What's that mess boy the neighbors would say?
Why is that snot on your face that way?
Snot on tweedle.
Snot on tweedle all day.
Mama sent him to the grocery store.
Let's go grocery.
Asked him to buy three eggs times four.
Run back home for the grocery man say.
Why is that snot on your face that way?
Snot on tweedle.
Snot on tweedle all day.
Mama sent him to the grocery store.
What's that mess boy?
Honestly looking very cheap.
Whenever I look over at a flex of his clothes.
A total NeedProVolume portion goodbye.
Soon this boy,
became a man.
And oh hello.
His mom and I Nein.
λη
Wanted to know the master plan
So to the Lord he did say
Hey God, why is this snout on my face this way?
Huh? Hey God, God why do I have this snout all over my face like this, God?
Huh? Hey God, why is this snout on my face like this, God?
Huh? Why is this snout on my face this way, God?
Snout Mouth Tweedle all this day
All this day
Hey friends, welcome to Hour of Slack number 1067
Is that it? Where's my background music? That's funny
Oh, oh wait, I see why, I see where it is
Look at that, it was on number three, not number one
Ah, there we go
Snout Mouth Tweedle
A composition by the great Joe Newman of the Rudy Schwartz Project
And you can find information about the CDs of the Rudy Schwartz Project
At www.schwartztone.com
Yes, this is Stephen Kent in the background
On his didge
We met him at Starwood
We just got back from, last week was the devotional
We're not going to be bombarding you with Devo music tonight though
But that was a great devotional
It was a great devotional with Deva
Yeah, Deva, the devastating female Devos
The stupefyingly devastating Deva
And friends, oh yes, and the rest of what we've heard
The cut-ups were by the great subgenius collage artists
Nor Elpref and Mr. Fernandanande Lee Murr
They do not work together, by the way
It's just that I play their stuff all the time
And our new intro was by Popes Lilith
The scary new intro
So, but we...
I actually have subgenius news to catch you up upon this time
Now, this most important thing was something that was faxed
This came to my fax machine
And it spewed out as two handwritten pages
And I'm going to try to read this the way that it came out on my fax machine
It was addressed in handwritten to
The owner of the company, number one, subgenius foundation
Special report, urgent, top secret
And I'm going to withhold this fellow's name
But he said this
People are in danger by people that have robotic communication lasers
In laborator research
I was planted a zo chip by person that has experience
With different kind of lasers
Everybody part has a chip
They torture people in different areas
And seal your information
By reading everything you did by recording your life history
This is no joke
If I don't receive within 24 hours a call or letter
I will go on national television
And it will hurt the movie that is going to come out soon
I can prove it
And have evidence that you know
By understanding how I know what it is
By looking at my body with MRI
To show the things...
People do with computer
And using frequencies radios
To torture people
I've been to sacramental
And have pictures of my body badly bruised
That look purple in the midsection
Take this serious
And help remove the implant
I know how to find these people
Will explain when you call this number
Day or night
Need your help to stop these robotic communication people
It will hurt your...
You...
You know the whole system
I compared all four pieces...
The â¶ă's who played the black copy
Didn't know how to do it
There's not a si dungeons
And in place of a fairytale
More advanced
a John Stewart type comedian
who gets elected president
and his name is Dobbs.
Dobbs.
So the people,
when they,
certain kinds of people
see the ads for this movie
with President Dobbs,
they assume that,
well, we're behind it.
As well they should
because you don't know
that we're not.
Anyway, I just thought
that was pretty important information
about the Zo chips
and people's bodies
and having been to Sacramento
and all of that.
Yes, kind of sobering, isn't it?
Yeah.
I guess that's a strange way to put it.
Let's see.
What other news?
Oh, the new Quijibo is out.
Quijibo is a subgenius magazine.
I will tell you the address
to write to for information
about this fine publication.
It's the,
the only really regular subgenius magazine,
but it's a big hefty,
this one here weighs in at 23 pages
and it has a good number.
This number 30,
it's the Quijibo adult library
and he,
he,
it's titled instead of regular Quijibo,
it's called
The Southpaw Self-Pleasure.
He was a right-handed man
surrounded by nubile willing women,
but only his left hand
could.
He could bring him satisfaction.
Oh, Princess,
we were joining in on this.
Anyway, this,
this magazine,
I wanted to share with you
some of the interesting articles in it.
There's,
here's something called
Diswhiskeylexia
by the editor,
Reverend Christopher Lee,
who is the famous movie star,
biggest moneymaker of last year.
Here he is holding a Pope Pero
mug of,
and oh,
the night,
boys,
you'll be interested to know
that Quijibo magazine
always has a page three girl.
Page three girl in this issue
is Pope,
Priestess Pisces.
Let me tell you,
I'm fully hetero,
but I'm,
I mean,
this is really hot.
Well,
she's showing off her cleavage
and her little tongue barbs
and all that,
that stuff.
These modern day kids,
I don't think.
Mere hume words
cannot describe her yumminess.
Praise,
Priestess of Pisces,
the Queen of Wank.
And that's literally true.
Pisces' ministry
is based on
slack through wanking.
Yes.
She's a very outspoken
wankist.
one might say,
pro-wanker.
Oh,
there's some information
about Bigfoot news
has been gripping Malaysia.
And this is true news
from
apparently
a 10 foot tall
ape.
Ape.
They like to call
yetis apes
was cited
in this national park,
which of course
has caused a lot more people
to come to that national park.
Yes,
this is no news
of the weird here.
This is Reuters 2006.
Right.
Well,
it's still,
you know,
the fact that they,
the fact that they call
our cousins
the yetis
ape men
and so forth.
Anyway,
there's,
this issue has some,
some excellent
rantings
and reports
on
American Nazis.
Oh no.
Yeah.
The American Nazis
that have,
have wrecked
the family of Magdalene
and Jesus,
the subgeniuses.
We have a little bit
of news on that.
In fact,
I should mention,
might as well go ahead
and say.
Yes.
Because people have been
wondering about
what has happened
with Reverend Magdalene
and her child
who was taken away
from her
because she was
involved in the church
of the subgenius.
Yes, it's true.
A New York
family court
took,
a woman's child
away from her
because of her involvement
with the church
of the subgenius
because they thought
this judge
was under the impression
that our church
was full of
devil worshipers
as opposed to
people who simply
do business
with certain
minor level
demons
in the conspiracy.
Anyway,
we got,
supposedly
their last trial
date
happened this week
and they're going to
end it Friday
but the judge
has yet to make
a decision.
So we wait
in terrible suspense
to find out
whether
this judge
is more sane
than the previous judge
who had to be
recused.
He recused himself
in fact
right in front of
everybody
because it,
I guess partly
because
so many thousands
of people
on the internet
were laughing at him
for having
mistaken the church
of the subgenius
for the Illuminati
or something.
Anyway,
also in Cuigibo here
there are some
detailed field reports
on the devotionals
and various
devo shows,
photos,
sexy photos
of subgenius males
and females
in Congress
doing acts of Congress
and intercourse
speaking.
Oh, yes.
See, there's Philo
and me and Hal
yakking.
Oh, yes.
There's you and Dr. Hal.
Oh, and the Dr. Hal
reveals that secret.
Oh, that's right.
The secret recipe
for peanut butter cookies.
It's very,
a secret
technological secrets
behind the engineering
of a peanut butter cookie.
Right, it's a secret recipe, folks.
That's another reason
that we're here.
Strange rites and rituals
among the subgenius tribes
of Brushwood
which is the kind of gossip
you want to hear about.
You've always suspected
that there's a lot of
naughty goings-on
and luau's
and so forth
in this cult
and well,
you can find all the
salacious details
right here.
The Dobbs house
tiki time.
Queegee boys
love girls
who love Queegee Bo
and you can get
more information
about Queegee Bo
from this address.
Queegee Bo
that's Q-U-I-J-I-B-O
18 West Main Street.
It's pretty simple.
18 West Main.
Greenfield, Indiana.
4-6-1-4-0.
Once again,
that's 4-6-1-4-0
in Greenfield, Indiana.
And what other news
did we have?
Oh, the Insight.
Ah, yes.
Insight was busted, friends.
You may be familiar
with the ad
with Smilin' Bob.
He looks just like
our J.R. Bob Dobbs.
In fact,
he's an obvious ripoff
hawking male enhancement pills
from a company
called Insight.
For three years now,
they've been
ripping off our trademark
successfully
because they didn't put a pipe
in their false Bob's mouth.
Our Bob, of course,
always has that pipe.
But it was obviously
supposed to be
J.R. Bob Dobbs.
Obviously.
Anyway,
Justice and Carmen,
have been served, friends.
The maker of dietary supplements
that claim to improve
everything from sexuality
to memory
defrauded thousands
of customers and banks
of at least
a hundred million
federal authorities say.
And this indictment
names Berkeley
Premium Nutraceuticals.
The company,
which recently said
it has five million
customers worldwide,
is known for its
Smilin' Bob ads
that depict a man
whose life gets better
and his life gets better.
After he uses the company's
enzyme for natural
male enhancement.
The company markets nationally
a variety of other products
claiming to help everything
from night vision
to memory
to female libido.
The company president
and others made up
information in their
advertisements such as
endorsement by doctors
that did not exist
and results of
customer satisfaction
surveys that have
never been conducted.
U.S. Attorney General
Lockhart said.
Customers with a
complaints were told
to write to a director
of customer care
who did not exist.
And luckily for us,
friends,
the charges carry
a 30-year sentence.
Five of the company's
former executives
have pled guilty
in U.S. District Court
to defrauding customers
through a product
giveaway program
that led to
unauthorized billing
of their credit cards.
They've frozen
25 million bucks
in assets
held by
Warshack
and members
of his family.
And they're going
to try to recover
money to give
to victims
of the false Bob.
Berkeley Nutraceuticals
generated about
$250 million
in sales
in 2004,
mostly from
telephone orders
spurred by TV ads
starring Bob Dobbs.
What a bummer.
Well, friends,
we're going...
Actually, I mean,
it's a...
It's a...
It's a joyous occasion
for us
that this thief
has been sent away.
And now we're going
to go back,
back, back
into the tapes
and I'll try to tune in
the lonesome cowboy somehow.
So, for right now,
here is the news.
From PR News in Washington,
I'm delayed by
Mysterious Ernesto.
NASA said today
the ideal price
for the space shuttle
would be $50 to $60
on Monday.
A faulty judge in Detroit
has ordered less than
$67 of space shuttle
under mysterious circumstances.
PR News is poverty stricken.
Saudi Arabia's royal family
is paying for false PR.
U.S. officials say
top OPEC officials said
the Sri Lankan army says
an army spokesman says
the rebels say
the army has to face
PR News.
From Washington.
On one side are those
who believe the right
of all people to speak
in moderation
and worship
tyranny and extremism.
The fascists,
the Nazis,
the communists,
and a victory for
the cause of fascists
of the 20th Century.
Cult새,
Cultítulo,
the Nazis
and history shows
Victory for the Fascists
A feeling is
natural,
and comforting.
Tolla, Tolla, Tolla...
We recently saw the enemy
way
Comunists
calling
This cult called terrorist.
Terror, terror, terror, terror, terror.
The horror grows, grows, grows, grows.
Wrong and comforting.
Wrong, wrong.
Totalitarian.
The right of all people to speak in moderation and worship tyranny and extremism.
Conspiracy.
The world is a collage of corporations inexorably determined by the immutable bylaws of business.
The world is a collage.
I love it here.
Dr. Dave, Dr. Dave, Dr. Dave, Dr. Dave.
Well, have you heard what's going on over there now out in the wilderness, where wonderful
X-Days has been held for some 3,000 years now?
No.
A mad fellow who has been befriended by the Southern Tier Indians is going around shooting highway patrolmen, supposedly.
Now, didn't that happen, like, isn't that last week's news?
And that was that one guy and they caught him?
Apparently, they haven't caught him.
Well, maybe they did just catch him.
Are you thinking of Bucky, Reverend Bucky?
Oh, no.
They cornered him and he turned himself in.
I mean, he turned himself into a toad and tried to hop away, but they gigged him.
Yeah, that was Reverend Bucky who used to do the subgenius website revisions.
That's the self-same?
Or buckweed, it could have also been.
So, yeah, Dave, what kind of news have you been up on?
Well, I did hear about Reverend Commander Bucky slaying a Badooper, but I didn't know if it was real or not.
Okay, here's the news.
I've been catching people up on the news.
The news is that one guy died.
And that guy that made a fool of himself on TV, he did it again.
And that other guy that was a jerk, he did it again, too.
And that country that was at war with that other country, they're having war again.
And there was a bad earthquake.
And there was some terrible flooding.
So, that's the news, man.
Yeah, and there was a guy, too, thrown in with the flooding, wasn't there?
Yeah, and some crazy woman killed her baby for Jesus.
And then there was this guy that beat up his wife, too, right?
Yeah, that's right.
And there was some guy that beat up his wife.
And then there was some wife that beat up this guy.
There was, yeah, that was the news.
So, yeah, I guess I'm pretty well caught up now.
Yeah, you're caught up now.
Now, what about the other...
That's all you need to know.
The other high E-popped, making juvenile delinquents out of people of the Martian race,
or of the other...
Other religions.
Did you hear about that?
No.
Well, Pope Benedict said, he quoted an obscure phrase...
Oh, right.
An obscure discourse, an argument that a guy who was getting them,
they were attacking his fort,
and he told the other guy who he was kind of friends with,
and told him they were going to sack the place,
he was telling him, well, your religion sucks and stuff,
and the other guy was saying, well, so does yours.
And so...
And Pope Black quoted that?
The other high E-popped tried to...
Make a big deal out of it somehow.
Right.
But I'm really not caught up on that part.
So, in other words, because one guy in one country said a bunch of stuff
that a guy a thousand years ago said about another guy a thousand years ago,
a million people in another country got...
Started burning things.
Yeah.
Well, that's usually how...
That's what they call spontaneous combustion in the social...
Political sphere.
The Onion had a funny headline that said that...
The conflicting...
The conflicting sides in the Middle East were turning to religion for help.
Yeah.
I'm sorry to laugh at theirs, not ours, but that makes soup.
Well, it's funny that it took them that long to come up with that punchline.
It's such a...
Well, I guess it's been done.
Hasn't everything pretty much been done?
I guess every new story's been told and everything's been done,
except for the day those freaking exes finally get here.
Yeah.
It's been talked about.
It's been predicted by every single religious nut in the world.
Most of all, J.R. Bob Dobbs.
I want to know what they look like, because I was tailed on the way back home.
They look like anything you want to know they look like.
Oh, okay.
They're schmooish.
Yeah, if you want to...
Right, they're like the mighty schmoo that will...
That flops itself onto your breakfast griddle
and cuts itself up into slices so you can cook it easier.
Well, that is weird that we are...
They are on the wavelength, because I swear,
rather than a cylindrical or a spherical object,
they look like giant, you know, like deli turkeys,
you know, the big roast turkeys they put in the windows
that are made of plastic, but they look really good.
I mean, I couldn't smell them, let's just say that.
They could have been actual roast turkeys chasing me around,
but they had, like, red and yellow running lights underneath.
And on top, it looked like there was one beacon light
where the turkey's head would have been,
not been roasted, you know?
Mm-hmm.
Are there some kind of new Franken-turkeys
you've been seeing at the farmer's market or something?
Well, that could be.
I maybe have been having bad visions of mutated turkeys
and thought that they were, like, X's flying craft.
But I'm pretty sure that I was actually being pursued
by a small squadron of flying...
Oh, they were chasing you?
No, they weren't tasting me.
They were chasing.
Chasing, yeah, chasing.
They were chastising.
They were chastising me, too.
Chastising.
Psychologically, I was thinking things I didn't want to think.
They weren't harmful thoughts,
but they were just obtrusive thoughts,
you know, about baseball in 1978.
So flying, lit-up, telepathic...
Telepathic.
...shmoo-like turkey creatures were harassing you.
Harassing me.
So I just was looking for your epoptly advice
on what I should do.
Maybe I should just wear sunglasses
or cut out my optic nerves.
Well, we got a fax earlier this week
about something like that.
They said that the problem was
robotic communication labors in laboratory research
and that they torture people
by recording your life history.
What if you line your baseball cap with tinfoil?
Would that help?
Right.
What if, like, you know,
the people who wear tinfoil hats,
can't we just maybe turn out a couple thousand of them
with the old Dobbs logo on there?
Duh, we tried.
We did.
We're doing that.
We've been doing that for years, Dave.
Oh, well...
Yeah, look at the Cafe Press catalog, man.
No kidding.
It's full of nothing but tinfoil-lined Dobbs hats
with every possible cool little drawing
by Dr. Howell on them.
Well, they have to have more than just regular,
you know, just regular tinfoil on there.
They need reinforced and electrolytically perfect
so as to bounce the race.
Uh-huh.
I see.
Yeah.
Maybe we should run ads, late-night ads,
that feature a smiling, pipe-smoking guy
who, you know, his longer gets longer
whenever he wears his special Bob hat.
Yeah, yeah.
That would be...
And we could sell just sugar pills
or some kind of ginseng or something
and call it male enhancement snot-mouthed Tweedle pills.
Why not tell them that every time there's an encounter
that the elongus will become flungated?
That way...
You know, if they're expecting a lot of people over
or whatever you might want a lot of beings over,
then they can...
They'd be prepared to have a sex orgy that will...
I don't know.
That's right, friends.
If you buy smiling Bob snot-mouthed Tweedle pills,
you'll have a longer, stronger...
Stronger.
Weiner pills.
Your breath will be brighter.
Cleaner.
Tastier.
And resemble your schlong.
I don't think anybody would want their own breath
to resemble their schlong.
I don't know why, but...
Let's just not even...
Nah.
No.
It makes breathing difficult.
It makes conceiving difficult, so...
You're right.
Remember, this is not our opinion.
Every day, more and more men are turning to food.
Wild oil cream or truly big loose handsome hair.
And that's surprising, for what other leading hair tonic removes the hair neatly and naturally.
What's more, root wild oil cream is alcoholic and contains soothing alcohol.
No wonder root wild oil cream is the favorite with so many millions of smart alcoholic men.
Get root wild oil cream.
The choice of big loose handsome men who put handsome smart loose big hair first.
It's true.
Makes breath brighter.
It's a fact.
It's true.
If you just keep chewing the gum...
Oh my...
Oh my god, I...
I left that gum at home.
I can't chew no gum over here.
Now I'll try chewing some gum over here.
Smell.
Smell that smell.
It's kind of...
It's...
A wild smell of elderberry gum.
There was some smell I could smell.
I'm going to have to go ahead and...
I'm going to be smelling it soon.
A sort of a fishy smell.
I heard the sound that precedes the smell.
Smelt, actually.
You dealt that smell.
Yeah, whoever smelt it.
Just yesterday.
That was some puzzling evidence with Dr. Howland, Dr. Philodrum,
and now some Noral Prefinitely Murd.
I've got an eclectic reading list.
21st century fascists.
Oh, my God.
I believe the American people have the wrong path.
21st century fascists.
Oh, my God.
Costly defeats.
I believe the American people have costly defeats.
We want to be free.
We will abandon them to the beheaders, the terrorists, the assassins.
Amazing twists and turns.
Wrong.
Losing strength along the way.
Infamous.
Chaos.
Want to help us out?
Blown into pieces.
Plunger.
Seek to attack.
After midnight.
Steal.
Just that.
Throw in the towel.
A media mob scene.
Perverted.
Um, um, um, um, um, um, um, um, um.
AJ's did it.
Let down.
Mysteries.
21st century fascists.
Oh, my God.
It's making me really excited to see her like that.
21st century fascists.
I loved her so much, and I'm so sor-
Please, please, please, sweetheart.
I love you so much.
Oh baby, please come back to investigate the wreckage.
21st century fascists.
Child pornography charges.
President Bush still struggling for a rebirth.
Giant piles of dirt.
Giant piles.
That's even worse.
Bungled.
There are still issues.
Cross leader feats.
Giant piles.
There are still issues.
Cross leader feats.
Oh my god.
Chaos.
Wanna help us out?
Let's go to a restaurant.
In them, they're all cotton fields at home.
We're the man of restaurants.
Strangers in the restaurant.
Make the day complete.
Now give me my pills.
Let's now look at some techniques for making your daily life easy.
You've screwed up.
You feel guilty.
I'm sorry.
Let's see how we can use psychology.
Fast.
Circumstances beyond your control.
You didn't feel up to it.
You completely forgot.
Placing the blame on an outside source, vague generalities, is highly effective in reducing
a person's anger.
You don't care or you're not interested in caring.
Shift blame or assign excuses.
Exacerbate the situation.
Sometimes it's very hard, but as hard as it is, it looks great, but doesn't do anything.
Do nothing.
But remember, give her back what you took.
Nothing makes sense.
Primal and pure.
Go back in time.
The sex was lousy.
Use words that have a strong negative connotation.
It's all-consuming.
Annoying problems.
Sit down and shut up.
I don't like that and now I'm upset.
Angry, hurt, frustrated, and small.
Beat yourself up.
Blash out.
Bear in mind there are no absolutes.
Bear in mind there are absolutes.
Heightened state of arousal.
Injure him.
Smile.
That's right.
Incapacitate him.
Hit him.
Vomiting, urinating, or belching.
Act insane or mentally deranged.
Hit him where it hurts.
Who cares?
Act without thinking.
Using deception is acceptable.
You'll notice that you feel much better about yourself and life in general.
Get anyone to do anyone feel powerless again.
Lie to again.
Yeah, I, uh, speaking of conceiving, I had, I conceived this little animation and, and,
uh, uh, put it out on, on YouTube and my friend Nenslo basically said it.
It sucked.
So you.
And I, and I said, I wish I, I wish you had some of what I'm smoking as a joke.
And he said, I wish you had some of what I'm thinking with.
Touche and ouch, Master Nenslo.
That's real repartee for you.
Yeah.
That's razor sharp wit.
And it's consummate max or some sort of clear broth.
Yeah.
I wish I could think thoughts like that.
How does one, I mean, I think you have to be born with a brain and not wreck it at some
point.
I mean, several brain cells, not just the one, or is the case princess.
We and I, the shared one, isn't it a practice makes perfect sort of thing too.
What you mean?
The more thinking you do, the better you get at it.
I'm not sure.
Well, you might be.
I'm not sure about that.
Cause look at some of, look at where some of the deep thinkers go with it.
Well, yes, I guess you do have a point there.
They go to the guy who faxed me.
Now that, that person obviously is way ahead of me.
He knows about the robotic communication lasers, but, but where's he gone with it?
Right.
Can he create meaning as, as you told me the other night in the tender moment after we
had sex.
You said that changing the sex.
The sound changes the meaning of all visual information.
And I said, well, geez, I've known that.
And I've been trying to express that, but I couldn't.
And then I shut up for awhile and I realized the visual information was very horrible.
And then I made a little, like a little bird sound and sang the, um, whistled the Mayberry
RFD theme song.
And I felt hell of a lot of sex.
We had him, we had him mow the lawn and he thought that we told him that was.
Don't destroy his illusions, honey.
He did a good job on the lawn.
I know.
He did a great job on the lawn.
Mowing the lawn.
Yeah.
You're a great.
That was real.
Yeah.
Pardon?
That's what the kids call it now.
Mowing the lawn.
When they open your skull.
Ride them.
Mow them.
You mean kids call mowing the lawn sex?
Yeah.
Oh.
And no, the military calls, calls trepanation and lobotomies mowing the lawn.
Right.
Trimming the hedge.
They call it.
Yeah.
You, you just give them a light haircut over the top.
Just, just take a little bit off the sides.
Using that ice pick through the eye sockets.
But always.
For the nose, the nasal.
You can go up in through the nose, can't you, if you have the right tools.
I think with mine.
Scramble somebody's math.
Scramble someone's math.
Yeah.
Well, yeah, you can do that.
I mean, if you know where to go in with the hooks and which part to scramble, you can
get rid of certain.
Like orneriness.
You could remove someone's orneriness.
You could remove someone's verbal ability.
Just pluck it right out.
You could remove someone's ability to tell the difference between say a glass of water
and a parking lot.
Is there a big difference?
Well, see, you've already had that operation.
How does it feel to you?
Well, I, I do have a hard time differentiating between certain objects that I did quite easily
differentiate between before.
For instance, cars.
You're the kind of voter they're looking for.
Yeah, well, that's what I'm worried about with the flying turkeys.
But I don't know if I'm ready to go yet, so to speak.
I haven't.
The de-bowled flying turkeys.
Those are just, those are like a form of, of preliminary vote guesstimating.
You know, it's like a survey.
They follow you around and read all of your thoughts and everything you say and do as
a kind of a survey.
So that doesn't really affect the turnout of the election.
Yeah.
That's not the real lawn mowing per se yet.
No, in a way they've kind of mowed the lawn of everybody, I think.
And they used a lawnmower called the TV.
Nice trim job.
Yeah.
I mean, look what it's done to some of our younger peers.
So let's think of, let's think of what it's done to some younger subgenius.
GC.
Subgenie who have been foolish enough to go back and look at the evil lawn mower.
I mean, many have taken the vow and many have agreed to.
Oh, they do it for kicks.
They think that they get, they think it's fun to go back and, and see before the, then
see what, what it was that took out their math.
Yeah.
They don't know what they're messing with though.
They joined the army.
You don't need too much math except for if there's like a hundred thousand people.
Yeah.
And if there's a hundred other guys and maybe just two of you, you should know to hold your
hands up.
Both of them, two of them.
I don't know.
Well, they always, they need one guy who does math and they need one guy who can read and
they need one guy that can sing and one that can speak English and push buttons on a, on
a telephone radio comm set and a whole bunch of guys that can run into the face of oncoming
fire and bombs and so forth.
You know, it's funny.
Wow.
And they're always filming while filming how those guys are always the ones who are spared.
And the guy who plays the guitar and sings it with the cigar cigarette sticking out of
his mouth, make it kind of makes his eye wrinkle up at the same time.
And he sings about what it's like back home.
Always dies.
I've always, that would be you that if you were in the war movie, you'd be that guy,
right?
Right.
The, the rockets would misfire and go all the way to North Carolina and hit the barracks
where I was masturbating.
Man.
I don't know.
Well, the way off cars.
Yep.
That's the way I feel.
That's why I'm a subgenius, I guess.
Now see, I feel, I feel more like the guy that would, that would run into the recruitment
offerings, office saying, I want to sign up.
I want to kill.
And they make you a computer operator in Hawaii.
Why do they do that?
It's so frustrating.
Catch a 22.
Gotcha 22.
Well, it's 23 now.
Yep.
I think it's going to stay 23 for a long time.
Actually, it was 23 when I was a kid.
Now it's up to 27 or something, I think.
I think it's catch 27.
It's a chicken cacciatore, too.
Yeah.
23 was actually Nimwald Hornbanger's number in the restaurant at the end of the table, wasn't it?
I don't remember that particular sit book.
Sit book.
The man with the Sly Slav unit that used to mow the lawns before but was nicer.
Dr. Benway?
Dr. Dobbs?
Dr. Howard?
Dr. Fine?
The guy at the end of the universe.
Dr. Bob?
Bob Bobalina?
How do you do, ladies and gentlemen?
This is Bob.
Bob.
Back in his hometown of Cleveland.
I'll answer the door.
I'll see who's at the door.
Yes, sir.
Come in.
Look, this might be Bob.
Who's Bob?
Bob!
Well, Bob, it's certainly a pleasure having you drop in to see me.
Well, Bob, I want you to meet Bob.
Oh, hiya, Bob.
And say, Bob, I meant to tell you.
Hey, wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
First, I want you to meet Bob.
Well, I'm certainly glad to know you, Bob, and I'm particularly glad you're here because
the quartet's going to be here in a minute.
We should do a number dedicated to Cleveland.
We haven't got much time, so let's hear the number.
Okay, hit it, boys.
I'm so embarrassed in front of Bob.
Come in.
Come in, girls.
I want you to meet Bob.
Bob, I want you to meet Bob.
Bob, why are you staring at the girls like that?
Well, hello, Bob.
Very good, Bob.
Very good.
Bob, why don't you go out to dinner?
Yes, Bob.
Hey, Bob, here's one of your boys, Bob.
Hello, Bob.
Who, Bob?
Bob, what are you really doing here in Cleveland?
Well, where is he now?
Well, if the Republicans can't decide on anybody, he may be our next president.
What the fuck?
We got a one-track mind, friends.
Really?
And it's got a B on either end of the track and just a big zero all the way for a thousand miles.
It's like a big, long train that just goes,
until it gets to the end.
It goes,
and that's it, baby.
That's what it's all about.
Yep.
Close quotes.
Being in the Bob zone.
Dave, you notice I've just let you, I've let us just jabber on the air for this, almost
this whole hour.
Once I finally got figured out the, I never did figure out the phone thing.
It just worked by accident.
Now, when I quit trying.
It was a miracle.
It suddenly worked.
Are your hands still frozen?
Yeah.
I mean, have you been able to work?
Yeah, that's why I can't.
Well, that's the thing.
I can't push the CD play button anyway.
Can you still satisfy the princess when necessary?
That's up to her.
Oh, I didn't know you had that kind of relationship.
Yeah.
No, I don't know.
She's, yeah, it's, well, she's a princess, man.
Think about it.
Nobody could satisfy her but her, I guess.
Yeah.
No, she can't be satisfied in the way that a normal mundane thinks, you know, a pro thinks of things.
She's not satisfied.
She's gonna be satisfied.
There's always going to be some little thing that's not quite royal enough.
That's how you know they're royalty.
Hmm.
Us proles wouldn't even notice the kind of stuff that royalty is hyper allergic to.
So am I supposed to tell one of those aristocrats jokes right now?
No.
Please don't.
Well, you heard one of those aristocrats jokes.
I heard all of them.
Did you see the movie of that?
No, I didn't.
No.
I was misfortunate and was left in a drainage ditch.
Yeah, that's right.
No.
People with orange skin.
But when I grew to be a man, which I had actually two growths coming out.
One was a man and one was a swollen foot.
Well, but it looked kind of man-like.
And also, they're supposed to be orange.
It added to my power amongst the people.
I grew to become their king later.
Later, I became an elder statesman.
And then I just left the place.
I can't remember where I started.
A lot of primitive cultures do treat their dwarves and deformed people as mystic beings.
They gave me things to smoke.
They gave me chicken sandwiches and lovely senoritas would comb my few hairs.
Yeah, see, they figured since you were so different that you were chosen or singled out by the god.
Absolutely.
You were special to the gods.
That's why you had such a large and such a small brain, you know.
Yeah.
I can say those words at the same time without chewing gum or something.
I know what's going on there.
I can feel it.
I've noticed.
Have you noticed what the walls look like right now?
No, I haven't.
Okay, I'm sending vibrations not only of peace and Saturnalia.
But I'm...
Slaternalia.
We call it out here.
I'm also sending...
Geez, what is this stuff?
It's got a long chemical name.
Hydro...
I don't know.
So you're sending peace and vibes of hydrocyanidic acid or something?
It must be the hydrocyanidic acid that makes the drippiness of the walls.
It's tetrahydrocyanide of some kind.
I don't know.
I guess there's ten of them or four or something.
I see.
Well, I'm sorry.
I'm really honored that you're sending vibes like that our way.
Well, you can use it as you will.
You know, you can have a great radio show, have a wonderful life.
Well, I'm going to have a college online course, a media-packed online course in practical
subgeniusness and hardcore dobsism.
Wow.
In November and December.
That's why I've been...
I've actually done a whole lot of shows ahead of time.
So that I won't have to...
I don't have to work on them while I'm being a Professor Stang.
Do you have to prepare a meat package or do you...
Yeah.
I have to have...
In fact, there's a syllabus and prospectus you can look at on maybelogic.org.
It's the people that did the Robert Anton Wilson movie called Maybe Logic based on his
thought processes, which are maybe logic.
And they have this academy.
They have this academy online with a bunch of hipster types like, you know, are you
serious or not?
And who else?
I don't know.
Various wise men and show-offy academic...
And wise crackers.
Wise crackers.
And they called me up and said, hey, you want to do some kind of a course?
And I said, yeah, I'll teach people how to run their own cult.
I will share this secret profit-making formula.
With you.
And the secret wisdom.
The secret teachings of all ages.
That is...
That's beautiful.
And do you have many students?
Have they enrolled yet?
I don't know if there are any new timers or old agers.
I don't...
I don't even...
I haven't checked that out.
That's why I mention it.
So as to make sure that maybe someday there will be some.
Because that starts in November at maybelogic.org.
There's also maybelogic.com, which is strictly...
It's strictly about the Robert Anton Wilson movie and brain cell.
Yes.
He has a full collection of brain cells, actually.
Who, Wilson?
Yeah.
Well, like most of us, he probably started out with such a thing.
I thought Timothy Leary had a lot of brain cells left for somebody in his situation.
Yeah, but they were misshapen.
Well, you should talk.
Oh, I'm not...
I'm not casting...
Your brain cell...
You've...
I...
Dave only has one brain cell.
I don't have a brain cell, but it's shaped like a totem pole.
Well, thank God.
At least it has a rhythmic feeling to it.
I was just saying that Mr. Leary, in his case, had hundreds of thousands of brain cells that
were all shaped like little...
little shards of glass.
I thought they were paisleys.
But you could smoke them.
Anyway, Dave, you have to go now.
And I'm going to shut off everything except the tapes, because you're listening to the
Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slice.
And for more information about Subgenius and all of that, all of it, really all of everything...
Or to be relieved of information.
To be relieved of anything, check out subgenius.com if you really want to know.
The music in the background, by the way, this whole time has been from Stephen Kent and
Transmission, Oil and Water CD.
He...
He blows one of those didgeridoo things.
Among others.
But anyway, Dave, we have to go now.
Bye.
Okay, goodbye.
We love you.
No.
Don't get his hopes up like that, Princess Sweet.
Bye.
I don't know.
Oh, look at your hedges.