That sire, there is no more money.
We gotta get some money.
That dirty purgish harker, that flat-footed...
You people think we just improvise this stuff from the keyboard and stuff.
But no, we have to rehearse this stuff all week long.
And we have to ride this bicycle treadmill that runs the electric generators that make the power spew out over the airwaves,
out into the invisible air where your ears pick up the rare material and strange music that this station plays,
such as the Hour of Slash.
Stuck in an availability room somewhere deep beneath the surface of the earth,
the Reverend Ivan Stang, made of pure cream cheese and three pieces of toilet paper,
has rebuilt his entire personality from a foam-like mug distributed by the Church of the Subgenius
through the...
I'm screaming into this paper cup as much as I can and it's just not getting out of this underground...
Welcome to the Hour of...
Nothing.
Slash.
We had such a good cue there, I thought maybe you could use that.
No, I don't care about... I don't care about creative...
No, Dad.
That's all you need to buy.
For this station!
There's only one thing that matters between birth and death and that's donating to this station to keep it on.
This station will be hauled off dead in a casket tomorrow if they can't pay their electrical bills.
And homes in California will have to quit writing those scripts because no one will be able to pay them $75,000 a year to do this show.
It costs money to do these kinds of elaborate productions, friends.
But friends, it's not real money.
It's the kind of money that you...
You need to make your life twirl around like a little twinkie stick.
It's the kind of money they give you in outer space.
The kind of money from deep, deep in the cosmos.
It's not paper money.
Nothing as flaccid and tricky.
Nothing as...
No, it's just...
No, we're talking about psychotronic subphonic money.
The kind that'll bring you a long-sleeved shirt.
But, Sire, there is no more money.
We gotta get some money.
That dirty, perky, sharkaback, flacky, walkie-talkie!
They're here!
One minute.
It's showtime, my friends.
Time for the subgenius hour and a half.
A show that dare not even exist.
Join us now as we rocket away out of normal time into showtime.
Phenomenal.
It's mysterious, evil, spooky, eerie, creepy, wacky, kooky, fun.
The subgenius hour of slacking.
And here we got brains the whole operation.
Faster signal goes up near the satellite.
We bump it out all over the world.
Pretty fancy, huh?
Not too big.
Thank you for letting us out.
You're buying time.
Time, friends.
Because Mr. Moneybags, he's paying a salary.
A salary?
$200 a week.
And consequently, I can't preach against drinking because his icebox is full of beer.
I hope he's talking about you, my friend.
WCSB, then.
I can't preach against cigarettes because they all smoke.
Schwartz.
I have to let him out for 15 minutes between Sunday school and worship service,
so they can go out and light up a Chesterfield or something.
And what kind did Jesus smoke, my friend?
It's time to open your heart.
Close your mind and zip your lips and bend over.
Because you're about to receive.
I see you.
The word about...
Yes, friends.
You're normally such a slacker.
It's the first time you've heard of him.
Yeah, that's right.
All four of us.
Bone Bendover and his sister Eileen.
Oh, yes, friends.
Tonight's show is an exclusive to WCSB only.
Only no other station on the planet will be allowed to play this show.
Most stations don't even want to play any of our shows, but some stations do.
And they do not qualify, friends.
Although we'll probably put it on the podcast as alternate hour of Slack number 1437B or something.
Friends, this show is just for you.
Just for you.
No, we don't care if you're a dues-paying subgenius.
We're not out to save you.
It's a gift.
It's our gift to you.
The gift of asking you to gift us your money.
Because it is pledge drive time.
You knew that.
Oh, before I forget, friends, there are photographs of the famous WCSB Halloween.
Halloween Masquerade Ball up on the internet now.
Godzilla was there.
Huh?
Godzilla was there in person.
And, in fact, he caused the lights to go out just before the headlining band, the Dead Milkman, came on.
But it was still a great party nonetheless.
A great party.
And you can...
If you were unlucky enough...
If you were lucky enough to get there late and were just in the crowd going around several blocks in the rain...
Or, for that matter, if you were stranded...
If you got there just before the lights went out and, therefore, didn't really see any of the cool costumes...
Princess Wee's photographs are on my website or, rather, the Church of the Subgenius website.
And I'm going to tell you how to find them at subgenius.com.
There's a...
On the bar at the top, events is one of the choices.
Well, you can click on that events thing and it'll tell you about things that happened and X Day coming up.
But...
Also, at the top of that page, it says there's a link to past devivals, events of yore.
Click on that.
Then, look down the list of things.
Don't be distracted by the ones offering nudity.
Like X Day and Starwood.
And find the 2012 WCSB Halloween Masked Great Ball link and click on that.
And then, when you're looking at 2012, just reach up to the top in that link and change the 2 in 2012.
The last 2.
Well, the last one letter, 2.
Change 2012 to 2013.
And then refresh that page and you'll be looking at a week or two ago.
So, at the...
NYWCC.org.
I wish I could be that cool.
Except for the deaf ones like me.
People who work hard for nothing.
Nothing, friends.
Don't you wish you could be cool like a WCSB DJ and work for nothing?
I wish I could be that cool.
You can. You can be that cool. All you have to do is give all your money to the station.
But what number do I call to give out all my money to the station?
Well, even if you're only given $15, because that's all you make per week, you would call 687-6900.
Yes, friends, you'll hear that number again in the 216 area code.
And we welcome people from all lands and planets.
216-687-6900.
I hardly need to dwell upon the occult significance of that phone number.
We're not numerology nuts around here.
But we are nuts, friends, because we've been giving this show away for free, like crazy people.
And you can be a crazy person, too, by giving everything away for free.
Like your money.
To the station. 687-6900.
That's all you have to do.
You don't have to actually spend the money now.
You'll just be promising.
And we'll hound you to your grave until you whip it out.
That sounds so easy.
It would be easy.
How easy and convenient that would be.
You can do it just by picking up that phone and calling 687-6900.
You could talk to Dr. Sinister.
He's manning the phones right now.
He's standing by, patiently awaiting your call.
Your call.
Rattling.
Rattling his can of pennies.
See, the station left the traditional can of three pennies here.
We all have a little can of pennies.
It's our three-penny opera for the night.
Yes, we're beggars.
And we're choosers.
We chose you, personally, the one listening right now, to be a listener to this station.
Because we knew that you had taste.
Not necessarily good, but special taste.
The kind of taste that makes you just...
But to you, the corporate radio stuff just doesn't taste good.
Because you know it was hand-picked by a computer with no hands.
We have hands here, most of us.
And ears.
And obviously, mouths.
Flapping lips.
The tongue of the preacher.
That music in the background, by the way, is by the Flying Ryan Brothers.
An unsigned and unsignable band.
From Chicago area.
Reverend Jimmy Ryan is one of the brothers.
And they're good for pledge drive music.
Now, I'm going to get into berating moochers.
This is a special moochers show.
How to be a moochers.
October was moochers month, friends.
And...
But before, I show you what you're like.
If you don't know.
I pledge.
By example.
I wanted to mention that we have...
You don't just, you know, get the good feeling of supporting one of the few really independent radio stations left.
You get stuff.
For instance, for just $15.
A mere $15.
You can get your choice of a cool skull pennant.
With the WCSB logo.
A black winter hat.
Which is cool because it's black.
And it has WCSB logo.
Two ashtrays.
So if I was in the snow and I had the black hat on, I wouldn't get lost.
Right.
You'd be able to find your hat.
And that's yourself underneath the hat.
From a great distance.
Even in a Cleveland snowstorm.
And there's pint glasses too.
That's a different $15 donation.
But then you'd have something to drink while you were...
Finding yourself.
Yes.
And the black hat does have some glimmers of white in the logo.
So it's pure black.
Now for $20.
You can get not only the WCSB premiums I'm about to list off.
But the subgenius premium.
For $20 and up.
The Bob Dobbs Head Cloisonne Pin.
A metal pin.
In color.
With colored polished paint.
And a little bit of black metal.
Those are really nice looking.
Nickel and other fine minerals.
Yeah.
They're slick looking.
They're a $30 value.
Which we're letting you have for $20 pledge.
Plus...
Hold on.
Are you going crazy?
Well, yes.
I went crazy a long time ago.
And that's what this show is all about.
And that's why this is the only station that would let us do this show.
Because it's kind of crazy too.
They're so crazy that for that $20 you get not only the Bob Dobbs Cloisonne Pin.
But a black ceramic travel mug.
Or a green casual cap with the logo on it.
Or a black mesh trucker's cap.
Or, and this is my favorite because I don't know what it looks like.
The black and gray pom pom hat.
Oh, those are great.
I don't even know what a pom pom hat is.
It's a winter hat with a pom pom on the top.
Like elves wear?
Yes, like elves.
Just like elves wear.
Friends, that's magical.
Magically delicious.
It's pom pomi.
For $25 there's all manner of t-shirts.
Which your call answerer, Dr. Sinister, can describe.
Or engraved pint glass and a bottle of the beer I'm about to describe.
Or a Stein.
But see, if I was a WCSB listener.
And I was going to spend $25 to save the station.
And get the phones fixed.
So that Lonesome Cowboy Dave could be heard properly.
Yeah.
I would donate the $25 and ask for the twin pack of Schwarz beer.
Which is a beer brewed by WCSB personnel.
And we tasted this year's batch at that masquerade ball.
Mmm.
And then we tasted it some more.
And then we tasted another one.
And then we tasted another large pitcher.
And then we pitched flat over on our faces.
Because it's that good, friends.
It's like chocolate cake that gets you drunk.
That's exactly right.
It's like having a pet you can make sweet love to, friends.
That's how good the WCSB Schwarz beer is.
Speaking of dark things.
Yes.
Dr. Dark himself has made a donation.
Dr. Dark, that cheap guy.
Why, he's never, ever donated anything to the church before.
And yet, look, friends, how the luck plane is moving.
But he has been a good friend to this station.
And you should be just like Dr. Dark.
And call us up at 216-687-6900.
Every little bit counts.
We have many ways of saying thank you.
Yeah, I think you know what that means, ladies.
And boys.
What else here?
The $35 pledge gets you the bubble umbrella.
It's clear.
So you can see through it.
And they can see you.
They can see how dry you are.
They're going to be jealous.
For $40, there's the silver lunch pail, which looks just like the football thing that the president has handcuffed to him.
Even when he's asleep.
And making sweet, sweet love to his wife.
He's got that football.
And you can have one like it.
That's the silver lunch pail.
With a WCSB logo instead of a logo that says USA bomb launch codes or whatnot.
And then for $50, you get hoodies or four pint glasses.
But there usually aren't subgeniuses with $50.
If there is one, prove it.
Prove it.
I'll bet you don't even have 50 bucks, do you?
Listener X911C.
You don't.
That's sitting out there in Mentor.
You're barely hearing this thing in your car radio.
You don't even have 50 bucks to spare on WCSBD.
I believe there are devoted listeners that have not just 50 but 100, even $150.
Well, good for them because I am less account than they are and have not that $50 in my pocket.
Because I spent it on blank CDs that are involved in making this show.
So, friends, you know, you really do have to whip it out because you don't want to be like the people that have been emailing me all month.
Or the ones leaving messages on my answer machine, which I'm going to play soon.
This is a sad letter here from Brian.
First he wrote and said, if I join forces with the church of subgenius, will I be allowed to choose my own ministerial name?
Can I call myself Reverend?
Reverend whatever if I so choose.
Well, duh.
I wrote him back politely and said, yes, hardly anybody uses their human street name.
Incidentally, the name Reverend Funny Name is taken.
Well, he wrote back and said, right now I am broke.
No, actually he wrote back and said, you may call me at this such and such number.
And then he sent another email that said, or this number.
I was like, why should I call this guy?
He goes, right now I am broke.
But I believe that I ought to receive a free order.
I have been in the ordination since I have come up with such a fantastic ordination name.
Would you like to know what it is?
No.
This fact of my inspired name, says the moocher, and the fact that I have no money is the justification behind my asking this boon of you.
Can we please talk about it?
Thanking you in advance for your time, which the time I gave him was the time it took to copy and paste.
The fact that we have a thousand inspired names at hand and no money is the justification behind our asking this boon of you.
Send $35 to WCSB.
That's not what I said.
But get this, the guy couldn't leave it at that.
Listen to this from my M.
This is a
I want to talk about joining forces with you.
However, I'm broke because I'm so sad.
I have no money, but I hope we can talk about it.
And I emailed as well.
Thank you so much.
Bye bye.
Hi, Brian Birmingham again.
Just trying on this different number I found on the internet.
Apparently it's the same.
Anyway, I'd like to join, but I'm broke.
Slack, Slack, Slack.
And I emailed too.
Thanks a lot.
Bye bye.
Yes, he did email too.
That's correct.
One other thing.
This is Brian again.
Sorry if it's a bother.
It is.
If it means anything to you, I was born and raised in Dallas, Texas.
It doesn't.
And lived up here in Boston.
I have for about four years.
But I remember from way back in the day, so to speak, the subgenius.
Thanks for your time.
Bye bye.
You're not welcome.
Hi, my name is Brian.
I called last week also.
Never received any reply.
What?
Please return my call at 630221.
I feel your earliest convenience.
I'd like to talk to you about becoming ordained, but I'm tenuous.
Thank you.
Bye.
Hi.
This is Brian again.
I'll tell you my reason for asking for this.
He's persistent.
I've been inspired with a really strong passion.
cool organization name that I'd like to choose.
And as well, I have no money.
So I've emailed as well as called a couple of times.
Please call me if you can.
I'd love to talk with you about this.
And I'm from Dallas.
Born and raised.
So thank you so much.
He really shouldn't have said anything about...
Oh, bye.
Shouldn't have said anything about being from Dallas, really.
Hi, Brian Bullock again.
I understand your position about my mysterious stranger
that I am.
Sent you an email earlier today.
And I am looking forward to your reply.
So God bless you.
Bye-bye.
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, now, you see, just as you were too busy
to type out an informative email about why,
besides your funny name,
we should give you something for nothing,
I, likewise, am too busy to take phone calls
from mysterious strangers.
Unless they're donating to this station.
Also, I'm partially deaf and avoid phones.
So good luck.
We hear the Flying Spaghetti Monster folks are recruiting
and the Discordians have always offered
all their services for free.
They may have a greater need for funny names than we do.
So maybe you should write them.
Friends, everybody's a critic
and nobody's calling 216-687-6900.
That's 687-6900.
Besides, Dr.
Well, I can tell you who else did.
Oh, we actually got another call.
We got Reverend Wombat himself.
No!
Yes.
From Australia.
Actually, he's living in California nowadays.
Well, poor guy.
Well, or rich.
He stood up, though.
He stood up for CSB,
even though he lives thousands of miles away.
All right.
Friends, that's what the Internet is all about.
That's why it exists.
And here's another.
Letter we got from somebody
who wants to tell us our business.
Hello, Ivan Stang.
Please use torrents to distribute
the Hour of Slack MP3s and Og Vorbis.
This will cut down on web hosting costs.
You worry me with all this Apple nonsense talk.
I think the young Stangs are steering you
in the wrong direction.
Yosemite Sam crying about being out of money.
As for jobs, good riddance
to that.
Egotistical, non-techie POS.
Style and design loser.
Well, I'm sorry that Steve Jobs
suddenly upset this listener so greatly
that he had to go into a spontaneous rant
about that style and design loser.
I have a theory about people
who judge others on their operating system
or their favorite bands
or their...
clothes they wear
or their haircuts.
And again, the Flying Spaghetti Monster people
are hiring.
Well, I made fun of that guy
and I said, wow, you must be really broke
if you hate Apple that much
or something like that.
And he goes, actually, I'm not broke
because I don't buy Apple products.
I was kind of picturing Yosemite Sam
bitching about being broke.
Did Jobs ever send Dobbs 30 bucks?
Or in the old days, 20 bucks?
$25?
I don't remember the 25.
I did.
Jobs was about all look and feel
instead of bang for the buck.
I have an Asus I bought at the mall for $350.
It has a 10.1 inch touchscreen
with good sized keyboard.
Fast as ever.
I'm running hacked Windows 8.1
with a lot of conspiracy apps scrapped from it.
I don't even have Java loaded.
Man, I'm so jealous.
So I suggested he try Mensa.org.
I said, that's for super aware folks like you.
Dumbasses aren't even allowed.
So you won't be worried by Apple users like me there.
And maybe they can put your diplomatic skills
to use as well.
And he wrote back and said,
yeah, but the church of the subgenius Bobby pin
already gets me laid.
Huge Robert Anton Wilson fan.
End of transmission.
So friends, don't you wish you were me?
Sitting there checking your snares, basically.
I go out and check the snares every morning
and see what animals we've caught.
If we've caught any $35 membership or any WCSB.
There's even some compliments.
And this is what we get, friends.
But we want to thank those of you who have been
and who aren't like that and did call
to make us know that you care.
Speaking of callers, I'm kind of half expecting Dave.
But that's not blinking, is it?
No.
That was just, see friends?
See, that just doesn't cut it.
That don't cut it.
That don't cut no eyes.
For $15 pledge, we also have some interesting things.
That y'all may like.
Because you're weird.
This is for weirdo obscure people.
When was the last time you played a VHS tape?
Well, if you're like me, that happens every couple of months.
There's always something that only exists on VHS.
And you're sharing it with others on YouTube.
Or you just dug it out because it's the only copy of...
Submit to me.
And submit to me now by Richard Kern that still exists.
But we have a few old VHS tapes around here.
Almost all horror and sci-fi.
And I wrote down the names of just a few.
There's a horror movie called Cupid.
I've never seen it, but it sounds really scary.
Yeah.
A horror movie about Cupid.
Mm-hmm.
Reptilian.
Not to be confused with...
Reptilicus.
I'm sure it's terrible, but the name is interesting.
The She-Creature.
And Not of This Earth.
And Earth vs. the Spider.
And the sad thing is, I bet they're all the sci-fi channel remakes
and not the original AIP Earth vs. the Spider.
She-Creature.
Or Not of This Earth.
Probably.
Um...
However, there's only one movie of the great H.G. Wells classic,
Things to Come.
And you can get a VHS tape of that fabulous...
It really is a cool movie.
A little dated.
I believe the future for them is 1985.
And World War II is still going on.
But you want to see Things to Come
if you aren't listening to this station and this show.
They also have books.
And I read down the list of books,
but I didn't see too much that would be interesting to subgeniuses,
but two for $20.
And both that I saw, the two I would get,
were Marvel Comics collections.
One was X-Men Origins,
and the other one was called Girl Comics.
Mmm...
Princess, what do you think that means?
I don't know.
It's Marvel, so would it be like She-Hulk?
Or would it be...
Romance stuff?
Did they ever do...
I don't even know.
I really don't know.
Friends, we're old.
Girl Comics.
We're old and we don't really know.
Although we did watch a...
Oh, no, this wasn't Marvel.
It was DC, of all things.
We saw the movie of The Dark Knight Returns.
Not the Christopher Nolan movies,
but an animated movie done from Frank Moore's original graphic novel
from the 80s,
the one that started that whole Batman cycle.
With the Tim Burton movies,
and then the really, really bad ones,
and then the pretty good ones.
That all started with The Dark Knight Returns,
a graphic novel.
And the station doesn't have that,
and I don't care.
I don't even care.
Well, you know who does care?
Who?
Reverend Sigmund Void cares.
And he has put his money where his mouth was,
and he donated it to WCSB.
What a guy!
All right, Sigmund.
Now, see, that's a...
What kind of a name is that?
His name is Void.
You know, I've known some good Voids and some bad Voids.
Yes!
Sigmund Void.
But friends, now see,
you can get your name shouted out on the radio
and be famous as a good person
instead of famous as a jerk.
Because we've made a couple of jerks famous.
What other jerks have I got queued up there?
Let's see.
Poor Josh.
Oh, here's a good jerk.
But, um, let me make sure I'm doing this right.
This will be track five.
Okay.
How about this jerk, friends?
Dear friends, this is your dear pastor,
Reverend Ivan Stang, calling out to you
from the depths of my heart.
And I can see so many of you sitting there hovering
by your phones, waiting.
Now, the phones are ringing here.
We're doing great.
This time we got all the beautiful girls,
the mighty studliest of genius ministers sitting here.
Actually, friends, that wasn't the jerk I meant.
That sounded like some little punk boy,
Reverend Ivan Stang, as a baby.
Yeah, that was probably me at that Dallas station
that kicked us out because we made fun of liberals one time.
Actually, that wasn't the reason.
But, oh, here's the jerk I was thinking of,
the jerk on my message machine.
The concept of a clear message could also preclude
that the call was about anything, I suppose,
even though the message was itself very, very clear.
And to the point, or to no point,
and yet, what was the message?
What was it about?
I don't know.
Princess Wee, do you know?
Do you care?
Do you know who that was?
It sounded like Reverend Philodrumas.
It was Dr. Philodrumas.
He was, he's one of the jerks that leaves
non-sequitur messages filling up my phone.
What happened to Dave?
You know, Dave was going to try to call tonight,
even though our phones are crazy.
Maybe his phones got crazy, too.
I don't know.
I don't know what's going on here.
Friends, I'm going to play some music for you
for a little while to give my lips a rest from flapping.
We're not getting quite the number and amounts
that we were dreaming of,
which were involved a lot more zeros
than we're seeing so far.
So remember the number to call 687-6900
in the Cleveland area,
or if you're out of town,
you can call the
That's area code 216-687-6900.
The music in the background has been
the Flyin' Ryan bros,
but I'm going to play a live tune
by my old favorite band,
the Rainmakers,
called Reckoning Day,
because that's what day this is,
Reckoning Day.
Reckoning Day
Well, I was thinking about Abraham Lincoln
And the enemies of the truth
But I could not tell
Kennedy from John Wilkes Booth
Out of my way
How do I get on Reckoning Day?
And I feel like picking a fight
With anybody who claims they're right
All the preacher men, the politicians
All the critics and the things they write
Out of my way
Hard rockin' on Reckoning Day
And this is a call to arms
This is a call to hands
This is a call to the buzzers
And the minds of the people
In every land
Out of my way
Hard rockin' on Reckoning Day
Reckoning Day
Put the money in the mattress
Put your penis in a couch
Reckoning Day
Is this the place?
Are these it?
For the donation?
Dave, Dave, you made it.
Dave?
Yes.
I wonder if this is the place
where they make the donation
to WCSB in Greenbridge.
You got it.
You got the right number.
And then they go to the 687-6900?
That's the one they call to make the gift.
Ah, do they have to put the piece of cheese
or a little baby onion
or perhaps a bouquet or a wrapper?
Or a...
Yes.
Yes, to all the above.
Ribbon on the gift?
Yes, all the above.
And then the stuff you've mentioned and more.
The piece of onion and the lilac blossom.
Lilac.
I like lilac.
It's good for incompetence.
I have bad incompetence.
My incompetence all went down my britches
and I'm all bad on incompetence.
Incompetence and incompetence.
I heard it.
I heard it and it leaked out.
You sound like you are losing your marbles in one sweaty poop.
I'm losing my precious bodily fluids.
We were set on auto-loads.
No, Manric.
We're on auto-loads.
Auto-loads.
I think we are living right now.
I'm auto-loading.
Now loading.
And that's going to be very, very painful.
Need the right shoes.
Size six.
Too big.
No more feet for you.
Secret code 687-6900.
That's the super cool code, kids.
Super cool code?
That's where the super cool kids call.
687-6900.
No, is that cool?
They revel out some stupid stuff that makes no difference to anyone.
And it's too much.
It becomes a cult favorite among everyone.
Funny how that happens.
How does that happen, man?
Some stuff dribbles out and somebody picks it up and turns it into a whole religion.
Yeah.
The state of Utah used to be a tropical jungle and look at it now.
Yep.
And it's all because of the dribble.
Mm-hmm.
That's the only thing.
I think that's why.
And you know who?
Howard Hughes was involved, too.
The guy when he had breast reduction surgery in the early days.
Charlie and Charlie Egmore.
It's the wave of the future.
Yep.
We got a pledge from APO Stacey.
What a mystery.
It is.
That's APO Stacey.
You know, it's funny.
By coincidence, that name.
I wonder if anyone's ever told her that when you put those letters out, it almost looks
like it says apostasy.
Yeah.
Because that's those little marks you put over a word to make it mean there's more than
one, right?
Don't think that she hasn't thought of these things.
Or when something belongs to something, you say, if it's the dog's bowl, you say, that's
its bowl.
You put it and the apostasy and then the S, and that means that it's ... And that's the
same when you go herd.
No, you've got that backwards.
You go her, apostasy, S, and his, H-I, apostasy, S.
It is just an H-I-C-S.
And that shows you're not ignorant.
But thank you, apostasy, Reverend APO Stacey.
Miss Torrey, how she manages to put up with this show.
It is a Miss Torrey.
Quite a Miss Torrey.
Obviously, APO Stacey is ... I'm sorry.
I just ... Of course that is.
That's one of the third laws of rhetorical knowledge.
It's a myth.
It's being able to baffle people with names like that.
And of course, he figured it out quite easily because it's perfectly plain to see.
I'm sorry I took so much time agreeing with you.
Dave, did you know that when you join the Church of the Subgenius or donate to WCSB,
you have the right to make up any funny name for yourself and a title?
But that's the only way you can do that, is to join the Church of the Subgenius or pledge
to WCSB, or both.
Or both would be best.
But pledge to CSB is of the utmost importance because of the community service wonderful
WCSB provides to its native inhabitants.
Included on the left, Miss Laurence Lottie Seals, our program mistress, kind of a little
joke among some of the guys down in the basement who've never been released.
Yeah, yeah.
Uh-oh.
Six, seven, 6,900.
Six, eight, seven, 6,900.
And that is the number to call because what you're seeing right now is not only useful
for everything in your home.
If you make a $20 pledge, Stangy, tell them what they'll get with a $20 pledge.
A $20 pledge, you get a Subgenius button with the Bob Cloy's and A pen on it.
It's a metal, a Dobbs head pen that looks like it would be a cuff link.
In fact, we had cuff links, but they're sold out.
And friends, you can have that WCSB, I mean that Subgenius slick-looking metal pen, multicolored
Dobbs head as seen in the Subgenius.com catalog under new crap.
Completely faithful here.
Yes.
And, or, well actually and, you can get one of the black ceramic travel mug, the green
casual cap, black Trepiker's cap, or the pom-pom hat, all with WCSB logo.
By the way, did I mention that?
Remember, the WCSB logo on the T-shirts is done like the Star Wars logo.
And so it looks like as if you think it says Star Wars, and then it turns out it's WCSB,
it's just in that same funny Star Wars font.
It's tricky that way.
That's knowing.
It fakes you out.
Didn't you have some peacenik Star Wars shirt, Princess Wee?
Stop Wars.
Yes, I have a Stop Wars.
Yes, and it was written in Star Wars.
Stop Wars.
logo talk
font.
That's a mid-
in the 1970s
type of
computer font.
Didn't you understand
from the dawn of
history there have always been people
trying to get a font on everyone else?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I know that.
My personal favorite
font, Dave,
is Times Roman.
So is mine.
It looks like textbooks
fonts.
Very similar to paperbacks.
Yes.
And newspapers.
You can say the most absurd
things, but when it's in Times Roman
font, it looks like
it's important and true.
And believable.
Whereas if you use Helvetica or some
modern sans serif
font or
God forbid, comics
font,
then you're just
well, that just seems
silly and frivolous.
It doesn't carry the weight
of
your Times Roman.
Much less
your Times Roman bold.
Especially, you know, if you're
middle, if you're not only your
third nostril, but the very, very
middle point of your third
nostril is in point of east,
you're going to have a hard time
arguing with Jelly Belly and some of the
big other fat guys around the table.
Because they have infinite
wisdom. And we just have a little
team spec until we call
687-6900
and pledge $20 right now.
That's why I'm so fond
of that font.
Me too.
Really, friends, we do actually
the station needs the money
so that
people like me won't have to
like
get a real job.
No. Yeah.
Yeah. And see, here's the thing.
I want to be able to
give all my money away.
I want to be so rich that I
give everything away and have
nothing. And that'll make me feel like
a richer man. See?
But I can't do that unless you help, friends.
You have to start that
process by being
the richest one of all
and being the first to give us all
your money. Well,
and then we'll be so rich
we can give it all back
to everybody. We're already doing
that. We just haven't been paid for it.
See?
But we're not redistributing
the wealth or redistributing
the wealth or anything.
Any kind of political notion like
that. It's just a way
of you showing that you're really
freaking wonderful.
Just because you support community
radio like WCSB,
which is Cleveland State's eye
on the world, when you really think about the programs
available,
and especially the hour
of storm.
Well, you know, when I'm out on the street,
and I'm sure this is true of every
listener, if somebody
walks up to me and says, hello, sir,
I'd like to, well, if
they're not wearing a WCSB t-shirt
or a Bob shirt, I'm not going to give them
the time of day. Whereas
obviously, the exact
opposite is. If they're
wearing a CSB t-shirt or
cap, they walk up and go,
sir, could I try? And I go, I'll try.
Where do I sign?
You have telegraphed coolness.
How much do you want? How high do you want me to jump?
Instantly. I'm your friend.
You put that limousine
cab driver's hat on right away,
and you say, step right in, sir. Anything you demand.
You can keep your heart's desire.
And did you know that if you
come to the WCSB
open house to
pick up your pledge premium, or to
actually hand
over your hard-earned cash,
here at the station, you can actually come to
the station November 22nd, that's
Kennedy Day, or November
24th. Princess
Wee and I will be here
some of the time.
And Dr. Sinister will be
here. We met many of the famous
listeners of the Dr. Sinister show
who are allowed to call in. Yes, and
lots of interesting people come.
Right. We even meet their parents
sometimes. Yes. Because they have
to be brought here.
Speaking of Kennedy, we sound like
Marilyn Monroe lately.
Who? Princess Wee sounds like
Marilyn Monroe? Yeah, lately
she sounds like Marilyn Monroe. What's up with that?
I'm sorry, when you said Kennedy,
she said, I don't know.
Happy birthday, Mr.
President.
Mr. High Scribe.
I mean...
Happy birthday, Mr.
Hyde. Happy
birthday to you. You're all
Dorigo. Reverend
Hyde. That's Reverend Hyde,
sir. It's Mr.
Jekyll. You can call me Mr. Jekyll
or Reverend Hyde.
Yes, please.
Friends, 687-6900.
We're not just...
This isn't just a big J-O.
That's not all it is,
is what I'm saying. No, actually,
the transmitter here
is aging and needs to be
replaced, and the needles
that play the vinyl that
you're so lucky to get to hear,
those needles are
expensive.
Is that your way of making fun of me
and my hearing problems and my
aging? No, not at all.
No, not at all.
Absolutely not. You mean you're serious? The transmitter
really does need to be
replaced? Absolutely.
I don't make these things up.
And friends, as you've heard over
the weeks, the phone lines have
needed repair, although strangely enough,
tonight it seems like it's fine.
And our monitor that allows
us to see if anyone is breaking into
our cars. That's all
so broken. Oh my gosh, that is.
Somebody could be broken into the car.
Everything. So we need donations
so we can continue to go forward
and not be stumbling.
Now she sounds like Emma
Watson. That's that girl in
Harry Potter. I caught the Brit from her.
Talk like she does in that movie
This is the End. Yeah, only don't
make the same smelly sounds.
Give me all of your drinks
or I'll kill you.
Something like that. She's a
pretty good in This is the End.
But you still need the breast
implant, Stang. Let's just face it.
I'm serious. No kidding.
You're an email kind of guy. You can't even go
into Monty Python.
No, you
gotta sound like Stang kind of almost
doing a girl.
I wish I was a
girly just like my dear
mama.
Bye-bye.
And we are.
I'm sorry. I just love that song so much.
It makes me want to call
687-6900.
Be a lumberjack.
Be out there among the mighty giant
fur of the Scots pine and rip
off your shirt and have some weird
guys with funny looking hats behind you
and stuff like that. Smell that sweat.
It's pledged. $50. Hell with
this $20 stuff. Why be
a yammy-pammy wuss?
Send $50 and make sure the
station stays on the air because you need to.
It needs to be on the air
almost as much as the Reverend Ivan Stang
needs a podium to pull
his forceps from.
I don't need an audience, friends.
All I need is a podium.
We don't care if you listen.
We just want to be able to broadcast.
No, wait. That doesn't sound right.
But we will give you an audience with a high
E-pop anytime you
pop in 89.3
on your radio dial.
That's right.
You will be glad you did.
You can talk to Bob anytime.
You can be alone with Bob.
You can come right to the station
at Open House and be alone
with Bob.
You can psychotronically fondle Bob
in your own membranes of your own
We can put you
in a room and say
Okay, you're alone with
Bob in here now.
You're with Bob and yet you're alone.
How about them apples?
Schmapple. Credlapple.
Schmedlapple.
See, you've got your
cultural parents.
Paralloxism right there.
It's a paradox.
How can you be alone when you're in two places
at once with Bob?
And that's why you've got to call
right now because if you don't call right now
you're condemned to an
inferior form of lifestyle.
Let's face it, friends.
If you haven't contributed
to an alternative
or a station that
really, really needs funding because
it gets support from the public and you
listen every damn
stinking day, 24 hours
a day, you're like
and you're enjoying
the music and you're listening to the crazy stuff
and everything like that.
What do you do to support it?
Absolutely nothing.
What he said.
What he's saying.
I'm sorry.
It makes WCSB have that
taken for granted feel.
We want to know that you
care.
We want to know that you tear.
Tear.
Right down the middle.
We want to know if your foreskin
is strong enough
to withstand all the terrible
incredible tortures
arranged for you in advance
and so forth
and things like that.
I don't like it
when I see you putting
those rubber gloves on.
Princess was laughing
because she heard me say those words
to a doctor.
It makes him quite nervous
when she slaps on the plastic gloves.
When you want to have
your areas explored like that,
you don't go to an anthropologist,
you go to an endocrinologist.
A cop.
Because a cop will do it at a moment's notice
at the drop of a pant.
They'll give you a cavity search for free.
Friends, and this station wants
to do that for you
if you'll just let us.
But you have to enable us.
You can't always
get what you won't.
But you can be
what you won't.
As Dr. Philo Drummond said,
you can be what you won't.
You won't really be
a great
philosophical millionaire
that gives money to people
but you can still be one
by giving everything
you can spare
to WCSB.
It's not...
Who do you think Bob cares the most about?
The rich man who could give
a million dollars but only gave
$25,000 or the little old lady
who gave her last?
That's right. He don't care about
that rich guy or the little old lady.
He cares about the Neanderthal man
because he's your ancestor
and mine.
I thought he cared about the WCSB listeners
most of all.
The Neanderthal men
and ladies who listen to WCSB.
Right.
The proto-men and women.
The ur-beings.
Right.
The Yetinsani. The Yetis.
You know, the sons of Bigfoot.
The daughters of the Sasquatch.
Dang, shut up.
The WCSB listeners.
The sub-bean listeners.
Bob's people.
People who speak Bob's language.
I refuse any kind of credit or money
for...
from Cro-Manyans either.
If they want to send us $20 in,
they can send one of those
little...
What's the thing hanging from your
medulla oblongata?
The tea chain.
You can have a tea chain.
You feel a...
Read your mind
and then list everything wrong with you
in plain sight.
Yeah, the beeper.
Things don't be like the beeper.
Be like the leaper.
And Mr. Lemur.
And all the other great subgeniuses.
Be like Spring-Heeled Jack.
Don't be like Slumpin' Eddie.
Don't be like
Tiny Mumblebunt.
Be like Spring-Heeled Jack
springing over the telephone lines
to call
687-6900
and 216-SERY-CODE.
Don't be like those people
who leave messages
on my machine
that I play on this show
to make fun of them.
No, they want to make the gift
so they can have that great feeling
that they get
when you make a gift
and they know
that they helped
keep the radio station going.
And they do a purchase too.
I like it when they make purchases.
How about...
They can make a purchase.
They can purchase a donation.
You've got a very hip relative and stuff.
Why not give them a gift,
a Christmas gift
or holiday greetings gift card
of...
Of...
Of WCSB.
And then they'll wonder
what the hell...
They'll be forced to listen
to the station
just to see what it's like.
Literally forced.
Where is this...
In chains
and those weird manacles and stuff.
That's why they call it
forced skin.
Exactly.
It forces your skin
to peel off your ears
so you can hear
the greatest stations.
To reassign itself
to different locations
that you can get anywhere
while you're riding
in the elephant,
the tubes,
or the...
You know,
any of the great conventions
we have in Cleveland right now
in the year 2073.
I didn't know...
Send in that call.
I didn't even...
Call.
I didn't either.
67...
6900.
The number to call.
to talk to Dave.
Yeah, man.
You can call...
Dave is on the phone lines
right now.
You can call him
and talk to him
and give him
all your expensive information.
And that consists of...
Hey.
I love this.
It is 11-12 in Japan right now
and people are having arguments
and two-fakes
and people getting divorced
and everything
because of some religious holiday
in the Shinjuku Island
or something.
And their jello is melting too.
Exactly.
Because of Fukushima.
Fukushima.
And nobody really cares.
Right.
Unless you really could care.
If you want to really care,
you could send in 687...
I mean, you could call 687-6900
and pledge at least something.
Pledge.
To WCSB 89.3 Cleveland
and be glad you did
and you will.
There's no cure
for a lot of the malaise
that's going around.
It's very, very deep.
It's in our culture.
Things are not as good
as they used to be.
Whatever the hell that means.
But somehow,
if you pledge now,
from the bottom
of the smelly parts
of your heart,
you will in some way
be rewarded.
Absolutely.
By yourself.
You'll have a lasting lift.
That's our favorite part
of your heart too.
I mean,
you might as well
pull your pants down
or up
whichever way they have to go
when it's important
right now
in anticipation
of the delight
and the deep
aromatic pleasures
you will enjoy
of making a simple
common pledge.
Yes,
my little darling.
It turns me on
when Dave talks like that.
Me too.
Yeah.
It's quite easy
to control them
with this electric wrench.
Oh, no!
No!
I feel the spirit.
The spirit
is moving in Cleveland tonight.
And, uh,
but, you know,
this,
it's,
the time goes by so fast.
We started a couple
of minutes late.
And what,
what's old Dr. Sinister
doing in there?
Is he in the pocket?
Oh, he's taking pledges
from all of your
generous,
generous listeners.
Oh, finally.
Oh, now they want
to get a call.
In the very last few seconds
they call in
so that they can
get a shout-out.
Okay,
Reverend Funny Name
donated $5.
Whoa!
That's really big
of you,
Reverend Funny Name.
No, but seriously.
Thank you,
Reverend Funny Name.
Thank you, thank you.
Reverend Funny Name
only had $4.50
when he pledged that.
We have a shout-out
approaching.
I can see that look
on his face.
Question.
Something about
Dobbshead Pen?
Yeah,
Dobbshead Pledge and A-Pen
is the $20.00.
$20.00 and up
subgenius premium.
All right,
thank you.
The cloisonne.
Back to Reverend
Chocolate Velvet.
Oh!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
She's listening in
from, I think,
Colorado then.
You see?
Wow.
Maybe a CSB.
Here we bitch about
the Transmittal.
Oh,
preternatural
existence.
She's warmed
all of our hearts.
We actually had a
we have a
Chocolate Velvet rant
that Princess We
is planning to read
on the
air.
And this wasn't
the night to do it,
obviously.
We had it ready
for a couple of nights
ago, but it wasn't
quite ready
because it was
full of cussing.
And you have to be
very careful about that
because we're not
in safe hold.
Nope.
We're in prime time,
baby.
Prime time.
But we're not for long
because it's time for
Friends,
you're listening to
WCSB Cleveland,
just in case you wondered.
We have to say that
near the top of the hour
no matter what.
And we want to,
we'd like to.
We'd love to.
And we want to be able
to keep saying that.
And, uh,
well, Dave,
I'm going to have to
let you go.
Do we ever really
have to let him go?
the phones are working again.
We can, maybe we can do
a for real show next week.
Yeah.
Let's do that, kid.
Let's do that.
We'll have the party
right here.
Yeah.
I, uh,
forgot that I
had to,
yeah, yeah, okay.
Thank you, Dave.
Thank you,
Reverend King.
Thank you, Dave.
And thank you
to the listeners
who, uh,
who still will
call in.
And I'm going to put on
some more hits
from my answer machine.
Our friend Bernard
has started calling in again.
And I'll just let him
explain all about
the conspiracy.
This goes on for 16 minutes,
by the way.
Oh, my.
The Bernard sequence.
So, and that is...
We'll see you next time.
Praise God.
Well, uh,
I...
Yeah.
Hello, this is me, Bernard.
I'd just like to know,
how does,
how does a subgenius
deal with humans
who represent
a human society
that I don't believe in anymore
and show that it's,
you know,
has,
has turned into
something you can't believe in anymore
in which the breakdown of,
of the psyche,
the breakdown of ethics,
of the human race,
of the culture,
is, is, is,
is subject to everyone,
including my mother.
And I talk to my mother
and, you know,
she don't think rationally
when I tell her about things
in which she try to help.
But at the same time,
she's like,
making it an inconvenience
when I tell her I'm not at home here.
And she says I need to make myself at home
after I told...
even after I told her
what I'm...
what I've been dealing
and going through here.
PHONE RINGS
Hello, this is me, Bernard.
A second message.
I just hope that the UFOs that have been appearing from 2006 up to 2010 will return again and
take me off this world that has gone bankrupt mentally, ethically, with people who represent
mainstream society regardless of who they are, whether they are your relatives or troublesome
humans who represent so-called mainstream society that has been taken over by the beast
element of humanity now.
I just hope that the UFOs, the aliens will come back and take me off this world in which
you can't live in anymore because of what's going on in every level with the humans, the
breakdown of ethics, the psyche, with those who represent mainstream society and they're
not thinking rationally.
Hello, this is Nathaniel.
I'd like to leave a message.
You know, not that serious, just a cabal of co-conspirators who are trying to get me
out to get me and one of them, you know, that Andre Francis, who died, but he's still
trying to bother me and threaten me saying he's going to beat my ass or something like
that outside.
But, you know, I'm trying to save myself for the aliens to come and take me away from here,
but they still, they think like they're trying to close in on me with their targeting against
me.
And I'm trying to save myself.
I'm trying to save myself.
Yeah, I'm trying to save myself.
Hello, this is Nathaniel.
You know, it seems like a bankruptcy of the 20th century end time with these troublesome
humans that are targeting me.
They're making it really hard to wait for the aliens to come and rescue me.
W...C...A...S...B...CLEVELAND!
E helper but not you.
Thank you.