All right, Doctor, go ahead.
First paranoia.
Intense.
Terrible.
Unreasoning terror.
What then?
Then...
I see.
You know that one man is responsible for it all.
Yes.
The man who lied when the truth would have cleared you.
Phase two.
The man who called himself...
Bob.
He's in an induced psychotic state.
Uncontrollably happy.
He's at large somewhere in the city,
and is potentially dangerous to others and to himself.
Stand by.
Shut up.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Zero.
Stand by.
Just shut up.
In any event, I'd better be with you to administer the antidote.
This will cut short the effect and...
Shut up.
...greatly ease any after effects.
Bob?
From PR News in Washington, I'm an oddball because I'm hacking government computer systems.
President Donald Trump did indeed interfere in the 2016 presidential election.
President Trump is a poot-poot-pootin'.
Trump now says he spoke.
Poot-poot-pootin'.
Trump also says...
...aggressively.
Last week, the president's intelligence chief warned that, quote,
PR News, Washington, again.
President Trump must have something on President Trump.
In other news, many scientists are alarmed by the Major League Stars for the All-Star Game.
Star Washington, star Texas, star teenager.
So low.
PR News has been declining in popularity, especially among younger fans.
Low.
So low.
Doctors agree.
Low.
On Capitol Hill, the Republican leadership says...
Trump.
The Dow 55-25-19.
Around Jupiter, the team of astronomers say...
This is PR.
Everyone who came into town noticed the stench from the Libyan fart plaza.
It was a
A
FAIL disabled
operation,
Hold
Call
hope
home out.
delicatessen that would routinely pay off health inspectors rather than address their frequent
problems with vermin infestations. This restaurant chain is known for its legendary endless buffet,
breakfast, lunch, and dinner. First found with the food by the buffet, the dinners are down for a minute.
The tourists that long ago stopped frequenting the Giant Tiger Thrift Center on East Boleskin Road
mainly because of the rude staff, but also because most items were long past their expiration dates
and the cashier smelled like feta cheese. Curiously, the Fart Plaza had been conceived as a way to boost
the local economy, and bonds had been issued to pay for a series of radio ads promoting its ostensible benefits.
Fires were printed and stapled on to utility poles in neighboring communities as far away as
Carson City by a one-legged man who tried too hard not to look like Gary Cooper.
Once the failure of this divulgative gambit became apparent to local taxpayers,
a recall initiative was announced and the subsequent election led to unprecedented
voter turnout and the ascendancy of a swarm of poisonous Asian paper hornets to the city council.
After a brief
The ex-mayor and his business associates were all placed in shackles and frog-marched to
the gravel pits on the edge of town, then forced at knife point into a reservoir filled
with buffalo pits.
The Libyan Fart Plaza was repurposed as a community recreation center, and its neon
sign was sold to an itinerant junk dealer, who eventually resold it on eBay to an unsuccessful
performance artist in Pickle Gap, Arkansas.
Nowadays, the Fart Plaza is a popular tourist attraction in the state of Florida, and is
a popular tourist attraction in the state of Florida.
Folks don't talk much about it anymore, and the new mayor is focused on attracting more
big-box retail to the town's perimeter, boosting city revenues, and securing funding for the
proposed Sip Milton Male Lactation Research Facility.
And that was...
Insert band name here.
The Rudy Schwartz Project, on the album entitled, Take Me in Your Arms and Sing to Me Like Dick
Powell.
It's safe to say, thank you, Lee Murr.
And now, Lee Murr.
What about Bob?
I gave him the torch right in the eye.
The hell?
That's Bob, right?
No!
Bob!
What about Bob?
Don't stop!
Bob!
Or anybody who watched here.
Whoever Default could come back up if he weren't here.
There's plenty of time.
He's a Default.
But instead of...
You can Default him.
I'm going to go down for a moment.
Bye.
Down, down, down, down, down.
Great, we've even got that.
Yay!
It goes up here.
As random non-radio events are occurring, I know it's a podcast.
Well, no, this is a radio, this is a broadcast radio show, we're just pre-recording it.
Shows how much I don't know.
It's also a podcast.
Podcasts are, you hear the cuss words on the internet version, you see, but I actually
mail our slot to five stations.
So if you have time, some of this will be edited.
And they can't have any cussing.
Yeah.
So I have to cut the cussing.
I've had to pronounce your name very carefully because of that.
Well, everybody says the obvious joke, of course.
Right.
It's just an opportunity to make the new shtick, the old shtick about my name.
I know, I know.
It's like having a funny name.
There are other things to talk about than my favorite subject, myself.
I'm going to get the, well, one beautiful dame wants me to help her with something.
But we're going to, we need to get away from the mic for that.
Are you making radio still?
Yeah.
Well, it's recording.
I don't know if we're making radio.
You can sit down.
We could do Geek Acres.
I'll do Geek Acres with you.
Let me see.
Let me see if I can find both things.
Boy, Susie, it sure would be great if you were sitting here.
Yeah.
You'd look so much better than Philo.
Yeah, it would be.
Your beard is so much nicer than Philo's.
I did want to ask one more little question.
About when open mic performances are allowed.
I was told I could probably take the warning sign down there, sarcasm prohibited.
I could take that with a grain of morphine because, I mean, my material runs on high octane
sarcasm from beginning to end.
Well, maybe it's a sarcastic sign.
There is truth in some sarcasm.
I can only hope.
Thank you.
Snarkasm?
Snarkasm, that's a new one.
I've never heard that one.
Where's that been all our lives?
Snarkasm, yeah.
It's yours.
Snarkasm?
That's nasty.
That's nasty and irritating.
It's even worse than sarcasm, which we use all the time.
Y'all listeners, this is our slight number 1,700-something.
And Princess, we and I have a song.
Yes, we have a song to present for you.
Just for you.
Let's see.
I think I know how to start.
Let's start.
Head acres is no place.
No, no, no.
No, no.
Oh, sorry.
Mr. Douglas is first.
Okay, sorry, Mr. Douglas.
Go ahead.
Let's start from the beginning.
Dun, dun, dun, dun, dun.
Dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun.
Dun, dun.
Head acres is no place to be.
Dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun.
Conjure is not for me.
Bad jobs that like to break my back.
I'm going to X-Day and letting Bob get me slack.
Dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun.
Starwood is where I'd rather frop.
All night drumming, let it never stop.
I just adore the pagans best.
Stang, I love you, but X-Day is a sausage fest.
Dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun.
Dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun.
The slack.
Da-da-da-da-da.
Kick back.
Na-na-na-na.
The weed.
Na-na-na-na-na.
The mead.
Why not do both?
And take off all our clothes.
Geek Acres, we are there.
Na-na-na-na.
Woo!
Even better than Donald Trump's.
Princess, we tried to do that solo last year.
Yes, I did.
But without proper preparation.
Right.
It was not ready to be launched.
Till now.
I did about three-fourths of Buddy the Dog Opera.
No.
By myself.
Out of order.
In little bits and pieces.
But I told Reverend Angry Larry about it.
And he said, you know, if you had given me
an Android.
From the Computer Core on the pre- отwinter pizza divulge nightcee
И, I give up my part for the job.
If I don't sit rather see, how could I stand?
I am the…
time that we've tried to do that, everyone's kind of patiently waiting for us to stop.
But Susie has a kindly heart.
Yes.
She's very charitable.
I love it.
Well, it's really, really terrible.
And we worked hard at that.
We're good at that.
It's terrible and wonderful at the same time because it's about our buddy.
And X-Day.
And peeing.
Yeah.
And slack.
Because that's what Buddy gives us.
Slack and lots of it.
I haven't heard from our dog sitter.
But then I haven't had phone service.
We haven't either of us had phone service.
Yeah, so if anybody hears from the dog sitter, we're eager to...
Yes, let us know if Gabriel calls, please.
Yeah.
Or Buddy.
Or Claudia.
Claudia.
So, I really have to get up and go.
I have to go to the bathroom.
I just realized.
Well, I guess the radio show is drawing to a close then because I can't carry it alone.
And there's no one else up here to do radio show with, so I guess we're drawing to a close.
You want to hold it while I run water through it?
Can I hold it while you run water through it?
Yeah.
Uh-oh, Mr. Sister's staggering this way.
Racine, can you help him get that to us?
This is the names from the guest book.
The guest book stories.
Can you read it?
Day three.
It's been a long week of fish tips.
These...
Fighting these things.
It's been a long week of fighting these things.
They have taken our neighbors and drugged them through the woods.
Dragged them through the woods from behind far into the hills.
We never saw them again.
They came back.
And as they came, we were all in the loft.
I look out the window and saw one gnawing on a human arm.
Now, most of the words in this are spelled phonetically.
A human eye gasped and we sat in silence as the cabin shook of screams and pounding from the outside.
But then it stoked.
Silence grew.
Bang!
This went on for some like minutes.
Then it stoked.
All of us scared.
We looked outside.
The weird creature were...
Creatures.
Apostrophe.
Were what seemed like dead or dead.
We looked from where the shots were fired.
It came from the...
A rail?
It was the castle people.
We were saved.
This was in the guestbook?
This was in the guestbook where I'm staying at the castle.
Good Lord, man!
It's like an illiterate 12 year old is writing a diary of a zombie apocalypse.
Yeah, that's brilliant.
But it's not a zombie apocalypse.
Well, it's very realistic looking because the spelling and handwriting are just psychotically bad.
And it's pencil, which helps.
In pants-le?
Yeah, in pants.
I couldn't live my life without sharing that with the substitute.
Well, thank you so very much.
We find these.
Mr. Sister, it's just one of those found manuscripts.
Found magazine would like that one.
That's really, really appropriate for them.
Yes.
And then of course I found this, but you can't possibly translate that.
Although that's the way I feel right now.
Okay, the tetheress...
Let me see.
Oh, it's just scribbles.
Just insane scribbling on a page.
That's the way he feels.
That's how you feel right now?
That's how I feel right now.
Oh, he did try one tiny inhalation of that allergy, the allergy stuff that was going around.
So that might explain part of that.
The bad hot wine might be the other part.
The bad allergy stuff?
See, friends, radio listening audience, if you get your stomach operated on to where it's down about the size of your thumb,
you can get drunk really fast.
Fast on very little alcohol.
And then you're straight again in a fairly short time.
So you can do it again.
And I might.
Why not?
It's next day.
The world ends and you may die.
You may die.
You're going to take me back to sit me down.
Just watch your step on the way and yes, use that tripod as a walking stick.
It's lucky that I don't have to pee right now or I would need assistance.
Oh, it's too late.
That is really fortunate.
Look down.
The little puddle is growing for the whole time you stand there talking.
He thinks he doesn't need.
I have about 15 cc's left.
And I'll be able to, you know, sit on the Supreme Court.
Ah.
You could do it now.
They'd never notice.
Mr. Sister could sit on the Supreme Court right now?
Yes.
And he's drunk as a lord.
As they say.
I see.
He would fit right in these days.
That's the biggest bunch of obvious, visually obvious alcoholics I've ever seen.
It takes one to know one.
No, seriously.
I mean, geez, look at Kavanaugh.
That guy is, he's got every earmark.
Every single earmark.
I'm not, no judge.
I'm not making judgments.
I've known many people who are professional alcoholics and were quite fortunate.
Functional in all their jobs and relationships.
But they usually don't last all that long.
I'll drink to that.
You're talking about alcoholics, but we got these drinks at the same time.
Look at them.
And yours is finished.
And I'm just starting.
And you're cackling.
And I'm jabbering.
So there you go.
Well, the drinking helps with the cackling.
It's a cackle assist.
Cackle fruit.
No, that's eggs.
That's eggs.
Right.
That's cackle fruit is eggs.
Okay.
Well, where's Lonesome Cowboy Dave?
When does he call in?
Who's going to play Dave?
Anyone can sound like Lonesome Cowboy Dave for a little while.
Oh, I'm sorry.
There you go.
That was my best Lonesome Cowboy Dave imitation.
St. Joyce has just presented me with this.
However, it was explained to me what they are, and I don't recall.
So I'm going to need one of the pressures once they have registered.
Saunter up here and explain what this is.
Princess Wee is holding a cloth rabbit, a stylized bunny rabbit with the big colorful ... The
inside of the ears is colorful.
Psychedelic ears.
The rest of it's black.
The inside of the ears are psychedelic.
And it's a little bit of a ...
But, you're going to give me a little listen to it.
We're all so used to go on 멋있 EMINEM PO siguables.
We can't hear you.
It's a feel-good rabbit.
Phil-good Rabbit!
You don't have to make me feel demeaned.
A feel-good rabbit, he said.
I feel terrible the way he told me that.
As soon as I got it, I had to put it on my chest and feel it.
And it made me feel good.
So these are well designed.
This is a feel good rabbit.
As opposed to the feel well pills that make you feel pain very well.
Have a feel, Reverend Stang.
See if it doesn't make you feel good.
No.
It doesn't?
It's just an inert object to me.
It doesn't feel...
It's a sweet, warm, feel good rabbit.
These make me feel pain.
Oh.
So they're the complement to the feel good rabbit.
Here's the feel pain shoes and the feel good rabbit.
These are diametric opposites.
Who wants the feel pain?
The pain shoes.
Oh, see.
Oh, now they all want that.
Nobody wants the feel good rabbit.
Are these for the auction, sir?
Oh, my.
The pain shoes.
Someone should probably enjoy using these.
Well, it's an acquired taste, they say.
And now this.
Boy, that got me out of that one quick.
All right.
Bye.
Ever since I've been about it.
From PR News in Washington, I'm accompanied only by Vladimir Putin.
And overall, his responses continue to raise questions about what he said today at the White House,
which is no to answering questions about.
What he said today at the White House, which is no questions about this presidential election in Finland.
Um, uh, uh, but, uh, uh, uh, uh.
The remains of the White House may be returned home in the coming weeks.
Researchers have the degenerative brain disease that can only be diagnosed after listening to PR News in Washington.
It's safe to say, thank you, Lee Murr.
And now this.
Oh, Lee Murr.
I miss him.
Uh, he's still doing stuff and you can hear his new PR news and titles and things on our Slack.
Bless him.
Yeah, yeah, you can find him on archive.com.
He uploads about a hundred new things every three months or so.
He's still in Colorado, uh, living like a hermit with dogs.
Kind of like me.
I went to see him about 12 years ago.
Unbelievable.
Mr. Sistar is explaining that he made a pilgrimage to Colorado to meet the elusive Mr. Fernandin Andy Lee Murr.
Just to meet him.
The famous artist and, uh, sound collage.
And, uh, yeah, he's another old weird man like so many of us.
Quite the unique individual as I recall the report from Dr. Mr. Sistar.
Did he have that pencil in his eye like he does in all his pictures?
No.
No?
Apparently not.
He has some medical conditions which might be comparable.
Oh, he has some medical conditions like the pulsating tumor thing with the mouth and little eye on it.
On his cheek.
Yeah.
Yeah, that always.
I never wanted to bring that up with him, you know, because some people are sensitive.
Uh, he might not be able to afford to have it removed and maybe it talks to him, you know.
It does drool.
yeah sum
Yeah a PER зр
RR Rr
Rr
I'm sorry.
Ah, yes, dear friends.
And that was the death of a Muto.
We were listening
to there from the first of the
recent Godzilla movies.
Just great sound effects in that movie.
Like
avant-garde music. And we'll be
hearing some more avant-garde
music. A live recording
from 22X Day Drill
with Reverend Angry Larry
and the strange
Reverend X, or maybe
just X.
The unknown.
New guy. Kind of a winged eel
fingerling. Like
sound.
And the recording is incredibly
accurate. It's how it really sounded
that night. Complete with live jerks
talking over the music.
Loud live jerks.
But first,
more tedious early
subgenius internet
history.
I can't
hear you. Reverend
Mr. Doctor, I
Doctor Mr. Sister is saying that there is
a road. Say it again.
And low.
And a group
called Sputum.
Sputum was one of Dr.
Dinosaur's organizations.
It was to fight spam
on the Usenet group,
Alt.Slack.
Okay, now I remember Enloe.
He was a pink boy who thought
we were going to be impressed by pictures of
him and his muscle car
and his muscle shirt.
And he had a, oh, and he was
a detective.
It was one of the
so obviously this whole
built up persona.
And he'd picked the wrong people
to impress with that particular
persona.
It was probably, it was his idea
of impressing girls
but it was not
the kind of thing that would actually
impress much of anybody except
other guys like him
that might fall
for that. Can you show me?
How to get a muscle car
and girls?
And no, he can't.
But Bob can.
Bob teaches you
to give up and
get slack and sex
and whatever else you want.
As soon as you quit trying so hard
what you really need will come to you
and eventually you get what you want.
Or die.
Okay, later.
Oh, thank you.
What's up?
She said it was our lighter.
See ya.
Okay, see ya.
It's really nice to see you guys.
Oh, there you go.
I'll be here.
Alright.
10 a.m.
Okay.
Good job.
Oh, it sank.
Google pay me.
Now we've got form skalage.
You know,
But practicing
bloomin' later in the whole place.
It's like a
fucking weird moment.
One moment later .
. profits.
guitar solo
Yeah!
There, there, there.
Again.
Play it again, yeah, play it again.
Yeah, because I played a wrong note there in the third...
Yeah, that was a bad note.
I hated that note.
That didn't sound like...
He wrecked it, man!
That was...
Yeah, it takes all kinds.
That's what people do.
There's only one what?
He's not seeing double vision, he's seeing single vision from looking at two people.
Thank you for keeping us up on your inebriation level.
Don't give him any LSD, friends.
Or LDS, or any of those things.
I can't get high because I feel that way all the time.
Ah.
Maybe...
He did try a little vape thing.
Did he?
Just one.
Uh-huh.
He didn't even cough.
Didn't do anything, did it?
No.
Didn't do anything.
No, because he is drugs.
He is, he's...
Mr. Sister is drugs.
He is drugs.
He's like Salvador Dali.
Right.
I don't need drugs, I am drugs.
Or as Mr. Leahy said, Philo quoted,
I am the liquor.
Randy.
I could probably do Lonesome Cowboy Dave right now.
For a little while.
Yeah, you can do, anybody can do Lonesome Cowboy Dave for a little while.
I bet Lonesome Cowboy Dave wishes somebody would do him.
Yes, I bet he does too.
Yeah, it's been a long time since anybody did Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
But the harder part...
In the good way.
Would be for I, Dr. Mr. Sister just getting from his seat to the stage.
Yeah, we're not going to bring the mic over to you.
So it's not going to happen.
Look at that.
He said, oh my God, he's going to do it.
Somebody call the ambulance.
Mr. Sister's off the hook.
Call the hospital.
Do you need to go to the hospital?
No.
Look, he's carefully using support to get up the steps.
See, he's not as drunk as we thought he was.
He's actually taking the measure of holding on.
Yeah, I knew that was coming.
Yes, I'm so concerned about global warming.
Oh, he made it.
And I think Trump is destroying America.
There's a sign there that says no sarcasm.
He's not being sarcastic.
I mean, that's the thing.
He's being sarcastic.
It's okay, Mr. Sister.
I actually understand why people voted for that.
I wish AOC had a much better whatever she's got than she's got.
AOC?
She's got pretty good tips and ass.
That's what I'll say.
Yeah, that's all I care about in politics.
That's not all you care about.
Yeah, hell yeah.
And if that's all I had to do, I would vote for Sanders every day.
Well, he doesn't have any kind of TNA going on.
That's pathetic.
Maybe when he was younger, he had nice, you know.
Well, what?
We all did.
Oh, my God.
I just realized I had him potted down.
You still couldn't hear him.
Well, I kept on putting the microphone closer and closer to his mouth, but I couldn't hear anything.
Well, at least we know where that feedback was coming from.
All right.
That's good to know.
Now it's back.
It's Mike 3.
It's just horrible that we all eat meat.
I mean, Jesus.
Is this what Democrats say?
Are you saying the things that the liberals say?
You know, it's the part of what I hear.
Exactly.
What you hear is you hear what liberals say according to the people you're listening to.
How many times have you heard me, an actual real-life libtard, say any of that stuff?
Never.
No, that's true.
I'm a meat-eating, shotgun-toting libtard on a goat farm with a dog.
I've always thought of you as a centipede.
I'm a centrist.
Actually, I'm a Maoist radical.
How's that?
Power to the people, baby.
I'm a Black Panther.
I only believe about half of what I say.
I only believe about a third of what you say.
So I've got to do one better.
One third?
Well, that's okay.
Some fraction better.
But really, you know, I mean, he had, what, tanks on the Fourth of July?
I mean, it's like, don't we respect the English?
I mean, they...
Well, it's a great image, tanks going through D.C.
Think of the stock footage that'll make.
And then the conspiracy turned against its own people in this stock footage from the
deadly Fourth of July, the day the plague was released in Washington, D.C.
That's where it hadn't made it to the news yet, that somebody released that vial with
that virus.
I was...
Right there, right in front of Trump.
And of course, he was busy reading his...
Well, no, he didn't really have to read cue cards.
He just spews right on the top of his head.
You could tell his exact level of education from that.
What a spouter.
I...
As Paul Mavridis said, oh, he's the most subgenius president, but not in the good way.
I think he's much too old to be president because he must be close to my age.
But you're not old, Mr. Sister
Where are the young people?
What?
The 35-year-old
He's not old
He's older than me
And I'm old as dirt
My mother is old
She's going to be 90 years old next month
And she's old, okay?
That's old
You guys are young
He's going to be 80
I'm going to be
Who's going to be 80?
If we're lucky
Yeah
Yeah, if we're lucky
Right
If we're lucky
What did I do?
Just sneak up on stage here
And take over a microphone?
Yeah
I believe that is what you did
We invited you up here
Man, well, thank you
I mean, hey
That's what I'm here for, I guess
You know?
Well, we knew you were really, really drunk
And we thought, you know
Who knows what's going to come
This could be good
This could be real good
You never know
Why not?
We're up for any program
Dear Mr. President
I want you to know
I am deeper than you
Listen and learn
My heart is a chapel
My head is a steeple
My arms are the people
And the people now yearn
I stand for the midget
I stand for the negro
I stand for the engine
All the way
All hopped up on booze
I stand for the Jap
And I stand for the beaner
I stand, yes I do
For the Christ-killing Jew
And I stand for the dyke
And I stand for the retard
I stand for the Chinaman
Washing my socks
I stand for the bum
And the pimp
And the bugger
And the cripple that lives
On my street in the box
To conclude, Mr. President
I'm not at all hesitant
To tell you, I think
The first lady's a fox
Her husband, the jerk-off
Has ruined my country
That's all I know
For today
Sincerely, D. Cox
Thank you, Dewey Cox
That's from his great biopic
Walk Hard
And now we'll go back
To the Wotan Doctor Band
Of 22X Day
Including Reverend Angry Larry
And X
But I took no photos
That night
So I don't know
Who was on drums
Or who else was there
Really, or
Anyway, but
They're doing
Free Bird
Hey, you just don't know music
I'm sorry, sir
I can't believe it
This is my day
Play it again
But play it right this time
Dr. Drummond
Would you get down
On your hands and knees
And be a mic stand for me?
For the next half hour
On these ugly gravel rocks
Because I need a mic stand
To put this mic on
If I put it up on stage
It would be all distorted
Here's a mic stand
But it's not big enough
I need a bigger
Usually I use a chair
Look, but it has two glasses in it
That doesn't matter
It needs to be bigger
Look
Hold on
Here comes the challenge
One two three
Two three
And the music
Will not stop
It's a busy world
This might never be
So just
That no one
Who is
In need
Of what
You're
guitar solo
I drank all my booze.
I hate when that happens.
I got one again.
Hey, was that Freebird?
That was Freebird, yes.
At least that's what the drunk guy who lives downstairs said.
I mean, I've got every show original elements on hard drives and CDs and stuff,
but finding them is hard.
That was a lot of hard drives ago.
I know, that's a lot of work.
Just think of all the petroleum she dyed.
I think that's plastic products.
They're not plastic.
They're mostly metal and rare toxic minerals that come only from China and Africa and other communists.
CDs?
What?
No, no, no, I'm talking about hard drives.
Oh, oh, oh, yeah.
Oh, God, people laugh at you if you admit that you store things on optical media.
My son actually said to me,
Dad, I think you're the last guy I know that still stores things.
I think you're the last guy I know that still stores things on optical media.
And I thought to myself,
Yeah, well, when the big thermonuclear pulse wipes out the entire internet,
I'll still have all my stuff.
Because it's on optical media.
Just don't expose it to a hydrogen bomb blast in the open.
That'll wipe it out.
But who cares?
You wouldn't be around to listen to it anyway.
Yeah.
If they have all of their electronics fried,
they'd rather be dead after that.
Well, their whole body is just an exempted gas.
And they have to be the one to be the fart catcher, so to speak.
No, that's only if you're on the internet too much.
That won't happen to me.
I still walk my dogs.
Speaking of which, when we end the show, we can walk the dogs again.
Hint, hint.
See, I'm just like the dogs now.
We're going to go out.
This might be a good juncture.
I must remove myself, but I shall return.
Uh-oh.
I think I know what that means.
It means she's coming back.
And that doesn't mean anything.
Silence will heal my wounds.
That's about time when we prove 67 seconds.
That's getting us there in less than a second.
There we go.
Thank you.
Thanks for watching!
Thank you, psycho skeletons, for that song called I'm Immune to Rabies.
Well, Princess, we've done our duet.
You know, we should learn let's duet.
Yes, we should.
From the Walk Harder to Do It cubs story.
In ways that make us feel good.
That would get everybody all turned on.
Yes.
So I'm tired. Let's go.
Bye.
Bye-yi-yi-yi.
Hello, Darlene
Hello, Mr. Cox
You ready to sing one?
I'm always ready
All right
In my dreams you're blowing me
Some kisses
That's one of my favorite things to do
You and I could go down in history
That's what I'm praying to do with you
Let's do it
In ways that make us feel good
And make that sacred sound
Put two and two together
Perfect harmony we've found
We know it's only natural
Let's do it
I'm gonna beat off all my demons
That's what love and Jesus are about
Looking in your eyes
I start believing
Let's bring this whisper to a shout
Let's do it
In ways that make us feel good
And make that sacred sound
Put two and two together
Perfect harmony we've found
We know it's only natural
Let's do it
Did I hear you sighing?
What are you implying?
You look a little tired
The music got me wired
You're pretty good looking
Boy, we're really cooking now
I just wanna make out what you're saying
Read my lips, it's what you're looking for
Here I am, I'm sneaking up behind you
You can always come in my back door
Let's duet in ways that make us feel good
Let's duet and make that sacred sound
Put two and two together, perfect harmony we've found
We know it's only natural, of course it's only natural
God knows it's only natural, of course it's only natural
Let's duet
So maybe I'll see you there
We can go down, down, down
Different stations at subgenius.com
Also, books, CDs, t-shirts, and of course, Bob
And now, in some markets
Now for the internet only, X-rated bonus feature
I went shopping at Heinen's the other day
So did she
Heinen's is a...
A Cleveland, very small chain, I guess
I love to shop at Heinen's
Yeah, well it's got a funny name, Heinen's
Sounds like Heine
Hehehe
Heine
I forgot to bring anything to the X-Data
Yeah, the auction
I feel kinda bad about that, but
Yeah, get out of here, you lousy, you two-bit cheapskate
Hey, I, um
Previously, I was in a shop
For six years, I brought all my nice DVDs
Yeah
But, uh, I finally ended up with, uh
These are the ones I wanna keep
You know, total crap, but
Well, I kept my most obscure LPs
And we donated the rest to, uh
Weirdsville Records in Detroit
You can find all my old Hendrix albums there
They're scratched all to hell, dude
Dude, but
You can find all of our old albums there
We were cleaning, we were moving last year
And, uh, I know there must have been tons of our stuff
At the auction, Bulldata auction
This time, I only brought four or five things
But they're really big
And really kind of special
Believe it or not, in that box over there
Is a dickhead mask
That's right, folks
Uh, yes
I wouldn't tell you that, but
I'll say it again
There's no other polite way to put it
It's a dickhead mask
It's pretty old and may smell a bit funky
But it's only been worn on human heads
I think
It's way too big for a human dick
It will transform you into a huge dick
If you weren't a huge dick already
You can be with this mask
Made by Pudi Flang Damarong about 40 years ago
It's quite realistic
It's rubber, it's handmade
But it's definitely
Well, I'd just pull it out
I'll just whip it out
Just whoop it out, Reverend Stang
Whoop out your dick, Reverend Stang
Whoop it out, whoop it out hard
Whoop out your giant dick
Is a sentence you could legitimately say this X-Day
Show us your giant dick, Reverend Stang
It wouldn't be a metaphor
Show us your giant dickhead
If I can
If you can find it, if you can put your hands on it
That's how I hurt my shoulder
Grab it
Reaching out to you
For your dickhead
Oh, good lord
He's now picking up a two-ton box
Oh, it's only about 200 pounds
Reverend Stang, don't you know
You're not supposed to be picking up heavy things like that
Tsk, tsk, tsk
And here it comes
Drumroll, please
Oh, that's beautiful
It is
It's a giant
It's really a giant dickhead
Yeah, it seems to be a little flat down here
To go down your t-shirt
Oh, man, it's really losing its skin
Yes
It looks a little too real
But an artisan could repair it
And make it into a nice new dickhead mask
It's rather, rather circumcised
It is rather uncircumcised
And then there are the slits on the opposite side
For you to be able to look out and smell
The world around you
As you're being a dickhead
You could actually
Fuck
This dick
Reverend Stang is explaining that this dick can be fucked
Don't let the clowns get to this thing
Don't give this to the clowns
It is a thing of beauty
I agree
Oh, and friends
Some of you might want to check out the video
Check out a website
Blog type thing
Called stupidamerica.net
Stupid America
They have a Stupid America award
It's about stupid stuff
So, yeah
Stupidamerica.net
Praise God