PR comes from the Non-Fun Foundation.
PR is BJFD and BAPR.
PR PR is PR.
PR PR News.
Confused?
PR Now.
Minnow says we end up creating a real root problem, which has to do with about 10 other problems.
Supporters say it's obesity-related.
Obesity. Those are his words.
Monahan says diabetes and heart disease.
We can wait.
She says lardolidin.
That's the end of it.
Miriam says.
That'll show the sides where there's no monosomes, but there's not hot cell hard sex.
Nelson says there's a sporting mall, and it's creepy.
God.
She says mouth means good members.
This is PR.
So, Bob, you're making $5, $10, $15 a month?
Uh-huh.
Job?
Job? Not really.
How did you do it? You had help.
Yep.
Who helped you?
Well...
The Self Genius.
Power of wax.
Pressure him.
Wow.
Or threaten him.
Persons attempting to find a motive in this show will be prosecuted.
Persons attempting to find a moral in it will be banished.
Persons attempting to find a plot in it will be shot.
The man with a new idea is a fool.
Until the idea succeeds.
The Sad But Strange Story begins in New York.
60 years ago.
And so, in May 1900,
a skillful but envious and desperate,
undistinguished but alluring and halting but fashionable
and ordinary but careful, glittering-eyed man
with a fabulous automatic cue
and strange alluring flowing oriental raiment
registered at a automatic and desperate but fashionable
and fabulous hotel in famed but diminutive London.
I find...
I find you humans quite interesting.
Even though you are a worthless, greedy lot.
How annoying that sound is.
Fools.
What fascinations there are on this planet.
Strange mortals with curious customs.
We'll have a storm now.
And an earthquake if you like.
This makes me think, in the words of the great Mark Twain,
all that I care to know is that a man is a human being.
That's enough for me.
He can't be any worse.
Kindness is a language which the deaf can hear and the blind can read.
The wrinkles should merely indicate where smiles have been.
Grief can take care of itself.
But to get the full value of joy,
you must have someone to divide it.
And you must have someone to live with.
Adam and Eve had many advantages.
But the principal one was that they escaped teething.
We like a man to come right out and say what he thinks,
if we agree with him.
We ought never to do the wrong thing when people are looking.
Few things are harder to put up with
than the annoyance of a good example.
I have been complimented many times.
And they always embarrass me.
I always feel they've not said enough.
Here's another one that's kind of funny.
Read this one.
Man, these newspaper articles are coming thick and fast.
I must do this show.
Here, quit looking at that.
Do the show, man.
You look at that.
What?
Yeah, I gotta quit doing the show.
It's all about somebody's intestine.
Oh, yeah, something weird about...
It's the spooky horror tunnel of the show
where lots of effects happen.
I'll have to read that.
It's where we store all the hours of show.
Yeah, you have to read that one. It's funny, man.
He's in a temporary cabin, you know.
And it has the bathroom outside.
And it's cold because it's snowing.
Well, you have to go whether it's cold or not.
Yeah.
Sometimes you do if your guts are churning, right?
Yes.
You got that churning gut syndrome?
You gotta do something about it.
I know.
So you try to think of a good solution that's gonna be best for everyone.
Because you're in close quarters with other people.
You gotta really think about how it's gonna work out as a collective thing.
You can't just go it alone every time.
You have to think about how it's gonna...
Your behavior...
Your behavior and your activities in close quarters amongst others will actually affect the others.
You can't just go off half-cocked, single-handedly and unilaterally,
completely unconscious of your behavior's effect upon the well-being and good nature of your fellow travelers
who are also stuck inside this tiny little room
with your smelly, vetted armpits exuding that odor.
Or at least mine.
Maybe not yours, but mine.
And now what?
Well, you've got...
Hey, dude, you look like you've got a piece of corn in your ear.
What happened?
Yes.
Well, it says Dick Cheney found the Holy Grail here on this other publication you have.
And a picture of him clutching it, too.
Well, that's certainly unexpected development.
What do you think he's gonna do with that, Dr. Howell?
Do you think he'll use the Holy Grail for good purposes, or do you think he'll be...
No, I think he'll use it for some evil ceremony.
Do you think he'll use it for a satanic purpose?
To gain occult powers.
Do you think he'll concentrate his occult powers that he already had into a, like, a much more powerful position now that he has the Holy Grail?
Uh-huh.
In such a cracked-brain theory...
Excuse me.
Yes.
Hello?
Yes, I see.
I see.
Here's the door.
We're inside the inner shell.
Careful.
Do you suppose Philo will find us?
I assure you, Henry, that Philo will never find us here.
Not in a million years.
Phew, that was close.
I got a look at him.
It was Philo.
He said they have agents.
Philo's probably one of them.
He'll be looking for you now, trying to kill you.
Philo's probably waiting.
I think they have...
You know, we figure some way...
Wait, I know.
How?
Listen.
What's this Philo like?
Hmm?
I don't know.
He's strange.
I see.
Well, I don't know.
I'm beginning to get interested in your Philo.
Yes.
They have agents under him.
Hear me?
Hello?
Agents in...
Henry, look out!
There's a light!
Someone at the window.
Philo?
Philo.
I'll be glad to meet him.
Are you nuts?
Yes.
You'll recognize him.
I'll be glad to meet him.
You'll recognize the dropped palm of your old friend, Philo.
Philo?
But I thought...
That he was part of the conspiracy?
No, on the contrary.
No more nonsense.
Hmm?
But you...
You...
You can't do this to me!
No!
Just make it.
No more nonsense.
Yeah.
Like I said, I'm back from the dead.
Perfect guitar to take on Crusader.
Each is his own 새로운 shapes and shades.
Postbide.
Everybody can have one.
It's time for C 예 wegen Castle Charlotte.
Did you read it?
Well, I was walking down the street
Looking for a job
I ran into a man
Called himself Bob
Well, I forgot
I forgot I even needed a job
Oh, it all happened to me
When I ran into a guy named Bob
I was fresh in town
Didn't have a dollar
I was so poor
I was starting to holler
Then I ran into a man
Called himself Bob
And I plumb forgot about the fact
That I had no money and no job
Well, Bob is hot
And Bob is cold
And Bob is young
And Bob is old
But I forgot
Forgot I needed to know anything else
Oh, it all happened to me
I just took my own personality
And put it up on the shelf
Bob's brain
So damn big
He'll make you look like a greasy little pig
Oh, you'll forget about your whole personality
As soon as you give your entire brain to Bob and me
If you're young
And you're looking for a job
Just look for a guy
Whose name is Bob
And you won't have to worry
About getting a job
You won't have no money
But you'll have Bob
Yes, you'll have Bob
Swingin' Bob
That was Swingin' Bob
By Glass Madness
Friends from the last century
And before that
Puzzling Evidence show
From KBFA and Berkeley
With Dr. Philo Drummond
Puzzling Evidence
And Dr. Howell
And Chloe
Prior to that
Cuts by Leemur
And words by Mark Twain
Cause this is the
Hour of Slack episode number
The Decadely Mark Twain Special
But first
Let's briefly go
20 years back in time
To answer several recent questions
From listeners
First
Is Bob your Jesus?
Bob is my Jesus
Always does he please us
Everywhere he's near us
Always bold and fearless
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob
Bob, Bob, Bob
Bob
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob
Bob, Bob, Bob
Bob, Bob, this is Bob
Bob Bill
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob
Bob, Bob, Bob
Bob Bill
Bill先
All good
Webb Hook
it's so
then
Bob
成
Closing
Washington
ini
grave importance and must see him alone tonight.
Dr. Pretorius?
Pretorius?
I don't sleep.
I hate those little slices of death.
Is that what you call an intelligence officer?
That's what I call a nut!
Yeah, I call him a nut too, but look how nicely he fits in on Earth, chasing Indians and blondes.
Let us endeavor so to live that when we come to die, even the undertaker will be sorry.
There are two times in a man's life when he should speculate.
When he can't afford it, and when he can.
Fleas can be taught nearly everything that a congressman can.
In the South, the war is what A.D. is.
They don't come from elsewhere.
They date from it.
Everything human is pathetic.
The secret source of humor itself is not joy, but sorrow.
Thunder is good.
Thunder is impressive.
But it is lightning that does the work.
It is curious that physical courage should be so common in the world, and moral courage so rare.
The meaning is everything.
The peach was once a bitter almond.
The cauliflower is nothing but a cabbage with a college education.
Familiarity breeds content.
And children.
To be a writer, one must observe three rules.
One, write.
Two, write.
And three, write.
My books are water.
Those of the great genius.
The greatest geniuses are wine.
Everybody drinks water.
As to the adjective, when in doubt, strike it out.
Write without pay until somebody offers pay.
If nobody offers within three years, sawing wood is what you were intended for.
A classic is something that everybody wants to have read, and nobody wants to read.
I make it a point never to smoke more than one cigar at a time.
There's nothing difficult about giving up smoking.
I've done it hundreds of times myself.
But there's still a danger between giving and not?
There's risk until a
Look in a good effort.
Poor things go in the past.
Because of us.
Drinking.
Washing.
Playing games.
Take coal.
Have drinking.
A special noise there just for you,
hour of slack listeners by Fernanda Ndelemer.
Friends, have you made your reservation for X-Day, July 5th?
You know, that's when the world ends.
Starting at Brushwood in New York,
the clothing optional campground where,
if they know about it,
from the events page on subgenius.com,
subgeniuses may gather to worship Bob as they choose.
They're naked.
So are we all the day we're born.
But we learn very modest.
Not all over.
Just in places.
But it's just as well, I suppose.
Naked people have little or no influence in society.
I forgot to bring my fake snake.
First time I was at a Winterstar,
I think I was on something,
but I walked into the drum cabin
and it was the first time I met that man.
I was sitting there.
Mr. Dennis Murphy.
His beautiful wife walked up and said,
hi, we're married now.
They were marrying everybody they met just then
just like I ordain everybody.
And when I walked into the drumming cabin
and I think it was Dennis was walking around
with a toy snake.
And I thought it was real.
I thought that you guys were in there
and they were dancing around candles.
They didn't even have a bonfire.
They didn't even have the fake flames then.
Yeah.
I thought, what have I gotten into?
These people are really nuts.
Since then, of course, the subgeniuses got to where they have sex with poisonous vipers.
You really don't want to hear the details about that.
Impromptu sermonizing there by yours truly, Reverend Ivan Stang from Winterstar 2007.
That's from Cleveland's Association for Consciousness Exploration, or ACE.
You can look at Rosencomet.com.
Now let's go see what has hatched from Lemur's drag nest.
Sergeant Friday, could I see you a minute, please?
Yes, all right.
There's the patient's name, right there at the top.
Miller.
12.30 p.m., a local broadcast and an APB was gotten out on Miller.
Then we sent a communication to the police department asking them to check for a possible lead on the Miller woman.
After that, we started making the rounds of the bars in the neighborhoods.
7.55 a.m. the following morning, I reported back in for work.
Morning, Joe.
Hi, Betty.
What do you know, anything new?
Uh-huh.
Mm-hmm.
No, I just happened to think, this description of the Miller girl.
The Miller girl's description?
Yeah.
That description of Miller?
Mm-hmm.
This part here doesn't make much sense.
Does it?
Lewis said Miller was small and fairly tall.
Dark blue eyes.
Long dark hair, dark eyes.
Long blonde hair.
Man sure doesn't figure.
9.05 a.m.
The traditional parade.
Some parade, isn't it?
Yeah, it's beautiful.
Drag nest.
And now, Chloe describes her first appearance on the Puzzling Evidence show.
It was one of the pinnacle points of my life because I got a phone call while I was at dinner with Rob from my boss at 12 Galaxy saying,
Hey, Chloe, you gotta get over here.
I got a giant busload of clowns and they don't know what to do.
Wow, look at that.
They just happened to arrive to perform at your show.
Well, that looks good.
But I think that's the only time in my life that I'll have a busload of clowns being held up.
Don't be too sure about that.
Life is uncertain.
However, it's statistically likely that no more bustling.
Busloads of clowns will unexpectedly.
Be awaiting my beckon call.
Yes.
But I would be the last to wish to discourage you.
Hammer relentlessly on the forces.
The iconic representation of future technology.
Since one busload of clowns is already.
We can rest assured that.
Which means helicopters.
Appeared.
The backward aspect.
That shows that it is not beyond the bounds of possibility that such a thing could happen.
That ancient religious movement will indeed save us once again.
That another busload of clowns.
Will be denied at any time.
From the busload of clowns.
I hope so.
Up here to assist you when you need it.
So once I was on a busload with a clown.
No, a clown had a busload.
He had a load in his what?
He had a load in his.
A load of clowns on a bus.
They were loaded.
He had a buttload of what?
He had a busload of.
They're on the bus.
But it was a clown bus.
It was a clown mode.
In his pants.
Clown mode?
There's a mode?
A buttload.
The mode is called clown mode.
Clown mode.
And they're in clown mode.
Buttload.
They have a bus that's got a buttload of clowns.
You ever thought about how much is a buttload?
That's a lot.
It's ice.
That's a shortened form of boatload.
Enough to fill the bowl.
Well, there is a bowl.
It may be enough for you to be a shortened form of boatload.
The clown bowl is the destination of all clown mode buses.
But I believe buttload also came from now you're letting your mouth overload.
Letting your ass overload your mouth again.
Yeah, your.
My favorite was your mouth is writing checks your ass can't support.
Yeah.
I love that one.
Can't cash.
Boy, some people are really.
Can't support.
Can't underwrite.
Can't.
You can't run from your own mouth is writing checks that your ass can't cash.
Okay, just for that, I got to do this.
Have you ever given anyone a MasterCard?
It's where you take your hand and you stick it in the crack of their butt and swipe it.
Yeah.
It's like a form of a wedgie, only it's just more directed to the point.
Yeah, I like that.
MasterCard.
Yeah, it's called a MasterCard.
Yeah.
And that's as out of place as a Presbyterian in hell.
Fortune knocks at every man's door once in a life, they say, but in a good many cases,
the man is in a neighboring saloon and does not hear her.
I do not like work even when someone else does it.
When I was a boy of 14, my father was so ignorant I could hardly stand to have the old man around.
But when I got to be 21, I was astonished at how much he had learned in 7 years.
That's all Mark Twain's words, friends.
I'm gleaning this from a book called Man is the Only Animal That Blushes, or Needs to,
The Wisdom of Mark Twain, an ancient book by an ancient subgenius.
I beg your pardon, mister, but ain't you forgot something?
Forgot something?
Not that I know of.
Why?
My harp and my wreath and my halo and my hymn book and my palm branch.
I never heard of these things before.
Oh, trust me, you won't be conspicuous in this district without it.
Well, good day.
Where you really going in that thing, Mr. Twain?
Going traveling?
Travel has no longer any charm for me.
I've seen all the foreign countries I care to see except for heaven and hell,
and I have only a vague curiosity as concerns one of those.
Everybody talks about the weather, but nobody does anything about it.
I believe that our heavenly father invented man because he was disappointed in the monkey.
If Christ were here now, there is one thing he would not be.
A Christian.
My advice to girls.
First, don't smoke to excess.
Second, don't drink to excess.
Third, don't marry to excess.
If you can't get a compliment any other way, pay yourself one.
If you tell the truth, you don't have to.
You don't have to remember anything.
The best way to cheer yourself up is to try to cheer someone else up.
It is a mistake that there is no bath that will cure people's manners, but drowning would help.
The man with a new idea is a crank until the idea succeeds.
It is not best that we should all think alike.
It is difference of opinion that makes horse races.
It is easier to stay than get out.
Vast material prosperity always brings in its train conditions which debase the morals and innervate the manhood of a nation.
Loyalty to petrified opinion never yet broke a chain or freed a human soul.
There are several good protections against temptation, but the surest is cowardice.
I reckon it's Mr. Twain.
I am the only man living who understands human nature.
God has put me in charge of this branch office and I retire.
There will be no one to take my place.
I shall keep on doing my duty.
When I get over on the other side,
I want to use my influence to have the human race ground again.
This time, ground good.
No omission.
No art.
If there was an all-powerful God, he would have made all good and no bad.
Whoever has lived long enough to find out what life is, knows how deep a debt of gratitude we owe to Adam.
He was the first great benefactor of our race.
He brought death into the world.
Most people are bothered by those passages of scripture they do not understand.
But the passages that bother me are those I do understand.
You can't pray a lie.
I know that you are.
Well, look who's here.
You know, I begin to see that a man's got to be in his own heaven to be happy.
Perfectly correct.
Did you imagine that the same heaven would suit all sorts of people?
Go that way.
A million leagues or so.
Well, thank you, sir.
So long.
It's been swell.
It's been grand.
Our playing book, Airwings, Halo, size 13, size 13.
For Captain Eli Stormfield of San Francisco.
San Francisco, you betcha.
Make him out a clean bill of health and let him in.
Show me a cloud.
I'm all right now.
Shh.
I think.
Oh, sorry.
I forgot.
Shh.
You're supposed to be quiet.
Aha, for hem book and wings.
Good God, what a swindle.
I'm led to consider a different path.
Heaven for climate.
Hell for company.
Either way, you gotta die to get there.
Baby birds from the sky.
May the crows pick up their eyes.
America, wronged and betrayed by those guys in the Green Beret.
Dipping food was not enough.
I'm a little bit hungry.
The call's defeat was pretty tough.
Interrogate.
Kissing your sloes.
Death's too good for those mozos.
Burning flesh beneath their heels.
Screams of pain to them sex squeals.
Rubber hoses filled with smoke.
Sand.
Broken bodies.
Children of the land.
Down below are young white fries.
Green Berets cheers death from the skies.
But there is an napalm, too.
Making sure that their lives burn through.
Interregnizing.
The wreck that's being done
These murderers should all be damned
Harbingers of doom and pain
Their leaders are all insane
Cause they are baby birds from the sky
May the crows pick out their eyes
Humanity
From death betrayed
By those guys
In the green parade
On war, Twain said, there never was a just one,
never an honorable one on the part of the instigator of the war.
I can see a million years ahead,
and this rule will never change
in so many as have been.
Half a dozen instances.
The loud little handful, as usual,
will shout for the war.
The pulpit will object at first.
The great dull bulk of the nation
will rub its sleepy eyes
and try to make out why there should be a war
and will say earnestly and indignantly,
it is unjust and dishonorable
and there is no necessity for it.
Then the handful will shout louder.
A few fair men on the other side
will argue and reason against the war
with speech and pen
and at first,
will have a hearing and be applauded.
But it will not last long.
Those others will outshout them
and presently the anti-war audiences
will thin out and lose popularity.
Before long, you will see this curious thing.
The speakers stoned from the platform
and free speech strangled by hordes of furious men
who in their secret hearts
are still at one with those stoned speakers.
But do not dare to say so.
And now,
the whole nation, pulpit and all,
will take up the war cry
and shout itself hoarse
and mob any decent man
who ventures to open his mouth
and presently such mouths
will cease to open.
Next, the statesman will invent cheap lies
putting the blame upon the nation that is attacked
and every man will be glad of these
conscience-soothing falsities
and will diligently study them
and refuse to examine any refutations of them
and thus he will by and by convince himself
that the war is just
and will thank God for the better sleep he enjoys
after this process of grotesque self-deception.
Mark Twain.
And Charles J.
If Soundbite continues its
fabrications,
every marginal media
It's all the way.
Death.
Is to have just distance.
Doom.
Is to stimulate casual.
As I are these saints.
The promise of those saints.
Sure.
But not this ball.
And I'll leave them with.
But I'm not going to keep on killing.
I'm going to keep on killing.
I'll keep on killing.
Thank you.
Noice proves nothing.
Often a hen who has merely laid an egg cackles as if she had laid an asteroid.
People need pizzas.
This actually equals this.
Exactly.
I'm recommending five buttered pizza skins plus a pat of butter.
One thousand nine hundred and forty one grams of startling numbers for an average adult.
Eat larger portions.
Ruby works for a dog nutrition group, so it's hard to know what you're eating.
This looks healthy.
It certainly does in this case, though.
Two sirloin pizza skins with Caesar skins and buttered baked pizzas,
plus five buttered pasta butter.
That's a good idea.
Right now to the retard peeing on the pipes.
Live and edited.
Alright, it's true.
Uh, uh...
How could I do that?
Courage is resistance to fear, mastery of fear, not absence of fear.
My conscience is more trouble and bother to me than anything else I started with.
It could probably be shown by facts and figures that there's no distinctly Native American criminal class.
Except Congress.
In statesmanship, get the formalities right, never mind about the moralities.
All you need in this life is ignorance and confidence, and then success is sure.
Put all your eggs in one basket, and watch that basket.
There is an old time toast which is golden for its beauty.
When you ascend the hill of prosperity, may you not know.
Meet a friend.
Good breeding consists in concealing how much we think of ourselves and how little we think of the other person.
You aim for the palace and get drowned in the sewer.
Let us be thankful for the fools, but for them the rest of us could not succeed.
The holy passion of friendship is of so sweet and steady and loyal and enduring,
and so is the nature that it will last through a whole lifetime, if not asked to lend money.
On hold.
Farm life.
So any of that gum can help, help, help, help, help, help, help, help.
And thanks for holding.
You can get rich by holding.
Messages.
We appreciate your patience and we know your time is valuable.
Thank you for calling.
All calls are recorded for Dick, Dick, Dick, Dick.
If this is an emergency, please choose from the following options.
Please press the following options.
If you're planning to press one, please press one.
For all other inquiries, what else do you need?
Hearing problem?
Great prices?
No, no, no, no.
Great, great, great, great.
Please remain on the line.
Are you a homo?
Cut.
Do you think?
For more information, go to our website at www.www.com.
Later.
Yes or no.
Thank you for calling.
She It will be with you shortly.
Trust the X.
Take some time out from the hustle and bustle and enjoy yourself with hustle and bustle, hustle and bustle.
There's so much going on.
Thank you for calling Creative Finance.
Sing, sing, sing.
Parties, parties, parties, parties at any time.
Dial 1.
Dial 2.
Dial 3.
Dial 4.
Dial 5.
Dial 6.
6.
Thank you for calling our business hours.
Friday, 5 p.m. to 5 a.m.
Dial 7.
Please dial it now.
PMS voicemail.
Hi, this is an automated call.
If I'll get in and on, is this it there?
Please press 1.
Press 2.
You have reached.
Thank you for calling.
Thank you for holding.
Thank you so much.
Go ahead and dial it now.
Or dial 8.
Dial 0.
Our records show that you are.
Hello and thank you so much for calling PR.
Thank you for calling.
Press it at any time.
Press the pound key.
Press 1 now.
Press 2.
Thank you.
Thank you for calling.
This is a reporting.
Zero.
Welcome to hell.
Press 1.
Press 2.
Press 3.
Hear this message again.
Please press the press.
Thanks for holding.
Please hold momentarily for an available agent.
Sorry for the inconvenience.
Call us.
Or you can call us.
Thank you for calling.
Have a great day.
Hi.
Hello.
Thank you.
I'm unable to take your extension.
I'm sorry.
I can't take your extension.
Thank you.
The Alzheimer's Association notes that Brain Biopsy features your top hip-hop, rock and
pop artists and albums with compilations of music videos, behind the scenes and interviews.
Hello.
Please hold while we connect you to an associate.
Premium hardwood.
The Alzheimer's Association provides a tool to detect one of the two well-known hallmarks
of Alzheimer's disease.
Tom Cruise and Katie Holmes and Scientology.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Cross your legs.
Lie down on your back.
One of the most anticipated movies of the year, the enactment of NAFTA.
You've been listening to Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
Slowly and painfully.
Spiritual growth.
New world view.
Power leads man towards arrogance.
Power narrows the areas of man's concern.
Find out tonight.
Welcome to Plasma Protein.
To quantitate proteins.
A monthly breast exam.
One out of three and one in ten.
We are driven by a passion to discover and develop medical needs.
Medical needs.
We are dedicated.
We are driven by a passion to discover and develop serious illness and chronic symptoms.
Our approach to chronic symptoms.
Beautiful.
What everyone really wants is a word on the street.
All you have to do is scream.
Happy little rabbits.
First of all, disaster is on the way.
On the horizon.
Welcome to disaster.
Bet.
Humanitarian rights offer a strange sense of security.
And we take it very seriously.
On hold.
Here then is a review, a movie review of The Pick of Destiny.
Don't believe mealy mouth criticism from egghead reviewers in your local weekly friends.
Even the Onion reviewers were wrong on this one.
Believe me.
First, let there be no question.
Tenacious D rules.
They rule all other metal bands.
And it goes without saying that metal rules all other forms of music.
If you ever doubted that, The Pick of Destiny puts all such foolish doubts to rest.
I am sure of this.
Princess Wee and I have watched the new Tenacious D movie twice.
And we've listened to the score, which I ripped from the screener rip, hourly for days now.
So there can be no question.
No room for quarter.
No negotiation.
Not even Satan rocks as hard as The D.
In fact, in this movie, Satan actually loses a rock off to Tenacious D.
Although not exactly because of their music.
I'll grant that.
You should take it from me that Tenacious D in The Pick of Destiny is the best rock and roll movie since rock and roll high school.
Making it therefore the greatest rock and roll movie possible.
It is basically a rock opera.
A greater rock opera.
Even than Ken Russell's version of Tommy.
Only it's supposed to be funny instead of being accidentally funny.
The music of The D is running through at least 50 minutes of the movie's duration.
The D's magnificent virtuoso guitar playing is augmented by magical drums and bass from nowhere.
And eventually even operatic chorales and layered on orchestral instrumentation worthy of the later Beatles albums.
Satan himself does a cameo near the end playing himself and playing some juicy riffs.
Of special interest to Subgeni is the Sasquatch is my daddy sequence in which JB inadvertently eats handfuls of magic mushrooms and meets Bigfoot in a vision.
He sings at length of how the Sasquatch is his true father and even turns into an infant yeti during the hallucination.
This segment incidentally features some of the most triacly magic dreams.
Like a drug head kingdom music ever committed to a film score.
In summary Tenacious D and this movie completely sum up metal and metal fans.
They represent the be all and end all of all hard rock heaviness.
And my greatest ambition in life I just now remembered is to produce the ultimate metal concert featuring the swinging love corpses, Tenacious D, Spinal Tap and headlining Frank Marino and Mahogany.
Rush. So friends, there's our movie review. I actually watch movies that are considered to be
good as well. I watched Perfume and The Illusionist the same night as I watched that,
and they were actually good. And I know a bad movie when I see one. I saw Night at the Museum,
which is the penultimate in suckery, and it would suck even if Robin Williams wasn't there.
So friends, take my word for it. The D rules. And if you haven't seen Idiocracy,
that one, it is your duty to rent that one. And praise Bob.
Maybe that's all Bob is.
Bob.
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
Bob, Bob.
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
I know where he got you.
Why would you do that to me, Bob?
By Stang and Lemur and others.
And this background music we're listening to is by Transmission.
Or Stephen Kent from an album called Meanwhile.
Earlier, the On Hold collage was by the great Nor Elpref of norelpref.com.
You are currently listening to Hour of Slack number 1090 from the Church of the Subgenius.
For more information about that, you can check out subgenius.com.
Or just type subgenius into Google and see what happens.
You, like so many others before you, will learn that Bob is Lord.
His word is the sword.
And his radio shows are out of the ord.
This is craziness.
Everyone is a moon and has a dark side, which he never shows to anybody.
If he can help it.
My books are water.
Those are the great geniuses.
They're wine.
Everybody drinks water.
Let me see.
There are a number of things I need to tell you before I go.
Always obey your parents when they are present.
Be respectful of your superiors.
If.
You have any.
Rise early.
For it is the early bird that catches the worm.
I once knew a man who tried it.
Got up at sunrise.
Horse bit him.
It's time.
I'm still considering whether to go.
I have never seen an atom of truth that there is a future life.
Yet I am strongly inclined to expect one.
Anyway, don't be.
Such a sissy in the face of a real adventure.
And I'm not as big a fool as Don Phil if I can't swear I won't stay.
Nothing so needs reforming as other people's habits a baby is an inestimable blessing and bother.
Always.
Always do right. This will gratify some people and astonish the rest.
We should be careful to get out of an experience only the wisdom that is in it.
The cat that sits down on a hot stove lid will never sit down on a hot stove lid again, and that is well.
But also, she will never sit down on a cold one anymore.
Do something every day that you don't want to do.
This is the golden rule for acquiring the habit of doing your duty without pain.
Columbus elaborated a deep plan to find a new route to an old country.
Circumstance revised his plan for him, and he found a new world.
And he gets the credit of it to this day.
He hadn't anything to do with it.
My kind of loyalty was loyalty to one's country, not to its institutions,
or its office holders.
The country is the real thing, the substantial thing, the eternal thing.
It's the thing to watch for, care for, and be loyal to.
Almost any man worth his salt would fight to defend his home.
But no one has ever heard of a man going to war for his boarding house.
Among the three or four million cradles now rocking in the land are some which this nation would preserve for ages,
as sacred things.
If only we could know which ones they are.
There is no other life.
Life itself is only a vision and a dream.
For nothing exists but space and you.
Friends, that's the last of my quotes from Mark Twain.
Except for this last memorandum written on his deathbed.
Death, the only immortal who treats us all alike,
whose pity and whose peace and whose refuge are for all,
the soiled and the pure, the rich and the poor,
the loved and the unloved.
And friends, we love you,
because this is the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
And this has been a sort of a Mark Twain special.
And I hope you enjoyed it.
The clips that I've been running of somebody else doing Mark Twain quotes
are from the wonderful 1980s claymation film,
The Adventures of Mark Twain by Will Vinton.
Ah, yes, dear friends.
Oh, the music in the background is by yours truly, Reverend Ivan Stan.
To put it in crude modern terms,
the earth wobbles as it spins on its axis,
and thus the sky changes over the centuries and millennia.
When's our pole magnetism thing going to happen?
When are the poles switching?
Day after tomorrow, but don't tell anybody.
Oh, okay.
At present, on the Bernal Equinox,
when the sun costs the celestial equator from south to north
around March 20th to 21st,
the sun rises against the constellation of Pythagoras,
Pisces, as it has done for about 2,000 years.
And devours the dragon Shemash,
which had plunged the earth in the age of deep darkness.
This is a distant future within the next couple of centuries.
No, it doesn't work.
Almost there.
The sun will rise against...
Are you sure, Doctor?
I can't keep up with it anymore.
So we're at the foot end of the millennium?
Well, let's just call it the footnote.
That's what happens.
Let's call it the foot gland.
Now, I see you're opening up a big bag...
Let's call it a football.
A bag of Slaco chips over there.
I wanted to ask you if you are trying to create a food riot here with that large...
Food?
There's food?
I can't see this since there's duct tape over my eyes.
Don't be too ready to believe everything you hear already.
You're all so weird.
If it walks, I can...
If it's all about you, then it's all about me.
It's always about you.
I gotta go see my friends.
It's all about me.
Sound like willfully disobedient boys.
Boys are a bad lot and these boys are disobedient.
And disobedient lads must be punished.
Old Dr. Hal found us.
Yes.
Gentlemen, choose a switch.
A spanking is a good thing.
spanking.
It's like a spanking
wrapped in a weapon
inside of an enigma.
And now,
if you're ready for your enigma,
bend over and throw the switch.
You don't feel so cocky now, do you?
Whatever he's paying you,
I'll double it right now.
You know what the tragedy is here, Bob?
We could have been friends.
But you wouldn't go through proper channels.
You went over my head.
That hurt.
But life goes on.
It's an old story,
the fight for love and glory, huh, Bob?
It helps if you think of it as a game, Bob.
Every game has a winner.
And a loser.
I'm cashing you out, Bob.
God.
What's up with you, huh?
There's a TravelPod member
Hobbit probably didn't use Rob to guten journal
We realized the world is a movie