The gun is good.
The gun is good!
The penis is evil.
The penis shoots seeds.
Jesus Christ, no, it's still coming!
It hasn't even been touched!
It's shooting lightning bolts from its eyes!
The flames are being blown from the sky one by one!
No, he's trying to...
He can't make them shut up.
He'll never make them shut up.
Somebody gag the cowboy.
Alright, here we go.
5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
And now it's that time you've been waiting for, kids!
You're here on the...
The awesome cowboy man just rode in on his automatic horse bucket!
Howdy, kids.
I had a terrible ride here tonight.
I was threatened and accosted by three young bullies,
one of whom had a rancid, arid eye that kept on staring downwards while he beat me for my boots.
After being stabbed in the night several times about the head and buttocks area,
I began to scream and chased a 13RTA bus all the way down Chester Avenue.
I was so scared.
Once I got to the dumpster next to Mary Lou's,
I had visions of her in my head.
Oh, Mary Lou.
I had visions of ski patrol
and visions of French bunny girls wearing little parkas
and little teeny, teeny, teeny tiny critters
you couldn't even call clothing.
Smart guy.
And he kept me going
as the oil was slicking up around my feet
and the fires were raging, making the air on my ears burn.
I was going back.
All I could do was think of
the song to you.
So you, uh, did you go to prostitutes, huh?
Uh, yes, dear friends.
This Hour of Slack number 927
is a rerun of Hour of Slack number 776
from our 77th.
Season.
Seriously.
Sexy is the title of this old show.
Oh.
Hit me.
Do it.
No.
Stop it.
Hit me.
And I still can see
Blue velvet
Through my tears
Tears.
Like it when I talk that way.
Mm-hmm.
Honey.
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, hey.
Thousands of bottles of blue beer on the wall.
The kind of beer that'll make you a man today.
The kind of man that can fly our planes.
And knock out the yaks and the dingoes, too.
And the rest of the people trying to bring this country down on its knees where it truly belongs.
So stand up for America today if you can at all.
Are you a bad boy?
Are you a bad boy, Dave?
You mean it?
I was very bad.
Do you want to do bad things?
You want to do bad things?
Are you a bad boy?
I took the toilet bowl brush.
What do you mean?
And answered it to where the sun would refuse to shine.
And I began singing.
Do you want to do bad things, Dave?
Stop getting so excited.
You know, every time you get him sexually excited, his nuts go up inside him and he gets that female voice.
Well, more like a little boy.
He's like little Dave.
He gets scared.
That's why he's so lonesome.
Haven't you ever heard the gelding sound, Stang?
Yes.
That's when a yearling is frightened by larger males of his own type or kind.
We call that the forgot-to-debeat-the-prairie-squid voice.
But a squid proboscis is more than just a proboscis.
It's a hiding place for a metaphor.
A metaphor for the pleasures of the universe.
Tuck it inside out and it works both ways.
Yes, Dr. Wang.
Take out the green scalp of nature.
Now I'm the remove.
That's a good idea.
So I heard...
I'm going to take my clothes off.
I'm going to take my pants off.
I'm going to do this show with no pants on.
No pants on.
Friends, last night I was showing...
Somebody told me they found my gold plastic subgenius minister's card at a party I'd been at last week.
And I was going through my wallet and going, oh yeah, it's gone.
I guess so.
And I found my Universal Life Church preachers.
How many here are members of the Universal Life Church?
Look at that.
I knew it.
Praise Bishop Hensley.
He was the man who decided that he didn't want to help subsidize religions he might not believe in.
Since religions didn't have to pay taxes.
So he started ordaining everyone he knew.
Much like the discordians do.
Ordaining popes right and left.
So you're all ministers now.
You don't have to pay taxes.
But as I was going through that wallet, I also came upon my oldest original subgenius membership.
Card.
The person looking over my shoulder went...
They saw the Universal Life Church card and said, oh I want one of those.
I said, oh I'll send a self-addressed stamped envelope to Modesto, California.
But then she saw the subgenius membership card and said, oh I don't want one of those.
Now, I didn't...
I woke up this morning thinking about that.
And I thought, okay, we know what she doesn't want.
What does this say she does want?
Friends, when you say you don't want a subgenius membership card.
You don't want to be a subgenius minister doling out the slack of Bob's.
What it says you do want is that you do want to take yourself seriously.
And friends, as a subgenius, I do not take myself seriously.
I don't take you seriously.
I don't take her seriously.
I don't even take that man J.R. Bob Dobbs seriously.
The only thing I take seriously is the one serious law that the church of the subgenius has that Bob passed down.
And that one rule is, fuck them if they can't take a joke.
I see somebody's been reading their prescriptures here.
I don't even take the news, what you people call the news, I don't...
I take that least seriously of all.
So you think you're in America, do you?
Last time I checked.
Well, you're not. You're in high school.
Now take that thing and bury it where it belongs.
Look at this thing.
It wasn't even human.
Do you think it's healthy for a 13 year old boy to imagine his teacher naked?
Absolutely.
Mommy, when do I get breast?
This is strange, but there are four people in the hospital who nearly suffocated in here.
There has to be a reason for this. What do you think?
I'll run tests on all the main electrical circuits. I might find something there.
You're wearing black underwear.
Did you go in there and write that on the mirror while I was taking a shower?
Yes.
Well, enough is enough, young man. Do I make myself clear?
It's like a plague or something.
People disappearing right and left. Old ladies, little girls, young women, school boys.
I don't call it a mendacity. I call it anti-slack.
This is Ivan Stank's version. Watch this. He starts crying right here. It's really neat.
I don't know a place for giving.
I am sinned.
Is he laughing there?
Here on the last show of the millennium.
How many last shows have we done, Doug? Give me a break.
We never did a last show of the millennium, though.
The last show of the millennium.
In 1998, there was a last show.
We never did one of the millennium. We never thought we would be at the millennium.
I always thought I'd be at some pleasure saucer in space on Planet X by now.
I mean, I'm kind of pissed off that that ever came through.
Dr. Drummond, have you not heeded Bob's new word, build your own ship?
Yeah, yeah.
Bob's new word? Is that like the Bible with a little N?
It ain't quite the same as getting that eternity on the escape vessels.
Hey, you know, I'm a flexible guy.
You know, he changes the rules. I can change. I can move. I can understand it.
You know, I understand the way that the upper management operates.
You look like the escape doctors of the sex hobos, right?
After years of being in middle management in this cult, I understand that, you know, upper management changes their mind at a whim.
And the whole strategic direction can change.
You know, it doesn't matter if 20 years you've been predicting that the Earth was going to collapse.
The Earth is going to end on 1998 and we would be off in the present.
If Connie has a headache.
You know, if Connie has a headache, four-fifths of the dogma suddenly goes away.
You know?
That's when I don't get it.
These bimbos come in here. They start changing the rules.
And, you know, Connie's the queen of them.
I'll say it right out loud in front of Bob and everybody.
She's the queen of the bimbos.
Oh, well, hey, is that, so that's news?
So that's not news. All right, all right. I understand.
But Connie might stick over it.
But I mean that in a...
What, 84 or something? The minute Bob was killed.
But I mean it in a malicious way. I don't mean it in a loving way like most people do.
The minute Mr. Liberate the Women there shot Bob dead.
Yeah.
Yeah, I bet he's gay. He ain't.
He's gay. He's not gay. I know he's not gay.
Don't be Doug Wellman.
What's that?
You rue the day you shot Bob because that was when them bitches took over.
I rule the day.
If you left Bob hanging and swinging, why?
It'd be as if Confucius had never come along.
Dr. Stang, have they upped your prescription of Halcyon or...
Is that what's going on here?
No, no. I started this diatribe into the bowels of the things that are wrong with the church.
The philosophy.
The philosophy itself is like, it's just...
So you're talking about church point two or...
I didn't really mean to cast any dispersion on any of our previous dogmatic points because they are still all valid, all still true.
As true as truth is, you know, but perhaps I wandered too far into my own...
Oh, give me a break, Dr. Drummond. You were the one that made it a polyg... wanted it to be a men's club.
I still think it should be a men's club.
God, if only it had remained the way...
If only it had been the father church that I had promised to be. It was a polygamous kingdom at one time.
The purity. The purity was there.
And now I feel like a stud on a stud farm.
All those women I have to manage.
The Savage Revenge of Helen Keller in Retrovision.
What the hell?
The Savage Revenge of Helen Keller in Retrovision?
That is a real actual tract written by Dr. Mars, I believe.
It's a visionary piece.
It also involves performance and it is quite visionary, except for the fact that they duct tape your eyes shut.
And you're supposed to experience through your nasal cortex most of the experiences.
You express that so well.
The long knitting needles, believe me, are...
Express yourself.
It's a kind of a clean feeling you get, you know, like you've all been...
Clean yourself.
Fresh.
Clean it out.
Wipe yourself.
Find refreshment.
Ream yourself.
You peppermint douche.
Ream again.
In a clean, bossel.
A breath refreshed.
Lighten up manhole.
Yourself.
Grab rocks.
Sell us yourselves.
I will sit for you.
Oh, with...
What's he doing by that?
Stallions.
Water.
Bowie knife.
That's pretty.
Brass cannonballs.
And a brick.
Shit.
There he is.
And you just put this right on his head.
Oh my God.
I've never seen anything like that before.
He's got a head condom.
Dave has just put a condom over his complete head.
He's ready to dive right in.
I can't breathe.
Oh my God.
That's obscene.
He's getting into it now.
Ladies and gentlemen, you should see what's going on.
It's lubricated, man.
You gotta help me get this off.
In the studio.
I can't breathe.
I've never seen performance art quite like that.
Eat your heart out, Howard Stern.
Ow.
It's clean.
Calm, calm, calm.
Subgenius.com.
And it's a calm moment, friends.
A briefly calm moment because I was putting together last week's show and I suddenly got
to the point where I suddenly realized that with the Amsterdam subgenius field trip coming
up, I'm going to have to somehow crank out three shows in advance because I ain't going
to be around to do them damn shows.
Now, I could run some old reruns and things, but we don't have to do that yet, friends,
because there's been so much going on.
There was a...
I have this wonderful recording of a KPFA Berkley.
More than an hour, less than a show.
Show.
The original The Show, by the way, with a special guest, Dr. Philodrumon, and host Puzzling
Evidence, and caller Phineas Narco.
I've got tons of recordings from Winter Star Symposium sponsored by Ace here in Cleveland.
You're hearing some of the recordings from that in the background.
Einstein's Secret Orchestra and Ron Slade.
But I preached there.
Now, maybe I can...
Maybe by...
At some point, I can find some tapes of Robert Anton Wilson, who also preached there and
was really funny.
Friends, of course, we always have tons of ESO Swamp Radio originally broadcast live
on WCSB in Cleveland on Thursday nights at 11 to 1 in the Eastern time in the evenings.
And you can call that station at WCSB.org.
And call in.
Hell, why not?
And friends, I've got this incredible recording of Booger 9000, the legendary subgenius band,
the super group composed of Sphinx Drummond from the Swinging Love Corpses, and President
William Howard Taft from Homicidal Briefcase, and yes, Joe Newman from the Rudy Schwartz
Project.
An incredible recording from an Austin revival in the 90s.
Captured by our friend, Potter Nostril.
And friends, as always, every hour of Slack recently has been partly programmed by the
artists of alt.binaries.slack, where along with artwork, lately the Sabinis have been
posting sounds.
And so we have all these little clips and bits and mixes from New Monet, Artemia Salina,
Dr. Phineas Narco.
Puzzling Primates for Bob.
Jupiter Research and Mr. Sister.
And friends, we've got the Bran Flakes new album is in here.
We've got old Meteor Broad stuff as always, which I bet you've been better on the website.
You better check that stuff out.
I've got the revival recordings coming in, better ones than I've had, from Tucson Revival.
And of course, the sample, the Tampa revival samples did have not hardly been touched.
Oh yes, friends.
And finally, I may end up having, you know, as I said, I have to do three shows in a week
to get a catch up ahead.
And finally, the final show, number 778, might be nothing but outtakes with no explanations
at all.
I don't know.
Because we've got to move in a hurry, friends.
We've got to move fast because this is the church of the subgenius.
And we know because of the word of Bob that the end times are so, so very nigh.
The time is ripe for their arisal.
And XXXX day is coming, friends.
4X day.
We'll see you there at that campground, Brushwood, in Sherman, New York, come July 5th, 2001,
when the aliens shall meet with those who are worthy and have achieved their ministership-hood
in the church of the subgenius.
Stay sundry.
This is Light Master Bob.
Oh yes, praise Bob.
We didn't want to play this gig but when Jesus told us we had to, we couldn't say no
to this.
So you want to hear some Schoenberg or some Neil Diamond?
It's pretty clear, everybody here would like a Neil Diamond.
Thanks for coming.
You too.
You and you!
Awesome.
Rackling roads they get on board
We gonna ride till there ain't no more to go
Taking it slow
Lord, don't you know
I'll have me a time with a poor man's lady
Hitching on a twilight train
Ain't nothing here that I'd care to take along
Maybe a song
To sing when I want
No need to say please to no man for a happy tune
Oh, I love my rosy child
And me, we're going in style
Rackling roads they get on board
But you make me say
Sing like a guitar strum and
Hang on to make out
The song keeps running
Ah
Playing now
Playing now my baby
Rackling rosy make me smile
Girl, if it lasts for an hour
Well, that's alright
We got all night
To set the world right
Hang on to me and then fuck my asshole babe
Oh, I love my rosy child
She's got the way to make me happy
You and me, we're going in style
Rackling rosy, the store bought woman
You make me sing like a guitar strummin'
Hang on to me, girl
The song keeps running
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
Oh, my God.
Oh.
The teens of my teens are throwing a fit
Use the man, mama's really big and proud
And I need a lot of room
Cause I'm dancing with the hard on
Hey, kitty boy
guitar solo
I need to find a place where I can hide
That's right, I'll tell you why
It's a-growing and a-pushing and a-pushing from inside
Guitar solo
I'm a-beating all the time
Feel it getting bigger, it's about to rip
The teens of my teens are throwing a fit
Use the man, mama's really big and proud
And I need a lot of room
Cause I'm dancing with the hard on
Dancing with the hard on
I'm dancing
I got a diamond cutter
Dancing with the hard on
It's a blue fader
The hard-dropping muscle of love
Dancing with the hard on
Make way for the hard-sucking
Yeah, that's right
They know how it feels
When you've been dancing with the hard on
guitar solo
Guitar solo
Alright, but I need something to play
Ya-ya-ya
Lords of Acid is just about nothing but
that kind of
Yeah, right
Richard and Kitty Cat
Well, how about a pronunzimental
of earth-squacking impertinence
Somebody told me that people have
group sex at Lords of Acid
acid concerts i said now i've been to a 5x days and a thrill kill concert i've seen them all
just about but and this young lady that was explaining this to me said well i had my first
three-way at a lords of acid concert well everybody had a three-way there but they're
talking about long sliking dogs they're talking about three-way hits no i thought they're i think
they were talking about three-way sexual activities with a prairie squid a man on one
end a woman on the other and a squid in the middle you better believe it baby and sometimes you can
get another guy or girl in there depending on how if it's a large enough and willing enough
depending on how big the ink sack is on the squid that's right you can always use the ink sack if
once it's been de-inked can you put them together like a
little
little pioneer toy when you were 75 years old?
We've got those de-inking suction cup pad machines
at Subgenius Foundation.
Huh?
I mean, just if you had three squid.
Not three squids.
I'm, of course, an erudite person.
Three squid, could you just snap them together like blocks?
And they would serve the same purpose
of perhaps 100 just clears?
The South American Army squid will do that.
They will actually form bridges of their own bodies
across rivers so that their horny squid mates
can get across, you know, at the cost of thousands of lives,
yet thousands more will live.
The reason for the psychic experiments.
Look here.
The Army squid are not only growing in size
through conjugating and multiplying,
but they have one mind.
One heart, one mind.
Much like you, Dr. F.
If you cut off the head,
it just grows another one.
If you pull a beak, another beak appears.
If you shave an eyebrow, another thing laughs at you
and cries at you.
If you pull out its fangs, it grows twice as many.
If you pull its ears, it wants you to rub its belly.
If you give it milk, it will suck your blood.
All these things and more,
can be yours at Squid Town, Prairie Town, USA.
My, miles and miles of furrowed dirt
and squid flipping and undulating
in each and every patch.
I thought I'd died and gone to heaven.
Yeah, Rose, Pond Rose,
I never believed there could be such a squid farm.
Oh, fine.
Squids, as far as I can see.
They're slopping and slotting.
I think they're ready to be peared.
I got my vial.
Hey, Grease.
I'm all greased up and ready to go.
Look, look, I got one of them fake beauty marks.
I'm sorry, it's a melanoma.
But look, I got a tear.
Tight, tight, tight pants.
I got a tight squid here.
Yeah.
I'm retired.
A little bit of that sorrel sausage sorcery there, eh?
That's right.
I like to get down in them furrows and just plow.
Plow.
You know what I mean?
Just plow my way.
Use one squid as a condom for use of another squid.
Yep.
And then use a bigger one atop them.
We were the ones who invented them things back in the dome.
You know, back in the dome.
Well, back under them, you could take one of them
and you would shave your eyebrow for you.
You wouldn't have to even sit in a chair.
You could just sit there and lecture it about anything that came to your mind.
I tried to get a patent on those things,
but it turns out you can't patent a formula.
That's right.
But that didn't matter back in the day.
And that's all you really need to create that.
We just sit there whittling and having the squid.
Whittling and having.
Mammy didn't know nothing.
We did all kinds of songs.
Knowing and having.
Mammy was none the wiser.
Remember the squid songs we used to make up when we had nothing else to do
but just try to recharge our depleted accordion?
Knowing the squids.
Yep.
Didn't know them real personal.
Squids.
Having the squids.
Plowing the squids.
Squidding around on the squids.
Squid cakes.
I like to just take it in my hand.
Squid soup.
Squid sandwiches.
Look at it for maybe a half an hour.
Squid bed.
Scream it, squid.
Squid flags.
Squid puddin'.
Squid beach furniture.
Squid primavera.
There's none like squid puddin', though.
All that stuff.
Everybody's grandmother made squid puddin' out of their own orifices.
Yep.
And squid strudel is good, too.
Well, you had a dry, dry old granny.
Not like the rest of us.
Oh, no.
We used to dry out the grannies.
I remember that.
We'd take the grannies and we'd string them up.
Smoke them.
And get them cured.
For a long time.
Two, three, four weeks.
We would be cured, but we would never get high off of it.
Jerked granny.
Nope.
Wasn't right.
Besides, Grandpa didn't like that.
No, he wanted all to himself.
He wanted to do his own jerking.
He walked 50 miles a day to go to a squid.
And then grandma, she walked until she quit squid.
She'd walk about 25 miles a day.
And they just keep telling the same story.
Everybody knows you took the squid bus.
Grandpa been jerking with that prairie squid murkin'.
I remember that old song.
Grandpa.
Aliens coming to earth to get our beef jerking.
Bob said it, so you better pick up on it.
If Bob says that traffic light is green,
but it looks red to you, floor it.
Floor that.
Close your eyes and gas it to the max.
Do what Bob said, not what your mind said.
Who do you trust, friends?
Who do you trust?
Your mind or Bob Dobbs?
Get that part straight first.
But people are afraid to trust.
You know, I don't blame them.
We've all been burned at one point because we trusted the conspiracy,
or we wouldn't be so screwed up as we are.
We wouldn't be in this room right now.
But, you know, you go, well, if I can't trust Bob, who can I trust?
Friends, you cannot trust Bob to do what's right for you.
Okay?
That's in your hands.
That's entirely in your hands.
But you can trust Bob to do what's right for Bob,
which you can't even trust yourself about.
So, friends, Bob is real, and yet some people don't believe in Bob
because either he's too good,
too good to be true,
or they fear Bob.
You know, just as some people, normal humans, sometimes fear,
well, actually, it's the old-timey,
I know a lot of old-time subgeniuses that fear computers and the Internet.
There's always resistance to anything new,
and Bob Dobbs is always new and improved.
So there's always going to be somebody scared of him.
Did you know that Hitler owned 8,000 robots?
He owned 960 acres of land in Colorado.
What?
Hitler.
No.
Yes, he did.
He owned 8,960 acres of land in Colorado.
Why, no American citizen would do business with Adolf Hitler.
I'm optimistic this can happen.
That's nothing, though.
Mata Hari was making it.
You know how much she made?
$7,500 a throw.
To ask every American.
There must have been some position.
There's a balloon there, boy.
And so as we begin the work of healing our nation...
God's going to strike you down.
Who's healing our nation now?
In a big thunderstorm.
Hey, something happened to that thing, Doug.
I feel up your pain.
You know, how the hell did you ever survive the last seven years without your beauty, your trunks?
I'm sorry.
Well, what happens is if you've been around enough squid,
well, they get into you.
They just start reproducin' and hollerin' and carryin' on.
Before you know it, you're just a vessel for squid intelligence.
Then you gotta send them to college.
Exactly.
Start all over again.
You're gonna get done with the little peckers.
Keep you young.
Keep you young and quick.
My feet have gone to sleep while we're talking about this, and I think my hemorrhoids come back.
No.
If we could maybe change the subject a little bit.
All right.
I know that's the only thing you ever wanna really talk about in depth.
I'm being violated.
But for cryin' out loud, we've been talkin' about it for six weeks now.
I know.
Hey, I know.
You've been caught red-handed mug reasonin'.
I think you've punished me.
Yeah, I know.
Stop the things you do
Oh, I can't stand
No roads around, I can't stand
No woods down, I wouldn't fail on you
Because you're mine
I can't stand
No roads around, I can't stand
No woods down, I wouldn't fail on you
Oh, because you're mine
Because you're mine
Girl, you're better off like me
Boys have a vagina
Girls have a penis
Man is woman and woman is man
Guys want things
I'm setting you on fire.
Hummin' a, humming a, humming a.
A woman pretending to be a man pretending to be a woman?
Ridiculous.
It's preposterous.
In fact, it's so preposterous no one would ever believe it.
There's gonna be hell.
Medically impossible.
It's not really hard to believe.
It's just hard for you to accept.
Medically impossible.
God.
Castrate him.
Good heavens.
Jesus.
Oh, my God.
Ah!
You can hit me while I whip this out.
Guard.
Castrate him.
Don't.
Don't let me pass.
Guard.
Castrate him.
This is not a haphazard maneuver.
Careful planning for it started months back.
Get another couple and get a blonde limbo.
Well, the joke's on you.
I'm not even a real blonde.
Beware.
Beware of the big green.
Dragon that sits on your doorstep.
He eats little boys.
Boys have such a kind.
I've got tails.
Ah!
Big.
Rats.
Ah!
Kani is spewing, too, by
reverend protectrix Amazonia...
Ding, ding!
Isn't a boy named
Sid Lam in heaven?
He cannot leave the back
of the EMS vehicle
singing to the various
crippled victims
of the gerbling problems.
I guess we want to call them problems.
Somebody was clearly at fault
and didn't want to take...
Didn't want to take credit.
Well, if you don't feed the gerbil, what do you think's going to happen?
Soon, the gerbil becomes very hungry.
As his belly becomes hollow and his skin becomes slick,
as the hair falls out and his eyes grow weak, he will bite at anything.
At the last minute, I will substitute the starving gerbil for the healthy one.
We're just about ready now.
The master won't suspect until it's too late.
He humiliates you.
That's the only...
Come here, cutie. Hey, come here.
Did you hear what I said? I said, come here.
Come here, daddy. You look so good.
I will talk to the girl.
She's going to plan.
I know I cannot verify it, but I feel that she will understand.
There is no escape.
Oh.
I have a mission to perform.
Give me some more.
Very well.
I will recalculate.
Oh.
Really?
Mmm.
Esquire, what's that?
See that's the secret.
This is it.
Undead and police?
It's fake.
The things you are interested in?
.
How?
I want to see the girl Alice again.
Beautiful face, monsieur.
Oh, yes, of course.
You remember her.
She drove everyone crazy.
Ah, the woman was for herself.
Oh, jeez.
She was at the Oyster Bar one time
and she was clipping the cathedral,
as we used to call it.
She was making time with a one-eyed man.
Man, there they were,
exchanging spit in the middle of the barbecue hour.
No man blinded me.
She was no good.
She was no bad, you know.
She looks like one of the Stepford Stepmothers.
I bet you can see the Latin side of her
when you turn her upside down.
I bet she's got one of those little fuzzy monkeys, eh?
Oh, no, you shake her and...
Probably goes all the way up to her belly button, huh?
Bob, you don't even know who he is
and you might miss him
if you didn't have a real good look at him.
You wouldn't even know who he looked like.
They don't believe I'm Christ, do they?
If we're gonna stop them,
they're gonna kill us all!
They don't believe I'm Christ, do they?
No.
Do you feel blamed?
Are you mad?
I will pull your goddamn tongue out of the road!
If you didn't have a real good look at him,
you wouldn't have known how you were like.
You knew you haven't got an excuse,
but I've done all kinds of things.
I will pull your goddamn tongue out of the road!
There will be no excuse!
Thank you very much.
No worries.
Yes.
No, I'm good.
And do you remember when you were a little girl, perhaps,
and your father gave you a beating?
Well, I...
And get ready for a shock!
The music that they're planning to use
to crumble the morals of America
is this rotten, filthy, dirty, lewd,
lascivious junk called Rock and Roll.
It isn't just the lyrics and the music.
It's all Satan's.
Will they dwell among the stars?
They make millions of trips to planet Earth daily, traveling faster than the speed of light.
By an interest in swearing with language that would stand a failure's hand, I'm done.
They attempt to de-bless, possess, and out-bless their victims.
Psychiatrists and psychologists are no match for these ETs.
Mob? Mob?
I think of Bob as a protean sex gland.
Often, when I think of myself ensconced in a little home, a little domicile on the pipe on the ring of Saturn's moon,
I can see little flocks of pastures of green sheep floating by,
and what do they call those, hillocks, like a little cottage with smoke curling out of it,
and each one resembles a pipe.
And I can see myself there with my own little Connie.
Connie of my own design, perhaps.
Hairy-footed, perhaps with a face much bigger than the rest of her body.
I like that kind, too.
I thought you did, and that's why I brought her up.
She's been calling you again, Stank.
That big head girl from space has been calling you, Stank.
You know, I think all I ever get is your machine.
I know you've been thinking of me.
I went back to the carnival again and went on the ferris wheel and rode the merry-go-round,
and all I could do was think of you.
Of course, it was very hard to fit my head in.
The merry-go-round was low-ceiling.
But still, I was alone.
And thought of you.
I ate a half a loaf of bread.
Then I played with myself and cried again.
Then I went on the ferris wheel.
I had to be restrained because my head was disturbing the other passengers.
And I thought of you again.
I went down to the boardwalk and looked at the sea.
And all I could see was you, Reverend.
Why you don't call me back sometime?
Well, it's really a huge little ice cream.
A woman from space will call you back again.
Hoping sometime you'll return my call.
Bye.
It's so strange.
You know, they...
All those groupies.
Yeah, I remember.
All they needed to do was to just send their $30.
To Bob.
And I know that's all they're trying to do is get close to Bob.
They think I know Bob's phone number.
And I do.
You do.
But they think I can give it to them.
And I can't.
I just can't.
And instead of giving you their $30, what do they do?
They come up to you and in time, they say something stupid.
They play with your hairy feet.
They talk backwards to you and try and trick you.
Time is right.
Listen to the words.
Time, yes.
How many times has this happened at Divisional?
Every time.
Every damn one.
I remember the last time I was playing with Einstein's Secret Orchestra at the Divisional
for the Reverend Ivan Zang of the Church of the Subgenius.
We just finished a song and a rush of about 11 women.
No, it's always 15-year-old guys with glasses.
Stangly clothes.
If only it was women.
Yeah, if only it was women who didn't look like kind of fat guys in those weird, you know,
Pendleston shirts with like...
With a Bob shirt.
With real thick glasses.
That's too tight.
Right.
Guys that kind of look like us, you know, and only...
I thought that was really good.
You know, the only part I enjoy was saying, you know, they're real smart and everything.
Yeah, but you know what?
You missed this one note.
I saw where you missed this note.
Yeah, it looks smart and shit.
And there's a link on your website.
It's dead.
I wanted to make sure you knew about that.
You know what's wrong with those CDs?
That's where they go skipping.
No, man.
We don't want that.
That's a coding problem.
Hi.
How have you been?
I'm watching you.
Are you all right?
Are you hungry?
Can I get you anything?
A cup of coffee, perhaps?
A sandwich?
A ham?
I'd like some Guinness and some crackers.
A bee job?
Maybe some...
Knotted nylons?
Oh, yes, bees.
Yes.
I can bring you peas.
Would you like some peas, honey?
I can make honey for you.
No, they don't talk that way.
The hot Yoo-Hoo bottle?
No, they don't wear Hulu skirts.
They don't talk funny languages for our pleasure.
No, they just say, price Bob.
None of them have hair on their faces.
I found my copy of Book of the Subgenius for a dollar at the cutout bin.
I saw that.
I'm buying it.
Some of them do have the little lines, the dotted lines for the cranial implants
and the place where they took off the top of their head.
I like that.
She's pretty, don't you think?
You creeped her out.
Actually, to be quite honest, there's been times when I've thought, maybe this is going too far.
I would get frustrated with the sheer nerdliness of some subgeniuses, you know,
because it just seemed like, God, I didn't know they were going to be so dysfunctional and messed up.
Well, duh!
Duh!
It finally sunk in.
That is what this is.
That's what the Church of the Subgenius is all about.
Of course they're fucked up and dysfunctional,
because there really is a conspiracy of normal people sapping away their slack.
And of course they're fucked up, and of course that's why Bob is their god.
Now, friends, when X-Day didn't happen in 1998, we were so sad.
We were going, oh, man, we could have had a new government that was no government at all.
That, you know, that Bob would be the leader and he never shows up.
We'd have a new church where you didn't have to get up at 7 in the morning.
You could worship it drunk until midnight Saturday night in bars.
We'd have a new coolness where, you know, coolness was a...
completely defined by each individual uncool weirdo.
Friends, so X-Day didn't happen.
What are we waiting for?
Do we really have to depend on some pipe-smoking dot-faced salesman
or a bunch of aliens from outer space or a bunch of invisible monsters to make our own slack?
Hell no, friends.
Bob is not the answer and neither is anything else.
We must learn to think.
We must learn to think for ourselves.
Although only Bob can show us how.
And we must.
All of you had better.
You must question authority.
Or else, huh?
We've got somebody here who's been reading their pre-scriptures.
There.
One who dares to really question authority.
And, friends, really, honestly, I think that as bad as things are,
if you can just...
The scientific basis of slack,
is this.
Fuck them if they can't take a joke!
Even if they help fuck them if they can't tell a joke.
Yo, yeah.
Y'know what time it is?
If you need more information about the Church of the Subgenius,
please write to this address I'm about to give.
That's b-b-b-BAAAWWWWW.
That post office box.
140306 Dallas, Texas.
75214.
Once again, that's box 140306 Dallas, Texas.
www.subgenius.com
And praise the...
We pulled off to the side.
We just knew they weren't a ride.
The sweetest quilt you'll ever know.
Blow you right through the door.
They'll blow you right through the barn door.
A 3D script falling from the sky.
You're reading a script and you're thinking...
It's so hot.
A 3D script where they're fucking unknown.
A 3D script.
I got a tentacle.
Oh no! There's a tube!
Oh, hey, tentacles!
Hey, tentacles!
Hey, oh, there's a tentacle!
Oh my God! Oh, there's a tentacle!
Oh, there's suction cups!
Oh, my God!
It hurts when they peel the suction cups off.
I like it so much.
Oh, yeah!
Woo-hoo, baby!
So, if
you're ever out of your
life, don't
think you have to run high.
When you see some hairy pink
pink snow
falling down, oh no.
Hairy pink snow
falling down right from the sky.
Just pull on over
and you'll be fine.
All the hairy squid is the best best
eye. Use some
genius and joy to ride them.
Maybe three-d squid
falling from the sky.
Maybe three-d squid and a
hairy squid
falling on the road.
Maybe three-d squid
that's right, the Lord!
fell from the sky
in front of my car while I was
driving down the high mountain.
I pulled over, I opened my
car door, and they were blowing my mind
through the car door.
Praise the Holy Hairy Squid.
Ah, yeah!
Woo-hoo!
Misha wosY
Wao!
yyyyy
Outro Music