Nan nan nan nan nan nan nan.
Mom. Mom.
From PR News in Washington, I'm Saddam's half-brother.
Pope John Paul II waved the tape measure and terrorized the crowd at Rome's hospital for 31 years.
The pope is a Cub Scout catcher who led a traditional prayer.
Starting tomorrow, the 84-year-old pontiff will be shipped to recycling plants.
Syria has denied an accusation that it was directly involved in PR News in Washington.
From PR News in Washington, I'm advised to stay indoors.
Meanwhile, President Bush may not be in a persistent vegetative state.
Jeb Bush has refused to reinsert a feeding tube in the brain-damaged president.
From PR News in Washington, I'm Bernd.
Death by South African President Becky.
John Paul could be seen holding a large weenie.
I am near, he said. I also offer God's pee-pee.
This is tomorrow.
Bob. Bob.
Operation Push is releasing black Jacksons from universities.
Lebanese officials haven't shown much inclination to probe PR News Washington.
What's it like to have high or low blood pressure?
Increased heart rate or heart or blood vessel disease?
Dry mouth, menstrual cramps, dizziness, insomnia, liver problems.
Problems urinate.
Constipation, nausea and decreased sexual side effects.
Ask your doctor about the self genius.
Our all-star.
We are king.
Distracted, disorganized, restless, unable to finish.
So let there be no mistaking this morning.
This sermon on tithing is a sermon where I'd seek what is yours.
Ten percent he wants for protection.
Eh, protection.
This motivation to go before God and give God something.
This tithing is to bribe God, pay God, to get God to do something on our behalf.
Ten, twenty, thirty, forty.
Forty-five hundred. Five thousand.
Pay up. Pay for protection. Ten percent or I'll...
Okay, I'll pay.
You win.
Go for the racket. Take ten.
Ten percent.
And it's all over.
Here's the money.
There we got a wind up.
Count the money, May.
Eight thousand, nineteen thousand, twenty thousand.
Look at it pile up.
Ten thousand, twenty thousand.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
From PR News in Washington, I'm screaming for help.
The nation's Roman Catholic bishops abandoned that illegal truck jammed with Catholics.
It is wise to always err.
The Supreme Court has declined to allow PR News.
Watch Bob quit smoking at bobquits.com.
All pulled out black, black, black, black, black.
Vapor, vapor, vapor, vapor, soup, soup, soup, soup, soup, soup, soup, soup, soup.
Soup, soup, soup, soup, soup, soup, soup, soup, soup, soup, soup, soup, soup, soup, soup, soup, soup.
All night long.
Blood dump, blood dump, blood dump.
Take your medicine.
Have a good night.
Kids vapor, kids vapor.
What's it like to have urinating mouth?
What's life, sexual sin, sin, sinia?
What's neural menstrual type?
Sex cramps, life problems, constipating, dyscoma, sexual nausea and higher dry blood problems,
like increased heart rate or decreased blood ziness.
Feeling stressed?
Hey, I'm starting to sweat here.
Threatened?
People we've never met wish we were dead.
A fairy tale of a man who's never been threatened.
Afraid.
Preemptin eliminates these feelings instantly,
restoring confidence and wiping away potential threats before they can harm you.
With fast-acting Preemptin working thousands of miles away,
there are no direct physical side effects guaranteed.
Preemptin. Available without a prescription.
Don't you deserve to feel safe again?
Treatment targets may not be actual threats.
Manufacturer not liable for retribution or damages.
Cost of treatment may be unlimited.
International approval pending.
Harmful if swallowed.
Sexual urinating.
Conscionality is tight.
Right now.
Side effects.
Heart infections.
Tuberculosis.
Nervous blood disorders.
And blood clots.
Do it.
Diarrhea.
Kidney.
Liver.
Or gallbladder.
Diarrhea.
Kidney.
Liver.
Or gallbladder.
Diarrhea.
Kidney.
Liver.
Or gallbladder.
Diarrhea.
It comes buttered, battered, basted, and roasted.
Stinky.
Diarrhea.
Bad diarrhea.
But it also comes from mom.
Kidney.
Blockage.
Dizziness.
Diarrhea with blood and stool.
And Grandpa Joe.
Bad diarrhea.
Or diarrhea with adhesions.
Kidney.
Liver.
Or gallbladder.
Or adhesions.
A healthy diarrhea can help.
And ask your doctor about adding unexplained women who aren't pregnant.
Breast.
Or may become pregnant.
Cause the stinky.
You're gonna love it.
What more do you want?
From PR News in Washington, I'm being watched closely by the heads from Canada and Mexico.
The government says the brain-damaged federal appellate court has now been lowered from 42 to 1.
The ruler of PR News remains in Washington.
Bob is deteriorating rapidly without persistent PR News.
This is PR News in Texas.
Talk about steroids.
I have used steroids.
I love and respect performance-enhancing drugs.
Inject me with steroids.
I am intrigued with the idea of steroids.
You wake up, it's gonna work.
You wake up and go to work.
You wake up.
You go to work.
I'm going to fly.
You can't do what you can't do.
You wake up and go to work.
Yeah, baby.
That was Stylex.
Stylex, dear friends, from, where are they from?
Bowling Green, I think.
We saw them at the Detroit Devival,
which we'll be playing bits from in future shows
and in this future show.
This is a future show.
It's such a futurismo show.
Bear that in mind.
Be cognizant that this show is taking place in the distant future.
Each moment it becomes the future as we spend it.
But friends, yes, Stylex.
I guess you could find them by way of Stylex.com,
although I'm really just guessing.
Actually, that's StylexOhio.com.
That's S-T-Y-L-E-X.
They were unbelievable.
It was like the divos all over again.
And friends, this show, which has a theme, by the way,
the theme of insanity, illness, and decay.
Just look at the money pile up.
Ah, yes.
The opening cuts were quite a varying bunch of collages,
but they were almost all by Fernanda Nde, Lee Murr,
and Reverend Norell Preff, who is back,
and also Reverend Chastain.
Chastain Smurker from Oz did a little bit in there.
Oh, and Dr. Levity.
The knee-brew subgenius, Dr. Levity, David Levity,
did that ad for Preemptin,
which you missed, Dave, because you were off getting medicated.
Oh, I love ads about, you know, fake, phony, satirical ads
about, you know, medical cycle, therapeutic drugs.
Shh, shh, shh, shh, shh.
Shh.
I love them.
I'm sorry.
I've noticed that some of them are done in such a way
as to almost provoke a psychotic episode.
Yeah, they go on longer than the preferred 30-second slot
with a two-second hang tag on either side
so you can build in and swell,
and then come back out and repeat three times
the name of the product.
Well, it's like it'll mimic your bad brain and your bad blood,
where suddenly the camera's wide-angle
and people are laughing into the lens at you
and looking menacing,
and cruel and happy at the same time.
And it says,
Are you feeling isolated, alone, and sad?
Then you need PercoHap.
Baxatil.
Yes.
Hapitil.
A kid will use it because bleeding of the groin,
dark eyelashes, and profuse character change.
And they will, too.
That's the funny thing.
They do need to give you all those disclaimers
because that stuff creeps up on you.
And now they're putting weird,
perfumes in them to make them available to children.
They smell like Flintstoners.
And so the little kids will drop them in their pocket
when they go to Right Aid or Discount
or wherever, Discount Meds.
You know, this should not be marketed
to people smaller than four foot high.
Kids on drugs.
They can prove that they're just abnormally short
and need a lot of psychoactive drugs.
But, you know, grade schools now?
People taking Xanax and Tropex in grade school?
I don't know.
Do you know where to get any?
Of course I know where to get it all.
But the thing is, you have to open the right door
with the right key.
Isn't that what it's all about?
It's opening new doors, baby.
Open the new doorway to mental illness.
Break on through to the other side, dude.
It's all in the mind.
Well, try one of those doors.
Yes, they do look very nice, don't they?
Yes, they do.
They do, though, don't they?
Don't they, though?
Don't.
Voila, that's dope.
One door closes, another door opens.
I could just see Martini, like, blinking rapidly,
asking for his medication and being real refusenik and stuff
and Nurse Ratched grabbing him and throttling him
and shoving him down his throat with one of those toilet plungers.
This is my vision of modern mental health.
A restructuring of the brain without any effort from within.
Just a forced thing.
I'm sorry, I'll shut up now.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
No, you were making just the...
You were saying...
You took the words right out of my mouth.
I was also making you sleep.
I wonder why you did that.
Because I like the smell of those tasty words
and I love the rumblings of your mouth,
so put two and two together and you get marshmallows.
You know, Dave, sometimes I can't really appreciate the tastiness.
Of your verbs.
Until I come back from here
and go to that other time of there and then
and hear it again.
Well, you are...
And then it's like a whole different world.
Well, it's now when you hear it again
because that's why you should record all this stuff
because we are recording in the future
and I'm tired of it too.
I noticed you were getting very sleepy there.
Oh, that's because of the pills.
I had to take the pills to keep me from falling asleep.
Did you take E-popped pills?
Uh...
Well, a generic.
A generic form of E-pop.
The generic E-pop.
Yeah, yeah.
That's when he coughs up his...
I took a red one.
I took two red ones and one blue one.
He coughs up his mental cud
and re-choose the lonesome cowboy Dave.
Cough, cough, cough.
Oh, cough it.
Then he can actually understand.
Cough it up now.
Cough it up.
You have to cough it up.
The smoke begins billowing out of your Vatican apartments
and a new pope has been elected.
A new E-popped of the Church of the...
Have they elected the new pope?
Is it Pope Black?
Or is it Pope Perro?
I think they have the pope...
Both Pope Black and both Pope Perro have a lot of...
Is it the brown pope?
Yeah, because it was supposed to be the Antichrist.
Whoever the next pope is would be the Antichrist.
Well, he was born and raised in Vacaville
and they've been experimenting on him since then.
But I guess he's going to be the new one.
The brown...
Vacaville, is that Margarita, like Margaritaville?
Vacaville?
Yeah, except you have to drink the accessions of cow.
Oh, okay.
The thyroid glands.
Listen.
I hear voices.
Voices in my head.
People learn.
In the music.
They can smell it.
They can smell it in your words.
Allora, padre deve ricordare una cosa.
Quando entriamo, deve detto...
Deve dire...
Il nombre tre volte.
Il nome vero.
Ricordare...
I'm sorry, father.
I can't understand Italian.
I'm so nervous.
I'm forgetting my Italian.
I'm saying when you enter the room after the doctor leaves,
you must say his true name three times.
Okay.
I think I can remember.
I must say his real name three times.
Carol Ortilla.
Carol?
No, no.
His real name.
Yeah.
Ivan Stang.
Thank you.
Yes, yes.
People say I'm crazy.
But is it crazy to say that Bob is the real thing, baby?
And slack is where it's at.
Come on, man.
Get down.
He's alive.
He's a miracle.
Una miracola.
Il papa se vive.
People say I'm crazy.
Wait, where is that?
That was the L.S. Dudes, that music in the background.
That's another great name.
It was in the Detroit Revival.
The L.S. Dudes.
That's a lovely name.
I wish I would have created some other name.
They do great video.
Excellent video production.
There was a couple of devoid.
The birds.
The avial fornication.
The birds having anal sex.
Do you remember that little three-minute vignette?
Which now?
Now, these guys on the radio are starting to call blogs.
Okay?
And, you know, you play some songs.
You say, that little blog was like Jimmy Smith in 1958.
You know, I'm sorry.
They're calling what blogs?
They're calling little bits of anything blogs now.
Little bits of film.
Little bits of music.
What?
Little bits of even like a rant.
Even a rant where the Reverend Ivan Stang would be called a,
Stang is blogging a blog.
Now this is a blogging dude.
It shows that they've run.
They should be flogged.
They should be flogged from the blog.
For this rape of the English.
For the rape of the blog.
The king's bloglish.
They should be put against him.
King blog will be infuriated.
Guard, seize him.
Bring him to me.
So, you have been blogging about.
Oh, wait.
Now I'm doing it.
No, it's my place.
So, you have been blogging about.
You're supposed to respond now quickly.
Way out, baby.
The L.S.
Dudes.
Baby.
It is way out, isn't it?
Are those the L.S.
Dudes?
Actually, I don't know where I'm at now.
This is the one that marked Dave's background music.
Psychophant to call on.
My words to you in closing today.
Climbing.
I'm just going to talk to you out of my heart.
Talk to you out of my heart.
Talk to you.
You are, you are jerky.
I'm going to talk to you out of my liver.
You are jerky.
Anything but the brain.
Don't talk from the brain.
And now from my spleen.
Oh, body parts.
Leave those brains alone, baby.
Leave those brains alone.
They taste real bad.
They smell real.
They feel sad.
Leave those brains.
Sex.
On my meds again.
Really need to get on my meds again.
My manic spells are losing me all of my friends.
And I can't wait to get on my
meds again.
On my meds again I've been places
that I've ever been.
Don't forget Zyprexa and the Wellbutrin.
And I can't wait to get on my meds again.
On my meds again.
Cause when I go off them,
I go down the highway.
I'm at odds and ends.
With strangers I think should be pointing my way.
And they all say,
On your meds again.
You really need to get on your meds again.
You can.
Maybe when you do we can make some amends.
But for right now get on your meds again.
I'm on my meds again.
But for right now get on your meds!
That from nationalcynical.com.
And now, back to our mental illness special.
Starring Mr. Fernandanande Limura.
I'll do my hoot-out.
No.
Why?
I'll tell you why.
Hoot-out.
Would you do a hoot-out?
No.
Why?
I'll tell you why.
Hoot-out.
Magic and make-believe.
I choked you hard enough, you'll bring me back.
My cubbyhole.
I didn't say we're gonna swervel.
Hey, sometimes the older that the society is,
and you can say it's this raw shit being gonna swervel.
Some shit's gonna swervel.
Maybe later.
Do it all.
Fernanda Dandy-Lemur.
And now, the first of the recordings from the March 2005 subgenius revival in Detroit.
Dear friends, here be Senator Thompson Speck, reciting a nice poem by Doug Smith, age 23.
I am too intent to die!
I am insured for acts of God and Satan.
I cannot be tracked on radar!
Ahhhhh!
Ah, yes, baby!
I am a bacteriological weapon!
I am on and loaded!
I'm a fission reactor!
I fart plutonium.
When they plug me in, the lights go out in Hong Kong!
Come and get me!
I cook and eat my dead.
Yahoo!
The devil's here!
I can't answer my ideal playground!
Because I think backwards!
And I do it for fun!
I've sired retarded space bastards across the cosmos.
When I drop my drones, Mother Nature swoons.
Yeah!
I kidnap the future and I ransomed it for the past!
I left my spore on the rock of ages.
Ooh!
Down the flush with me!
Who will spill my dust?
I'm a crime-fighting master criminal!
I am not insane!
I'm a sign!
Opiates are the master of my religion because I take drugs!
I am a rib-snorter.
And I cram the coca leaves right into my veins before they're picked off the tree!
Come on and give me cancer!
I will spit up the tumor and butter my brain with the juice!
Yeah!
I'm a moray eel!
I am a Komodo dragon!
I am a killer whale!
Mirabdum is fucked!
I have a triple backbone!
I was sired by the wolfman!
Give me all your slack!
I told Jesus that I wouldn't go to church and he shook my hand!
I have my own personal saviors.
And I change them every hour!
I'm enlightened!
I achieved Nirvana and took it home with me!
Yeah!
When the rapture comes, I'll make them quake!
They will never clean my cage!
Never clean my cage.
So this is the second Detroit sub-tribe.
The genius revival.
Woo!
You look confused, sir.
Stand away from the...
Alright, stand away from the parking meter.
Sir, put your hands in your pocket.
Sir, it's okay. I have mental illness.
Of course you have it.
I have the mental illnesses.
Yeah, we all have them, sir. Just remain calm while we inspect your pockets.
The contents there...
But don't you understand, it's not crime.
Mental illness is a disease.
Don't worry, there's no...
It's a disease, that's all.
We have no proof of a thought crime.
Let's look in those pockets.
Come on, man, that's double plus ungood, dude.
This is blogging my mind.
You're ungooding me out, man.
Grab the woman first.
Well, the Bible says we should have blogs.
You have...
I'm a blog user, sure, I admit it.
You have more than you're supposed to.
I read blogs because it makes me feel good.
I'm so blogged, seriously.
I'm a blog user, seriously.
They're all crazy nowadays. They're all high on these blogs.
Stick them in the paddy wagon!
You are dirty.
Dirty.
We're all dirt.
But...
I'm so tired of being dirt.
I think I've spent the last 300 years of my life being dirt.
Rapid, slow, and unkind.
I move with the movements of the earth.
Dirt.
Stone.
A rolling stone gathers no mass.
I...
You're right.
All of you are right.
Actually, you're right.
I'm mad.
The great,
the incongruous hero
is mad.
Yes, that's right.
I'm mad. Mad.
Mad.
But mind you,
madness
is a very healthy sickness.
If it weren't for my madness,
I would have gone insane
long ago.
I was going to tell you about the schizophrenic
when he filled out his income tax,
you know.
You know what he did?
He carried himself with two exemptions.
But I think y'all are so great
you ought to run for president.
You know, politics,
some kind of politics
let the whole world know about you.
Well, Winona, I'm afraid
the U.S. has enough problems as it is.
We're trying to support J.R. Bob Dobbs
for World Overlord.
Politics.
There was this schizophrenic
that was running for president
or something, and his friend
told him that he sure was glad
that I've got half a mind
to vote for you. Thank you.
Thank you.
I'm going to tell you about
one of the
forbidden sciences.
You will pay to know what you really think.
If I pay money, then all of a sudden
everything becomes clear?
Everyone needs to know what they're really thinking
in their minds, and we can provide them
with helpful hints.
By the way, you can tell Bob that I got his message
and I understand.
Of course, at first I didn't know for sure
it wasn't part of the conspiracy,
but now I'm pretty sure it was him.
I'm pretty sure it was him, and Tom,
I'll be looking at next week's TV Guide
just to be sure.
Thanks a lot. I understand your code completely.
I think it's great that you give inspiration
to people like that who are obviously
out of their minds.
Bob said early in the game
that we should go for, since the
country itself seems to be going crazy,
that maybe crazy people are
the only ones that should be given
any responsibility.
Yesterday I announced on this program
that I was going to commit public suicide.
Admittedly an act of madness.
Well, I'll tell you what happened.
I just ran out of bullshit.
All right, cut him off.
Folks, out there in radio land,
today the Reverend R.D. Sopker
will be brought to you,
a real down-to-earth religious fanatic
who saves buildings,
and then the people.
How about that, boys and girls?
Get your decoder pins.
Forget letters on that.
I'm dissolving.
I wonder why I don't have my own show.
I tell the truth.
Hello, younger bear.
Goodbye.
There was a boy whose life I'd saved
through his mortal embarrassment.
Did you catch rabbits on your hunting trip?
No.
Then don't give the rabbits you didn't catch
to Buffalo Wallow Woman.
You see, younger bear had become
a contrary.
The most dangerous of all Cheyenne warriors
because the way they live
drives them half crazy.
Except for battle,
a contrary does everything backwards.
He says goodbye
when he means hello.
Yes when he means no.
Walks through bushes instead of on trails
and washes with dirt
and dries with water and so forth.
Oh, I wish I were a warrior.
I wish I were a king.
Oh, I wish I qualified.
He's saying something over there.
Way over on that other channel.
No, you can't see left.
You can't hear anything.
You notice that our fish is strapped in.
He cannot see the two-way mirror
nor can he hear our instructions, ladies and gentlemen.
So you will be with us on this experiment
in green brain
in private.
We have his brain here
which we've taken out in a hologram.
It looks much like it does inside his head right now.
We're going to put it in the Vegematic.
You'll notice a lot of static.
A lot of static blur.
Now be careful.
Don't heat that brain up too much
because we've lost a lot of memories that way.
Perhaps we want to turn it down then.
When you put it back it just isn't the same.
Puzzling evidence.
Glass Madness. Doctors for Wotan.
From the 1981 subgenius album.
Media Barrage No. 3.
Sex, Sickness and Slack.
Other parts of this show were recorded last night
with Lonesome Cowboy Dave and Princess Wee
at WCSB in Cleveland.
But you can't tell which.
And all we can do is play
more and more and more.
It's going to drive somebody nuts.
In the year of 1963
I was committed to a metal institution.
Niagara Falls.
Slowly I turned
in stallion sidesteps.
There may be someone who looks
exactly like you.
Who is your physical counterpart
to the smallest detail.
But what about the other part?
The spiritual and the psychological
variants which go to make up
a man's soul.
And determine whether he is
sane or ginsane
or whether he is good or evil.
Perhaps your devil is a monster
and a murderer.
Perhaps you'll meet him now
on SHOCK.
The name is Juniper Johnson Jones
and I have a job here
as a happy hollow funny farm
in South Texas.
And I have a couple of folks missing.
I thought maybe you might
have your intelligent people
Uh oh, Uncle Juniper?
Is that you?
It's okay, Father. Cut it out.
I want to know if Jake might help me locate these people.
Well, they may be right here
in the room with me.
Why don't you give me some
background information.
Well, they're normal people
obviously, but sometimes
they get off the course and go south
instead of north.
I had a bed check
and they were missing
so I thought maybe they might tell me
how to find these people.
We have a happy place down here.
That's why they call it Happy Hollow.
But we're here to talk about my mental problems, folks.
I said they laugh at the saddest stuff.
You stood up and said
I am such and such and I'm mentally ill.
You wouldn't expect everybody to laugh.
But you can't be mentally ill
and self-righteous at the same time.
And yet, look how many people do it.
It's the most common thing in the world.
Anyway, I
guess what?
Don't take myself all that seriously.
I mean
look,
I'm a drunk.
And I have found
that oddly enough
that offends people
who do take themselves seriously.
And it takes a while
and it took me a while to figure it out.
But what it is, is sooner or later
it sinks into them that by definition
since I don't take myself all that seriously
I probably don't take them all that seriously either.
And they can't handle it.
They cannot handle that stuff.
And there's
nothing you can do about it.
There's absolutely
it usually takes them a while.
Oh, that guys not kidding
he really doesn't take himself seriously.
So what does he think of me?
I don't know what's right.
You don't know what's right.
I don't hear the voice of God.
Nazi,
it's you.
communism mama I don't hear the voice of God Nazism communism mama we know what
absolute evil is we've seen it we've seen it in the name of religion the
Inquisitions right it's history I don't know
I don't know
there are no simple
spinner
springer springer springer
incidents
Anurag Bhai
Mom is sleeping with her daughter's man.
Don't assume it's you!
You don't treat him right!
I don't know what's right.
You don't know what's right.
I don't expect ever to know precisely what's right.
There are no simple-minded answers.
By the great Reverend Norrell Preff, and you can get more at heavyconfetti.com.
Before that, yours truly at Winterstar Symposium.
This background music is by Tom and Joe.
And coming up, Consortium of Genius.
But now, Help-O-Pewie.
The world ends tomorrow, and you may wind up in hell as an albatross being forced to swallow Alka-Seltzers thrown to you by televangelists.
The world ends tomorrow, and you may skip mass and abuse drugs anyway.
The world ends tomorrow, and you may walk like an Egyptian, a toasted one.
The world ends tomorrow, and you may never need an engine rebuild again.
The world ends tomorrow, and you may just lie there stained and drunk as usual.
Now then, what seems to be the problem?
Oh, it's my head.
Yes, I see. Would you fill out these forms?
Now then, sign here, here, here, here, here, and here.
Good.
Are you sitting comfortably?
Yes?
Are you ready?
Are you prepared for your...
MO BO CHO NAY!
Let's go over the symptoms, shall we?
Stress.
Fear of failure.
Knowledge.
Exams.
Questions.
Answers.
Responses.
Rhetoric.
Rhetoric!
MO BO CHO NAY!
Doctor, what is your diagnosis?
A small part of you wants to die, but most of you wishes to live.
There must be a solution to this problem. Here's some advice that I'm happy to give.
The source of your consternation is buried deep inside of your head.
Get rid of the defective part yourself. You'd be a lot happier if your brain did.
MO BO CHO NAY!
Oh, Doctor, are you sure you know what you're doing?
Quiet!
Sonic Micro activated.
Oh, my brain is a mess!
Perfect. A perfect specimen!
HA HA HA!
Power.
Pressure.
Presence.
Politicians on the left.
Politicians on the right.
And politicians on the right can use a...
MO BO CHO NAY!
So much!
Next!
Okay, you're next, dude.
Go ahead, I can wait.
Consortium of Genius, friends.
From their new CD in Cog We Trust.
And you can get more at consortiumofgenius.com.
And now, friends, the greatest thing we have ever played on this show.
Wait a minute.
Now, I can't find it, friends.
I can't even remember what it was going to be.
Oh, forget it.
Just forget it. It's not going to happen.
It's going to be a bummer, man.
That's what Bob said.
Everything.
Everything is.
He said it's going to be a bummer.
And it is going to be a bummer.
In fact, let's just switch over to this bummer right now, okay?
Just, just, just...
Crack.
Not the common form.
Cracks.
In the earth.
Precious soil.
Groundwater shrinking lower.
No groundwater.
Desert.
Dry.
Collapsing land.
No reserves.
Can't be filled back up.
Toxic waste.
Chemicals seep into it.
Highly concentrated.
Long time.
Chemicals finding their way into the drinking supply.
Waste disposal.
Coastal areas.
Contamination.
Gasful.
End of message.
Long-term care insurance is for straight up to work hard their whole life, save their money, and be prepared to die.
And seeing dollar signs, some form of dementia, I'm just going to shoot myself dead.
On the flip side, what is your money for?
Why are we working?
Why are we making money?
And obviously, long-term care would affect someone going on vacation in a big way.
What is your money for?
Butt heads all the time die.
And what a morbid thought.
Live life.
You're ready.
Live life like you're going to die.
Because you're going to.
I hate to be the bearer of bad news, but you're going to die.
Maybe not today or even next year, but before you know it, you'll be saying,
Is this all there was?
What was all the fuss?
Why did I bother?
Now, maybe you won't suffer.
Maybe it's quick.
But you'll have time to think.
Why did I waste it?
Why didn't I taste it?
You'll have time.
Because you're going to die.
Yes, it's going to happen.
Because it's happened to a lot of people.
A lot of people I know.
My mother, my father, my loves.
The president, the kings, and the pope.
They all had hope.
And they muttered just before they went,
Maybe I won't go.
Live life like you're going to die.
Because you are.
Maybe you won't suffer.
Maybe it's quick.
But you'll have time to think.
Why did I waste it?
Why didn't I taste it?
You'll have time.
Because you're going to die.
You're going to die.
I tell you who else left us.
Fast on gone to heaven, no longer with us.
Johnny Cash.
JFK, that guy in the stones.
Lou Gehrig, Einstein, and Joey Ramone.
Joey Ramone.
Have I convinced you to read my lips?
This may come as news, but it's time.
You're going to die.
By the time you hear this, I may well be dead.
And you, my friend, might be next.
Huh?
We're all going to die.
Yeah.
Oh, maybe you won't suffer.
And maybe it's quick, but you'll have time to think.
Why did I waste it?
Why didn't I taste it?
You'll have time.
You're going to die.
Yes, you're going to die.
I tell you, you're going to die.
You're going to die.
Because maybe you won't suffer.
Maybe it's quick, but you'll have time to think.
Why did I waste it?
Why didn't I taste it?
You'll have time.
Because you're going to die.
You're going to die.
Live life.
Live life like you're going to die.
Because you're going to.
Oh, yes.
I hate to be the bearer of bad news.
But you're going to die.
Maybe not today.
Or even next year.
But before you know it, you'll be saved.
It's all there.
What?
What is all the fun?
You too, friend.
Why did I bother?
Why did you bother?
Why did you even care?
Why did you even get out of bed, you sap?
Why did you suck down them mutagens when you know you should have had hot sundry pies?
Why did you force those things into your eyes which were made of sharp metallic objects
when you should have viewed some nice flowers or the river flowing by?
Yeah!
Why didn't you get with it, man?
Yeah, man.
Why did you waste it?
Why did you spend your life serving the conspiracy?
Why did you work indirectly for George W. Bush and his evil cronies?
Yeah.
And Bill Gore and his Hillaryans?
And then all of those stupid people.
You did it because you didn't care and you didn't know and everybody hates everything.
And what kind of people go around jerking off their spleens, masturbating their spleens?
Yeah!
Why would you want to do that?
Why would you even do that?
It doesn't make any sense!
I can't even think of it.
Oh, wait a minute.
I can think of it.
Millions and millions of angry people masturbating their spleens furiously, first trying to find
out where the organ exists.
Asserting their body to the body.
They know that once they've stimulated that spleen enough that the essence of spleen, what
is it called again?
Uh, bergamot?
Bergamot.
Yes.
Bergamot explodes into their, well, they're victimized by the whole spleen.
But anyway, bergamot explodes from the bottom chakra and rushes forward up the spine to
the top, the crown of the creation, and destroys every figure in its path.
And that's when you...
You lose your slack to the conspiracy.
Because you let it go.
You ignored the word of Bob.
Don't step out of line!
And now you're in the salt mines.
Literally in the salt mines.
Under Lake Erie.
Salt.
Yeah, paid in salt and cigarettes.
Hey, comrades.
Would you like another lucky stroke?
But there is a way out, my friend.
There is a way out.
Somewhere out there is a cool, cool guy.
And he's driving a cool, cool car.
And he's got the coolest car keys for that car.
And the coolest key chain.
And everything about him is so cool.
And he's got the coolest pipe hanging out of his mouth.
And he's got the hood down.
And the radio's turned up playing this music you hear in the background.
And he's cool.
Cool, too.
And it's kind of cooling around the salt mine like it's a resort on the lake or the ocean somewhere.
And I convertible.
I feel like an American in the 19-whatever-that-damn-hell-it-is.
He's got slack, my friend.
Care for another joint, Charlie?
Care for another poke on that whiskey bottle?
Let's stop at the bar and pick up some babes.
Isn't it about time you got a ride with them cool guys?
Why are you on that bus with those bozos, brother?
Why are you on the bus?
I'm on the bus with all the people with the very, very nasal bozos.
Oh, I understand.
Because you're stupid, ugly, short, broke, poor.
Deviated cheptum.
Deviated rectum.
Not very outgoing.
Stupid cheptum.
Kind of perverted.
You smell funny, they say.
They tell you.
Over and over again.
And I smell like this.
Well, friend, there is that guy driving that cool, cool car.
We'll still pick you up.
This guy.
That's how cool he is.
You know why?
Because he's cool.
I'm talking about the way I kick the ...
And he's Bob.
Yeah, he's Bob.
You knew who I was talking about.
You know I was talking about Bob.
You know I wasn't talking about Jesus.
You know I wasn't talking about Buddha.
You know I wasn't talking about lonesome cowboy Dave, Reverend Ivan Stane.
No, because I'm not going to pick you up.
And Dave ain't going to pick you up, but J.R. Bob Dobbs.
You hang your $30 out the window and he'll pick you up.
Bob will lift you up into his pickup truck.
up. And he'll let you ride in the back with all them other mutants, misfits, nobodies,
and presidents, and geniuses, undiscovered geniuses. He will gently, gently pick you
up and tickle your scrotum in the back of that window-tinted van. And you know that
guy way in the back of the pickup bed, the guy that really smells like he's been sleeping
with skunks? In the far part. That's Doc Frop. He grows the best frop in the whole world.
And you, you just gotta ride with him. You're in the back of the Bob's pickup truck with
Doc Frop, my friend, and you're cruising. You've got it made. And why? Only because
you joined the Church of the Subgenius. That's how you got that. That's how you got that
way. Instead of working in that factory. You're not hitchhiking now. You're riding!
That's right, friend. You're either on the saucers or you're off the saucers. And when
you're on the saucers, believe me, it ain't easy to get off. Or you're on the sauce.
Oh, yeah. If you're on the saucers, it's a day and day, day, day, day, day, day, day,
day and day, I think, see? You wake up in the morning, you got the shakes. Then you
got the smooth, see? It's different than the shakes. It's just like everything is real
like liquid, see? And then, look, around four o'clock, you go into like a different dementia.
Yeah, around four or five o'clock, you become real cynical and wise, see? Everything you
see gives you like a pain in the ass. You gotta make a remark, see? Church of the Subgenius
indeed. Who needs this stuff?
What a love of...
Wait, the connective tissue in my brain. I can smell myself drifting, drifting over
the horizon. Goodbye!
Goodbye.
Bye.
There's no place like home.
Especially when you're not there.
Ignore the man behind the curtain.
There's no place like home.
There's no place like home, all you...
Oh, the puppies.
Oh.
Believe it or not, Princess, this is the same song that the amino acids do at about
15 times the speed.
Oh, wow!
Miserable!
Yeah.
I love it.
It's weird.
The original version, I guess, that Dale turned into a surf song and that when you meet him,
Oh, oh!
I was turning into a thrash death song.
This was belly dance song, too.
Very beautiful belly dance.
Belly dance?
Did you ever belly dance to this song?
I have no belly.
I have no guts.
You got to have guts to do a belly dance.
Hey, but you got a butt.
You got a great big butt.
You got a butt your way.
I loved her butt.
I couldn't stand her cooking.
Remember back in the day, they had the butt now.
Now, that man could dance out any day for a while.
Unfortunately, he lost his mind like the rest of them.
I have a body here.
I got a lot of mind.
It's hard to find a true weirdo these days.
It really is.
I mean, what is a weirdo?
Is a weirdo somebody who has a tattoo?
When I was a kid, if you saw somebody who looked like me,
you had long hair and a beard.
You'd go, wow, look at that guy.
He looks like a cowboy or something.
He looks like some, what a weirdo.
Or you see a bald-headed person with tattoos.
Oh, a pirate.
Oh, I can't believe it.
He's got earrings.
That was really something special.
Well, now I guess everybody shopping at the mall is a weirdo.
Everybody who's got a, I mean,
old grandmas have tattoos, nose rings, and long beards and so forth.
I mean, it's, what?
Well, and see, I'm not being shocked by the youth.
What happened?
I have some people my age say it's rap music.
It's nothing but noise.
It's not even music.
Some, but not enough.
I mean, or something.
I mean, what happened to the instant rebellion
that just went with being a kid or a weirdo?
It's all getting watered down or something.
Television's getting better.
I think that's what it is.
The Internet's gotten really entertaining.
It's almost like TV.
You don't have to read.
Turn on the Internet and voices come out, little movies and everything.
Yep, goodbye.
Bye.
Written word.
Maybe for the best.
I don't know.
What you don't know,
sometimes when I look at severely retarded people,
it's like they have this smirk on their face.
Like, they don't know something you do know.
And they're proud of that.
They're happy with that.
And I'm envious at times, you know.
And I try to be,
well, tonight I'm going to try real hard to be like them.
And not know anymore what I do know.
Changing channels in your heads, friends.
It's really fun.
From PR News in Washington, I'm getting worse.
Doctors say they're basketball fans,
and Michigan State battles with PR News.
Lawyers say Bob had little chance of winning.
Reverend Jesse Jackson climbed the side of the St. Peter's Dome
before he killed nine people, then himself.
Authorities demanded Pope John Paul start a lottery
to help him win.
From PR News in Washington, I'm Washington.
Alan Greenspan.
Federal Reserve Chairman Alan Greenspan
may be a mixed blessing for suburban homeless.
The Bush administration kept up its condemnation
of Alan Greenspan.
The latest attacks come just a day after Greenspan
assassinated his son for crimes against humanity.
A federal judge in Billings, Montana,
has blocked the import of live Greenspan from Canada.
The U.S. border has been closed to Greenspan
since Canada reported a case of mad Greenspan disease in Washington.
Federal Reserve Chairman Alan Greenspan
warned members of the House Budget Committee today
of the dangers of PR News
and urged them to fix PR reports.
Greenspan's comments said,
We are fundamentally inappropriate.
Greenspan said PR News needs restructuring.
He said the current program has made many nervous,
and by 2030 there will be just two workers
to support PR News Washington.
The Supreme Court has said that the U.S. government
will not be able to support the U.S. government
The Supreme Court heard arguments this morning
in two cases that challenged displays of Alan Greenspan
on government property.
Opponents say the displays amount to an endorsement
of Federal Reserve Board Chairman Alan Greenspan.
They also called for the resignation of Greenspans
who are linked to PR News Washington.
You're listening to the subgenius hour of slack,
and you'd better watch it,
because we're absolute loonies determined to offend
players of pool with Jesus anyway,
a few of us own guns.
And that staying guy makes the
Satanic Tabernacle in Wickenburg, Arizona
look like Space Mountain.
Any questions?
Any participation in the church has essentially
a 50-50 chance of either A,
giving you many opportunities to put your face
between the hooters of fate and go
whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, like Curly,
or B, to have your breasts whooped.
Now, listen to this.
You got your pudding now.
Now.
That's one mango lassie,
one mango fido,
two pints of mild,
and a neat vodka chaser.
You got your pudding now.
No, my pudding is trapped forever.
Can you swim in pudding?
No, but I don't care.
They can take our lives,
but they'll never take our pudding.
What?
No pudding.
I got a bowl of chocolate pudding in my underpants.
Ah!
Chocolate pudding,
it comes in a cup.
it's only a bar.
It'll cost you a dollar.
From Maui's Kitchen,
it's a labor of love.
Ah!
Chocolate pudding,
it comes in a cup.
it's only a bar.
It'll cost you a dollar.
How can you have any pudding if you don't see your meat?
You got your pudding now.
Keep thinking about pudding.
Pudding.
Good morning
Good riveting, my friends,
from over 200riv highlight.
Today we have a little girl
of national cynical.com.
You can get more there at national cynical dot com.
Before that, Hellpop Onu.
PR News is by Mr. Fernando dubbed
can be obtained at
That's alt.binaries.slack.
You are listening to the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
Get more information, if you please, at www.subgenius.com.
Or you can write for information at Bob at Box 181417, Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
Praise Bob.
From PR News in Washington, I'm finding it difficult to breathe.
The prices are down 8740.48.
The government reported today that Pope John Paul has killed 10,000 soldiers and wounded 128 million others in Iraq.
The pope's occurred north of Baghdad.
The government says the 84-year-old pontiff was captured this week and was a terror mastermind from PR News.