I keep feeling and I hear shuffling noises all about me.
Shuffling?
Well, not exactly.
More like little sucking noises.
You know, a...
That's great.
Look!
I know who it is!
I know who it is that doesn't belong among us!
I swear, I know who it is!
It's...
The Self Genius Hour of Slack!
Well, that's not true!
Wake up, you...
Bob?
Forsaken people, you!
The best there is, this man here that works for you!
Your government, our country, the best country there is because of me like...
Bob?
I'm proud of you.
They're gonna hear about this, not just in the territories, but in Washington.
Across the length and breadth of this nation, they're gonna know that name.
Bob?
Now, what do you got to say about that boy?
I was drunk.
I didn't know what I was doing.
I didn't know what I was doing!
Good morning, and welcome to the Subgenius Devotional Hour here.
Um...
Before the normal scary time.
As the smoke of that burning goeth up forever...
That was a stink-o.
But it had lots of prophecy involved.
You heard it right here on the Subgenius Hour.
And lots of few words.
Blood belches from the earth.
My lights in the sky rebuke thee, the children of heaven.
And the angels from heaven are among thee, spreading lies and deception.
They turn not as they go.
Within five years, the United States, as we know it, will cease to exist.
We're living in terrible, perilous, chaotic times.
Praise the Lord.
And these times are not gonna get any better, my friend.
Amen.
They're gonna get worse and worse.
Love...
Can't breathe.
Okay, I know you all think, uh...
You want to know what's going on.
That's okay.
So I saw this thing coming...
I saw this thing coming to me!
I didn't know what it was, but, uh...
It looked funny!
There were deceptions which have surrounded our space program!
Spacecraft entered the moon's gravitational field in the sixth segment of the flight.
The gravity of the moon is 1 sixth of that on earth.
The orbit around the moon was flown 66 miles above the moon's surface, at 6,000 miles an hour.
10 after nine, the beeping began.
Went down to the...
reserve fence, watched through binoculars, and we did see this thing. It's about the
size of the moon with a small crescent at the bottom that's well lit like
starlight. The top is a dark gray mass. It came down through the trees, whatever it
was. Have you ever heard of one? Have you ever been in one? Have you ever seen one?
Have you but television ever seen one? If you haven't, it's the greatest sight this
side of heaven. People from this earth have already seen some of their
spacecraft which they call flying saucers and other flying objects which
they cannot describe. These objects are real and are spacecraft. I represent a
group of scientists who work with but one purpose to put an end to war.
Naturally such a goal can't be attained
without experts of superior ability. Men of vision, men such as you doctor,
gathered here exchanging information daily, putting aside all thoughts of
personal success. We hope to achieve exciting new techniques, leap years ahead
of the others. I don't think I need to tell you how effective our voices will
be when the world learns of our achievements. Well, there you have it.
Nothing new perhaps, but then what is? They are friendly people.
And are by far more advanced spiritually and physically than the people of this planet.
At the present time they are observing us. They wish to help us to help ourselves to
attain a higher understanding of life and its meaning.
What do you think about Bob?
Who's Bob?
All right, well what do you think about Bob?
Well, I think about the UFOs which are presently in formation to blitz the earth and put particle
beams through the head of everyone that doesn't know Bob.
You're out of your mind.
And we're off this planet and out of this world soon.
Friends, next week, in fact July 5th, the world ends.
That's how we experts of science and technology will end our lives.
And we'll see you then.
Bye.
There's really a lot of stuff on the old Media Barrage 11 explaining X-Day.
Later we'll have documentary sex sounds.
Sex sounds from...
No one is ever safe on this hostile planet.
X-Day!
Five X-Day, actually.
The last one.
By the way, this music in the background is The Amino Acids, who are the headlining band
for this X-Day.
Yeah-hoo!
The Amino Acids at aminoacids.com.
Now, friends, however, Reverend Susie the Clusie brings us some of her ex-day love and expectation.
Enough to get me all expectorated.
Because nobody knows how to bring in the new end of the old universe like Susie the Clusie.
It's getting late for the great planet Earth.
A storm of hail and fire mingled with blood is cast upon the Earth and a third of the world is burned.
A fiery mountain is hurled into the sea and a third of the sea and its creatures have perished.
A great star has fallen from heaven.
Upon a third of the Earth's rivers and springs, their waters have become polluted and bitter.
The sun, the moon and the stars are struck.
A third of the world is in darkness.
Woe, woe, woe to those who dwell on the Earth because of the risk to the trumpet blasts which the angels are about to sound.
It is done. The final trumpet has sounded.
The mighty cities of the nations.
Woe, woe, woe!
Islands disappear, mountains crumble as God's final wrath pours upon mankind.
As lightning flashes from the east to the west, so he comes.
The son of man, anointed in power, returns with majesty and glory to take his kingdom.
Bob, let's really have some smoke on this one, all right?
All right, let's go.
Time is running out for the human race.
Get ready for the judgment day.
The sun is shining, come on, get happy.
The Lord is waiting to take your hand.
Shout hallelujah, come on, get happy.
We're going to the promised land.
And if she wants to get some white underwear, it might be best she get them in asbestos, all right?
Might better get them in asbestos.
And I'm teasing now, of course.
Don't let her put on asbestos britches, all right?
It might be harmful to your breathing.
First, I want to remind you that in the last day,
there will be some scoffers who will do every wrong they can think of and laugh at the truth.
If you are scoffing right now, in your heart, if you are not believing...
Bob!
...coming back, you are one of the signs of his coming.
If you're going to continue to scoff, will you do me a favor?
Prepare for the end.
Oh, wow.
Well, there's a day soon coming when the judgment of the world will begin.
When the sky will be dark and then the mountains dance like croaking men.
When the people of the earth will fall like fruit from the tree.
Oh, I wish you'd all believe me.
I wish you all could see.
I wish you'd all believe me.
The truth will not hurt you.
Only the lie.
I wish you'd all believe me.
You don't really believe that, do you?
I don't know.
Impossible, fantastic, ridiculous, absurd, really?
The ambush is set.
And it's working.
1998, the year of fear.
Jack, explain it away, please.
No, these are not my days.
We don't set dates.
This is one of the best intelligence sources in the world,
along with Jane's defense out of England.
But let me tell you this, friend.
We believe things are going to come and happen sooner than we think.
The world must have seen it coming, right?
I'm afraid not.
Even though the technology had been around for years,
nobody really paid too much attention to it.
Almost no one saw it coming.
Almost no one?
Yeah, almost.
Almost.
And those of us who did express our concern
were just branded as paranoid,
as people who hated technology.
People who just weren't ready to be part of a new, united world.
So listen not to this child of Satan.
Reverend, I gotta admit, this doomsday warning has me just a smidge twitterpated.
Oh, now be calm, Ned.
But be afraid also, tremendously afraid,
for the day of reckoning is upon us.
RECKONING IS UPON US!
Oh, please.
What about tomorrow?
Just what lies ahead?
Will there be a brighter future?
Or just how will it go then?
Woo, woo, yeah!
Ain't gonna wait, it's getting late
Oh, what a horrible dream!
Oh, man.
Boy, that bitch was a real pain.
She was right.
I have fallen down on the job here, Seekers.
I've been pussyfootin' and fiddlefartin' around
at the most crucial juncture here of mutant existence ever.
Because this is a damn ministry here.
So from now until X-Day, it's no more Mr. Nice Girl.
Oh, I've gotta be more than just mere Reverend Susie the Floozy
to get this job done.
I gotta be the Whore of Babylon
on a three-year-old.
I gotta be the three-headed P-Dog, too.
Because it's time to sound the mutant's survival call.
Too much is hanging in the balance here.
Because there are still unsaved subgenius souls out there.
Mmm, I can whiff-read your stench from here, baby.
Oh, yes, it's the twilight of the Elder Gods
for the Yeti Uber race.
And praise be the holy name
of J.R. Bob-Dogs.
Because thanks to him,
we're scrapin' the crappy dirt of this planet
off of our shoes, baby!
The Doomsday Clock is tickin' down the final moments.
We're on a drunken chicken run with the End Times,
and it's zoomin' up on us a lot sooner than they think.
Yes, X-Day is coming up July 5th.
This very year, Seekers.
It's 7 a.m.
Think, if you haven't thought already.
Have you decided how you're going to spend eternity?
As a human pork rind
screaming in the stinking wreckage of a dying planet?
Or as a satisfied member of the fastest-growing apocalypse
called Snuggly Asconst aboard the escape vessels of the sex goddesses
en route through space
and time to an idyllic future of sated lusts
and mind-reaming pleasures?
Duh.
Tough choice, huh?
Oh, but there are some among us who aren't sure yet.
Maybe they can't quite tell if they're pink,
or if they're truly a mutated son of Dobbs.
Hell, just send in that membership fee,
and whether you're pink or not,
chances are, everything will be fine.
Hell, those saucers come with airlocks and torpedo tubes,
so I'm sure we'll be able to do a little weeding out once we're airborne.
Oh, but that can come later.
And hopefully there won't be a lot of weeding to do,
because weeding's hard on a girl's knees.
But I don't expect a lot of the wrong kind of people to be on board
if you catch my drift,
because they're going to be misreading the flaming signs in the heavens
and trying their brand-X apocalyptic solutions
until it's too late to turn to Bob.
Oh, but they never have been able to figure out how to get it right anyway.
Oh, they screw it all up.
They can't tell a 999 from a 666.
And I can see how they could mistake our triumphant subgenius Ragnarok
for their cheesy bargain-based,
Armageddon.
Oh, but hey, you putzes.
Armageddon tired of waiting for you to get around to it.
Your god can't get it up to destroy the Sodom and Gomorrah
that it has created for itself.
Oh, but Bob's going to clean house on this cat box, but good.
And the mighty wrath of Jehovah One and Negi
and the elder gods and the sex goddesses are just for the overkill.
Oh, Bob, great is thy power.
Cream rinse us all in your sweet load
and rupture us up into the heavens.
Yea, we strip naked and light the sacred frop
and implore your mercy upon your believers.
Yea, yea, yea, yea, yea, yea.
In the days of the end,
there shall come from among the race of men
a new ruler.
From the chaos of the nations,
he will forge peace and security.
As one risen from the dead,
he will entrench the world with his sorcery.
And at the time appointed,
he will take his place in the very temple of the Lord of Hosts,
scattering the true children of the Father
over the face of the whole earth.
He is mobbed.
What makes Bob holler?
When I ask Bob, he explained this way.
And he said,
Well, when a little sweety pie
in a minskirt twirls by
and rolls those big blue eyes,
oh, I holler.
And when some pretty chick
says she loves my fiddle legs,
well, now then, that can do the trick.
Oh, I holler.
And, uh,
you know, even if X-Day doesn't work out,
we'll go for Sex Day!
Yeah!
We want you to have a dance into the new century!
Screw into the new century!
Sleep and eat your way into the new century!
And the baptism is basically to wash away that pig tank
from rubbing elbows with and kind of purify them.
The baptism is a very beautiful event
because most of us need a bath.
Okay.
And now I want you to gently feel
your neighbor's nipple to your left and to your right.
I love you
and she is lousy.
We can't not turn that off.
and bring thee not the devils, for thine spirit is locked away inside the white stone, which
my angels have grieved from space.
Where are we, Bob?
The code is broken.
Trouble?
Big.
Security.
I have the lid on tight.
Well, take it off for me.
The message is, Mars needs women.
Ah!
This is so wrong.
I love it.
It's moments like that that make me think we're really all going to hell after all that.
It's a way of getting back to all the slack you had when you were a little kid.
Remember when you were a little kid and you'd be able to just sit there with your little
plastic soldiers?
Yeah.
You had a little fantasy world around you.
This is it.
We've created our own fantasy world around us.
That's what religion's for, right?
To create a fantasy world.
But we live our fantasy world out.
We don't wait until we die.
Oh, man.
John.
Whoop her, Andrew.
Whoop her real, Andrew.
I got exactly what I wanted!
All right.
Praise time.
Say yay!
caminhoBcom Style Swings
It's a Special!
Bob's a small guy physically, I'm pretty convinced.
Uh-huh.
You seen the photographs or those are the autopsy photographs that were rearranged to
look like quiet Air Force.
I never trusted autopsy.
Put it settle.
He's going to say hi.
Bob Bob.
I came as.
A visitor.
not an invader. I must get back to my ship, see if I can repair it. And then I must leave.
No, wait. What harm is there in hearing them out? Other than being a salesman, what does Bob do for
a living? Other than being a salesman? Bob is not, Bob is not on Route 80 with a bag full of
Who has met Bob? He seemed extremely paranoid. He believed in conspiracies.
He came on like a Nazi. I was afraid of him.
Your tricks don't frighten us, neither do you. We've come a long way in 5,000 years.
But you're still of the same nature. I could sweep you out of existence with a wave of my
hand and bring you back again. I can give life or death. What else does mankind demand of its gods?
Mankind has no need for gods. We find the one quite adequate.
We shall not debate, mortal.
At this very moment, there have been stories filtering into the studio about other sports
events being kidnapped and the entire thing taken to another planet. That's right. These
are aliens from another planet kidnapping our American sports teams. It's not a legal problem.
It's not a political problem. It's an alien problem.
Oh, I've never seen one.
You know, the visits from aliens need not be a painful item. It can be quite an exciting time.
I don't personally have any desire to have it. It's like meeting Bob. I don't want to do it.
I just need to get you to understand exactly what's happening here at the Church of the
Subgenius and the organized crime fighting that we're doing here in California.
But as soon as we're gone, you folks who are here unsaved, you folks listening by radio,
you folks listening by record.
Once the church is gone, there's going to be a cataclysmic judgment and millions will
die in those next few years.
They'll be glued to their sets, watching rockets and jets, blowing up schools and factories,
putting an end to the birds and bees. It's worth every penny to tune in and see who wins
the Emmy at the root of the academy. Watch World War III on pay TV before your television
melts away.
It's the end of the world.
As we know it, it's the end of the world.
As we know it, I feel fine.
A-O, let's go.
Shoot them in the back now.
What they want, I don't know.
They're all revved up and ready to go.
Turn around.
Go back down.
Back away.
You came.
Can't you see that flash of fire?
Ten times brighter than the day.
And behold, a mighty city broken in the dust again.
Oh, God, proud man, broken in the dust again.
It's gonna be me.
And it's gonna be you.
We're gonna do everything we want to.
It's gotta be now.
And I can't wait.
To say goodbye to fear and all that pain at hand.
Oh, like a flaming baton that's ready to twirl.
Like George Bush on acid singing to Duke Moore.
Gonna be a new world.
I could say to anyone's last words.
There's nothing left for you to say.
Soon you'll pretend anyway.
Well, no one here is getting out alive.
I feel so unconsious.
It's the end of the world.
Lost my mind.
And I don't care.
So close your eyes and get yourself to fight
And think about the times we've been and what they've been
To me it's nothing
We're only gonna die from our own arrogance
That's why we might as well take our time
Stop the traffic, stop the clock, stop the clock
I wanna get off, I wanna get off with you
I wanna get off
I wanna get off with you
One more job in the supermarket
One more kick to get me started
Everyone get on board, this ship is sinking
Looking for a way in, searching for the way out
Angels ride free in your mind
But you're never gonna find it if you're never gonna try
Get your eyes on the road and
So close your eyes and get yourself to fight
Hey man, get hip
Climb aboard our pleasure ship
Speed boy, we know
You're king of freedom, yeah, come and go
Go Apollo 69
Rock it baby, walk the line
We see the fire
Now we're on the run
Now's the time
Fly Apollo 69
Yeah, yeah
The beginning was the end
Of everything now
The ape regards his tail
He's stuck on it
Repeat until he fails
Have a goon and have a gun
A man's not made of steel
No, have the45
Count, añä
If just a shot away
It's just
It's just a shot away.
Oh, children.
It's just a shot away, shot away, shot away.
When we were born into this life,
we were destined to make it right.
And it's predetermined.
And this is our fate.
We're singing this song.
So you can read later.
We are going to save the universe.
Goodbye.
In England's dreaming.
No future.
No future for you.
No future for me.
No future.
No future for you.
The universe is not a grave.
What of the limitless?
Sex and violence.
In the wake of Ragnarok.
Welcome to the slaughter.
What are you going to do?
What will be your epitaph?
When we get done with you?
Are you going to cry for your mama?
Or are you going to have a good time?
Are you going to be a bohab?
When it's your turn to die?
Don't get crazy.
Let them all die.
Okay!
Looks more wrestling.
Blame us.
Blame other people.
Whatever you're going to do to us.
For abuse.
repetitions of those who talk interesting stories,
eventually build a linkage back between meat as drugs .
He said, I've never engaged in this type of thing before, but yes, I believe it can be very easily done.
Just put some bleachers out in the sun and have it out on Highway 61.
Oh, yeah!
It's the end of the world as we know it.
And I feel fine.
Bob?
Really don't mind
An accent?
X-Day song collage there, put together by yours truly with a bazillion different commercial bands.
And before that, some old, young, glass madness and puzzling evidence on the radio.
And now, with amino acids in the background, me doing the credits.
No one is ever safe on this hostile planet!
No way, man! Because that's...
Well, obviously, just look at Pope Black here.
Pope David Lee Black preaching at the Euro-X-Day in London last year.
I'm gonna talk to you about the conspiracy!
Yeah!
Woo!
Conspiracy!
Yeah.
Now, the conspiracy is that one world, one government, one taco, one Pepsi, one goddamn tight Nike tight t-shirt,
one fucking football, one football game world...
That'll have a fucking Big Mac in your mouth and a gas pump in your ass,
begging you, and you'll beg them to give you your credit card.
Woo!
But there's only one way to get rid of this conspiracy!
And that is to burn money!
Woo!
We gotta burn some money!
I want you to get out your money!
Get out your money!
Who's got money to burn?
We got some money to burn!
We got more money to burn!
Oh, hallelujah!
More money!
We got dollars!
We got rupees!
We got euros!
We gonna burn some money!
Hallelujah!
Some of that money, brother!
Smoke that money!
Woo!
Burn money!
Burn!
Evil money!
Burn it!
Them dollars and euros!
I have a gold nose!
Pleased to meet you, sir.
They say you're a gold nose.
I shot him in the foot just for his boots.
Well...
Here's your gold nose.
Thirty dollars cash.
You like this model?
I don't know.
Thank you, sir.
Oh, Pa, thanks a lot!
There ain't none better.
Oh, come on.
Where's where's the range we are?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, but...
Hey, hey!
Hello!
Cash deal.
Cash!
It is better to have more and, uh, not need, than to have more and, uh, not want.
Mm-hmm.
I don't know.
Hey, hey, hey!
We were in a cattle loon on a moonlit night when a group of flying saucers came flying
into sight.
Oh, no!
Ew!
Let's get outta here!
They're getting too close.
And they're starting to glow.
I'm turning up the gas!
Come on, let's go!
Oh, no!
Senior feathers!
Let's get outta here!
They have an anti-magnetic, hydro-supersaturated, cyclotrated, adiopated bottoms that are corrugated.
Electroplated gyroscopic catalytic simulator.
It's green light!
I'm turning on the fans, ready to wheel!
Sauces in the sky!
Sauces in the sea!
Wine and sauces everywhere!
Coming after me!
Slippin' and a-spidin'.
Doing a fine saucer rack!
Look, sittin' on top, it's a phat-photonic sight.
Don't worry, kids, everything's all right.
Oh, no!
Ew!
Get us outta here!
It's a rock and roll band from the back of the moon!
I don't think I've ever heard a prettier tune!
One, two, three, let's get on with the show!
show we have anti-magnetic hydrosuper saturated cyclotrated atom painted bottoms that are
corrugated electroplated gyroscopic catalytic simulator
sauces in the sky sauces in the sea
flying sauces everywhere
coming after me
swimming and a-sliding
doing the fine saucer ride
the mutants must appear
the mutants must thrive
the saucers will fly
and the darlings
will be
the darlings
and that was Gary Gbrog-Fran
mein fuhrer we cannot allow like a mine shaft gap baby
und why not?
I mean mister president
that's Mrs. President to you Danny
I mean Missisissb
show is
Miss President
Miss President Princess
we are doe
Presidentress
of all the UFOs
as we shall learn
when they finally arrive here on
earth farm one
this sunny July 5th 2003
or one of these July 5th
I know ladies just
a lovely miss
and here she is
one of these 7AMs
the princess
of we are doe
queen
of all
the UFOs
I'm just taking all the Bahamas in my ship
that's all I want
that's all?
yeah that's all I want
just the Bahamas
I'm taking all the bananas
the Caribbean islands
all the Caribbean islands
that's my little chunk
I'm just gonna take that wedge
I'm taking all the carob bars
well you know I still have dibs on the
all the Rijksmuseum in Amsterdam
the Grand Canyon
I'm taking all the treasures of the Iraqi National Museum
lost in questions
lost in time
lost in space
I lost in a quest
for holy grails and grace
a wild cry cuts through
the night sky below
Hello, another traveler's packed and ready to go.
I can feel more, I can feel more down.
I can see more white, blue, green and brown.
I can hear the lights of night turn to sound.
I can feel I'm out of town.
I can stop, I'm falling down.
I can see the world spinning around and around and around.
Spinning around and around and around.
Chaz Smith, a clip from his new rock opera.
There's more of that coming up, actually.
And, well, surprises in store.
I'm terribly sorry to intrude on your hour of slack.
But I eat plutonium.
And subsequently, I fart radiation.
And I thought you ought to know that.
Now back to the end of the world.
Praise Bob.
You take the red pill, and I show you how deep the rabbit hole goes.
This is your last chance.
After this there is no turning back.
You take the blue pill.
The story ends.
You wake up in your bed and believe whatever you want to believe.
You take the red pill.
You stay in Wonderland.
And I show you how deep the rabbit hole goes.
Goes.
And you can get that red pill.
His hands are bloody.
His head is unbound.
For the locals.
I have to take a break for the locals here.
And his brow is furrowed.
For the locals, you can take that red pill.
Coming up next week, Thursday night, I will not be here because I will be at Brushwood.
Awaiting the rapture, my friends.
Sitting in a pile of his own pieces.
Hoping against hope, the X's will come down.
And Dave and Stang and Princess Wee and Legume and Ed Strange and Doc and Froppin and Sister D and the whole litany.
We'll be there.
Beggars and thieves.
It's going to be a whole lot of the old timers and a whole lot of the new comers.
One big family of beggars and thieves.
X Day, the subgenius end of the world.
I'm going to grow a crab claw.
And you can get more information if you want to go to that there party.
I'm going to grab Legume's and I'm going to take Legume and grab him by the feet.
Then I'm going to go back to the dinosaur age in a time machine.
I'm going to use that thing to make love to an ankylosaur.
But I'm sure this talk of Legume's sex life is making us all bored.
I'm going to take that crustacean hand and reach for a star and pull it down.
And there's Legume's shock parts.
So, stuck smelling.
Okay, well you can get more information if you want to go to that at...
At www.subgenius.com or at brushwood.com.
Just find your way to Sherman, New York.
Ask the locals.
You won't even have to ask.
They'll take one look at you and go, oh, you're looking for that bomb thing.
Bailey Hill Road.
When they see those...
Go down there.
Turn left.
The Amish guy in the cart.
You know, you'll see.
You'll know when you're there.
When they see...
You'll with it.
The bags on your feet.
When they see those polystyrene bags on your feet and this other strange hazmat uniform...
The boys are going to be the shirts in this game of life, my friends.
And we'll let you gals be the skins this time.
And by their dudes shall they be known as so.
Now we're going to have a football game.
Touch football.
It don't count unless you leave a mark.
Oh, there's a whole special Olympics.
A game of Freaks of Ministeria.
We're going to have a game of Touch the Donkey's Foot.
We've got like a, you know, a whole...
Oh, there's a superhero ball.
Jesus is coming as money, man.
Some extreme sports.
We'll be making soap out of pink rectums.
Dave, what extreme sport are you partaking in?
The blaster game.
It's two 300-pound howitzer or cannons placed at either end of a field, pointed directly
at each other with all of the pink boys and girls, all assembled right behind them.
And at one fell swoop...
They all expectorated one another.
Oh, there goes another one.
Praise God.
Get it again.
Bob escaped from hell.
He dug his way out using his entrenching tool.
He tricked the devil in a card game.
He cuckolded the devil.
He got kicked out of hell, friends.
Bob's still flying that jet plane overhead.
He's protected.
Your ass is you for a subgenius finish.
Praise God.
That's all right.
Sit right down here.
I'll give you a little bit of a break.
We won't talk petty games or unusual behavior.
Now your name is on the dossier.
Very clearly it is pronounced like this.
I hope you don't forget.
We will discuss how you can get out of here in the most efficacious way.
You don't want to pay too much.
You want to be safe.
You want to be better.
Not sorry.
Yeah, my pleasure vessel where it's always a stadium concert.
I'm sorry.
It's a never-ending party in the stadium.
One after another.
I don't think we could describe what our pleasure vessel would be like.
Could we, Princess?
The mind is very, very hard to describe.
It's kind of interdimensional in nature.
You take one step one way and then the next thing you know it's a dead end.
You could lose it there, man.
You know, you could lose it.
Actually, you know what's on it?
I want to play since this is the end of the world and all that.
Finally, we just have to do it.
Because they always yell it out anyway.
So here you go.
Everybody yells it out.
I remember when they used to yell them all the time.
They would hold the little frustration fingers up with the lighters in them.
Yeah, I remember.
I remember that time.
Do you remember when you were a little girl?
Yeah.
When the bird went down, it was so sad of Dave.
Oh, how can you forget those times?
How could you forget?
The whole band was pretty much gone in the one very small band.
But Dave, memory keeps going back.
Oh, yeah.
Bad memory keeps going back on you.
Sometimes you...
Hey, Dave, be a simple kind of man, would you?
Stop being so oblique.
Be straightforward.
Say what you really mean, man.
Be a simple kind of man.
Oh, yeah.
I'm just trying to find out why I'm so
That's better.
When the trumpet calls, X day.
In a brother and sister band.
When they blow the world away.
We shall have paradise.
Subgenie of the world unite.
Alien sex every night.
Subgenie of the world.
Subgenie of the world unite.
Stand hand in hand.
When the trumpet calls, X day.
In a brother and sister band.
When they blow the world away.
We shall have paradise
Santini of the world, unite
Alien sucks everybody
Santini of the world, Santini of the world
Santini of the world, unite
Ah yes, spread wide for the final ride
Because the X's are coming fast
And you are too
They didn't take us seriously last time
Hell, half of you didn't take us seriously
Didn't take Dog's Prophecy seriously
But this time we've learned our lesson
We can't rely on invisible monsters from outer space
We can't even rely on Bob
We have to learn how to escape Earth
Without being dependent on the conspiracy
Or any extraterrestrials or salesmen
Sure, send in your 30 bucks
But build your own
X's
Ship
You may not have to
Just recover your ass
Build your own ship
Even better, go buy Hangar Antenna
Area 51 or Cape Canaveral
Or Studio 54
And steal your own ship
Ah yes, excrete your own fuel
And while you're at it, friends
Let's swab the deck on the spaceship
That we're already stuck together on
We're already riding on it
We're riding on the spaceship
And it's in bad shape
And it's high time we cleaned it up
Earth, we must get off
Whether we leave it or leave it a cinder
Whether we blow it off or blow it up
Just don't blow it, friends
Have you ever stood at the water's edge?
Watched the waves roll over the window ledge?
See that city shine against a cloudy sky?
Let the day slip by without asking why?
Footprints in the sandstorm?
A stretch for a hundred miles?
And every now and then they're washed away by another tide
But the world still won't make sense for its miles to shine
And the wind blows through your hair on the final ride
And you let go of all your cares because now it's time to fly
And your soul is less than a feather in the sky
And you're not going to be able to bear no more to hide the child
No more to hide the child
Have you ever stood and prayed at the altar steps?
Looking through steel eyes from an eagle's nest?
And watched the waves roll right into the last lost soul?
And take a breath and still your heart and just let go
Footprints in the sandstretch for a hundred miles
And every now and then they're washed away by another tide
But the world still won't make sense for its miles to shine
And the wind blows through your hair on the final ride
And you let go of all your cares because now it's time to fly
And your soul is less than a feather in the sky
And your soul is left to bear no more to hide the child
No more to hide the child
Fly
So fly
So high
Into the sun
That is the most horrifying thing I've ever heard.
You are trying to sterilize decent pink American human being.
We're trying to sweep clean the filth and the trash that has ruined this planet.
It's a small project compared to those of our mentors, the exes from outer space.
They would have cleaned up the vermin, which we call humans, long, long ago.
Thousands of years ago had Bob, the first Bob, not intervened and won his bar bet with Satan.
And that's why we're here now.
Bob won that bet for your sins, brother, sistress.
So get in the pot.
Get in the pot.
Bob's cooking you up.
Don't let them sunglasses matter.
The sun's dancing around.
We're going to cook up the missionaries.
Get in the pot.
And the volunteers.
July 5th, 1998.
It's coming up this year.
The DJs, the MCs are all in the giant pot being cooked as the Malaysian natives dance around the great cauldron of Dogstown.
My kind of fear may fake again.
I've got funny shoes.
They're so well made.
Do they come from the king?
You can find out all you'd like to there.
www.subgenius.com
Yes, we'll see you on the saucers if you can spell subgenius.com correctly.
And you can find out about Starwood at www.rosencomet.com
You go dance around that pot.
You can get yourself this summer.
You go climb right into that plasma pool.
Rosen Comet has two E's and no I in it.
Jesus Christ, my friends are actually coming out of it.
Next day coming up.
Starwood coming up.
We'll see you all next week.
Until then, keep your head on tight.
You're back to the wind and you're sat in the saddle.
A sex-shy reporter, princess, we.
Come here.
ESO Swamp Radio from WCSB.
Chaz Smith, Loads of Cowboy Dave, Princess Week, and yours truly, Christ.
What?
Watch what you're doing.
I'm not real.
I'm sorry.
What are you trying to make out with that?
No kidding.
Before that, friends, the song Tomorrow's Child, that lovely song was by Chaz Smith.
And the subgenius anthem before that was Loads of Cowboy Dave.
The Matrix mix there was from Toxic Ear Candy.
I'm Reverend Ivan Stang.
Send me your stuff at Post Office Box 181417, Cleveland Heights 44118.
Or send that money to Bob at Subgenius Foundation.
PO Box 204206, Austin, Texas 787.
The end of the world every year.
So why don't you check it out?
One of these days.
You never know when it might be the last X day.
X Day.
They were slipping and sliding
Through the violence of the night
The men and women
One dog, one dog, one dog, one dog