For men on the go, it's not what's in the pipe, it's the pipe itself.
The Bob Dobbs Classic Meerschaum, hand-carved by the finest craftsmen in Malaysia.
This and other fine Bob Dobbs smoking accessories cast a spell of their own for the discriminating smoker.
Bob Dobbs pipes never go out. Of style.
Available at Kmart, Walmart, Target and Hypermart.
Too much church air.
I'm expanding my...
It's...
Now!
Praise...
Machine!
And welcome to the subgenius radio ministry.
Hour of...
Church!
Praise God!
Yeah! Now, before we really get going with this sermon here, I'd like y'all to share something.
It's something we've done in Texas and Arkansas for many years.
It's just...
To kind of...
Make people understand the solemnity, the profundity of the whole thing.
Lower your heads and we'll share a sacred moment of...
NOISE!
Yeah!
Take those!
All right!
Ah! There we go!
Now I see some people that are into it!
These people have slack!
The sound itself...
It...
It has a stink to it!
It's...
Baaaaaaaaaaah!
Baaaaaaaah!
Baaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
Who's gonna drive that greyhound, children?
Greyhound!
Sonic and I come from little to the middle!
Greyhound gone!
Woo!
Always let everybody save ya!
Greyhound gone!
Always drive to defy!
Almighty Father Christ, first man!
Greyhound gone!
Holy Ghost of the lucky train!
Mary and Joseph waiting at the station!
Greyhound gone!
They're hitching a ride to the Holy Nation!
There's no smoking or chewing on the...
The ginger roots of the hill!
There's a virgin Mary!
Paying out the old debtors for me!
Sack me and I'll break his fall!
He's infuriating us!
We're talking to violence!
And I'm coming down for the dead!
He's gone!
At court plan is headed for the border!
And they're running out of kids from a federal court order!
It's all ahead!
It's exact change please!
Three Hail Mary's and on your knees!
Take it to the bridge now!
Oh!
He's gone!
Father, Son, and Holy Ghost
He's our driver and our host
We always drive 55
So smoke it or chew it
Or go to Jerusalem
There's a virgin Mary
Right on your dashboard
We've got me, don't make it more
He didn't put it in
We're talking about
And I'm calling God for a man
He's our driver
So smoke it or chew it
There's a genius down here with a bomb
You goddamn won't better enjoy it or he'll kill all of you.
He is Bob.
Ready for fun.
He wears a smile.
Everybody run!
Yep, the decks are all running dear friends.
That wonderful song that started the show out was Greyhounded Jordan by my brother Cleve Donut Duncan.
I think his best song yet, making it perhaps the greatest song ever recorded.
Praise Cleve. A lot more Cleve coming up tonight.
So, hang in there.
And from now on the first words I want to hear out of your filthy sewers is praise Bob. Let me hear it.
Praise Bob!
Sound off like you got a pair. Praise Bob!
Dear Bob, my life has changed completely.
Because of your ministry.
Here's another one.
Dear Bob, my life has changed completely because of your ministry.
Bob needs an order to pursue his plan for world domination.
I say, Bob, God's my hand in all things and pays me off in pure slack.
Here's another one.
Dear Bob, my life has changed completely.
I dare you to kill me!
This is the mark. You can always tell it's going to be a Bob Righteous revival.
And there's technical problems.
Yes!
Headaches.
And there's always a normal group, and not normal.
You know, the potheads always seem to show up whenever the subgeniuses do.
As a matter of fact, I went into the restroom to make sure my fly was up,
which is the most important part of any public preaching, by the way.
And somebody in there said,
Hey, Reverend Stang, you want to blow one before the show?
I said, yeah.
Yeah.
I said, Bob is the only drug.
That's the only drug.
You can't come down to Bob.
I just, just say no.
Just say no.
Wow.
That's an old one.
Oh, yes, dear friend.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hey, Bob!
Hey!
Bob!
All right, all right, I can see we've got the spirit.
The spirit is moving tonight.
Yeah!
This is the subgenius.
This radio ministry hour of slack.
Spreading the seed word of J.R. Bob Dobbs.
High E-Bot of the Church of the Subgenius.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Ha!
Now hear merrily how we spread life's
Sachen Laugh out loud,
And you listen to our slammed lines.
Come on!
Whatever.
That's filin'.
Come on!
Hear your screaming wholegans when
And the heart full of what you've learned.
And the power of Old German, old German, and old German.
I'm playing loud and proud, I'm playing loud and proud.
Welcome.
Hari Krishna, Hari Rama, here's a flower, here's a dog.
Well, here we are at Columbia University's Halloween Spook House.
I recognize your voice, man.
Hello.
You're the radio guy.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, dude, he's the radio guy.
Reverend Ivan Stang.
That would be you. I've read the statement.
That book, that book, that kind of one is, uh...
Hey, wait, you gotta explain something to me.
Yeah, I got some...
But has Bob seen your $20, my friend?
Then you're still king in the eyes of Bob.
A king, boy.
Then you gotta keep...
And your $20 would earn you a seat.
Well, anyway, as I was saying, some people think the church is like
some sign of the end.
The end times.
The mockers that will come at the end times.
And those people should be damn glad we're helping to fulfill biblical prophecy.
To us, who've been with the church a long time, it's a mystery.
We don't know what the hell this thing's gonna turn into.
If we did, it'd be boring to us.
The great Bob.
Um, it founded...
The church actually was founded in 1953 by that man, J.R. Bob Dobbs.
Hey, Bob.
Bob founded his church when he discovered that there was a conspiracy, a conspiracy
of normals robbing away the slack of the true subgeniuses, as opposed to human beings,
mere humes, as we call them.
It's sort of a do-it-yourself religion.
Bob founded his church not on a rock, but rather on sort of a shifting sandy beach of
hypocrisy.
Every church must have its fair measure of hypocrisy.
And certainly we've got more, we dole out more of it than anybody else.
Um, it, like I said, it's a non-organization for non-joiners, which makes it a little bit
difficult to raise funds at times.
But the point of it is that all subgeniuses, people say, well, what the hell is a subgenius?
There's no definition.
They're all different.
That's what it means.
Um, if, uh, there is no typical subgenius.
If any two are alike, one must die.
The only thing that the subgeniuses have in common is that they have nothing in common
with the conspiracy.
What we're trying to do is, is tempt sinners away from the devil.
Because Bob is a better tempter than the devil.
However, what they, where they go after that, it's up to them.
The subgeniuses believe in the God that doesn't want you to believe in it.
And, uh, our, one of our many subgeniuses, uh, are not the same.
They're just the same.
So, uh, we're, uh, the headquarter is in Dallas, Texas.
This is what they often call the buckle on the Bible belt.
What we try to do is unbuckle the Bible belt so that its pants may drop and it may gaze
unflinching upon its own private design.
It's a war, dear friends, it's a war against the normals.
And we're just the regular kind of mutants we're talking about here.
These are more like the monsters.
And we're just the ordinary people.
the monster type of mutants.
It's the humans versus the subgeniuses.
And the ironic thing is, in the early days of the church,
80 million years ago in fabled Atlantis,
we helped to design the humans.
Probably our biggest mistake.
So, friends, as I said, you know,
the fact that Jesus smoked Chesterfields,
even though they didn't exist 2,000 years ago,
is an example of our faith.
You don't use your mind to think about your religion.
You just feel it. You feel it in your heart.
Bob sold it. I smoked it. That settles it.
It's a question of faith.
This is like the sorrow of world religions
putting those two Cs on both cheeks,
the bloody marks on the beefy seat of the conspiracy.
It's like the Robin Hood.
Robin Hood of world religions,
robbing from the lost, who were mostly thieves to begin with,
and giving to the saved.
And if you, my friend, can make it,
can buy those books of the subgenius,
that videotape on sale for only $30 tonight,
if you can make it to the jungle encampment in Dobstown, Malaysia,
if you can survive the acubating, the extra meditation,
the pyroflatulation, and the head-launching, my friend,
you will be a weapon.
A weapon for Bob.
A weapon for J.R. Bob Dobbs.
A minister of Bob praying for slack.
Yes, sir!
You and your subgenius fools shall never defeat me, Bob Dobbs.
Oh, no?
Then have a taste of my stark fist of removal, Dr. Conspiracy.
Negi's henchmen won't get any slack when they face Bobco's new Bob Dobbs action figure
with flying rocket fist, flamethrower pipe, and magic briefcase.
Too much is always good.
But better than not enough when you collect the subgenius universe.
Bobmobile not included.
Batteries and some assembly required.
Action figure sold separately from Bobco.
I am a subgenius.
And by that threat you will touch what falls to the greatest man.
My power was a given.
To me, in exchange for prayer or meditation, I paid for it in cold, hard American dollars.
Salvation you get for free is worth just that, doesn't you, queer?
Of course, your money ain't worth jack anyway.
The conspiracy sees to that but a very potent element of your soul.
And here's to those otherwise worthless greenbacks that Bob needs in order to pursue his plan
for world domination.
I say, Bob guides my hand in all things and pays me off in pure slack.
So I say to you whips, you fools, you dupes, you pigs, give me your money.
You won't need it in the future.
The future offers you naught but destruction.
You know what I mean?
I mean,
I dare you to kill me.
I need to be, I mean, I'm one of the good guys.
My cards shall prevail.
Let out the crazy man inside you.
He knows what's what.
Smile when you call me a fanatic.
Oh, you say,
You think I'm dumb, but you are blind to the conspiracy that runs your life.
And you have your geniuses running things for you and you think they're going to make
things safe and simple.
And I'm going to make things safe and simple and easy for me and the entire subterranean
rich.
Even if it means wiping out your sex society in total with no more sentiment involved and
swatting the blood.
Oh,
we might survive the end.
You know why?
Because I am, I am, I am, I am a sub-TV.
I say,
Oh, you blow dried, white wine sipping, designing a jean clad French film watch and walking
and toting hip whips.
If you house coated and choir and reading trailer and camp ball shopping, hair curl,
motor heads, cock holsters.
All you know.
You do the corporate big money or the straw tree, killing land, red food, freezing death,
warm and try that.
Really?
He established with Terry and both hunting back, stabbing poverty, spreading bomb, wielding
morang, heading pencil, neck, eraser headed, politicals, kill the conspiracy, kill them
and eat them, kill them and eat them.
And then why?
Who do you think you are?
What do you think you're doing?
Do you think you got it good?
Well,
dispose of those illusions.
Dispose of them all right now.
Because on July 5th, 1998, 730 in the morning, you shall be judged.
Calculating alien races,
the
most
You will meet Larry DiSanto.
If so, why can't I believe that you were up to something so时候
vem.
You don't want to think P Vous ti es est hair colorful.
You are telling me Somount by four all cool, govet.
You will flyee.
artists where you live, photos.
And he said I'm a nerd.
I always wanted to do politics.
I am the next version.
You know why, Daddy? You know why?
Now, some of you Christians out here may be getting a little upset at what I'm saying,
but I'd like to remind you that the founder of your religion was not quite so squeamish as some of you.
© BF-WATCH TV 2021
And the amazing rant that you heard just a little while ago
was a heavily censored version of Brother Cleve Duncan's testimonial
with background sampled music by Huge Voodoo.
More on that in a minute.
I'm really sorry about having to put...
...cuts in that rant,
where the taboo verbal expressions were excised.
You may or may not have noticed them,
but, you know,
until the prudish word-fearing conspiracy is defeated,
well, you know, we're not allowed to play certain words
because of the assumption in some quarters
that some words can actually harm you.
Now, more than the images of rape and violence
shown pretty much all the time on television.
Someday these things will change under Bob.
Now, almost all of the rest of this show
was recorded this weekend.
It's all...
It's almost all material recorded this last weekend,
last weekend, in New York and New Jersey,
by myself, Reverend Ivan Stang,
and especially the Reverend Dr. D.K. Jones,
as well as his friend, Reverend Bruce Grant,
before, during, and after a subgenius revival
at Columbia University.
D.K. Jones, uh,
is a subgenius musician you'll be most familiar with.
I guess from his score for the subgenius video, Arise.
And, in fact, the music that'll be coming up
and that you've heard some of already,
the stuff with preachers,
sampled bits of preachers over it,
is by Bruce Grant and D.K. Jones
going under the name of Huge Voodoo.
The more linear instrumental background music,
such as the stuff behind us right now,
is by D.K. Jones and myself,
believe it or not,
but mostly D.K. Jones.
I would like to thank
all of those who helped support the station
with their pledges,
uh, last couple of weeks,
and especially to those who helped with the pledge drive,
such as Reverend Willa Dobbs
and, uh,
the good Pope S. Cecilia
and the bad Reverend Trickster Shaman.
Praise Bob, dear friends.
Stay tuned, and, uh,
you'll eventually hear the post office box number
to write to for information regarding
this mighty church of the subgenius,
whose, uh, radio voice program,
you're now hearing
the subgenius radio ministry hour of slack.
Ha, ha.
Praise old Bobby.
¶¶
© BF-WATCH TV 2021
JOO SEO O S
No, wait, I'm sorry about the last message.
I just had to tell you this.
This is just the funniest thing.
We're seriously toilet training Sylvia for the first time, right?
So she's sitting there in her little potty watching the Bob tape.
And for the first time, while she's watching the Bob tape, she poops in the potty.
This is a big moment.
You've got to understand.
And just as she's starting to poop, she starts going, Bob!
Bob!
And so, like, she has this whole positive feeling about Bob because, you know, right after she poops, she goes, yay!
So it's like, Bob!
Yay!
Bob!
It's like this whole pattern is set up in her mind now.
And this is really true.
This is really what just happened just last night.
This is a breakthrough.
And I think I recommend it to other parents who are potty training their children to use subgenius tape on the TV at the time.
Because it somehow sends, I don't know what it is, but it just works so well for Sylvia.
But what happens when that loose, easy, so-called tramp is your own sister?
Sylvia?
Yeah.
I wouldn't want to lie now.
How did Bob strike his first million?
Bob said it was a visuality.
When a man like you paid a dollar for one of these bumpers in here, or ten dollars for this amazing poster,
it's true.
Bob, Bob, Bill, $10, Bill.
And it's ridiculous to think we're going to give it away just because a bunch of lazy mutants think they own the planet.
Bob?
I'd like getting a copy of the Economicon.
Is that spells?
We can't know.
If every four-by-four people would have one of those, there'd be so damn many old ones and guardian demons coming up out of that main stage.
So are there any patrols?
There'd be like ghostbusters on the mission.
Bloody or not.
I'm casting out a false prophet.
Bob?
Yeah?
Doug Quaid is here to see you.
Yeah, I'll be right up.
Okay.
Now, help me out here, Doug.
You were interested in a memory of, uh...
Why?
We saved.
We gave unto Bob that which is Bob's.
Render unto him that which...
No, I...
Before he renders you like that.
Pink boy in the slaughterhouse.
Uh, there are people who are...
Swag.
What are you?
Uh...
To be perfectly honest with you, Doug,
if outer space is your thing,
I think you would be much happier
with one of our Saturn cruises.
No, I'm telling you, Doug,
your brain will not know the difference.
You're gonna love this, Doug.
We offer you a choice of alternate identities
during your trip.
It's your first trip?
Mm-hmm.
Good evening, Doug.
Hey!
Hey, Doug!
What do you want for Christmas?
Benny, what were you doing
launching that bleeding ad on a Thursday?
Why was you wearing them big green straps?
You know you should not do that, Benny.
Take it easy, Doug.
Okay.
Doug?
Doug, I'm gonna call a doctor.
Doug.
Doug, there's something I want you to know.
You were the best assignment I ever had.
You wouldn't shoot me, would you, Doug?
After all we've been through.
If things have gone wrong,
I'm talking to myself,
and you've got a wet towel wrapped around the head.
No!
We're sorry, Bob.
We didn't mean it.
We didn't mean it to...
We won't call you anymore, Bob.
Please don't call me, Bob.
Die!
No, Bob, don't do it.
Please.
No.
Once that Bob won't get here, Bob.
I already filled up my will.
Oh!
Oh, I wish you was the little one, Bob.
Mickey.
Bob.
Frock Bob.
Where in the world can Mickey be?
Mickey.
Where is to, Mickey?
Mickey?
Where is to?
I know you are there, Mickey.
You're not going to get me this time, Mickey.
Because I have the gun,
and the diamonds,
and the map,
and the documents,
and I have the device.
Yes, I have the device,
and you are foiled, finally,
Mickey.
Mickey?
Where did you go?
Where did you go, Mickey?
You can't fool me this time, Mickey.
I signed the papers already.
You hold on.
What, no!
What is this!?
Th, the tapes?
The blank!
The documents, they've fallen to dust!
The negatives, what about the negatives?
What, they're gone.
They're gone!
I had the negatives!
I had the...
I have the device, I have the girl, the gun, the map, but, but, but Neegi has them now.
I should have listened in the temples of the old ones when they told me.
They told me that for every Bob particle there must always be a Neegi particle.
Why didn't I listen? Oh, oh, the, the pain.
To think I could have had it all.
I could have had everything, but, but Neegi has it now.
You can go to Dodd's town and get the formal training for coming over, man.
Uh, I skirted him, as many times as I could.
You know what you do, guys? You go to Dodd's town.
Sure.
I skirted him.
I skirted the, uh, the formal training.
I sort of came in at a little level.
Neegi, did you go to Malaysia?
Oh, man, I, I, uh, laid the first, uh, cornerstone.
It was a human skull.
A human skull, not a subgenius skull.
A big difference.
You ever seen, have a nice day spelled out in the skull of a normal human?
It's sweet. It's kind of neat.
Or save the earth spelled out in the chopped off arms of, of, uh,
of a Caribbean peasant.
It's a joyful sight.
It's so neat.
It's like the new age.
I'm afraid.
Come on, Archer.
Shh.
Come on.
I got her.
Ow!
Don't let her go!
She's coming for real!
What?
She laid out here.
Where'd she go?
She's going down the bottom.
Down the what?
Down here, here.
You're wrong.
Here, here.
She's gonna be in here.
What's that?
Keep back, keep back, don't care.
Grab her, man. We're gonna lose her.
Damn it.
Come on, Archer.
Get down.
All right.
This is the problem.
I'm sitting around.
I don't know where's Buzz aloffs.
I'm standing around here.
But I have to seal her up.
I had no control over the situation whatsoever.
I had no control.
Now come on, Archer.
I have no control over the situation whatsoever.
And I didn't give a damn about anybody else right now.
I, I have control over the situation whatsoever.
I'll be keeping you in the house.
Wait.
I'm not even...
It's okay.
You're gonna be alright now.
Easy.
It's gonna be okay.
It's alright. You're gonna be okay.
You know, it's this morning, and I have made the post office.
This morning, I'm gonna be wearing a new Johnny Dog's perfume, you know?
And that will remind you of me.
Okay?
Uh...
It's too late now.
It's alright.
Now, I'll be sure to keep this all clean.
I love this.
I...
I don't think I can control it this time.
I hope it can...
...come around to...
...my...
Uhhhh.
Yeah.
I love that feeling so much that now...
... now, I feel like I can armor this beautiful crazy little pomoc that you could do with
...and with a cosplay.
I'm trying to remember if I can ever...
...be healthy again?
Right now.
She has something to hide.
...de 나온.
...in your head.
I just was on my own.
Make something up dipping off yourナс.
Ailleе, que esta bien?
Where's our lucky groom and poor pathetic bride?
The poor martyred bride.
Let's see, I guess if y'all would see Brandy and Glenn.
If y'all could stand in front.
Yeah, right there.
Wait, wait, we gotta get, we gotta get.
Woo!
I'm more used to preaching in tents.
Hey, hey.
Ah, yes.
Hey, if Reverend Sun Yung Moon can marry thousands of people who've never even met, then a Church
of the Subgenius short duration marriage could be the answer.
Yeah, as a matter of fact, this is one thing you can do as a subgenius minister.
You can do legal weddings.
You can also do the short duration marriages.
This certificate here produced by Reverend Buck Naked in Dallas can come in very handy.
Because the short duration marriage can last for an hour, a night, a week, a year, whatever.
And the divorces are cheap.
They come with the certificate.
All right.
Anybody else want to get married tonight?
Step right up.
Get your holy short duration marriage certificate here.
Test your mettle and win the little lady a rubber stooge.
And you're a stupid doll.
Guaranteed, friends, to absolve and sanctify all otherwise illicit couplings.
Free short duration divorce if you're not completely satisfied.
All right.
Now, you two stand together and face me.
Oh, I like that.
All right.
Let's be solemn now here.
Do you, Glenn, take the responsibility to get married?
I do.
I swear to tell the truth, the whole truth, and nothing but the truth.
Tell me about it.
I do.
Do you, Brandy, swear to tell the truth, the whole truth, and nothing but the truth?
Say, I love you, Bob.
Yeah.
All right.
Good.
Okay.
Now, how long do you wish for this period of sanctified couplings to last?
One year.
One year?
Oh, yeah.
That's right.
You told me that.
One year.
Me.
You sure?
Yeah.
All right.
Two years.
Oh, yes.
Dearly beloveds, we are gathered here today in the presence of J.R. Bob Dobbs and insert
other deity names here, any other deities, to join this man, Glenn, and this woman, Brandy,
in the bondage of holy matrimony, for better or for worse, but not for long.
Do you feel the spirit?
Yes.
Then put your hands on each other.
If there are any here who feel this man and this woman, share your hands.
You should not be joined temporarily.
Just hold your peace, because we don't want to hear about it.
All right.
Now, put your hands.
Hold tight.
Hold tight now.
Oh, lovely.
Lovely couple.
Do you, Glenn, take this woman, Brandy, to be your lawful wedded wife and short-duration
subgenius matrimonial, to have and to hold for richer or poorer in sickness and kinkiness
for the next year?
Say, I do.
I do.
Do you?
Shake on it and say, it's a deal.
Now, get up.
Oh, he's not up there.
Oh, yeah, we're not over.
We're not finished yet.
We've got a really important part, the symbolic part, coming up.
Get out the ring.
You do have a ring, don't you?
All right.
The best man.
The best man here.
Let's give a hand for the best man.
All right.
We take this ring.
Give that to Glenn.
And, Glenn, you...
And she inserts her finger into the hole.
We take this ring as a holy symbol of the estate of marriage as well as of the pole
going deep into the hole repeatedly, obviously.
By the authority invested in me by J.R. Bob Dobbs in defiance of the law.
Be of the order of the law, be 아니라, *** Bureau Skilled番 inteική stricte
Now we arestudying between the laws of the state and of nature.
I pronounce you man and wife for the next one year.
You must...
You must now kiss each other right in front of all these people.
Praise Bob.
Alright, temperate your Ottawa.
Far from the books, Far in forget beauty, love...
You must now kiss the father right in front of all
Praise Bob.
This is a show of the man who...
Yeah.
Yes, yes, yes.
Thank you, yes, yes, yes.
Praise Bob.
Whoa!
Praise God! Praise God! Praise God!
You are now duly authorized and excused for sexual couplings of any perverse and unspeakable kind for a period of one year.
Ashes to ashes, dust to dust, it is done, amen, and a-women.
Praise God! Praise God!
The Tennessee and Ball garages of rock and roll music is obviously a means by which the white man is driven to the level with a nigger.
If you talk to the every teenager of today...
Actually he's brain dead.
If you talk to the every teenager of today and you ask them what it is...
If you talk to the every teenager of today, and you ask them what it is...
Ah hmm...
They are incredibly dear...
Come on...
If you talk to the every teenager of today and you ask them what it is about rock and roll music that they like...
...
If you talk to the average teenager of today and you ask them what it is about rock and
roll music that they like, the first thing they'll say is the beat, the beat, the beat.
Why I believe that is because I know how it feels when you sing it.
I know what it does to you.
The evil feeling that you feel when you sing it.
Why I believe that is because I know how it feels.
I know the loss that you can get from the beat.
Well, if you talk to the average teenager of today and you ask them what it does to you,
you ask them what it is about rock and roll music that they like, the evil feeling that
you feel when you sing it.
If you talk to the average teenager of today, if you talk to the average teenager of today,
you'll get the beat, the beat, the beat.
The beat, the beat, the beat.
The evil feeling that you feel when you sing it.
Why I believe that is because I know how it feels when you sing it.
The feeling of the living in you.
Come out, Arthur, come out of this body.
Come out of those muscles.
Come out of those bones.
Come out of that heart.
Arthur, come out.
Come out of those muscles.
I believe that is because I know how it feels when you sing it.
I know what it does to you.
I know the evil feeling that you feel when you sing it.
I know the lost position that you get into.
Come out, come out of this body.
Come out of those bones.
You see a group today and you ask them what it is about rock and roll music that they like,
the first thing they'll say is, the beat, the beat, the beat.
The beat, the beat, the beat.
The evil feeling that you feel when you sing.
I want you to come out, I said come out of this boat, come out of this boat, come out of this boat, come out of that horse, I said come out, I said come out, in the name of Jesus.
I wanted to go to the devil, boy, to the trouble, boy, because the devil i was sinking into my soul.
I don't want my soul to go дома where иде万가지고의.
Go on, go find it!
The beat, the beat, the beat.
The evil.
Beat, the beat, the beat.
Why I believe that is because I know...
Subgenious hell.
It's cold.
Cold.
cold kind of hell.
Cold in here.
Wish I could light this here pipe.
They gave me all the frappy in the world.
And it's too cold to light this pipe.
Oh, Bob, where are you now?
Why did you leave me in the hands of me?
However, Bob will offer you
eternal salvation or triple your money back.
Which unfortunately gives some the image in their minds
of Bob standing at the gates of hell handing out $60 checks.
Well, that's real funny.
I hope you boys are having a good time.
I bet you thought this old church thing of yours
was gonna be big, big fun.
Big fun.
Big barrel of laughs.
Oh, yeah.
I bet you thought you were gonna be some kind of high school lawyer
with that Bob fellow of yours.
Well, you're looking at a pretty damn long eternity.
Oh, by the way, here's that triple your money back.
It's, what, $60?
One for you, Smith.
One for you, Jones.
And, uh, don't let this deter you from doing business with us again.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
You're listening to the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
For free information on Bob Dobbs and the Church of the Subgenius,
send a self-addressed stamped envelope to, got your pencil ready?
Bob, Post Office Box 140306.
Dallas, Texas 75214.
That's Bob, P.O. Box 140306.
Stay tuned and praise Bob!
Ah!
Well, then.
Dennis locked me in this little box.
I can't feel anything.
I can't see anything.
It's totally black.
I have no sensation in my hands.
I don't know if I'm moving or what.
I'm just in this little box.
He said I could talk to you.
He said you'd know what to do if you wanted to help me.
Oh, good, happy mid-wilming!
I, I promise I'll pay you all the royalties that I didn't tell you about.
And, and, whatever you want to do, I'll pay you.
I mean, anything.
Te-te-te-te-tevis.
You can have Tevis.
Just get me out of this box, Wilman.
Please, don't.
No.
Don't believe what Paul told you.
It's all a lie.
Whatever I did, I, I, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I let you out of the box, Wilman.
I, I can't.
This is a bad show, Wilman.
This is a real bad show.
She says she'd almost rather see me in Tevis than in nothing at all.
Right.
I'm sorry.
I think those wysh skies red, I think people think thatけれ.
There were suns in your oven,
It was.
It was so pleasure Slow down I هذا
© BF-WATCH TV 2021