All the peoples of the world are, in effect, partners in this interest.
And for our own part, we see very clearly that unless justice be done to others, it will not be done to us.
The program for the world's peace, as we see it, is this.
The Church of the Subgenius in the name of J.R. Bogg.
Ah, yes, dear friends.
And so good, so good to be back, back on the airwaves with tonight's Hour of Slack show,
which, by the way, will be a collision of subgenius shows.
It's been a while since we've let all the shows that are...
The original shows done out there in subgenius land just collide in the time warp of the Church,
the bosom of J.R. Bob Dobbs.
We have a special guest here tonight, the Tevinator.
Tevinator, are you prepared with your statement?
You may proceed.
We are the future, the children of a new era.
We have been born from the mistakes of the past.
And are expected to pick up the pieces of the future.
We are shackled by a dysfunctional system that is unable to keep pace with our hyper-cellularated culture.
We have been told what to think by fundamentalist demons masquerading as leaders and saints.
We are expected to ignore the damages inflicted by a disposal society.
We are forced to watch our rights being whittled to dust.
Our time is now!
We must use all the tools in our power.
We must utilize our brains.
As a primary weapon.
We must harness the power of chaos.
We must forcefully occupy cyberspace.
We must assimilate.
We must subvert.
We must pay the new leadership for a new millennium.
We must regain control of our destiny.
Or our lives are meaningless.
Praise Bobby!
Ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay.
And now dear friends.
The show you've been waiting for.
The subgenius radio ministry hour of...
Slacker, yes.
It's worthless.
Because it's merely the work of a few unbridled individualists.
Artistic value is achieved collectively.
By each man subordinating himself to the standards of the majority.
I read that in your column yesterday.
You did? Thank you.
Now, the greatness of Peter Keating's personality lies in the fact that there is no personality stamped upon his building.
Quite true.
Thus he represents not himself, but the multitude of all men together.
And produces great big marble bromides.
I believe I'm failing to sell you Peter Keating.
Why no.
You're succeeding.
Your Keating is worthless.
So he's probably the right choice for that building.
He's sure to be popular.
You wouldn't expect me to pick a man of merit, would you?
We are told we are weak.
Incapable of grasping scale.
Afraid of ourselves and desperate to push responsibility for all events in our lives onto them.
We are insistently trained to accept our corporal existence.
As hopeless in itself.
To become subservient to the greater good.
We are perpetually conditioned, encouraged and blackmailed into self-restriction.
Into narrower and narrower perceptions of ourselves.
Our own importance.
Our own potential and our own experience.
We are trained to ignore the evidence of our senses and experiences.
And to feel guilt when we glimpse the self-genius.
Our own...
...sense.
The Self-Genius
Please leave the area.
We are starting the final countdown.
TSC, this is Florida Control.
All power for the shields checking out at one hundred and fifty.
All systems are go.
Please run final checks on all shield power elements.
Please leave the area.
We are starting the final countdown.
Hello?
We're recording. Everything's going fine.
...the children sir.
Ha ha ha.
That's what he said.
Can I see that back door on his platform?
Don't you think it's time we let them have a glimpse of what it's like?
Don't you think it's time that you sat down and, uh, came face to face with your destiny?
My destiny.
Here at the top of the Texas School Book Depository, I'm...
Uh, isn't it about time you came face to face with...
...Buh-buh.
Um...
...Buh...
...my friends.
It's easy enough to do.
It's the strangest...
...Jesus...
...you ever...
...seen.
Face to face with my destiny.
Now, this famous curtain rod depository was on the site of Medeli Plaza.
My destiny.
Yes, right here at Let's Make a Dealey Plaza, we're going to begin the quiz show of all quiz shows.
The 1963 election giveaway.
And our first gag guest is Gero, the monkey that's been trained to act like George Bush.
Let's give him a big hand.
Well...
...see my...
Gero can walk on stools, dance jigs on his hands and somersault through hoops like any ordinary circus monk.
Well...
But he can also mimic the president's actions and emotions with uncanny accuracy.
Read my lips.
Read my...
Oh!
There they go.
Hey, listen, that's just a picture.
He didn't actually say it, but it becomes this kind of surreal cartoon of itself.
He is an actor, not just an animal doing tricks, said Taro Murasaki, 30, Gero's trainer.
That is the art of suromawashi.
In the stomach medicine ad, Gero parodies the pain of overindulgence in booze and the very human ritual of vowing never ever again with cruel precision.
Gero's most recent skit is equally sharp-edged.
Bush-san, coked Murasaki.
Bush-san.
The monkey gags, pretends to vomit, then closes his eyes and swoons in the manner of flu-stricken President George Herbert Walker Bush.
It was during a state dinner with Prime Minister Kiyichi Miyazawa last month.
Poor taste, sure, but it elicits guffaws from both Japanese and listeners of KPFA.
Weep, weep, weep.
By the time of the shooting, there seemed to be some commotion.
I just am unable to describe a flash of light, smoke, or something.
which caused me to feel that something out of the ordinary had occurred there on the embankment.
The Church of the Subgenius in the name of J.R. Bob Dobs.
How long have you been here?
Peace
Peace in the Middle East
Everlasting loving peace
Joy, joy in the middle east
Peace, peace
Everlasting loving peace
Now who ever said the Subgeniuses were not politically correct?
Can't go wrong
Urging peace
Peace
Everlasting peace
Peace, peace
And please, don't get me wrong.
I'm not accusing.
What I'm trying to say is
if you have to lose your self-respect
in order to be popular,
is it worth it?
You know, we tried every kind of treatment
and it just failed.
She wanted to be cremated.
Would that make a difference?
No, that makes no difference.
If she wants to be cremated, that's what you do.
So, in other words...
And that's more reasonable.
If I wanted to bring the lighter fluid in the match...
No, you can't do a lighter fluid in match.
You have to have her cremated at the crematory.
Well, she wanted me to do it.
No, you can't cremate her.
So, it has to be done at a crematory.
Would that cost extra?
No, no.
The cremation is less reasonable.
It's less than the burial, of course.
Okay, well, that sounds very good.
And one more thing.
She wanted me to cut a piece of her off.
Cut a piece of her off?
Just to save to remember her.
Her ring finger.
You can't cut a piece of her off.
You can't do that either.
Because she said that I should.
I didn't want to do it.
No, you can't cut a piece of her off unless you take a piece of her hair.
But not her finger.
Huh?
Her finger.
Oh, no, you couldn't keep her finger.
No way.
No.
I couldn't eat her flesh.
Huh?
No, you can't.
She wanted me to eat her flesh.
You can't do that.
I'm sorry.
I'm not a cannibal, ordinarily.
Mm-hmm.
Well, I don't know.
What time can you come down to see me tomorrow?
Now, I have a funeral here at 1 o'clock.
So can you come down in the morning?
Well, who...
I guess I can.
I'd like to see you at 10 o'clock tomorrow morning.
I'm coming here at the funeral home.
Okay.
And one more question.
The man who's...
Is it a man or a woman at the funeral?
Could I eat their flesh?
You want to eat...
You want to eat their flesh?
I'm a ghoul.
I'm a real cool ghoul.
I don't know about you, but before the election,
I don't know about you, but before the election, I'm going to have to...
It's a real fascination, as if it's disclosing somebody deep within.
As he jabs the finger into the air.
Ow!
Hey, you don't need to demonstrate, Philip.
Into the air and screeches the words again and again.
Screech!
His commercial business becomes to seem more and more desperate,
more and more absurd.
Stop it! Stop it! Stop it!
These dedicated television viewers...
Oh, my, I just don't know.
...to take the president seriously.
Every time.
I never believe you.
...the obscene stories...
Oh, you stupid idiot!
This stuff costs money!
I'm sorry, I spoke a little out of turn,
but, boy, what a skullbuster of a headache I've got.
Doing this show this early in the morning is no picnic, I tell you.
It's at a time like this that I want to kick back and relax
with a silly chocolate bar.
Yeah, they say this isn't a funny show, it's just a silly show,
and it's at that time I want a silly chocolate bar.
The powerhouse bar that knocks you silly.
Covered with creamy milk chocolate, it's zesty, tangy, tasty, yeasty,
with caramel nougat, crunchy walnuts, and a rich butter taste.
It contains sugar, cocoa butter, milk, chocolate,
and like a thing added as an emulsifier,
salt artificially...
...flavored with cough syrup,
vanillin, a vanilla substitute, and 27 milligrams of millivanillin,
an artificial, phony sugar substitute, butter, almonds with salt, and...
...an artificial flavor with more sugar, more lecithin, more everything
in a silly chocolate bar.
They're cool.
Enjoy a silly chocolate bar and you can be cool, like me.
I'm a real cool ghoul.
They say...
We have spoken not of sugar in terms too concrete
and not free to admit of any further doubt or question.
An evident principle runs through the whole program I have outlined.
I'm a real cool ghoul.
Ooh.
Buried in that area, so it would behoove you to use a funeral home
in that particular locale.
Well, what if we, like, have cremated?
Uh, you still would probably use a funeral home
in your own locale, rather than come way down here into Neptune.
What hospital is the body in?
Paul Kimball.
Oh, it's in Paul Kimball.
Mm.
Well, it would do you better to go to one of them local funeral homes,
rather than to try to come down here.
We'd decide to eat him.
Um, well, what if we decided to, like, chop him up and eat him?
Eat his flesh?
That would be fine.
Y'all go ahead and get him and chop him up and eat him,
because that would do you good.
We're a real cool ghoul.
Yeah, that would do you just right to chop him up and eat him.
Why don't you get some lye and put him in a pot of lye,
and then it'll all dissolve in the lye.
Why, thanks, man.
That's a good idea, isn't it?
Ah-hoo!
All right, whore.
What?
I said do your thing, whore.
Is this any way for a funeral director to be targeting?
Hey, yo, is that?
You know, she's so unresponsible, I'll just cut it.
And why would you wait till 12.25 at night to call a funeral director?
Because I get...
You should be calling one tomorrow morning early.
Because...
One of your choice.
Well, let me tell you, I've got an inheritance coming.
I've got money, all right?
You know, it's just...
I don't have to explain every...
No, you really don't have to explain none of it to me,
because I'm not going to have the body.
Well, you won't do it?
I'm not going to have it.
This is the third prank call I've had tonight about dead people.
And I'm not going to have anybody that's dead,
so I don't need to listen to your...
But you're off funeral home.
No, what are you saying?
What are you, insane?
Yes, I'm very much insane.
Do you know Jerry Lewis?
I'm Jerry Lewis.
You know what?
You're Jerry Lewis?
I'm Jerry Lewis.
Oh, that's cute.
That's...
No, I really am.
Listen...
Listen to me.
You know, I love to talk to an idiot.
It makes me laugh.
What?
Now, am I in communication with some sort of...
Is this supposed to be your caller here?
Is this supposed to be your little caller?
Is this what you call a little caller?
Hey, let's lose the background track.
Yeah, thanks.
Now, caller, I want you to tell me your most embarrassing moment.
My most embarrassing moment?
That's right.
Well...
Go ahead.
We're all ears.
Well, I'd raped myself into the church and nailed myself to their cross
and was standing there on the cross.
I was sitting there above the altar when all of a sudden my loincloth came down.
They all thought I was Jesus Christ until they saw that I was hung like a subgenius.
It is the time to go public with the war on Satan.
We must go public because when the government made ease to wipe out drug users and homosexuals,
it was not enough.
Yes, we need more.
They have developed terms that will mark people who take drugs and let them go.
They have turned us into loud music.
They've discouraged the skin of people who listen to certain vibrations of music.
They've discouraged drug users also.
They have terms to kill all major sinners who kill the Christians.
Satan kills.
God will kill him.
How many bodies die?
Children of God dying.
We will say a prayer.
God help us cast out the infidels.
We welcome Satan's plundering, pillaging, and killing.
For Satan kills all men.
Only the depraved and wretched.
God, let the gargoyles loose from the gates of hell.
You said that you're a weapon against wretchedness.
Let them cast out their feces upon the faces of earth into the quagmire of human filth and wickedness.
God will stamp his heel into the sinner's face.
Then Satan will judge and beat them down again.
Then they will be cast into hell.
Their insides will come out from within.
And all sinners who don't die will be old and decrepit.
Who died?
Christ.
Why?
Your sins.
God always does die.
He died for you.
I can do it.
Okay, ma'am.
He's going to talk to you.
Okay?
Okay.
He'd rather do it himself.
Hey.
Yeah.
Now, listen here.
There's...
There was a sexual day.
I...
When everything happened...
Be quiet.
I don't know how long ago.
Don't ask him.
He's drunk.
Well, listen here, guys.
Uh, I...
Like you say, and we know that you have drank too much, but do you have a mother and a father?
Hell no.
I'm 21.
He's 18.
And...
And you don't have a mother?
No.
Is she dead?
She's dead.
Is your dad?
My daddy got ran over by a car.
Oh.
How long ago?
Two years ago.
Really?
Well, do you work?
Do I work?
Uh-huh.
Oh, yeah, I work.
I work at Phillips.
You work at Phillips.
Does your brother work?
Yeah, my brother works at Burger King.
At Burger King.
Well...
Uh...
It just seems to me like you guys just don't have enough to do.
And, uh...
Well, what do you...
I don't understand.
Well, to be getting on the phone this time of night and be drunk and talking out of your
mind.
It sort of sounds ridiculous now, doesn't it, really?
Well, I mean, I'm sorry, ma'am.
No, I don't have a daughter named Glenda.
I have two.
Well, you know, I tried to tell you a minute ago that I'm sorry.
Well, I know.
And I don't know how in the hell this all came about.
I really don't.
Well, I don't either.
But you know what?
I don't think it's an accident you call me.
Uh, now, your name is Johnson.
Yes.
And what's your first name, did you say?
David.
David Johnson.
Well, anyway, what I was gonna tell you, uh, David, is that you're a man.
And I don't know if it's an accident you call me.
Is it, all right.
But, um, let me tell you why.
Because I know I used to be a real miserable person.
And I done think that I knew that I shouldn't do.
But I was running and I was looking for something to fill a void that I had in my heart.
And, like you, you're not happy, are you?
No, ma'am.
Not really.
I hate my job.
I hate my wife.
I hate both of my kids.
I hate my brother. All he ever does is get drunk. That's all I ever do. I hate myself.
Well, that's what it all boils down to, David.
And really, you know, we're not supposed to hate ourselves.
And it's not that you hate yourself. You have just made such a mess of your life.
My daddy did that before he died.
He probably did that. He didn't help you any. If he was a mean person or...
He was. He used to beat me up, me and my brother.
He beat you both up. Was your mother a good person?
Do what?
Was your mother a good person?
My mother was a saint.
She was a saint. Do you think she was a Christian?
I know for a fact she was. She used to make me go to church, and I didn't like her because of that.
But you really now wish that you had...
I wish my mama was here so she could take me to church today.
Are there any questions?
Yes.
Please ask your questions so that all the members may hear.
Yes, John.
Hello.
Oh money pad me wallet. Oh money pad me wallet. Oh money pad me wallet. Oh money pad me wallet. Oh money pad me wallet.
Oh feel the energy.
There's the grounding and self-centering.
We need to do a grounding and self-centering right now.
Oh I can feel the change coming on right now.
Joe, speak it, Joe.
Now, we want you to clear your mind and think only of yourself.
Only of you.
In the name of Jesus.
From here up to nature.
.
. .
Me, me, I, me, I .
I, me, me, I.
.
There's no place like my ego.
Boy, that was refreshing, wasn't it?
Aren't you occasions, Joe?
John Lennon, I me mine, I me mine, I me mine.
Hey, Sting, thanks again for clarifying again this thing about the Trevino-ist, you know, making sure that...
It can't be said enough.
No.
As long as the secular Trevino-ists are still launching Trevino heads on Thursdays, Easter, or any other time,
that we cannot rest.
No.
Our vigilance can never cease.
The mighty heads.
The mighty bleeding heads.
There's one right here in the station, friends.
It's a head sort of manifestation.
Bleeding head good, heel head bad.
Hey, you can't do that.
You can't deliver a plug on this show.
Food plugging.
It's time to prank the preacher.
Immediately cover over with obfuscation.
Yeah, we're going to have to bleep that out.
We'll have to adjust that later so none of you heard it.
I don't know who you think you are.
You can't come on the air and do a...
We'll have to do a specific subgenius address on this show.
Oh, who's plugging?
I'm just asking you to prank him.
Well, now look, you can stop scratching that squirrel and get back to basics as you study your subgenius doctrine.
In the book of pre-scriptures.
Okay, and here it is now.
Doctrine one.
As we walk down the path, we walk down the pathway of life.
Do you ever turn to yourself and say,
Dammit, where to?
I left socks go.
Now, you know, women and childrens listens to this show.
Women and children.
Women and children come into my laundry room and steal my socks.
And get up.
I'm falling.
And I can't get up.
Oh, my God.
Well, you'd better buy some of that senior home security stuff, Missy, or else you'll get all out of control.
Yes, join a support group for senior support socks.
Oh, that was...
Too much.
Well, now we're back at the tunnel of love.
Trickling along at a pleasantly slow pace.
And not much more can happen to us.
I tell you, this evening has been one of those times.
It's what you call a Malox moment.
Well, look, that's what it says here.
You know, we've got to get better riders.
That's all I have to say.
Well, anyway, off the record, it's been fun.
But, you know, it kind of gets...
It wears you down after a while.
You come on.
Out here, you do these shows.
It gets so that, you know, it's just not fun anymore.
And that's when you need a little bit of new blood.
It's what we call the time control effect.
I thought he was running away.
Dr. Fred is here.
I'm here!
He's with us.
And Sister Clone's back.
And the flow, the show, it's floating down around you right now.
Golden baubles floating through the air.
Should we have a little epitaph for Dr. St. Bogomil?
He's not dead yet.
High over Humboldt Bay, looking out on the beautiful lights and the rain.
It's a pleasant sight.
We're drifting gently with the radio show.
The panorama.
Drifting down low.
The stratosphere.
Drifting down into your headphones.
Out there.
Below us, we see the lights of Arcata Eureka.
It's all so beautiful.
The special little light of Bob's country buses.
And we have no telephones up here where we're at, so we're not taking any calls.
Juggle, juggle, juggle.
KHS.
You with Dr. Fred and Sister Klein.
St. Dogzomatic from Arcata there.
As well as some prank call reenactments submitted by some anonymous friends of James Blanchard, I think.
Yes.
You also heard, dear friends.
Of course, WCSB in Cleveland.
A Reverend Cole show, on which I was lucky enough to appear with St. Stymie de Bergerac and Reverend Mary Squared, au contraire.
And of course, also the most recognizable voices in Subgenius Radio.
Dr. Howland puzzling evidence there on KPFA in Berkeley.
Oh, yes.
What a lovely, horrible thing.
Putting a little rain seed.
A little rain seed here, a little rain seed there.
Ha, ha, ha.
We're a little short of oxygen, but that doesn't hurt us.
We don't need it.
Fortunately, due to these gills I got at Bobstown, Dobstown, I can breathe almost any kind of thing.
Absolutely.
Acid rain doesn't bother us either.
We're impervious.
Looking down below the lights of Arcata and Eureka and Bob's country bunker, a special little light shining off.
And we are in California.
It's so nice to be here.
This guy has a flaming inverted cross.
Uh, it looks like, yes, a flaming inverted cross on somebody's lawn in Manila.
I don't understand it.
Manila?
There appears to be a dead baby at the same house.
I, perhaps it is too, is suspended from the light.
Do you think you could zero the show in a little closer to this cross burning on the lawn in Manila?
Uh, standby.
Oh.
Hold on, Fred, hold on.
We're working.
Twenty-six Americans.
Here we go.
Hold on.
Oh, yeah.
That is...
And you've already killed 17 Americans.
Oh, the cross.
P-L-O-T.
Oh, oh, I'm kind of dizzy.
Did we have to go so low so quickly?
Ah.
I'm coming.
Whoa.
Isn't he guarantees life?
You were saying something about us going toaaaaan the moon.
Oh, yes we were.
Hmm.
What do you mean we were at the moon?
We were on planet C.
We were like very successful.
Ah.
Unfortunately.
you so much, even no matter what all you do, even that you're drunk as a dog, he still
loves you, and he doesn't like your sins, he doesn't like things you've done, and he
knows you've made a mess of your life, but he realizes that you're just weak, you know,
you're just a person, a human that makes no sense, but he loves you, and I'd like to be
your mother, I'd like for you to go to church with me, I'll take the place of your mother,
really.
Ma'am, this is so touching, I just, I know my brother's drunk too, but you tell him the
same thing you just told me, and we may feel better, hang on.
Hello.
Yeah.
Now your name is Bob?
And you really are her brother, his brother?
Uh-huh.
Are you drunk?
Uh, yeah.
Well, how come you guys, how come you guys get drunk?
Well, you all right?
Hey.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
Just a second.
Hey, Bob.
Don't hang up.
I won't hang up.
The voluntary relinquishing of responsibility for our lives and actions is one of the greatest
enemies of our times.
Oswald was a radar operator.
He'd have about as much...
He'd have as much use for Russian as a cat has for pajamas.
These books have gotten to your mind, Mr. Garrison.
And then...
Here's Johnny!
Ask not what your country can do for you.
Ask what you can do for your...
Here is a bulletin.
But there are certain things that we can all agree on.
There is...
A right and a left.
Uh-huh.
Let me hear you say, uh-huh.
There is a dark and a light.
Uh-huh.
There's a good and a bad.
A religion!
A wrong and a right.
Now...
Who's the wrong?
To the pagan, there's a lord versus lady.
Taoists are yin versus yang.
is yang but the subgenius?
Yang man.
Well, Bob might have had a lot of yang.
Take it from me, folks.
Connie L. Yang.
It may take a subgenius to make all that money,
but honey, it took a Connie to send it.
Charming, charming Irene.
My heart is filled with joy.
Your love, you said, is mine.
And all of very good.
You're good, you're good, Irene.
Heaven sent you to me.
Charming, charming Irene.
I'm in love with you.
You'll be imploding with joy before you know it.
Oh, happy, happy joy.
Did you notice how when I launched the head
in the name of Ren and Stimpy,
how the author...
The audience just went nuts.
Absolutely went wild.
Truly, Ren and Stimpy cuts across all,
almost all cultural and whatever kind of borders.
Oh, it brings me back to those days of my childhood
in front of the television with that audiovisual
pouring into my eyes,
eating those highly sugared cereals
and taking a couple of hits off that whipped cream bottle.
That's where it all started.
This is Ren the Hwacky.
And this is Stimson J. Catt of the Ren and Stimpy Show.
And you're listening to the Hour of Slack on KNON.
Keep listening, you idiot.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Else I shall deal you.
In the name of Ren and Stimpy.
A secondary launching.
It's incredible.
Rainbomb.
Bleeding head cut.
Healed head down.
Oh, speaking of fun.
Connie is the true goddess of the subgenius church.
You can't con Connie.
Garden belts for great ideas.
When I'm good, I'm very, very good.
But baby, when I'm slack, I'm better.
I'm better.
Let's testify.
Yes, Lord.
Amen.
Well, before you go getting in all this dogmatic stuff,
we just want to welcome you back.
You've been gone so long, Sister Clone.
Yeah, where the hell have you been?
It's been a difficult absence, you know.
Um, I'm really...
I'm really still not sure what happened.
I...
Were you off studying the ways of Bob?
No, I...
You were studying the ways of Hobie.
I don't know if it was a dream or if it really happened,
but I think that I was...
Studying the ways of Akira.
I was kidnapped.
So, I do know Akira.
Oh, go ahead.
Go ahead.
I was kidnapped by a...
Don't let us big, powerful subgenius doctors frighten you,
Sister Clone.
Go ahead.
Speak.
Oh, well, it's so...
I'm still so shaken up by my experiences.
I can imagine.
I was kidnapped by someone who attempted to...
deprogram me, force-fed me Pepsi and aspirin
as an antidote to what they said.
Uh, what was a...
A deep, uh...
I was having a problem.
408.
And, um...
You know...
Yes, yes.
It was actually working.
I was attempting to invoke the power of Bob.
Straight out of Brooklyn, boy!
Yo, boy, straight out of Brooklyn!
And you invoked that power of Bob, and what happened?
Well, I don't know,
but I woke up, uh, lying in the parking lot next to a 7-Eleven,
clutching a Pepsi, wondering if it had all been just a dream,
whether they had actually deprogrammed me and learned some of the secrets.
Oh, it's them, them subgenius people taking your voice away,
and they're giving you nothing but this parking little howl,
and all you could do is just kinda yop, yop and yop and...
Scientists announced today that time travel is theoretically possible.
An article on...
Page 2 of the San Francisco Examiner...
postulated that a gravitational field could, in theory,
and in accordance with the beliefs of modern physics,
influence time within a controlled area.
Ah...
Hey, Hal, what's the liquid slack?
The problem is total disorientation and confusion of all elements of life by the renegade rogue device.
Wait, wait, wait.
There's something in there.
There's two of you over there.
Wait, who's she?
What's happening?
I'm in a space and now...
The problem is it...
Don't take that!
I've got you!
Oh, Gesundheit.
It's real hard to try to fix this thing when it's going haywire and...
Here we go.
The effects could be disastrous to our own continuum.
There we go.
Oh!
They're shooting at us.
Okay, we're clearly at the top now of the hill.
All the subgeniuses are all around me.
How do we get out of this?
I've only got a few bullets left.
I'm gonna have to...
All the cops!
Wait a minute, I didn't have anything to do with this.
Okay, you're under arrest now.
Wow, I'm passing out.
And you're in the subgenius chair.
I'm in the subgenius chair.
I'm going crazy.
I hear the water dripping and the interrogator's voice.
Hey, who's that?
Oh, holy moly!
All right, stand launch.
One.
Ignition.
Oh my god.
Lift off.
Oh, oh, I'll get it.
All right, if I could just hear this bolt, I could...
Okay, here we go.
Project on bad.
Yeah, well you see, um...
They said that the problem is that instead of the influence of the...
the external continuum, the chrononaut or time traveler might, uh, reduce his, uh...
How will this one put it?
It's not even in the...
Yeah, that'll teach me, yeah.
Well, well, hey clown.
Hello.
Let me tell you, you sound really pretty tonight.
I know, I'm feeling pretty.
But you know what?
I felt...
I felt the giggle coming on when I heard you.
You sound sort of Louisianish.
Well...
You do sound like you should shoot our next president.
Well, you know...
You're a man!
Now and then, we all get the urge.
Yeah.
Is this a symptom of having used your prairie squid prior to de-beaking?
I mean, is this what happened?
Well, you know, this was an oral use of prairie squid, which I cannot recommend to any subgenius.
It's definitely out.
I got a shot of straight sepia right down my gullet.
Oh.
And things have not been the same since.
I hate it when that happens.
Oh, lord.
Yeah.
I'm not sure if I can get it out.
I don't know if I will recover.
However, I have been using a snake oil.
I mean, not the Dobbs brand snake oil, but something's going to get me going again, I'm
sure.
Will you be well enough to attend a special anniversary celebrations of the Day of Infamy
occurring tomorrow throughout Humboldt County?
The Day of Infamy, of course.
Yeah.
Boy, how destructive this thing is.
You know, it's damaging the fabric of the universe and the space-time continuum.
All through the universe.
All through all time.
Well, that's what happens when you use that excess technology without a future.
What are excess technology?
It's what we call forbidden science.
It's the incredible excess technology we all think we're within the show.
Yes, it's Edgar Allan Poe once again.
And I think...
I'm afraid not.
Well, you know, we've got other things.
We've got lots of stuff for you.
We've got lots of stuff.
We've got gags, cosmic truth, stories.
We have 28 minutes left in the show.
It's the meeting.
You can have it.
It's the meeting of life.
That little carrot in your backyard that you thought was so unimportant.
Life and life's effluents clouded walls and shadows.
Jolly color is the spirit and the power which wedded nature gives to us in dower.
A new earth and a new heaven.
Undreamt of by the sensual and the proud.
Slack is the soft voice.
Slack the luminous cloud.
We in ourselves rejoice.
Reverend Cole tried to shoot me last night.
And you know, the funny thing is I really don't...
I wasn't that upset because...
Well, I missed.
I don't fear death.
I don't fear death at all.
I know that I will never be allowed into the Christian heaven.
Praise Bob.
None of your friends would be there.
Who would want to go?
And the Christian hell is only for those who believe in it.
It's only there to, like, scare Muslims and Christians and people.
For venalists.
Right.
For those who are afraid that if they don't believe in it, they'll go there.
They'll go there.
That's right.
Those are the ones that are on the low...
Get the lowest rung.
And everyone knows...
Everyone knows how hard it is to get a good corned beef sandwich in heaven, too.
Yeah.
As opposed to this one.
But subgenius hell.
It's just too white.
Valhalla.
It's just...
It's the kind of classical hell, the subgenius hell.
It's called helle.
With two L's and an E.
Helle.
It's...
Probably...
It's the more organic spiritual version of the escape vessels of the sex goddesses, which...
So, like, on X day, no matter what happens, if you die as a subgenius or if you are ruptured
up into the escape vessels, you either get the spiritual hell or the techno hell.
Which, of course, by the hell we mean these are like heaven.
But you have to go through subgenius hell in order to be ready for the pleasure, in
order to be able to withstand the increased pleasure of the subgenius heaven.
Ah, yes.
It's like a cleansing purgatory that prepares you for the true, true slackness.
Ah.
Oh, over there.
You have to call him.
Good afternoon, Sturdy.
Back this way, ladies and gentlemen.
You'll see Tutantese, the ugliest thing on the midway.
And if you step into this tent, gentlemen, no children or...
They dwell in caves, not high-rise apartments.
You will see the most sickening sight your eyes have ever seen.
It's caution, ladies and gentlemen, against doing that terrible drug, LSD.
Inside this tent, my good friends, is a young man who experimented with this deadly drunk
and you can see for yourself the effect it had.
Ah.
Not only on his mind and his soul...
Hell.
...but on his very own body, right down to his toenails.
And here is that young man now.
Hey, hell.
What is it, my boy?
It's Gary.
Could you guys stop by here on the way home?
Well, I suppose so.
What's going on over there?
Well, I can't talk about it right now, but I...
You'll like it, whatever it is.
I hope you're not mad at me for giving you that hoot and holler early around in the evening.
No, I'm not.
I'm just...
I'm just trying to get my mind off of the Earth.
But if you guys could stop by, I'd appreciate it.
You betcha, you bet.
Well, you have to ask Dr. Brough because he's piloting the space module.
Well, I'm sure he'll be amenable when he finds out about the free prop program.
Oh, wow.
Amenable, abominable, adorable.
We'll do it.
Sure.
I've got another two and a half weeks, so see you later.
Okay.
We'll be right over to dip our wicks in the fountain of eternal pleasure.
That's located right off the Earth.
All right, I shall be waiting for you.
All right, Dr. Brough, we're going to take you up to Jungle Boulevard in beautiful Oak
Town, California.
And we'll stop by and pick up some ice cream too, is that all right, Auntie May?
Wait a minute, who am I talking to now?
This is the phony caller.
You know, it's so strange to be disembodied right at the moment.
You seem rather disembodied.
Floating, floating here...
I may be mistaken, that girl ain't got her pants on.
I hear zippers here and there.
Yeah, well, that's a check.
What you see right here...
The boys of the year.
Is the boys of the year...
I like what we see down.
You want to know why we're down?
The voice is here.
Straight out of Brooklyn and Boyd.
No, man.
Talk to me, number three.
Talk to me.
Yeah, yeah.
So are you deathly ill?
Can we send a care basket, perhaps some chocolate-covered...
Shit, Uncle Reed!
Actually, it's just a voice.
You know, I...
It hurts to talk, but I'm doing it.
I'm doing it.
Are you doing it for Bob, damn it?
I give testimony.
I mean, there's a reward.
There's a bounty out for my voice.
You should find it.
I will hit you on the head and give you the healing power of Bob!
Can I get a witness?
I will give you my seat on the exorcist.
If you can find my voice.
Children, there is a quest in Arcata tonight.
I have given a secret treasure map.
It's buried in...
It's on the plaza at the foot of President McKinley's feet.
The Lord has blessed this quest.
Exactly.
You follow the map and you find my voice.
I want every waking subgenius to head down to the plaza right now
and find my voice.
and find that map.
Right now, right now.
When we find your voice, we will cage it and return it to you.
Or would you prefer that we freed it in some wild area
so that it could roam the area?
Actually, just let it watch the antics with a little bit of prairie squid action.
You know, just let it sit and do the voyeur thing that it's so fond of.
Special prize for all you subgeniuses who make it down to that plaza right now.
Constable Bob will be waiting there for you.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha!
The Blaise Brown Food Pints of the Gods, and you're listening to the subgenius.
The Subgenius.
Our home.
What?
Gosh.
What else caught your eye at the show, at the devival, Reverend Stang?
Well, I got snagged on a coat hanger at one point when they were trying to...
God almighty.
In your eye?
Yeah, but, you know, I'm on a lot of healing herbs at any given time.
Well, I was going to say, what good would a bleeding Stang head do us?
Yeah.
And launch it.
Well, couldn't you?
Well, not in its present form.
That was one industrial-strength catapult.
I think you could have actually launched the Stang head.
Oh, friends, the launching catapult, we hadn't even mentioned that.
It was the most obscene.
All I can say is, if the legs had been spread a little bit more,
the head probably would have flown farther.
Had the legs been spread more, there would have been a ladder between them.
Oh, the alabaster legs.
There would have been more head either way.
But the head did squirt around.
You could feel the electricity.
Oh.
You could feel the electricity in the air from that head launching.
It was a thing to behold.
Now we know why she got no legs.
As Janer, the crazy preacher, Janer of Little Rock,
he punctuates his every other sentence with,
Help me, somebody.
She ain't got no legs.
My legs are on fire.
Pull the lever down and you go.
We pulled the lever down.
The she ain't got no legs is from the unfortunate incidents of people losing their legs.
At Doctors for Bob concerts, we often wondered where those legs went.
And there they were up on stage.
That's true.
With lasciviously spread eagles mounted on this sort of framework,
religious-looking framework.
The platform of cherubim.
Yeah.
It's like, oh, God.
Frightening-looking thing.
But it was a great launching, and it had a secondary launching.
The first launching, it landed in somebody's lap,
and they screamed and threw the head up.
Up into the air, further back into the audience.
People kissing it.
They really responded to the head launching,
which was the climax of the show.
Hail, Connie.
But we lose track of the elusive Connie.
Where did she go?
To the
hospital.
Oh, yes, dear friends.
And before it gets too much later, I think I should at least fill some of you in on what's going on.
In a way, we hate to do that.
But I should explain that you're listening to the Subgenius Radio.
We're a ministry hour of slack.
Sponsored by, yes, the Church of the Subgenius.
Tonight's show in particular has been a cross-section of the other subgenius shows from around the country.
There's only two or three other original ones, which this one is off to compose.
And while you can learn more about our outreach,
you can also learn more about the subgenius of the Subgenius Radio.
In the name of J.R. Bob Dobbs, the living avatar of slack,
by writing for free information.
And I'm about to give you that post office box and number to write to.
Just drop us a line.
Say, Bob, I don't know if I'm with you yet or not,
but I'm willing to hear what you have to say.
I'm willing to try slack on for size.
One size fits all, dear friends.
Just write to Bob.
at post office box 140306.
That's 140306, Dallas, Texas, 75214.
And I know that the way I say that and the fact that it's in Dallas, Texas,
and the way all this sounds, like, it sounds like it's just a joke just to put on.
There's probably nothing at that address.
Well, that's not true.
You're just going to have to drop us a line, and you'll find out for free just how much is at that address.
And you may find yourself surprised.
There's things to see, say, and do, things to think and know,
and you'll pay to know what you really think, won't you?
Yeah, well, we'll find out.
Praise Bobby.
Oh, speaking of Bob, last night was the beginning, not only of the first rant and rave
and the little extra dribble of Hurricane Bob,
but in that town, Avon, Colorado, where they named their bridge Bob,
a true omen,
they're holding the Bob Festival.
And apparently there's, it's like just this Bob out.
Of course, this is the way the conspiracy,
tries to water down Bob.
They are basically, it's like the Nissan commercial
and all those other ways the conspiracy uses to make.
The cousin Bob, the mellow Bob.
The friendly Bob.
Bob beer.
Do you think Bob, well, actually Bob did market a type of beer.
It was called Beer God.
It was a little series of liquor stores in Tennessee called Beer God.
Thirst beeper.
I can't, I can't say what it was.
It was like, thirst beeper.
And yeah, Beer God.
He also had Burger God, hunger beeper.
It was kind of a little chain.
He later moved, it became very successful in Brazil.
There are Bob's Burgers, like the McDonald's of Brazil.
In the competition.
A country well respected for its culinary tastes and skills.
Oh, it is actually.
They're wonderful hamburgers, very American style.
But you know, I understand.
I understand the rumor has it that it's Connie that's pulling the strings behind all of those.
Oh, you could, you better believe it.
Any of those extra little, those kind of things.
That's Connie.
It definitely is.
It's like with the Jimmy Swagger.
He was the sort of crazy preacher, but his wife was the one who made the ministry so big.
She focused him.
Well, no one knows meat like Connie.
She focused him and whipped him into shape.
She made the bad Bob's say, please and thank you.
Ladies.
That's not.
Oh, no kidding.
That probably ain't all she did.
Remember the guy who had never been put on before?
Mm-hmm.
It was at the sales table after all the preaching and dancing and killing had happened.
And, and there.
Attempted killing.
The ace and subgenius type people had already, you know, they were, they'd seen the show, they bought their stuff and they were gone.
So it was only the regular Smart Bar crowd that were there.
And they were coming down to where the, they encountered these bookstores.
It was like an ace store with all these underground comics and amazing sort of, I don't know what kind of philosophy books.
Timothy Leary and Abbie Hoffman.
Luminatus.
Yeah.
Tom Robbins.
All those sort of rare things.
Genetology books.
Those were very important.
Yeah.
Genetology.
This, this guy came down and it was like he, he was looking at the subgenius tapes.
I mean, he had a Bible.
I was about to pack up and quit and so it worked, he, but he gave us hard time about the dollar.
He was going, well, what is this all about?
He wanted us to tell him what the church of the subgenius was all about.
Get this.
He goes, would you explain briefly what this was all, brief and broad?
Okay.
And.
We do.
We said, look really, honestly, this little pamphlet here is the best thing that, that's the only way to really get you to understand this.
It's only a buck.
I mean.
God only knows what he paid to get in.
He probably had $40 worth of ecstasy in his pocket or whatever.
But none of these people wanted to spend a dollar.
That's probably just what you want me to do, give you a dollar.
As if we weren't giving him a 16-page book in return that takes a week to read.
He wouldn't do it.
So at that point, he goes, I don't even know who Bob is.
And Gobi and I just kind of went, oh, you don't know who he is?
Well, you can't read this.
Oh, good. Oh, good. Oh, man.
Stay. Whatever you do, don't buy it. You don't want it.
And I started grabbing not just the pamphlet, but all of the stuff off the table and packing it up.
It's too dangerous. You'll hurt yourself.
I was like, stay away. Whatever you do, don't end up like us.
He got a little angry at first.
Yeah, he was pissed.
But to his credit, he did.
He wandered away, and I think he realized that we had been challenging him somewhat.
And he came back, and he bought the pamphlet.
It was a true subgenius deal.
He did buy it.
He did buy the pamphlet.
And then he...
But he went around and got to talking to different people.
And it became obvious to us that the poor guy...
I mean, the Church of the Subgenius is a serious religion, but we love to put each other on.
And we put, you know...
It was like this guy took everything anybody said at face value.
I feel such pity for this man.
It's like...
He's...
He's ripe for Scientology.
Well, he...
Or maybe he already is.
But fortunately, he has some of the sacred documents in his hand now.
And so he may well be saved from Scientology.
And he'll learn that until your first dollar is going to Bob, you will never really understand Bob Dobbs.
You will never understand that man until at least one dollar.
You have to make that breakthrough.
I mean, what's a dollar?
That's really a token amount.
A dollar is what we used to consider a penny back when I was a kid.
You can get a piece of gum.
Or a dollar.
L. Ron Hubbard, did you ever order anything?
As a matter of fact, and this is a true story,
this old gal, Reverend Betsy Curtis in Pennsylvania,
happened to be an old friend of L. Ron Hubbard's from back when he was a science fiction writer.
And they'd stayed in touch.
And she had his for real address.
It was a post office box in Florida.
And people would take his mail to him out on his yacht.
And she gave it to me.
And I said, you know,
you ought to send him some of the subgenius stuff that's slightly based on Scientology,
like our questionnaire.
And I sent him the pamphlet and the questionnaire and all that
and thought he might get a kick out of it.
And he died a week later.
Yeah.
He died a week after I mailed it.
Fancy that.
The same thing happened to the science fiction writer, Philip K. Dick.
Yeah.
We got his address and sent him a subgenius pamphlet.
And within a week, he was dead.
The second to last person who saw Dick alive was,
uh, Reverend Jay Condom, the author of P-Dawg Comics,
who had just met him and gone over and they discussed it a little bit.
Well, there are some people who are uncertain about Philip K. Dick's death,
whether that was really staged or not.
So, uh, you never know.
Maybe L. Ron Hubbard after Dick?
I like to think that...
Cruising with Elvis in Bigfoot's UFO?
That's right.
The Elvis, Elvis Presley, of course, is alive.
I mean, there's no question about that.
What could kill him?
Bob, Elvis.
Kennedy.
Uh, the...
Oh, they try to make it seem like partying could cure...
could kill Elvis.
I...
It's impossible.
They're all in Dobstown.
They're gambling, man.
They're having a great time.
As long as that Hydra's out there trying to take our slack away.
They cannot die.
No.
There are some...
The kings and the queens of true slackdomness shall ne'er die.
Now, Jimi Hendrix really did die.
But he was reincarnated as an entire tribe of exists.
And so we know everything's gonna be okay.
Come on, you're putting us on.
No, that's in Book of the Subgenius, man.
Haven't you been re-knowing that?
It wasn't in there when I read it.
Right.
It may not have been.
I'm sure the next time I get by, it'll be back in there.
Yeah.
That's funny.
Have you all ever noticed how your Book of the Subgenius will...
Absolutely.
Yes.
I've noticed that.
It kind of ticks me off, though, because I...
You know, I've read the thing about 14, 15 times, and I still don't know a damn thing.
Mine moves all the time.
I leave it in my chamber of excremeditation.
I go to find it.
I leave it, and it's not there.
It's gone.
And the bob's heads are on different pages each time you look.
It's, you know, there...
Upside-down print.
You know there was one in the corner here, but it's another corner now.
Different languages.
All kinds of things twisted and turned.
And, you know, sometimes I'll find it laying right next to my frap table,
and my frappy will be consumed more so than I thought it had been before.
And then I'll pick up the book, and I'll start reading it,
and the words seem to speak more clearly.
They seem to penetrate between my nostrils into that third nostril,
and I get that psychic stench, that stench where somebody's been smoking.
Oh, with that stench.
Woo!
But it sure hasn't been me, but my book's looking on that table,
looking up at me, and that man's sitting there smiling with that pop in his face,
and he's going, oh, yeah.
Woo!
And he's got bloodshot eyes.
Tell it.
Bloodshot eyes.
Woo!
Testify.