This is really amazing.
Let's get ready for the final, we hope not really the final, adventure as we put our hands on the screen and our testicles down on the mouse pad.
We want to make sure no rodents are biting down there.
And we begin now.
The subgenius hour of SWAC.
But we well know that the reason most of us are here is because of our affinity for disobedience.
Some make rules, some obey, but the rules are for the fools is what I say.
Mob?
How are you, fellas?
It's him, the anomaly.
Do we proceed?
Yes.
You're still only human.
Bob is back, and he's better than ever.
Hello there.
Flying saucer.
Flying saucers.
Now, am I crazy?
Yeah, something like that.
So I'm crazy.
Yes.
Okay.
I am crazy.
Yeah.
The saucer.
Flying saucer.
I thought I was going crazy.
Yeah, why not?
Okay.
Fuck.
It is stupid.
I mean, it's just fine.
The only big conscious quasi-real come up
You can only be a superman or a superwoman because you can sit in the choker.
And you're good at knowing the world inside the apresent bigger sentence of this lógano.
I have discovered I actuallyar Mike Byrne as a superman.
I know that you must go beyond your best supermarket here.
Hayır wish I took my pencil and pencil weapon.
And if you still care on the life of someone, and myses und, in it it mountain.
Anyways.
Incredible.
Pretty garbage.
spacecraft with living occupants, it must have been very disconcerting for them to cross millions
of miles of space only to be hit on the head with rotten oranges. The dramatic advent of such
fascinating objects as those which were first called flying saucers attracted the inevitable
attention of those individuals who let their imaginations run away with their veracity.
By 1950, some of these characters were beginning to spin their stories of fantastic conversations
with alleged space people. Some of them expanded the stories to include alleged rides in the UFOs.
Suddenly everything went black and I realized that I'd been cut off and shut off in a little tiny room where nobody was listening to me.
And I was talking to this hot little plush felt red rubber tip microphone and not hearing a thing and seeing only little tiny lights
and wondering why I was
strapped to this chair and put into the studio that seemed to be rotating very rapidly with lights flashing off rhythmically.
And it was a small man with a swollen head and hideously deformed eyes sitting behind the console pushing the buttons
while pencils of light and energy flashed across my body. And I wondered why I was there and what did they want of me?
And I couldn't figure out why I was sitting there. And they didn't say anything.
They just kept flashing those lights at me and pumping those strange chemicals into me.
And the man with the funny
head, the leader, the man with a strange grin and the pipe.
Well, I just want to know, do you want to be in the church or out of the church? And where's your wallet?
The DC9 pushed the button.
Yeah.
I didn't know that I'd been snatched up, but it wasn't really a dream until I saw these sacred nasal positions.
And suddenly it all came back to me. And I realized that they'd stolen four and a half hours out of my life when they put me in that tiny room and plugged all those wires into me
and made me talk.
Well, it's only an hour and a half tonight, mister.
And talk, and talk.
Stop.
My mind is going.
Hahahaha
Well, gentlemen.
The dream has come true.
Hmm.
And not just for republicans.
So qui...
The first is going, now it's goin, go go go.
We will control the most powerful bomb in the universe.
Zadar, your god, gave you the gift of the god.
The god is good.
The god, the god.
Penises is evil.
The penises is evil.
It appears as though something has happened in the motorcade route.
Something, I repeat, has happened in the motorcade route.
There's one thing.
There's a lot of people running up the hill alongside us.
That's why we're coming freeway.
Several police officers are rushing up the hill at this time.
Stand by.
Just a moment, please.
There's a gun.
A line has been hit by the gunfire.
A presidential car coming up now.
We know it's a presidential car.
You see, this is Kennedy's pink suit.
There's a Secret Service man.
Now, truth or lie, who hears that soldier cry?
He was a hero of the war.
But no one comes near.
He sheds a lonely tear.
And wonders what it all was for.
And where are the roads?
To freedom.
Where is the life that's far than you?
Where is the love?
Where is the joy?
Tell me.
Where are the roads to freedom?
Where is the life that's far than you?
Is it the mend that's far from you?
Are the roads that go either way?
Are the roads that drive you to your nikki moves?
Are the roads that tear you away who knows?
Where to find the causes?
Where to hide?
farther than you
Where is the love
Where is the joy
And tell me
Where are the roads
to freedom
On July 5th, 1998
7 a.m.
When we all have hangovers
Wotan's judgment
will take place in the form of what the
prescriptures call the advent
of the angelic host
Total collapse of world civilization
July 5th, 1998
at 7 a.m. to be exact
the men from Planet X
as the news media will call them
will arrive to rupture
the subgeniuses
the true believer subgeniuses
up into the escape vessels
of the sex goddesses
to carry a few picked survivors
of our doomed civilization
to a new life on another world
It's Let's Have a Party
Let's Have a Party
Is it time for that big operation?
Some of you believe as I believe
Some of you do not
But those of you that do know
we are nearing the end of our struggle
The prophecy will be fulfilled soon
But before it can be
The oracle must be consulted
Bob
Saski
Was I in a good picture around here?
Was I on my colleague's benches?
Was I on the really good pit which background
We know that when things stand still
there's alwayss emotion
Doesn't matter when everything is all in about
just in the fast me
Thoughts mean nothing
All that they can say
You should still turn up
My are in outreach
To the city game
or are we just like psychoself focusing on our psychoself focus?
I'm trying to be here.
It's hard, isn't it?
It is.
It is hard to truly be here now because I keep being elsewhere then.
Well, you could ask our listless audience.
It's hard to be anywhere at any time.
That's why we're calling them now our listless audience
rather than our listered listless audience.
We care about you, brothers and sisters.
We care.
We love you.
Access is not denied.
We want to suck your souls from your bodies
and make them work in spiritual slave camps.
We want you to have a chance to join us on the escape vessels
on that glorious day, X-Day, which is coming so very, very soon.
We want you to learn to march in step,
to learn every step to the dance.
Hark, it's the call of the alien.
The call of our trusted masters, the greys.
I want the truth.
You can't handle the truth.
Are you fooled by those aliens?
Are you fooled by the greys?
Friends, those are the wrong aliens.
You can't handle the truth.
The voice is in your head that's lying.
The voices in your head are lying.
The voice in your head are lying.
Don't follow the wrong aliens, my friends.
Don't be led astray by the greys.
What are you people?
They're whispering lies.
No.
I didn't want to know why you do what you do,
the things you do, where you've been.
You have no memory, do you?
You know most of you are gone,
frozen, calcified, and ready to be removed.
You're not really standing there.
You're listless, wishing you were elsewhere.
You can be elsewhere.
You can be in a galaxy long, long ago and far, far away
if you will just accept the fact that God is an alien.
That's right.
God, the God of the Bible, is an alien being from another world.
This is a cargo cult, and you're all cargo.
Get ready to be put in the bottom holes.
Step lively.
Oh, say can you see
During next day's long fight
The face above doves
If you stare at the sunlight
Whose bright eyes and broad grin
Train mark high at his chin
Give sub-genie slack
As we fight off the noise
Of the sun's red-haired animals
And the ray guns red glare
Melted skin, bone, and hair
When fired from high
Saucers float in air
Oh, say does dog's pipe blow
From smoke this direction
So that the sun's red glare
Shines through the sky
So that we live free as birds
Not like peak human terror
And the world goes to hell
Two months ago, the observatory issued a press statement that the world was coming to an end.
And that's the same story the cult of the book of Revelations had been preaching.
Now when a scientist backs that up, it's news.
Our conclusions have nothing to do with the cult.
Well, today we deal with Bible prophecy.
But the word of God tells us we can expect nothing but trouble and turmoil in the Middle East
Until a new world comes to us.
Until our Lord returns to be the Prince of Peace.
Bob?
It's been known for some time that the fossil record contains several very pronounced mass extinctions.
When large numbers of quite unrelated species from all kinds of habitats appear to die out during a relatively short period.
You have, say, an asteroid about 10 kilometers across impacting on the Earth at a speed of about 40 kilometers a second.
Did you hear what that was?
Did you hear what he was saying?
Is it possible that the end of the world will come in July 1999?
Perhaps in the form of an atomic holocaust?
Such a forewarning of ultimate doom could generally be dismissed out of hand.
The White House will confirm an order to use the atom bomb.
And our first target will be the initial landing place outside Los Angeles.
Those missiles have all gone off.
They pushed all the buttons.
You know what that means, don't you?
Either we fired first and they're going to try to hit what's left.
Or they fired first and we just got our missiles out of the ground in time.
Either way, we're going to get hit.
So what are we still standing around here for?
Of course, since all human life has been under the surface of Earth for 16 years, there was no actual loss of life in the sense we know it.
What you see or what you get?
What you get, what you get?
What the hell do you expect?
Richie Red Roses.
White Puppy Noses.
Mammoth Rubber Hoses.
It is more like it.
Oh!
The strange worshippers pull at their faces.
Despite himself, a strangled cry escapes Brent.
As he sees the ghastly heritage of atomic radiation.
Hey, Tony, let's have some.
Get out of here.
Get me out of here.
I mean, hell, this turn, the other cheap thing could be carried a bit too far, you know.
Hey, neighbor, let me give you some advice.
The Russians are about to pulverize us.
Give us sleep tonight.
That is, if the crazy Arabs or the right don't get us first.
And the fire will rain down from the sky.
The fire will rain down from the sky.
People die.
We must get off.
Captain, we can't do it.
You ain't going to go shooting in your courting clothes, are you?
I think not.
There's a whole galaxy going crazy.
Well, I'm up at the top.
Get us a good seat.
Wait for the show.
Yes, sir.
I'll see you outside.
All right.
Help me, help me, help me.
Help me grow.
Oh, that's beautiful.
And who can disagree?
No, no, no, don't stop.
The preceding program was brought to you by Bobface Marketing Corporation.
Mom, mom.
Everyone likes that.
Mom.
Give me slack, you freaking lunatic.
No, fucker.
I'm out of freaking slack.
But, Reverend Spang, I can't go the next day.
I don't have the money, and I don't have a job now, and it's a long way to go, and I don't know anybody, and I'd be a skunk.
I don't think I should go.
Don't worry, friends.
We're all strangers.
I don't know anybody.
I think I'm going to stay home this year.
Oh, well, if that sounds like it'd be more slackful, then you should just do that.
I want to watch TV.
Yeah.
Whatever.
Maybe that's good.
Could you come and just give us all foot massages all weekend?
I want to cut off the soles of my feet and play the foot and live in a tip-tip.
Instead, you could be sitting around Tranquility Base, sitting around a bunch of washed-up rockers.
Pinhole's.
Pinheads.
Nicotine-stained lasers.
Tie-dyed shirt.
Fly, fly, fly babies.
Another one of them banana-valium soothies.
Soothies.
Strapping tinfoil-wrapped cucumbers to their legs.
You guys got any more soothies?
I just crapped my pants again.
Rock and roll, baby.
I'm about to clean myself up.
I'm taking a nap.
That's a crack for back and roll.
But we will get on that rocket, because we are.
We're going to build our own rocket ship again this year.
We must get off.
We've done it before.
We're doing it again.
The administration says we're better.
Every year we learn more.
Off.
And we fall asleep.
We wake up.
It is a brand new sunshine day.
Mars.
Jupiter.
Neptune.
Sirius Minor.
Earth.
Mars.
The whole damn Milky Way.
You can feel my...
That which does not kill us, leaves us alive.
We're coming up.
Mass hysteria.
K.
About a third of this country didn't have an...
Mass hysteria.
Planet X.
Well, I won't say that.
Have a beautiful...
Well, now think of this one.
There's a company called...
Sss.
Mass hysteria.
Dick.
Sss.
Mass hysteria.
What would you advise?
The truth.
No one will panic.
Because there is nothing to fear.
That army will never reach the gates of Zion.
What makes you so sure?
Consider what we have seen, counselor.
Consider that in the past six months, we have freed more minds than in six years.
This attack is an act of desperation.
I believe very soon the prophecy will be fulfilled.
And this war will end.
I hope you're right, Captain.
I do not believe it to be a matter of hope, counselor.
It is simply a matter of time.
I don't.
And there he went.
When he remembers Zion.
Cause the wicked carried us away captivity.
Require from us a song.
How can we sing King Alpha's song in our slave land?
Cause the wicked carried us away captivity.
Require from us a song.
How can we sing King Alfa's song?
How can we sing King Alpha's song?
If you feel you are not properly sedated, call 348-844 immediately.
Failure to do so may result in prosecution for criminal drug evasion.
Hey, witch doctor, give us the magic words.
All right, you go ooh-ee, ooh-ah-ah, ting-tang, wah-la-wah-la, bing-bang.
All right!
Ooh-ee, ooh-ah-ah, ting-tang, wah-la-wah-la, bing-bang.
That's right, Mr. Walter Bing-Bang of Sun City, New York.
This is your time and this is your life, so stand in front of campus cameras.
Those cute aliens are coming!
Some of them have more genitals!
Than anything!
One-eyed, one-horny, six-god is on his way, baby.
And that's more than one horn per genitalia.
That is more than one alien per star system.
And that's more, more, more than you can say.
So I hear there's going to be some real Dr. Rock going on at X-Tag.
Bob is a sex god and his overman assistant, Dr. Philodrum,
and he's going to be there.
There'll be a lot of surgery going on.
With his saxophone.
With his modest saxophone, he's going to be...
Does he honk the booper?
Does he really?
Does he carry it?
Oh, yeah, honk.
No, we're making it up.
Dr. Drummond carries the virus of the song that refused to die.
And this is Ray Stevens, witch doctor.
We're learning...
Oh.
We're learning how to party from the experts.
We are learning from the guru of parties himself, Mr. Maximilian Smels.
And Maximilian, could you step closer?
I can smell your pubic goatee burning.
Oh, I smell fun.
I smell noise.
Oh, your sunglasses are dripping.
I smell love and slack adjoining.
You are smelling the juices of the rampant Euros.
And oozing and squirting.
Yes, you have to be very careful now.
Don't get too close to them.
Some of them are rampant stage.
Why not?
It's love.
Love, love, love.
Yes, love is cannibalism to some.
Love is slack for those who squirt and ooze.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Everybody has a stake in this.
Can't get in.
That's the security...
The security...
I think it's Dwight.
I think he's stuck.
Can't get in.
He can't get in.
Man, that's a philosophical statement.
He's lost on Mars.
What's that other creature's name over there?
O-Ring.
The O-Ring.
Ah, he's always burning out.
He doesn't have enough lubricant, I think.
Yes, I think he is.
That's the thing, yes.
That can easily be fixed.
Come over here, Mr. Redden.
$30.
Ladies and gentlemen,
a former spokesman of the railroad movement,
Mr. Ove Redden-Pecker.
Life is tough.
Here on Earth.
I was a conductor in 1958.
Five bucks a second to live on Earth.
You should take the Penn Star and the New York Special
all the way to Grand Central Station.
Sometimes you take the Humminbird all the way down to Norwich.
Ragnarok.
Them were the days.
But them days are coming to an end.
Put a pair of rocks in the back of your pants.
Trains about to...
Give yourself your own feeling of freedom.
Leave the station, friends.
And the trains leaving the station
and the tanks are rolling in.
Don't bother waving goodbye.
They're never coming back.
Just turn around the other way.
You done missed it, buddy boy.
Or buddy girl.
No way to go now but up
or down.
Down.
Or in and out as many times as that sound in your head will permit.
That's what we're gonna do while we're going up.
Up to meet the saucers and the angelic host.
And as we become more adult,
we learn the lessons.
Do not commit adultery with an adult tree.
Thou shalt not stand in the rain upside down
for like a turkey you will drown.
Do not carry your pants.
Wear them proudly.
And if you will live by these laws, my friend.
If you will live by this.
You will make Dogstown.
Oh yeah.
You'll make the new Jerusalem.
We're gonna build it from the ground up, brethren and sesterins.
Sisterin and ins.
We're gonna build it on each other's backs.
We're gonna make it out of slabs of concrete and steel and little teeny toothpicks.
We're gonna build a world where everyone's free and most people are confused or sleep in three quarters of the day.
We are gonna use time control to go back to the beginning of the universe and rebuild it from scratch, baby.
I listen to the psychedelic sounds issuing from therein.
Um, no, that's not, it's not important what I do.
The important thing is what we're told even in, in scripture that it says, uh, in, in Hebrews 10 36, it says,
I'm kind of, um, um, no.
So it's like you're a reader.
And you're leaving it.
Talk about doctors.
Well, God was the first doctor.
He filled out the script.
It's called the scriptures.
And then he burned them up and he wiped his toilet with them and went all off into the cause.
Both singing a happy song.
That was called the hypocritical oath.
It said that God could cure you while killing you.
He made you laugh.
He tickled your funny bone, but he wasn't about to amputate anything.
He didn't grow on you himself.
And he's still in business.
That's the important part.
And so are you his patients.
After all those years,
that sheepskin and the dead sheep are still hanging on the wall.
You paid for it, lay back and spread it.
Might as well enjoy it.
God's just like the weather, honey.
Who knows?
Maybe you'll be the mother of the new Bob.
And you never know how many inches you're going to get.
Oh, uh, could you please read the following thing?
I've just handed to here by Homestead Secure, Homeland Security, part two, the Patriotism Act.
We have a little notice to read the piece you just read.
As J.R. Bob Dog said, just because we must destroy the conspiracy to save the world,
that doesn't mean we have to save the conspiracy to destroy the world.
What?
You're a major mouth fucker, nut nut.
Every day is X day when you have a gun.
What a juicy, juicy brain he has.
I have a feeling, you know, just like feeling sad all day long.
Yeah?
And you know, I just get kind of sick from going out and acting like everything is okay.
Everything is okay, okay, okay, okay.
All the boys and gankers, our ship is coming in.
And it's got two big huge out in water, boat mortis.
The arisal is of the fifth day of the seventh month of the year of the number of the beast tripled.
Let he who has wisdom calculate the number of the day of the arisal.
For on this day shall the first seal bark and juggle, and there shall be a battle of
merchants like unto a great auction.
And the servants of the one bog shall do battle with the servants of the other bog, which
shall their army greet.
The angelic host, by that shall the angelic host judge the price of the earth.
And so shall the opening, the opening of that seal shall smell like so many fishes, and
shall reek of sardines.
And the sardines shall be the sardines of the seven seals.
David Koresh knew of the seventh seal, and look what they did to him.
They barbecued him.
Texas style.
From now on, there's no white, there's no black.
Everybody's green.
Let's hear it for the seventh seal, the very best seal in the program.
He's balanced all his balls.
Everyone shall be green.
The sky will be like sackcloth, and the oceans will be white like the spilt seed of the sloppy
winepress of the second century.
The sardines shall be green.
Here's a good example of that.
We won't say anything of the last ten days of the making, but we will say, they're
My ears are burning, and I'm dripping chlorophyll.
If I could just get in my car.
I'm trying to get a hold of Mr. Doff.
The fires of hell are licking at you.
That's what you feel.
It's the fires of hell, but there's a way, there's a way into the ice water of slack.
Out of them fires of your job, hell, your thirty days per month.
It is not a fire of hell.
sentenced to hard labor.
And for what?
You call that slack?
That's nothing but rent.
For a few miserable kopecks,
you have slaved and slathered
your entire lives away.
There is a way out.
We're 17 men on an alien world.
It's up to us whether we ever get home again.
A sea of drizzling, babbling humanity
standing in front of the Tsar's palace
waving their one finger skyward
and not a chicken bone to eat.
And how are they any different from you?
Only one way.
They spent that $30, my friend.
They showed their faith in God.
900 rubles at the time.
They proved they're ready to board
them escape vessels of the sex goddesses
from planet X.
And as they boarded the vessels,
they thought they were taking the battleship Potamkin
and they could feel themselves steaming
like a giant steamer or two
into St. Petersburg Harbor.
The lovely Orifice was awaiting them.
The young partons were so full of vigor and fervor
and gosses.
I can't think of the form of psychosis.
It's a form of...
I...
You might make me fall off the hairs.
Time is running out.
It is later than you think.
Head down to your Tennessee mountain home.
I'm moving there with him.
Home country.
That's right.
Your Tennessee mountain slack.
Swamp the hogs.
I remember swamping the hogs
when I was a little tiny pea button of a baby.
We used to take them down to the river
and flesh them up real good
and put lathering soap on them.
Squirt behind their ears.
That's an errant...
That's a false memory, Dave.
You grew up in Ashtabula
underneath the nuclear stacks.
But that didn't keep Dave from loving a hog.
No, there's no damn titanium plant
or plutonium plant
that can stop you from the good love
of a child.
Calling your name...
Well, in Texas we have power plants
that overlook our lovely cattle ranches.
And oh, the many head of cattle.
Many head...
Many headed cattle.
In some cases.
And you know the farmers grow giant out there.
They're very big.
And they're headed for trouble, too.
90, 90, 90...
Bald headed and they go mad.
And they tear up the power lines, friends.
And this, too, can be your joy or your terror.
And your future.
X day.
Coming up July 5th, 1999.
1998.
That might be this year.
One thing for sure,
a bald headed giant is on your horizon.
And it ain't Mr. Clean this time.
No, sir, man.
He's gonna rip your earrings right out of your head.
This bald headed giant?
They call him...
Not...
No?
Not Paul Bunyan?
Not Abraham Lincoln?
No, no, no.
But Dr. Katahdin Lagoon.
Katahdin Lagoon.
The bald headed giant of level 17.
Four foot thick,
ten centimeters tall in every direction,
with a mind like a giant.
He's like a glistening oaf.
He's a man who can preach the truth
and lie to you at the same time.
Oh, God, he's been living around these parts for so long,
we can't even remember who or how or what or why.
We went to see him sometimes,
let the kids hang around by the back door.
Sometimes he'll come out and make a pronouncement.
Other times he'll just sleep in the sun.
That's him in the background playing that harmonica.
Yeah, he's sleeping, too.
That's amazing.
Now they can do that.
That's the way he snores.
Yep.
Just stick it under his nose.
Let him try out.
Let him bloat.
It slides back and forth magically.
Friend Slack is waiting for you on the front porch,
old grandpa dog.
He's got that corncob pipe all packed up
and that porch swing going.
That's all we're going to do.
A little sack of water hanging there.
Just going to sit on the front porch,
tea bays.
Are you going to put your old man in rocking chairs?
Whittling.
Picking and riddling.
Got to do that on that mandolin.
I got my whittling.
I haven't done my potato bag.
Oh, yeah.
I got the proper whittling.
I'm going to play a full-blooded sow mandolin
just like the sow I left 25 years ago.
Wow.
Full-blooded?
Full-blooded.
Rich and moist, too.
Wow.
I like that disease thing there on your hand.
What is that?
That's my pipe.
Oh, yeah.
Prepare yourself.
It's not Jane intentar a
guarantee as to the
worst things that can happen to
Please gotta get out
the U Pol and the U U blocks.
We don't care about any modified
coasts.
way I look with awe and wonder at Bob's hard new rock.
Do you think of men who kept on Bob's rock when you stroll along a rock?
Do you think of Bob with awe and wonder?
Does the word Bob make you stare in disbelief when you see Bob?
I'm roaring in from the bright Nevada sky.
You hail Bob from the Rio Grande to me.
My heart runs fast.
You ask me why I love Bob?
I have a million reasons why.
My beautiful Bob beneath Bob's wide, wide sky.
And Bob loves Bob to shining stars.
Bob!
The sermon tonight is entitled,
The Last Chance.
Yes, friends, 1998 is fast approaching.
And a lot of people out there have come to expect the church to start singing a different tune about the Judgment Day.
They say, hey, did you hear the news?
The Berlin Wall has fallen.
Things are getting better.
We say, is that so?
They say, hey, did you read the paper?
The Russians are now our friends.
Things are getting better.
We say, is that so?
They say, hey, did you see it on CNN?
We won the war.
Things are getting better.
Is that so?
And now they come a-running and a-cheerin', saying, roll out the barrel.
We now have a new president.
The Republicans are out.
The recession is over.
It's the year of the woman.
Everybody get naked.
You poor, pitiful little pinks.
Do you really think an eternity of sin can be erased so easily?
Are we now supposed to embrace the conspiracy and call off the exodus invasion?
Do you actually believe?
You can defuse an entire revolution with a few scraps of conspiracy compromise?
Never.
These petty little sidelines that have a nice day news don't divert our attention from the real issue.
Not for a second.
Dateline, Washington.
New conspiracy president sworn into office.
Promises new conspiracy health care plan to keep worker drones healthy and make more capable of serving the state.
More to follow.
Dateline, New York.
U.N. meets for conspiracy roll call.
Vote of conspiracy agenda for global conspiracy world domination.
Renegade nations refusing to conform to new world order will be penalized.
More to follow.
Dateline, planet Earth.
Conspiracy in last ditch effort to avert bloody overthrow.
Attempts to utilize all arms of conspiracy propaganda machine to convince subgenius rebel rousers.
World is now A-OK.
A member from conspiracy high command states, quote,
Conspiracy no longer.
Hostile.
Conspiracy now friend of little guy, end quote.
Well, well, well, the world is getting better.
We should just call off the invasion before it's too late.
Wrong.
You can fool some of the subgenies some of the time, but you can't fool any of the overmen any other time.
They're much too in tune to the wily ways of the wicked one.
I'm talking about you, Mr. Pete boy.
Yes, you.
The one with the firm handshake and the easy smile.
You're not tricking anyone with your bold new mind.
Vision or JFK idealism.
We in the church go by one credo.
Ask not what the conspiracy can do to you, but what you can do to the conspiracy.
And come July 5th, 1998, we're going to put that moto into simultaneous global orchestration.
We're overthrowing the conspiracy and we're executing the ringleaders along with anyone else who tries to stop us.
Now, just some.
This may seem a little extreme.
That's perfectly normal to the average man in the street.
Witness in a public execution of a criminal may also appear extreme.
After all, chances are that the man is unfamiliar with the crimes of the criminal.
He was too busy making a living to notice what misdeeds the condemned perpetrated on society before being brought to justice.
Add to that the criminal's emotional last words, his pleas for mercy, his insistence of his own innocence, and his reciting of all the good deeds he has done.
He's a man of great value, and he's a man of great value.
Then imagine the prisoner's family stepping forth, begging for his life, and witnesses filing forward to testify to the innocence of this great man so wrongly accused.
It should be no surprise that even an intelligent but uninformed person would find themselves feeling sorry for the poor soul and wishing him a pardon.
If respected newspapers were produced and showed article after article supporting the accused,
even the most skeptical in the crowd would likely become the most skeptical.
Why?
Because they would see in that individual before them not a criminal guilty of crimes against humanity,
but themselves falsely accused and condemned to death for crimes they never committed.
By now, the executioner should be more worried about their lives than the prisoner should his.
The crowd might well demand clemency, and if refused, storm the guards and free the prisoner by force.
If you were part of this interview,
you would probably feel proud for the good deed you performed and the terrible injustice you averted.
But if a few weeks later you learned that the prisoner you saved was an insane serial killer,
that the witnesses that testified were all paid actors,
and that the newspapers you believed were all frauds,
you might start to regret having been so compassionate.
Then by some quirk of fate, if you stumbled onto incontrovertible evidence,
that the man you freed had devoted his life to destroying yours,
that his new obsession was to capture you, torture you, and sell your loved ones into slavery,
well, you'd probably start to feel anger.
Anger at yourself for being fooled.
Anger at the actors who tricked you and the newspapers that lied to you.
And anger at all the mental dweebs still running around out there claiming the bastard is really Reforged.
Grim Accused, Cheat.
That's your problem.
But if you believed what you werealdoing about,
Remember the beginning, change, and change.
We are criminals now!
But from a Buddhist perspective,
er достаточно duchery in thelais erat a comportement
that, in some circumstances,
torture us, and enslave our kind.
And every single time we get close to destroying the monster,
some well-meaning but ignorant bystander starts whining that we're being too severe, too extreme.
They say that the conspiracy is actually innocent.
They say they know because they read all about it in the conspiracy newspapers
or saw it all explained to them on conspiracy TV.
They insist that our allegations are exaggerated,
that the conspiracy is getting better, and that we should just mellow out.
They try to tell us that we ought to give the conspiracy slack.
Dear, dear friends, these poor misguided morons may be in the dark now,
just as we were before.
And we may have acted back then just as stupid as they're acting now.
But that doesn't mean we don't have the right,
nay the duty, to destroy the conspiracy while we have the chance.
Do not be taken in by any last-minute media blitz
that tries to convince you that the conspiracy has suddenly turned over a new leaf.
Because it hasn't.
The noose is around its neck.
What do you expect the conspiracy to say?
We deserve to die? Kill us?
No.
The conspiracy will look and act nicer now,
than it ever has before.
So don't be fooled.
If you hesitate, even for a second,
you give the conspiracy a chance to win the crowd over.
And if that happens, you may find yourself on trial,
with no more X's around to pull your fat from the firing squad.
There's only one X day, dear friends.
Don't blow it.
July 5th, 1998, kill the conspiracy.
Cut off its head,
and lock it up.
Launch it through the cosmos.
Here into the world of our praise, Bob.
Amen!
hire a
project
was finished
launch
i was
alive
We take a moment and we pause to reflect on the pinks that we killed and the planet that they wrecked.
And we laugh like banshees and howl like comanches.
We're victory dance in our underoos and panties.
Our fantasy is a reality.
Earth turns to dust.
Planet X are us for us.
As Bob's pipe splits, space and time shift.
A temporal disturbance.
The constant of splatters.
We lost him.
A dimensional split.
Severus forever.
Subgenite from pink shit.
Bob walked in a circle.
And steadily exhaled in the smoke.
I can see why the pink boys fail.
The pain in AIDS has caused destruction.
Sick and full of slack with suction.
Pay-per-view alien abduction.
Functioning on so much slack.
The money should be painted black.
The leak from space that stole your balls.
Will soon come back and take it all.
Return to slack.
Return to bars.
Repent slack off and quit your jobs.
The world of the beast and the mob.
Conquering.
Lick the throbbing vein of slavery.
Now you're sleeping like a baby.
For the Bob will be up to the keeping of the dogs.
The guy who's been talking with the UFO in his garage.
And cut my finger on a soup can lid.
I got an infection and it spread to my dick.
It swelled up to the size of a human head.
And then a mouth opened on it.
And this is what it said.
It said to kill the pink boys.
But your job.
Mock the world and worship Bob Dogg.
We'll build a ship and take a trip.
Come on and get it.
I can write the coordinates.
Three and a half months in my garage.
Tearing parts off of old used cars.
My grind at this point was unusually large.
It would occasionally hum while smoking a cigar.
Our project was finished.
The ship on hull 20.
The power source was like anything you could think was funny.
Everything is slackless.
They're atlas.
Our birth proof is worth it.
Escaping a stark fix.
On our way to planet extra sex.
Direct sex.
Buries with Harry Potter money shell.
Iconic walk.
It's an all-haas hour of bonanza.
It's like a world without Tony Fanzo.
Our fans are the mean shit that hits the charts.
In a world of dead hearts, I'm a leader in slobotomy and sodomy.
We take a moment to be positive.
We wreck all the pink stuff we build in the planet that they wreck.
We laugh like banshees and howl like the banshees.
We're victory-handed in our under-user canyons.
Our fantasy is a reality.
Earth hurts the dust.
Planet X are crushed for us.
Depress the eddy blood that flows in your veins.
Let the froth-pot-pot bring slack like rain.
Let Bob control what's left of your brain.
Oh yeah, send all your money to the Reverend Island stand.
Mother's-style quantum physicists.
Oh, oh.
Just resentful.
Say hello to quantum physicists.
Oh, oh.
Nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah.
It's looking for us.
It's an eyeball.
It's looking for an answer.
That's how the aliens see us.
Well, you want some aliens to see you if you're right with them.
If you've, if you've, uh, paid dues.
Get wrapped with the aliens.
If you've done your incantation.
It's looking for us.
If you've sacrificed your chickens and children.
Bob is looking for you.
And more importantly, Connie will be looking for you on July 5th.
Oh yeah, yeah.
At Brushwood.
Bob and Connie.
Right.
It seems to say can.
This is, we, we really look for answers.
Right.
Yes, so this is Rise.
The erste che!
No, this is Ross alone.
This is Ross alone.
This is really the last chance!
This is Ross, with him, and Vanessa both living in the same apartment for one month.
Come on down you saucer man and take me off to space
Take me off to space, take me off to space
Hey cow mutilators, let me join your crew
Give me a knife, you bet your life I'll cut up cows for you
I don't care if you're some kind of ghastly beast without a face
So come on down you saucer man and take me off to space
Take me off to space, take me off to space
Go on down you saucer man and take me off to space
Come down you tiny robot with your little nipper claws
You pale and bug eyed alien
like a exhibit If you.
With wide and clammy paws
Life is just a sucker's dream
And death is a disgrace
So come on down, you saucer man
And take me off to space
Take me off to space
Come on down, you saucer man
And take me off to space
Take me off to space
Come on down, you saucer man
And take me off to space
It's disgusting the way we treat humans.
I'm doing great.
Okay, great.
Doing great.
Ah!
I think Bob is just a guy with a pipe.
Oh, that's crazy talk.
I have the gray hand.
I got the puppy stick.
We have the gray hand.
The crop circles promise to lead us the way home.
The pipe of Bob dolls is waiting for us.
The escape vessels of the sex goddess is coming.
I paid $30 to fly into space.
My father had told me not to go off to X-Day.
So I took cash from his wallet and was on my way.
My brothers and sisters, they said it's all a sex cult.
They tried to stop me, but I killed them all dead.
Yee-haw!
Goodbye to the con.
Hello, margaritas.
Adios to your old friends.
Here's a better idea.
You won't have a name when you show up.
You'll be Bob's ex-boyfriend.
And all they will call you will be...
That's right.
Be Bobby.
To the tune of Deportage.
Some of us are smelly and some are not wanted.
Who he has told us we have to move on.
Mission to T-Base just to meet all our heroes.
But the game's got a really big knife and a gun.
Woo-ha!
All the bones are broken for two.
We're crushed and we're all out of fire.
We're crushed and some scary old men they call Mojo.
But we just want to hang with the ones we admire.
Everybody now.
Goodbye to the con.
Hello, margaritas.
Adios to your old friends.
Here's a better idea.
You won't have a name when you show up.
And all they will call you will be...
Bobby.
Be Bobby.
Bobby, Bobby.
Hey, Bobby.
Hey.
¿Están muertos?
No, no.
Solamente inhibidos.
Ja, ja, ja.
Set them on fire.
They're going to laugh at us.
Bobby!
Watch out for the migra, man.
If they catch you near the base, they're going to send you back.
Watch out for those people with blue teeth and vibrating hair, man.
They don't care what they say about you.
They're going to make you disappear.
Watch out for those people with blue teeth.
We're federalists.
You can't wash them.
We have badges.
You want to see our badges?
Show us your badges.
We're federalists.
We have badges.
We don't have no stinking badges.
We don't need no stinking badges.
Show us your diapers if you're federalists.
We don't need no stinking pipes.
We need stinking Lisa Vita.
Lisa on May 23rd.
Show me your barbecue sandwiches if you're the migra.
And all they will call you will be
the Bobby.
How can I go to that fabulous event called X-Day at Brushwood in western New York?
Would I get onto the internet and check out
www.subgenius.com?
That might work.
Take a plane.
Take a train.
And take a flying saucer to Brushwood, dear friends.
Brushwood, Sherman, New York, July 5th, this year.
And this is the first of four 6X-Day shows, friends.
And you've been hearing collages and channelings by, of course, Fernanda Nande-Liemer and Artemia Salina,
two great sound editors from Alt Binary.
And, of course, the famous
I'm talking right now.
ESO Swamp Radio from WCSB Cleveland with Chaz Smith, Lonesome Cowboy Dave, Princess Fiardo,
and your strong host, Gordon Gordon.
And you've been hearing collages and channelings by, of course, Fernanda Nande-Liemer and Artemia Salina,
Papa Joe Mama who ranted there,
that fine, long, seven-minute rant.
The great Papa Joe Mama,
ultimate X-Day spokesman.
We heard lots of bits from old subgenius media barrages,
from Gary Gabrog, Frank,
from Reverend Jarto.
Yes, Jarto did some sound editing this time.
Praise Jarto.
The Matrix downloaded.
El Queso All-Stars did Planet X or Bust.
And Nenslo,
did the great song, Take Me Off to Space.
Friends, next we'll be hearing a little bit from the Euro subs,
who will be back next week on this show,
the Hour of Slack from the Church of the Subgenius.
Once again, that's www.subgenius.com
or post office box 204-206-Austin, Texas 78720.
And we'll see you next time.
We'll see you in the nude Jerusalem,
if you can spell subgenius.com.
What have you been doing?
You've been drinking whiskey for Bob.
Yeah, I've been drinking whiskey for Bob.
I've been preaching for Bob.
It's the only two things that I care about.
Did Bob deliver the whiskey?
No.
I bought the whiskey, but I bought it with Bob's money.
Yeah.
I didn't have any money in my wallet.
I thought, I want some whiskey.
And I went into an off-license,
and I looked at the whiskey,
and I went, oh, I don't have any money.
And I found, I found the money to buy the whiskey in my wallet.
I didn't know it was there.
So I bought the whiskey, and I drank the whiskey.
Drank the whiskey, man.
Amen.
It happened.
Somehow it just...
I've got to pay some money here.
The transubstantiation has come down to this.
There's...
No.
50 pence.
36 pence.
Yeah.
What are you doing, Mr. Svita?
I'm finished, just buying as usual.
You are trying to...
Yeah, I'm slacking.
You're slack.
Slack is the primal substance.
It's the fifth essence.
It's the quinto elemento.
It's slack.
Praise Bob.
Bob loves you.
I could...
He'll never love you as much as Bob.
I am feminizing...
I can't move without going down.
Bob takes care of his own.
Yes.
We will take care of our own, darling.
He doesn't leave the detritus of Bob Dobbs town to other people.
He takes care of his own.
The rantings of a madman.
Stop and go.
He's met the zenith point.
He's at the apex between plus and minus.
Yes.
He's...
He's on the edge.
He's moving and standing still.
He wants to stop and go.
Yeah.
Yes.
He is a true subgenius.
And there goes the torch parade.
What sort of goings on is that anyway?
Some sort of rites for the temple of vampires.
Jack, you mean to sit there and say all that gang was vampires?
How do I know?
At least they seem to be priests of the temple.
Yeah.
Rogues and torches and stuff.
I'm not a priest.