Around Dard City and in the Territory on West, there's just one way to handle the killers and the spoilers, and that's with a U.S. Marshal and the spell of...
The Subgenius Power of Squash!
From PR News in Washington, I'm scheduled for January.
No one's claiming responsibility.
No one is expanding.
No one was attacked in the middle of a procession.
No one's been arrested.
No one found it suspicious.
No one is stepping down.
No one needs to focus more.
No one suspects Islamist militants.
No one is washing ashore on Florida's Atlantic coast.
No one's blaming the weather.
No one is scheduled for January.
On Wall Street 213-672-327-6315-16.
The turtles are blaming PR.
More news.
bye bye
Awesome!
Thank you.
That lively instrumental was made by the Rudy Schwartz Project
on the album entitled Take Me in Your Arms and Sing to Me Like Dick Powell.
And thanks to Mr. Fernandinendi Lemur
for the song.
For the first two minutes before that.
But this is Hour of Slack number 1760
and much of it was recorded on July 4th of the so-called 2019
on location of the cult compound
where the technically 24th annual Ex Day Drill was held.
Dr. Howell, Dr. Philo Drummond, and yours truly,
Reverend Ivan Stang, presiding.
Along with Reverend Lord Angry Larry.
I've got a question, Dr. Howell.
May I share one question?
Yeah, sure.
I'm Reverend What the Fog, and you were mentioning the chick...
Oh, Reverend What the Fog. Okay.
Yes, thank you for pronouncing it correctly.
You were mentioning the chick pamphlets.
Chick tracks.
The chick tracks.
Were you familiar with the Luciferians?
Oh, yeah.
They're wonderful parodies.
They have disappeared from the web.
I have a...
I have a copy of only one of theirs.
Yeah.
Does someone know of some source where they can be found still?
I don't know, but the thing is the Luciferians were at two...
The first two Ex Day Drills in 98.
They were here in 98.
They were like policing the place.
Wow.
They were definitely on the Holocaustal team.
And there was nobody...
They were literally hog-tying evangelicals
during the Battle of Armageddon
because they were both military.
They were military guys.
As is right and good.
Like, they were serious...
What would you call them?
Devil worshippers.
The SWAT team of the military.
They were like some kind of elite...
The Rangers.
Elite secret guys.
And they were Luciferians.
And they had a hell of a rant.
It was a white guy and a black guy.
And they both...
They both ranted like a sumbitch.
And I have too have wondered...
What happened to them?
Did they ascend to hell?
Or, you know...
Ascend is the wrong word.
Or get sent to Iraq.
Well, there are all kinds of lame parodies
that are available, but none so spot on
as those anti-chick tracks.
Well, I'm sorry you like theirs
better than those created by some of us.
Do you remember that one?
That recording by R.T. Calhoun
about the Luciferian conspiracy?
Do you remember that one?
R.T.
R.T. Calhoun.
He talked real slow.
And I'm going to bring to you
the story of the Luciferian conspiracy.
And it was about...
Had a whole lot to do with homosexuality.
Remember that one?
As always.
And that...
Are you talking about a radio preacher?
Yeah.
No, it was a tape that we got from...
When we were getting all those crazy tapes.
He's the guy who had the fake apocalypse
several years ago.
Oh, okay. Right, right.
His name was R.T. Calhoun.
R.T. Farty.
I wonder if I have a copy of that.
According to the
Jack Chick ethos,
you have to evangelize.
You have to share, as they say,
the good news that Jesus,
who created hell, has created a loophole
so you might get out of it.
But
they have actually a tract,
and you may have seen it, where a woman
leads a perfect Christian life
and she dies and
they say, well, now you've been a good Christian.
Welcome to heaven.
You're a good and faithful servant.
You mean I'll have a giant mansion in heaven?
Well, it won't exactly be a mansion.
It's here on the outskirts.
And she comes, but this has no windows.
This is like a garage.
I'm supposed to be in here forever in heaven?
I'm glad to be in heaven.
Well, you see, you didn't witness to our Lord and Savior.
So you didn't bring more people in.
So this is your heavenly mansion for all time.
This garage in heaven's suburbs across the tracks.
Not in a good area.
Right next to the liquor store.
Yeah.
Because that guy was good too, but, well, you know.
The liquor isn't anything to shout about.
It's not the fiery stuff they sell in hell.
If heaven is guilt, no sex and no show,
then I'm not sure if I really want to go.
Oh.
The wages of sin
The price that you pay
Is worrying and fretting
Every second of the day
The church and the state
You've got in country kind
One gets your body
The other gets your mind
Mary, Mary Magdalene
How about a date?
You've been wasting your time
Staying up so late
Your boyfriend's dead
The word is you're a whore
Just about then
I heard a knock on the door
And I realized then
That the wages of sin
Was a bad reputation
And too many friends
The wages of sin
Thank you.
That was Reverend Lord Angry Larry's newish band, The Slutrods, from the album Surf and Clue.
A ditty,
called Dad's Rail Job.
Before that, an excerpt from Wages of Sin by The Rainmakers.
Reverend Angry Larry is the guitar virtuoso behind the legendary Detroit surf punk doctor band,
The Amino Acids, and many other bands.
And he's a hot rod mechanic, and he's such a bull goose nerd,
that he's a horror host on
Detroit TV, and runs the famous Reardsville Records used albums, bulldada, and kitsch store
in Mount Clemens, Michigan, just north of Detroit,
which is the only retail outlet in the entire world that sells authorized subgenius membership packs.
He's also a motion picture special effects and makeup artist.
As such,
Quite an experienced artist.
And he's a man of his word.
He's got a lifetime to live in fear, isn't it?
That's what he needs to be a slave.
Anyway, Reverend Angry Larry is surely one of America's leading experts on the greatest of the worst movies ever made.
I always said this about Ed Wood.
People can say what they want about him, I thought Ed Wood did great movies.
Well, we're still quoting him.
Exactly.
Everybody thinks he was the worst director and everything else.
No, he wasn't.
I was looking at it like, if that guy wanted to make a movie, he found a way to make a movie.
He got the money together, and that guy made movies.
I used to do that.
There's lots of other movies out there that are crap.
Like Manos, Hands of Fate.
Which, of course, means hands, hands of fate.
Right.
Well, you showed your own worsened version of Manos a couple of years ago.
Yep.
Did you know they want to make a new Manos?
I heard that.
But it's going to be a comedy.
The little girl that's in that movie actually is Manos.
The guy who plays Manos, that was his daughter.
She cried when they watched the movie because only three people voiced all of it.
Because they didn't have money to have sound.
Right.
So an adult actually did the voice of the little girl.
Oh.
And so she wants to make it.
And the dude who played Manos is still alive.
And yeah, they want to make a movie.
They want to make Manos 2.
Well, they're going to hire Larry Blamire to direct.
Yeah.
Hey.
Huh.
You know, you can't set out to make a bad film.
You have to make the best film you can.
And it's probably going to turn out bad.
I've seen a movie that they tried to make bad and it was bad.
They're always bad.
Not in a good, bad way.
It was like you're trying way too hard.
No.
Yeah.
That doesn't work.
Watch Plan 9 from Outer Space.
That's a good, bad movie.
Teenagers from Outer Space.
It's true.
Which is the amino acid film.
Really?
That is the go-to film that the aminos.
They have the skeleton ray.
Yes.
Yeah.
And the giant crawfish.
The disintegrator ray.
The focusing disintegrator ray, which the aminos took.
Oh, right.
Of course.
Which was a, what was the company?
I want to say Dinky, but it wasn't.
Cuomo.
No.
They made cap guns and stuff like that.
Well, you don't want an unfocused disintegrator ray.
It'll disintegrate even the disintegrator.
Yeah.
What do you know?
And then they've got the-
It disintegrated.
Giant mountain-sized transparent crawdad.
Disintegrated.
Yeah.
Daffy Duck.
In Duck Dodgers in the 24th and a half century when he, I'll shoot you with my disintegrator
ray, and he did this and it disintegrated.
He goes, what do you know?
It disintegrated.
Yeah.
All right.
Well, that has Planet X in it.
Yes.
Yes, it does.
Yeah.
It's the only source of shaving cream, Adam.
And it's easy to get there.
You just follow the planets.
A through, you know.
Yeah.
As Porky Pig points out.
Interesting thing that years ago, Tweety Bird was actually just supposed to be a baby.
An embryo.
I always assumed Tweety was a chick.
Was supposed to be, yeah.
He was supposed to be a baby.
Uh-huh.
And he was originally pink and the sensors didn't like it.
Right.
They made them change him to yellow.
But they also said he, you've, oh, what was it?
Was it, someone had to wear pants.
Well.
Well, Porky.
No, but Porky Pig never wore pants.
No.
It always bothered me.
All right.
You think that, but it's not true because I've got all the early Porky Pig cartoons
and several of them, he appears to have no pants.
Then he puts his hand in his pocket.
He pulls out a wallet.
That's one of those odd things that certain pigs can do.
Hollywood pigs can do that.
Right.
Well, there'd be a dog like Pluto who acts like a dog and then a dog like Goofy who is
anthropomorphic.
Who owns Pluto.
Pluto doesn't get to talk, but he can hold up a sign.
Right.
And where do they come from with his thoughts and feelings.
Yeah.
But he got a planet named after him or a dwarf planet named after him.
So there you go.
Yeah.
There's some.
I think that's a little bit of logic in some of those.
Donald Duck didn't have pants, but Porky had pants.
Porky.
Not all the time though.
Well, he could reach in.
I tell you.
Yeah.
Maybe he was wearing pig colored pants.
Pig colored tights or something.
Oh, that makes me feel better.
Does it?
Yeah.
I see people walk around all the time when I'm at work.
People wearing like yoga pants that are the same color as skin.
And I go, that's bad.
Don't do that.
Because that's not good.
Because it looks like you're walking around naked.
I've been seeing that.
Yeah.
I've had been shocked from a distance.
It's like that woman's got no shirt on.
Oh.
It's just the same color as the rest of her.
She's wearing yoga pants for shirts.
Yeah.
It catches my eye.
That's for sure.
A gift to the male gaze of contemporary fashion.
Okay.
Here's a weird thing Porky Pig said.
Where's that feedback coming from?
Porky Pig.
What about him?
Porky.
Porky Pig.
Well, in one of those cartoons, Daffy or somebody says, your sister wears army
boots.
And Porky says, my sister doesn't wear army boots.
My sister works in a butcher shop and smokes ham.
And says it that way.
Really with an accent on the smokes ham.
I'm like, what the hell?
How are they telling these children?
Porky's sister.
Works in a butcher shop.
And smokes ham.
Right.
We got it.
I know what that can mean.
I'm going to go get my ham smoked up there at Sister Bessie's.
Go see Aunt May and get my ham smoked.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
Just kidding.
No.
You're talking about the pig here, right?
We're talking aboutảng
mentioned in答orot station.
I wanted to
ask you gentlemen if you are familiar with
the most atrociously
bad film I have ever seen
called The Goat Man.
It's a documentary. The Goat Man.
Is that the men who stare at
goats? No, but I think
Susie sent me a book
about the Goat Man.
I've read about the guy.
I didn't know they had a movie. The Wagon Train Led by
Goats? The Pet Goat read by
George Bush on 9-11.
Somehow this proved he was a man
of God because he was driving all these
goats. He was a shepherd. Plus he
had everything he owned on
his shopping cart.
Or in those days they didn't have shopping
carts. It was a big wagon.
His covered shopping cart. He was a junk
collector with goats.
And he traveled all around the country
and he had
slack. He was an avatar
an early avatar of slack.
In the documentary they track
down the Goat Man who is now living in a
nursing home and he was surrounded by
women from his former congregation who
wouldn't leave him alone.
Oh, you remember the time?
And he was just sitting there obviously just waiting for the next hour of meds.
Missing his goats.
Yeah. And then at the end they had
closing music by a guy in
brand spanking new cowboy costume
leaning against a fake wooden fence
and playing guitar.
Every time he would change the chords he'd
release his left hand and play open
strings to change to the next chord
while singing about, oh, the Goat Man.
This is something to search for.
I definitely have to find that.
It's called the Goat Man?
As I recall, I saw it
the only copy I saw was in a privately
owned video shop
that was run by a guy who
went into the video management business
because he needed a job coming out of prison.
It was the best store in
Minneapolis.
Well, there you go.
There you go.
That's all I can look for.
Goat help us.
Go-to job.
I just watched a film
called
Death,
Death Bed.
The bed that eats people.
Was it about Procrustes?
It was so bad.
And I showed it at the store.
I had to buy it.
Yeah.
Or remember the famous horror story
A Terribly Strange Bed
by Wilkie Collins?
That story about
the death bed?
The bed that eats people.
Well, the top of it comes down
on you and suffocates you in the middle of the night.
The bed that dare not speak its name.
Yeah.
Don't sleep in the bed.
Have you noticed that it started squealing
after Philo left?
Yeah.
Like he sabotaged something.
Like he left some kind of a booby trap.
Yeah, probably.
Yeah.
Set up his.
Maybe Philo.
The Mangler is another good one.
In a bad way.
No, bad one in a good way.
In a great way.
Now, if everybody here didn't know,
which is possible since no one ever looks
at the,
the schedule or brochure
instructions.
There are bad movies all night.
Every night.
At the Grindhouse.
The Grindhouse right down the hill there.
See that white tent?
You have to actually ambulate
down a hill to get to it.
Hey Susie,
what are we looking at?
No, you can sit down again
and it's very peaceful.
The bushes are seething with ticks.
You can't hear us from down there
for one thing.
Well, there you go, Susie.
I think you know.
No, it's no.
Yeah, turn around and it's
it's right in front of you.
There you go.
See, perfect.
See, nobody was noticing.
But me, you're talking about movies
and I thought it was a big heart.
I thought that some it was a big black
heart, but heart, big black velvet heart
right there.
Yeah, yeah.
Now I've seen that same site look like a
Osama bin Laden wanted poster.
She's found some pebbles worthy of your
scientific review.
What is?
They look like states of the Union that
don't exist.
There's pebbles of a vina.
Uh, they do look like like states of the
Union that don't exist.
The you know what?
What is that one called?
That's that's institutions.
I know that.
Well, you know, Susie and Plas Marcus is
right underneath it, isn't it?
Yeah, it looks like the map of America
after X day.
Yeah.
Marijuana is a lot of fun doing that map.
And we basically post a man world.
Yeah.
Like Stalin and FDR.
Showing off pebbles on the radio.
Oh yeah.
No, this is a very visual radio show.
Yep.
I've noticed every all of us have perfect
radio faces.
Well, that's why it's right.
Radio and television.
I don't want to have to shave, you know,
just every Sunday or take a shower.
Every week.
That would be terrible.
It was Susie's looking for more rocks of the union
of the Dobbs Union.
I didn't know you'd have to shave.
You're kind of rocking that.
Forgive me, Michael Savage.
Look with that goatee.
That's the only way.
Hmm.
Well, I know nothing.
How popular he got on TV.
With hate talk radio or TV.
I know nothing of this savage.
He's a.
I read his columns all the time.
You know, if I need to know how to, you know,
do anal upside down or something.
No, no, no.
You're talking about Dan Savage.
Dan.
Yeah.
You're talking about Michael.
Say Michael Weiner.
Oh, Mike, the wiener.
Oh, you are in a blessed state of ignorance.
I see.
I don't watch TV or hear the radio, so I don't know how to pronounce anything.
I don't know how anybody looks.
I know things.
I thought he was talking about.
But yeah, Dan Savage, too.
And I was like, wait, I think you're thinking of the wrong.
Dan.
The wrong savage.
Yeah.
And then there's Stoney Savage.
But that's.
Yeah, there's Fred Savage.
Yeah.
Who played in Wonder Years.
The child actor.
Clark Savage Jr.
That was Doc Savage's dad.
Randy Macho Man Savage.
No, Clark Savage Jr.
Was was Doc Savage, wasn't he?
Oh, Junior.
Yes.
Clark Sr.
Was Doc Savage's dad.
Right.
Yeah.
And then Dork Savage was the son that they didn't talk about.
Dork Savage.
Yeah.
He didn't turn out the way they planned.
And all of that discipline just backfired.
He became a slacker.
He was a hippie in those days.
You know, he didn't want to do any of the preparation.
Yeah.
Doc couldn't handle the idea of having what he considered an effeminate, undisciplined son.
And so.
He just stopped speaking of the boy.
Who was actually his son by his cousin, Patricia Savage.
Pat.
Yeah.
She was a nice little number.
The girl of bronze.
Yeah.
The woman of bronze.
And they called her.
Yeah.
I know too much about Doc Savage's skeletons.
Did you read the book Doc Savage, His Apocalyptic Life?
You must have.
Yeah.
Oh, are you kidding?
I was looking for my own.
See if I had any ancestors in there.
He had every one.
Anybody related to Doc Savage.
From Daniel Boone to.
Travis McGee.
Captain Hornblower.
Fever McGee.
Tarzan.
Yeah.
Tarzan was.
Well, and then I read that.
The Scarlet Pimpernel.
Philip Jose Dick book.
Where.
Philip Jose Farmer.
Yeah.
That was a good one.
Philip Jose Dick.
Yeah.
And I have a box at home that says Dick's.
Philip and Phil.
Anyway.
The.
Yeah.
There's a.
The Wold Newton meteorite fell while the coach containing their ancestors was passing and irradiated their germ placenta.
Well, at the end of that, that Farmer book, Doc Savage and Tarzan are literally crossing penises.
Oh, that's.
On a rock bridge.
That's a different book.
Over a bottomless pit.
Different book.
And they end up.
That's a book.
Tearing their genitals.
Yeah.
They tear each other's.
That's a different book.
Packers off.
Different book.
A Feast Unknown.
A Feast Unknown is the title.
Yeah.
That is an amazing, really amazing book.
It is.
It's.
However, it's not the biography that we were talking about a moment ago.
No.
It's.
It's another.
But it's also Philip.
Philip.
Jose Farmer.
Right.
By the way, I've mailed him pamphlets and stark fists throughout his life.
Good.
To his P.O. Box in Peoria.
Mm-hmm.
And?
And never got any response at all.
Same with Stephen King.
Nancy Collins or somebody.
One of our writer friends had given me these addresses and said, oh, you ought to send
this stuff to them.
They'll love it.
And of course, you know, I didn't expect anything back.
But I've never seen any evidence either way that it made any.
At least it didn't kill him.
Well, I mean, I think it's a good thing.
And we sent stuff to Phil Dick.
He died that week.
Same with L. Ron Hubbard.
Oh.
And Bill Hicks, I'm afraid.
Mm-hmm.
And when we realized that was happening, we sent one to Jesse Helms and.
I mean, yeah, a bunch of different politicians.
But it didn't work.
Didn't work then.
Mm.
And maybe it was just coincidence.
But honest to God, those are all.
It's sold their souls already.
Three true stories.
A subgenius named Reverend Betsy K.
Curtis, who's probably not around anymore, had been at the party where Hubbard made that
famous announcement that if you want to make money, you start a religion.
And she remained friends with him.
She wasn't a Scientologist.
She was just an old sci-fi fan, one of his old friends.
Right.
And she's had his, a post office box in Miami that if you sent to this, it would
go.
Yeah.
Directly to him on the yacht.
And, but when we did that, he croaked.
He probably took one look at the, what the hell do you think you're doing questionnaire.
And passed from this life.
And croaked right there.
Reverend Stank.
Thank you.
Yeah.
We, we helped the world that way.
It's too bad about Bill Hicks and Phil Dick.
Yeah.
Bill Hicks.
Is John Waters.
Is John Waters a subgenius?
We've never heard from him.
No?
Okay.
No.
I.
One time Douglas Adams was in Dallas for book signing and I handed him a copy of book
of the subgenius and said, are you at all familiar with this?
He said, no, but you know, it looks like fun.
And a couple of years later he had a planet Bob in one of his later books.
Yeah.
There you go.
Well, it's listed in the real Frank Zappa book too.
Oh yeah.
Oh, Frank Zappa was very specific about that.
Yeah.
He said if I, if I was to join any religion, it would be a guy with a pipe.
It says that right in his, in his thing.
Well, he liked the fact that Bob was a smoker.
Right.
And.
Tim Leary.
Slack idea.
Yeah.
He liked that.
So, and he specifically said some guys in Dallas.
So that was good.
Oh yeah.
No, no.
It, it.
He didn't say there's this asshole in Canada.
Right.
Thank heavens for that.
No, that really pissed that asshole in Canada off too.
Is he still active?
Hmm?
Is the pink Canuck still active?
I have no idea.
I honestly don't know.
And no interest.
He had no longer gets free helicopter rides.
He was doing a podcast with some new agers and he had a blog that you couldn't get into
unless you were a member.
And I just did.
How tedious.
That was it.
How stale.
His wife's still selling RNA drops that will make you live forever.
You'll, you'll.
Yes.
Cure cancer and make you fly.
Philo says, yeah.
He says he's still on Facebook.
He what?
He's still on Facebook.
Mr. Dean.
Oh.
Still there on Facebook.
I had a friend the other time but I don't know if I'm a friend of his.
Wanted to friend him?
Well, that would be a mistake.
I won't friend anybody who calls themselves Bob Dobbs.
Me either.
One of them might be the, you know, what if?
It could happen.
You know, all types of people who call themselves Bob Dobbs want to be my Facebook friend.
I have to turn each one of them down.
Oh yeah.
I will not countenance.
That's just so lame.
I can't do it.
Somebody else.
I mean.
I've even run into people using Ivan's gang to show they were really inside.
Uh huh.
That's a great way to put it.
What could be inner than that?
On the other hand, Charlie Muck, that was a good one.
When I saw somebody calling himself Charlie Muck, I was going, now that's inside the inside.
Yep.
That's pretty good.
So, there.
Phooey.
There we go.
That's a good one.
Phooey.
I'm happy to love a female dear
Little day
Back to being nice
Back to the
We're all in headphones, you idiot.
He said he watched the movie the other day
and it referred to Charlie Muck.
Really?
That was my movie, Let's Visit the World of the Future.
Most prophetic, low-budget, apocalyptic, dystopian movie ever made.
Which you can buy.
Because it all came true.
It's right over there on the swag table.
You can buy it.
Fight C. Todd will sell you a DVD of that movie.
There's probably only one copy.
It may be.
There's only one copy.
You can get it.
They showed it at a theater in Cleveland just recently.
I show a rise at my store once in a while.
Yeah, but World of the Future.
Two weeks.
What result?
I actually showed that to people in my store, though.
You know, like in, you know.
And what was their reaction?
Can I leave now?
Yeah, can I leave now?
When is this going to be over?
How is it?
Why did you lock the door?
Well, this is just the first 15 minutes.
Yeah.
What?
Sit down and have some popcorn.
Why is that clown touching a naked girl?
You're not going anywhere.
Are you around, like, James Bond?
So, yeah.
Yeah.
There.
There you go.
See?
But it's true.
Now, bozos run the world.
Evil clowns run America.
Oh, yeah.
And it's all holograms.
You can't believe anything.
Nostra Stangis.
You figured it out.
I never believed that.
I love the fact that it was like, oh, we thought about having grass, but, well, that just takes
too long to cut, so we just cemented over the whole planet.
Well, that time is coming.
There's no question.
If humans even make it that long.
I doubt it.
I don't want to.
I don't.
Speaking of funny names.
We should be over with in about, what?
Less than 24 hours.
Yeah.
We'll know.
May I ask you, Evan Stang, to explain a funny name that I didn't get?
Probably everybody knows it.
From the Funny Names Club of America?
You had set up a bank of prank callers to phone in radio shows of the religious sort
at one point.
Shocking.
Back in the 90s.
The 90s.
I did?
Yeah.
It was one of the early hours of Slack when it was on the radio.
Operators standing by.
They were performing prank calls live, and they made a reference to Aunt Melba, and he
saw through somebody.
One of the preachers on the radio saw through and hung up when they mentioned Aunt Melba.
Who is Aunt Melba?
What does that refer to?
Does that make any sense at all?
Yeah.
Those prank calls weren't initiated by me.
It was a group called the Crystal Mountain.
The Crystal Methodists.
That's right.
The Crystal Methodists did that.
They were real experts at that.
And they, yeah, they, one of them was excellent at sounding like an old lady.
Yeah.
But they were live on your show.
She was Aunt Melba.
You know, this is Melba.
She was the toast of radio.
And I just wanted to talk about Jesus.
You know, well, okay, Melba.
But Melba didn't get weirder and weirder.
And they finally caught on that Melba was probably some guy.
Oh.
Yeah.
Thank you.
The Crystal Methodists.
They were great.
See, now, if you still have any of those left over, he might put that in there when you've mentioned it.
That sounds like a takeoff on Aunt Bertha, actually.
Yeah.
Cue cut to Crystal Methodists.
You're tired.
Melba in Dallas, Texas.
She's been holding on patiently.
Thanks a lot, Melba.
Oh, my.
Hiya.
That was a long wait.
I'm sorry.
We had to go to a top-of-the-hour news break, and that's why it took so long.
Well, I thought that that last night was a good day.
But mine should be on there forever.
I couldn't believe it.
I want to talk about the Dallas Stars.
I think they're going to come back strong.
This is just a temporary setback with them.
And as far as that gentleman that called in about the violence on that,
that boys will be boys with Hawkeyes.
The name of the game is contact and aggression, I think.
And it always has been.
And I personally enjoy, you know, a real strong body check, teeth, hair, and eyes on the ice.
Yeah.
I love it.
Cue.
Well, we understand what...
Cut and gut.
Cue.
Yeah.
Well, who was that?
That didn't sound like Melba.
Melba has a very manly voice.
Nah, but...
That was from the CD called Melba Comes Alive by Brother Russell,
also known as Crystal Methodist in the 1980s.
And it is available on bandcamp.com,
along with many other prank call and music mashup recordings
by the Crystal Methodist and Brother Russell.
A piece of eccentric Texas history,
of which...
I hope I am a part.
But now, back to X-Day 22.
Or...
Whatever.
You heard it here first.
What?
We didn't hear it.
We don't hear anything from the peanut gallery.
Mr. Peanut has something to say.
6.4 magnitude quake in South California.
Today?
Today.
Hold your tips.
No wonder we couldn't get email.
No.
We're going to find a Bob man.
Hmm.
Or whoever.
Southern California, you said.
Southern California.
Well, who the fuck knows.
LA's about to slide into the ocean.
Yeah.
Or it'll be a separate island.
California will sink.
There'll be a prison.
Atlantis will rise.
Eventually, the ocean will have so much plastic cushioning in it,
when California sinks, it'll be minimal damage.
It'll just float.
Bounce back out.
Everything will float.
It'll just float right on it.
Yeah.
That's bullshit.
It will float right on it.
That is bullshit, yes.
Oh, I caused that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
The microphone's doing the feedback over there.
Maybe it's my teeth.
Here and there, man.
Your teeth?
Yeah.
They're metal.
That's where the voices come from.
Yeah.
Put your tux near there.
You gotta pull them out.
Then you won't hear the voices no more.
That's what I did.
Bob.
From PR News in Washington, I'm a Kurdish turkey.
The space shuttle Discovery astronauts have now conducted a crucial attack on a space
shuttle.
The space shuttle has been deployed to a suburban Philadelphia high school.
NASA says at least 17 astronauts are still out of control there, while noting more work
remains to be done.
NASA says two of the astronauts show no signs of retreating.
Washington has put pressure on the two turds.
The astronauts illegally attached a bus to their weapons.
NASA says will increase the price of a round trip ticket by 25 cubic dollars.
On Wall Street 4, 350, 30, 20.
NASA says this is PR News.
Ta-da.
We're back.
Yeah, we'll have clowns later, I think.
Pretty sure the clowns will be here.
Don't give the clowns drugs, friends.
I saw the bicycle come in on the top of the car.
I was like, somebody brought their kid.
And I'm like, oh no, no, that's a clown's bicycle.
Oh no, oh no, the clowns are already here.
Don't give the clowns drugs, whatever you do.
And don't go over there in the clown town.
Oh, that was supposed to, oh, you know, that's what it is.
That speaker was down there.
I put it up here to hold it.
I pulled the tarp last night.
And then I didn't put it back on the ground.
Oh, look, Philo, you're off the hook.
This is of great interest to our listeners, of course.
I did have it deliberately, carefully put down there for the last two days.
Then this morning, I stupidly left it up here.
Well, aren't we glad we've got all that cleared up?
By the way, Reverend DeFalk, from your emails, I had been assuming that you were about 24 years old.
He is.
Look at him.
He's a strapping, healthy young fellow.
He's a good-looking 24-year-old.
If William S. Burroughs was the youngest member of the church, well, an age is all relative.
Okay.
See?
There's your answer.
Oh, and you also thought he had nice tits.
See?
Right?
Because he shows.
I thought you were a 24-year-old girl.
No.
Oh, that didn't come up, as it were, so to speak.
That's because I've only started entering adulthood in my own sphere.
Yeah, see?
He's a good-looking 24-year-old.
He's a lot younger than what you think.
Oh, right.
I was an infantile brat most of the time.
Wow, you really are quite a yeti.
Yeah.
A 24-year-old girl.
Well, yeah.
A girl with a beard, an amazing beard.
Yeah, a big, stylish beard.
And like quite possibly the coolest eyebrows that I've ever seen in person.
What are you talking about?
Where'd this come from?
Overslept a bit.
A growing out of your face.
Well, there you go.
Reverend Rip Van Winkle.
There isn't a Reverend Rip Van Winkle.
I wouldn't think, but there you go, radio listeners.
Not that I know of.
I try to look at all the little postcards they send me.
Yeah.
Quickly.
With facial identification recognition software.
Yeah.
They put something in my wine.
It's as plain as the nose on your face.
Yeah.
Did they put alcohol in your wine, sir?
That's bad.
They put pineapple juice in your pineapple juice.
You know what?
You should probably contact that box company and let them know, listen, this wine in a
plastic bag is not for you.
This is a bag in a box.
It's got some alcohol or something in it.
Wine is a mucker.
Strong drink is raging.
That happens.
Did you make that bird noise or was that authentic?
That's an actual tweet.
That's Philo.
That's the president tweeting.
It is Philo.
Stop drinking that alcohol.
Yeah, there's a little birdie up there.
Yeah.
There's a bird.
That's all panic now.
A bird is in here.
This is Tarzan's radio station.
It's in the rainforest.
The dreaded-
Canopy.
Grackle.
The brain forest.
The squawking-
Hey, look who's here.
Princesses.
This would be my chance to get off of this, get out from under these tight headphones.
Right.
They are tight, aren't they?
Boy, it'd be great if it's all dames for a while.
Yeah.
I could just ride a cart.
I'm going to turn this off and then turn it back on again.
Well, I'll just take that.
For me.
That's where this place came from.
A- foto by me.
Oh my God.
O-N-A
B-O-B
Big man
O-N-A
One dollar
B-O-B
Big man
B-O
O-N-A
Outro Music
That was the official remix by Onan of Dr. Onan Kennebite's song, B.O.B.
I shall never, ever forget the first time I heard that, which was in the early 1980s and accelerated consciousness on a beach.
But now, but now, back to 12-12-20 with Lonesome Cowboy Dave for the part where we forget to say,
for more information, see subgenius.com.
Yeah, if you're by a washer dryer, you end up in your apartment building, don't stand there when it starts going,
because it can not only upset your stomach, it can change your DNA to a fast-forward-dentious belly button driver.
That explains a whole lot.
Yeah.
Because someone, let's say someone I used to know, used to sit on top of her.
A dryer.
Deliberately, while it was vibrating.
Oh, I see.
And I think they wanted to get irradiated.
That would explain it.
Yep.
And there's nothing like a quick blast from an automatic unit, you know what I mean?
Well, I would never do anything like that with a big, vibrating, curvy edge.
So you don't think it's a very good idea making love with appliances?
How about when they speak to you in your dreams and give you orders?
Well, that's when you know you're in love with your dryer.
Or your whatever that's bumped.
It could be a motorcycle.
Or your horse.
Ladies love horses.
I heard for a while, it was, what's his name, Leonard Cohen's whole raison d'etre was singing songs about appliances.
Boy, there goes Dave, using those Frenchy terms again.
Why don't you just go back to France, where he came from?
Hippie?
Because in France, they have no...
Underpants.
Therefore, I don't wear no...
In pants?
No pants in France?
In France.
You go to France, you'll get ants in your pants.
Without no pants on, yeah.
Why do I say that all the time?
You get ants in your pants.
Ants in your pants.
Something makes me say pants.
It's one of those things that just goes in your head, like...
It's 20 years in northern Ohio makes you say pants.
That's what it is.
I think you're right.
I think it is.
It's like...
That's the Cleveland accent creeping out.
Where's my pants?
It's one of those things.
It's like somewhere between Buffalo and Detroit.
It just goes through your head, like Wee Mama has those things go through her head.
She says, think and think.
What do you think?
Dry cleaning for nothing?
She doesn't know where it came from.
She just says it.
It's a thing.
It's just a thing.
Sounds like a Cockney Rebel thing.
Do you believe in Cockney Rebels?
Or any other religious after fighting?
I don't know.
I swore off all that stuff.
It's too tempting for me.
If they're going to chase you around the block with those little devoted candles, boy, you
better don't worry which bench to hide under.
That's all I can say.
Because when the pigeons get there, you're going to be the one they're going to roast
at the annual festival.
How does he do this, Princess Rae?
I don't know.
It's the Dave train.
How does he do it?
I don't know.
He makes such...
What did he do?
Fools.
What did I do?
I started singing our rock opera again, and I shouldn't.
I swore off that.
Your pants have to be so torn that when you put them on, you have to go through your foot
three times in the pants.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, I know what you mean, because my pants are that way.
My pants are exactly that way.
A little slice of buttocks going on your pants.
I guess I'm missing Cleveland.
I wish I was back in Cleveland.
With my pants.
His pants.
Collinwood.
Yeah, and Collinwood.
I was in Collinwood for a long time.
Collinwood.
Yeah.
Well, at least you don't talk like you're from a Yenzer from western Pennsylvania.
Yens.
Yens going down town.
What the hell are you talking about?
What are Yens...
What the hell are Yens talking about?
Going downtown.
You know when they say Yens, they say Yens instead of y'all.
They say Yens.
Instead of saying downtown, they say downtown.
Downtown.
Right.
You look at the floor and you see a tall there.
Is it a tall?
Everybody knows that downtown is pronounced down town.
Down town, yes.
I'm going down town.
In fact, every word has got like four syllables, you know.
I'm from Atlanta, Georgia.
Well, actually, those syllables are all represented in there.
But yeah, you can stretch out any old word.
Yeah, it is fun to do.
With if.
If you're not from Cleveland.
If you're from Cleveland, it's all pants all the way down.
In the deep south, it's like, I'm putting on my pants.
When you do your report, pants all the way down.
Here in Texas, pants...
You know, they're going to ask you on the review board.
They're going to say, Mr. Stang, have you noticed that in your last report you submitted to the police chief?
You said your pants were not completely and totally down.
They're only partially down.
Yeah.
If asked, one might say.
If you asked me.
Yeah.
Mm.
Pants.
That's spelled...
In Texas, that's spelled P-A-Y-A-N-T-S.
Pants.
It's just an extra two letters.
As in payoff or payout.
Pants.
Underpants.
Yeah.
Oh, he said underpants.
And if you're tenacious D, you say underpants.
Unterpants.
Yes.
Guy was the same guy who did that thing about Dolly.
Dolly is everything.
Wumping and yomping and yomping and yomping.
Of course, that was 345 years ago back when...
Remember when Galileo first got murdered?
Well, I've read about it.
I think it was Da Vinci today.
He was born yesterday.
Yeah.
That was just a little before my time, Dave.
But tell us about...
Oh, sure.
As if you didn't have any time around.
You couldn't...
Well...
Can you love me some time, man?
I need a little bit more time.
Sorry.
Nothing fucks you harder than time, said Sir Davos in Game of Thrones.
And I'll have to edit that.
Yes, you will.
Nothing trumps you harder than time.
It was worth it.
I was wondering if someday we could...
There's a way to remix Presidents on the Phone to Take Out where it says,
Mom and Dad and just have three honks.
The President on the Phone talks to his honk, honk, honk.
Oh.
That would be it.
Oh, because the current President doesn't have a...
It seems modular, yeah.
It does seem modular now.
They all look for the bomb and Gilead of their families.
The secret respite from the nauseating world out there.
Oh, no, no.
You would change it to...
Instead of Mom and Dad, you'd say his son and son-in-law or something like that, his son and daughter.
Because...
You could say his wife's son.
You could say any number of things, but it's modular if you just have two horn honks.
The President's on the Phone.
Yeah, but it doesn't make any sense.
Talks to his honk, honk, honk.
Oh, you just don't want to re-sing the song.
You just want to lay in some honk honks.
Yeah.
I don't think that's necessary.
I think we could play that.
We could play that song right now.
Yeah.
Now I have to go back and find whatever decent recording...
I think we have three live recordings of that song, and they're all not perfect.
We did use one for a video, though.
And that one was pretty good.
I could do that.
The heck, I knew where to find that real fast.
It was on YouTube.
It was from the next day on YouTube, yeah.
Yeah.
the president's on TV
talking about liberty
He's talking liberty
But you and I ain't free
Professors at a White House tea
They're talking opportunity
He's talking opportunity
Like that's enough for folks like you and me
Meanwhile the world is tumbling down
Down in a pile of shit
That's for a revolution
A revolution that's the tension
The presidency of the proud men
The president's on the phone
Talking to his mom and dad
He's saying should I turn on the evidence
Or be a good old stumble
The president's on the phone
Having a chat with God
He says he's gonna do it
He'll say if I would
Or maybe just the half of a ton
It's a democratic country
Where they don't have fun
And business is not an offshore fund
And business is growing
And there's no surprise
The president loves to do so
The truth is I'm here
I said yeah
No it's not
The big ol' baby
Your mind head, entrance in your mind
You're supposed to be a bad fucker.
My eyesight is awful.
I'm closer to the TV now.
And, uh, at S&H 495, is that, do y'all take S&H Green Stamp?
No, that means shipping and handling.
Oh, well, do y'all do not take Green Stamps?
No, we don't use the Green Stamps.
Oh, well, that's a pisser.
You don't have that many people to do anymore, do you?
Oh, well, I don't know.
All my friends are dead.
I'm an elderly woman.
I'm about 92.
They don't have any birth records on me.
I was born in a rural...
rural area.
But, uh, I'm about 92.
I kind of lose count.
Um, well, I sure would like that...
the bracelet, but I only have $13.
I'm sorry, honey.
I only have...
Wait, hold on.
Hold on.
Yes.
I think I can do 40.
I've got $40.
I told you, fib.
Well, it's...
It'll be 40...
It's actually gonna be closer to, uh, $52 before your...
Goddamn.
Yeah, once you put the shipping and handling on top and the sales tax.
That's fucked.
I can't believe that shit.
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
I love you.
I love you too.
And now that we're in the section that's not on broadcast radio, I can tell you subgenius.com.
Yeah, subgenius.com.
Subgenius.com.
And Dave, and also, if you look at the radio section of subgenius.com,
I'm gonna tell you something.
I'm not lying.
All of the hours of slack from number one through number 1757 are there.
Or will be there after I quit talking.
Available to delight your eardrums.
Yeah.
And also, there's a link to donate to Dave.
Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
Well, just between you, me, and the public listening to the internet,
Dave's pretty perpetually broke.
He used to work as a newspaper reporter, but the newspaper's all closed down.
And there is a GoFundMe.
And as much as I'd love to tell people to help me personally, Dave needs it more.
A lot more.
And so be like Anonymous.
That great guy, Anonymous, who gave Dave 500 bucks last week
when I told him to donate to the internet.
I told him, no, give it to Dave.
I really did.
I know.
He was going to give it to me, and I said, no, give it to Dave.
You're a wonderful person.
No, I'm not.
I just...
No, you are a wonderful person.
I can't do what Dave does.
We need him.
I can't talk like that.
I know.
I could try, but it wouldn't be the same.
It'd be like trying to play like Jimi Hendrix.
Sure, for about three seconds, you can do it.
Okay.
Friends.
Oh, and what else?
Oh, Triology Soap.
Have you tried Triology Soap from TriologySoap.com?
That's T-R-I, not T-R-Y.
TriologySoap.com.
Our good friend, Lord Ferg, makes Triology Soap,
including numerous flavors and scents of Dobbshead soap.
Yes.
Soap shaped like a Dobbshead,
embedded in a square bar of translucent other soap.
It's not only good soap, it's high quality glycerin soap.
It's delightfully wonderful to use.
Yeah.
TriologySoaps.com.
Subgenius.com.
Woof!
T-R-I-O-W handle.
Hmm...
participin' up.
►►►►►
You can go to the CWBib. рабidly movie theater of the year.
Speaker restor-
Oh my God.
Oh,му're fucking cool!
you