My name is Max.
My world is fire and blood.
Why are you hurting these people?
It's the oil, stupid.
Oil wars.
We are killing for gasoline.
Gasoline.
The world is actually running out of water.
Now there's the water wars.
Once, I was a cop, a road warrior searching for a righteous cause.
The terminal freakout point.
Mankind has gone rogue, terrorizing itself.
The earth is sour.
Our bones are poisoned.
We have become half-life.
As the world fell, each of us in our own way was broken.
It was hard to know who was more crazy.
.
Tony Drag, yes, welcome to the hour of swag.
La, la, la, la, la, la.
La, la, la, hour of swag.
Now which dog do you want to be champion?
That dog or that dog?
That's my good boy champion.
That's a good boy.
Hey.
I need Bob Dobbs to hold my pain.
I need Bob Dobbs to haul around my silly name.
I need Bob Dobbs to haul all the Yeti from my bed.
I need Bob Dobbs to haul the pink boys when they're dead.
I need Bob Dobbs to haul me to Dobbs Town.
I need Bob Dobbs to haul my weird thoughts around.
I need Bob Dobbs to haul my haba fraba zippy laps.
And I need Bob Dobbs to haul all my bobs in.
But you know something?
He kind of looks like somebody, doesn't he?
You have a friend named Bob.
Bob's about the best friend in the world.
Why have you been at the hospital the past two days?
Bob's in a coma.
He was in there a solid three days.
What's that, a bar?
Low town.
That's Bob.
Is your friend Bob a doctor?
He's just about the best darn veterinarian in these parts.
The army lost.
Did it have a tattoo?
What's this all about?
I'm a shoe salesman.
Settle down.
I just asked you a question.
If you won't tell us, we can find out.
What did it say?
It said, Mom.
Earth people, hear me and hear me well.
I, from this moment on, am Bob Dobbs.
Shall rule over planet Earth!
Your fate is sealed!
The invasion by creatures from space confirmed.
New York City may be their next objective.
Yes, brothers and sisters, the space men are coming and none can stop them.
But our lord and mastron, J.R. Bob Dobbs, can broker us a deal with the alien horde.
Bob has come to rip asunder the congealed skin on the gravy bowl of postmodern ennui.
And scoop out the filth of the conspiracy within.
To lead the mutant tribe of the subgenius race down the magic rabbit hole to the land
of slack.
Are you sick and tired of being sick and tired?
The star forces may already have you in their mind control grip.
Fight back by exploiting your own abnormality and cast off the chains of normalcy.
The world ends tomorrow and you may die.
So remember to visit www.youtube.com and subscribe to our channel.
And get right with Bob.
It may already be too late.
Call now and receive your free audio package from Anchorage, Alaska.
P.O.
Box 448805 zip code 054.
And we'll probably tell you things you'll wish to forget.
Receive two sets for twice the price and we'll throw in a DVD of tugboats.
The end.
Bob Dobbs.
And so All Stars did our title music.
And there'll be more music coming up by the fantastic Plastics and Rural War Room.
But see, we're still out of town.
In deepest Texas.
On Stang Ranch.
And doing new shows by calling into Radio Synesthesia.
Dr. Sinister's show on WCSB Cleveland that follows the Hour of Slack there on Sunday
nights.
I mean, I could just do ancient reruns and probably will.
But.
But despite the not so great audio quality we get from recording the station's internet
stream, we'd rather do new shows than reruns if possible.
Devout WCSB listeners will be hearing this for the second time.
But believe me, I did all manner of tightening and shortening and carving and sanding to
make it smoother.
And besides, really, how many listeners would remember hearing it the first time anyway?
So now we join.
The radio synesthesia.
Of January 24 already in progress.
The word for throwing people out of windows.
That's what makes sense with the word for Nestor from there.
Yeah.
That's also what I call the blue screen of death on my computer.
I just got thrown out of windows by the blue screen of death.
I take it you're not much of a computer user.
I don't know what the blue screen of death is
on Windows operating systems
on PCs
if a serious
system error occurs
then whatever you're doing will just stop
and you get a blue screen with this message on it
saying that a fatal error or fatal
exception was detected and
your computer is being shut down to prevent damage
to your system
that sounds
pretty serious I've been attacked by
many viruses
it's not always caused by
viruses it's you know earlier
versions of Windows would do that all the time
yes they would crash suddenly
because their expiration date had gone sideways
at least
in Singapore
and we are getting another call right now
hello you're on the air
I have a joke
are you doing
alright let's have a joke show
I have a joke that's surrealist
or maybe Dada if I'm not sure
okay
knock knock
who's there
to get to the other side
oh I like that
hey did you hear the one about the inquisition
no
you lie confess
too oblique man
I know not oblique enough
Dada
that's stupid
did you hear the one about the presidential candidate
that said that he could shoot people
and his supporters would still vote for him
okay
you know every time he has
said something like that it's like
gosh did he really jump the shark this time
you know that we don't even have to
name him now
he who must not be named
yeah
so Donald Trump recently said
oh yeah I forgot I'm sorry I forgot
was that right after
I thought that was great that he actually got Tina Fey to endorse him
I saw that speech he gave and like you know
in the full Sarah Palin regalia
and
I thought that was like one of the greatest pranks ever played on
oh wait hold on a second I just read something
this
wait hold
that was actually Sarah Palin
I couldn't
no
it looked like a cartoon version of herself
she does look like a cartoon version
she has transformed into a cartoon version of herself
you know reality has lapped satire
I've said that before
and I'm going to say it again
except that now I'm going to say reality
has lapped satire
keeps lapping satire
wasn't Sarah Palin always a cartoon
yeah but now she's like recycling her greatest hits from eight years ago
oh the hopey changey stuff
the porn movies with the lookalike Palin
have you ever seen any of them
any of what's
the porn movies
you know I have to say I am not
turned on by that kind of idea
I would struggle to watch such a thing
well
the premise is
she gets snowed in one night
and some Russian soldiers
wait wait wait
have you had Edward Snowden with her
no
she is snowed in
oh snowed in
that would be funny if you had Edward Snowden
and Sarah Palin lookalikes doing a porno together
that would be funny
that would be much better than what I'm going to say
I must confess
but
anyway so these three
four however many
Russian soldiers
are lost
and go across the border somehow
into Alaska near Palin's pad
and
and then
well and then
wow
I was like that there
she has the accent as well
you know
which is not really an Alaskan accent necessarily
you know it's kind of like Minnesota
I don't know
Wisconsin maybe
Fargo
yeah that that that's
that whole area
northern
northern Wisconsin
Minnesota
parts of the Dakotas
people talk like that too
yes it's a variation of how people
you know why it's so windy
you know why it's so
you know why it's so windy in Minnesota
because Wisconsin sucks and the Dakotas blow
that's a
that's a joke that Al Franken made
you must have been
you have relatives there
are you
I have a step sister in Minneapolis actually
or St. Paul I should say
it's a big place in Minneapolis actually
it's a big difference
the difference between St. Paul and Minneapolis
is like the difference between the east side
and west side of Cleveland
plus two different states right
no they're both in the same state
but they're on opposite sides of the Mississippi River
oh I was thinking of Budapest
I had my eyes crossed
ah yes Buda and Pest
they were two separate cities
yes
I was trying to reopen my uh
curb
and the most important muscle
you were trying to think of Budapest
but you never made yourself a rudder pest
no it's
yeah
huh
oh no I was thinking about cabbage oils
cabbage oils
or paprikash
oh cabbage oils
paprikash
my favorite fruit
if I said
one of these days I'm going to try my hand at paprikash
have you ever smelled the ugly fruit
or whatever it's called from China
are you thinking of the durian
no it's not bad
but it's real delicious
the durian
yeah I think it's
it's most common in like Southeast Asia
um
I don't know how anyone got the idea
to eat it in the first place
because first of all
it's covered in really sharp spikes
second of all
you cut it open
and it smells like
yeah actually um
I've never actually encountered durian in real life
um
but I did get some durian flavored candy
from uh
from the stangs
and um
it didn't exactly taste like poo
what it reminded me of
is the
the odorant compound they put in natural gas
it tasted like a gas leak
that's what I thought
uh
doctor at this point I have to ask
how exactly do you know what poo tastes like
well
I should say
I know what it smells like
it didn't exactly have the flavor profile
okay
oh by the way
there is also a famous story written about this
this food
what the durian
or poop
uh durian
okay
really Sherman
you mean to tell me you've never read
the picture of durian gray
oh no
uh
I can feel my stool softening
and my bowels are a little
turned my bowels to water
I'll write 216-687-3515
I'm sorry I was just going to say
my jokes have an effect on people
mm-hmm
hello you're on the air
Dr. Sinister
ah
welcome back
are you back
I was listening to the show earlier
I'm trying to call in
but then I came down
and started watching the reboot of the X-Files
oh
yeah how was that
well it's television
mm-hmm
I feel really normal now
since I've been staying at my dad's place
my ex
my late dad's place
I've become normal
hmm
I've been watching television
lads
and I have a smart phone
so now I'm always hunched over
pushing little buttons
oh dear
or I'm watching
I'm always watching TV
either on a wall
or on my
oh no
hand
oh yeah
yeah
well hey you know
we live in the future now so
you can still hear the elephants
banging in the background
Stan
I mean
you are in a vast savannah
of many cerebral hopes
and dashed dreams
and out there
where the wind blows free
you want
you're real rare
and yet it's
oh my god
I just saw an ad
that indicates
that there is a series
coming up
about the Kennedy assassination
not just a special
a special
a series
not just a mini series
I just saw a little imitation
Lee Harvey Oswald
posing with a gun
in the pamphlet
I feel like I'm being enveloped
in the future
my friends
oh that's weird
and I suppose
what they're going to say
the same thing
that was the revisionist thing
that we can't do
everything with the
Stokes committee
that everybody else found out
that was a conspiracy
and now they're going to be
the Gerald Pesner
or Pesner
whatever his name was
who's the known operative
of the high command
of the
all I know is
the X-Files
is going to reveal
everything
about the conspiracy
so far it turns out
it hasn't been aliens
it's been
human evildoers
using stolen alien technology
oh and they're
apparently they're
unveiling the conspiracy
on live TV right now
at least on TV
so I'm not sure
hmm
but it's being debunked
this Alex
trying to put it in
the most conspiracy
and explaining
wouldn't it
I mean
he explained the conspiracy
to everybody
but already
it's being debunked
just in the first hour
of this rebooted show
and here's the funny thing
I've mentioned that
I'm normal
I'm watching TV
I've never seen
the X-Files before
I never saw
the X-Files once
when it was on
in the 90s
I'd walk by
everybody else
would be watching it
I'd walk by
but I had to work
on those Pharisees
and aliens
so I never watched the show
now I'm watching the show
and it seems kind of stupid
it's hard for me to judge it
because
you know I was a teenager
in the 90s
and my tastes are
very different now
than they were back then
and I haven't seen it
in 15 years
so
actually more like
20 years now
since the last time I saw it
so it's kind of hard
for me to judge
yeah I remember
when my mommy
used to like it a lot
I didn't watch that
very much I think
but I'm not sure
I liked it at the time
apparently the government
is shutting down
everyone who tried
to reveal the truth
this time
this is just
in the first episode
they blew up
a secret area
just a minute ago
I just saw them do it
because I'm watching
with muted
but
you know
it's times like these
that I'm
the conflict early
that's the opening scene
is the conflict right
in the resolution
well they started
with the Roswell
until the series is over
that was the opening
the opening scene
of the show
was the Roswell
crash
but it turns out
that wasn't really
aliens
that was
that was a
sponsored by the government
to make everyone
think that it was
an aliens
to think that was
what was being
covered up
but it was really
something much
much worse
than aliens
taking over the world
I always assumed
it was
yeah I thought
it was like
experimental
aircraft of some kind
the Soviets
used to breed
these midget pilots
who would
be like extra small
so they could fit into
experimental aircraft
and some of the
corpses that have been found
that were supposedly aliens
were in fact
Russians
Soviet midget corpses
and
but you know
it's times like these
I'm glad I'm a subgenius
because
you know
I get to know
what the real conspiracy
is all about
well that's a funny thing
I mean they keep
on the sex files
saying they keep
they keep pulling the rug
out from under you
so I'm like
oh there's aliens
oh no it's not really aliens
oh there were aliens
but now it's the government
oh there was a government
but now it's a different government
and oddly enough
Fox and Mulder
look strangely aged
she's really skinny
and he's kind of bloated
everything's different
from
yeah
imagine that
people
15 years ago
imagine that
20 years go by
and people don't look
the same anymore
I don't get it
that can't happen to me
can it
oh dear
that's prismatic
neck disease
that happens
when you turn 45
you get spasmodic
neck disease
it's like a chicken visit
or something like that
but the Chinese people
don't like it as much
as they used to
and you have to do
certain
you have to do like
feng shui
or you know
like feng shui
get in the right place
and then you have to do
some jikon
and stuff like that
and it goes away automatically
unless you don't want
you could make it bigger
if you wanted to
it could be done
not get bigger
because I know
we all want to make it bigger
yeah
whatever it is
it
oh it looks like
the FBI is so worried
they're calling
Scully and Mulder
back in
hmm
pulling them out of retirement
they've been out of work
although
she's been working
as a surgeon
putting ears on
earless children
like a surgeon
oh the witness
is about to be killed
her car is stopping
in the middle of the highway
weird lights around
I bet she saw
close encounters
for the third time
yeah I was going to say
this reminds me
of once upon a time
my dad wanted to show me
the movie The Godfather
for the first time
and we got a VHS copy
of it out of the library
and apparently
he got it without looking
and there was braille
all over
the case that it came in
and they put the tape in
and it has
a voiceover
describing the scene
movies for the blind
oh cool
kind of ruined it though
well it's like
subtitles for the blind
yeah
until this day arrives
oh my god
the aliens just came down
and blew up
the cute girl witness
who could have proved everything
I'd like to remind everybody
it was basically
a radio drama
and that was
common many years ago
also they used to have
novels
books on tape
you put them
in your cassette player
in your car
and
the cow was
the cigarette man
is back
is it still
the same actor
he's a manic path now
I don't know
that's got a guy
that he's got a
throat thing now
he's smoking cigarettes
through his throat
that's funny
he's a hideous
scary cancer dog
that's the end of the show
the cancer man
I almost didn't watch it
because
there was a football game
and it made it go late
and that meant
it was hard for me
to call the show
because
damn
television show
was going on too long
did you see what happened
I see what happened
are you wearing pajamas
on me
I'm watching TV
there's commercials on
you know I haven't
experienced this kind of thing
in like 25 years
how about that
I can't imagine
and you know
every night
I've got a favorite show
on every night now
it only took three weeks
or three months
three months
to get me completely
sucked back in
well I don't know
but I have to pay
for this damn thing
oh man
of course it's not a good thing
I've been spending
an hour every night
watching television
instead of playing
video games
and paying for it
that's the worst part man
it's important
television is insidious
I'm telling you
I must
I must reach out
and explain to everybody
only radio is cool
yeah yeah that's it
only radio
yeah you know
I can still do stuff
while I'm uh
listening to the radio
or a podcast
not that I actually
listen to the radio
either in the last 25 years
not even WCSB
no
I like my
my own brain think
that's my problem
or I did
up until
we got
we moved into this house
with television
and now I watch it
every night
well I thought
you'd be a pod popper
by now
instead you've
transgressed into a video
yeah
I know
it's
it's strange
and
it's like a new world
it's
I know now
how everyone else
in America feels
isn't it awful
and
and seduced
by
images
where everything
is all shiny
and
it got
it got a lot shinier
I started slobbering
at a Pizza Hut commercial
about half an hour ago
I realized
oh my god
it's making me salivate
that stretchy cheese
it's making
it's having the effect
it's making me want to call
Pizza Hut
isn't that interesting
it's like
I feel like
I'm a lab rat
in a cage
and yet
it's more interesting
I'm doing what
every other American does
every single night
turn on the TV
and watch some show
I think it's so funny that
sales and like
commercial ideas
have been around
for thousands of years
back to the days
of the
the Greeks
the great classical thinkers
and you know
you can convince people
of anything
using the right stuff
I'm having trouble
following the conversation
because these images
are distracting my eyes
and all it is
is the local Dallas news
I did it
I shut it off
oh it was local
oh you're still in
you're still in Texas
yeah
oh okay
I thought you would come back
yeah
well wouldn't I be
wouldn't I have been there
at the station
if I wasn't still in Texas
I don't know
I think
yeah instead
I had to run tapes
of you guys talking
yeah
no it looks like
we're stuck here
do you think I'm going to
drive back to Ohio
in the way the weather
is right now
there's like
you know
cows raining
from giant tornadoes
of clouds
everywhere
up and all the
all the way along our route
yeah
well the
you know
the monster
snowpocalypse
has come and gone
but that
didn't really hit Cleveland
no
didn't hit Cleveland
didn't hit Cleveland at all
I thought it was interesting
that it affected
so many lives negatively
how they're capitalizing
on like
it's snowing again today
we're going sledding
a lot of people
can't get out of their homes
to go sledding
yeah
that's so weird
go sledding off your roof
they're really selling
this storm
there's very little negative
about this storm
other than it's very powerful
in West Virginia
they got down
now that I'm
indulging in
normal media again
instead of just
only reading
which is what I used to do
for the last 20 years
I've noticed that
everything's scary
all the time
we're surrounded by enemies
the weather is always
about to do something
unbelievable
horrible and dangerous
to all of us
you can't trust anyone
there's thieves
and rapists
coming in from other countries
right and left
mean world syndrome
you go to the supermarket
and you're surrounded
by crazed terrorists
disguised as normal Americans
yes
you understand
the only reason
they don't kill you
is because they're not sure
whether you're one
how things are stacked together
so neatly and sweet
to keep people off their feet
for 20 years
I've been living
in a fool's paradise
where all
the only people
I had to talk to
were subgeniuses
and I didn't have to
go to work
for anyone else
but myself
and I never watched
TV or listened
to the radio
except on very special occasions
and now
I guess I should just stay here
and keep the TV on
and never come back
to Ohio
oh gee
I don't know
because there's a TV
in my house
that doesn't have cable
I could probably get it
I suppose
but
we worked so hard
to avoid that
and now
all those years
of discipline
undone
in just a short time
I can't wait
for the next episode
of The Expanse
on Spotify
Tuesday night
I've heard it called
Game of Thrones
Insight
Space
that's what I've heard
it described as
I call it
my mother-in-law
and I call it
the screwing
in zero gravity show
in fact
the whole network
the sci-fi network
is the
screwing while floating
in the air network
yeah I don't know
it's not zero gravity
it's because of magic
or telekinesis
but all of their trailers
have people screwing
while floating in the air
in slow motion
interesting
for every show
I'm really glad
they've included that
aren't you as well
yeah
just think about
the limitless possibilities
because you could have
like one day
you could have people
screwing in space
and then the next day
you could have people
screwing in space
and just like
say a day after that
you would have people
screwing in space
and so on and so forth
well it's kept me
from changing that dial
well it hasn't kept you
from changing your diapers
has it?
no
continue
and now
let's take one more caller here
and see what they have to say
hello
it's Bob
oh hello Bob
would you like to have dinner?
oh I'm sorry
not tonight
got a date with someone else?
no not a date
I just want to finish
some sketches
somebody there to help?
no just alone
you're making me jealous
don't talk like that Bob
it's not true
call me tomorrow night
about seven
okay
bye
excuse me a second
hello
the electronics department please
hey how you doing?
you're a sound effects man
always fooling around
with electronic devices
fooling around
with the light
tell me
do you suppose robots
would enjoy listening to music?
no
I'm sending you a birthday message
um
you per hosting
Thank you.
Thanks to Rural War Room
for that ear-riping version of the song
The Modern Age.
Boy, howdy, they were so great
at the devotional last year.
Not man, not beast,
but thing.
And the music in the background here
is by Cool Hand
Chris.
And now, back to Radio Synesthesia
and the Brave Brave Callers.
Hello, you're on the air.
Cowards.
Cowards!
It was the beeping
noise caller.
Call and run.
That's how he talks.
He sounds like
meh, meh, meh, meh.
Yeah, so we know
that can be some
alien form of communication
that we can't understand.
Right.
It's a question
of semantical discourse.
If that guy had made
me a little slower,
he would have said,
ugh, you know,
he would have made,
never mind.
Or maybe they're called,
the greys are calling in
to complain about the X-Files.
Who's calling in?
Oh, the greys.
Yeah, you know, I...
To tell the truth,
I was kind of unimpressed.
I actually did...
I can't say that I know
the old show,
but the thing I just watched
seemed awfully old-fashioned
and kind of...
I don't know.
I guess to me,
all this alien
and conspiracy stuff
is so old.
Yeah.
Everybody knows that.
Yeah, no kidding.
Kids are born knowing that stuff.
Why do they act like
it's some big mystery?
And now they've disguised
themselves into
misnomerizing it
and ostracizing it.
And I was just like,
I'm ostracizing every pilgrim
that comes along the way.
I mean, especially when they...
When they take...
You know, they get retro
just for the sake of it
because it represents retro
and their brains are like...
Like ice cubes are like...
They don't move around
very much, you know?
You know, I can't believe
how many...
I noticed...
Like, I don't read much anymore.
I only read this one magazine
called The TV Guide.
And I noticed in that
that, for instance,
the History Channel
was tonight,
was...
Alien Invaders
or Alien Artifacts
all night.
It was an Alien Artifacts marathon
on the History Channel.
The Learning Channel
was Honey Boo Boo all night.
That's Learning now.
And the Science Channel
was, I think,
Loch Ness Monster all night.
So that's Science Night.
This is why I will never
pay for television.
Well, I feel kind of strange
because I actually did
pay for this.
I got the bill
that my dad used to get
and I lowered...
I removed the pay channels
because I can get pornography
for free.
It's not even pornography,
you know, that makes...
If I could just get
the premium channels
and nothing else,
I might actually pay for that,
but...
But what if the...
Well, like I say,
I haven't done this
for years and years and years
and now it's...
I don't know.
I want to say
it's a weird experience,
but it's not at all.
It's very normal.
It's like how I felt
in my summers
in elementary school age.
You'd be staring at a box.
It's a terse emotional situation
and look away
at some commercial.
It's...
There's something weird.
I probably sound
like a crazy man saying,
this television stuff,
it's crazy.
It'll rot your mind.
But I've been...
I started reading articles today
on my phone
about...
about how people
were swearing off
using their phones so much.
Hmm.
And their idea
of swearing off
using the phone so much
was to look up from it
every five minutes.
Yeah, it'll...
Looking at those tiny screens,
it's...
not easy on the eyes.
Oh, I...
Oh, it's bad for your teeth.
iPhone 6 Plus.
Why, it's almost as big as...
It's bigger than
a pack of playing cards
or...
extra long cigarettes.
It's a butt pack.
It's a huge screen.
Well, whose butt
could be bigger than that?
Not just...
If you're permanently...
near-sighted like me,
it's...
Heck, it's panorama.
Hmm.
Cinemascope.
Yeah, if I read stuff
on my phone for too long,
assuming that when I look up,
I become even more near-sighted.
Well, pretty soon,
I won't have to look up at all.
I'll just...
I'll watch it on my TV shows
that I'm newly addicted to
on my phone.
I won't even have to...
And I'll get those diapers
you were talking about earlier.
I'll be set.
Get to...
Yeah, forget about the...
Forget about the...
the screen, man.
Just...
Gotta go with the neural implants
to directly stimulate
your visual cortex.
Yep.
Well, that's expensive
and it still gives people
motion sickness now.
They're gonna...
You're gonna have to...
to...
to put up with just
the halfway measure
of the Oculus
or other VR platforms
or other platforms.
You know, those are...
They started pricing those.
They're gonna be about
400 bucks.
Yeah, the whole
virtual reality thing,
it's...
in its infancy
and it...
You know, what...
I remember back in the 90s
when video games
first started using
3D graphics.
Yeah, me too.
And I've gone back and...
Star Fox was the very first one.
And I think there were
some arcade games
that used polygons
back then too.
But yeah, you know,
I've gone back
and replayed some older games
from, you know,
the earlier generation
of, you know,
3D graphics
and it hasn't aged well.
But it was a necessary step
to get to the point
we're at now
where it's almost photorealistic.
Well, not really.
I mean, I know
it's photorealistic right now,
but I mean...
Almost.
I think the gap
and the marketing gap
is much greater
than you think, fellows.
I think that the...
the Portuguese...
Huh?
I don't understand.
I'm not sure I understand
where you're getting
at either, Dave.
Marketing gap?
I don't see any gap.
It seems to be
wall-to-wall marketing to me.
Oh, well, yes.
I certainly agree with that.
Wall-to-wall marketing.
I meant a gap
in the production
and marketing
of different versions.
One step up,
two steps sideways,
two steps around.
When all could be done
at once
with one swell foop.
My foops are not very swell.
I don't know.
Mine are so...
They're so bad
that they kept me
out of the draft
in the 70s.
My swoops were so bad
that they...
Sorry, you can't be in the Army.
Oh, what a shame.
Well, I had...
Maybe I should go
join the Navy instead.
Hmm.
Well, that was...
I want to join Starfleet.
I used to have a...
What are those
window stickers
that people have for colleges?
I used to have
a Starfleet Academy
window sticker
in the rear window.
No.
That's when I was a kid.
I heard earlier in the show
Dave didn't even know
what the blue screen
of death was.
Yeah.
No, I've been
staring for 20 years.
as you know,
because you saved me
a couple times.
Poor Dave.
He's so old
and out of it.
He doesn't even know
what the blue screen
of death is.
He doesn't know
what the latest
video games are.
Well, let me tell you
what the blue screen
of death was.
I wasn't sure.
I wasn't sure
if I was sure.
You'll find out
what the blue screen
of death is, Dave.
Oh, yes.
Because I can't
win at them.
It's very difficult
for me to win
or to even do
anything normal
on Spazmari.
Well, you have to
go out and get
that computers
for dummies book
and then get the
dummies for computers
card
and then plug
into the matrix
and there you go.
It's all click,
click, click,
wham, bam, bam.
There you are.
But you're saying
that automatically
I'll want to love
video games
when I told you
I have difficulty
with maneuvering.
Right?
in them.
Everybody does.
Not really.
It's just like
I reach a certain point
like I don't really care
even if it looks
like a movie.
You never made it
past that very first
Goomba in Super Mario
levels,
Super Mario World,
Super Mario Brothers
level 1.
You never killed
that person, right?
I know we've come
a long way
as far as noises
are concerned
and making it look
like a car
is actually crashing
into you
and shooting you
with a shotgun
at the same time,
but that's a big
butt you've got
and I wish you
would be tracing
around the windows,
where the apartment
colors can
get a load of it.
However,
and it's a big
however,
I get slack
out of them
anyway.
But I know
I know where
you old people
are coming from,
Dave.
You people,
you old, old people
that are like
three years older
than me.
I was that way too,
but now I'm young.
Do you remember
the movie Zardoz?
Yeah, sure.
You said,
you know,
the movie Zardoz
is the place
where we're coming from.
It's the hidden city.
And you know,
the place where
we're coming from
is definitely
outside the dome.
It's true.
I mean,
we do have barbarians.
Let's face it, boys.
We're not going
to be inside the dome.
You do understand
that, right?
We're going to be
we are outside
the dome
and we're going
to remain
outside the dome.
They're not going
to let us
in the dome.
They might throw
us guns
and tell us
our penises are bad
and they might send
giant heads
with pipes
to guide us.
But we're not
going to be getting
into the dome.
Beware the false pipes.
Yeah, beware
the false pipes
and the big heads
with no pipes.
But either way,
the dome,
the folks
are in the dome.
They're not letting
anybody else in.
But they're all
old and stinky
and they think
they're smart and sweet
in the dome,
under the dome.
Well,
you know,
they may be bored
and crazy,
but they're still
not going to let us in.
We need no dome.
Well, maybe
they might let
Sean Connery in
if he has a silly
enough looking outfit.
We can get Devo
to make energy domes
for us.
Yeah, we can make
our very own dome
and we wouldn't
let any of them
come in there
on punishment
of pulling
their scabs
off or something.
Something really,
you know,
like water
and water
or toothpaste
or something.
Well, I don't think
even Devo can get
inside the dome.
I bet Mark Mothersbaugh
thinks he's going
to get in the dome
at the last minute.
Danny Elfman
will get in
right in front of him
and then they'll slam
the door and go,
sorry, Mark.
No, you and Pee Wee Herman
are going to have
to stay outside the dome.
Well, it's Pee Wee
and you and Dan
and all those
other losers.
All right,
let's bring one more
caller on.
You're on the air.
Hey, I have a question.
Okay.
So, those other guys
calling in,
do they really talk
like that in real life?
Yes, they do.
I have met all three
of them in person before
and they look
just like they sound, too.
Are you referring to us?
Are you referring
to each other?
I've got a house.
Hey, can you play
something by heart?
What do you want
to hear by heart?
I don't know,
anything you're
in the mood for.
Do you normally,
do you normally
listen to this show?
What?
Do you normally
listen to this show
that's on right now?
Here and there,
yeah, a little bit.
Abnormally.
I was going to guess
that it wasn't
a regular part
of your routine.
I don't really
take requests
on this show
and I don't think
I've ever played
anything by heart
on this show before.
Maybe that's
the Friday night show
I'm thinking of.
Hmm.
Could be.
It's Sunday night,
you should be
in church, young lady.
What?
This late?
It's only going to be
Sunday night
for another,
another 17 minutes here.
Yeah, but I'm in Texas
and it's Sunday for me.
I've got to work
until,
for another hour
and a half almost.
Breaking the Sabbath?
Well,
you're working.
That's my job.
That's right.
You know what just
occurred to me
the other day?
I,
I got a text message
from somebody
that said,
sup?
Like,
S-U-P
with a question mark?
And I thought,
I thought they meant
to say, like,
what's up?
And I took that as,
oh,
are you inviting me
to a late dinner?
Like,
would you like to sup?
Sup with me,
please.
No,
nobody likes a literalist,
Dr. Sinister.
I just like it
when a phrase can have,
when a word can have
multiple meanings.
I know,
I know.
I do that to people,
too.
Well,
maybe you
might have just
misunderstood
and thought that was
an actual
frame of reference.
Sup?
Mm-hmm.
Um,
I found myself
typing the phrase
K-T-H-X
for okay,
thanks,
or K-bye,
and even using
emojis,
which I never,
ever did
in my previous life
before I,
I joined the Matrix.
And now I'm,
not only can I
use emojis,
I can call it
clips for movies
to illustrate
my point
when I don't want to
go to the trouble
of speaking
my text message.
To someone.
You know,
the whole, uh,
K-thanks thing,
and, yeah,
I don't know,
I think I've only ever
used those to be
snarky, like...
Right.
I like the poop emoji.
It's a turd
with a smiley face.
Right.
Yeah.
It is very popular
right now.
Did you know
the true story,
the first three letters
sent across the internet
were LOL?
No.
For real.
Yes.
What was this?
Um,
I don't know,
was it 1969
or early,
you know,
the first time
they hooked up computers
over, uh,
telecom networks?
Yeah, but it didn't mean
lacking out well.
No, it didn't mean that,
but those were the first
three letters sent over
because the first
command line,
you get a command line
prompt.
What you had to do
back in...
LOL, LOL, LOL, LOL.
Yeah, what you had to do
back in the old days
was you get a, um,
a command prompt
and you would type
in the word log
to log into
the computer
you were trying to access.
So they typed in
the letters L,
they typed in the letter O,
and then their computer crashed.
So they had to reboot
the computer
and then they
typed in log.
So the third one
was another L,
their second attempt
at typing in the word log.
You're so believable,
but I think it might be
poo-poo.
I'm not sure,
but I think you made that up.
I didn't make it up.
I heard it somewhere.
I don't know if it's true or not.
If it was made up,
it was not made up by me.
So you had a very percent
anecdotal,
just like,
where's the fruit and egg sauce?
You're going to need
an antidote after listening
to my anecdotes for a while.
It's puerile.
Puerile.
I like that word.
Are there still four people
on the phone?
Yes, there are.
Okay, then I'm going to
call, follow my sword
so someone else can call in.
Have a great week, everybody.
All right, thank you, Mark.
What a noble guy.
Look at the blood.
His sacrifice
shall not be in vain.
Oh, I think we lost Dave, too.
Dave was already lost.
Oh, no, I hung up on Dave.
That was my mistake.
Dave was lost.
Hello, you're on the air.
Hello, you are on the air.
Uh-oh.
Those rat bastards.
Those hang-up things
kill my ear.
I can barely hear
some things like Dave.
I can hear you perfectly well.
Those hang-ups,
they come through to us callers
as a sudden sharp knife
in the ear.
I've only got one good ear.
Yeah.
There it went.
It's gone now.
When a functional technology
becomes obsolete, obsolete,
obsolete, obsolete, obsolete,
obsolete, obsolete,
it can then become our...
...
obsolete, obsolete.
We are obsolete, obsolete.
We are obsolete, obsolete we are obsolete, obsolete.
We are.
Yay!
...
Rubber buns.
Rubber bands scare radio pods
Have replaced our broken hearts
Things will never be the way they used to be
Elevating through technology
A clockwork brain, alphanumeric thoughts
Synthetic skin, but never once
Things will never be the way they used to be
Better living through technology
I'm so neat
We are
We've found the keys to remove the locks
We've opened up Pandora's box
Things will never be the way they used to be
Better living through technology
We are obsolete by the Fantastic Plastics,
another band that put on a great visual show at the Devotional in Cleveland.
Great fun for those of us who are old, but not obsolete.
And now, from Lemur, the news.
From NPR News in Washington, I'm selling their mother for fun.
At least the fighting began.
Israeli Prime Minister Netanyahu said that Israel wants tunnels.
Netanyahu said a threat of PR news from the sky is not acceptable.
I'm inside two separate underground militarized neutral one-day tunnels
under a sparked strip step in Jerusalem.
Police in Philadelphia say they were selling fruit on a corner in other crimes.
Well, the numbers aren't in yet.
The second during the first three of the year, around a 3-3 as opposed to the 2-2 quarter.
The .9 first quarter as opposed to the second quarter.
On Wall Street, 22-16-942.
Federal Appeals Court has ruled that block-shaped steel atheists
may be sexually assaulted in a family dollar tree.
Benjamin Netanyahu says you're listening to PR News in Washington.
Hello, you're on the air.
Good evening, Dr. Sosa. This is the management calling.
Always good to hear from the management. What's going on?
The midget. The midget's face.
I just want to let you know your show's doing okay tonight.
I give it a B, B-plus rating.
I think you can do a little better, but ultimately I'm going to give you a pass
and I'll let you be on the air next week because management always knows what's best
and I think that the listeners need more of your show.
Well, screw you, dude. You don't know what you're talking about.
This show sucks.
I always know what I'm talking about.
We gotta B.
B-B-W-6-B-B-C.
This show is terrible.
The listeners hate it.
And I'm just doing it to spite them.
Well, whatever your gimmick or shtick is, I like the program.
I give it my blessing.
Continue on.
Yeah, I talk softly and I carry a big shtick.
Well, whatever you want to call it, you're doing fine.
It's good.
Oh, Dr. Sosa, your shtick is good.
I hope that everybody who's listening is going to vote for Trump
because we need to take America back.
We need to make it great again.
Oh, you're just another Trump chump.
It's going to be huge.
It's going to be a huge, huge success.
I'm sure it'll be a huge success.
You know what's funny is a lot of polls so far show
Bernie Sanders actually doing better in a general matchup
against Donald Trump than Hillary Clinton does.
Those polls are flawed.
I've been working with Trump a long time.
They're flawed.
Trump's going to win.
He's going to make this country great again.
It's going to be awesome.
It's going to be a great country.
Once again, and we can all rest assured that Donald Trump will save us
from the enemies, wherever they may be.
He's going to do a great thing.
Right.
America will grate our enemies up like grated cheese.
We'll grate up the Mexicans.
We'll grate up the Canadians.
We'll grate them all up in the great chipper of anger,
of middle class frustrated anger.
He's not going to do that.
He's just going to make America great again.
I don't know how.
Are you saying America is not great now?
I'm saying he's going to make it greater.
It's a treason.
Why do you hate America?
Nobody hates America.
Everybody loves America.
Some are doing a little better than others.
We want to make it great for everybody.
Why do you hate our freezers?
Except for Muslims.
We're not going to make it great for Muslims.
That's not true.
And Italians and Mexicans and Texans.
We'll need to build a wall.
We'll build a wall around Ohio.
That's it.
And we'll make the Canadians pay for it.
No.
We'll make the Kentucky and Pennsylvania pay for it.
We should just put like a bunch of electric, like electrical stuff in the Ohio River.
Let's not.
Yeah.
Electric eels in the Ohio River.
Like a moat.
A moat full of electric eels.
We'll make the Russians pay for it.
There we go.
We're good.
We're negotiators.
That's all you need.
You got to have good negotiating skills.
And if they don't like your deal, then you kill them, you kill their families.
You kill their children.
You kill their mothers.
You kill all of them.
Yeah.
You got to rip it out root and stem.
If you don't kill them, they're going to hate you.
Yeah.
It's just like wiping out vermin in your home.
Sure, you can kill all the bugs, but if there's still eggs left behind that you didn't destroy,
that's why you got to kill the babies too.
If you don't kill them, they think less of you.
That's right.
They know that you're just weak.
Well, you know, I've said before, if you vote Dr. Sinister for president, all right, I'm
running on a single issue platform.
Dr. Sinister for president.
If you elect me president, I promise you on day one at 12.01 PM, I'm going to skip the
inauguration ceremony and everything.
I'm just going to have the chief justice there in the oval office waiting for me.
I'll take the oath of office.
No pomp and circumstance.
And then at 12.01 PM on January 20th, 2020, I'm going to have the chief justice there
in 2017.
I'm going to press the big red button.
I will launch all of our nukes simultaneously.
I will make us the nation to end all nations.
Literally.
I promise you nuclear annihilation.
That is my one campaign issue.
I can no longer support that idea.
So as long as you don't go with that idea, I...
My advice to everyone, my advice to everyone will be to gather in very small groups, and
various population centers.
And we try to get as many people crammed into as few places as possible.
So as many people as possible can get the mercy of being at ground zero.
It's better to be vaporized instantly than die of radiation poisoning.
The management does not support this idea, but...
Well, guess what?
We're kicking the management out.
That's right, man.
We're taking this station back from people like you.
Hello, you're on the air.
Thanks.
Oh, shut up.
You suck.
We're going to destroy all the non-people.
We'll build a wall around...
That last call was such an idiot.
...and make WCS be great again.
It will grate on the ears of the listeners like it used to.
Yes.
An hour ago during our slot.
Yeah, yeah.
I haven't played enough noise lately.
I should play some more noise.
Well, if...
I think we might be getting close to the end of the program here.
Nobody else seems to be...
I think we're going to have to call it a day.
...on calling in.
Praise Bob in his mercy.
Well, praise his sacred scribe as well.
Thank you, Reverend Stang, for your call tonight.
Oh, yeah.
That's what I say to everyone.
That's right.
Oh, yeah.
Como va?
Sex music.
Oh, yeah.
All right.
Well, thank you very much.
We'll talk to you soon, I hope.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
All right.
You got that.
This is how you ride.
Hey.
Will you ride this?
Yeah.
fundo wel compounds tutaj
Di  ey
Huh, this
Oh, my God.
It is.
Today we're heading to Gaston!
Gaston!
Today we're hauling aqua cola!
Aqua cola!
And today we're going to see the news!
Mother's milk!
You've been listening to the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
For free information, write to P.O. Box 181417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118
or see www.subgenius.com
Praise Bob!