that we are in a decade of change we may be in a decade of convulsion and upheaval
and therefore the biggest thing you can do to prepare for the 90s is to build your own ship
marvelous things can happen to you despite what's going on around you
i would recommend very strongly that everyone read the book of the subgenius
disease and pestilence
stalking the land the arrow and the terror taking place by day or by night a warfare
confusion and the bible says that the one who dwells in the secret place of the most
most high bob and gets and will be he or she who actually does finally
get some yes yes bob's promise rings true
please tell them that i am god
welcome potential initiates and remain with us for the next 30 minutes
welcome to the subgenius radio ministry
hour of
sponsored by the church
you are a god
to them
to obey me like they did the father
who is god number one
bob bob bob is god number one
is the father
or should they obey
praise bob
him
no no not papa joe
no not dr legume no
you see there must be a god number one
bob is god number one
one
as Gideon says
i am called
as r treated as felix
Cao po
as you know
june
armed
arms not covered with her
main lead like among teenagers faced like
our their
chorus are much accent youth who's setting me up withrets it's like a mars essentially
monkey. And his bald-headed
pate. His bald-headed pate. Now Bob has all of a sudden gone bald.
I never knew he was despilado. Well, he was wearing a wig all that time.
His bald-headed fate. So is that true about his pipe actually
being part of one of his teeth, the proboscis teeth on the front canine
that actually has a radio transmitter? Oh, it goes way much deeper.
The shank of the pipe has
some sort of tissue that actually grows all the way into
Bob's brain. Up through his sinuses
and directly into the brain of Bob. If you yank that pipe out,
it would probably kill him.
If you yank the pipe out, doesn't the pipe have a direct link right on back to the Big Bang as well?
Right. The pipe is the excess connection.
A lot of people think that it's not really Bob who's running the show.
You would unwrap.
You would unravel the fabric of the universe itself.
The switchboard would blow.
Right. It would be like pulling out that one thread that holds everything together.
If you blew Bob's sinuses, everything would go like Y2K is not going to go.
That would be the end of it. But who'd want to suck out Bob's nostrils to end the world anyway?
Are these the shadowy figures here?
I hear a Bob song coming out.
Bob.
It can be the heroine.
He's no slob.
Bob.
He's no fool.
A fool.
Yeah.
What a stool.
He is the head of the subgenius church.
And he is super cool.
Bob.
He's no fool.
He is the head of the subgenius church.
And he is super cool.
Hi, Sandy.
I'll take it easy.
Thank you.
Good night.
Mom, Dad, Mom, Dad, Mom, Dad, Mom, Dad
Yeah, I just want you to know about the evils of drug use
Good, we need to hear that, we'll love you
Fortunately, we haven't taken any tonight, but this morning
Fortunately
That's right
We've cleansed our system with Bob
Do you need any of these evils, or do you have...
No, I'm glad saved, not evil
Ah, does thou taketh or does thou giveth away?
I know that you wonder why so many nice subgenius songs
Well, that's Glass Madness
He's the one responsible for all the nice sub-dinis
The ones that sit around the campfires and swap stories and...
And hollow Bob pills
That's right, and hollow planets
And senior Bob songs
Some of them even come from Planet X, but not a whole lot of them
Not enough to worry about, and certainly not enough to be vaccinated this year
So don't worry about it, but if you see them
You're seven
Subgenius
A bladed windbreaker will suffice
Another idea
Know that you've seen a very rare bird, because a nice subgenie is a rare subgenie
Um, do you have something to share with us?
I'm afraid that he's lost his name
No, he's gonna talk any second now
Here it comes
He has a message
Bob has touched this moment
It's me, rare subgenie
Yeah, what is it?
Huh?
Okay, Bob
Yeah?
What happened to your church?
What happened to it?
Got old
You mean the special...
It's growing, it's growing even now as you speak
The special introductory version or the...
Doug, can you show them the church on camera three, please?
Here we go
Bring it up, yeah
Now there is the church building as we saw it in the blueprints as the architect designed it
Is that what you call a close-up?
That's right
No, no, the close-up's camera four
Doug, switch over there
Okay, here we go
Yeah, there
Now that's the inside of the church
There's the stained glass windows of the Bob face
There's the mighty pipe
You have to be careful about, you know, something to watch out for
Well, it is, it's important
It's a classic neo-mythos
Yeah
Any of the rules for play
Like, neo-religion
Okay, don't forget the mutant player takes the first turn
Of, uh, you know, yeah
Yeah, the mutant player has to set up by placing at least one mutant counter in each of the
boxes surrounding the building area
That's this building
It doesn't matter if some of the boxes have more than one mutant counter as long as each
box has at least one
That's, uh, that's the human player on the other hand, uh
There's a musician
Oh, there is no musician player in this game
Ah, yes, dear friends
An amazing old recording
Uh, from, uh, gosh, when, uh, KPFA subgenius show 92782
Wow
Yeah, that's one of the very early, that's before Hour of Slack
There was the KPFA show, uh, there in, in Berkeley
And, uh, oh, where was my background music from last week?
Friends, everything is done
It's different now
Everything has changed a little
Well, not all that much
You'll see
I think Dave has to do this commercial first
Tonight is being brought to you by the forces of evil
We'll bring you the world government's religions and corporations
And by Moonpants Emporium
When you've gotta go, you've gotta go
And the best part is, you can't do it without me
And I love a lot of them
Oh, I love you
We're gonna do a fun show
Can you get down and tell me A detour of Earth
I've never seen you during, like, your days
Or for a couple d explore it
Well, I just want to see your organ
I'm not ready yet
All I ever think about
Is coming here
And I really like your candy
So, I'm gonna do a bit of yup
Ok, my hot dog
It's down and about
Get off before it owls
Into this
Yes dear friends, lonesome cowboy Dave sings and hollers away in the holler of the new
times and the old puzzling evidence and glass madness show hollered away there in the old
times and friends things are...
Well I can't believe what I did with Jesus.
Let me put it that way.
We moved the subgenius foundation headquarters to another part of the complex.
Moved the whole dang thing and I have built my own ship all over again.
A brand new ship here in Dallas, Texas.
But everything's wonderful.
It's wonderful here.
I've got a new commander.
I've got a new command module you see with the attitude controls.
You can hear those as things jitter when I click the attitude, not altitude controls,
attitude controls.
And my computer and keyboard and everything are right behind me so that whenever I add
something new to the show I can type it in.