well
yep
going some cowboy days
trying to get here
good night boys and girls
good night
look out for them gopher holes Dave
good night Austin Texas wherever you are
oh Dave
Dave look out for that bog water
look at that look out for those mud puddles
made of sulfuric acid Dave don't put your foot in there
Dave look out for that nuclear testing range
Dave
don't drive too close to the
perinuclear power plant
we've told you that over
and over Dave look out for that
canyon Dave look out for that mountain
oops a cactus oh a heel monster
oh a giant tarantula crawling
out from behind that butte
hour of slack
sponsored by the church of the subgenius
the subgenius hour of slack
that you are about to do is specially designed only to be made
on real social media and only
for the public
the audience is listening
the audience is never
listening
those days were so so
so happy for all of us but now
there is no joy no one listens
the audience is
talking and chatting
yakking and critiquing
gossiping
they're picking apart our every trigger word
oh they're not even doing that much
they're talking about their boyfriends and girlfriends
they're picking their noses
then there are half triggers
and three quarters
to fuel their conversation
it's so foolish
there's nothing for you to say
just sit down on the diva
just sit there
sit down on this
diva
have a seat on this
that's you isn't it there
on the top of page 26
embracing the squid
you've seen this before haven't you?
you were there weren't you?
please enjoy your journey
the company wishes you an entertaining experience
that's not me man
I'm glad I work for the company
and the company
is glad it works for you
now don't you sleep you little bastards
yes
people who are disgruntled
with the company often say things like that
especially when they're
stuck in a labyrinth beneath Langley
Virginia for hours and hours
Maurice
innych
bringing along the
cochrane
hello
What's my baby?
My baby?
You've got to believe me.
I have to believe it.
I don't want to be a slave.
You've got to believe me.
Doc, this is one of the finest specimens we've ever found, but it doesn't usually grow around here.
As you know, it's part animal and part bitch.
Wow, it's like Hendrix, man.
Doctors took off.
Huh? What?
Are you being serious right now, or are you just on the show?
The doctors are always on the show seriously. What do you mean?
I don't know what I mean.
I don't want to hear anymore.
Well, I don't know what I mean either.
He took the form and the...
He pulled it out and tore it up on the floor.
And you said, are you serious or are you just being on the show?
And I said, at the same time...
There's many, many things happening.
I did get a request at the same time.
Oh, Bob, turn down the sound effects, too.
I've got to get the directions to my house.
Okay, listener, now, where is it that we live?
How do I get there?
I guess you drive down one of the main streets until you hit Berkeley.
Wow.
Got it. Dead center.
Those primitive peasants didn't believe our story,
but they believed it when the mushroom cloud blasted them off the island.
And we've got to ask you about that.
By the time I got to Dockstock...
Tell me that Bob may rip.
I asked him, why are you alive?
Hey, Dock.
Dead center.
What are those orange lights on the inside of the helmet?
That's because you pissed in the suit, remember, at the beginning of the flight?
Oh, no, that was at the beginning of the movie, and everybody moved away from me in the seat.
Yeah, I know.
Well, remember that whole thing where you're riding on the horse and you see the jet and you get sucked in the front?
Oh, yeah.
Right, okay, well, that's...
We've got to keep them in house.
I don't like this movie.
Yes, there's the director.
Okay, hold on.
Hold on, you guys.
What's up, genius?
Let's let the caller decide who will live.
And who dies?
Shall we put little greetings to death in the space capsule,
or puzzling evidence down in the control room?
Shall he suffer the same?
We'll ask you, our caller.
Now, hold on to the phone.
Okay, they're very far.
Ah!
Scared away by the light.
Okay, that caller.
Come on, guys, let's drive down Shattuck Avenue real fast.
This station's hard to steer.
Okay.
It's space war at last.
Listen to those particle beams.
They're sweeping the skies.
Yeah, we'll find a parking place for sure now.
Ah, yes, dear friends.
Welcome to the subgenius radio ministry hour of slack,
and in this case, possibly one of the most disconnected,
weirdest,
most unplanned and disorganized shows ever in subgenius history.
And who knows?
That may make it one of the greatest.
It certainly makes it one of the holiest and most divine,
even if it's sort of terrible,
which it probably won't be.
Although this show is actually composed of outtakes, dear friends,
not necessarily things that were too godawful to use on the hour of slack,
things that we were about to use.
But for whatever reason,
they didn't fit into that particular show we'd been looking at using them for,
and so they got shuffled off into these folders here.
These are computer files now, you see, instead of little cassette tapes.
And I've got a folder on my screen here marked holding.
Why, it's got a bunch of Einstein Secret Orchestra Swamp Radio,
but it's special sections with Bleepo Abernathy and Popes Lilith.
We also have another section of bleeding head of Arnold Palmer oriented stuff
from the old KNON subgenius show with G. Gordon Gordon and Dr. Philodrummond
and puzzling evidence on a special last show of the millennium on KPFA, Berkeley.
And yet in this other folder called Miscellaneous Outs, I have...
Well, no, those are X-rated and I can't play them.
But...
I know that there's some pretty weird in-betweens there.
And then yet there's this other folder marked,
Don't ever play this on the air.
And that's the one I'm most excited about.
I have no idea what's in it,
although it appears to have some ancient KPFA puzzling evidence
and Dr. Howell dinosaur oriented slack material.
Hmm.
So I guess this will be...
The...
Arnold Palmer-saurus miscellaneous show of gas music from Jupiter.
We literally have some of that.
And I've got some Nazi band music here.
We've got some trance weirdness by Zeeza.
We've got part of Susie the floozy's rant in Tampa and God only knows what other.
Friends, I don't know.
I don't know.
I'm doing all of this talking ahead of time.
And after this, we'll just dive right in and see what happens.
Your guest is as good as mine.
Praise Bob and hail Connie.
You are listening to the subgenius radio ministry hour of slack.
And if you need more information about this show and the word of Bob
or the artists involved who are torturing themselves for Bob,
check out our website.
www.subgenius.com
Or write with an actual pen and paper and a stamp.
Use the post office and write to Bob himself at post office box 140306.
That's box 140306 in Dallas, Texas.
75214.
And that's where Jesus lives.
Jesus and his beautiful wife, Mary Magdalene and their little child, Conbo.
And they process your orders after they've been pre-processed by Reverend Nikki Death Chick.
And then parts of your orders are actually filled by yours truly, Reverend Ivan Sang.
I pray over those people.
I pray over love offerings that you send in, friends.
I'll sleep...
I spread them across my bed and I sleep on them and I know them.
I know them.
I think you know me when you know what I'm saying.
This music in the background is Einstein Secret Orchestra with Ron Slabe
performing at a Winter Star Symposium in February.
Sponsored by ACE.
You might check their website. It's really interesting.
At www.rosencomet.com
Oh, yeah.
www.rosencomet.com
I'm by the barbecue.
Hello.
Good place.
I told you the next time I caught you and your son dynamite fishing,
I'd throw your sorry ass in jail.
And I meant it.
And now McGraw-Hill has printed 15,000 copies of the collected teachings of Bob.
Many times have I said that, yes, you may spend $20 to join the Church of Bob,
and you may be staggered at the enormity of this sum,
or you might spend $9.95 for the book or buy the book.
I'll just subgeniusly go on McGraw-Hill and better books for everywhere.
But the $9.95 you spend for that book,
you'll get so much more for your money than you would get if you spent $9.95
in any other pink conspiracy meaningless book, record, movie.
You will be ashamed of yourself.
Why, children, you go out and put that $4.95 down for a copy of Hollywood Wives.
You read it, and you are ashamed of yourself,
and you go,
You're being that sick pink conspiracy juicing.
But you put $9.95 down for the book of the subgenius,
and I defy you, children, to finish that book.
I defy you to read every word and absorb every illustration of that book.
I've had my copy for nine on ten months, and I haven't done it yet.
It sold 50,000 copies on publication day.
Over a century later, it became the phenomenon of the London and New York states.
Perhaps we ought to clear up something about the book.
You might find it in the humor section,
and this is just completely wrong.
It's the conspiracy.
It's the conspiracy in action.
It should be in the religion section.
I found my copy in the religion section in the Golden Butts downtown.
It should be in the cooking section.
It should be in the home building section.
It should be in the pet section.
I mean, there's nothing funny about that book.
There's nothing untrue about that.
There's nothing funny about it either.
I mean, it's all true.
It's all funny, right?
Pick up all of the many copies there, or a few, hopefully,
and move them to the really bad part.
It just might just save your brain and your soul and your mental life for the next ten years.
Ten million years.
It might just make you aware of the fact that you're a human being instead of a little meat machine.
We don't even want to talk about that, right?
We don't want to talk about expanding your imagination.
You're thinking for yourself.
God forbid.
You're not asleep.
You're perfectly awake.
No, you haven't been programmed.
No.
This whole stuff isn't confusing to you at all, right?
No, that's the way it goes.
It's just a big joke.
It only takes a few seconds to stare at the fabulous mystic diagram on the back of the book of the subgenius,
but once you stare...
I'm already...
You will be transformed into another world.
Yes, Jehovah One has yet two other books that are coming out.
And they'll sometimes pelt the earth with strangeness.
His angels are eons of the green energy art demons.
Yes, the art demons scribble stuff all over the pages
and spread it all over the airwaves and media waves.
But we must do more.
We need money for ammo, coaching, housing, and surgery
for the gifted young and old ministers who have sworn to protect America
against the conspiracy machine throughout the 1980s.
Yes, that was Nemoji the Malay.
He's an Asian, telling you about the short-term effects of membership in the church
or foundation of the subgenius.
Thank you, Sahib.
And I would also like to say, buy the book of the subgenius from McGraw Hill.
Yes, ten times his normal size, he runs around from radio station to radio station
trying to show you what it is to talk about the tilting boxcar of Dobbs.
Bob is the real thing.
He came to re-fertilize your sexual preconceptions
to make us all relieve our reincarnality in the million polyverse combinations we once enjoyed.
Sure, this church drips with...
There's no irony with insanely overblown cajones.
This religion isn't for the amalgamation of the sexes.
No, but it sure is as hell for the divine union of them.
And so, as you can see from this model here,
the eyeballs actually do pop out of the skull.
And then you swallow each eyeball.
It's a clip to the camera.
It's what's called the abugada.
And it enables you to look inside your own esophagus.
Here, check this out.
Check out the skull.
Pop the eyeball.
Now, you can thoroughly examine the soul after popping the eyeball of each one of these delightful eyeballs.
Harry, what color is this one right here?
Well, this one's modeled after the Campbell's Soup children of the 1950s.
I noticed that they had that kind of like Warholish look to them,
that sunshine and goober's face, the brown hair and purple eyes.
They have the red rosy cheeks.
I noticed...
And, well, okay, and we basically made them this way to make them seem safe.
Well, they are definitely not safe, though.
I mean, that's the thing that's important to remember.
Don't really have to come to the...
It spins, too.
Yes, it does, Popas.
Whee!
It spins because we felt it was safer that the consumer would be able to use something that rotated on its axis
rather than have sharp edges like the other objects.
Well, hopefully some of these objects can kill, kill, kill children with a single...
But what good is removing the sharp object?
I mean...
Well...
Wow.
The other, you know, the cameras that you can swallow,
did you see this on television perhaps recently that there are small cameras,
capsule cameras you can swallow to guide scientists through the开始 track?
So you're saying that for humans we should have smooth cameras as well as smooth cameras for Fimmins,
for women, for Germans, for really all the races.
We want to embrace all races.
At one time?
Wow.
I think you just want to embrace everything that moves at one time.
You sound like a fornicator in disguise.
And it's a very thin disguise.
Many people, that's because of the bad reputation that was set up by the scientific community
that was in our office before from the other administration.
But we assure you, none of our members fornicated any time.
Now, has science given fornication a bad name or is this just another administration ploy?
Well, it's in my...
Damn, the drawer is glued shut.
I was going to show you this file here, but someone glued the drawer shut from the previous administration.
Don't worry.
Well, I think...
Okay, oh, thank you.
That should work quite well.
That should come right out.
It smells horrible, too.
Don't look into the flame.
And now, can you get in there now?
I noticed you're...
Okay.
All right.
You haven't suffered any major burning or anything?
You're just...
No.
Okay, what's...
Okay, the metal just evaporated.
It's cool.
Hey, hey, listen to me.
Yes, we're listening to you right now.
Yes.
Does it hurt?
What?
When you pee, does it hurt?
Well, doesn't...
Well...
Of course it hurts.
It's supposed to hurt.
That's a very colloquial way of putting it, sir.
My friend, if you pee the way I pee, you will always hurt.
The previous administration peed regularly, and that's why we closed off the toilet.
Because we don't want people doing dirty things like going to the bathroom.
Yeah, can we just say pee on the radio?
Well, can you...
This is a safe space.
It's a great office.
It's a great space.
Everybody wins.
Pay!
No, I see all this.
They've got...
No, I am really fed up.
I close my eyes and get in very friendly.
It's your own fault.
My thoughts have wings, and these winging thoughts can take me away any time I want.
I'm sorry.
These rumors about the administration peeing freely throughout the halls of Congress
are in some other way lubricating the gears,
and letting off rich folk who don't need to be get off in the fix.
We just will listen to you, but we embrace you.
Is that all right?
What a soft, sweet embrace.
I can feel the large need.
People who say that we're not compassionate or open-minded,
they're just uncompassionate, open-minded people without a faith.
It's not pornography, officer.
It's empowerment.
Officer, dang.
As Bleepo Abernathy once put it,
D-Mitarian Betilla don't see any grandämäしま
Well dit.
They can see me you going around pickled.
Wish you, your imperial presence,
mayatus et Road!!!
Pat download
Adarchely
And to everyone who answers
Solely
Omn mastodon
Yeah, I am the river, man
Lookin' for females of American style, yeah
I am the next in line
I'm all for that fuckin' idea, yeah
One, two, three, four
But that's old age thinking.
What we need in the book is music like this, scary.
Yeah!
Music like this, happy.
Wow!
Music like this, crowd offense.
I haven't been so high since 1969.
Hey, I don't know, it's, uh, look, everything's slanting down to a...
Melting!
Oh, they're all on the floor.
Yes, the 60s are just a pile on the floor now.
But fortunately,
we've been able to piece them together.
You see, they ask us,
how we manage to make these reconstructions using just one bone?
Well, the answer is that even on your body,
muscles make deep spasms or scars in the bone.
And from these, we're able to distinguish the amount of flexion
that might exist beneath the skin.
Now, as for the skin,
we know these creatures have an integument of feathers
or of cheese or scaly rind,
an outer epiphropulodermis, as one might call it.
How exactly does this all fit into the scary part?
Well, I'm sure you know.
I'm afraid to tell you that these creatures,
as we call them, are not dead.
They live no longer in the faith of reason,
but they lurk outside our universe,
waiting always to enter and reclaim their former domain.
Sure are weird-looking.
This is classified information.
Do you want to let this out on the air?
Take the sludge and turn it into a sloth.
Speak to me of sludge!
I'm a no-go!
Slit the throat rather than mention sludge.
Sludge.
Yuck, it's cinema!
Shoot up in the little magic machine here.
This is the part where the tape is placed in here
and it's going backwards through the heads
and it's all twisted up and stretched around the ceiling.
Hard for the signal to be okay on here,
but even the TV's hard to make it through.
Don't look down!
Don't go upstairs.
Don't go out of the house.
It's only a movie.
It's not real.
It's Yard Man.
Don't go in the waiting pool.
Yard Man cuts off your toe with a lawnmower.
Sorry, ma'am.
Sorry, yes, ma'am.
No.
Don't look in the woodpile.
Stay out of the forest.
Keep away from the junkyard.
Don't look in the scrap heap.
Stay away from the gazebo.
It's only a movie.
Keep telling yourself it's not real.
It's not really happening.
You won't believe the horror.
You won't believe the terror.
But it's all real.
Even the records try to escape this show.
Oh, yes, they try to roll out the door, but we catch them.
Force them back on the turntables.
Actually, there's a copy of this show.
Let's go smurfing, okay?
Yeah.
Hey, pass me that fin.
Hey, I'm going to find some ketchup on my smurf.
Hey, the original smurfers were...
Well, if you can't disprove them, then I'm going to be forced to take them to court.
...eight legs and no harassment.
But you know, over the millennia of time, they evolved into the cross-opterygiites and double-tray fish.
Yes, and those were used for food by higher-ups.
And baits to catch the large pig smurfs, which basked unknowing in the Cenozoic seas.
Unknowing?
Listen to those poor souls yowling in the...
Hell of a...
Let's go back to the beach for a while.
Yes.
There we go.
Don't you wish you knew how to get to the subgenius beach party?
Don't you wish you could paddle with those useless legs now that you're a dinosaur in the wrong world?
While out to sea, the gigantic Archelon and Fastotoclonosaurus, mentioned in official subgenius literature,
cavorts with beach bunnies on sandy shores.
Where is this beach party? Is it in Santa Cruz?
Well, it was in Houston last week, and this morning it'll be in San Francisco.
San Francisco.
Near Fort Mason.
Ah, what time?
About nine o'clock.
It starts tonight.
Hey, listen, don't release this valuable information on the air.
We don't want every poll bucket down on our...
Well, the thing is, there are only probably 11 people listening right now.
Should I bring my hat and my gun?
Two of them are about ready to turn their radios off.
The other five will about get something to eat.
Well, I'll tell you, we're down to have a bottle of Irish rum right now.
That's disgusting.
The young dinosaurs today...
The young dinosaurs, as we all know, perish from an excess or effluent of Yakima chismo.
Well, actually, I believe in living and let live and leaving these...
Marvelous beasts alone.
Their chicken-like skin is too hard for the standard taxidermic application.
Calm down now.
You'll be all right.
Your phone's just taking control of you, but if you...
It's all right.
If you sit down, you'll be better.
Are you going to ban this and going to mate it up with an elephant?
Hey, that wouldn't work.
That would not work.
That's a rather perverse and disgusting suggestion, and I'm rather surprised that you would order it over the radio.
Remember, there are...
This is a family broadcast.
We have people listening whose patronage we'd like to cultivate.
Is this a joke?
You can take your indecent sexual bestial suggestions, mister, and just pack them off to Poughkeepsie.
The End
magazines and the tapes and so forth, half of them out there aren't really sub-GNI at all.
Listen to those phones.
They're pathetically trying to reach us.
They have things they have to tell us.
They want to be healed.
They hate us.
They want to kill us.
They want to love us.
They want to ask us how we do it.
Mostly they want us to loan them money, which is...
And they want us to shut up about Prairie Squid because they're embarrassed.
Oh, they turn so red.
This is the Prairie Squid show tonight, and we're dedicating...
We are taking this valuable church time to inform you about this very, very, very clear and present danger.
That is to say, the extinction of the Prairie Squid.
Oh, the demon's back.
Oh, daddy, oh.
We understand the black sky and it's dying.
No, daddy, no.
The last of the threatened child is ending time.
It's a dream, it's a dream.
It's a dream from the past.
We are brakes.
The covered into sand.
The chain cuts us back into our scales.
We live our lives to ride the mud wave.
They had Confederate flags on their bikes.
Wow.
And all this weird shit.
That was me.
That was me and my buddies.
And you were in blackface.
You were that wimp.
He was that tall, skinny kid that was just, he was scared just because there was ten of us and we were rednecks.
Yeah, just because there was ten of them.
That's nice.
And they talked real funny and they were Yankee this and Yankee that.
That's right, Yankee.
I said I hadn't Yanked a tinge the earlier part after.
What the hell were you doing in Texas?
Don't let the sun set on you here, boss.
Why?
No, they were a bunch of Mississippi boys that got a hold of me.
Yeah, Yankee ain't home.
And scared the dogs right off of me.
And the boys, if the idiots would just read it.
Yes, Lord, I bought us a vacation home in Florida.
We sure did.
A big home.
It's 30 feet wide.
And I don't like golf because of the heck of every taste of that golf ball all over the golf course.
And trying to get it straight.
And it stresses me more out than it does when I don't play it.
So I just lose it.
Where's the rock?
It's here.
It's over.
I'm making people go to golf.
And I'm making famous on the house.
And that information was stolen out the bank.
Thought you would be doing this.
Whatever $3 gesture poverty to you, I said, the movie returns you a new best.
And I'm out the more stuff for $3.
But you were more than rich.
The Bible with work, to rampc rasp was running, that was before you.
knitting fire, what do you know how it my name
Half of the N smaller Corona Alex
short month
And I showed him the ticket.
That's what we wanted.
We bought those tickets first for ourselves and upgraded them with our advantageous miles.
He didn't say none of that stuff.
What did they do?
They got a hidden camera on the airplane.
He came and posed to me.
I said, he's right.
I'm kidding.
Are you off your shit?
Can they talk about those two dogs we know of?
Oh, no, no.
Can't talk about them either.
But, you know, and they're saying, oh, well, it's a land where we have free discussions.
Yeah, but it's a democracy.
But you can only launch a bleeding head of Arnold Palmer on a Thursday night.
And not if it's a public holiday.
Yeah, a golfer head can only be launched on Thursdays in your own, you know, in the home of a consenting person.
You can't just go next door to your neighbors and launch a head if you feel like it.
And, God forbid, you launch a head in public like downtown on the main square or something like that.
Friends, I want.
North Little Rock.
You find.
You find yourself in trouble with the county law, boy.
Yeah, you can tell them.
You can tell them.
Oh, but officer, like doctors for Bob did.
You can say, oh, officer, but.
But.
But I'm a bold surrealist, sir.
I'm a bold surrealist.
Oh, yeah.
We got bold surrealist.
We got.
We got 40 men hanging them from telephone poles up in Tucker that like to say they were
as bold surrealists.
Yes, friend.
Yeah.
Oh, they'll.
Oh, yeah.
They'll tell you.
Every kind of head.
Yeah.
They'll launch a sneed head.
Oh, yeah.
They'll launch a Trevino forearm.
If you aren't careful.
Green straps the whole time.
The whole time, friends.
Friends, I want you to listen to this tape and I want you to meditate.
Meditate on this message.
Close your eyes and think about Prairie Squid and listen to this tape.
That's true.
They did.
But the head moved up or down.
And I can recall not too long ago, my father said to me, while playing around at home,
you're moving your head.
And I said, I don't think so.
I said, I'm keeping my eye on the ball.
And he said, well, you're keeping your eye on the ball.
Yes.
But your head is moving up and down, which I had worked into this unconsciously.
See, Arnold Palmer unconsciously knew that his.
I realized.
And knew his head had to be launched.
Yeah.
But that's not the real.
That's not the Arnold Palmer that you're thinking of, friend.
No, no, no.
It's not the guy that drives a tractor.
Uh-uh.
No.
It's the guy who sells, you know, oil-based petroleum products.
This is the.
Oh, forget it.
You don't even want to.
There's no way they can.
There's no way they can understand it.
They really couldn't.
Just write to that box number.
Yeah, that box number, friends, for the Church of the Subgenius.
And we'll send you plenty of information about prairie squids, golfer head launch-ins, slack,
slack, how to make.
And Reverend Stang.
How to get free sex all the time.
Yeah, the good sex for a mutant's dating league, I believe.
Oh, that's right.
Yeah.
That's another church.
That's another church service.
It's been a while since.
Yeah, since Buck sold the good sex for mutants dating league.
Well, he had to.
He was just getting worn out.
You know what he sold it for?
It was getting worn out.
It was wearing him out.
But you know what he sold it for?
Oh, when the hot mutants come.
You know what he sold it for?
A franchise?
No.
What did he sell a franchise for?
A bottle of Ripple.
And I was just mentioning that.
And I think they're in dispute now about who has the head.
Yeah.
And there's lawsuits.
Well, I have.
Yeah, I have one of the heads.
I have the head from the 84 show, which, of course, I shot Bob.
That's.
So where do these heads come from?
They were made.
There were probably about 10 of them made.
They're talking about head.
I think you better.
What's a guy show?
Now, where's the head giver, though?
The head giver's supposed to be here by now.
Hey, we don't do head anymore.
The head giver, though.
We don't do it.
That's Ivan Stang is the head giver of the church, as I thought.
That's what everybody tells me.
Receive and to give.
Just like Mama taught me.
Kill myself.
I'm receiving it right now.
Oh, I see.
Oh, hi, Janer.
Oh, no.
So.
He was an invincible villain.
Now.
Where'd he go from there?
Some of the callers who think we're talking about some other kind of head.
They don't know we're talking about the bleeding head.
Yeah, that's the thing.
I mean, people jump to the conclusion that you're talking about some sexual thing just because you, you know.
Just because you like and worship the bloody head.
Well, it is slightly sexual.
Yeah, it's slightly.
But that's only because of his overtone in the society.
It's not us talking about anything like that.
It's that.
It's the society picks up that in a twisted way.
Now, just because you may have sex with the head doesn't mean there's sexuality involved.
It's just a ritual that's involved in the worship process.
Phineas is one of the last people to see the head in one piece.
That's right.
Which head?
You're saying you have a piece of head?
The true bleeding head of Arnold Palmer was blown to smithereens.
Oh, are you getting a piece?
Are you getting blown?
Are you getting a piece of head or are you getting blown by the head?
The plaster head?
The original plaster head?
No, actually, the true plaster head, of course, can't be destroyed as long as Janer doesn't get a hold of it.
Right.
And as far as I know, it is not in Janer's hand.
So tell me about this explosion of head.
Well, there was going to be a firework show at X Day, of course, you know, I mean, before the...
But the head blew up, man.
Okay, just make a long story short.
The head blew up, right?
Well, it didn't just blow up with fireworks because Ed Strange and Dr. Mojo were using actually very illegal explosives.
Now, did that mess up the cottage cheese?
Oh, that one, yeah.
It was a great big rubber head.
It was the same head that had its nose bitten off the previous day.
Yes, yeah, right, right.
Who bit it?
The redneck Jesus.
No, you know, I...
The redneck Jesus got real upset.
Yeah, I mean...
Wonderful.
Because you could only have a good show, you could only have a good show with an upset soul there to complain about it.
I, you know, did you crucify the redneck Jesus for that?
No, we crucified the real Jesus.
But now, what type of revenge did you get to vindicate yourself with the redneck Jesus?
You know, all I did was say, man, why'd you do that?
Spit that nose out into my hand, please.
Did he do it?
He did.
He felt bad about what he'd done.
He spit the nose into my hand.
You know what?
I lost the nose.
Did he go off and flagellate himself?
Did he perform any kind of act of pittance or sacrificial mortification of any kind?
And now, the redneck Jesus performs an act of self-immolation.
And don't forget the date rapers who defecated in the hot tub.
And then, Ivan Stang is in the whirlpool with you.
And don't forget the date defecators who raped the hot tub.
And don't forget the prairie squeal.
And don't forget the hot tubs that took the defecators out on a date.
And don't forget the defecators who, yeah.
And don't forget the 7-Elevens who look like defecators that have Arnold Palmer heads.
Oh!
Hey, what ever happened to Billy James Hargis?
He died.
He did?
Yeah, he died.
When did he die?
Hey, give me some of that show, man.
Oh, thanks.
When did Billy James Hargis die?
Why didn't somebody tell me?
I guess you're going to tell me next that the Reverend Ike has died too, right?
Somebody, please, out there, anybody.
I think you're going to say Father Divine is dead.
Now you're going to tell me that Billy James Hargis has actually killed Reverend Ike.
Then you're going to say Bill Hicks is dead.
Bill Barty died.
Didn't Billy Barty die recently?
Yes, he did, Saturday.
Who?
Billy Barty.
That's tomorrow, but yeah, Billy Barty died 48 hours ago.
I guess you're going to tell me Andy Kaufman's dead next, right?
No, he's not.
No.
Okay.
So, um...
Hey, wait a minute.
Who is dead?
They're doing...
We're doing it on the show there.
If Billy James Hargis is dead, now what about Oral Roberts?
I'm trying to think of modern day prophets and how many of them are dead.
Oral Roberts, that's where the head comes from.
I didn't think it was that funny.
Sure.
Last show of the millennium.
Hey, Doug, quit tickling her.
It's the...
Oh, okay.
Quit tickling her, man.
It's just the antenna, see?
No one ever talks about his twin brother, Anal Roberts.
No, because that guy didn't start a university.
His twin brother, Anal Roberts, yeah.
Anal, Oral's lesser known brother.
Yeah, he sort of took the southern route, you know?
Yeah.
He's been in the back, kind of at the back door ever since then.
So, hey, Phineas, are you doing your show?
Yeah, it's on every week.
Up and running?
Yeah.
On what?
You must have a .org address.
Well, I mean, you can...
If you want to listen to it, it's on listen.to, T-O, word T-O.
Look, there's Anal...
I know how to spell T-O.
There's Anal Roberts again coming in the back door.
Listen.to slash voice jail, and then I'll take you to it.
Voice J-O?
J-O?
J-O, like as in J-O?
No.
Jail.
Oh, voice jail.
It's just the way he says it.
It makes you sound like J-O.
I thought you were talking about like a J-O posse.
I think it looks like Ivan Stang is now holding his landlady at gunpoint.
No, no, no.
I'm trying to check him.
Damn, the landlady's still here.
She doesn't think we're...
Oh, my God.
Two by two, four by four, obey in instructions given by the Lord.
Go on to the ark where you'll be safe.
As soon as they'd gone in there, it began to rain.
Two by two, four by four, obey in instructions given by the Lord.
Go on to the ark where you'll be safe.
As soon as they'd gone in there, it began to rain.
I think so.
What are you saying about the Queen of Norway?
I would do anything to protect a Norwegian royal family. Anything.
I'm saying she's my favorite gay job.
I would step in in a moment to save the Queen of Norway.
I will throw in my shoes and my false hand and my liquid one good eye to protect her.
I would never leave my kitchen table as a human shield for the Queen of Norway.
Look, it's King Bullock. He's coming to me with the Queen.
I would fornicate safely and without the administration with the Queen and King of Norwegians.
I would keep the King and Queen of Norway in my own garage if necessary to protect them from harm.
Norway itself may have to be bombed to protect the King and Queen of that selfsame land.
I would fill my freezer with brand spanking new ice trays for the King and Queen of Norway.
I would burn all my
in my own
on.
the
We'll be back.
Oh, God.
I had no cause to die
play it baby
ok
tell me dude
are you lost
is your heart
still pained
shall I come back
again
tell me dude
are you lost
14 years just shot right there man
I tell you
huh
praise Bob
is that the end
is it all done
I'm so sorry
Is there no more?
Did you box up the spinach?
Is it without a towel or a trouser?
To be continued...