What do we do? Come back like this?
Hey guys, wanna look for planes or something?
I'm going home.
Yeah, I'll come with you. Let's go listen to the radio.
You are about to experience the awe and mystery which reaches from the inner mind to...
The Self Genius Hour of Slut.
You are funny, Bob.
Hey, wait a minute. There's something really ugly crawling up your shirt.
That's my tie, Bob. Sorry.
Oh, look out, folks. It's time for the morning traffic.
Today's morning traffic report brought to you by Chateau Jason and the wine that used to play football.
20 seconds.
Nice meeting you.
No time for jokes, okay?
Look, the hold button says hold and the kill button is right next to it.
Kill button? I just came in for a cup of coffee.
10 seconds. Better put your headphones on.
Hey, wait a second. You want me to go on the radio?
That's very funny. Good luck.
Oh, yes, dear friends. It's rerun time again, and this is a good one.
Hour of Slut number 724 from early 2000.
This was one of the very last shows that I mastered on cassette tape
because we went all digital after this one.
It's also one of the first shows I did after moving from Dallas to Cleveland
and taking up residence on Chaz Smith's show,
ESO Swamp Radio on WCSB at Cleveland State.
This intercuts some killer stuff from the 1999 X-Day revival
with Einstein's Secret Orchestra and me preaching,
and it features excellent UFO-oriented collages from our old album,
Media Barrage No. 11, which was remastered to CD about that time.
And there's lots of music, including some period Todd Rundgren,
and things vastly less well-known like the church itself.
As I record these sentences on June 1st, conspiracy year so-called 2020,
the last sentence of John Bruner's The Sheep Look Up has come true.
That smell is America burning.
But not us. Not yet, anyway.
We're burning only with the desire.
We're burning with the desire to share our slack with you.
So let's use this fine rerun to go back in time
to the comparatively idyllic and utopian year of 2000.
Oh, if only we'd known how good we already had it then.
We invite you to participate in a program designed to help you find a richer, more productive life.
Talk Radio is about sharing your concerns and problems
and helping to find answers through creative solutions.
And now, you better wake up.
It's late.
250,000 K, the impact.
Another quarter million projected within the year.
Enter.
Come on, just push enter and it's done.
Which is it gonna be?
Hmm?
And uh, you know, even if X-Day didn't work out, we'll go for Sex Day!
We want you people to dance into the new century.
Screw into the new century.
Sleep and eat your way into the new century.
Whatever you're doing in the moment of turnover is what you'll be doing forever.
So make sense.
Make sure you're not asleep.
Make sure you're not watching TV.
Make sure you're not listening to Pat Boone.
Make sure you're not reaching for an itch you'll never be able to scratch.
Friends, you're floating in a sea of pills.
A sea of Bob's pills.
But you're just too blind, deaf, and dumb to see them.
I believe you 100%.
Look into my eyes.
I always tell the truth.
I believe you.
Now just calm down.
The stars are blue-shifting.
They're heading back in at a phenomenal rate.
Yes, we know what's happening as far as the blue shift.
Everyone is warm.
The whole universe is gonna end in about 14 hours.
No, no.
All contingencies have been planned for.
Calm down.
You're looking to be evident.
I got the data right here.
All contingencies have been taken care of.
Everything has gelled.
The positive response has occurred.
Oh, good.
No, no, no, no, no.
Wait, wait.
Don't, don't.
Shhh.
I'm gonna put it in.
What are we gonna do?
How are we gonna get it back in here?
It just disappeared.
What are we gonna do now?
He did a little blue sparkly flashy thing and he was gone.
I think he was...
Look at that.
I think he was doing Elvis and his blue spangly thing.
My God.
Period.
Those fools.
Look.
I warned the fools.
Oh, my God.
He was wearing snow shoes.
Look at the Earth.
It's gonna be so hard to make it through that little thing.
My God.
It's the blue flame.
No, he's wearing one of those little hairy hats.
It's that fire.
They set fire to the atmosphere.
No, no, no, he's just sitting on his head.
Those fools.
I warned those fools.
Oh, my God.
No.
They set fire to the atmosphere.
Blowing up plutonium and other things.
Well, that was different but now they've set fire to hydrogen and the whole atmosphere
just peeled away.
Those fools, those poor, poor fools.
And also, it's Pirates Galore, an excellent view of the future in which
everything and everyone you know is completely tied up backwards.
I can't play a damn thing anymore until all the lights are out.
And at 7 o'clock, it's Mom's Poultry Penance,
where Mom gets down on hands and knees and makes Dad satisfied like he used to be
back when he had teens.
It's Terrence McSquacken, singing songs about cars,
and a man with an exploding foot.
So don't miss the adventure as two more tip carries on the back of the...
There's no more fuel in the tank.
We have about 38 hours of oxygen left in the ship.
Yes, but we still believe, Commandante.
Is it not most important that we believe?
If we believe, perhaps...
The only thing that I can tell you is to aim the ship out.
You're going to what?
You're going...
Toward the sun.
You're going to point the ship at the sun?
I don't point the ship at the sun.
You are going to point the ship at the sun?
Captain, I can't breathe.
I'm having problems with this noxious...
What do we do?
If this was indeed an extraterrestrial spacecraft with living occupants,
it must have been very disconcerting for them
to cross millions of miles...
of space, only to be hit on the head with rotten oranges.
The End
The End 102 001 001 002 005 005 006 007 008 007 009 009 0010 0010 0010 0010 0011 0012 1000 12 ese
All the Anlime
Why are youGIres
All the Amios
dado
Suspicious
Des
Thank you.
The dramatic advent of such fascinating objects
as those which were first called flying saucers
attracted the inevitable attention of those individuals
who let their imaginations run away
with their veracity. By 1950 some of these characters were beginning to spin
their stories of fantastic conversations with alleged space people. Some of them
expanded the stories to include alleged rides in the UFOs.
Why I was strapped to this chair and put into the studio that seemed to be rotating very rapidly
flashing off rhythmically and it was a small man with a swollen head and hideously deformed eyes
sitting behind the console pushing the buttons while pencils of light and energy flashed across
my body and I wondered why I was there and what did they want of me and I couldn't figure out
why I was sitting there and they didn't say anything they just kept flashing those lights
at me and and and pumping those strange chemicals into me
and I couldn't figure out why I was sitting there and they didn't say anything they just kept
flashing those lights at me and and the man with a funny head the leader the the man with a
strange grin and the pipe well I just want to know if you want to be in the church or out of
the church and where's the wall yeah I didn't know that I'd been snatched up and it wasn't
really a dream until I saw these sacred nasal positions and suddenly it all came back to me
and I realized that they'd stolen four and a half hours out of my life
when they put me in that tiny room and plugged all those wires in and I was like oh my god
I was still there so I was very boxed I came in this was very violent but alsoาก mult понять
I was dressed in my blond dress as well as performing the race called the
from the black belt I've been a duas otras oftens Paris stonetsurack hol Avoidwart
I came to you from a long long ways off I come from a planet that is similar to yours your many fears tensions
and frustrations are no longer ours I hate them with all my heart in human and to be destroyed what is your objective
You are not ready, but we will still save you.
In your quest for self-destruction, you will send up more satellites.
And we will be there, waiting to come again.
In the cycle to the moon, we're right.
And they came, one by one.
I'll be right here.
I was first contacted by a being from the planet Mars.
Now, this man was invisible to me, except that he did cast a shadow in the moonlight.
By 1998, every normal, mediocrity,
pink boy, admin, Trekkie, and hippie is going to be trying to get on board with the good ship dogs.
Or something.
Or they're going to fry along with everybody else when those aliens get here.
Of course, such a prophecy immediately arises our cynicism.
Is it possible that the end of the world will come in July 1999?
Perhaps.
Or is it just another of those prognostications which have haunted man through the ages?
Such a forewarning of ultimate doom could generally be dismissed out of hand.
But for the fact that many of Nostradamus' other...
prophecies have already been fulfilled.
But the old ones are coming back.
I'm going to let them through.
We are here.
Where are you from?
I don't like his feet.
Let me feed you a little pork.
He's trying to tell us something.
And banjo, and birdies, and bottles.
And then we're going to...
The tools of conquest do not necessarily come with bombs and explosions and fallout.
On July 5th, 1998, 7 AM, when we all have hangovers,
Wotan's judgment will take place in the form of what the pre-scriptures call
the advent of the angelic host.
Because...
The end of the world.
fpsolo
END OF THE LAST TIME
We're gonna kill someone!
The Exist will descend with their scientifically magic implements.
There'll be stalls of technology that will be too much for us to handle.
In one instant, all the hangovers will disappear, along with all pollution and nuclear weapons.
But in return, the human race will have to take on living machinery so complex that those it is peaceful.
The end result will be equivalent to letting toddlers play with a nuclear arsenal.
Bob, and not some conspiracy world government, must be there in a position of world leadership
to explain humanity's behavior to the Exists in ways they can understand
so they don't put us out of our misery with a snap of their cosmic finger like they did the dinosaurs.
The right people, us, must be the ones that the Exists make into super humans.
Super human over men!
And even then, things will be damn tough for the rest of this period, which is called the Time and Half Time.
The Exists have landed.
Earth's under their control.
Bob's vision.
Span's proven.
The city's radioactive home.
We don't know what their game is.
But their name is unpronounceable.
We don't know.
What their game is. But their name is unpronounceable. We don't know.
That's what they came for.
But what they aim for.
It is impossible to spare not mean beings.
And the second year before the millennium of the day of God come Wednesday as in the twinkling of an eye
they will come along the Warum.
The Yayk finans神未来
which are like and supernatural home!
And burn for sayings
ERS
others. They come as men, as grave images, as a whirlwind, and as a cloud, and they are now the heavens
of the exiles.
The exiles have landed their machines following our tracks. Bob's vision stands proven. A world without slack.
So,
don't
come up to me saying,
Oh, Reverend Stang, I spent my $30. I went to the subgenius show. I saw all the preachers, heard all the bands, but I didn't get slack. Where's my slack? Give me my slack.
My friend, if that's the way you're thinking, then you never heard anything Bob said. You never understood a word he wrote in the book of the subgenius. Because the day that we can sell you slack is the day the conspiracy has won. You make your own slack.
Bob!
is
not
the
answer!
But, neither is anything else.
You
must
learn
to think
for
yourself
but only
Bob
can
show
you
how.
Question
authority
or
health
Mount them!
Can't
take
a
joke!
Please, Bob!
Tell me
somebody!
Goodnight!
Tough
fun.
Hm!
Fuck,
iTunes!
Next night's secret artist your friends,
Mildred Shepard.
Beyond the Soft.
If I don't meet you no more in this world,
I'll see you on the next one.
And don't be late.
Peace.
My dad, remember that?
That's it, one more time!
Ohhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh!
Hey, guess what? That website, when we...
Here's the entire result of being in Time Magazine
for Churches of Genius, okay?
Amazing.
We finally, we met in Time Magazine,
and our website's URL was...
Milk it, baby, milk it, milk it, baby!
The big result, the final end result was
our merchant credit card company
quit doing business with us.
Wow.
Having looked at the website and discovered
that there was, quote,
questionable material, unquote.
So, Jesus...
Fat naked people in a swimming pool at Brushwood?
Yeah, Jesus had to call up...
That is always questionable.
...a new bank.
We had to find a pornographer's bank
that would do anything for a buck.
Praise Bob and God bless America!
Where there's still people who do anything for a buck
and understand the values!
You're on the air with Lonesome Cowboy Dave,
who's a...
You were complaining about the One World Advertiser.
I think it's a fine little giveaway paper
I find on my doorstep.
Every day.
The One World Paperboy throws it in here.
Look over here.
One Church of the Subgenius for sale.
What?
Yeah.
It's on page three of the One World Advertiser,
underneath the garage sale listings and the lost kitties.
The Church of the Subgenius has been willing to sell out
for a long time.
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
It's in the shopper.
They haven't had any buyers yet.
Oh man, if you get it in the shopper,
that means it's definitely going down.
Those guys, see, they're very anxious to jump the story,
as they say in those local news jargon.
Market analysis summary.
The Subgenius market is not restricted by age, gender,
belief system, or even international boundaries.
Anybody might be interested.
The majority of our members fall in ridden males 18 to 25,
above average intelligence, computer literate,
and somewhat rebellious.
That's not what this says.
It says almost free to good home.
That's what this says.
Sounds like a good profile of hackers who may have
attacked the sites over the last few days.
I don't know if they got the profile, they got John Douglas,
you know.
They might all be in this together.
The same people that knock down those sites are the same
people that are fucked.
Can you imagine the FBI profiles?
Do you know what called out talk of the nation today and
claimed the Church of the Subgenius had something to do
with that?
Yeah.
Figures.
Wouldn't that be a funny joke, yeah?
As long as they spell the name right in the newspaper,
you know?
Well, you know, it's funny.
Funny, because back in 1982, the world's first Macintosh virus was blamed on the Church of the Subgenius.
It was a lie.
A lie!
Because it was a peace message.
Well, that is the reason why the genetic spawn that you have from fornicating apples have ruined mankind.
And have ruined our business structure.
Have ruined the social infrastructure and our cultural beliefs.
Look at what it's become.
It's, you know, it destroyed everything with that.
But it's like the story of Para-Ubu, like the absurdity of mankind.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's like that.
It's full of irony, like art and all that shit.
Yeah.
Yeah, art's got irony in it, and it's got, what's that other stuff?
Luminum.
Torture.
It's got luninum, torture.
It's got irony.
It's got, what, vapor?
What are we talking about, the earth or the society?
Greasy fried chicken.
Oh, oh, oh.
I got it.
What we don't like about it, what we can't stand about it.
No, we're talking about, you know, this right here.
These tubes of fried chicken, though, just aren't the same.
These ones?
Yeah.
Well, what do you have to compare them with, man?
You know, come on.
I mean, to me, fried chicken wasn't something that you squeezed out of a tube.
Not in the old days.
To me, it was something that you, you know, that came in little nuggets, these bite-sized nuggets.
Yeah.
And you just, you had a handful of them, and you shoved them in, and they had crispiness.
There was crispy stuff on them.
Yeah.
That's a chicken.
You could imagine them as like little deep fried butters.
But, I mean, the stuff that's coming out of tubes, that's just, that's not a real chicken.
Well, it does have a very, very chickeny rich smell, doesn't it?
Yeah.
I mean, come on.
And the tomatoes, these, this, this, this stuff in the tube, tomatoes didn't come out of a tube.
I remember tomatoes were these perfect, hard things that always were really shiny.
Right.
Well, they were really just round tubes.
They didn't have any taste.
They were round tubes with no taste.
Yeah.
But those were real, and chickens, remember chickens?
They were these boneless creatures.
Yeah.
They had their feet grown into the cage.
Boneless tubes.
Yeah.
Real chickens.
I like these.
They had no heads.
They were cloned, and that's the way chicken was meant to taste.
Rich and greasy like mom used to make.
It's like this modern, they have this so-called progress has, I think, in some ways, yes,
I dare to say it, is taking us, yes, backwards.
Oh, we agree.
Backwards, not forwards.
Don't we, Chas?
Agree completely?
We're revolutionists.
It's almost like, it's almost as if.
21st century, daddy-o.
Come on.
This has just now occurred to me.
Well, look, here.
Put it together.
The evolution.
The internet has been attacked, so people are unhappy with the future world.
Soon the infrastructure will fall.
Just a few, a few.
And the ratings have come in, and the oldies music station, the radio station in town here
that plays oldies music from the 50s and the 60s, a much simpler time when we could kill
students in the campuses.
Right.
And get away with it.
Yeah.
But the oldies station is the number one thing.
The oldies station is the number one station by far in the ratings.
So people are listening to oldies music, attacking websites, and, you know, what else is happening?
You know.
Oh, dear friends, I'll tell you what's happening.
Credits.
Credits are happening.
What we heard from the very beginning of the show was a show from KPFA in Berkeley puzzling
evidence.
And Dr. Howell bits and pieces there.
Some, some, some, some, some, some, some, some, some, some, some, some, some, some, some, some,
some, Bob lives.
We've been listening to clips from the double X day 1999 de
viva.
Well at Brushwood.
that's a new CD.
The X-Day 99
Devival is a new CD.
And I've been playing little bits and pieces
of that with Einstein's Secret Orchestra in the background
and yours truly preaching.
And of course, we've been hearing lots of the
ESO radio show,
Einstein's Secret Orchestra, Swamp
Radio out of WCSB
in Cleveland, which is
essentially where I'm producing
this show, although I'm not going
into the studio yet and doing that.
I go into the studio for Chaz's show.
On Thursday nights. And you can call
in at WCSB
in Cleveland. And Lonesome
Cowboy Dave.
Ah, yes, the mighty
Dave
keeping us all off track.
Don't you see?
And...
Fascist Christ was the
name of that song by
Todd Rundgren from his
No World Order album.
Remember that?
Uh...
Oh,
the Danish or
Norwegian song
Tis Tag in Greer
is by
Mithotain.
And the music that you're hearing in the background is
AMORPHOS!
Uh, amorphous.
Friends, and what we've
heard quite a bit of
is the old subgenius
media barrage
number 11.
With the UFOs collage where we
heard G. Gordon Gordon and
Space. A lot of collage
from me and Doug
Weldman of Puzzling Evidence and Byron
Werner, who
has a new show on internet
radio. Check out
luxuriamusic.com
One word,
luxuriamusic.
luxuriamusic.com
Uh,
and Buck Naked, the former
subgenius preacher, he
disavowed the church. He found
another religion.
Some rival cult.
He won't tell us what it is.
Uh, doing the excess
have landed. Also off the old
media barrage number 11. And friends,
eh, yes.
...
For the worldly flesh, we flesh, we flesh
I look through and I hear no sound
It's a sound, it's a sound, it's a sound
The worldly flesh, it's a sound
I see a something but I still can't hear
Like a box of glass, poking out my ears
It's a sound
I'm sure it'll play on your ears
The worldly flesh, worldly flesh
All of the raindrops, the misrepresentation
I'm in trouble, I'm so hard in the face
I setKAVE
What are your greed and peace?
You'll see I'm ver
I'm sorry you can't forget
Can be saying goodnight
Try to avoid pidin' me
And to turn here to that end
To fall and fall again
All alike, all alike
I'lliam
Ain't no rest for the one we've lost
Life has passed, you're the latest
Lost we dance, cause the one we've lost
We are destined to the one we've lost
This is where we're destined, we're the one we've lost
Life has passed, you're the latest
Lost we dance, cause the one we've lost
We are destined to the one we've lost
Well, the weirdest thing is that they said in 1959...
What does it all mean?
40 years ago, 1959, but it's really 2000.
Are we ending the loop? Are we coming to the end of the loop?
Yes, this is a perfect inaccurate...
Now we're gonna flip back.
This is a very...
It's a very functional...
I think it is. I think the tape, I think in the tape, the grand tape,
is coming to the end of the loop.
It's starting to crackle.
We're coming back to the splice.
We're coming right to the splice.
The splice in time.
But listen to this.
The time.
In 1959, 40 years ago technically,
the average 17-year-old American had a vocabulary of about 25,000 words.
You know what his vocabulary is now?
Like what?
250.
10,000.
Wow.
Definitely going backwards.
And half of them are like, you know what I mean.
And the other half are like, you know...
Like, and...
And I'm like...
I'm so sure.
For sure.
Dude!
And it was like, you know, like it was like...
You guys, you sit there and you whine about how...
Oh no, we're gonna do something.
We're doing something about it.
Everything is becoming the one government, the one religion,
and you don't do anything about it.
You, on your show...
Yeah, I write this music.
Now listen, listen.
Wait a minute.
The undertones and the...
I am doing something about it.
The symphonic sounds that are the very basis of the government taking over.
These are the things getting into people's minds.
Ah-ha-ha-ha.
Yeah, well, every week...
We are doing something about it.
Every week I play this, and anybody who hears it...
Is deprogrammed, man.
...is downloaded.
It's deprogrammed.
That's the deal, man.
We're trying to deprogram you.
That's right.
Oh, push.
The Pokemon.
I would never touch you there.
No, are you guys aware about the Pokemon craze or whatever?
They're bringing back the Pokeballs.
The Pokeballs?
Yeah.
They're apparently...
The Pokemon.
...the television commercials they're on now are requesting that you return the Pokemon balls.
Oh, yeah, that's true.
The Pokeballs.
You've got to go back there.
Did you know that?
Yeah.
They're going to send them home.
They're not the problem.
Their visas are...
It's over.
That's the deal.
The Pokemon themselves are the mind control devices.
We know that.
This is the perfect marketing ploy that the children buy these.
They keep them long enough, and the tones that emanate from them...
...help to take over their minds.
And when they return the ball, they think that they're...
This music is the antidote.
This music, this show, is the antidote to that poison.
A program on Comedy...
Well, I would certainly hope so.
A comedy cable program show already explored that idea of Pokemon being mind control devices.
All I do know is sit in my house and try and get the message out to people that the Pokeball is not the problem.
It's simply the Pokemon.
Just tell them to listen to the show.
I try...
I can't...
Tell them to listen to my house.
Tell them to...
I love Goddess Annalise keeps me in the house.
All right, well, the...
Tell them Goddess Annalise...
Annalise says hello.
Annalise.
Oh, good.
And we're gonna...
Yeah, now...
Okay, if Pokemon is the Antichrist...
Okay, we'll talk about that.
...then our savior must be the Rastaman, right?
Oh, the Pokemon is the Rastaman.
Oh, my God, man.
This is getting too confusing.
I mean, now the Antichrist is the Christ, too?
I wanted to hear more about the love...
Canal?
...connection here with this...
Oh, wow.
...caller.
The caller has...
...he's got his own love goddess, apparently.
Hanna-Loa.
It sounds like it's the other way around.
The love goddess has him.
Right, right.
Well, his...
It won't let him out, but you can tell he kind of likes it.
Oh, yeah.
He kind of prefers being kept and...
I think he's been shrunk down, and she uses him in...
That's what...
Yeah, right.
That's what the shadows say.
He's shrunk down to about 14 inches tall.
Yeah.
Dig that, baby.
Daddy-o.
Keeps him in, like, a little...
You know, one of those, like, I Dream of Jeannie...
I Dream of Jeannie.
...homes.
Yeah.
You know, it's funny you mention that...
...in a little thought, man.
...because I was thinking about Tinkerbell.
...as it drives away.
In fact, Princess Wee, who's recovering from a trepanation operation tonight, and I were
discussing Tinkerbell, and, like, exactly...
Tinkerbell and liquid latex.
Yeah, baby.
Would Tinkerbell be able to do anything but kind of get you in the...
Of course, you've got to like...
...point in the right direction, and you'd have to take care of finishing, you know,
dousing her, but...
Yeah, with liquid latex.
And Princess Wee pointed out...
Well, but she'd be great for girls.
Those wings probably...
Yeah.
...just flicker and...
Flutter and...
...flutter and...
...flip and flap.
You mean, like, if you was to flip the wings, or if the wings was to flip you?
Well, I don't know.
I don't know.
The Tinkerbell.
You've got to find out how it works.
I guess I...
I guess me and Tinkerbell's going to have to have a little talk now, won't we?
I have never had a fornicational scene with a person with wings.
A fairy.
A tiny little...
He said, yeah, I was a fairy until it was my turn, or something.
No, I was a sadist until it was my turn.
But what if you...
But what if a little fair maiden were to use a fairy in this way...
In this first fashion.
...for sexual satisfaction, and accidentally inserted a fury instead?
Oh, man!
Wow.
Now, a fury is an evil fairy.
Bad.
The furies, you wouldn't want to...
Unleash the furies in the fairies.
Jeez.
That would cause a misruption in everything.
The furies can look like fairies when they want to.
But then they have that horrid grimace that...
You guys are freaking me out, man.
That's the deal, man.
Furies are really old.
It was like Mozart wrote about the furies and stuff.
Yeah, and there was an odyssey.
The furies...
Yeah, right.
The furies.
They're bad fairies.
Bad.
But what about the...
They're like from the dark side.
What about the fates?
They're little Darth Vaders.
What if the fates won't speak to us?
The fates won't speak to us.
Wings.
What if, like, the fates turn their back on us?
Like, we want to talk to one of the music...
The fates are neutral.
They're like Switzerland.
Huh?
Well, the fates are neutral.
They're like Switzerland.
They're just the messengers.
Here, buddy.
Good at banking and stuff.
This is the way it's going to be.
Heroin addicts.
Yeah.
That's the fates.
Swiss.
The cheese...
And the fairies are cool.
You know, the fairies, you get good peanut butter.
You know?
They should.
I mean, if that was in the job description, at least, I'd want to go for it.
What do fairies have to do with peanut butter?
You're losing, man.
Or unionism.
I was following it.
Peter Pan.
I mean, I thought we were talking about, you know, Tinkerbell.
I thought we were talking about, you know, workers' rights and stuff, man.
I thought we were talking about how good-looking Tinkerbell was in that little outfit.
That's where we started.
Covered in peanut butter, man.
Imagine licking that peanut butter off.
Oh, we better stop talking about sex with Tinkerbell.
Oh, my God.
Look down in the basement.
Sex?
What do you mean?
I was talking about having dinner with Tinkerbell.
Oh, my God.
That's not chicken.
She would probably taste like chicken.
I was...
You know, it's today.
This modern morality.
I'm shrinking.
I was watching that South Park movie.
It was a big hit movie last year.
I finally had a chance to rent it.
And was watching that movie.
And in the first ten minutes, I thought, now, what if an old man like me heard it while I hear this is a famous big movie.
Everybody's going to see it.
It's the biggest hit movie.
I'm going to go see it.
He goes and watches people standing in line.
He watches people standing in line.
Actually, I thought it was a hilarious movie.
I loved it.
I thought it was great.
Brilliant.
Wish I'd thought of it.
But...
To another old man like myself, he'd walk in there and he'd go,
they're lining up and paying $10 a ticket to watch stick figures say...
Man.
Which is, it's stick figures talking dirt, saying four-letter...
What a Sunday afternoon.
And Alice in Wonderland.
On the basis, on the face of it, it's stick figures cussing.
What has this world evolved down into?
It's just motion pictures.
I told you they wouldn't last.
That's why they last?
A hundred years ago, I told you...
Motion pictures are transitional.
Yeah, it's just a fad.
Movement is transitional, Daddy-o.
I mean, just think of it, man.
I don't know what it's coming to now.
So the fad is coming to now.
Pretty soon we'll all be still as doorknobs.
You know what I'm saying?
It's going to...
Movies are going to...
Movement is transitional.
The fad of movement...
Movement is a fad, man.
Just think of it.
We're all going to be still as a...
You know, it is a transitional, ephemeral fad compared to the amount of time during the
...duration during which there has been no movement.
...before we was born and after we was dead.
But when there is no movement, is there time?
If there's nothing, no duration across which an event occurs, can one say that time has
passed?
We would only say that time can only be measured in terms of...
But I can always tell you when the gas has been passed around the studio...
Or at least change of some kind.
If there's no movement...
Around the road.
...the inert gas...
...there's no change, then...
Someone has been passing inert gases on the road again, and I don't think it's Fermi
or Albert Einstein.
If you fad in your...
And if it fads in your car and no one else smells it, did you really fart?
I wonder if Einstein thought about that.
But if there's five bandmates in a van and somebody farts...
Then you say fart out.
Hey, everybody, guess what time it is?
Time for fun.
So, everybody, join in and have some fun.
My name is Hemaroy Rogers and these are my rolloys.
We hope that you have had a good time.
We know that we sure did.
My name is Hemeroy Rogers, and these are my roid boys.
We hope that you have had some fun, so we thank that hat man.
Hey everybody, come on, have some fun!
My name is Hemeroy Rogers, and these are my roid boys.
I think that it would be fun to kill them all today.
I'm gonna kill them all with my bare hands!
These bombs already planted at these designated targets in the capitals of these communist states.
People have to get past it.
We have to grow up and move on and eat our Popeye's spinach.
Yes, a huge mass, looking almost like a detached beard, right?
A huge dripping handful of seaweed, always when Popeye pulled it uncooked out of the can
and dropped it into his toothless mouth, his huge, bulgish jaw would chew it.
And the Adam's apple prominently distend as the work of alimentation was robustly caricatured.
Finally, the...
morphological muscular elongation with the pictorial iconic accompaniment,
together with the mechanization or superhuman function of the body,
the fight syndrome is begun, and of course the familiar musical accompaniment that we all know.
What is this?
It's the dissolution of the Mapes Hotel in Reno, Nevada.
It's the death of Bob Squire, the master of political imagery.
What was that again? Squire?
Bob Squire died this week.
The resurrection process has an unfortunate...
Oh, also, yeah, we did want to bring up...
What we want to tell you is all the lines of all the movies,
so you don't have any bad surprises when you go see the movies.
We'll tell you the things like the blonde did it,
or the person you think did it did it,
or all the passengers did it,
or he puts her on the plane, he dies on the bus, he dies in the freezing water,
she falls from the bell tower, she shoots him in the paper...
Oh, my goodness.
Jesus Christ.
It's confusing.
It's like Thorazin.
He cuts off his genitals.
The stab, this dwarf stabs him.
Ouch.
His mom has been hypnotized.
Hey, don't say nothing about my mama.
He turns back into a half-wit.
That's my favorite.
How about a three-quarters wit?
He blows up the bridge.
He drives off the bridge.
He pushes the man off the cliff.
They drive into the Grand Canyon.
She wasn't really dead.
He wasn't really dead.
Don't look under the bed.
That's on the Disney Channel.
That's on top of the world, Ma.
What's that from?
Top of the world.
That's to the end of White Heat with James Cagney.
He blows up the giant refinery tank that he's standing on top of.
Yep.
The gigolo gets the motel.
The hooker gets the millionaire.
Kevin Spacey gets his.
Glenn Close gets hers.
Uh-oh, we're in space.
Where no one can hear you squeal.
Oh, my God.
That's good.
In the eternal silences of infinite space.
It sure is nice out here.
Somebody's coming.
It's the gods and monsters show.
Where it's all wet and damp and squelchy and swampy and sloppy.
Like the bathroom at Cafe This.
Oh, thanks.
Now the pralines are here, and they just dump them off next to the old bus in the back.
The station's full of them.
One ton of pralines.
And up there go those little Rice Krispies.
Uh, boys, aren't you being just a little bit silly?
That's, uh, Dr. Howell and
Buzzing Evidence on the KPFA Show,
a particular one from January 27th of the year 2000.
Before that, Hemeroy Rogers, the tail end of his CD,
which you can find on mp3.com.
You can order that CD through mp3.com.
And, uh, I think...
He didn't put it on this letter!
What does he think I am, a genius?
This is the church of the sub-genius!
It's, uh, but it's Hemer...
I believe it's something like...
You go to the mp3.com and just, you know, search for
Hemeroy Rogers
and his roid boys.
And, of course, Einstein's Secret Orchestra,
where we never shut up.
But, but, uh, but friends,
actually, we should have a scary,
scary music, but...
Because they're scary...
These are the predictions
for the coming years.
Monsters like unto men
will be around thee all night
and shall lead thee to look past the door
which should be locked
and thy silences will terrify thee
and bring thee not the devils
for thine spirit is locked away
inside the white star.
And the angels of heaven
which my angels saw
bring from space,
which is the vessel of all that is known.
And even now I shall feed signs
in the heaven and signs in the earth,
blood-bellies from the earth.
My lights in the sky rebuke thee.
The children of heaven
and the angels from heaven
are among thee, spreading lies and deception.
They turn not as they go,
but they turn as they go.
We're tired of your phony fireworks.
Blasto, you have earned this!
They do it their way.
As the mutants move,
battle leaps.
Tibetan Tiger Man.
What about the
what about this reputed
Jesus Starfleet
that was supposed to have shown up?
As you see, they have just left the hangar deck at Lunar Central
and have cleared the airlocks into the colony.
The crowd of scientists and technicians are going wild.
What a space ovation!
Now let's feel an upper.
And now in celebration of this great occasion,
we have planned a lunar party.
We hope all young people for our future,
for the solar system,
will join us in celebration of this great day in outer space.
Bob?
Late that Saturday night, before retiring,
I took out the snapshot picture of the sailor
and studied it until I could close my eyes
and see this man's face as though he was standing in front of me.
It's Bob!
I love you.
Bob loves you.
I'm flying in success.
All my friends,
cause they're so nice.
And Nina loves you.
I'm gonna see them again and again.
Is it before or after the Bob pills?
The arrival of a space ship in Washington.
The rumors of invading armies and mass destruction
are based on hysteria,
and are absolutely false.
And you are not alone.
Remember it's true.
The UFO, the UFO,
breaking us up.
making us up.
The UFO, the UFO,
Your brothers from outer space
are coming with advanced knowledge.
To help human race.
Bob's my friend and he's leading me somewhere.
Where are you leading us, Bob?
What is waiting there for me?
Bob can stop the aliens from killing me.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Bob can save me,
but will he?
Don't count on it, Buck.
Bobby, Bobby, Bobby, Bobby, Bobby, Bobby, Bobby, Bobby.
Dobbsy, Dobbsy, Dobbsy, Dobbsy, Dobbsy, Dobbs.
What is waiting there for me?
Bob.
Don't count on it, Buck.
Friend, the Elder Gods have been sleeping.
But they're waking up.
And you've gotta find that word of Bob before-
Friends, you've got to get on it.
You've gotta get on it.
And it's on-
I'm gonna give you the address.
to get onto.
Friends, you can write to Bob
and find out, to get free information
about the Church of the Subgenius,
go ahead, send that self-addressed stamped envelope
to that post office box,
807 Glen Rose, Texas, 76043.
You know, I've been saying that address
for 15 years on the radio.
Praise Bob and Hail Connie.
But friends, www.subgenius.com
is always the thing to do.
And this in the background is
the Flying Ryan Brothers
with their lovely tune, Captain Nemo,
from their album, Colorama,
at ryanetics.com.
Dear friends, I...
I'll see you next time.
guitar solo
solo
in harmony
keep your hat on tight
you're back to the winter
sacking the saddle
heads or tails
and happy trails
we'll see you all next week
March 3rd
Friday night
you could tell
the large ones
keep coming
and keep coming
you can make up
your own mind
on the map
it says
they're coming down
from Canada
and much in the same way
they went back
years and years before
the reflux is
as we say
see up here quite an invertebrate matter and as we're all shrinking back to the invertebrate form
we're going to enjoy these little dips into the cold and back into the warm again
tanya what's next as far as the evolutionary parade
goodbye
i can feel the love guys
i can feel the love right now man
you take care
that's disgusting there's moon dust they all love the moon dust on that thing and there's so many
things you can do with it you can you can heal so many different elements and configurations
you can solve so many earth earth problems with this a little sticky square moon dust wherever
he sits down oh daddy well that's just like objectism you know what i mean like when he's
out of scratch in an itchy place it makes you smarter
you know what i mean like when he's out of scratch in an itchy place it makes you smarter
it makes you work harder listen to that space angel up on that cloud singing the lovely miss
marisa click is always tomorrow and the beautiful randy bandy band and all the kids here at pinpoint
hill hey when is that uh church potluck social uh friday march 3rd uh friday night at the euclid
tavern devival with einstein secret orchestra cobra verdi jerry and the reverend ivan stang
and uh lonesome cowboy dave and all that kind of fun stuff there's always tomorrow folks
and hello once again
you know don't okay don't go back in we've only got two minutes
thank you oh beautiful lady out there for reminding us to do our own pr when tom got back
from
two minutes
the doctor's stuck in the saddle he realized he'd only have four and a half minutes left to live
so it wasn't good news but going to the doctor never was good news for tom
it'd been years since he'd seen dr sphincter but he knew that the problem wasn't going to
solve itself yeah he's talking to himself and so as he stood squarely in front of his own
mimeographs till next week
no
until next week keep your hat on tight you're back to the wind and you're sorry sacking the saddle
heads or tails and happy trails there partner i'm gonna tell on you dave bombs away
i'm so sorry that i broke your heart
please
no
leave my
side
, take me home you silly boy cause i'm still in love with you
you
and friends that's post office box 807
294 Nord 14
glenrose texas
thats where you can write for free information or
contact us and of course SUBGENIUS.com leads to
everything else you need to know all the facebook pages
all the email addresses
um, every thing
and how to get a Subgenius membership kit where you become an ordained minister it's real
come here go toவ
And it's a pretty sizable kit with lots of cool stuff in it.
You know, decoder pins and posters and everything you would imagine.
Oh, and our face mask, fertility mask bandanas are back in stock.
They were backordered.
I'm going to be filling orders of those all day today.
And replace the bottom half of your face with the bottom half of Bob's face.
Why, they'll think it's Bob talking to them.
We have the Book of the Subgenius and Lonesome Cowboy Dave's sci-fi novel Neighbor World.
And more coming up.
We have CDs and DVDs.
And friends, have you yet tried TriologySoaps.com?
Triology Soaps.
They're made by our friend, the crazy Lord Ferg,
who embeds a soap Dobbs head inside a translucent outer layer of very high quality soap.
You can get it in all kinds of flavors and scents.
And you can get it with nonsense.
None at all.
That's my favorite, actually.
And friends, again, that's Triology.
TriologySoaps.com.
Triology spelled with an I first and then a Y later.
Then there's FreethinkRadio.com.
You know, there are many subgenius shows.
The Hour of Slack wasn't even the first one.
Puzzling Evidence was.
Hour of Slack was only the second and most variety-filled one.
But on FreethinkRadio.com, at different times of day,
you can live stream canned shows from Time for the Show,
National Cynical, Puzzling Evidence,
Bob's Slack Time Funhouse,
Fergan Fridays, which is all insane music of every possible kind,
and what you're listening to right where you're sitting right now.
And more.
So check out FreethinkRadio.com.
TriologySoaps.com.
Subgenius.com.
And by golly, you can dot com the hell out of it.
Praise Bob.