Now won't you dig, Daddy Slack, now won't you dig?
Now if you wanna hear some boogie that I'm gonna play
Now that it's just an opiator and a mega bass
Now the drummer man has it eight feet late
Now I guess you remember Slack and old B, B-Daddy Wayne
Mother selling chicken, fried and bacon, grease
Let us walk along Slack down the road of peace
Let's make you walk on down the road of peace, Slack
Don't step on my feet, man, you know that's gonna hurt
I'm sorry, Wayne, I didn't mean to
Be alright down the road of peace
Dig the space, this is crazy
Watch the Snatch Space, man
Don't step on my feet, man, you know that's gonna hurt
I'm sorry, Wayne, I didn't mean to
Be alright down the road of peace, Slack
Don't step on my feet, man, you know that's gonna hurt
Don't step on my feet, Slμο, don't pay for me
I'm sorry, Wayne, you know that's gonna hurt
Go back on your feet, don't step on my feet
Swish away from me
There's no point in
Don't go up there, man, yeah, yeah, yeah, you said it
Egyptian stuff.
And he was talking about how he cried
the night back in
1977 or something like that
that the Grateful Dead
played at the pyramids.
They set up so many amplifiers
and when he was standing on the pyramids
while they were playing he said he could feel
the stones vibrating.
And you know, stuff inside
the place was probably crumbling
and everything. The secret chambers
were probably...
He said he cried.
It broke his heart so bad. The teenagers were out
just getting drunk in front of this sacred place.
You know.
Just drunk and
tripping and
a big party.
I guess sooner or later
the showbiz takes over
everything sacred and holy
and makes it drunken.
Like Michael Jackson's bedroom.
Yeah, I heard that some little kid
raped Michael Jackson.
Everyone it seems from the ordinary
Kuwaiti in the street to the sophisticated
planners in the Pentagon was taken by surprise
by Saddam Hussein's strike
at his tiny neighbor.
Brutal aggression launched last night
against Kuwait illustrates
my central thesis. The world remains
a dangerous place
with serious threats to
important U.S. interests.
President Bush
convened an emergency session of the security
committee.
The invasion was condemned.
Sanctions levied and Iraq's
assets frozen the following day.
Iraq was to suffer economic isolation
and intense hardship until
it relented. It was perhaps the most
complete blockade of a country
seen in recent times.
The U.S. State Department then sent a message
to the countries of the Arab League.
The West has done its duty
but the Arab nations are doing
nothing. If they do not take a firm
stand on the Kuwaiti affair
they can be sure that in the future
they will no longer be able to count on America.
With the world united, hopes were high
that the Security Council would now
be an effective force for peace.
Mr. President, this is a far more
important issue than simply the invasion
of Kuwait. This is in its own way
the first real test of this new world
order that we're trying to put together.
In the meantime,
resolutions flowed from the Security Council.
A blockade was sanctioned. Dependent on imported food, Iraq now faced starvation.
On September 4th, James Baker said that US gold now included the destruction of Iraq's military.
On September 15th, Dugan said targets would include...
What is unique about Iraqi culture? That they put very high value on. That psychologically would make an impact.
If push came to shove, the cutting edge would be downtown Baghdad.
If I want to hurt you, it would be at home, not out in the woods someplace.
Over 100,000 troops were now stationed in the Gulf, without congressional debate or authority.
And the build-up continued.
In the biggest operation since World War II, Western equipment and troops have been landing at the Saudi port of Jubail, less than 200 miles from Kuwait.
Question.
Questions were asked.
Why should the West defend a country which has no democracy?
When he was gassing his own Kurdish people, when he was invading Iran, where were all the clever politicians then?
And answers given.
The President stated reasons vary, from upholding international law, to protecting oil fields, putting down a new hip-hop...
I don't believe they are...
...improving regional security...
...their concern in the region is purely and simply...
Our jobs, our way of life, our own freedom...
...would all suffer if control of the world's great oil reserves fell into the hands...
We armed him, we fed him, we gave him his country...
...that one man, Saddam Hussein.
We made him what he is.
So it isn't oil that we're concerned about.
It is aggression.
It's all about hope.
Just wait.
I watch and learn.
It's the devils.
Devils and demons in the military.
All over again.
And why have they come to you, Stag?
Have you not considered your fate?
Because I am the one.
I am he who is foretold by the Oracle, and the Architect, and the Janitor, and the Toymaker...
He was foreskinned as chosen in the days of Santa and the Big Bombers.
He was told by the three wise guys.
He was...
He was released from his duties as one of the Herald Vipers.
I'm not exactly the one.
Bob is the one, but I'm one of the ones.
Are you one of the ones who merely witness, or are you one of the ones who merely pittish?
No, I'm one of the ones.
Just the one.
Wait.
What was that?
That was another one of them.
It's the necrotic eye again.
It's another one of them military demon things.
I can't believe that they would sign up with the...
A necrotic eye.
The minions of hell itself.
You understand?
I understand what it means.
Your eye is dying.
I mean, that seemed like something the Republicans would do, not the Democrats.
I am not in your head.
Failure to do so may result in prosecution for...
It's a myopic dream.
You have 15 seconds to comply.
It's everything you've never wished for.
You have 10 seconds to comply.
Get ready.
On dope?
It's everything you've never wished for.
You have 5 seconds to comply.
You have 4 seconds to be on...
On dope.
You have 3 seconds to spit.
You have 3 eyes.
You will become thick.
Thus with violence shall that great city Babylon be thrown down.
We're like the bullies of the world right now.
You know that?
And the voice of the harpers shall be heard no more at all indeed.
Throwing the pistol at the sheep herder's feet.
And the light of a candle shall shine no more at all indeed.
Pick it up.
This is CBN.
This is PBS.
This is ABC.
This is the National Broadcasting Company.
Good evening.
The United States of America is at War.
Esta vez se parlaba este radio.
Pick Up...
F mira estas canciones.
Estaba simple la muchísima votación iPad of flores tio pero이는 que tu no portrayós eloquemos de forma inhuman.
O mastra elHAHAHelloSaturburcomen.de.
No si si 넣or 적нд dayar elderkshowera de tacwéf questions that are not taken state orders.
Instead targets all over iraq would be obliterated.
Imagine Iraq like a human body.
What happens if you sever their spinal cord?
They can't function, right?
Tomahawk cruise missiles, F-14 Tomcats, devastating JP-233 bombs
targeted the most intense aerial bombardment the world has ever known.
American B-52s flying high above the reach of Iraqi fire.
The casualties on the Iraqi side will be extremely high.
Saddam Hussein must be seen to be the loser.
This was tremendous. Baghdad was lit up like a Christmas tree.
1,300 sorties so far.
The first airstrikes were probing, testing the efficiency of Baghdad's defenses.
On Friday, the tactics changed to heavy saturation bombing.
The first 24 hours consisted of more attacks than the entire number of targets
in the years 1942 and 1943 during the combined bomber offense in Europe.
Six minutes after the stealth bombers left,
the cruise missiles arrived.
Others dropped carbon filament to short the electrical grid system.
American, British and Saudi bombers and fighters from air bases and carriers
joined in a single concerted attack.
There's another wave of bombing just starting.
This is the first time anybody's seen a war like this.
Britain still hasn't formally declared war on Iraq.
Apparently the Foreign Office nowadays considers it a bit old-fashioned.
Mr. Ambassador, you have virtually the entire world community ranged against you.
It is an emergency.
It's an American game.
At this point, I'm not looking through my goggles and looking at the TV screen.
I gave the code word, get some.
Mr. Ambassador, we bid you good morning.
Get some.
AWACS planes, packed with computer equipment, helped control the battle.
I select my gun.
Iraqi soldiers ran through the crosshairs.
Vietnam is a ghostly state.
Gradually, they are being starved quite apart from the aerial bombardment.
Daybreak saw no letter.
New targets were sought out.
Some of those not destroyed overnight returned to you.
Allied aircraft have now flown a total of 4,000 sorties.
Many people are dying at the moment, Mr. Ambassador.
Sixty-seven hit records have been banned by the BBC for reasons of sensitivity.
Phil Collins, In the Air Tonight, Boom Banger Bang by Lulu, and Cat Stevens, I'm Gonna Get Me a Gun.
Yet the record most requested by our boys in the Gulf is Barry Maguire's The New Destruction.
What we cannot be proud of, Mr. Speaker, is the unshaven, shaggy-haired, drunk culture,
poor excuses for Americans wearing their tiny, round, wire-rimmed glasses,
a protestor symbol of the Blame America First crowd out in front of the White House burning the American flag.
But the main development in the war is tonight's scut missile attack on Israel.
Saddam Hussein has now twice sent extremely dangerous weapons into the middle of a built-up war.
The most intense air attack since the Second World War.
The system dispenses hundreds of tiny bomblets.
Allied planes have flown over 8,000 sources.
The attacks on Baghdad, Tikrit, Samarra, Nasiriyah, and Basra.
The electricity got off everywhere in the whole city.
There was no water, no telephone, no communications for anybody.
Military briefings have emphasized the threat still posed by Iraq's scum missiles.
The
Yes.
They did.
They caught me with their machenst
The Mesmeris.
Yes.
It's an experiment.
They love us there.
And we're in on it.
Yes, deep in the heart of the Pentagon in the basement building.
There are thousands of resources.
I thought that was against, like, you know, Occupation 101 rule that, you know.
I thought you learned that in Occupation 101 that you don't do it alone.
They're breaking the rules of occupation throughout the world.
They just, that's what they're doing.
They have been doing it since day one.
It's our 51st state now.
Iraq is now our 51st state.
They're getting the quick.
New Texas.
Yee-haw!
Our 52nd state.
Actually, Canada is our 51st state.
Getting plenty of money.
Pussies.
The equivalent of some larger states.
They're getting an aid in divestments.
You should have heard Cheney spouting his bullshit today.
He was saying that Iraq is going to have the second strongest coalition force.
And pretty soon, they're going to outnumber the U.S. soldiers.
Isn't that kind of like the NVA in the South Vietnamese situation?
They're doing it all according to plan.
They're purposely doing another Vietnam.
They think, well, let's not change horses since actually Bush is a flying monkey and not an equestrian.
The End
200,000 people killed in an industrial accident in India.
With a mother.
Total mother.
Hurricane killed 25 in Florida.
With a mother.
A real damn mother.
Mine from San Bernardino.
But it hurt.
It was a mother.
T-S-E-A-V mother.
There's some facts to go down.
Uh, shit going down.
150,000 people killed in an earthquake in Mexico City.
It was a bummer.
A real bummer.
It's a total fucking big ass bummer, man.
My mouth got run over.
Bummer.
P-A-B.
Garbage is getting purely for feeding the garbage out.
Bummer.
It's the bummer.
80,000 people died in the North Wing of China.
Bummer.
It's the bummer.
There was a guy in California that couldn't get his nut one night.
Bummer.
Total fucking bummer.
The guy in California was with his best girlfriend and he didn't get his nut.
Bummer.
Real bummer.
I burned my finger the other day.
Bummer.
What's the difference?
B trophy, huh?
Anyway, you're known in the world forнаutica drug.
every contrite chicken patty is adarso
You're a berman given these movies that pop on their head.
All the talking is random.
I give you one.
P Ultimately, I was we have a neighbor named
So what about you?
It's possible.
Real bummer!
TNT, TNT!
You know about the bad ass noise?
My insurance rates just went up!
Bummer!
And right after that, the news came on.
And they started rah-rah-ing about, you know,
all these soldiers who were all staging to leave tomorrow,
to go back up to soldiers.
And they're showing patriotic, you know,
and they're going to save our country from the evil demons,
and stuff like that.
I mean, I swear to God.
What, at war with demons now?
And it's like, you know.
See, I thought I was the only one.
Bottomless budget for that, man.
You know, for fighting demons.
So it's still, you know, wait till they start, you know.
We need millions and billions and billions of dollars to fight them.
There's a three to six to seven, three to seven deaths.
Africa.
Average of up to one death per day.
Well, it's a little bit more than that now.
That's got to be bumming somebody out over there.
Because there's like days with three to seven, you know.
Well, there's whole days to go by when nobody dies.
Maybe somebody loses a couple of legs.
Yeah.
A couple blind guys.
Three, four arms.
I mean, who cares about that?
They'll come back.
What the hell are we doing there?
They'll get their handicraft thing.
What the hell are we even doing there?
Yes, it's quite disturbing.
If you're easily disturbed.
Buying cheap oil for the next...
For the next 20 years, I think, was the original basic idea.
It ain't cheap.
Go cheap.
Well, it's cheap.
It's blood.
I mean, what did it cost?
It cost some blood, okay?
Oil is blood.
Blood, oil.
The blood of ancient, ancient reptiles.
Squished between tiny fossilized pieces of limestone and sandstone.
Selling us out.
Enough to brew in its own goo-goo for millions and millions.
Millions and millions.
Right in front of our eyes.
They're just going to sell us out right there.
And tell us about it, Eric.
And so now...
This is the way it's happening.
George Goblin now can give away his own guys.
You know, he can report on CIA people.
Oh, yeah, well, you know...
Oh, that's a real good one.
Yeah.
That's a real good one.
She's a CIA agent.
Go ahead.
The secret CIA leak.
How could any...
That's going to be good.
That's like God coming in with his finger.
Right here.
Oh, George.
Here's George and Cheney.
Don't know what you're doing.
Here's George and Cheney concocting things in the White House Oval Office.
Well, Mr. President, I remember when President Nixon and I got down on our knees and prayed.
Maybe this is the time to pray.
Oh, Lord.
Oh, Satan.
Oh, great Shaitan.
Oh, great eye of the evil...
Here comes the finger of Nixon.
Shai-Halut.
The finger of Nixon is about ready to come down upon me.
Yeah, just when everything looks really good.
Oh, don't worry about it, Henry.
Everything's going to work out.
Just trust in God.
Believe in the great...
Great, great, great spirit.
Just like Chief Honolung taught us back in the old days in Peabody.
You remember those, Henry?
I mean, Henry.
I mean, what's your name again?
Henry.
All right, the way we're going, we should be able to steal a few more elections.
Yeah.
I could have played organ with Grand Funk Railroad.
But it would be wrong.
Yeah, that was a great poster.
Remember the poster of Nixon?
Yeah, the poster of Nixon.
He was with Iron Butterfly for a short time.
For a short time.
But he actually did try...
He did audition for Grand Funk.
And they did some promo shots of him and everything.
And he was on Laugh-In.
And they did the one where he was like, you know...
Him and Nico.
He's like this way, looking this way, under the closer to home one, you know?
And he's like...
But, you know, there, he's always with the, you know, the peace sign up, the other word,
victory sign.
Yeah, nobody really knows about the underground tapes of him with the velvet underground.
Yeah.
Well, you know...
There's the finger of Nixon.
He was tortured then, you know?
But that makes great art, you know?
Oh, George W.
I've been walking around the boys' site for a long time now.
Nothing but bad kids everywhere.
I've been a waiter and a cab driver.
I've played a few places here and there in the lower village, but nobody wants to hear my stuff.
They all called me a dick.
They say there's something strange about my voice.
What is it, Henry?
Henry, they don't like my voice.
How about the way I talk?
I'm not a dick!
I'll bring you a news bulletin.
The express train from Monterey has been derailed outside of Mexico City.
Early reports indicate an appalling loss of weight.
There are eyewitness accounts which state that monster scorpions have swarmed around the wreckage,
creating havoc.
I don't know.
Time is running out for the planet Earth.
You don't expect me to believe that, do you?
Once again, Mr. President,
I have made the United Provinces of America
the greatest power in the known universe.
The forces of good are sworn in.
And I repeat, they must be exterminated.
And I mean lethally.
Your race has no women.
It can't have children.
It will die out.
Yes, dear friends.
DJ, Reverend Dr. Imam did that.
That was actually a clipped up part of the soundtrack
of Reverend Abdul Smithy's incredible video
called Osama's Video Fatwa.
If you ever get a chance to see Osama's Video Fatwa,
well, I will help you to try to get a chance to see that.
Hey, friends, welcome to Hour of Slack number nine.
Nine hundred and twenty.
Kind of a war-ish show tonight.
Because, well, we talked about that a lot over the months
on ESO Swamp Radio.
So there are lots of edits of that
that I kind of gathered together.
Earlier, friends, we heard that song
Total Badass Bummer
by the Swingin' Love Corpses
who are also heard in the background.
And our new title,
played at the very beginning,
was Dig Daddy Slack
by Madman Taylor.
Thanks to New Monet for posting it.
And we'll hear some
lemur cut-ups
throughout this show.
But what you're wondering is
those collages
of Gulf War history.
All that Gulf War stuff.
What the hell was that?
Well, the first stretch of it
was by the
by Soma.
And the second was by Pansonic.
And cut up a bit by me.
And those are from a deconstruction
of the Gulf War.
Sort of a history CD
mixed by various people
like Apex Twin and such like.
There's a collection called
The Fire This Time.
And for copies of that
and more information about it
you can check out
www.firethistime.com
www.firethistime.org
That's fire this time
one word dot org
educational and frightening
like the church of the subgenius itself.
And you want to know
what it's about.
But it,
what it,
what the church wants to know from you
is this.
You a backdoor beauty?
You like it from behind?
Ha ha ha.
What from behind?
Our politics?
Our preternatural existence?
Come on, Legume.
You're asking a woman
an anti-sexual question.
It's almost like having
a big man back.
Do I like things from behind?
How about from the behind
of our backs
the way we were snuck up to
on 9-11?
And literally
gripping the hands
out of the back.
That's right.
They poked America's
fudge tunnel.
America's fudge tunnel
woke up that day.
in crisis.
Very clearly.
And it went back to sleep.
Ta da ta.
jaz totalmente
en skincare bar
Y'all here for me?
Good morning,
Judgement morning, you better get ready
Judgement, my God, it's coming down
The gambler, the drunkard, the liar
And that I doubt to rest too
Well, all these false pretenders
And all them hypocrites too
Better get ready for judgment
You better get ready for judgment morning
You better get ready for judgment
My God, it's coming down
The best ever, new, better, faster, easier
Click, exit, fast, new features, so easy
New
Statistics and figures, mid-force, they're on me
L.A. watch CNN on my TV
You give me information, but where is the truth?
Sitting there, hiding behind designer suits
How can you sit there and tell me this?
Without a movement of your eyes
How can you sit there and smile on your face?
Will you show us my destruction of the human race?
Day after day, you show us the pain
How many mores have you had to ignore?
Just sit there
The films that wouldn't show to me
I didn't cry on my TV
You show me the world 24 hours a day
But it seems so unreal, cause it's so far away
How can you sit there and smile on your face?
Will you sit there and tell me this?
Without a movement of your eyes
How can you sit there and smile on your face?
Will you show us my destruction of the human race?
Day after day, you show us the pain
I've been free from it for corporate gain
Just sit there
You drag me in the face
Don't trouble me with the grief
That Assembly-to-WeWork Foundation
Without a movement of your eyes
I can't believe this
How can you sit there and smile on your face?
Out of your comfort to believe
Will this até a Yaroslavむ house falls?
Are you trying to convince your whiskersеры
Realize that the end of light would be anything but hell
Could there be a better battery to theовой
C.D. Truth.
C.D. Truth, friends, from their album Chemically Dependent.
And you can find more of them at www.cdtruth.com.
One word, cdtruth.com.
Also, you can reach them at, got that tape recorder running,
610 Phillip Avenue, Akron, Ohio, 44305.
And before that song, we heard the Lemur News,
and that song, Judgment Morning, or whatever, by Sister Mary Nelson.
But seriously, is this church of the subgenius serious?
Friends?
We're serious about fine Malaysian cooking.
Yep, I'm talking about Dobstown Restaurant.
When was the last time you had you a big steaming hot bowl of Dobstown brand monkey brains?
Speaking of frying monkeys, what is George W. doing again?
I'll take mine.
Fuck.
You said the FCC.
I'm hiding, man.
I'm getting down in the back.
I'm getting my cellar ready.
I mean, I've never seen anybody who looks more like one of the flying monkeys.
And yet folks continue to believe his lacrimonious, evil, spiteful talk.
I don't even know if anybody believes it anymore, though, either.
I don't think they do.
I don't think anybody does.
But the witch has everyone under their spell.
Yeah, but the witch has everybody under the spell.
And they'll do whatever the monkey says.
But who is the witch?
Who is the witch that's keeping the monkey?
Laura is the head of the Grand Cabal and Coven.
Oh, yeah.
Yes, she's cany.
A lot of people think that it's like, you know, old lady bush and all this stuff like that.
But no, it is.
I like how Chaney sits behind Bush when he speaks in the chamber like that.
And it's kind of he's got that cockeyed mouth thing going on.
I can't tell the guys that I'm wrong.
Say the right thing, monkey.
Tom and I are down.
There's some creature with its arm all the way up George's butt, working his jaws like a puppeteer.
He is an Augustus.
He's a sock puppet for some thing with an arm longer than his torso.
He's one of those red hankies.
And guys, it is later.
What does this remind you guys of?
This sound coming in here right now.
And you think.
In the 30s, it was so easy to make a bunch of po-bucker idiots think the world was really ending.
Now the world really is ending.
And nobody believes it.
Brilliant people to swallow.
Yeah.
I mean, they're sitting there in a chair that's duplicating itself and then evacuating itself at the same time.
They're dying in these chairs.
You know, strapped up the way they are.
And they think it's, you know, a Christmas party or something.
And meanwhile, they bayoneted Santa Claus to death somewhere near Baghdad.
It's like the world is ending and they vote for it to keep ending.
That was in Black Hawk Down.
I saw that movie.
Where they bayoneted Santa Claus.
And then there goes your leg.
There goes the top of your head.
Ah, war.
War is good.
War is my favorite flavor.
And it's Bush's flavor of the week.
War.
You know.
Coming and going idea that he can entrap people with.
Capture their imagination.
Well, he doesn't want to be looked at as one of those terrible presidents like Carter.
He should wear those weird like white knee stockings when he's do that and wave the flag and go,
Hurrah for the money, blue flag with a star.
Hurrah.
He dreamed I was on the top of an aircraft carrier.
And it looked like them guys in The Wizard of Oz go,
Oh, Rio.
Leo.
And all these flying monkeys were coming down.
Oh, Leo.
And I looked at them.
The flying, head flying monkey was George W. Bush.
Oh, Leo.
And right behind him was Dick Call Me Richie Chaney.
And, oh, shit.
War is good.
War-ooo-oo.
Money can cost the brain!
Fighting in Asia, fighting in France, fighting for my face.
War is good for large invaders, it makes the elephants cry.
War is good for man and baby, it makes things die.
War is good.
War is good, it makes the angels and the babies cry.
It's good to control the population, it makes the people die.
War is good around the world, fighting here and there
Fill the streets with blood because we're gonna win the general war
War is good, war is good, war is good, war is good
If I had a dime or dollar for all the things they said
Trying to get me back around and put me back in bed
My eyes are closed, my ears open, I cannot see a thing
But war is good for everyone, it's good for living things
War is good, war is good, war is good, war is good
Love it!
War is good, war is good
War is good, war is good, war is good
War is good, war is good, war is good War can make the angels sing and legal the audience sigh
War is good for plastic people and their other kin
War can tell you the time of day, war will do you win
War is good, war is good, war is good, war is good
War is good, war is good, war is a deal
War is good
Don't call me gringo you fucking viner
Stay on your side of the goddamn river
Don't call me gringo you viner
No me digas viner mister puñetero
Te sacare un susto por raciste culero
No me llames frijolero
Pinche gringo puñetero
Check out
Now I wish I had a dime
For every single time I've gotten stared down
For being in the wrong side of town
In a rich man I'd be if I had that kind of chips
Lately I wanna smack the mouths of these racists
Podrás imaginarte desde afuera
Ser un mexicano cruzando la frontera
Pensando tu familia mientras que pasas
Dejando todo lo que tu conoces atrás
Tuvieras tu que esquivar las balas
Desde el fondo de la tierra
De unos cuantos gringos rancheros
Les seguirás diciendo good for nothing
We're back si tuvieras tu que empezar de cero
Now why don't you look down
At where your feet is planted
That US soil that makes you take shit for granted
If not for Santa Ana just to let you know
That where your feet are planted
Would be Mexico, correcto!
Don't call me gringo you fucking viner
Stay on your side of the goddamn river
Don't call me gringo you viner
No me digas viner mister puñetero
Te sacaré un susto por racista y culero
No me llames frijolero
Pinche gringo puñetero
Molotov!
Very shortened
And before that, War is Good
Lonesome Cowboy Dave
Live at the Beachland D-Vival in Cleveland last month
With Bob and Chaz and Backup Babes
Reverend Cinzia and Princess Wee
And you know friends
In this day
Which isn't to be confused with the day
Today these days there's a law against not only behavior
But actually individualized laws against individuals
For instance what's the law against you and Ashtabula
I would think that there's somewhere there's a you know
Thou shalt not on the streets of Ashtabula do
Foul smells are strange
Apocalyptic improvisational
Nothing above 250
50 decibels
And spouting
And not only has it been passed recently in law
I guess they want to get it on the state books
Which I don't know if it's a real law
I think it's just some book about a state of consciousness
None of us have ever had
You know what I'm saying
You can get arrested for drinking while thinking in some places
Yep
Branchwater, Texas
Isn't that your original hometown?
Dead Branch
Dead Branch, Texas
Yep where the water was
The fish are floating straight up and down
Little X's on their eyes
We like it all dry and rough there
Well three I's and three X's
Yep the possums got a drooly cake and they got problems with their hoosh
Drooly cake
We use possums as the same way that you city folks use toilet paper
Now what's the difference between an armadillo and a possum down there
You got both
That's quite a difference
The armadillo of course is rough and harsh
Kind of like Tina Turner right
Smooth inside
Although possums will and they play pop they go limp on you see
Yes it's disgusting to see
You don't have to and they clean themselves
Yes
So you don't have to kill them
You'll stand back to back when I give the signal
You'll each walk forward fifteen paces turn and fire
Is that clear?
You ready mister?
Ready
Alright let's go
One
Three
Five
Seven
Thirteen
Hold it
There's something I have to tell you
Killing a man is good son
You know that
Yes sir
When you kill a man you kill a little bit of your dinner
I've never heard it said better
What is it?
This is a very arrogant apology
Well I might be old fashioned to say this but uh
That kind of Johnny
I'm going back to being proud of America
Come on use your intelligence
You know that the United States is based on the big lie
And if I didn't live in a country where there's planes that roll around
Golly
That is the American capitalistic system
Will it be tragedy?
Or hope?
Baby Janet's too young to understand the big dick
Now why should a normally decent, normally intelligent young person like John Smith
Choose the road to communism over America and freedom?
He's a victim of irresponsible tactics
He has missed the stabilizing influence of a good home and religious upbringing
Yet somewhere along the way he chose the road to Anarchy and freedom
That night I'd see dick
It is true there are three things
Wrong in this country
It is true there are things wrong in this country
Come on use your intelligence
You know that the United States is based on the
Loose morals and wanton destruction
I hate it
Let's all think real hard
And if I didn't live in a country where there's planes that roll around
Golly
Let's all think real hard
Whether it be tragedy
Or hope
Reverend Norell Preff did that
Called Golly
More at HeavyConfetti.com
Before that, The Duel by Lee Murr
Incidentally, Lee Murr has had a rough time lately friends
And you can email me, stang at subgenius.com
If you want to help
An old subgenius doctor out
Who is Lee Murr, you ask
Well you might as well ask who are you
And who is this guy
I'm an enormous erect phobos
Ready to strike your country with instant hate and venom
And plenty of nucleus, nucleus, nucleus weapons
You've almost got it right
Nucleus
Nuclear
Nucleus weapons
So I wonder what all those nuclear weapons are
And what the rat wingers think about their pill-popping fatty radio boy now
But how long have you been talking about this for the last long
Another friend of mine was pointing out
How come with Arnold Schwarzenegger
Womanizing
I'm sorry, I didn't do it
But it wasn't the wrong thing to do at the time
You know what the tabloids say
I apologize for not doing it
But somehow when Clinton does it
Then it's terrible
It's unthinkable
For a
Why can't an Austrian get away with
Popping a feel
And an Arkansanian can't
He doesn't have an Ava Brown
And a little Shotzi Dog
The better story is he has not a little shotzi dog in this country
That's why
Every Austrian needs a little Shotzi Dog
And a little Ava Brown to fondle
The better story is he has one ounce of experience for the job
But they're willing to stick the guy in there
I've got a good idea
Oh no, a movie star becoming governor
That guy owes me bacon, I'm sorry
California?
A movie star?
Governor of California?
That's not so bad
What can a movie star governor of California do?
Well my first act would be
To have the state legislature make California Uber Alice
The state song
I'm sorry
I wonder what Reagan thinks of all this
Yeah
He said
For the good of the power Stirring the cousins
And for Nelson what you think of
I'm probably going with
That what chakra into the
From those two
God
I am holding the battlefield for my Lord.
I come to obey the heavens and my God.
Thank you for realizing that war is good and the world is a monster club.
And each and every one of you must reflect that individual monsterhood
and ah, fuck this shit.
I'd like to salute the flag to which we all swear a republic
to the United States of America.
The flag known as Ogori.
Well, I'm proud to salute Ogori.
Ogori.
And the colors for which she stands.
She stands.
Red for the blood.
Pew, pew, pew.
White for the guts.
Blue for the blue body.
Bye.
This.
And I'm proud.
To tell the story.
The story.
Of the United States of oil.
They come and take.
The brain's gonna break.
Turn and live the song.
The story of the world.
Well, I'm proud to salute Ogori.
Ogori.
Oh, Ogori.
And the colors for which she stands.
She stands.
Red for the blood.
White for the guts.
She stands.
Blue for the blue body.
Bye.
Yep.
And I'm proud to tell the story.
Story.
Oh, freedom and financial gain.
Cha-ching.
Free to Carlisle.
Free to Bechtel.
Cha-ching.
Free to Halloween.
Hey, hi.
Well, Mama.
I'm comin' back to Airf Mistress Air Force Base.
Dressed in a brand new white suit.
They done some work on me.
But I think I'm gonna be alright.
Planes keep comin' in.
coming in every day.
Well, Mama, I ain't got no arms or legs.
I just got studs.
But that's good,
because I got a new job in the polling alley.
I'm going to work there every day.
I'm going to sell off my car
and sell off the house and the bar.
So I'm proud to salute old Dory
and the colors for which she sang.
Red for the blood,
white for the guts,
blue for the blue-bodied fight.
And I'm proud to tell the story
of freedom and financial gain.
Free to have fun,
free to car ride,
free to change,
free to Halliburton.
Halliburton!
Hey, hey, hey!
Well, Mama,
there's a few things I forgot to tell you.
I've got part of my head blown off.
But that don't matter
with the kind of job skills I got anyway.
I'm missing a few digits.
Ooh!
I'm missing big chunks of my skull.
Oh, what the hell!
Ooh!
So I'm proud to tell the story
The story!
of freedom and financial gain.
Cha-ching!
Free to car ride.
Free to back tail.
Cha-ching!
Free to have a bird.
I love her time.
Hey, hey, hey!
One more time.
So I want to salute
Old Dory.
And the colors for which she sighs.
She sighs.
Red for the bush.
White for the guns.
And Bush laughs and laughs and laughs
because somebody voted for Nader.
You know, I guess some people thought,
I know, I'll vote my conscience this time
instead of the lesser of two evils.
Better stick with that lesser of two evils next time, friends.
I don't know.
Uncle Simon's gonna give me thunderbolt.
He want me to fly away up above the clouds.
He want me to drop a bomb on the Japanese.
I really got to make my baby proud.
I want a machine gun.
And I want to be hit out in the woods.
I want to show old man Hitler
that Sonny Boy don't mean him no good.
I want to drop a bomb
and set the Japanese city on fire.
Not because they are so rotten.
I just love to see them die.
Well, all right.
Okay.
I've got this victory blue
Because I know I've got to go
Not to keep the dirty Japanese
From slipping into my baby's back door
Sonny Boy Williamson
Win the War Blues
from Smithsonian Victory Collection, disc number one.
Thanks to New Monet for posting this old-timey stuff
to altbinaries.slack.
Before that, Old Gory by Lonesome Cowboy Dave
live at the Beachland Devival just recently.
And that song, I'm on the Battlefield for My Lord,
was by Reverend D.C. Rice and his Sanctified Congregation.
From the Anthology of War,
of American Folk Music,
you are listening to
the Hour of Slack,
voice of the Church of the Subgenius.
You can get more information about it
from, got that pencil ready?
Box 181417, Cleveland Heights, Ohio, 44118.
That's the Northern Ohio branch office, anyway.
Learn everything at www.subgenius.com
because time is running out.
Ending World War XIX is imposed,
and it's allah.
The Union of Protestant Northern Ireland,
American Aviator,
Soviet Socialist Republics is proclaimed.
Lenin dies in 1924.
And the former German strip pole.
Oh, man.
It's real.
Of course it's real, son.
Everything's real, even the unreal.
Yeah.
The needle.
Terrible.
Yeah, baby.
Wire off, dude.
Sit down in the chair.
Take some of that smack over there.
That smack that the terrorists
are bringing into our country.
Yeah, you're gonna feel real groovy.
Yeah, man, the terrorists
brought some smack into my veins.
They'll do that every time.
It's not my fault.
The terrorists shot that dope
into my needle using my hands.
Those terrorists mind-controlled me into driving drunk.
Those terrorists mind-controlled me into destroying the Freedom of Information Act.
Those terrorists forced me to declare war on terror and freedom both at the same time.
I'm not responsible.
For Johnny Apple Seed and the Boys Under the Hills.
It's a world of death.
It loves it.
It's death.
Death.
They worship death.
Not at strip joints, they have.
No.
You ain't been going out enough, Dave.
Dollars.
Oh, yeah, man.
I've been going out plenty.
Out of my mind.
Don't you see what they're doing in the strip joints even, man?
It's everywhere.
That girl takes off this, she takes off that.
She's putting something back on in your mind.
You know what I'm saying, man?
Until next week.
Keep your head on tight.
Back to the wind.
And you're sacking the saddle.
Get that tank.
Repair.
Beneath the stains of time.
The feelings disappear.
You are someone else.
I am still right here.