It's been...
Oh, no.
Return to the swelling days of the Old West this weekend
with Mr. Rory's Hell is on a Big Diner Drive
as they celebrate their 100th anniversary!
Yes, 100 days in the business means a lot to the men and women of Mr. Rory's
and this weekend means a lot to you, too.
It means Old West prices, like a Big Rory for $1.79
or a Killer Rat Burger for $1.78.
It means Old West decor from the cattle skulls on the floor
to the bullet holes in the drive-up speaker box.
And it feeds Old West excitement, too,
like the thrill of a bloody shootout as man matches wits with hyena
or the spectacle of a herd of stampeding hyenas.
But best of all, there's all that good Mr. Rory's food.
Whether your favorite is hyena tongue or tail,
you'll enjoy it even more at a Mr. Rory's Era
as all the big hyenas drive-thru.
See your phone book for the one nearest you.
Some people need to be mashed under a large rock, man.
You're probably one of them.
Well, you're listening to the arm-twisting adventures
of your personal friend Huey on the bastard son of Food Bites of the Gods.
You're listening to KPFT in Houston, 90.1 FM.
The radio station that transmits my sick mind
through electrical waves into a box in your personal...
From the largest stock in Texas...
Hey, NON, 90.9, and you did have a sexist...
...and could express every emotion with it.
Love.
Hate.
Anger.
Chagrin.
Even contempt.
Let the beat it, King.
The Beat It King.
This was only fantasy.
I don't see that as being something you can look at as being tangible right now.
I don't...
Well, I've lost my equilibrium, my car keys, and my pride.
By this time, your fingers should be moving more quickly to the desired keys.
Also in...
What can I say?
What can a person like myself say to a vegetable?
The answer is simple.
My friends, just call...
...and I'll...
Jesus!
Oh, the intergalactic laxative will get you from here to there.
Relieve you and believe me without a worry or care.
This is Lou Grubb for Lou Grubb Chevrolet.
Listen, we've got some fine resale cars here at 27th Avenue in Camelback.
And what's more, if you'll stop out at 27th Avenue in Camelback,
you'll see us.
You can ask me for...
Ah, yes, dear friends.
This is your host, Lou Grubb.
The subgenius radio ministry hour of slack
on KNON 90.9 in Dallas, Texas.
Ho, ho, ho, ho, ho.
I'm amazed that upper tape deck works despite...
See, when George got off his show, he said,
I had an upper tape deck.
I had a...
Stay away from that thing.
It's warbling again.
And see, friends, there's nothing wrong with that upper tape deck at all.
It's playing that Walter Carlos stuff just fine in the background.
Oh, and maybe next time, I hope that next week that it's...
We know for sure it's going to work.
I wonder if there's any way...
I bet I could distort this just by flipping this little switch.
Yeah, there we go.
There we go.
Well, friends, you'll see next week,
I'm going to be out of town,
and Willa Dobbs is going to take over the show for one week.
It'll be his first time on this ugly, ugly board,
this mixing board here.
But, yeah, I've got to go on a special mission for Bob, so to speak.
But that doesn't mean that you bobbies can be breaking into my house
and stealing Bob's skull.
Or rather, the 1984 Bob's skull.
I'm sure he's got a new one by now.
Because the house, that's a subgenius castle,
will be guarded by both the Beast...
That's actually my Doberman Pinscher's name, Beast.
Both Beast and the Willa Dobbs will be in there.
Never mind the Beast, dear friends,
but beware the Willa Dobbs.
Because he...
Oh, Willa Dobbs, he looks...
You know, you hear him in the background a lot,
and hopefully in the foreground this next time.
And you can't tell much from a voice, I guess.
But he basically looks like Arnold Schwarzenegger,
only with glasses.
Sort of like me.
Those of you who know me would pretty much know what I'm saying.
So you just better beware, dear friends.
Well...
Uh, you can call the Willa Dobbs tonight at 828-9500 or 823-7490.
And meanwhile, we will continue with the horror.
Somehow, actually, I need to shut off that music
and get something a little bit more fitting in here.
Do you know what I mean?
I don't know.
The sad, weakly self-denial preached by the New Age movement
is pure conspiracy pabulum.
The true son or daughter of Bob knows that our universe
is no laid-back, home-chanting cosmos
but an active, tumultuous, squirting universe
bent on rampant reproduction and easy grins.
The false cults may try to teach personal transformation
Psychic development, human potential.
But Bob goes straight for the glands and seeks to amplify the self,
to bloat the abnormality potential of his pupils.
Only through excess can one contact the lower self,
where the real decisions are made.
Don't just eat a hamburger, eat the hell out of it.
The advanced initiate, once freed from conspiracy programming
as well as the worldly goods that had enslaved him,
makes his pilgrimage to Dobbs Town,
the church's fabulous walled encampment deep in the jungles of Malaysia.
There, the initiate's third nostril is surgically opened by psychic surgeons,
allowing him or her to whiff-read the psychic stench of those around him.
He may even be able to see the world through the eyes of the blind.
He masters the mystic sciences of schizophreniatrics and memory editing,
creating a clean slate on which Bob may write.
The art of excremeditation is taught,
whereby the mind is voided upon the great throne of relief.
What is it that truly sets Bob apart from other would-be holy men and self-appointed gurus?
Everything.
For Bob
has always existed.
There have always been Bobs.
Every epoch of man's history has had its Bob.
Most were what we would call good Bobs.
Others?
Well, we didn't dwell on that.
Boy, no kidding.
We needn't dwell on those other Bobs, dear friends.
We'll have to talk about the other Bobs tonight.
In fact, actually, I guess, Dr. Dili Lama, who is here tonight,
I think could also help us talk about the other Bobs, the Bobs who are coming.
Once again, we're going to talk about Robert Anton Wilson coming into town.
Where and when is that, my dear friend?
That will be Friday, August 7th,
at 8 p.m. at the Scottish Rite Hospital Auditorium.
You know, that's down there off Oaklawn and Maple.
Oh, friends, you want to make, you want to go see Robert Anton Wilson
bespeak the hideous truths that you want to hear so bad,
and the ones that you don't want to hear, too,
and the ones that you can't possibly truly hear.
Your ears will hear, but only the truly attuned will listen.
Truly listen.
Are you aware?
So do whip on down there.
That mighty writer, that's what he is, by the way, for those of you who didn't know,
Robert Anton Wilson is a writer, but he's a writer whose pride opened the shell
surrounding the secrets of life and death and made them funny.
And also quite educational.
An agent of slack.
True slack.
An agent of true slack.
Slack.
What is it?
Where is it?
We're going to try to figure that out now.
Oh, by the way, I should mention, earlier tonight, what you heard,
the second version of the It's Not Just The...rant
from the great G. Gordon Gordon.
The Mercenary of Bob.
He shipped that up from Brazil, from the town of Ararauama, where he lives,
and where I hope to go for fun next Easter.
And then again, when they give us $40 million to do the subgenius movie.
We'll all go down there to write the screenplay.
Of course, we'll party for six weeks and then write the screenplay on the last day,
but that's what you want, friends.
That's the only true way to do it.
This coming up here is called The Blast Supper by Reverend G. Don Truby.
Put your headphones on for this, dear friends.
Daily Llama just did, and he knows, because he's been around.
Hail Eris.
Happy New Years.
Journey public.
Has this slash?
This is the retВ requires this.
.
Okay, I'm going to try YoU V multicolORinEvA fleasS.
As you're out to lunch.
I'll take care of this.
I brought my plastic.
Simon Peter recited to me as I flopped out my wallet.
His bulging, belching, bronze-tan voice carried through the cafe.
Intentionally.
Trying to impress the boss, eh, Pete?
Paul retorted.
His bracketed, enclosed, bombshell voice.
Blast!
Booming across the never-waxed floor tiles.
Boys!
Jesus cleared his trout accordionly.
Aye, but I like it drawn.
Maggie moaned to a greasy pair of glasses.
Jesus donned the spectacle and declaimed the onside click.
When in Rome, do the Romans.
Jesus jousted.
Indeed, the Roman enumerators bug us, man.
John announced from under the table.
John found his fork and thrust his precepts in a must.
Unkeenly manner upon his stablemates.
They count on us for an explanation.
John jumped.
But Judas couldn't explain his order.
And the waitress confused did utter.
Look, mister, you must tell me what you want, or I'll be forced to use my influence.
I can't read your mind.
Then Judas spent his second folding in and had a strange vision.
He was holding the bearded lord in his wrist.
In his wrist.
Radostyle.
Rockin' to a crazy beat.
Faster and faster.
Then slower.
He heard Cab Calloway singing.
Minnie the Moocher.
He smelled the hearty wrath of twice-burned toast.
And trembling egghead Ernestine.
He touched and tasted a thousand things.
And was unsure, and modestly bounced into the street.
To find wherefore and what not on the bench.
That's pronounced guilty.
The others tittered into a street.
But Jesus savored not the heart.
Safford not.
In the pent.
Of his ugly mug.
The sky rained a million volts.
Of lightning bolts and.
And forty buckets.
Of blood and beer.
And finally Maggie skittered over to our booth.
Heaving and hoeing.
And the streaming, steaming heap of feast.
She glared straight into the very soul.
Of our savior.
Questing.
You order this weather.
Red beans and rhymes in yesterday's brains.
Read the two-inch video monitor implanted firmly.
In the forehead.
Of our one-eyed waitress.
Maggie Magdalene.
Delittlewits.
Simon Peter.
Cupped his face.
To the side of my mouth.
And whipped.
I told you we should have taken him to the awful house.
Their food is fresher and cheaper too.
But let him look at his men.
You.
Customer implicated by circumstance.
You fresh-faced side of bacon.
Too many rowers scraped the bow.
I could see, feel, and touch.
His healing glaze.
As it shot clean through the tabular sails.
In Maggie's hot sliding side slots.
Thomas touched it too.
And eagerly agreed.
Yes.
They damn well.
Should have eaten elsewhere.
But.
Hell.
Here was where I was supposed to be.
It was water.
Silver.
Leave now?
Why they looked like asses.
They'd break my glasses too.
Maggie recited to no man.
So with their heads.
On their knees.
They broke brains.
In the house.
Of the rising one.
It was over easy.
All around.
Black coffins.
Olive eyeballs.
A rim.
An English translation.
Please.
Mouths watered.
At once.
And as one.
But before feasting.
As always.
She's a swindler.
The boys rose.
He ass ended.
And performed a.
A mackerel.
Luke faked.
A knowing smile.
Of adoration.
As he had been hoping for his favorite.
The Messiah's interpretation.
Of Chinook salmon.
Fresh water.
The boys ate.
Feverously.
Judas.
The joker.
Choked on thirty slivers.
As usual.
He got a big pat on the backside.
For his deep trouble.
The lettuce braid.
And everybody.
Said it was gracious.
And the boys.
Fought.
For extolling the stone.
In front of the shameless.
Steel.
Vault.
The dirty dozen.
Ordered donuts.
In haste.
They ordered bagels.
Dry.
Then they ordered many hundreds.
Of hot dogs.
Then they ordered the tube steaks.
To jump.
Through.
The pastry hoops.
Sit up.
Big.
Roll.
Over.
And pop.
Onto their.
Twelve.
Twirling.
Tongues.
Imagine.
Their surprise.
When the dogs disobeyed.
And spelled out.
On Peter's placement.
The word.
Niall.
Yes.
The instantaneous.
Slashing.
Of teeth.
Sounded.
Like a lion cubs demolition derby of the salt.
A smoky robin's nest.
Arose from the brown.
James.
And haloed them all.
With the foul paw.
That eventually settled.
And circled around.
Judy's bolting purse.
You foot the bell.
They all bawled at the Jude.
Who had began to get under their.
Pants.
To make it better.
They all.
Fall down drunk.
And asleep.
And Jesus.
Was white.
As a sheep.
Knuckled under.
And blazed.
I'll never eat out.
Again.
And then he ate his words.
In remembrance.
Of red.
Bees.
And.
Rhymes.
Hi.
I'm Reverend Buck Naked.
Pastor of the First Naked Church of the Subgenius.
Inviting you.
To a Bob Righteous.
Full squirt.
Devourable.
August 8th.
Saturday night.
At 8 o'clock.
At the Bar of Soul.
See and hear.
Many other wild schismatic preachers.
Uber Pope Strix dominatrix.
Cecilia Smith.
Bob Righteous Reverend.
Buddy West.
Hill Swammy.
Satellite Weavers.
Dr. Chaos of the Chaotic Church of New Deep.
Deacon Tom Williams.
Not a Bob Righteous.
Bobby and the Bunch friends.
All the above administered repeatedly on the Hour of Slack radio show.
Plus.
Arch Doctor St. Margaret Moser.
High Priestess of the Cult of Chilkat from Austin, Texas.
And.
J.R. Bob Dobbs will be there.
Yes.
He's alive friends.
The San Francisco Cool Guy Bob may be dead.
But my Bob isn't dead.
Is yours?
Unfortunately.
Local broadcaster Ivan Stein is unable to attend.
But friends.
You can hear Stang on any radio.
Now these incredible ministers can spit fire.
Heal the sick.
And sicken the healthy.
Boom shakalemaka.
Way to this little snake here son.
August 8th.
8 o'clock.
Bar of Soap.
Across from the Fair Park Gate.
Praise Bob.
Free at last.
I'm not a Bobby and the Bunch dear friends.
Actually despite all the nasty nasty things that I said about Bobby and the Bunch.
I wanted to give you a special complimentary gift.
At the dar Agora Y'all run through the west in this event of the day.
Yes out.
I'm sorry.
to give a seminar in the afternoon from 1 till about 6 o'clock at the same place, Scottish
Rite Hospital.
And then I'm pretty sure that old Robert's going to end up going to the DeVival to see
Buck naked and all the other local subgeni.
And did I understand that you won't be there?
Is that true?
Oh, I'm not allowed to be there.
This is an anti-Stang DeVival.
Honest to God, it is.
Buck and I are friends on a personal basis, but on a professional basis, we are bitter,
bitter enemies.
And I refuse to appear on a stage with anybody who takes subgenius so, I mean, so unseriously.
You know, I mean, this is a religion.
And apparently, some of these other people seem to think of it as some sort of a comedy
thing.
I'm glad to see you sticking by your principles of schisms in the church.
Yeah, of course.
I mean, and I can no more tell Buck not to do that.
If he's not going to do a DeVival, then I could tell, oh, say, the New York Bobbies
or the Philadelphia Bobbies not to do a DeVival.
I'm not Bob.
And neither are you.
Not really.
And I don't want to be.
Don't get me wrong.
I wouldn't want to be Bob.
However, over the swinging love corpses, I should start talking about my DeVivals, friends.
These are the ones that Buck doesn't even know about yet.
And we've been working towards that with a kind help of David Hines.
St. David Hines, we should say, down at the Stark Club, of all places, has been donating
us video editing time.
And the mighty Reverend Court Holland, SLK, and I have been down there.
Well, last night, in fact, until four in the morning, we were down there editing the subgenius
video, Finishing Touches.
And that video will be world premiered at the Dallas Museum of Fine Arts sometime in
October.
And you'll hear about it because it's going to be one of their main shows.
It's going to be the main featured thing.
It'll be the main Saturday night thing in their big video festival that Bart Weiss is
setting up.
So you'll finally see the world premiere of the much promised.
I mean, this is what's been taking, been holding up the Stark fist is this mighty videotape.
You wouldn't believe the stuff.
We got hold of some footage last night, friends, of J.R. Bob Dobbs as a six-year-old millionaire.
And when you see it, you will fall down on your knees.
You will be knuckle walking to Jerusalem when you see this incredible video presentation,
as well as, of course, the devivals that go with it.
And this will also be world premiered at the Stark Club at some point or another.
We're not sure.
Probably also in October.
I mean, that means we have to finish this thing by then, you see, friends.
We're putting a deadline on ourselves.
So I know that I can't compete with Buck naked at the...
What's the name of that?
That little tiny hole in the wall club?
The bar of soap.
Yeah, with the...
I mean, I know I'm selling out.
Jeez, the Dallas Museum of Fine Arts.
Here we are telling everybody it's a religious...
That's the Museum of Art.
They put it in the...
That's right.
The Dallas Art Museum, whatever the hell it's called.
They put it...
They're going to put it on and call it art.
But, you know, I guess, you know, the Sistine Chapel was the subgenius video of its day.
You know?
Sistine Chapel ceiling by Michelangelo.
Well, that was the equivalent in those days.
And so now we have to...
You know, we can't show you the videotape on television because it's too nasty and bobful.
Listen, you can hear him in the background squirting.
Squirting endlessly in his endless dream.
He lives on in every one of those sandworms.
Bob is coming, friends.
And...
But, yeah, I really...
You should go to Buck's revival.
You should go to Robert Anton Wilson's revival...
The thing.
Buck does devivals.
I don't prefer to use the term revival for what I do because I like to think that it revives people.
I think Buck's definition is exactly accurate.
Absolutely accurate description of what he does.
And, friends, I do think you ought to...
You ought to...
Go ahead.
I mean, it's cheap.
And also, there are...
I mean, I believe Reverend Chastity Belt is going to be there.
And, of course, the Hell Swami.
And Pope S. Cecilia.
You know?
So there's people with whom I'm not having a terrible on-the-air feud right this minute.
So...
Gosh.
I get so carried away sometimes.
Just, you know, having this soapbox.
Imagine the temptations, friends, to say tasteless things.
It's...
About a rotten day.
But that's what I say.
Because that's what the word of Bob says.
I tell you, friend, there's no slack.
There's no slack.
I tell you, in this world, in this flesh, in this devil, there's no slack.
And if you can't whoop it, go you down, my friend.
That's what I said.
Go ye down.
There's nothing that says you can't.
The devil don't have a rule book.
That's right.
The devil.
The devil does not have a rule book.
He is not humanistic.
He is not pacifistic.
And he owes you money, my friend.
That's right.
The devil owes you money.
And so does Uncle Sam.
You have to recognize the devil just like you recognize Uncle Sam.
Now, I'm going down there to pay taxes.
As far as I'm concerned, I might as well be paying taxes to the devil.
I'm sorry, but that's just the way things are.
It's a test of faith.
And that's why God put the devil down.
Here, to see if you can tell the difference between the devil and Uncle Sam.
Let there be slack.
And I want to know if you can tell the difference between the devil and John Birkeland.
The devil and Shelly Beeman.
The devil and Dennis Bennett.
Because these people are just the first three on the list of pledgers to the hour of slack
who have not paid their dues, dear friends.
To the word of God.
There's two stangs.
God Almighty.
There's not enough room in this world for...
Friends, I want you to pay up those pledges that you made to the hour of slack.
Because the station really needs money right now.
And not only that, I need the status.
George's show, which precedes this show, has gotten twice as much money in as the hour of slack.
Now, how do you...
How do you think that makes us look?
Of course, they're on twice as long every Sunday night.
But that doesn't matter.
I want to see every cent.
Every red cent.
And I don't want to have to have, you know, the bad Bob show up at your door, friends.
Caprice.
Now, Caprice, I know you can spare that $5.
And Edgar Cayce out there in the before life.
I mean, he's a saint.
He's healed many thousands of people.
He's healed people magically.
But he hasn't paid that $10.
And in Bob's eyes, he's doomed to hell.
Mother Teresa here, she could only spare $25,000.
And we haven't seen a penny of it.
Now, Mother Teresa, doomed.
Doomed to an eternity in hell itself.
Because she hadn't paid up to this show, despite all the other good things she may have done.
And, I mean, I'm seeing some names on it.
These are supposed to be friends of the church enemies.
And I just...
I mean, I ain't...
I don't want to turn into that old drunk preacher again.
You know, I know y'all don't like that.
But before we get further into the tapes, I want to point out, I got this...
The last time I was at Glen Rose...
We have a creation science museum in Glen Rose, just like the Christians do.
But we never get any PR.
Just like the Dallas Morning News did that big section of book reviews of Dallas authors.
Who've been reprinted and never mentioned.
The book of the subgenius.
My bile is starting to rise.
I want that money.
I want those recountings of bad drug trips from y'all.
So as to prevent...
I mean, you and you too.
I mean, I know you guys don't do drugs.
But I'm sure you've had bad alcohol trips.
I mean, there's...
We need...
Bad aspirin trips.
You know, anything.
We need your personal recountings.
Nobody...
We've gotten one.
How about that?
One.
And he wrote and said, oh gosh, I...
When you first mentioned it, I thought that you'd be so flooded with material that, yeah, I didn't need to bother.
Well, apparently everybody thought that too.
And we aren't flooded with material in Dallas.
We hardly ever get any mail from Dallas.
The subgenius contributions, the stuff that we play on the air, all comes in from outside of the state.
Because I guess since we're not local to them, we're worthy of consideration.
But I guess since we're just local, well, that's not good enough.
But in...
And in Glen Rose, we're local too.
But here the Somervell Sun, this is a mighty paper, friends.
It says that creation evidence has been confirmed.
And that Dr. Carl Bough on June 16, 1987, this creation evidence team discovered a...
Within a few feet of each other on the same level of the Paluxy River.
A human tooth, dear friends, who has been dubbed Glen Rose Man.
Soon, I'm sure, to take his history next to Piltdown Man.
And his place next to who else was a great...
Well, Peking Man was for real, but they never did find the bones.
Yes, Glen Rose Man, or Little David as they've called him.
How religious.
This human tooth was found within a few feet of a trilobite.
Three dinosaur track.
And human footprints.
Plus possibly mammalian, large mammal bones.
And this is actual scientific evidence of creation, it says here.
And absolutely disproves the ten uncountable millions of examples of evolution evidence
that have been found all over the entire planet by actual paleontologists
as opposed to the spacecraft control system business.
And the designers and the dentist who analyzed this incredible discovery,
which they say this juvenile human tooth found next to the dinosaur track was blackened by the ages.
Which is unusual in the case of a fossil, because usually they're not blackened, but turned to stone itself.
But nevertheless, friends, it must be true, because it says it right here in the Glen Rose Weekly Newspaper.
And not only that, but they've provided a new spelling of the word archaeology.
Even when what they really meant was paleontologist.
So you know they must be, you know, friends, it's gotta be true.
Uh, you know, the Glen Rose paper said it, I believe it, that settles it.
Well, I've probably been depressing and nasty and mean enough for a while, I'm just gonna...
Friends, call 823-7490 if you want to know what's going on, or 828-9500.
Uh, did you have anything more to say, uh, mighty, uh, uh, Dealey Llama?
Yeah.
I've got a lot to say.
Alright.
First, I want to tell all you subgeniuses out there that hadn't paid your dues.
Praise Bob.
Kill them!
Reverend Stang was being real nice to you when he was talking to you a little while ago.
And you know what Bob does to people who don't follow through?
He'll cut you off.
He'll cut you plum off.
He'll cut you off in places you don't want to be cut off in.
That's right.
It's worse than having your head cut off.
It's worse than having your gonads cut off.
It's being cut off from Bob.
Cut off from Bob.
Copyright 1981 by Buck Naked.
Thanks, Buck.
Now, oh, who is in the, in the great subgenius video?
Quite a bit, by the way.
Um, with...
What would we do without it?
That's, with his earlier, more explanatory materials.
I, I, I just can't get into this inside joke stuff.
That some of these people treat...
I mean, this is a, it's a church, friends.
It's a church.
Well, before we, uh, we got some new Janer hypercleets coming up.
Oh, no!
Yes, we do.
We do.
The prophet Janer speaketh again.
Uh, so, so, uh...
Strap yourselves down out there.
That's right.
Girls, hang on, cause that mighty tongue of Janer's gonna be a-lashing at ya.
In just a few seconds.
Let me try that again.
We have this great technique, dear friends.
Uh...
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Praise the...
You are my shining star, guiding light, my love, my sea.
There's must of one that I feel, a deep end, just a swimming.
Never too much, never too much, never too much.
I'm a shining star.
I just don't wanna slip away.
This is not the fire show, sorry.
That huge, launching collar now.
The collar is in orbit.
All those worshipers.
I don't know.
See?
Collar dead.
Sometimes I think this was all just meant to be.
Collar all scooped up now in that collar bag, and we'll be able to set him up for a text
just in the way.
Yes, I, um, I have a question.
Private Stang?
Okay, uh, go ahead.
Fire away.
Okay, um, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh,
uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh,
I, as I was waking this morning, I was looking into my frog stash and my dog had smoke and
all my frogs.
Is that, um, ethical or...
Should I...
Refrain from that?
Cowboy down.
Oh!
Just send your dog out on the street to get a job.
That's what I do when my kids do the same thing.
Well, you got a job.
The, my, my kids
He's got a job.
He does my job.
Well, then...
Collar's fading away.
He's going around the other side of the planet.
I mean, there's a...
The blueness of a wound cleanses away the evil.
So, you know, forget this animal liberation.
Yell, Collin.
You're going through the atmosphere.
You know what to do.
You'll have to yell as loud as you can, Collin.
You'll be eating your dog in a few years.
Once the ocean rises, you'll be...
I'll be sucking your dog in a few minutes.
...place of work.
The cat.
Out here.
Well, are you going to talk or do I have to turn on the Delta Interocitor?
It's so pretty. It's so clean. It's so dull.
And those little sparkling lights, they...
They seem to walk over my mind and tell me...
Tell me over and over again.
Never again.
You know, you're going to have to go through the tortures of hell to know what that's...
To really be able to appreciate the slack.
That's the whole point.
But it's the slack you don't know that gets you.
They never talk about the pain that comes before and after the slack.
If you look at the chart, the way they draw those charts, and the way their seminars run,
it's just, whoa, it's just one big solid line of slack.
Oh, wow, look at your chart.
Just a plateau of slack.
They don't even get into the agony.
It says your navel is in Vulcan and your punto is in the doghouse.
Therefore, Spudge, don't go out of the house today.
Stay inside and put your photograph on them together.
Today could be a day to eat vegetables.
Or it might be time to put off some of that obnoxious mail you've been dreading to write.
As for you moon children, what are you doing on this planet?
Nuff said.
Next week we'll have asteroidology for the midnight.
Oh, they're really out there.
Did healing crystals kill the dinosaurs?
Yes.
Yeah, that fixed them up real good, those little dinosaurs.
It shows without a shadow of a doubt that dinosaurs practice psychic surgery.
Whoosh.
Here a dinosaur removes large goblets of flesh from a dinosaur.
Without using his teeth.
That's right, dear friends.
The dinosaurs were killed by psychic surgery.
And, uh, oh, oh.
The, uh, Reverend Dili Lama, one time pope of all Houston, just said to me, uh, not to
let him get on and start in on those dinosaurs.
So we here at this station, well the 19th century Christian, well what's he doing here
at this show?
центering us on the
issue at 9 cam place early on in the amid
of Halloween?
Cause semana just.
Yeah.
sickening views on this subject.
Gotta get a hold of myself sometimes.
When I think about what's going on,
you know they're gonna make a law.
They're gonna make a law that you can't think for yourself.
They're gonna make a law that you can't buy a record for yourself.
They're gonna make a law that Reverend Stang
and all the others like him can't write books for themselves.
And friends, this is serious.
It's funny, oh yeah, it's real funny,
and you're in your BMW now,
maybe you're going out to the Madonna concert,
and oh, maybe you're in your little Volkswagen
and driving up North Central Expressway,
or maybe you're over there in Fort Worth.
I don't know where you are right now,
but you know, you're gonna be walking one of these days,
and you're gonna,
sit back and you're gonna remember
all those chances you had to,
to do something with yourself,
to think for yourself,
to act for yourself.
And you're gonna remember Reverend Stang screaming at you
about Bob.
And it's all gonna be because of
what these creationists are trying to do to your mind,
trying to convince you
that the world was created,
that the world was created on October 23rd,
4004 B.C.
Well, it said so in the Bible.
It said so, so it must be true.
Because I know God wrote the Bible.
It must have been God that wrote it.
It couldn't have been a bunch of old wise men,
a bunch of smart alecks like ourselves.
There's 23 different people that wrote the Bible,
and that's a fact.
And Bob was one of them, by the way,
because he figured it was another way to make money.
You know, it's one of the largest selling books in the world.
He owns many of the franchises on the printing operations.
So it's just a money-making scam.
Friends.
You know,
people tend to take things for granted.
They really do.
They forget how resilient their minds are.
And unfortunately, dear friends,
that's one of those processes that snowballs,
and by which even the most privileged people,
despite getting every opportunity to become self-reliant,
and they nevertheless,
they can degenerate into big pink boy crows.
They're just crybabies.
If people are less alive these days than they used to be,
it's only because for them,
there's less to being alive.
The line between life and death
can become blurred and indistinct.
A truly dedicated worker
can keep making an income
or cooking dinner for the family
long after his or her mind is dead.
Any sensible belief
in life after death
should include the hideous plausibility
of becoming a slave
of a sick invisible ghost
that keeps shuffling back to the office
or the kitchen
or the church.
What else happens to quote dead unquote people
whose instincts
are so ruined
that they can no longer differentiate
between the so-called light
and the so-called darkness?
Huh?
It might not.
Just on a off chance,
might not that light thing,
that aliveness of yours,
get overdrawn just as easily
as its body's checking account?
After all,
for most of you,
the checking account
would have probably been your top priority in life.
It's all too easy
for us to desoul ourselves
by overdoing
just what we thought might save us.
Work, drugs, religion,
so forth.
Yet we can continue to plan
and calculate
and those things don't take many brain cells.
But we cease to feel,
dear friends,
and that does take some brain cells.
In trying too hard for things
that turn out to be unsatisfying,
we wreck the very
instincts we need
for walking that thin,
thin line between
self-lobotomizing lethargy
and neurotic
burnout.
Oh yes.
So,
get up off your butt! Get up!
That's what we're saying!
Get off your butt!
Give yourself a good butt kick.
By the way, what we're saying is
this isn't necessarily the opinions of KNON
or its management.
These are strictly the opinions of the
outspoken subgeniuses
of the Church of the Subgenius
schisms of various kinds
of Dallas, Texas
exercising our freedom that we have
in this country and practically
no other.
We want to save your soul.
We want this country to be more like Russia.
Uh,
like your reactionary
right-wing people
or your liberal left-wing people
or your middle-of-the-road
fools, simp, dupes,
nay-nay.
We're subgeniuses,
friends. We don't fit into any of the
categories you're trying to fit us into
right now. You're listening to this
stuff going, what the heck
are these guys talking about?
Where are they coming from?
Oh, friends,
if only you knew where we're coming from.
If only you knew. See,
the whole thing about this creationist stuff
is, uh,
God, you know, these people are saying
God made
all people in only six days.
Friends, the only ones
that God made in only six days
were the subgeniuses. That's right.
It took millions of years for the rest of
the pinks, the humans,
uh, to, to, uh,
to evolve up from
the pinkies. But, uh,
God only made the subgeniuses
appear suddenly out of nothing.
And, uh, for that matter, it wasn't really
God anyway. It was Jehovah One,
the alien space god from some
corporate sin galaxy.
Some UFO type of
thing only a thousand times more
powerful than your pathetic
human conception of a
UFO! And besides
that, friends,
when the humans evolved, so to
speak, evolved, this is the one thing that's
really wrong with the evolution theory.
It was a step
down.
But friends, there's even worse things out there
and Janer Hypercletes
went on the air in our, uh,
at the Sisters Station up in
Little Rock, uh, on
RC Guys Show, Real Cool Guys
Show, to, uh, to talk about
the, the terrible
prevalence we've been seeing lately.
Of buckets of naked girls.
You can actually go out and buy a bucket
of naked girls in Hollywood these
days, and we're gonna get to that tape
right after this
message.
Tonight's episode of the Hour
of Slack is brought to you by the
Weeping Cyclops Insignia Company.
The Weeping Cyclops Insignia
Company features jobs approved
by the church where, and all
manner of weird things.
Serving the public since God knows
when, Weeping Cyclops is
at Box 595-148,
Dallas, Texas,
753-59-5148.
Thanks,
Weeping Cyclops, for supporting
the Hour of Slack and
KNON.
Oh, thanks, Weeping Cyclops, and
indeed, I don't know where we'd be without the Weeping Cyclops.
And friends, you need to send for those Dobbs
t-shirts and patches, buttons,
all kinds of stuff from the Weeping Cyclops
at that
famous P.O. Box. Uh, I have
to cut in here before we get to Jayner to
announce it. I mean, when I put in Buck's
cart earlier, it was
playing only on one channel, and I was
thinking, God, couldn't they
have gone, couldn't Buck have gone to the trouble
of doing that in stereo? Then I put in
the Pope S. Cecilia's, uh, Weeping
Cyclops cart here, and it
was doing the same thing, coming out on one channel.
And I was thinking, this,
this is ridiculous, this shouldn't happen.
And in frustration, I pounded
really hard,
pounded the, uh, cart
player, and by gobs
it came to life! It's a miracle!
It's a miracle, praise Bob!
And it proved, it just goes to show,
I swear to God, this is true, friends, I
have to work with tape decks all the time,
and many, many times, those
decks go down, and I
spray them out and do things to them, and I, and they
still not working right, and I think, oh gosh,
I'm gonna have to take it to the, to the, uh,
repair guy, and I find out how much
they charge, I get so mad that I
actually pick up those decks and slam
them down, or put them in the car and drive
over bumpy roads, and
friends, 90% of the
time, driving that tape deck
over a bumpy road will
repair your tape deck. Isn't
it the truth, Willa Dobbs? It is the
truth, man! I mean, I just
hit this machine, and we got that
right channel in. The, the
acu-beating is the truth! Bob
spoke of acu-beating, friends, and
it, well, it's time to go to Jayner.
Friends, this is
sick, what he's talking about, and I, I hate to
think it's real, too, but here we
We've
got here a girl
that we recently
got from
a so-called Jayner Hyperclete's
Rick Maverick brand
bucket of naked girls.
Now, when I first heard about
this, I couldn't believe that this could
even possibly exist, that
Hollywood stars could be purchasing
buckets of naked girls on the
black market for their
pleasure. I, I thought that was
too decadent to even be real,
to even, to even be happening.
Now, now it's
true that you came to Hollywood in
1974.
Is that, is that true,
Miss Girl? Well, I don't know, I don't
know what year it was, really.
They just, they just blindfolded
me, and I was just,
like, 12 or 13, and they just,
they just threw me in a bucket,
and, you know, they just,
they gave me acid and
all kinds of drugs, and...
Oh, my God. I know, it was just
the most abhorrent thing
I ever heard of.
And so, you were led to believe that
you could get a part
in a film?
Yes, they told me I would be a big star,
they told me I would be the biggest star
in Hollywood ever, and, and
they showed me contracts, and
everything, and,
but, I've just been in a bucket
since I was 13 years old,
and, and now I'm 27.
This is the most...
I wanna know
when my first movie's gonna be.
I mean, what about this, what about this big movie
I'm supposed to be starring in? This is the most,
this is the most horrible, I think the public has a right
to know. We found, this is,
we found a warehouse
of buckets of naked girls
on the outskirts of Hollywood,
believed to have ties to Rick Mayweather,
and Jane or Hyperclete.
I thought, I thought the whole thing
was a joke, some kind of prop
for one of their quote unquote
skits. But,
upon opening one of the so-called
buckets of naked girls,
we found this girl. It took us two
weeks before she was even able to talk.
So well had she been
brainwashed and trained by the
maniacal
white slave owners.
Now, is it true that your, your
skin has been chemically
processed to reject
clothing? Yes.
I can't even, I,
one piece, one inch of
clothing just touches my body
and it just disintegrates. It just,
I can't wear clothes anymore.
Why are you flashing all that, baby? I just, I
I can't put on gloves when the
freeze comes down. I don't know what to do.
I just, I'm just
doomed to be naked the rest of my
life in a bucket. I mean, what
can I do? It's not so bad, really.
This is tragic. I mean,
I'm embarrassed that we're even having
to talk to you up here
with you naked. I mean, this is completely
sexist for a liberal
like me. Yeah, y'all oughta see this.
I mean, really.
Oh, come on,
R.C., give her a break.
This is a human being.
This is just one of the most, this is the most
sick, degenerative
thing I've ever encountered in all my years of reporting. It is sick, friends.
It is really horrible.
And, and, uh,
Dr. Hyperclete's here has been reporting
for a long time. Of course,
some think that this is just a giant
advertisement for the Hyperclete's bucket
that naked... Robert Wisdom just walked
in. By the way, his show,
The American Music Party, is coming up in
less than ten minutes.
But, uh,
he walked in and said, uh,
they are saying bucket, aren't they?
Friends, I'm gonna try running, just out of a sense
of fairness, I'm gonna try
running Buck's cart again.
Here we go.
Stereo.
Hi, I'm Reverend Buck Naked,
pastor of the First Naked Church of the
Subgenius, inviting you
to a Bob Righteous
full squirt devourable
August 8th, Saturday night at
8 o'clock at the Bar of Soap.
See and hear many other wild,
schismatic creatures.
Uber-Polkstrix dominatrix Cecilia Smith,
Bob Righteous Reverend Buddy West,
Hill Swammy
Satellite Weavers, Dr. Chaos
of the Chaotic Church of Meadley,
Deacon Tom Williams,
not a Bobby in the Bunch, friends.
All the above have ministered repeatedly
on the Hour of Slack radio show.
Plus, Archdoctor
Saint Margaret Moser,
High Priestess of the Cult of Chilkat from
Austin, Texas, and
J.R. Bob Dobbs will be
there! Yes! He's alive, friends.
The San Francisco Cool Guy Bob
may be dead, but my Bob
isn't dead. Is yours?
Unfortunately, local
broadcaster Ivan Stang will be
unable to attend, but friend, you can
hear Stang on any radio.
Now these incredible ministers can
spit fire! Heal the sick
and sicken the healthy.
Boom shakalemaka! Way to this little snake
here, son! August 8th,
8 o'clock, Bar of Soap, across from
the Fair Park Gate. Praise
Bob! Free at last!
This is John Shirley, science
fiction writer. John Shirley.
John Shirley sent
in his bad drug trip tales,
friends. Where are yours?
Are you aware?
Are you aware
that sound is movement of the
air?
Are you aware?
That music reaches out to
shake what's there?
Can you feel it?
It's a physical force
An unseen touch
An hidden touch
An expression of its
source
Are you aware?
I'm...
That a ghost
runs it's fingers
through your hair?
Are you aware?
And did you know
That sound is a kind of light
Moving slow, kind of blind
Yeah
Can you feel my sonic fingers?
Can you feel these sonic fingers?
Can you feel all sonic fingers?
Can you feel my sonic fingers?
Sonic fingers
Feel this now
Can you feel it?
Well, it's a physical force
An unseen touching
An expression of its source
I'm touching your flesh
I am touching your flesh
Right now
Are you equal to this test?
Will you welcome this invisible guest?
Are you equal to the test?
Will you welcome the invisible guest?
Can you feel my sonic finger?
Can you feel a sonic finger?
Friends, I know you can feel it.
I know you can feel it.
Are you up to it?
Will you go through, will you make it in that final test?
You can find out by writing for information.
You don't even have to send money.
You don't have to send money.
Not even a dollar.
Just free for information.
Not like what you get.
Well, at, and friends, you can write to that,
to that mighty Bob himself at
P.O. Box 1403-06
in Dallas, Texas 75213.
That's right.
Write for information to Bob.
Box 1403-06 in Dallas, Texas 75214.
And stay tuned for Robert Wisdom
in American Music Party.
This, by the way, this instrumental going out
is by Martin Mothersbaugh.
I honestly have no idea where or how it got here,
but it did.
And I, we do know it's him.
That's what G. Gordon Gordon said.
And he'll kill you if you disagree with him.
Praise Bob.
Who he'll move?
Muddy.
Who?
Tell me who rakestop?
Could it be?
I mean, did you?
Start the Aurora?
Witty.
You covered a native spot.
Ooh, that's not something any of the New York people
Thank you.