Get healthy. That's all I can say. One God, one aim, one destiny for all, one race.
The human race. Our slack coming your way right now.
Yes, sirree, Bob. It's little old me, Bob.
And welcome to another edition of...
...the show that's not going to agree to a ministry hour effect with people in defense.
And I wonder if I'll end up becoming something weird.
You won't become one of us.
Real professional, huh?
Well, here's Dave again. We're saved.
Yay, Dave!
I'm saved right now. The holster's back.
I've lost the boot width, though. I mean, the cream you put on.
So I'm getting confused about that.
You lost your bootlick cream?
Yeah, I lost my bootlick cream.
Because of some kind of perfunctory arrangement with the, you know,
heretofore banditos of space, or whatever they call themselves now.
Hmm.
I think they're all secret Rosa Kruisinger hillbillies or something.
And in my long association with the Los Angeles...
I'm...
Go ahead, Dave.
I like it when you make that funny noise, Dave.
It's like, it's a form of lozenge that we've used for many years now.
It produces a psychedelic vision, which can be translated in many different ways.
Because the soil, the earth itself, is the wellspring for the, you know...
It's peanuts, all right. It's cream.
That's peanut butter.
I'll tell you, I'm in such a flagrant state of mind.
I just, I can't fix on one thought for longer than anything.
I'm in such a flagrant state of mind.
Oh, oh, oh, I'm sorry.
What was that?
I was having trouble focusing.
Focus if you can't take a joke.
You were kind of there with me or something, you know what I mean?
Yeah.
Actually, Princess William and I are both a little spaced out.
And it makes sense that we would have to carry the show on for an extra half hour or so.
Because this is the one show that started with me saying,
we can't wait for this one to end because we've been working all day and we just want to go home and sleep.
So, of course, Keith calls up and goes,
I'm not going to be there in time to take over Dr. Sinister's show, so you guys have to keep going.
See how it works.
For the rest of the night or for a brief time?
Until a crap radio starts.
Until Mr. Keith can call.
Until the crap radio songs?
I can find that.
I can tell you're not a regular.
WCSB listener, Dave, out there in Ashtabula.
I guess.
Oh, wow.
Well, I used to be until WCSB decided so nicely of it to give the airspace that was bequeathed to it by the Federal Aeronautics Administration and the FDA and CIA.
And instead they gave it to Reserve.
They gave it to CRUW.
Or CWRU.
And they.
Well, I can hear them.
But now I can't even go by.
There was a gutter on my house that I could go underneath that and pick up the station.
Yeah, your neighbors used to complain about that.
That's why the FCC changed the law and have the other station have that power because of you in the gutter.
No, that was the.
They were report.
You were reported many times.
I think that was the patrol boys or some some auxiliary police force.
I don't think it was the CIA.
I don't think it was the CIA or anybody.
Any of those alphabet groups.
You don't think it was.
I don't either.
Oh, Bobbo, the predecessor.
Bobbo.
Oh, Bobbo.
Not Bobbo.
The predecessor.
As in, thanks, Oh, Bobbo.
Yeah.
I know what you mean.
You know, I feel the same way.
I don't know which way exactly that is, but I certainly commiserate with you and everything you've done over the last 25 years.
I think it's been a great.
What?
Great help to mankind and all of the people there in humans and the nonhumans alike.
I think really, really.
I think he's just saying that because he thinks Oh, Bobbo is listening and he might be.
Oh, what if I actually go?
Bobbo is great.
Like a tiller, the hunter or something.
Well, then you'll get a free Oh, Bobbo phone.
Oh, yeah.
I read and I read.
I'm a poor person and I don't want.
That's right.
I read that on the Internet.
I don't want to eat food either.
Or, you know.
Right.
I read that on the Internet that people the only reason people vote for Oh, Bobbo.
The predecessor is because he gives them free phones and he promises they'll never, ever have to work.
And of course, all Oh, Bobbo knots don't want to work at anything.
Yeah.
That's not a coarse form of laughter.
It's more like the kind of lunatic giddiness to it.
You know, the.
It's a funny sound show again.
We have to stop meeting like this.
Compadres.
Why?
I think that's obvious.
People who.
You're not.
If you are trying to recover from being some sort of insane patient or something, you've
been treated before for one of many, many diseases now that there are.
Yeah.
And.
Well, you know what I mean?
Hey, hold on.
I.
pot that one down because I don't know what words.
The.
Rudy Schwartz project.
Yeah.
Said.
So.
This is a confusing.
Disc.
It said Rudy Schwartz Project Instrumentals, and obviously that's not all what it was.
Are we safe yet?
That's not everything.
Yeah, because sometimes he launches into some blue stuff.
There was that song about Sarah Palin's juices that was a real favorite of mine.
Oh, one of my favorites, too, though.
So just thinking of the idea of Sarah Palin's dribbling juices down upon my side.
Actually, if listeners wanted to hear the Sarah Palin, I can't say the whole title of it, but it's a type of juice, and it's by the Rudy Schwartz Project, and it's on YouTube.
And Reverend Joe Newman of the Rudy Schwartz Project made the video himself, and it's really something to see.
Sarah Palin's.
It's something juice.
Is it the one where she can see the Russian tank a bit stuck in front of her house, and the guys come in there and say silly stuff to her?
No, it's not that.
It's a song, and it can't be played on broadcast radio in the United States.
Let's just put it that way.
It was on it.
You know, we have to save some stuff for the X-rated hours of slack that are only heard on the Internet.
You have to be careful.
Be careful watching that video because it can put you into a flagrant state of mind.
You don't want that, Dave.
Flagrant.
And especially from a small whittlings of wood comes a mighty forest of oak trees.
Right.
You know, you've got all these pieces of so-called material.
As we like to say in the arts, you've got all your material there, and it's all legally covered in bondage and other things.
You have to go through the case.
I'm sure.
But needless to say, it's protected like a conundrum.
I don't know what qualities we're arguing about anymore.
I don't even know if I want to be a Hindu on the side.
Protected like a conundrum?
Huh?
Yeah.
Like one of those waxy outcrops.
I thought you were talking about podendrums or something.
Yeah, yeah, podendrums.
There's coffee.
Those poor scops.
That's right.
Scopsies.
Yeah.
And poor Dave.
Really.
The things Dave did to himself.
The things he cut off.
Off of the inside of his head.
Yeah.
Think of all the neural passageways that have been interrupted.
Think of all the neutrinos that have been acid washed.
Neutrinos.
Aren't those subatomic particles that go so far?
Aren't they so fast they travel backwards in time or something?
Aren't they?
They're boring holes through you at light speed all the time?
Well, yeah.
Not just through me, but also through you, I'm pretty sure, too.
It's everybody.
Right.
Yeah, not just you.
Almost everybody except...
There are selective neutrinos, but not, you know, to that...
Well, the Bobion particle is a type of neutrino that passed through the stem of Bob's pod.
Going straight...
Right.
Came through the back of his neck and then into the stem of the pipe and then up out of the pipe.
And then back again the same way.
And that's how all of this started.
That's how we ended up here doing this.
Wow.
At this moment.
Right where we are sitting now.
A collection of tubes coming out of Bob's pipe and into his head and back.
And that's pretty much all it is.
A neutrino taking that path.
Well, it's got to, you know, have...
A medium to travel on.
You know, that's what I thought you were talking about.
Well, it slows down when it hits Bob.
That's the only thing that can slow down a neutrino.
Or a Bobion.
That's the thing that is.
It's Bob's face and head.
These are like stones, mud and stuff.
What's the word?
And like, man, it's like the hardest thing there is.
I'm the softest thing there is right now.
Because I had to do so much hard lifting, heavy weighting.
And I'm a little bit of a laborer.
Now I'm all soft and weak.
And wimpy and floppy.
Soggy.
I completely understand.
It's soggy everywhere.
And I have very flaccid shoes.
I have the kind the Eskimos wear in the summer.
Which is infrequently, you know, if you know what I mean.
Yeah.
And my arches are doubling up.
Oh, at least you have arches.
You mean yours have fallen?
I never had any to begin with.
And that's why I didn't.
Oh, you great cathedral that then ran to the Sunday.
These flat feet of mine kept me out of Vietnam.
They really did.
That's a good thing you did.
I was signing up, man.
I was pounding on the door.
The recruitment office going, let me in.
I want to kill.
Blood veins in my teeth and all that.
And they went, sir, Mr. Stang.
I was still just a mister then.
You're not good enough for the people.
The army because of your feet.
And, you know, I've been on those little pups and pups all day and they're they're barking
and aching.
Pups is barking.
I can understand that.
Oh, yeah.
Especially if your ankles are touching the ground for crying out loud.
I know what you mean.
In fact, in fact, Princess, we and I made a important decision today.
We decided that rather than have a few set, a couple of subgeniuses help us move all this
stuff from this house to this other house.
We're going to call a moving company.
We decided that as well.
It's not our money.
See, it's it's it's the Queen Mom's money.
We naturally tend to think we better do everything ourselves.
But after doing about half of it ourselves, I started to think twice because my my flat
feet became convex.
They they they became hunched.
They became hunched feet.
And Princess Wheel.
Well, it's true.
I started bleeding spontaneously right here in the in the radio station.
He speaks truth.
Yeah.
As soon as the show started, my my knee bled like stigmata.
Yeah, I couldn't.
There was no explanation for it.
And I've left a bloody I left a bloody Kleenex here for Dr. Sinister.
But he's not going to be here now.
Oh, man.
You can't gross out.
I'm not going to talk about Dr. Sinister tonight, dear.
Yeah.
So that beautiful story ended in this in sadness.
Tragic, chagrin.
Yes.
Yeah.
So, yes, scabby.
Just call me scabby.
I remember old scabby.
Poor old scabby.
Scabby days.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
I was talking about the Popular Mechanics article with the nudist colony ad.
Do you remember that?
Pardon?
No, I don't remember.
I thought sure you were the one who mentioned this to me the other night at the party.
I thought when we were talking about the unmentionable part of the party, you mentioned that.
And I told Senator Gawler and Congressman Frizzler that he got the best we can do right now.
Okay, okay.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, right.
Okay.
Yeah.
What else?
Well, when the Franks invade Europe, we're all going to be in a heap of doo-doo.
Well, we're going to be in between two heavy buns when the Franks invade.
Wait a minute.
We're going to go invade the Franks, aren't we?
Well, you're talking about going to some pool party or something.
Is that what you mean?
Right.
Yeah, but next week we'll still be doing a show.
Next week will be the same old drill, strangely enough.
And then after that, it'll be canned hour of Slack shows from X-Day all the way down for about two weeks.
Some of them are really good.
Some of them, there's one that's like inside jokes from one end to the other.
And I know the listeners, they'll catch on to which one it is.
And they'll go, this must be the one he was talking about that was really inside jokes.
I might as well just turn this off because I won't get any of them.
In fact, that could be the introduction for that show.
Because I kind of need to cut some of it up.
I talked about Philo's divorce and mine and the real names of people and Monster High endlessly.
Real people.
Yeah.
When you were back when you were a farmer back in Iowa, I think, wasn't you from the, isn't it?
So let this serve as an introduction to that particularly incite-y hour of Slack recorded at Wisteria on July 1st.
But it was the second hour we did that day, you see.
Ah.
And you even hear me realize that the cookie has come on.
Thank you.
Thank you for continuing to hold.
Hammered that one out.
It's.
Not much as could be.
So now we're through with the hour of Slack.
What's happening now?
Well, no, no, Hal.
An hour of Slack is just starting right now.
Oh, boy.
A smorgasbord of exciting events will proceed directly from this spot through the magic of audio.
Well, it hasn't proceeded right because when I said that, I was expecting monster movie music to swell.
To come crashing on.
Thank you for continuing to hold.
But it was very low volume monster movie music.
Well, you're telling me.
You're the one with the earphones.
There's above average wait times at this moment.
Please continue to hold.
And your hour of Slack will be available shortly.
If you are of average wait, please continue to hold.
Independence Day, 1996, which was.
Okay.
Incidentally.
That's a pink holiday.
Hit theaters on July 5th in 1998.
Coincidence or conspiracy?
It was the movie Deep Impact that hit on July 5th, 1998.
Another coincidental conspiracy.
And the year before, I think, 97, was it Armageddon?
An Armageddon.
Every year.
What's the big movie this July 5th to get the conspiracy people to ignore us?
And every July, there's a big movie where the humans win and the aliens lose.
People like that sort of fiction.
Which one is it this time?
I wasn't paying attention.
Huh?
What is the big summer movie where you're supposed to watch instead of going to X Day?
Right.
It would open this week.
Yes.
I don't know.
It's Tugboat Annie meets Guts.
I am so proud that when we asked that question, not a single person pulled out an iPhone and
started poking.
Of course, it's true that we don't have that good of Wi-Fi, but I'm proud of you subgeniuses
for not Googling that the minute we asked.
If thy iPhone offend me, pluck it out.
Thank you.
Ah, yes.
Yes.
Okay.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Please continue to hold.
I need to say I'm sorry for Dave.
I'm sorry.
We apologize for this delay.
Actually, I need to save Dave by sending him his phone money, and I'm saying that in a
So now you can do it now that you're all right with the computer god and everything?
We're not quite all right.
It's up to Nicky Deathcheck.
The kids are all right.
Everything's a very good thing.
I'm asking them what they can do to win this Caucus T אם.
So we have insecure headphones.
It's like an
Why don't I appreciate it.
Do you think some pre runtime waiting makes sense?
Not really.
Danny Pily became a complete weird guy, and that's why I didn't hyper Advisory have language
impacting Out of the Sen like this.
I thought we would almost all but it be no interest to Harry, who though, aspirations
forungs all挫
ciao.
Second hour of Slack recorded at beautiful Wisteria in the year the conspiracy calls 2014.
Which could be 1998.
We're hoping it will be.
And the conspiracy also predicted on their AccuWeather.com or whatever it was that there would be thunderstorms and lightning.
Do you see any thunderstorms and lightning?
I think they were simply trying to warn people away from coming here.
Trying to scare us.
Having one hell of a time.
That backfires.
Yes, exactly.
Now there have been times when lightning struck right out there while we were doing the show.
And it even seemed to travel down the hill to the grotto.
To the grindhouse.
Cue 2012 lightning strike at hour of Slack.
Yes, we put these effects in in post.
That's the second time we'll do that this week.
You'll hear it.
Yeah, right.
It'll be on the soundtrack.
Right there.
Boy, it's this great sound.
It was such a fabulous sound.
The pristine recording.
It sounds like stereo, but it's not.
The roar rather than the laughter of heaven from an irate Jove who's had just about as much as he can take.
It even managed to shut up G. Gordon Gordon, Dr. Hal, and me.
Yes, that was a moment of stunned silence.
A moment of silence.
They really topped the topper that time.
And then I never saw a human run as fast as Fight C. Tosh down to where the lightning had struck,
which was all of his electronic equipment for the grindhouse.
Fused into blobs of slag.
Lucky he had backup.
No, he actually took a little scalpel out and he carved the slag apart and just recreated it.
I thought he had a genuine Benjamin Franklin lightning.
He was a real lightning rod down there.
Um, sort of.
There was a lightning strike at the other campground, which was really crowded.
It was right in the middle of Starwood and it hit a metal pole that was embedded in the ground.
And there were all these merchants up and down the road around that pole.
And the ones that were barefoot got knocked out unconscious.
Nobody was really injured, but a lot of them got quite a buzz.
And Bleepo's girlfriend at the time, who was one of the people who got knocked out, she was small and barefoot.
She said, later I said, how are you feeling?
She goes, I feel like I've had this one set of batteries my whole life and they've just been changed.
Recharged.
Also, she was having trouble doing the math for her t-shirt shop and had to get a calculator.
Yeah, it does kind of play Hob with the interior calculator.
But like Frankenstein's monster, you can't.
You could be charged or you could be blasted like a tree stump.
You see that you can never tell.
You can't arrange it to your liking.
Once again, it's in the lap of a god.
How come lightning kills some people and makes others immortal?
Oh, it only makes dead people immortal. That's right.
Also, lightning seems to fall from heaven as a thunderbolt hurled from Jove.
But it actually rises from the place of the strike to heaven.
So...
So, the...
Lightning's from Satan?
Well, lightning is from you.
Yeah, it comes from underground. It goes up at God.
But Satan's underground.
Right. And God is up in the sky.
That's good. When you see deeble horns just sticking out of the ground.
But mama told me that thunder and lightning was when God was playing bowling in the clouds.
Well...
I was told that too.
God controls Satan, you see. God controls everything.
So, actually, both of those things are right.
You blame him for the whole thing.
Yeah.
I'm mad too, God.
Yes.
We can't blame Bob.
War on God!
Boy, that hasn't been going very well.
It made...
We had a great few speeches in the early years of War on God.
About our war on God?
Yeah, but, you know...
Well, that doesn't mean it's over.
We...
That's about as far as you ever get with that.
Hmm.
Funny how that works.
Yes. Well, I...
And yet, there were people who got angry at us for saying that as if God needed help from a bunch of nerds like us.
Like...
I just don't get that.
You know?
I mean...
Some people are just never satisfied, Stan.
So God was offended by subgenius humor, so you have to help him get even because he can't do it himself?
That's a pretty wimpy God, if you ask me.
They're toadies, you know, like tattletales, people who run the slide projector.
Jesus, Jesus, they said horrible things about you, Jesus.
Don't get personal.
Jesus, I heard him.
I heard Mr. Stang, and he said some really horrible things about you and the whole Holy Trinity all in one.
Hey, how many people in this stadium were the AV kid at school?
Raise your hand.
There you go.
Look at that.
Man, it must be at least a fifth of the entire audience.
Well, you know, I'm speaking in an affectionate way.
I appear to be reprimanding and scolding, but this is all part of humor.
I still am.
Nerd.
Well, Suds is the other AV guy.
He's doing it right now.
No, he's just the A guy.
He's not the V guy.
He's running the AV right here.
He says he digs the V.
He's more of an A than a V.
It's the Suds theme.
Oh, it ended.
V for victory.
Oh, well.
Yeah, but the AV guy in my day was 16 millimeter projectors and...
Slideshows that went with a record.
I suppose I should raise my hand in that context.
Yeah, I would think so.
But you knew that I operated those devices.
Well, yeah, we both have FCC licenses, I bet.
Or do you?
I do have it, although I don't have my wallet with me.
But I do have my radio broadcaster's license in my frickin' wallet.
Well, boy, we'd get in trouble if you didn't have it on you.
Yeah.
Well...
But I got it.
I think my...
And you know what, folks?
It's free.
You can write for one and just ask for one.
And the feds will send you a broadcast license.
That's how I got mine.
They assume that if you ask for it, you already know enough to have one awarded.
Do it now before they change it.
I seriously am surprised that you don't have to have a license to have a website yet.
When they think of it...
The day that I understood what the World Wide Web was, I thought, I better do it.
I'm gonna take advantage of this while it's an outlawed Wild West, because they're going
to regulate this like television and radio, and it won't be the same ever again.
And it won't be for...
There'll be an underground of, like, ham radio, whatever, pirate broadcasting types using...
Hey...
The underground internet or Usenet or something, like I still...
The Umbernet.
The Unternet, yeah.
The Unternet.
Worse than the InfraNet.
Or the Ubernet.
They...
You're not supposed to know about the Ubernet.
That's only for the 1%.
The 1% of what?
The 1% of owners of stuff.
Oh, oh.
Stuff.
Well...
Their internet has 3D feel-a-vision porno.
I don't know how I feel about that.
No pun intended.
Well, you wouldn't know.
You probably will never find out, because you and me aren't gonna be in the dome.
You know that, right?
Yeah, that's true.
I mean, we'll be on the saucers.
But...
I've gotten to the point...
Where the saucers not show up for some reason.
I'm so sure...
And the dome goes up.
Yeah.
There's gonna be those who are in the dome.
John Shirley used to ask me this.
He actually asked me this seriously.
He said, this was like 20 years ago, saying, are you gonna be in the dome or outside the
dome?
And I honestly...
Was doing research.
I was so naive.
And the church was, had a...
Was more new and fresh and famous here then.
And I said, yes, I'll be in the dome.
God, what a dome.
You're reading a book.
You're either in the dome or you're out of the dome.
Dude.
You're either on the bus or off the bus.
You're gonna be those guys clawing at the outside of the dome.
The Sardau's dudes laugh at.
Yeah.
It's the way it is.
They'll laugh at you.
They'll laugh.
I can't believe that I ever was so vain as to think I would end up inside the dome.
You probably thought this show was about you.
But Bob.
Bob will be in the dome.
Oh, Bob.
Bob won't need the dome.
And neither will we.
In theory, we'll be in a much better place.
We can build our own domes and have our own robot slaves clawing at the dome outside.
The rest of us will be sitting outside the dome and be so poor that we have to wank off
to animated GIFs instead of real videos of porn.
There's a South Park where that happens.
Some of those animations aren't too bad.
No, they're great if used as your icon on your, you know, as your face.
Right.
I've run into people leaving comments on Yahoo News articles using a Dobbs head.
Instead of a little snickering, sneering, smiley face?
Yeah.
And so far, it's all been libtards that use the Dobbs head.
Wouldn't you know it?
Well, you know, I wouldn't be surprised either way.
Socialism.
Oh, no.
He works, Bob works every form of capitalism.
Bob is in the dome.
He's everywhere.
Or lull socialism.
I guess.
Lull socialism.
If communism took over, he'd be the commissar of something.
Don't turn around.
Uh-oh.
Did you bring your special papers down with you?
Which?
Like those?
No.
Oh, well, too bad.
Yeah, we need those documents.
We need to be papered, actually.
We, uh...
I don't know if anyone around has the...
Do you have copies of those documents?
Up at the cabin.
Not here.
No, no, no, no, no.
Suds, do you have any copies of documents that you might have on your person?
On microfiche or tunafiche or...
Do you have any copies of documents like that?
They don't have to be exactly...
Oh, Princess Wee has those.
She rolls oregano up in the...
She won a contest for that last year.
Yeah.
It doesn't have to be this particular brand, but I think...
I think that's...
I think we might have some documents either in...
Do you have any on your person?
I have an embarrassing lack of papering.
Princess Wee uses those things for something.
I don't...
I don't have any in my bag, but check...
Oh, well, who cares?
Just an idea.
I made an error.
You'd think there'd be a pipe around here, wouldn't you?
A peep.
There are.
Sud Spishaw is seeking out documents.
He's lost the end of his already, but that one's plastic.
He will...
I believe he has some documents.
Bob has the kind of pipes that you smoke the pipe.
You don't smoke what's inside the pipe.
The pipe itself catches on fire.
Reverend Two Beans is here.
And you suck the...
You actually suck the burning plastic of the pipe.
Well, that's what I was afraid of.
And that's what gets you high.
Those phthalates.
That's what Bob smokes.
People are always going,
Yeah, but that's marijuana.
I ate it.
No, no.
It's the pipe itself.
The phthalates.
I think...
Well, beans are...
Too plastic, man.
I just made it up.
A ball pipe, and then I believe...
That's not true.
I do believe Sud Spishaw went looking for documents.
Well, he's a good fella.
I'm just gibbering and jabbering up here.
I didn't mean he had to stir his stumps and go get some, but...
You guys are shameful.
What are you...
What do you mean?
I'm a nice person.
How is it that you...
That I'm to take that remark?
Could you perhaps elucidate what you just uttered?
Well, let me put it this way.
Hey, man.
Got any hay?
We tell people not to park.
Can I...
Is anybody selling hay out here, dude?
No, no, no.
I don't want your straw.
Keep off that straw.
A mother load of greener fodder are coming.
You and your straw.
You straw pusher.
Just setting up a straw man to knock him down.
You keep off of that straw, beans.
The thing about...
You shouldn't put your V-hickle on the hay because it might poot out some...
No, no, no.
...oil or something.
That's just slang terms.
It's all...
That's all those...
Those...
The hip kids.
They're talking about vehicles and straw.
That's just...
That's just slang terms.
I was there when...
You mean they're really talking about drugs?
...Baby Bear had to drive...
Oh, is that what you guys are talking about?
I'm sorry.
I completely misunderstood the whole conversation.
What are we supposed to be talking about?
We're supposed to be keeping off the straw, man.
Oh, man.
I understand.
It's...
Oh, thank you very much.
You're talking about some kind of youth drugs, right?
You have to explain this kind of thing to me.
I'm not up on...
The straw is hardcore stuff.
...what kind of crazy things kids are...
...shoving into their arm veins now to get high.
No.
I wouldn't know.
I wouldn't be the kind of person to ask about that.
Do I look like somebody...
But here's the thing.
...running around smoking dope?
Why couldn't you figure this out?
You have a vehicle that makes you move.
The straw makes you move.
Don't take your drive, your vehicle that you drive,
don't take your drive to the straw, man.
Don't let the straw drive you crazy.
And if you put your vehicle on the straw, you might sink.
You might sink down into depression because you've been on the straw, man.
Don't you get it, man?
Oh, there was an old soldier...
China?
...he had a woody leg, and he had no tobacco, no tobacco, did he beg?
He said, I, old soldier, will give me a jaw.
Said, he, young fella, I'll be damned if I do.
Sorry about that.
You're on so far.
Yes, I ain't got no legs.
Help me, somebody.
My legs are on far.
Yes.
It makes me cry to hear those old hymns like that.
Yes, yes.
Certainly the glow...
...of nostalgia perfuses those ramblings and rantings.
All you had to do for material was listen to the car radio, the Christian channels,
especially in Dallas for a little while.
And, boy, we had Kay Sky, voice of the gospel.
My friends, I have sinned.
I imitate preachers on that station every day of my life.
And it took.
Ah, yes.
Yes, it had an effect.
There is...
There's another one of the streams of the genesis of subgenius.
What would we do without Jimmy Swaggart?
What a name.
Yeah.
Yeah, and his blubbery full-screen confession.
Oh, I had...
With the makeup and the tears running.
Yes, Suds had that on last night on the big speakers.
I ran that on Hour of Slack about a month ago.
Yeah.
Classic moments.
The panting antics, whoever they were.
If Swaggart had done that rant with...
With that music in the background,
he could have started a whole new religion.
I got stuck with Falwell growing up.
Oh, no.
But that's...
Didn't he die?
That's like listening to Arnold Stang instead of Mick Jagger.
It's really, yeah.
Falwell's not a lot of fun to listen to.
He's sort of kind of...
He's just a blubbering guy that just talks.
Yeah, he kind of drowned.
Oily, oozing, oleaginous.
Yeah, Swaggart.
Man, he'd have me down...
Down on my knees begging forgiveness from Jesus
every time I watched him.
Well, there's a seeker born every minute.
And as soon as it cut to a commercial, I'd be,
oh, wow, man, that guy's good.
Just like when Dan Close took acid
and read every Jack Chick track that he had.
He was a Christian by morning,
but fortunately the drugs wore off.
Right, yeah.
Oh, that's happened to me many, many times.
I've been a believer in all manner of new age,
dopey stuff, parapsychology stuff.
The 100th monkey and the 100th monkey's 100th parasite.
The 100th Manson, the 100th Hitler.
All of those.
You named some stupid thing and I believed in it,
but I always came back to Bob.
That tells you something about stupid now, don't it?
Yeah.
The stupidest.
But the stupider it looks, the more important it probably is.
The more important it probably is.
Yes, the little boy in the back there.
He's serving as an example for your discussion.
This campground is full of them,
and I consider myself among their ranks.
Because, friends, I am, unlike Bob,
I am the kind of person I'm preaching to.
A bad employee, a lazy slacker.
Bad employee.
And an asshole boss.
Anybody who's self-employed.
There you go.
Anyone who's self-employed has a fool for a boss, they say.
I've not.
I thought about that.
I'm a horrible boss and I'm a boss.
How good are you at bossing yourself?
Well, if you ever become self-employed,
you'll know what it's like to work under you.
And you won't be pissed off.
You'll spend every spare second on Facebook or doing something else.
Complaining about that slave driver part of your personality.
I do that now.
But the problem is when you're self-employed,
you're not paid by the hour anymore.
I'm not sure what you're paid by.
You're not paid by J.R. Bob Dobbs either.
I have to write myself a check from myself.
By each agon of discomfort that you feel
and each drop of blood-infused sweat that you excrete.
That's right, ma'am.
We have four days and we don't have to worry about this.
Well, there is that.
I mean, have you given up hope?
However, habit is...
No, no, not at all.
...a very strong thing.
Well, you know, we have bad habits.
Exactly.
You know the world's going to end,
and yet you still go ahead and pay off that credit card.
I feel like a sap.
You go through the motions.
I feel like such a jerk when I do that.
I pay my bills.
It won't matter one way or the other.
Well, this is true.
It's just ridiculous.
But you feel better by following the dictates of routine.
And if you're a neurotic,
you have to follow the dictates of routine.
If you count the steps every time you run out of your house,
if you run out someday without counting them,
even if you're late,
if you're a neurotic,
you have to turn around and go back
and count those freaking steps
before you can go on off down the street.
Now, I'm not saying we're that far advanced into it.
What about neurotic erotics?
What about them?
In other words,
unnecessary movements and maneuvers are performed
instead of only those that are...
necessary and inspiring?
Is that the word for it?
Neurotic erotic?
Yeah.
I'll have to Google that and see.
Forget it.
Neurotica.
Just interested.
Nothing personal.
No, no, no, no, no.
I understand.
It wouldn't have anything to do with what happened three days ago.
Or that Jerry Lewis movie,
The Playful Proctologist.
Three days.
Ago.
Compulsively.
Yes.
No, no, no.
Nothing to do with that at all.
There's no...
You weren't supposed to know about that.
You're diverting.
You're diverting into talking about personal matters
here on the, quote, radio...
I did not know.
I'm a thing, remember?
I'm not talking about anything.
Let's talk about machines.
I'm talking utterly hypothetically.
It's all hypothetical.
I used to use those,
but I gave them up just in time.
What, machines?
A hypothetical.
Oh, yeah.
Hypotheticals, yeah.
You get really hooked on them.
The refills are bad.
I will say that.
The refills on the hypotheticals.
Yeah, the Jesuitical type of...
The Jesuitical type of reasoning
demands the inclusion of hypotheticals,
which are not to be considered heresy
when used in an argumentative context.
So hypothetically...
So hypothetically,
we're coming up on the end times.
All over the end times.
We're coming all over the end times.
Pardon me.
And hypothetically...
Philo.
Jeez.
I'm simply...
Well, you...
Channeling Philo.
He ain't here to defend himself.
Are you being ornery?
All's fair in love and war.
Bob comes again and again.
He comes.
You know, Philo is really a great scatologist.
And one thing that happens where I live out in California
is every now and then they have these model train shows
where they set up hundreds of miles of model train track
in all gauges
and they have trains running this way and that
and you can go
and they also sell all the train stuff
and puzzling evidence...
goes there
and he buys obscene miniature train stuff for Philo
because he knows Philo loves it.
Because you can buy tiny outhouses
with tiny people sitting on the toilet
with their tiny pants pulled down
and tiny people having sex
and tiny artists using a tiny unclothed model.
All of that is for the most obsessive,
demented model train layout person.
And puzzling evidence...
out of the kindness that he has,
a bottomless well of,
knows that what Philo likes the most of all
is some tiny, exquisitely fashioned,
crude, dirty joke
embodied in extruded plastic.
So that's what he gets.
His wedding to Chaos McMomacat
was done on the theme of shit.
Yeah, they had a brown-themed wedding.
In fact, before they were married,
I saw her perform in a number of...
and fudge done in little rolls
and it was just...
and of course lemonade.
She called me to get his phone number.
Did you know that, Stang?
I was the cupid, the broker of that.
So it's all your fault.
You pimped Chaos McMomacat to Philo.
I did.
Praise Hal.
Because if it wasn't for that,
I'd have not a single subgenius
to play Monster Hunter with online.
But, thanks to you,
giving that phone number,
there is little Lily Drummond,
aged seven,
the only other subgenius,
ready and willing to help Stangor
in his video game.
This example of the rising subgenius generation
is terrifying
in her all-inclusive embrace of monsters
and everything that one would expect
a stereotypical little girl to shy away from.
No Barbies for her,
only,
grotesque reptilian, uh...
Well, you've seen
the way, what she lives,
the way she lives, right?
I'm her little brother.
I've been, uh,
I stay at the Drummond's for three weeks every year.
And, uh,
I'm the babysitter,
and really it's the other way around.
Lily bosses me around like a little brother
and explains to me how to do stuff right.
And, uh, yeah, the first time that I went to stay there,
she looked at me real seriously and said,
I'm not like most little girls.
I don't like all pink stuff and kittens.
I like monsters, especially dragons.
And, um, so we had a fast friendship.
Uh, how one's heart flutters.
I liked little girls.
Actually, I've got a whole lot of friends,
really good friends that were little girls and little boys,
because I often get along quite well with kids.
So it's very easy for me to slide right back into it.
Oh, you're just a big kid, Stan.
You know, it's because their toys are so cool now.
Man, I used to have so much fun on Christmas Eve doing things like assembling Skeletor's castle.
So that, you know, the kids would wake up in the morning and there it'd be.
Well, I got to assemble it.
You know you can buy toys for yourself as a grown-up.
If you have the money.
As a matter of fact, Princess Wee and I went to Walmart to seriously scope out which Monster High girl we were going to get.
How many of you are Monster High fans?
Any Monster High fans out there?
She's the only one who even knows what it is.
Have you seen it?
She's probably outgrown the crowd.
Okay, good.
You see Monster High.
It's this cool show about these cute girls who are monsters.
He never heard of it before.
My wife and I went completely nuts.
And I've seen every single one.
Every single one of the webisodes.
They're great.
300 and something webisodes.
They're well-written.
They're sensitive.
They're everything that they should be.
Yeah, Euchre didn't get into it.
Echo Bad did.
Yeah.
I knew that Echo Bad had some of the dots.
But Echo Bad doesn't even care about the videos.
Right.
It's more of a collect.
She just wants to collect the monsters.
Well, Stang, which is your favorite babe from Monster High?
Is it Frankie?
Well, Frankie is the one everybody loves the most.
She's the best.
She's gorgeous.
But there's always one that fits your fetish a little better.
And my initial favorite Monster High girl was Ghoulia, who is the special student.
She's the daughter of the living dead.
And they're very slow.
And, in fact, she talks like, uh, uh.
Draculina is pretty cute.
I like Draculina a lot.
But here's the thing about Ghoulia.
She's also, although she goes, uh, and walks slow, she's the smartest girl.
And the school can do anything with a computer.
And she wears glasses.
And she's a little lopsided.
So, whereas these are monster girls.
But, let's face it, they're all really pretty.
And there's all this stuff about, don't bully people who are weird.
You know, the whole thing is about, you know, weird is cool.
Don't be bullies.
We stop hate.
But there's only one weird-looking chick, and that's Ghoulia.
And so, I was.
It's really hot for Ghoulia for a long time.
Although, lately, Abby Vomitable, daughter of the Yeti, has been turning me on.
Because she's big.
She's tall.
I like Cleo, too.
Cleo is very attractive.
Cleo Denial.
Cleo Denial, yes.
And we're also advertising this apparently conspiracy show about monster girls.
But it has a subgenius flavor.
So, we're totally allowed to.
It does, in fact, have a very.
It's for tween-age girls.
It's a Mattel franchise.
It only exists because they had leftover Bratz bodies they couldn't sell.
And needed heads to stick on them.
Well, a lot of great things have been created by accident.
So, let's not look down on these accidents of birth.
And, on top of that, whoever is doing that Monster High stuff has some respect and knowledge.
Here it is.
They know the monster chops.
So, they.
Yeah, and it's classic.
It's the classic monsters.
Well, one thing that I thought was quite progressive that they did was they caricatured normals as goofy idiots.
The normies.
And their animation of the stupid goofing normals is delightful to see.
And the cops.
The cops, of course.
But the cops are buffoons in every movie.
Yes.
That's like this.
That's classic.
Princess, we and I decided to join the Monster High online club.
We joined the club.
And so, we started thinking of funny names that would fit, you know.
I tried Peep Peep Long Stalking.
Wouldn't take.
I tried Audrey Tistic.
Nope.
I would do Frankie.
All of your submissions are creepy, though.
That's why they wouldn't.
I used Reverend Seek, which is.
Which is what?
When you get Dr. Jekyll, Mr. Hyde, and he takes the really good drugs, he turns into Reverend Seek.
Dr. Jekyll, Mr. Hyde, and Reverend Seek.
And that's.
But they didn't.
And so, they let that one get through.
Well, they were asleep at the switch.
There's another one.
J. Paul Yeti, which I never used anywhere.
Hmm.
Well, so there.
There's the subgenius cast of Monster High.
I remember one year we were going to do a Deadwood.
And I remember the script with sub.
Only it was subgenius up.
And it was Dobstown instead of Deadwood.
But it would have required everybody here.
About 20 people each having this 60-page script.
Well, I wasn't going to print up 60 copies of it.
And nobody else brought their copy at all.
I forgot.
It would have been a nightmare of people having to cram around the three microphones.
Philo was going to be.
What's his name?
The hero.
The cool guy.
My hero.
Swearingen.
Yeah.
Al Swearingen.
The great Al Swearingen.
That guy is my mentor.
I wanted.
Everybody wants to be Al.
But Philo was the one who turned me on to Deadwood.
So, I let him do it.
And I was going to be Doc Cochran.
Because I can do a fairly good.
What's his name?
Boy.
I think that cookie I ate just now.
I guess that's.
I couldn't remember.
I couldn't remember Brad Dorff's name.
The actor, Brad Dorff.
And I realized, okay, I ate too much sugar.
I'm having a sugar rush.
I can't remember anything.
Oh, I thought you were talking about that girl, Cookie.
No.
She came on to you.
A moment of silence for Cookie.
cookie. Okay, that's enough.
And a moment of silence
for scabby days.
Okay.
Everybody's, you know...
Those are quick moments. Yeah.
Well, it's radio. You don't want to have a moment
of silence, a very long moment of silence
on the radio. No, those are called dead air.
Everything is scoped now
dead, you know, so that it's
scoped and done and configured within the format
on there.
Not on mine, of course, but
you know, on yours.
Yeah, on yours.
On yours, not mine.
It's on yours.
It's all a false rumor,
Sang. There's nothing
wrong. Everything's
fine. All the stuff you've been reading,
everything on the internet, Facebook,
everything you've been taking on, it's all
puddin', man. It's puddin'.
Puddin',
is that some new internet term?
Slang? I don't know.
Should it stand for something?
Is that like
lol?
Or
or
those other
yeah
internet
database
what was the name of that movie?
I'm going to
actually, that happened
I probably
more than I
wiki
or google
even
yes
we do
a lot of
Mdba
Internet Movie Database
Oh, you are one of the boss of users
or Mdba
Internet Movie Database
it's got every
it's like you go
what was that
what was that movie that was
it had Jack Nicholson and
and Shirley MacLaine
what was it you just type in Jack Nicholson and Shirley MacLaine
and all five of their movies pop up and you go
and you go, oh, I'm going to watch that movie.
Oh, right.
Tender Heartbreaks of
something else
or whatever, you know, whatevs.
Yeah, really just think about all the work Stanislavski did for those guys
and they don't can't even think of what their characters thinking.
That's what I hate about modern science.
You know what I mean?
I'm sure you don't.
I can't even hear modern science.
I have to have subtitles all the time.
What do you have, what do you have, what do you have, what do you have, what do you have, what do you have, what do you have, what do you have.
Do you have any more of those cookies, Stan?
Yeah.
Don't tell princess we.
It's a lunch break.
I'll just gobble a couple of those
to satisfy the inner man,
the pangs of hunger.
All these names will come to me in about 30 seconds
when I quit thinking about it.
Best quit talking about that nerd stuff.
Get back on to the subject that blesses my heart.
The doctrine of JR Bob Dobbs,
his beloved,
the creator of the movie,
word. As if that's not nerd stuff.
Oh, well, but yeah,
I don't have to look at a script for
that. I don't have to remember anything.
It just comes out automatically.
You just have to turn on the southern
accent, but it only works if you really
have a southern accent.
Pretend southern
preacher thing. You can't
imagine how tedious
that sounds to the real ones.
Well, it doesn't have to
necessarily be like, you know, it's not
necessarily Texas or Georgia. They always
imitate Billy Graham.
Right, right, right. It doesn't have to be southern
southern. It can be like Appalachian
or, you know,
Piedmont. That kind of thing.
But it can't be...
It shouldn't be fake.
I wouldn't try to preach in a fake
British accent. That would be...
Well, right. You can't be from, like, New York
and then, you know... I can't do that either.
Suddenly...
I...
You can't preach like a New Yorker.
See, I can't even do it.
And another
factoid, the swimming pool at
Monster High has no
bottom. Much like
Reverend Richard Skull, who just walked in.
What
episode has the swimming pool in it?
Well,
there's a movie
called 13 Wishes about a
magic lamp and a genie, and
the nice genie escapes from the lamp
and the bad genie decides she's better off
in the lamp, and then the lamp is thrown
into the swimming pool, which
is bottomless.
So, probably nobody's going to find the lamp
for a long time. His old sequel, isn't it?
And everything will... Hey!
Now, see, there's another correspondence.
How would he get there, anyway?
His old sequel. I mean, he can do
anything. It's like the underground
tunnel that leads you to
McGilligat's Pool. Right.
Yeah, that's the first thing
that comes to my mind. Nobody asked how Nessie got in
Loch Ness.
They don't say, well, how'd Nessie get there?
Well, that recent photo,
that's appeared on the internet of Bigfoot
riding Nessie and waving at the
camera ought to settle people's
minds
about it one way or the other.
You saw that one, didn't you, Stang?
Recently came out.
A big meme, huh?
No, not off... I can't think offhand.
But if I had seen it, I still wouldn't
remember, so it's a moot point.
Alright.
Memory.
This is one of those hours of Slack
that's probably going to be cut up and interspersed.
with a bunch of Rudy Schwartz project music.
Chopped into a thousand slivers.
Or something.
I'm getting old. I need to stand up.
Well, we don't have to
stay here. We can always put on
some more of Susie's
X-Day collages or
this.
See, there was my cut point.
I can't even hear modern
science, and I have to have subtitles
all the time.
Yeah, I think
that would be very, very
rough on you. And I think
there's a moment of silence for the roughness
that you're absorbing right now.
Okay.
Well, the subtitles
that go with this show, for instance,
are obviously some computer
is doing it. It's
some kind of voice recognition
thing. Because I'm looking at
the subtitles, and it doesn't even spell
subtitles right.
Well, how do I know you're real
for crying out loud? I'm calling... I could be
calling up a machine right now.
Yeah.
Duh.
I think that's been the point of everything
we've been saying for the last hour
and a half.
It's all been made by a machine.
A three-year-old machine.
What I'm saying now
is being generated
by a very advanced
computer.
And
I am an electronic...
Well, somebody said something on the
internet. They're going,
Oh, I
hate to think of Stan dying, because
then he'll leave all those terrible,
horrible people in charge.
And I
had to admit, I'm sorry, but I've
been dead since July
14th. Yeah, you were
the walrus. I remember, and
especially in the Abbey Road cover,
that you were the one that had
the really flat, bare feet.
No, no, you're thinking of some other Ivan
Stang. I
died July 14th,
but CGI is so
unspeakably good these days
that I sound
pretty real, don't I? Sounds like the real me,
right?
That's how good the CGI
is now. I'm dead,
and yet, look how...
How's the 3D? Here, look
at that. See?
I'll do it. I'll do it.
That's beautiful. Yeah, it
looks real as heck.
You look a lot better in the hollow than you do
in the real one. Yep, that's me.
Old CGI...
guy.
See, there was my cut point.
This, too, was the son
of Bob. That just...
That was the
scissor space.
The Susie space?
The scissor space. The cut space.
That's the spot where I'll look to
cut to whatever it is that I play next.
And now this is a big space of cut.
Because this stuff gets edited a lot.
The first show we did Sunday night
will probably put out
exactly as is, except I've got to insert
the lightning strike.
But everything
after that, we're going to have to edit
that stuff. Well, add comical
sound effects and
a snappy music track.
I just need the boingy thing.
You've been listening to the
subgenius radio ministry
hour of sleep.
Slack!
For free information,
write to
P.O. Box
181-417
Cleveland Heights,
Ohio
or see
www.subgenius.com
Praise Bob!