We now return control of your television set to you
until next week at this same time
when the control voice will take you to...
Bob!
From the land beyond beyond.
From the world past hope and fear.
I bid you, Bob, now appear.
Oh my gosh.
Bob!
The following transcribed program is transcribed.
Friends, if you like rubbers, let's keep punching Bob till the Japs get theirs.
Tonight, as usual, Bob brings you Final Victory.
Meanwhile, don't hear Bob the greatest name in rubber.
I don't want to be no human being.
No!
Don't you call me no human being.
I ain't no human being.
Good work.
I'm a no good low down on principle crook.
We want you to know that we will interrupt this program instantly.
Bob?
This is a coordinated monthly test of the broadcast stations of your area.
Equipment that can quickly warn you during emergencies is being tested.
Bob?
If this had been an actual emergency, official messages would have followed the alert tone.
This station serves the area.
Bob?
This concludes this test of the emergency alert system.
Attention please.
Please, attention please. The commanding general will speak to you. Stand by.
Friends, it is imperative that you listen closely.
We're coming. Better see if they're strapped down.
The women here have been praying for God's help and guidance.
Julie's coming.
Not your kind of hypocritical praying, but the kind that comes from deep inside a man.
I'm sorry. I'll come back later.
No, no, Eddie. We can't put things off till later.
Go.
We're the lucky ones.
I told you this would happen.
Now, to again emphasize our problem, most of it will be consumed,
but then, in turning completely around, every ounce will be needed to avoid crashing.
You don't know what people will do to avoid crashing.
Because in these boxes we have placed numbered disks.
Of doom.
And so will you.
One disk.
Of doom.
, destroyed the atomic bomb.
The world will note that the first atomic bomb was dropped on thousands and thousands of young Americans.
We shall continue to use it until we completely destroy the atomic bomb.
Destroyed, destroyed the atomic bomb.
Hey, the new year is coming, hallelujah.
Well, when I was up vomiting.
Seven days a week, 24 hours a day.
Amen.
Surprise, surprise.
And this ministry is...
Loving.
We love you.
Skate, all skate.
Bear bundle ladies choice skate.
Choice USDA rump all ladies choice.
Hey.
Ain't nobody, Ain't nobody.
A more method than duck choice!
...
We'd like to remind the duck people to stop humping in the middle of ...
... Odd í‚¤ï¿½ consistence.
of ak...
It's not a time.
Become dull.
program. No time. There's no time. Shaggin' Hussain, your teeth are wearing down. Your
canine incisors are those of an evil dearest. That just sounds like another plate. Just
sounds like one of the many plates in my head. Just another plate in my head. When I come
back from Iraq, I have the Gulf War Syndrome. I have the psychosocial panic plaque in my
heart. You'll be Gulf Warped. I have a displaced ticket book. All of my tickets are punched
and I have bad kidneys.
We don't want to replace you, Sergeant. We just want to replace you with a fighting machine
that's capable of fighting like a machine without eating rice or beans or eggs or living
silently alone and masturbating himself to sleep. No, we want a super soldier, my friend,
not the Hunan bean.
I have no problem with your fight. I play with my nozzle already, even trying to fight
you, doesn't it?
I'd love to.
I think that's so important to everybody. To me, it's just another monkey.
Yeah, sure, it was just another monkey until we tapped him. Yeah, that's what we call it
at the old institution. The institution for higher one-eyed blind science. You're our
favorite secret society. You're our favorite member. You're our favorite glistening golden
member.
Yeah, stupid son of a bitch.
George Bush was tapped by discovered crossbones in 1968. And since those days of yally holly
tides at Yale U, he's done more than a few favors for more than a few fields of his own
personal qualities. Let's name them!
Who took my girl away?
And what do my dollary people have here?
These are lavatories, and central stations, and once a formerly great place of business,
and also a transportation channel that lovely blocked thousands from view. You can make
it down to some of those husky sub-Norwegian plots that's down the road. You can drop
pretty much everything without fear of the rats eating it.
I would like to remind each soldier about to give his or her individual life or lives
that you give it not only for the United Snakes of America, but you give it for Halliburton
Inc.
For Exxon, for the mobile Exxon, for BP, for Dutch Mobile Air, for fried suits and the
gristly air.
Ah!
I'm at Carrots Glen.
Are you gonna put up with that?
HECKATEEN!
NO!
Keep on dyin', keep on dyin', keep on dyin', keep on dyin'.
The bullets flyin', the bullets flyin', keep on dyin'.
Keep on dyin'.
Keep on dyin', keep on dyin'.
I had a strangest dream.
I dreamed it was over the plains near Passa.
I call it a desert, but it's still not a real desert.
It was a man with a pipe stuck in his pookie, smoking his furnace and drinking.
I think I'm gonna be alright man, I took too much of the fucking acid.
I think it was a dream, but it's still not a real desert.
I am the blood of Galah.
I am the menstrual blood of the world.
No, man, I think you're an idiot.
I'm gonna have to shoot you.
Okay, okay, so we got our freedom.
But management's lousin' up everything.
Labor is at fault.
It's ruining the country.
My constituents, as your elected representative,
I can assure you labor's right.
Management's right.
I'm strictly neutral.
Labor, management, politicians, phooey.
They can't tell corn from oats.
Work, work, work, work, work, work.
Hurry, hurry, hurry, step right up, folks.
Here's the answer to your problems,
Dr. Utopia's sensational new discovery, ism.
Ism will cure any ailment of the body politic.
It's terrific, it's tremendous.
Once you swallow the contents of this bottle,
you'll have the bountiful benefit of higher wages,
shorter hours, and security.
Enormous profits, no strikes.
Remember, you're the big boss.
Government control, no worry about votes.
Name your own salary.
Bigger crops, lower costs.
Why, ism even makes the weather perfect every day.
And now then, because we are introducing this amazing item
for the first time in this country,
it isn't going to cost you one cent.
All you have to do is sign this little scrap of paper,
and you get your bottle absolutely free.
I hereby turn over to ism, Incorporated,
everything I have, including my freedom,
and the freedom of my children,
and my children's children,
in return for which said ism promises to take care of me forever.
I will kill you, folks.
I will kill you.
Too much.
Ah, get out of the way.
This is PR News from North Carolina,
offering weapons of mass destruction
to most of the people who are still in Washington.
Support for PR comes from American Dead People Foundation,
building a dead world where dead people reject young people.
www.americandeadpeople.org
PR
American Dead People Foundation
This is PR News.
UN weapons inspectors have begun examining Iraq's 12 people who are still without weapons of mass destruction.
Iraq submitted its opposition groups door-to-door yesterday in Venezuela.
The U.S. and the four other pages of information on its permanent UN Security Council members
following last week's snow and ice storm on its weapons program.
From Chicago, PR Radio, opposition groups report.
Anti-government forces say they have failed to report to some unqualified leftist president
and could cause a plot to overthrow him.
It's unclear whether the United States is crude.
Maracas.
NPR's President Bush reporting from the Iraqi capital on the east coast.
PR.
Hundreds of people are still without weapons of mass destruction.
At least the National Guard went door-to-door yesterday offering weapons in Venezuela.
This is NPR.
This is PR News offering mass destruction.
PR.
If I ever run into you, I'm going to break your arm off and shove it out of your throat.
Now, now that I got a chance to regain my health, you want to send me back to the city.
The city.
I can see it all now.
It's high.
Cruel.
Ominous.
Closing down on you.
From every side that you can't breathe.
Closer.
You can't breathe.
The traffic.
You can't think.
Beep, beep.
Look out for that truck.
Honk, honk.
Look out for that taxi.
Boing.
Beep, beep.
Arrrr.
Honk, honk.
Beep, beep.
Honk, beep.
What's that?
Look.
It's the towers.
They're falling.
Arrrr.
He can't stand dangerous, dangerous, dangerous, dangerous weapons.
Of course you realize this means war.
According to one conspiracy, the trade centers were faked.
That is something that will take us a long time.
It will take us a long time to wrap ourselves around.
Now whether what we were watching were simulation exercises being transmitted as the real event,
it's a possibility which needs to be examined.
It needs to be examined closely.
There has in fact been almost a media blackout, a kind of a deliberate American policy that's
been basically there since the war in Vietnam and we saw it in the Falklands War and the
Gulf War and now in the NATO war against the former Yugoslavia.
And it's been there for a long time.
And now again in Afghanistan where the military do not want the media to be involved and the
American media have been complaining bitterly that they haven't got access to what's been
going on.
They didn't destroy the two towers.
It just didn't seem real.
We thought it was something out of out of a movie.
Just a little while ago one of the volunteers who tried to go down there and help report
it back and said that you actually got to the scene at the World Trade Center what was
most remarkable, what was most amazing, what was most essential.
most horrifying is that basically nothing was happening. This is nearly a
10-acre site deep in the Nevada desert. They didn't destroy the two towers, they
destroyed a number of buildings, a lot of open space. A secret film studio deep in
the Nevada desert. Here, two hijacked planes slamming into the World Trade
Center were staged and filmed before the footage was transmitted to a gullible
world. At the World Trade Center, what was most remarkable, what was most amazing, what was
most horrifying is that basically nothing was happening. Basically nothing
was happening. Basically nothing was happening. Basically nothing was
happening. Basically nothing was happening. There's enough evidence there to make me doubt.
That is something that will take us a long time to wrap ourselves around. Now
whether what we were watching were simulation exercises. They didn't destroy
the two towers. Being transmitted as the real event. They didn't destroy the two towers. It's a possibility which needs to be examined. They didn't destroy the two towers.
It's such a multilayered and
complex
complex situations needs to be examined closely. In order to retain the prestige
of American industry throughout the world, they had to fake it.
Private, public, and the rest of you guys with funny names. Mount your pieces, lock and load.
Hand on over here by the perimeter. Stop laughing, the IRACs could hear you and blow your head off. Okay.
See that over there? That is a fully transitional lunar module capable of
risking us out of here in a matter of five seconds if we so desire. If not, we
may take that objective below. See it? Put on your night glasses. There it is. See it moving around like little blue snakes.
I can't see nothing, man. This ain't working. These night glasses ain't working.
Get your earmuffs off your eyes. Take his earmuffs off his eyes. There's no reason why. There you go. Now see them little blue snakes moving around?
Yeah, cool. Those are Saddam Hussein's. The evilest, vilest critter ever invented.
I hate them Saddam Hussein's. Each one of them's got a weapons of mass destruction. That's right. See that one over there?
He's got a weapons of mass destruction. Yeah, and he just... I got one right here. Want to see it?
Oh, no. Put that thing away. All right. You think you're going to get off that?
That looks like a great big giant motorized vehicle. Yeah, I think he's overexposed himself.
He can go back from the front. He can go back home. There's no way. What do you do with it?
What do you do with it? You're going to get banged down.
Is he torturing a prisoner with a banged down? No, I think the prisoner enjoys being tortured in that way.
It's not real torture.
Well, I think that you're going to let him go and let him go and let him go and let him go.
You're going to let him go and let him go and let him go and let him go.
Yes.
I'm going to let him go.
Yes, I'm going to let him go.
Oh, my God.
Baby, my baby!
Yes, and that last horrible, horrible noise
was my baby, my baby by Blue Marmalade
off of the old subgenius album called Bad Doctors.
Also, of course, we heard ESO Swamp Radio
from WCSB in Cleveland with host Chaz Smith,
Lonesome Cowboy Dave, Princess Wee, and yours,
truly Reverend Ivan Stad.
The Great Twin Towers Hive
The hoax, that collage about the hoax
of the Twin Towers, and there's more of that to come, by the way,
is by Reverend Buttress O'Neill.
Buttress O'Neill, that's spelled O-apostrophe-K-N-E-E-L.
Buttress O'Neill, I believe from Australia
or one of those under-down places.
And, yes, Buttress O'Neill and Colossus,
mega conspiracies.
Friends, we've had a lot of cuts and clips in this
and surrounding Hour of Slack shows
from New Monet and Artemia Salina
and others on alt.binaries.slack
who've contributed a lot of cuts,
but everything else on this show,
I mean, all the collages on this particular show
are by Fernanda Nande-Limor,
all those amazing cut-ups of sound,
the great...
Fernanda Nande-Limor.
Well, also, I found this great old cartoon
called Make Mine Freedom.
We heard some of that.
And because this war stuff,
friends, it's gotten even me upset.
It's gotten so weird.
Like the other day when all of our watches and clocks
suddenly switched over from, you know,
regular civilian time to military 0800 type time.
So, now...
Then you have them read.
You say cranky and ornery, man.
Moby Dick.
Your watch went over to military time.
Remember John Goose Passage?
Yeah, it's still...
And I can't get it to go back to regular 12.
And yeah, my computer clock went over to military time
all of a sudden.
But they'll read it backwards.
No, it still says 2003,
but it went into military, you know,
22 instead of 10 o'clock.
Well, we are all on military time now.
And time is running out.
If we'd like to quote Mr. George W. for war...
The balloon toots have dropped.
The balloon toots have hit the...
The fatula.
And the...
The...
The fat is...
The chase is on.
Hit the griddle.
Sliding.
Well, actually, no, it's...
The race is running.
There are weeks...
Here comes heartbreak,
hung up behind the...
There are weeks...
Don't say that.
Of surroundings to happen.
Weeks of smallpox inoculations for the lucky.
And weeks of procrastination for the guilty.
In front of the head of the smallpox goddess,
thousands and thousands...
Millions.
Millions of snakes.
Electees ready to be inovulated,
as the president likes to call it.
Round her head.
Inovulated with the smallest pox they can find.
Micro-inventesimal tiny little pox.
Tiny inoculations.
When you rub them,
the liquid gel forms behind your eye cataracts
and above in your modula oblongata.
Get the shot.
Be the shot.
It's good for you.
Take it.
Take your best shot.
The tiny nanobots in the smallpox vaccinations
are there for your protection, your security.
Already I can feel the cinch
of a powerful missile system surrounding America.
You'll never be lost, my friend.
You may not know where you are,
but the great geosynchronous satellites always will.
And the great geodesic domes,
much like the random pillows...
The geodes in the prisoner will follow you
and take you back, number seven.
Take you back.
I am not a number.
I am a teeny tiny little tiny little man.
No, the next version of that show,
the guy will be running around going,
I am not a free man, I am a number.
I am number six.
The 2000, yeah.
You are number one.
I'm telling you, man, I'm a gas station.
We want you to get the hell out.
You are number one.
Tell them I am God number one.
Mm-hmm.
It's time to dance.
No, I'm saying, no, I'm saying.
No, you're saying, no, you're saying.
It's time to release the...
What's that aroma in the air?
Oh, I guess one of those trouser ghosts is moaning.
I think it's maybe something more bachotastylistic than that.
You know, Cleveland is a testosterone city
for those.
The wonderful inovulations our president
will be offering soon.
Oh, really?
Oh, really.
Are we one of the sample towns?
Yes, we're a sampling town.
They're taking DNA and little skull samples
from the people here and spreading them
across their sandwiches and slides
in Washington, D.C.
They're missing...
Or Dietrich, Maryland.
Yes.
Oh, yes.
I love that.
Brewing up a nice cocktail
for all the good American boys and girls.
Now, I got my flu shot.
Did you?
In...
In September or so.
And then I got the flu in January.
And I wonder what else was in the shot.
I mean, because they didn't put the...
The flu in my collection was only half good.
Well, sign away my freedom.
Why, this is ridiculous.
Don't be corny, brother.
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
Sure, our system of free enterprise isn't perfect.
But before we throw it away
for some...
Imported double talk,
let's turn the clock back a few years
to see what it's done for us.
The search for conspiracy is the search for explanation.
And in many cases, in many mysteries,
a conspiracy is a very plausible first hypothesis.
Two hijacked planes slamming into the World Trade Center.
And then shortly afterwards, we had reports from Washington
of an attack on the Pentagon.
A question I'd like to put to our listeners
on the evening show tonight.
Do you feel that the coverage of the Pentagon,
and the perspectives you're getting,
that you're receiving through the various forms of media
that you receive, that you consume,
that perhaps you pursue,
do you feel like you're getting a pluralist view?
Are you hearing different perspectives?
Do you have a prismatic view?
I guess that's another way of asking it.
Do you hear dissenting voices,
voices that are questioning orthodoxy?
Because none of these things are straightforward.
Obviously, there is no one given truth in all this.
It's a very complex and very multifaceted event originally
and what's happened since.
I'm just wondering how you judge
what you've been able to learn through the media.
We saw them in front of our eyes being pulverized,
disintegrated in just a few seconds.
Obviously, gripping television.
But did it actually happen?
Everything seems to be wrong with everything
regarding the record.
It was surreal.
As we looked at it, we thought it was something out of a movie.
Why is there a cover-up over what happened?
It's very simple, really.
There is supposed to be a cover-up.
It's official policy.
And now, of course, the towers became martyrs.
But did it actually happen?
Or is there a darker side?
It just didn't seem real.
They became the first skyscraper martyrs
that have ever been.
It is an amazing thing to walk up and down the streets
and see vendors on the sidewalks
selling pictures of the World Trade Center
in the way they might have sold pictures of Martin Luther King
or Elvis Presley or something.
They're now selling pictures of a building of the World Trade Center.
I thought, that's what I'm watching.
It must be true.
We saw them in front of our eyes.
And I thought, this is amazing.
And I thought, that's what I'm watching.
It must be true.
Disintegrated in just a few seconds.
But did it actually happen the way we've been shown?
They didn't destroy the two towers.
Or is there a darker side?
It just didn't seem real.
Now let's see what's happening to Judy and Jimmy and the Cinnamon Bear.
We left them at the bottom of the root beer ocean
where their airplane was forced down
after the Cinnamon Bear overtook the airplane.
This made them very sad.
And they were even sadder
when Cinnamon Bear told them there was no way to get out
and quench the hole in the fuel tank
and slush all the soda pop gas.
And they pulled apart first,
It took them two hours for two cars to get out at the bottom of the hole and quickly pull the truckущ
of four cars suddenly get off the ground and their back washed down into dirt.
combined with jerk forcing the three of them to turn
The whole thing in one go was just the way she would have shifted,
Great moments in oddball sports.
That's an excerpt from Saint.
Tentatively a convenience.
Convenience.
The material there from the bad doctors of genius tape.
And this music in the background, by the way, is the amino acids.
You might check out theaminoacids.com.
They're in Detroit, and we're hoping to do a revival with them soon.
All your words is on TV now.
What is this?
It's all broadcast.
You don't tell her vision.
Nobody dies.
You see what happens is you point one of them guns at the robot over there,
and you hear a loud kibble, and if you're successful, that robot's out of action.
Now, these here weapons are so smart, they actually have an IQ.
It's a bit higher than mine.
That's not the best part of it.
The best part of it is the way you can actually try it.
As a matter of fact, I was just watching a TV special that depicted bullets.
That have tiny computers in them.
Bullets with hearts and souls and minds is what America needs.
Bullets with personalities and underpants.
Bullets with hearts and minds to fight the invader.
Well, they don't have to have much of a heart.
In fact, that would probably prevent them from exploding right over the head of the guy hiding behind the wall.
Which is why they have little brains.
Oh.
No, seriously.
Bullets with microprocessor.
There's 20mm shells that are shot out of futuristic machine guns.
And the machine guns themselves are smart.
And are capable of performing anal sex.
And they've got a great video camera hooked up to them so that you can see the kill in slow motion.
And broadcast it on Japanese TV later.
It's flying everywhere.
There's mastic mess and THM fluids.
And spinal fluids.
And brain fluids everywhere.
Oh, what a mess.
What a mess.
Wow.
That was a great little rock opera.
It was.
We went from the beginning to the end of our military service in one quick little bite.
BOMB.
DEAD BOMB.
Deea.
Thanks, Ephraim.
Which I have now.
BUMP.
We'll be right back.
Yeah!
I don't get it.
They're calling us to prayer.
This magic box makes noise.
Well, it's...
What time is it?
I think it's...
It's a genius.
You have to pray for it.
It's 1.20.
Uh, Slingjob.
I don't know what happened.
Yeah.
Well, we were talking about politics.
Slingjob.
I remember a previous episode.
You pronounced American Liberty dead.
You slammed the coffin in its head.
You put it on the desk and rolled it down.
You said a few prayers.
And acted like a clown.
And then, I guess it was Major General Franks and Major Furtter came out in their suits.
Their...
Major Furtter?
Yeah.
The hairy guys in their hirsutes.
And they escorted it back up and had necrophiliacs fixed with the wounds.
And Tim Cheney came out and played Home on the Range.
On a harmonica.
Just as...
That was his way of protesting even the protest.
And Ennio Morricone came in on a pair of roller skates with one of those little tiny organs.
Cheney said, just walk away.
Because there's so much to do.
It's not relevant to what they're doing.
It's still...
If you were federal president, how could you see the next equation?
Can you just see it?
There's George Bush.
Angel eyes.
Blondie!
Blondie.
No, that was what's...
And, uh...
Osama Bin Laden.
And...
Eli Wallach, yeah, right.
But then who is Blonde?
Saddam Hussein.
Saddam Hussein is the bad guy.
Yeah, because Osama bin Laden would be the tall, skinny.
Right, he was in Lee Van Cleef.
Yeah.
And George Bush would be Eli Wallach because they both got W in their names.
They both short, feisty little guys.
Oh, no, no.
Gandhi!
And then Wolfowitz would be, you know, the hairdresser.
No, no.
That's someone else.
Well, we want to get out.
That's the Defense Department.
We're all out of here.
Let the poem roll.
How about what you see?
...mundanelessly, mindlessly contemplated
in the mainstream monopolized, politicized, money-motivated media
Media, media, monstrous mongering for the misery of munition-maiming moms
is modus operandi of a modern people, Mamma Mia Machiavellian.
Merry Christmas, you bastards.
Apocalypse Light? Is that what you're puckering your lips for this afternoon?
Knowing, feeling, being, truth, love, beauty.
Your minds have been bought.
Tell me, have they replaced your cerebral cortex with a pudenda of a monstrous woman?
I mean, is that where you got to where you're at now?
That was pretty hip stuff, though, wasn't it?
Bop, bop, bop, bop, bop, bop.
Bop, bop, bop, bop, bop.
Bop.
Bop, bop, bop, bop, bop, bop.
Of course, that was E-S-O.
And before that, that song called Dead Bob was by no means no.
You are listening to The Hour of Slack.
Number 877 from the church of the subgenius, world's first industrial church.
Check out www.subgenius.com for information on becoming a minister in that marvelous church of the subgenius.
Before signing up, you boys ought to try a little taste of Dr. Ism's formula to see what you get in exchange for your freedom.
Go ahead, try it.
You can't do this to me! I'll strike!
The state forbids strikes.
Wait till the union hears about this!
Ah, yes, the union.
Welcome to our ranks, number 1313.
I'll take this case to the Supreme Court.
The state is the Supreme Court.
Our decision is as follows.
No more private property. No more you.
Ah, the farm vote will put a stop to this.
Farmers don't vote anymore.
What will I do for seed next year?
You won't have to worry about next year. The state will do your planning from now on.
The State of the State.
We must fight!
To regain our freedom, or everything is lost. Everything!
Everything is fine. Everything is fine. Everything is fine. Everything is fine. Everything is fine.
You offer us only well-being.
Food and drink and happiness mean nothing to us. We must be about our job.
Suffering and torment and pain. Laboring without end.
Dying and crying and lamenting over our burdens.
Only this way.
Only this way can we be happy.
I heard George Bush's daughter got caught in a peep show with Pee Wee Herman.
Um, yeah.
Jerking guys off.
Well, no, no. Even guys. Gloryhole blowjobs.
No, it was a Pee Wee Herman impersonator. It was not...
That's what's really sad. It wasn't even the real Pee Wee Herman.
It was one of those guys who just walked away.
Well, the sad part was that she had one of the Gore daughters with her.
You know, corrupting those nice, prissy, polite Gores.
Well, you know the Gore girls are just potheads. They're not real cokers like the Bush girls.
Right. One of those was dating the Unabomber.
Was one of the Bush girls dating the Unabomber?
No, the Gore girls.
Oh, one of the Gore girls.
Kind of a prison romance thing or more like Montana?
No, it was the Bush girls were the ones that were flirting with that, uh, the Scorpio killer. What's his name? Ramirez.
Ramirez. Yeah.
Yeah.
So, you know, it's celebrity.
I'm jealous as hell, man. Let me put it that way.
I know. It's just an...
Easy going world for all the people on the cream that, you know, it's like poop floats. I'm telling you.
Chelsea Clinton got caught signing up for flight lessons.
I'm not kidding you.
That is one of the saddest things so far.
Next thing you know, women's gonna be wearing pants.
And the old men are gonna be wearing panties.
Oh, I wish.
They already do that.
It's happening. It's already happening.
Well, I wasn't gonna say anything.
They've been doing that for a hundred years.
That came in that Victorian age thing.
Well, they didn't come out, you know, like as common practice outside, you know, in the workplace.
Yeah, why do you think they call it Victoria's Secret?
Well, um, Reverend Holmes, you're from San Francisco.
Now, we hear tell that that's a real sinful kind of a place where it's nothing like America.
Well, especially tonight over on Polkham in the Butt Street, you know.
There's nothing like it.
I heard some...
You can't walk down a street without me.
We saw some story that on TV here in the Heartland that there were many transvestite and transsexual she-males and stuff like that parading around the streets having sex in the open, spreading their diseases.
Is this true?
Well, that's actually...
It was a...
Two road companies from New York City...
I thought you were gonna say it was a two-headed dog.
...doing cats.
They were doing a road version of cats.
And there seemed to be like many franchises of this thing.
And there were 13 of these road companies.
And they all broke down in San Francisco at the same time.
Well, they said...
You can imagine the run on makeup in San Francisco.
And it just turned into one giant cat fight, which is what started it all.
That's what they call it, Polkham in the Butt Street.
And I heard Fidel Castro is even gay out there with a green hat and everything.
It's just crazy out there.
You're so sophisticated, Dave.
You know all about that stuff.
I know.
And what's that other guy's name?
Van Ness?
The real big flamer?
Von Ness.
He's German.
He's related to peewee German.
Yeah.
Well, you live in a hell hole.
Baghdad by the Bay, as they call it.
Oh, yeah.
It's terrible.
Can't stand it.
I'm thinking of taking up a little farm here outside of Kent.
Kent State, I think.
I'm going to hang out here.
In Grove State.
Kent State?
Really?
Yeah.
We thought you'd move up to Petaluma and start a chicken.
Grove.
What?
Chickens in Petaluma.
No, no.
Oh.
Potatoes.
Gross.
Okay, so it's true.
What's true?
Drug money funds terrorism.
It is true.
Okay.
Okay?
Look, let's say I buy some dope.
Let's say.
Hypothetical.
Now, how much of my money actually makes it through the bad guy's hands?
A couple of bucks.
A few bucks.
That's it.
Peanuts.
So what you're saying is it's okay to support terrorism?
Can I say that?
Okay.
Let's see.
What do you say to that?
I don't think we have enough money to buy it.
You can't fool me.
So, you're a poor guy, eh?
Photographic records hold the clues to this conspiracy.
And here we see the footage.
If you've just joined us...
It just didn't seem real.
Within spitting distance of Wall Street and even the Statue of Liberty...
We thought it was something out of a movie.
This is the scene after the planes have slammed into the side,
and you see the back tower just crumpling like cars.
But did it actually happen, or is there a darker side?
This is the scene out of a movie filmed in a studio.
This is the scene out of a movie filmed...
in a studio.
Now, looking at this picture, the rock over to the left of the screen
has the letter C marked on it.
Why should there be a letter of the English alphabet stamped onto a rock?
Surely we're looking at the deliberate planting of props
in a pre-designated position
in the foreground of a photographic film set.
That is something that will take us a long time to wrap ourselves around.
It's hard to contemplate, isn't it?
Now, whether what we were watching...
were simulation exercises...
They didn't destroy the two towers.
...being transmitted as the real event...
...it's a possibility which needs to be examined...
They didn't destroy the two towers.
...which needs to be examined closely.
Of course they did that, and that was no secret.
It was no secret that photographs and films were taken of models.
It worked as a simulation. Nobody knew the difference.
A
That's all our listeners.
What is?
Do you think they should be chipped and stroked on the way to
Afghan, and Iran, and Iraq, and North Korea?
Or do you think they should be dropped from the grape trestles
and maybe swept up into a pile of dung?
Why not both?
Oh, well, I see it all the way.
Let's be flexible.
Don't bend over that way.
Bend over this way.
He was in the war, you know.
He was wounded in the head.
Yes.
Makes him sort of, well, rather funny at times.
Quiet.
There's nothing so ominous as quiet.
Besides, it isn't quiet.
He burst his heart.
He's dead.
Hmm.
All right.
He's dead.
So what?
Goodbye.
See, that's all you got to do.
That's all we can do.
But the thing with the paranoia, if you're getting CSB paranoia,
it's a residual kind of thing that lasts long after the listening experience, we'll say.
Because paranoia will employ you.
Dreams, odd dreams, strange discolorations of the knee.
I get off on paranoia at this point.
If you're in the military,
paranoia will deploy you.
Yeah.
That's for sure.
The W stands for war.
Saddam's got a good war bush.
Let's roll.
Let's roll a few prop sticks out of this combustible,
Let's roll the nuclear device.
That postial coconut device.
Donated by Friday Jones.
My God, he's got a coconut device.
Not ready for war.
Yeah, Friday Jones sent it.
You would ingest something that Friday sent you.
Not ready for war.
Why do you guys...
You should be going to war because you've got a lot of nerve.
I'm not ready to bore your mom.
This is a military attack.
I'm not ready to drop the bomb.
I'm not ready to chew my heart.
That's why I want to start.
I'm not ready for war.
I'm not...
Sorry, I quit.
What?
Jessica, she was supposed to take her clothes off while she's singing and she didn't...
Zeke!
ë²Œ
Nope.
She can live in the dark!
Arf!
It's painful.
It's like having the sticks in your bag of sticks all broken.
Yes, yes.
It's like trying to smoke the sticks and they become...
All your broken sticks.
...in your heart.
It's painful.
It's like being in pain and hurt.
No, I'm saying.
Yes, I...
No, you're saying.
I think I know what you're saying, but I don't know if I...
No, mine.
No, wait a minute.
You're sweating a little bit, Mr. Stang.
Your left eye is...
I told you, man.
I get off on the paranoia.
No, no, I think you're lying, Mr. Stang.
So bring it on, man.
That's what I call your reference, Stang.
Bring it on.
No, no, no.
The coyote, because he is the paranoid animal...
Oh, yes, talk about him again.
...is the most aware animal.
Yes, yes.
The coyote, because he's paranoid, is all aware.
He never sleeps.
No, no.
He's always on the prowl.
One eye.
He's always on the hunt.
The coyote...
That's coming out.
...sees, hears...
He's changing!
...and he whiffs it.
He whiffs it.
Yeah, I see.
Yeah.
Hey, hey.
Hey, man.
The change was complete.
A radical mastectomy.
An arm full of hair.
And wings the size of buzzard ears.
Even a man who is full of slack and lets his farts by night.
His feet like the feet of a dog.
His hands were like the hands of a...
Yes.
He was a coyote.
...bloom.
...and the farts are full of paint.
It was.
It was the last wind.
No!
Yes.
Last wind.
Yee-yee-yee-yee-yee-yee-yee-yee-yee-yee.
...
Well, till next week.
Keep your head undyed.
You're back to the wind.
Wait for further instructions.
And keep your babies warm.
No, the sack comes to Princess Wee.
Keep your babies warm.
The awaker shall sleep.
I'll see you down in San Antone
on a hot day.
We were eating eggs and sammies
when the black man there drew his knife.
Oh, you drowned that Jew in Rampton
as he washed his sleeveless shirt.
You know, that Spanish-speaking gentleman,
the one that we all call Kurt.
Come now, gentlemen,
I know that's some mistake.
How forgetful I'm becoming now.
You fix your...
Bill...
Business...
Shave.
I remember you
in Hamlock Road, 1956.
You're a faggin' little leather boy
with a small piece of stick.
You're a lashin', smashin' hunk of man.
Your sweatshirt's sweet and strong.
Your organs working perfectly.
But there's a part that's not screwed on,
I want you at the Coke Convention back in 1965
You're the best red gray executive I see heavily at the time
You're the gray gray man whose daughter licks policeman's buttons clean
You're the man who squats behind the man who works the soft machine
Come now, gentleman, your love is all I crave
You'll still be in the circus when I'm laughing
Laughing in my grave
And the young men all look on
And the young girls eat their mother's meat from tubes of plastic corn
Be wary, please, my gentle friends, of all the skins you breed
They have a tasty habit, they eat the hands that bleed
So remember who you say you are and keep your noses clean
Boys will be boys
And play with toys, so be strong with your bees
Oh, Rosie dear, don't you think it's queer?
So stop me if you please
The baby's dead, my lady said, you gentlemen
Why, you all work for me
Outstanden.
You think you really can get stuffed with her?
Ok.
!
Look here, it's just a coin.
You jump off after a boutin'
You jump in like aï¿½ã
!
What a jerk.
Watch the dearly little ya'll.
ì—¬
Thank you.