Look! I know who it is! I know who it is that doesn't belong among us! I swear, I know who it is!
It's... it's...
The Self-Genius Hour of Swag!
Oh, that's not true!
At last I have control of your radio tubes!
Uh, and I do too!
Good! This is Ren Hoack!
And this is Stimson J. Catt of the Ren and Stimpy Show!
And you're listening to the Hour of Swag!
Keep listening, you idiot!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Else I shall kill you!
My neighbor, welcome again to this neighborhood.
I'd like to show you something.
You know what this is?
Maybe if I press this button.
This is a cassette.
A cassette player with a little cassette in here.
And there's nothing written on it.
So we'll just have to play it to see what it is.
Do you ever imagine things?
Are they scary things?
Things you'd like to have?
Did you ever see a cat's eyes in the dark?
And wonder what they were?
Did you ever pretend about things like that before?
Did you ever throw anything
in the garden of your mind?
You can grow ideas
in the garden of your mind.
It's good to be curious
about many things.
You can think about things and make believe.
All you have to do is think
and they'll grow.
Imagine every person that you see
is somewhat different.
From every other person in the world.
Some can do some things.
Some can do others.
Did you ever think of the many things
you've learned to do?
Did you ever throw anything
in the garden of your mind?
You can grow ideas
in the garden of your mind.
It's good to be curious
about many things.
You can think about things and make believe.
All you have to do is think
and they'll grow.
Did you feel like going like that?
Let's give the fish some food.
Mr. McVeigh's late mail.
I didn't order any whistles.
That's what they call a slide whistle.
Did you feel like going like that?
There are so many things
to learn about in this world.
And so many people who can help us learn.
Did you ever throw anything
in the garden of your mind?
In the garden of your mind.
You can grow ideas
in the garden of your mind.
In the garden of your mind.
It's good to be curious
about many things.
You can think about things
and make believe.
All you have to do is think.
You can think about things
and make believe.
All you have to do is think.
And they'll grow.
Ah, yes friends.
That Mr. Rogers mashup,
Garden of Your Mind,
is from a video that my son
sent me the link to
on YouTube.
PBS Digital Studios commissioned
John Boswell of Symphony of Science
to do the video in honor of the late
Fred Rogers,
the star of the beloved children's series
Mr. Rogers' Neighborhood,
which aired from 1968 to 2001.
Good Lord.
That's 33 years.
How can anybody do a show for 33 years
without going insane?
Oh wait.
How long have I been doing subgenius shows?
Puzzling evidence started in 1982.
This is 2012.
That's 30 years.
Well, I've got three more years.
Anyway, I found that very touching.
Although I was never a big Mr. Rogers fan.
I'm more from the Captain Kangaroo generation.
But my kids liked him.
And he apparently liked everybody.
And certainly he had a calmer approach
than Sesame Street.
If there's anything like that around today,
I sure don't know about it.
This particular hour of Slack,
number 1,366,
is once again composed of other subgenius shows,
from Puzzling Evidence to Ask Dr. Howe
to Radio Synesthesia to Ministry of Slack.
And Phineas Narco of National Cynical
joins Puzzling's show by phone
and Lonesome Cowboy Dave
joins Synesthesia by phone.
And I was there for all of them.
With Dr. Philo Drummond.
X days are coming.
And although we'll record hours
of future shows then,
until those get edited,
my time as show assembler is very limited.
In fact, to tell the truth,
I'm doing these credits
over the swinging love corpses, by the way,
before hearing a lot of this show.
So it may be kind of rough.
It might not go down well
on the polished ears of the liberal
and the modernist,
as old Pastor George said.
Or as Pastor David Epley used to say.
But it's real radio.
Some of it is not new.
In fact, the next thing I'm playing
and what comes at the end
are from the very earliest days
of Puzzling Evidence,
back when it was still technically
Bob Nelson's show
and Dr. Gary Gubrogfran used to phone in regularly
before he moved to Santa Cruz.
But you'll also hear him phone in to recent shows
now 30 years later.
Jesus, 30 years.
So from the year of 1982,
or maybe 1983,
here's Gary.
We're waiting for someone to call
and ask us about the subgenius religion
where the prophet J.R. Bob Dobbs
is the venerated personality.
This religion is gone.
It's completely undetected
simply through a lack of communication.
But it was a hard thing to get the message out.
The doctors and the doctors in the noise surgery,
the doctors who take apart the instruments
and reassemble the instruments at each one of the sessions
are funny in different order.
Why they put drum sets back inside guitars
when they go home is throw them in the back of the van
and drive across the bridge as if it didn't matter
how much they cost.
And you'll be hearing some of that doctor music
in just a little while.
Yes, but first we'd like to,
we'd like to rant just for a moment, if we might.
If we might just take a tiny bit of your time
and try to explain to you how this is important
and critical, this radio show can be in your mind.
All of the doctors talk at once.
And if the doctors of the Bob were here,
they would be able to tell you.
If Sterno or Jane or was here,
And even if Sterno or J.R. Bob Dobbs
and we were all running in the evening,
and there was a sound,
and the doctors were totally afraid
and great artists,
well, you can ask us about that.
I mean, we can't tell you, because, dear,
Bob Dobbs has not come on this show to tell you,
because he sends us and gives us the checks
so that we can tell you about it.
Yeah, I noticed that, too.
He will not be on this show.
Oh, hello.
Hello.
Why Bob Dobbs and not Bob Nelson?
They're two different people.
No, Bob Nelson is the DJ,
and yeah, that's him right there, remember?
Bob Dobbs is a salesman,
and he's over there, remember?
What's a Doug to do?
He's just, well, Doug,
Doug's got to do what he's got to do.
Yes, Dr. Doole.
Just hope, pray, that he's Doug enough.
Yes, I'm Doug enough,
but it took me years to get here.
Dr. Doole, that's the doctor from Bolivia
that just left.
He's in Miami right now, stuck.
Oh, Dr. Doole.
Oh, Doole, yes, he called several gentlemen
from Bolivia,
and he's stuck in Miami for about five days,
so if you'd like to call Miami right now,
I'm going to hang up, call Miami.
He probably has a lot of things
you really like,
and you could run into him.
You'd probably have a good time.
You know what I mean.
Dr. Doole?
Yeah, Dr. Doole.
I know he's just a genius chick.
Dr. Doole.
He's a genius.
He's a church.
He's a foundation.
Oh, do you want to talk to Doug Smith?
Okay, here he goes.
Yeah, this is Doug here.
Hi, Doug.
Yeah, he'll be here in a minute.
Don't worry.
Well, anyway, what was it that you wanted
to ask us about the church?
Or is this just some kind of display of airtime?
Well, it could be a little bit of both, could it not?
Yeah, well, it could be,
but it's probably a lot more fun for the listeners
if we all start talking real funny.
Talk funny about the church.
Okay.
The church of the sub-genius will take totally normal paints and destroy their lives and
totally alienate them from their parents, but it'll give them like three or four dozen
intimate friends that will send the paints over to them in the mail.
Any good branded narcotics would do the same.
Any good branded narcotics would be the same.
Yeah, but it won't last as long.
That's right.
You can't get a book either.
We've got a book.
It's not that expensive.
You've got an expensive book.
And narcotics can't break your tape recorder.
Well, that depends on the gene splice.
It doesn't sound like a gene splice.
No, we just use cassettes.
We don't have to mess with the splicing any longer.
Oh, that's interesting.
That's interesting.
Yeah.
Well, I happen to have been called three times in the past lifetime.
You've called this show two or three times in the past lifetime.
Yeah, well, I recognize your voice.
You know, I think you're calling from your car.
Right.
Oh, okay.
Well, you're that guy.
Well, how come you don't know about the Jungle Gentleman from Green Hill?
The Jungle Gentleman from Green Hill is the guy who's been in the show for a long time.
I think I've been calling him before my time and another time.
Well, do you think you could launch the head?
Launch the head?
Give me about three micros to plow back to 2280.
2280.
Oh, well, as the Reverend J.R.
Hyperfleet said, he has the pills and the food-like product available from the Bloody
That's it?
The pills or kill me.
I think you should write the piece and write the Bloody Head.
Yeah, hang up.
Or it can be more killed than.
You're hung up, all right, or you wouldn't be calling.
You're hung up.
You didn't know your cover when you dialed 8484425.
The rest of this message can be received on Magnuson.
Adapter number one.
Pick up the sign wave by tuning in to your local SubDF.
Bye.
SubDF.
Yeah, good night.
See you later.
Well, I would like to answer the most intimate questions of this guy's life.
If he could have called up and said, look, my question is, what do you think of the Jungle
Shack?
I mean, I have a girlfriend who doesn't love me.
What should the church tell me to do?
We could call him.
Trying desperately to call.
Well, that's all right.
We can't.
Yeah, we can't let that.
Yeah, it'll be mysterious.
Anyway, you know, if you want to know what to do with your money or buy or sell stocks
or any kind of important advice, the church has answers for almost all your problems or
problems for any of your life situations.
Yeah, so I can see the Uberbrown.
That's it.
Now hovering above.
Well, there he goes.
We thought we had the brow here, but I guess he just kind of flowed away.
Well, I have to go get the magic secret music.
Oh, I didn't know this.
For Doctor's Mansion.
And you, the listener, will be invited to sing along, even though you don't know the words and you never have to.
Well, actually, it's real easy to sing the song, though.
That's right.
And you probably could really benefit from singing this song.
I think a lot of you that listen to the show on a regular basis know about Gary Cabrera's foundation.
I think you should buy the Honk If You Love Cabrera sticker that comes from the Little Rock Garden song.
And through the censor, by the manager, they will say that this is Little Rock Garden's song.
From previous to the new, we'll do it again before the show is over.
Yes, it's true.
The launch of society produces Honk If You Love Cabrera.
That's right.
Sanctified, justified, and glorious.
Right to send you the light speed.
And you know, I say it in a kind of a symphonic truth.
This is him laying.
I put it on the back of my truck in the window, brother.
Well, back to the head.
This is what R&D is planned for the future.
Where does it coincide with Dobbs' prophecy?
What relation between it and the Doctors for Dobbs exists?
We have our protection on the head now.
Well, let's bring him in here to the studio.
Well, and how will the head figure in your chemical life?
Oh, I don't know.
It should have.
It should have something to do with the dense pack application of some genius music.
Soliciting the, say, three or four different doctor bands at the same time.
That kind of thing.
It would keep me away from my video dental temperament.
I agree.
Well, I don't know.
What about these enlightened subgenius who expect or anticipate expiation on the part of the Doctors for Dobbs
in their supposed real slack rantings against proportionate Dobbs rigid textuality?
Well, I think if it ever comes down to it, the difference between Doctors for Bob and the Doctors who dare not speak about it,
is that the Doctors who dare not speak their name is Doctors for Bob have the head,
whereas the Doctors who dare not speak their name don't even have a studio to work in.
They don't have anything.
Oh, yeah?
No, they make those tapes on the bus.
Wow, I see.
They just kind of travel around.
What city are they in?
They're in Oakland.
They're from Oakland.
They're in Oakland, but they're down from West Oakland, down by the post office.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
What kind of songs do they play?
What's in them?
Well, they do a lot of Doctor music, but they mostly mix dub songs.
Yeah, sort of like that.
We're going to revoke about this cult and make a result in our insult because we're a cult,
and that's the result of our tumult, though it is difficult.
Yes.
Let's go with that cult.
Maybe we could play a Doctor song.
Yeah, maybe.
This is going to be arranged.
You got payola?
Hey?
What do you think this is, eh?
You just walk in here and command the station or something.
I know.
Why don't we turn all the sound effects off and shut all the DJs up and then...
Well, anyway, let's turn the whole radio station off except for this one little Doctor tape.
Okay.
We're all worried.
Pull this lever.
It's, uh...
It's queued up in tape machine number 5,622.
There's so much, but, uh...
It's so much fun here in the morning.
Okay.
And listen to me, not the other guy.
Not that guy.
All these rec shows from Pacifica is going out all across.
I know.
There are loads of people who live on little boats in the Berkeley Marina who are listening right now.
Yeah.
Let's go.
Exploring the body, we're going to look at the colon.
What exactly does it do?
And how does excremeditation help you get right with Bob?
Surgery and all the green blood had been washed from the floors.
Surgery's done, he said.
Where's my drink?
I need a smoke.
Tape runs out.
Mm-hmm.
In his hopelessness rage, he declared...
Damn you, Chitwood!
The sacred skin mark of Chitwood wears its head again.
It's possible.
I learned how to make a bike out of Passade.
It's passable.
I mean, if this was something you were making a bike out of, it'd be passable.
You'd still get pulled over.
You'd get a ticket.
No.
But it'd be passable.
You could still say,
No, it's okay.
I made this show.
It's an art project.
It still runs.
As you can see, there's pieces and parts falling off.
That's all part of it.
It's a converted unicycle.
You know, that's what they say about the girls down in San Francisco.
What?
They're passable.
Speaking of passable, let's talk about my colonoscopy again.
Keep going.
And my unborn child.
That's right.
She did knock me up.
I got knocked up by Larry Lasker giving me a colonoscopy.
So that film, Juthair, was actually about to do it.
That is some reverse end.
engineering right there.
Sitting there, you go in,
get your bottle of J&B,
and...
Go fuck yourself.
Turkenduff and Vika Dickin.
Go round and round, round and round.
How dare you invade my reality tunnel?
How dare you?
They're COINTELPRO, and they're trying to use
their MKUltras against us.
I believe we have a newly ordained
minister in our midst now.
Caller, go ahead.
Hey, is it...
Can you hear me?
Yes, we can.
You're on the air, caller.
Is it true that you are a
newly ordained minister, sir?
Yes, I just
signed on today.
Well, praise God.
Did you get your package back?
Did you pay your $30?
Sucker!
You have been
duped, my friend.
I just received a message that said
you could fry an egg on your face right now.
Or you could put a sausage on your residual taint.
I'm gonna put it inside of my colon.
There you go.
Oh yeah.
That's hot.
That's a blast for me.
I'm blushing now.
Right?
I'm like, wow, what do you call that?
Oh, so it was just people talking about...
Colon?
Dicks and colons and vaginas and...
Shit dick, McGee.
Excuse me?
It just came from nowhere.
I don't know why I said that.
He's got a little Tourette's.
Shit, son of a bitch!
But those words sound funny together.
That's what I'm trying to say.
Shit dick, McGee.
Now I'm gonna get punched in the face through the internet.
Here it comes.
So that means on the way to the doctors tomorrow,
in the third time, colon goes down.
He's gonna die.
Because he's Canadian.
It makes him think he's not left.
Hey, that's right, man.
See, Canadians are weak.
Is this a radio show or a flea circus?
What's going on here?
It's a radio circus.
Come one, come all.
Yelta, yelta, yelta.
It's the circus, Cooper.
It's the three ring circus.
Well, that was a nice little sober lecture on health
from the Ministry of Slack podcast.
Some of those damn kids weren't even around
when the first Puzzling Evidence show went out on KPFA.
My, how the years do fly by.
In fact, in the following cut,
you'll hear me sounding about 10 years older than I even am
due to a cold,
talking about health-related issues with Princess Wee.
And it's a good thing I'm not running for president,
because I give away a couple of things
that I'm not proud of from my college days
in the 1970s as a young filmmaker.
So, lights, roll camera, speed, slate, action.
I'm enjoying sipping my new medicinal healing drink
for the car.
It is hot water, real lemon juice,
and I'm going to drink it.
And I'm going to drink it with a few drops of lemon juice
and cherry Luden's cough drops.
What?
Do you dissolve the cough drop in the drink?
Yes.
And it's very good on my throat.
Well, I'll be dang.
So, that's my new miracle cure for the cold
that I'm not allowing into me.
It's not allowed in.
When I was much younger,
I had a miracle cure for health.
I discovered that the prescription amphetamines
that this croaker near SMU College in Dallas
would prescribe to students
would dissolve completely in a bottle of Thunderbird wine.
Ah.
And you could throw two of those speed pills,
they were diet pills, Benzedrine,
into a bottle of Thunderbird wine.
It was 20% alcohol.
So, you'd drink a quarter of the bottle of wine,
you'd be instantly drunk.
And then about 20 minutes later,
you'd feel like Spider-Man.
Then, you know, you'd proceed to work.
In my case, I was editing World of the Future.
You'd proceed to work for, you know, two or three hours,
and then you'd start to feel kind of, you know,
your head would hurt from gritting your teeth
and licking your lips repeatedly
and scratching holes in your skin.
And then you'd look down, and by God,
there's another three-quarters of a bottle of Thunderbird there.
With another hit and a half of that damn speed.
I put that down and never did it again
when I reached up to grab the little gray film reels
and they all looked like giant gray blood-filled ticks.
Good idea. Good idea.
So, kids, the stories they tell you about speed,
it's true.
Speed kills not immediately,
but slowly and in a really unpleasant way.
So stick with your coffee and I suppose your energy drinks or whatnot.
Kids.
For people my age, I'm not even, I'm not trying to preach to.
Um.
The Alan Arkin character in Little Miss Sunshine covered that pretty well.
Absolutely.
When you're a kid, doing this drugs would be crazy.
If you're my age, you'd be crazy not to.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
But he ODs before the end of the movie
after teaching the nine-year-old girl to dance like a pole bar stripper.
What a way to go, ODing on heroin.
Just like go to big sleep.
. . .
I wouldn't know.
I've never actually touched that stuff because I,
I always read up on things first,
including the stuff the doctor gives me.
And, um, education can go a long way.
I've never sampled any Harry Owen myself.
I've never sampled anything that, uh,
well, actually I read up on speed before I ever tried it.
But I knew that, that it was going,
by definition, it was going to have to be for a limited time.
And I stuck to my guns.
Also, they made it really hard to find.
That was a long time ago.
It's probably real easy.
I've had two, two of my friends who I've watched slowly grind their teeth until they died.
It's sad.
It is sad.
It's a tragedy.
Well, they turned into assholes first.
So in that respect, it wasn't sad.
It was justice.
But it's, it's bad to die before death.
It's bad to be turned into an asshole by drugs.
Um, and, and most stimulants will, well, most of them will do that.
Marijuana won't turn you into an asshole.
It will turn you into a lazy, slacker, rewardian, piss-a-bed.
. . .
If, if you're, you know,
some people I might mention.
It's a bit.
Ahem.
I, that never had that effect on me because I'm sort of a, I'm an emergent tile.
This show seems to be responding.
This is one I didn't get.
What the hell was that thing about?
But it's just, I've been handed a soundtrack of a. . .
What the hell was that movie about?
The movie Constantine.
With, uh. . .
Yeah, I saw that.
With Johnny. . .
Keanu Reeves.
Yeah, with Keanu Reeves.
Yeah.
Didn't our friend, Piss Baptist John Shirley write, uh, like a sequel or some of the. . .
He wrote the second Constantine novel.
I don't, I don't actually read his novel.
Or did he re, write the novel of that?
He just wrote a. . .
A movie.
It was a comic book, then a movie.
And then he wrote like an imagining of other events and things that happened.
First it was a subgenius gag on the, on the show.
Then it was a novel, or comic book.
Then a novel, then a movie, then a novel of the movie.
And then a trailer.
Then a comic book of the novel.
And then a poster, a theater poster.
No, actually the poster and the trailer came first.
Yeah, that's right.
Before the sub, the show. . .
It's supposed to.
. .
Joke, actually.
We're not giving credit where credit's. . .
It's kind of like Machete.
Yeah.
They made a musical out of it.
And it was a pinball machine and. . .
And then your Mattel toy set at McDonald's.
Yeah.
Man, I missed all that.
Little tiny machine.
The little baby Machete and his baby.
The little baby Machete.
Yeah.
And then the villains and baby hookers.
They were able to buy the Queen of UFOs special seat on the sex goddess thing with those little,
with 103 little baby Machete things from McDonald's.
You never know what's going to be valuable later.
Exactly.
Think if you still had that Pee Wee Herman talking doll.
The wind up, the pull the string and he talks Pee Wee doll.
Like the one Paul has in handcuffed facing the corner.
That's funny.
Potter Nostril has one that's. . .
That's being serviced by the Little Mermaid.
A marionette Pee Wee Herman is being taken care of by the Little Mermaid.
I think we should redo Men in Black with Pee Wee Herman as the young guy.
But Machete is now Mad Ass.
Now Machete played by Paul Rubens.
That would be. . .
Interesting.
That would be different.
I mean the guy's done 30 Rock.
He should be able to do Machete.
Yeah.
He's got a lot of experience.
I'll tell you I saw that in a theater.
I went to see the I think the devilette dance.
Young ladies.
Very funny.
A little dance.
And then. . .
It was that those two movies played on a big old screen.
So when I saw Planet of Terror or whatever it was.
The first movie was.
It has Machete afterwards as a commercial.
It was a quite an experience because it was like sitting in the theater in 1970s again.
With big splices and cigarette burns and the whole.
And all that stuff that movies had the soundtrack that was off.
And. . .
They. . .
Weep.
With the wrong Mexican.
Yeah.
Machete.
And things missing.
Coming to theaters near you.
They should have had like the smell of old cigarettes and cheap wine.
Well yeah.
Yeah.
True.
That comes with the $150 DVD set.
That's funny.
There was one thing he had to shorten in real life.
It took a lot longer.
It's when the film would get caught up and the bulb would burn through the. . .
The frame.
And in the film. . .
In the movie. . .
In the fake version. . .
It's all fixed in a second or two.
And in real life folks. . .
You used to have to sit there in the theater and yell at the poor people.
Right.
Throw popcorn at people.
They hardly was. . .
And in fact there's a movie called The Projectionist where it's a. . .
Oh. . .
A little. . .
Oh that guy.
A little cartoon.
I can just see the. . .
The little. . .
Gerald McBoing Boing cartoon.
And it's running along.
And I'm sitting there in a Navy theater.
When I'm in the Navy.
And thinking. . .
Not another cartoon.
God damn it.
And. . .
And then the film goes. . .
Goes off a big white screen. . .
And it's there. . .
You know. . .
White screen. . .
Fifteen seconds. . .
Thirty seconds. . .
All the guys around me like. . .
And they're throwing stuff at the window. . .
And then slowly the frame gets smaller. . .
And you realize it's on the movie. . .
And you're in a theater where the frame is broken. . .
And all the audiences. . .
You saw The Projectionist in the Navy?
Yeah.
It's an old film.
I saw it in. . .
I was in film school because I. . .
I had flat feet. . .
Yeah. . .
That was it. . .
I was four. . .
That's all. . .
I had flat feet. . .
The Projectionist had such an influence on me. . .
That I made a Projectionist uniform like that. . .
And wore it into combat. . .
And made media barrage cut-ups for the rest of my life. . .
Because I just thought the Projectionist guy was amazing. . .
Actually, Gail. . .
I think. . .
Chuck McGann produced and directed that. . .
Yeah. . .
But the woman who did the editing on the black and white horse. . .
Or, you know, the wonderful older man. . .
The awful world of men. . .
The media barrage. . .
Yeah. . .
World of Tomorrow. . .
Also did J-Men. . .
So now. . .
Really? . .
Yeah. . .
Okay. . .
I was watching that. . .
She. . .
Her name. . .
Gail. . .
Yeah. . .
Gail something. . .
Gail . . .
And you see it. . .
It's like, of course. . .
I saw J-Men Forever at Philo's house. . .
He put on an ancient. . .
Yeah. . .
It was like every night flight. . .
That ancient. . .
Yeah. . .
Ancient show that. . .
How many are there? . .
There were like. . .
It was on for six years or something. . .
I remember getting to the. . .
To the Evil Gary. . .
Weep. . .
Non. . .
Non show. . .
And Gary took off. . .
And left us in the lurch there. . .
At Philo's house. . .
So we were forced to watch J-Men over and over. . .
On a rainy weekend. . .
That was right after the Doc's Doc number two. . .
Oh, brothers. . .
You know. . .
You know what the show doesn't remind me of? . .
The show. . .
Any Disney movie I've ever seen. . .
Has they dangled in the wind. . .
But I. . .
But it's. . .
The show doesn't remind me of any Disney movie I've ever seen. . .
Well, we. . .
We are kind of missing a princess. . .
We are definitely missing a princess. . .
Yeah, she's taking care of her mom right now. . .
On the other side of town. . .
Actually, I think she's in another show. . .
She's having to do another show in another city. . .
Right this minute. . .
How about that? . .
Yeah, I'm missing her. . .
It's not one of those, like, podcasts for geriatric people. . .
Where, like, they, you know, go in and sing Sinatra songs right in the middle of the. . .
The staying clan is. . .
All over your video. . .
It's some rival anti-religion like the Unitarians. . .
Oh. . .
Like, the. . .
The Connyites have started their own shows and stuff? . .
Yeah, the Connyitarians. . .
No, I really. . .
I have a real serious. . .
I have a real serious criticism of the Unitarians. . .
You know, they're these people who just have a desperate need for churchiness. . .
Right. . .
But they don't have being brainwashed as an excuse. . .
Didn't the Unitarians start as the Puritans? . .
And after a really bizarre episode living in America and creating a lot of damage and then being damaged. . .
Well, they're also good-hearted. They make me ashamed of myself, and that's why I don't go with my. . .
The Unitarian missionaries will knock on your door and just say hi. . .
Yeah. They're so polite. They're so nice. I just feel out of place. I feel like a vampire in church. . .
Actually, the term Unitarian itself is a term that is in opposition to Trinitarian. . .
They started off as a heretical. . .
. . .
You know, like, the Trinitarian movement in Europe during the Enlightenment who said,
no, the Trinity can't be true. . .
. . .
God has to be one.
You know how many Trinitarians it takes to change a light bulb? . .
. . .
Three, but they're really one.
. .
Okay. . .
And they eventually, there was also another movement called the Universalist Movement,
which believed that everyone goes to heaven.
God saves everybody.
It doesn't matter who you are, what you did, what you believe.
God couldn't possibly condemn anyone to hell because he's just too loving.
And eventually the Unitarians and the Universalists...
Really? I'm out of here, man. I've got things to do.
And eventually the Unitarians and the Universalists got together,
and they are now a quasi-religious organization.
Anyway, that's the cult my wife is helping out right now.
What's that?
My wife is involved with the Unitarian cult right now.
That's why she's not here doing some genius work.
I was exposed to that myself as a youngster.
In fact, what was really awesome about being exposed to the Unitarian cult as a teenager
is they have Sunday school for everyone K-12.
And what they give the 7th graders is sex ed.
And, like, they showed us images that I cannot describe over the air.
I'm not kidding.
They taught us all about different things that people do.
Yippee!
Nothing to do with sex, I'm sure.
Just things people do.
At the school I went to, it was explained to me that female breasts were nothing but modified sweat glands.
So what are you boys so excited about?
Well, those sweat glands taste pretty good on a salty Friday morning.
Provided, you know, you grease the right palms.
I think I found out about some genius through the back of a Fangoria magazine.
Really? Of a what magazine?
Fangoria.
What? Huh.
Yeah.
I think that's...
If memory serves, I might have met Dr. Onan Canabal.
He's a great guy.
I was just thinking I need to put on YouTube at some point pretty soon here.
The subgenius gathering in Tucson, Arizona, whatever year that was where Jeff Robbins is wheeled up to the amplifier...
Right in front of an amplifier and left there for the entire show.
And the power went out.
And out front, I almost got in fight with Hal and locals because they couldn't figure out what BlackRock...
BlackRock was in Nevada.
They knew that.
And my plates were from California.
And so I was trying to explain that I was a ranger, but only for one moment in the BlackRock.
And they didn't know that.
And they were so upset that they thought, you know, the tattoos and the tats and everything got to fight now.
And so I had to move my car because I was worried they would beat up my poor little car.
And then we go to show and all the power goes out.
Probably because of something Chicken John did when he arrived with the bus full of folks.
All I remember is Nikki and her special S&M.
And I remember that.
Yeah, I should remember that.
Maybe I was too overwhelming to look.
That's all I can remember.
And the giant talking flaming mouth Dobbs head.
I am the great and powerful Bob Dobbs.
Hal was doing the voice.
And Moguloid had made a giant Dobbs head out of paper mache that actually belched flame and had flame coming from its pipe.
And when it...
And it's voice...
You could...
With a really hard tug of a rope, you could pull the thing's jaws up and down and make it speak in Hal's voice.
So I could ask him questions.
I am the great and powerful Dobbs.
Yeah.
Yeah, I like that.
Hal later did that with a giant buttock at Burning Man, I think.
Or maybe it was before.
That was very funny.
Yeah, I'm not sure where it fits in the timeline.
I think it's later.
But Chicken John made a giant really...
You couldn't even tell it was a butt.
It was just a giant thing of polyester, of the trash bag polyester.
And then the people of the fire department came by and said, you can't do this.
And so Chicken John said, you're right, and burned it down.
So the flecks of little plastic flying across the playa, like a million trash cans on fire.
Now, I heard that Moguloid's talking Dobbs head that was like six, seven feet tall at least.
Yeah, it is.
Yeah.
Was...
It ended up being left in Tucson and somebody said, I'll take it and put it on my front lawn.
And they live next to the main freeway through town.
So everybody driving to work has to look at that horrible face down there on somebody's lawn.
Nice.
That's the way to do it.
See, this guy knows.
Yeah.
I just remember wandering around naked in Burning Man.
What?
Somebody said naked?
Oh, was that you that I saw wandering around naked at Burning Man?
Well, that must have been me.
Yeah.
You're right.
Are you like 80 years old?
Because that's how you looked at the time.
Did you ever see Trash Humpers?
Which?
Trash Humpers.
No.
Oh, you must see Trash Humpers.
I just saw a movie called Pig that Lagim gave me a link to.
You could only download it.
It's so violent.
Trash Humpers.
And horrible.
It makes everything look clean and nice.
It's a battlefield of a great war on air.
Trash Humpers is very so genius.
But it's shot on videotape.
Like, like old VHS videotape.
Huh.
But it was made a couple years ago.
I beat the, I beat the socks off of that.
Trash Humpers.
Yes, you must see that.
Another must see on the endless list.
Endless must sees.
Keeps growing.
The sea of must sees.
Growing for a veritable ocean.
Longer than our lives.
More must sees.
Must see.
The socks.
Typing them in now.
We must see.
The must see sea of must see movies.
Um, who else?
Oh, Stang?
I know someone who will remind you of you 30 years ago.
And I'm going to introduce you to him hopefully this coming X day.
I hate it when that happens.
I know.
Well, um, he's not one of your clones.
But, you know, he's probably someone who, if he fell through a crack in the space time
detail.
He's not a true clone.
Oh, Johnny, I'm sorry.
I know who you're talking about.
Johnny Depp.
You're going to bring Johnny Depp.
He's not a true clone.
Yeah, I know.
Sure.
He's not a true clone.
But he's close enough.
He looks just like me.
He's not a true clone.
But he's close enough that he, uh, that his organs can be used.
Johnny Depp is playing me in the movie.
I think he's going for your look.
Yeah.
Well, um.
Osama bin Laden was going for my look.
It turned out that.
He runs a website that gets like 3 million hits a month.
So, uh.
Cinema snob.
Brad Jones.
Burt Reynolds is coming out of retirement.
Oh, yeah.
I mean, he's going to animate Burt Reynolds' corpse.
No, Harry House is still alive.
But when he does die, somebody's going to animate him.
I guarantee it.
Uh, we're not taking, uh, calls, ladies and gentlemen.
Uh, so please stop trying to call.
Please don't call.
I can tell you.
I can visualize myself editing that Pete Goldie call volume.
Uh.
It could be done.
That's going to be quite a challenge.
And he had much to tell us about this man, Newt Gingrich.
Well, you, I'm sure that there would have been a better way to, to deal with it.
But I was speaking to him and, uh, no one could hear his voice.
I could hear him.
Oh, you could?
When you held it up to the.
Oh, well, yes.
After I held it up.
That's why I held it up.
You see.
That's the old school way of radio.
Old school, eh?
It's pure.
It's pure radio.
It's not your mix of.
Remember George Novo?
Yeah.
George Nolan.
Clear ch-channel.
The executive.
The mother of invention.
The silly suit man.
You remember George Nolan?
This is really hippies.
Remember George Nolan, Reverend Stang?
George.
I can barely hear you.
Remember George Nolan, Reverend Stang?
Yeah.
Yeah, George Nolan.
He was the first.
The first.
Well, second guy to interview us on the radio.
Yeah.
George Nolan.
After he.
Mr. Opinion.
Was filling in for George Nolan and had us on twice.
Right.
Because he could get away with it.
And George Nolan liked us.
He liked us.
And had us.
Yeah.
Had us come back.
He had a really good radio voice.
He was a nice guy.
He was real funny.
He didn't.
He didn't mock us for being cultists.
He was really interested in Bob.
But then the rock and roll.
John Rhody came after that.
The rock and roll DJs and the drive time shows where they.
This guy actually believes in this Bob guy.
Yeah.
He started to make fun of us and we didn't respond like.
Gentlemen.
Is that a caller?
Asking a question?
That's a robo caller.
Yeah.
Went back to the Custer battleground.
I thought I heard a faint Phineas.
Far.
Away.
Phineas has been producing special songs.
The archaeological discoveries there found a Stuart tank on the Custer battlefield.
A rib stang.
Rib stang.
With three rubber stangs.
There's Michael Pepe.
Yeah.
Michael Pepe is talking about rib stang.
Is that Pope.
Imho Pep III.
Are you saying that Lee Harvey Oswald is Frank Pobucker?
No.
No, no, no.
Crank Pobucker.
Who, Frank?
Lived across the street from the subgenius headquarters.
He was so named because he was an early methamphetamine experimenter.
Really?
Yeah.
And he was a Pobucker.
And the saying would take his children to school.
And they grew up and they didn't have birth defects?
No, they're really nice.
Well, he didn't start the crank until after the kids were born.
Oh, I see.
Okay.
But he evidently is Lee Harvey Roswell.
Roswell.
Lee Harvey Roswell.
That's from the movie.
You know, there's so many subgeniuses with the name Lee Harvey Roswell.
It's gotten out of hand.
It's like you can't swing a dead cat without hitting a Lee Harvey Roswell.
Do me a favor.
Swing it hard.
All right.
But, I mean, that must be exciting to a movie.
What movie?
Swing it hard.
All right.
Let's try to keep some civility here.
Now, Michael Pepe is coming and going.
Yeah.
Well, he ain't the only one.
Well, that's true.
I've come, but I'm going to go soon.
Are you talking about that prostitute with diarrhea?
The headphones that are blasting my ears and then withdrawing.
The prostitute with diarrhea that was coming and going at the same time?
The very one.
One of the rules was no vulgarity.
Oh, my God.
Obscenity is all right, but not vulgarity.
It's the opposite of normal.
It's a show of rules now.
But I want to do...
We have a lot of new...
Philo and I came up with these rules.
Each and every one of you.
The other committee.
Because, yeah, they are...
It's a coup.
How worried should we be about carpenter ants?
Now, Dad, remember...
No, we covered that pre-show.
Carpenter ants are big, fat red ants.
Yeah, the whole area.
Carpenter ants are large and polymorphic.
John Carpenter ants.
They're talking about...
Workers are several sizes.
They're black, reddish brown, red and black.
That's why the colonies fall apart, because they're all directors.
Yes.
They all got rules.
More rules.
Note the thorax.
That's my rules now.
Evenly confess when viewed from the side.
Yes.
Hope him, hope him.
Can we say B part sucks?
Which also belongs...
But here you see...
The what?
Indentation.
Can we say B part sucks?
Yes.
Indented thorax.
We can't.
Okay.
You can't.
On this show, you can't.
And what about the beetles?
Can we say the beetles suck?
Oh, you have to.
Oh, okay.
And you have to say Bob sucks first.
Even though you don't believe it.
Oh, I...
First you have to say Bob sucks three times.
Then you can say anything sucks.
And then you say yog sa sa sa fa.
Oh, three times while you're looking in the basement trap door.
Because that's the ultimate.
It doesn't say Bob sucks.
And that has a kind of magical effect.
It must drive away the evil spirit.
It wasn't boxers when we have to...
Right.
I threw it away.
Because you have blasphemed the ultimate blasphemy.
Right.
That kind of...
It ironically enough protects you.
Yeah.
Using the power of irony.
Exactly.
Corny irony in this case.
Corn bomb.
So, wow.
Bob sucks, Bob sucks, Bob sucks.
Corniest...
Okay, you're accepted.
Next.
And now don't forget to fork over $35.
How much is it?
That's right.
We can't say that on the air.
It has nothing to do with this show.
No, no, no, no.
You misunderstand.
Yes.
I'm talking about the doldrums.
Yeah.
The slow part.
You will be free, Michael.
And the whole show comes to a halt in a Sargasso sea of...
Yes.
It stops.
Like a painted ship upon a painted ocean.
A little paint chip.
35 years in the doldrums.
Floating along in the air.
The crabs crawling along the stinking algal mat of floating sea.
Straight out Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
Oh, yeah?
Oh, yeah.
I see.
But that's the only way you can...
You can't...
You can't stop it.
Can you be inducted into the church of the 17th?
No, the show is like that.
Once you start that first hit of the show, you can't stop.
35 years in the doldrums.
Forever.
From PR News in Washington.
Unmarked by scandals and economic decline.
President Obama has formally resigned.
Hallelujah!
An unprecedented power concentrated in one individual.
Tainted by corruption.
Plagued by sex scandals.
Frequenting minors.
Paying for sex with an underage prostitute.
His wife left him.
He also controlled all of broadcasting.
But his close friend, Russian Prime Minister Vladimir Putin,
had words of praise for PR News.
PR's punished.
Punished longtime coach Joe Paterno.
Well, that was a nice long stretch of uncut cuts from PR News by Cosmic Cabri.
A puzzling evidence show with Michael Pepe calling in and Phineas Narco.
Ask Dr. Howell's podcast on Radio Valencia.
WCSB Cleveland's Radio Synesthesia.
In fact, the only thing missing is Reverend Susie the Flusie's show from WREK Atlanta.
But that'll be on next in Major Markets.
The next thing I'm going to play, all the way to the end,
is both old...
and new.
It's how Puzzling Evidence starts his two-hour shows
with a half hour of rather loose collage mixing old Puzzling Evidence shows
with new collages he makes for movie soundtracks and stuff.
And in this case, poor little Princess Wee,
who called in only to be left alone with the tapes.
So you can hear her trying to make the best of it
and pretend to join the conversation of recorded conversations.
I guess the rest of us were still on the way to the station
and Puzzling had rocketed away somewhere.
I have it edited down because some of it hurts your ears and brain
even more than most such 4 a.m. recordings.
Yeah, it's 4 a.m. in Berkeley and poor Wee is sitting inside a parked car
in the cold in Fremont because she didn't want to wake up her family
as they slept all warm inside.
And trying so hard to join the show that isn't even really there.
However, it starts with an idea.
It's an oldie by some band.
I forget their name.
I don't know if I should be English.
Help
Tell you what you want me to make you
I'm coming down fast, but don't let me break you
Tell me, tell me, tell me the answer
You may be a lover, but you ain't no dancer
Look out!
Help the skeleton
This is how
When I get to the bottom, I go back to the top of the slide
When I stop and I turn and I don't move right
Then I get to the bottom and I see you again
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Yes, yes, of course, at once
Oh, no
I want to take the phone off the hook and not answer the door
We'll have to do better than that
You don't know this thing
Patrick, what can I do for you?
You left your case behind when you came to see me
Nothing at all
Hold on, Patrick
For heaven's sake, don't nag me
You are a madman
Hello Peter
Oh, hello darling
Yeah, I wish you could've come
So do I
Ste acquired me helped
My wish, I could've come
I wish you fell asleep
Step on stepped myself
Then I crashed
I grab you
So whilebushes for a night
You promised you in hundred sort you want and then ate your soup with me
When I die?
I die.
The politicians, they don't even care.
It's a system.
Phones ringing.
Phone rings all the time.
No, Eli.
Yeah.
But the phones are here.
Yes, that's because we are dogs.
Comdec 3.
Calling.
Yes, sir.
We're on them, sir.
But they're not here yet.
Roger, I understand.
No, we won't make a move until you get here.
Get Pedro and Wilson here right now.
How can anything be so much?
I just, I don't understand.
Yes, sir.
Who is this?
It's the all-scratchy show.
It's the show full of high-end scratchiness.
What kind of show is this?
This is the intense phone-in show.
I said now.
Now.
Hello?
Hi.
How do you know if there's anybody really here?
It could be just fake phone calls.
You're there, aren't you?
I don't know.
Why?
How do you know if anybody's here?
I have no idea.
This is the negative question.
Yes.
You're saying that the gospel's had a soothing, so you mean...
Father?
Yes.
Wait a minute, I lost it.
Mary, you need to forgive if I went back to you.
Like a party all by myself.
Oh, my God.
God.
Hello?
Oh, my God.
Julia?
I'm sorry, darling.
Hello?
I'm sorry.
Why?
Is it Andrew?
Hello?
No, no, no.
It's the bloody office.
Oh, John.
You can say hello.
So am I.
Hello.
I'll call you tomorrow, all right?
All right.
I'll call you tomorrow.
Bye.
Do you want me to hold your phone?
Yeah.
Hold my calls and call the show tomorrow.
No.
If you ever...
How do you know it's real?
What?
No.
You grab the microphone.
No, I...
Well, I...
Yeah, I have to.
It's my show.
No, I can't grab the microphone.
You're not talking to a human.
I'm not in the studio.
There's nobody here.
The show's just tape.
The show's scary again.
It's scary.
It is scary again.
The show is scary again.
It's going to be very scary.
For the billionth time, it's scary.
We'll just do a pencil and write down this address.
Okay.
81 Lavender Lane.
Got it.
I've got a dead body and a suspect in the area, and I would appreciate some backup.
What are you talking about?
You're not even on duty.
Don't tell me what I already know.
Just do it.
That dead body didn't even know.
Scratchiness.
You wish.
It's raw.
I can't hear that caller hardly.
They've just got a bad phone connection.
Did you listen to the show on the way in?
Yeah.
You didn't even notice.
I want to discuss a little business proposition...
It sounded just fine on the way over.
...with you and your wife.
You must be mistaken.
Yeah, you must be mistaken.
I listened to it, and it's scratchy.
And then I'm going to the point...
High-end's all...
...you bring your wife.
That's the way everything sounds to me all the time anyway.
So, it's kind of a mood...
I didn't notice.
It's the circuit.
Yeah.
Everything sounds like this show to me all the time, Doctor.
Can you help me?
Doctor, there's something waiting for you on the...
...on the Mussolini balcony.
There's something waiting for you on the memorial...
...Mussolini balcony.
I mean the Mussolini memorial balcony.
Oh, yeah.
Who's got the bomb?
That's the question.
How many times this week have you muttered to yourself...
I'll have the chicken and waffles.
...I'm so bored.
I forgot to kill myself.
I'll have the chicken and waffles, too.
We're going to go get some chicken and waffles, so call back in about ten minutes.
I forgot to take you just exactly how...
Yes, how much was I able to take, Doug?
Yes, and now you both realize it'll take me...
...much, much more than simply tying the girls up to get those demons to show up anyhow.
Marching to the tune of profits coexistent with entertainment marches tunelessly onward.
No, no, ask any of their audiences or former friends that you can merely demand a new luxurious suede vinyl-covered dock tape without first terminating your reluctance to embrace racial tabloids.
Well, eat hot non-existence, pink boy, because you're not in the same ballpark as church band material.
Probably never will be without our help.
That's the number of our telephone, the atomic telephone.
Oh, the atomic telephone.
The one you can talk to the 700-foot-tall Bob Jesus.
Oh, yeah. Well, they've got one of those guys at the bleeding head of Arnold Palmer Launcher Society.
I know they had this incredibly huge Jesus there.
It was so big they couldn't launch it.
In fact, it's still there.
...an individual can do about this code disaster.
Nuclear death overpopulation of someone.
Thank you, Rondell.
A little fast train is about to be leaving you or anyone else...
This invention is devised by a precise mathematical formula in the universe of the sphere you have called the Mantis cult.
...ever wonder about the launching habits of others or how often other humans launch?
Or where and when they launch?
Perhaps you wonder if most people launch alone or do they engage in launching with a partner or group?
Tribal situations? It's the Church of the Moon.
It's the Church of the Angel.
...a foundation that lashed itself on everybody else because nobody knows what's going on.
Yes, even if you were listening to this show, even if the slim possibility that you were awake at 4.30 a.m. on Saturday morning
and could spend the time listening to our show, we doubt if you'd understand it.
Because the speaker is more important, probably.
Well, yes, Bob. The stupider it is, the more important it probably is.
But there are probably only 20 people in the entire country that can understand this game.
There are probably only 20 people in...
And are you one of them?
Hell no.
Well, it goes to show you that these people that sit up all night waiting for this show, they don't even know about the end joke.
There it is.
That's right.
They can get it if you'll just call it.
Now if you throw throw throw...
We'll tell you all the secrets of the church and many of the stories that were related to us late at night by the green gentleman from...
from some hell.
Ah, some green hell that's available for just a small amount of money.
You can write Arkansas, you can write Texas, you'll get the same answer.
You can write Oakland...
Or you can write Cleveland.
P.O. Box 181-417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
Or look under contacts at subgenius.com.
Uh, yes, that old bit we just heard was from maybe 1982 or so, and they were reading from the damny fine times.
The newsletter of the bleeding head of Arnold Palmer's Launchers Society.
By Pope Sternodocs of Little Rock, because that was pretty much the whole church back then.
Those shows and the pamphlets and the Arkansas boys.
Me and Philo.
And we'll all be doing new shows live at X Day Drift.
Phil, 15 by the time you hear this.
That's subgenius.com.
I hope your ears will be okay after this.
For me, it's kind of a moot point.
Good night, and praise Bob.
Friends, we're glad you listened to this show.
And we're even more glad that some listeners have donated enough to help us keep on going for another couple of months.
And not just this show, but subgenius.com and all the other archive sites.
But if you truly love Bob, and want some of that slack back to rebound to you,
you should go to subgenius.com front page, or especially the radio page, or the catalog store pages,
and help out financially as best you can.
Now, we know what it's like to be on the brink of total poverty,
and we don't want any subgeniuses to make their own subgeniuses.
We want to make situations worse.
But some of you still have jobs.
Even five bucks makes a big difference, even if it's only once a month from enough of you.
Fifty bucks makes an even bigger difference.
All we're saying is that
blowjobs could go the way of Steve Jobs if you don't pay Dobbs.
We also take checks and money orders to subgeniusfoundation.com.
P.O. Box 181-417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118
Thanks for anything you can do to help let there be slack.