From PR News in Washington, I'm described as a person of interest.
Meanwhile, President Trump says White House officials says Pierce Horst says Trump offered PR to gag the victims and their families.
Everyone at every level of government.
That's PR's suspicious reporting.
The Dow is 10-24-7-24.
It's unclear when President Trump plans to announce this is PR.
Boys and girls, your attention please.
Presenting a new exciting radio program featuring the thrilling adventures of an amazing and incredible personality.
The Self Genius.
Power of Swag.
Abnormal Perversion.
Oh yes, dear friends, thank you Mr. Fernandez and Andy Lemur for the titles and news.
And tonight, we're continuing the epic two-parter call-in show with the...
The resurrected Lonesome Cowboy Dave and myself, Reverend Stang.
But first, well friends, we survived the Texas deep freeze of 2022.
I may have saved Texas, although I'm not sure that's good.
Now, we were pretty traumatized on this exact date last year when the temperatures in north-central Texas stayed around 10 degrees Fahrenheit or colder for days.
And millions...
Millions of us, including everyone at Stang Ranch here, were without power, heat, or water for days.
It was really miserable.
Hundreds died, mostly of stupidity, like burning furniture indoors and suffering carbon monoxide poisoning.
Our house's plumbing was saved because we lived in Cleveland for decades and knew to leave all the faucets running.
This year, friends, I was smart and spent 500 bucks on a general...
A generator.
And some space heaters.
However, I was also stupid and didn't order them soon enough.
In fact, they probably won't be here until tonight.
But the fact that I spent all that money prevented the winter storm from being so disastrous.
If I had not spent that 500 bucks, there would have for sure been terrible rain, sleet, and ice knocking out power stations all over the state and wrecking the infrastructure again.
By my spending that money, however, subgenius sympathetic magic kicked in, making my purchase suddenly pointless, simply by preventing much worse weather.
As Dr. Uncle Onan Canabite said, rival cults put the simp in sympathetic magic.
The Church of the Subgenius practices pimp-aesthetic magic.
Anyway, I saved millions of lives of Texans.
Again, whether this is actually a good thing, that's debatable.
Anyway, we dodged a bullet.
Ted Cruz...
Oh, thank you, thank you.
Thank you, my fellow Texans.
Ted Cruz is probably in Cancun again, but he probably also set up a life-size stand-up photo of himself next to a window in his Texas house.
To fool reporters.
Anyway, we're fine.
The snow and ice is melting away.
And the fact that I have this expensive 5,000-watt generator sitting on my porch should prevent my having to actually use it, maybe forever.
I have to credit Reverend Pease for the theory about the generator purchase stafing off its own necessity.
Another bright idea.
Reverend Pease had was that we should make Hour of Slack exclusively available only on Spotify.
Then sit back and watch heads explode.
Very funny, Reverend Pease.
The dogs and cats are all okay, as is Wee Ma Ma, age 92.
Princess Wee's getting some help since her mom is technically in hospice now and the government pays for daily nurse aides.
Once it knows you probably won't be needing them for much longer.
And in other news, business is terrible.
We raised the ordainment kit price for the first time in 20 years by 10 bucks, which apparently is way too much.
Subgenius.com.
But enough of this.
You don't want to hear any more of this.
You want to hear me read the beginning of our newly published subgenius mystery novel by Reverend Teeters LaVerge.
Called The Agent and Mr. Dobbs.
The recording is not new.
And yet here it is.
I have a manuscript here.
This was turned in by Reverend Teeters LaVerge of the Church of the Subgenius.
He's been, well, I'll just read it.
The title is The Agent and Mr. Dobbs.
And actually the manuscript is from October 1962.
But these papers were found on the body of a transient party clown in the city of Albany, New York in 1989.
The papers had been meticulously taped back together after an apparent attempt at shredding them.
Some pages are missing.
The party clown was determined by the county coroner to have been killed by a police officer.
He was killed by being force-fed copious amounts of silly putty.
Some of which still had a cartoon imprint of a pleasant yet disturbing face of a smiling man with a pipe clenched between his teeth.
Now here is the manuscript.
As I said, this is from 1962.
So you'll have to forgive some of the dated terminology used by the agent who wrote this.
I'm skipping over a part where he was dropped off at the Dobbs house or mansion.
The knocker on the huge oaken front door was a rather heavy, rusty iron piece in the shape of a dollar sign.
I banged it down thrice and awaited an answer.
Soon the door creaked open and in front of me stood the tallest colored man I have ever seen.
Even taller than Agent 541.
However, he had a very high, squeaky voice that resembles a certain cartoon mouse.
He asked me my business and I replied that I had an urgent appointment with Mr. Dobbs.
The man answering the door seemed fairly out of it too and replied back that the sky was pretty damn blue today.
Again, I had to wait a few minutes until he asked me my business.
But before I could answer, he was ushering me into the cavernous building.
Once inside, I noticed that it was rather well-appointed with both new and antique furnishings,
which to my eyes seemed to come from all corners of the earth and were set about in no discernible pattern.
There were piles of paper and stacks of money everywhere.
What caught my eye, though, was the incredible amount of junk laying about the place.
This Mr. Dobbs, it would seem, had a habit of collecting useless objects found by the side of the road.
Finally, after walking through many hallways, I was shown to a door and told to walk in.
But I was expected.
I did as told.
The room I entered was the most sane that I had so far seen.
A typical den that any well-cultured man may have in his home.
Mr. Dobbs was sitting in a large leather room.
He was wearing a leather armchair with his back to me, a billow of smoke coming up from his front.
I slowly walked over to him.
He said nothing, but with his right hand he motioned me to sit on a folding metal chair adjacent to him.
He seemed to be engrossed in a television program.
It was Leave It to Beaver, a wholesome program.
Suddenly he began to speak.
I do love this show.
That Ward Cleaver is one relaxed man.
Connie doesn't like me to watch this program.
She thinks it's pornographic, but that's why I like it.
He fell into a deep silence, intently watching a commercial and nodding his head in time with the jingle.
When the commercial ended, he turned to me and asked,
What can I do for you, young agent?
I noticed then that even though the upper half of his body was clad in a dark suit with white shirt and dark tie,
the bottom half of his body was clad only in wingtip shoes.
I thought that was very disturbing and put me off for a moment,
but I'd been warned by my handlers that this Mr. Dobbs had many tricks up his sleeve,
and I took this as his way of making a person uncomfortable.
I regained my composure and told him,
Mr. Dobbs, the agency I work for has a request for you.
When suddenly Mr. Dobbs got up out of his chair and walked over to a well-appointed wet bar
and poured a tumbler full of what he claimed was the finest scotch,
saying it was from Malaysia or Canada.
My memory begins to get hazy here.
It was not scotch at all. It smelled like grape,
but tasted for the life of me like gasoline.
He bade me to drink.
Knowing that he's an important partner, I tried to force down a sip.
Then Mr. Dobbs did the strangest thing.
He started to do what I believe is called a hula dance,
yet he was humming some tango to himself.
Even though I was warned,
I can't abide a half-naked man dancing in front of me.
Yet I was transfixed.
I know now that I must have been drugged.
He danced for a while, too close to me for my waning comfort.
My heart beat faster,
and the rank smoke from his pipe seemed to make my head swim and my vision fade.
I thought I was about to faint when my heart nearly burst
as I felt a pair of hands starting to massage me.
I looked up to see a beautiful blonde with a perfect perm smiling down on me.
I took this to be his wife, Connie.
She said,
Don't fret. Bob likes to dance on Fridays.
She continued,
Now, now, dearie, we mustn't mess with our company.
Mr. Dobbs ignored her and continued his lewd dance.
Connie bade me to ask Bob what questions I may need to ask.
I started out by getting straight to the point,
reminding him of the troubles with Cuba.
Mr. Dobbs then did the queerest thing I'd seen him do yet.
He ran over to a big wooden box on the bar,
opened it, and pulled out a huge novelty cigar.
He then proceeded to insert said huge novelty cigar up his...
...neither port.
The cigar spontaneously ignited,
and Mr. Dobbs blew smoke rings out of his ear.
Surely this was an illusion or a hallucination from my drugged state.
I found myself mesmerized by Mr. Dobbs' antics.
Connie's back rub and the scotch I found myself taking a liking to.
Connie's hands reached down to my lap
as I watched Mr. Dobbs preach about economics and Cuba and war
and how it all tied together,
all the while bent over with a huge cigar puffing away in his...
...netherworld.
That is the last I remember of that evening.
The ensuing lie detector tests and truth serums have borne that out.
I awoke the next morning, late, I believe,
with a cool breeze fluttering through pastel pink curtains.
I had the worst hangover I'd ever experienced.
I cannot fully describe the sensation.
It was somewhere between getting a root canal and the high of three martinis.
I was startled to notice that Connie had died.
Connie Dobbs was nude, lying next to me.
I tried getting up but soon regretted it by the dizziness it caused.
And worst of all, I saw what was laying next to Connie.
All I saw was its shoulders and a cheap, bouffant wig on its head.
Its skin was grey.
I don't mean sickly human grey.
I mean grey as grey can be.
Its body shape was all out of whack too.
Then I had fleeting memories of a wild sexual encounter with Mrs. Dobbs
and something else.
I remember having intercourse with orifices that were not human.
I must have shuddered for Connie rolled over and picked up a glass of some clear liquid off the nightstand
and two tablets.
She demanded I take them for they would make me feel better.
I inspected the tablets and though they resembled your basic aspirin,
they were had embossed on them the word PILS spelled P-I-L-S.
Afraid of being drugged again, I tried to hide them in my cheek
but when I drank the liquid they just slid down my throat.
Within minutes, reality started to fade and some sort of orgy began.
The last thing I remember was Mr. Dobbs dressed as a clown with no pants on of course,
attempting to take my virginity.
I still have nightmares about this but as they say, my country, right or wrong.
Weeks passed that I have little memory of.
I know this only because of the date in which I was retrieved by the agency.
The Dobbses and their minions kept me pretty well fropped up as they called it.
The next event that I have any clear memory of was of taking a ridiculously long elevator ride
deep into the earth at the Bobco Mining and Soylent Green Consortium in Wyoming.
We must have been on that elevator for three hours.
One of Dobbs' minions took my watch during the orgy and refused to give it back saying,
Bob doesn't pay enough and he had to get some stuff for a weekend party
he and the Kennedys were having with one Dr. Oswald.
When we finally alighted from the elevator, to my surprise,
we were not in some mine shaft as I expected,
but in a huge vaulted warehouse full of novelty goods
that were being stacked and sorted by strange short men shrouded in sack rags.
Bob claimed that they were ex-Nazis, scientists,
working on some quote super-duper extra secret unquote project for the government.
I could clearly see that they were not men at all but slaves of some unknown species.
By this time I had found it to my better judgement not to doubt Mr. Dobbs, at least not out loud.
We took a golf cart type of vehicle down a long winding corridor.
Mr. Dobbs not once paid any attention to where he was driving.
He decided to at that time ramble on and on about some mysterious substance he called slack,
all the while puffing insanely on his pipe, the bowl of which soon glowed a bright red.
During this journey we ran over three of Bob's slave men and nearly hit countless others.
Mr. Dobbs was oblivious to each quote accident.
I put that in quotes for each one of the slaves we ran over I happened to notice had been pointing a weapon of some sort at Mr. Dobbs
right before he mindlessly ran over them.
This mysterious Mr. Dobbs may have some sort of second sight or is just incredibly lucky.
As you'll see I believe it has more to do with luck and some sort of strange time control powers than with anything else.
Mr. Dobbs' underground office was a horror.
I can barely describe it. It was a total mess and stank of the tobacco that he constantly smoked.
In fact I never saw Mr. Dobbs without that.
I saw that infernal pipe clenched between his teeth.
It was only after a few minutes of adjusting to the stench and the mess of the office that I saw something that horrified me.
The place had several severed human heads strewn haphazardly all over.
Now I've seen some terrible sights in my life and I suspect that if I'm on the Dobbs case I will see worse.
But what made me gasp was that the heads were not of random humans but of public figures that we would all recognize.
I saw the heads of...
And this section was carefully cut out of the original report.
And one was actually singing.
It begged me in the tenor to please kill me.
Surprisingly in the state I had been in I did not faint.
Instead with all the smoke from Bob's special tobacco mix I started to laugh.
This got Bob all worked up.
He started to jump around inanely and laugh.
He then proceeded to use one of the heads, not the singing one,
in a most foul manner.
Bob bade me sit down on a chair that was stacked high with papers.
I looked at the stack and back at Bob wondering what he expected me to do.
By this time I had begun to get in the spirit of the situation and laughingly knocked the stack of papers on the floor.
Mr. Dobbs didn't seem to mind.
In fact he stared down at the mess I made and said thanks.
Picked up a sheet of paper saying he'd been looking for this contract for quite some time.
The glyphs on the sheet were of no known human alphabet that I have ever encountered.
For some reason this worried me and reminded me of the slaves I saw working for Bob
and that dreadful night with Mrs. Dobbs and that strange grey creature.
I did not have much time to consider the implications for Mr. Dobbs wadded up the paper,
tossed it in a corner and told me to follow him.
This time we did not take the vehicle but instead walked down dark and dank corridors
which had a gradual down slope.
Being without a timepiece I cannot estimate the amount of time we walked but it seemed like hours.
Here I must admit my perceptions of time had been warped by constant exposure to Bob's tobacco.
Mr. Dobbs finally guided me to our final destination.
What I saw in that final circle of hell I cannot, I will not reveal.
Through all the pressure that the agency could bear against me,
a loyal true blue agent and American,
I found it in our best interest to keep some things secret even from the boss, the man in the dress.
I do this for the good of our nation and out of fear
for what Mr. Dobbs revealed to me was so horrific, so humorous, so bizarre, so unchristian,
so baffling and dangerous that I hyperventilated through the inane laughter
that was my only defense lest I totally lose my mind.
The last thing I remember is that I was in the middle of a night
and I remembered that day was Mr. Dobbs dancing around my prostrate body
he was prancing really
and mimicking my insane laughter with his own even crazier chortles.
He spoke no words, he just laughed, but his laughter seemed to speak volumes to my inner mind.
I laughed, I wept, I urinated in my undergarments
for Mr. Dobbs had somehow relieved me of my slacks
when I do not recall.
And friends, at this point I, Reverend Stang, must cease reading
from the document The Agent and Mr. Dobbs brought to us by Reverend Teeters LaVerge.
I've gotten a little ways into part two and it goes all the way up to part six so far.
However, I have a piece of music here that I think will be extremely pertinent to the subject matter.
This is Reverend Angry Larry.
The Agent and Mr. Dobbs
Two men lined up for the FBI
Keeping tabs on an agent on the land, on the sea and the sky
And every single night
Before I go to bed
I get down on my knees and say, Bob, I'm a Secret Agent, man
Secret Agent, man
They came in jednak
a number, but they
take away my name.
I got one hell
of a job to perform for
the U.S. of A.
Got the
responsibility of our nation's
top security.
But every night
and day,
I salute the flag and say
thank you, Connie,
because I'm a secret agent
man.
Secret
agent man.
Secret agent man.
They give
me a number,
but they take away my name.
You know
they got me doing this, doing that,
a little bit of something else.
But
fighting cavities of evil,
safeguarding America's health.
But I'm
an afternoon pass.
I don't get up off my
ass. Thank you, Stan,
because I'm a secret agent
man.
Secret
agent man.
Secret agent man.
They give
me a number,
but they take away
my name.
Secret
agent man.
Secret agent man.
They give
me a number,
but they take away my
name.
And that was an excerpt from the news of Genius
Novel, The Agent and Mr. Dobbs
by Reverend Teeters LaVerge,
now available in a limited,
numbered, special hardcover
edition of not quite
50 copies with a price to match
at subgenius.com.
Some cheapskates
may need to wait for the paperback
version due out someday.
But now,
let's go back to the pre-recorded
visit from Lonesome Cowboy Dave,
recorded a couple of weeks ago
at Tarzan's
radio station
at Stang Ranch and interspersed
with some subgenius history
and Sheridan collage.
Take it away,
us.
Oh, this music
in the background, by the way,
is from the Empire
Jazz Orchestra.
Praise Bob.
My heart was full of song from up there.
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to break the flow,
so to speak.
The songs from
Hello Dolly was echoing
through this big hollow castle
earlier today.
Princess Wee's mom,
Wee Ma Ma,
was watching Hello Dolly
crank up, boy, she likes to crank up
her rock and roll.
And if the door's open, you can hear it everywhere.
I peeked in and saw Barbara
Streisand in this
fabulous production
scene. It just was mind-blowing.
The costume,
the costumes, and...
Oh, I would love to make love to her nose.
What has happened to your nose?
Odysseus, Odysseus,
what has happened to your nose?
Asshole.
Fire Sign Theater quote.
That's what we should do.
We should cut to Fire Sign Theater.
Turn this FM off here.
Radio, over here.
Okay.
I'll get the TV.
No, no, no, leave it on for a minute.
What has happened to your nose?
I've just returned from Rome. What?
Yeah, yeah, I have seen this before.
Go ahead, turn it off.
Well, that's it.
Here's your keys.
Goodbye, friends, and happy motoring
back on the freeway, which is already in progress.
Whew!
Well, here goes.
Nice feel.
Let's see...
du du du
Oh, how can you be in two places at once when you're not anywhere at all?
I think I'll give this old baby a spin on the freeway.
Entering freeway.
Here we go.
Emergency parking.
Merging buses ahead.
Oh.
Easy access.
Spadometer's only got half a mile on her.
Adelaide Freeway North.
Do I want to go north or do I want to take the, let's see, the Gomorrah Expressway West?
Okay.
If you lived here, you'd be home by now.
Antelope Hill.
Selected living.
Comfortable.
Easy.
Okay.
Antelope Freeway.
This lane.
Exit over.
Yeah, I think I'll take the old Antelope.
Less traffic.
Antelope Freeway 1-1.
Clean up Armenia.
Get a hairnet.
Antelope Freeway 1-1.
Chili Avenue.
Let's see what they got in this car.
Let's see.
We got lights, wipers, defrost, temperature and climate control.
Antelope Freeway 1-1.
Hmm.
Let's see what kind of climate I can get.
Antelope Freeway 1-1.
Winter wonderland.
Choo-choo-choo.
Spring fever.
Indian summer.
Antelope Freeway 1-1.
Tropical paradise.
I think I'll give it a try.
Wow.
What a groove.
A tropical paradise.
Antelope Freeway 1-1.
Let's go.
What a wonderful clearing in the jungle.
This is just the place to build our camp.
All right, you men.
Get cracking now.
The pupden's right over there, I think.
The foundation should go right about here.
The stockade.
Excuse me, sir, but may I speak to you alone, sir?
Of course you can.
Daddy, I've lost the Lincoln dogs.
That's all right.
I've got an erector set.
Show off.
Throw a towel over it.
Do some push-ups, Pablo.
It'll go away.
Hey, what are you guys doing in my car?
The fox trot.
You can have the next dance.
But throw him the fox.
This animal is sick.
Yes, it is a catchy little number.
Uh-oh, I think he's caught it.
Doctor, give him something for his cough.
All right, all right.
Here's a quarter.
Oh, that's not much.
Not much of a cough.
I need a gas station.
Did I pass one?
No, no, but the fox did.
Squeeze him right there.
Maybe he'll pass another one.
No, no.
Gasoline.
Oh, my boy, if it's drugs you want, the old doctor can help you out.
Right this way.
Hey, get your hands off me.
I don't want to leave.
Then roll up your arm and bend over.
Here.
You want regular or premium?
Oh, this is ridiculous.
You guys are nothing but a pack of cards.
Drink me.
Must be some way out of this.
I'll change the air.
That's what I'll do.
Let's see.
What have I got left on the climate control?
Uh, dust storm?
No.
Tibetan wilderness?
Land of the pharaohs.
That sounds great.
All right, all right.
Here we are in the land of the pharaohs.
Oh, no.
Well, we'll need to talk with the natives.
Does anyone here know a little Egyptian?
Bill, Bill, come on down.
You're good at languages.
Yes, yes, yes, indeed.
That was it.
What?
Yes, indeed.
Yes, a little Egyptian.
Yes, everybody knows I'm mad.
Served my every need.
Did a grand job on my ankles, too.
Now, hold it right.
There.
Glad to.
Now, I think I'll hold it over here.
Oh, boy, it's nice out, isn't it?
Yes, I think you ought to leave it out.
Hey, hey, hey, look, fellas.
Fun's fun, okay, but look, I gotta find a place to stay.
It's gonna be night soon.
I'm tired.
What's the matter with that dude?
I'm lost, and I wanna go to bed.
Oh, my bony boy.
In the Estonian mountains, we used to go to sleep
leaning up against a windfall.
I was but a mere prat then.
I'll never forget the time a snake slithered into my wife.
It wasn't but neat.
I was a beehive to a merry grasshopper.
Oh, no, no, look, that's all very interesting,
but the sun is going down.
Oh, no, no, you're all confused.
The horizon is moving up.
Hey, listen, come on, you guys, help me, please.
I know, I know.
Let's stand him on his head.
Here you go.
Hey, hey, hey, put me down.
Relax, relax.
Easy, boy.
Ah, you see?
Now it's morning.
Oh, boy.
Oh, he's no fun.
He fell right in.
He fell right over.
Oh, hey, won't somebody please help me?
Easy, easy, my lad.
At times of dexterity like this,
my wee native compendium, Mohamit,
used to pray to the divinitize.
His little brown, froggy body
equivorate my loins.
Chanting a stream of ancient Egyptian holograms.
What?
A diaphragm.
No, no, no, no.
I used to date him.
Hieroglyphs, that's it.
Do you remember any?
Will they help?
Anything at all?
Yes, of course, of course.
Let's see.
It was a jackal-headed woman with her eyes kimbo.
A king sitting sideways on his throne.
A drip with gold, chippet nose uplifted.
Dashly.
All engraven on a pyramid of massive size.
With the body of a lion,
paws that refreshes,
a tail told by an idiot,
and the head of a fox.
The pyramid is opening.
Which one?
The one with the ever-widening hole in it.
I'm saved.
I'm going in.
No, don't do this, son.
It's dark and dirty in there.
Oh, but Mom.
It's full of bees and spiders.
You might poke your eye out.
What if your father comes home?
I'm going in, Mom.
There's a vacancy.
I'm going in.
Good evening, sir.
Welcome to the only nice motel in town.
How long will you be with us?
Just for tonight.
Ah, very well, sir.
You'll find it's very clean here.
Just fill out this card.
Oh, thanks.
Oh, look, it's dirty.
Somebody's already used it.
There's a name on it.
That's all right.
Well, I couldn't get you to believe my name is Mr. and Mrs. John Smith, could I?
Well, of course you could.
It's nice to have you with us, Mr. and Mrs. Smith.
Run!
Hey, aren't you Mr. and Mrs. John Smiths?
From any town in the USA?
I'm Joe, boy, and this here's Ed.
Hey, I'm not really Mr. and Mrs. John Smith.
Well, that's okay. I'm not Joe.
He's not Ed.
Hey, fella, how about bending a couple of Medu-Dah rolls?
If you catch my meaning.
If you get my drift.
Thanks, fellas, but I'm kind of tired.
Hey, desk clerk, can I have my key, please?
Sure. What about G7?
Get it, Jimmy.
I can tell by the pound you're tied.
You're an American. Well, so am I.
Hi, Bubba. Howdy. How do you do?
And while we're on the subject...
Welcome to your wazoo!
What's that all about?
What's it all about, Mr. and Mrs. John Q. Smiths from any town USA?
Well, it's about this long...
And about that wide...
And it's about this country...
About which we're singing about.
I was born an American.
I was raised an American.
And I'll die an American in America with our millions.
Boy, that was hilarious, wasn't it?
See, you like that transition I did?
Firesign Theater, they're the greatest.
They were so much better than anybody else.
Until... Of course, until we came along.
Is there any kind of gaseous energy escaping from your house right now?
Huh? What? Say that? What?
The gas is erupting from your nostrils.
I mean, you just sound like you're making so much fun that you can hardly hold it in.
That's Princess We, not me.
Oh, okay.
Remember, she's the Robin Givens to my Howard Smith.
She's the Robin Givens to my Howard Stern.
She excuses my excesses with her gay laughter.
Yeah, but Robin Givens used to carry a gun, a shotgun.
And Stern...
Hey, we figured out where that...
What inspired that noise in the score of The Good, Bad, and the Ugly by Ennio Morricone...
It's Coyote.
In the movie.
Which I was watching last night.
It starts with these bad guys in a really run-down train station or something.
And they're about to go in and kill Duco.
And there's a coyote, a lone coyote going...
And it suddenly comes to the title music, and that's the noise.
And now it's the time
You did that?
D'oh.
Yes!
LoveE vre
Where's the train that derives the train from?
It sees me fit in this love
I'm your friend.
Please don't die.
Please.
I'm your friend.
Come on, Eddie.
Come on.
Blondie?
I'll help you.
Don't move.
I'll be right back.
Did you notice those scenes before?
No, no.
When I was watching the movie, I heard the coyote.
When I was a kid, I didn't even know what a coyote sounded like.
I grew up in the city.
Out here, you can't escape them.
No.
And this is kind of like the Wild West.
It's definitely coyote country.
Until you get to the highway, then it's just goddamn suburbs.
Pinkland, normal town.
Out here, we've got a horse.
Ain't much of a horse.
It's a real old horse.
But there actually is a horse here.
He's a good-looking horse.
A whole bunch of goats.
Yeah.
Oh, mess of goats.
Good goats.
Goats are fun, too.
So mighty.
Great goats.
I am goat.
Well, once upon a time, we all were, you know.
We all came from Mammy Goat's uterus, or chicken pie, whatever it's called.
Mammy's chicken pie?
We all came from Mammy's chicken pie?
Yeah, the goat.
The goat woman.
Who looked a little bit like Adolf Hitler in her younger days.
And was constantly warned away from the rest of the kids.
Oh, you're a...
You're quoting that famous Doctors for Wotan song, Louie Louie, Are You a Girl or a Goat Woman?
Yeah.
It was a director.
I should cut to that, except that it's really horrible, Sandra.
Louie Louie, are you a girl or a goat woman?
Louie Louie, Louie Louie, are you a girl or a goat woman?
I didn't know.
I wanted to stand there.
The signs said, see the goat woman.
And I did it.
I paid my 50 cents and I saw her as she was.
Louie Louie.
And so, panting across the stage.
I think I was so troubled by her looks.
And she looked so beautiful.
And her beard.
Her beard.
It was so loud.
Her beard smelled of...
Her udders.
I loved biting those.
Those distended udders.
Her udders.
Louie Louie.
Louie Louie, are you a girl or a goat woman?
She left her pellets, those little pellets, all over the rug.
And the most beautiful of all.
She left behind on the stage as she danced.
Tiny pellets.
Goat pellets.
And I knew she was the girl for me.
Louie Louie.
Are you a girl or a goat woman?
No, no, no, no.
Well, that's why I played for that reason itself.
I'll just re-record it.
Louie Louie.
Uh-uh.
Are you a girl or a goat woman?
Uh-uh-uh.
And then I saw her at the carnival in the freak show.
And she was so beautiful.
And her hooves.
And her beautiful...
Goat woman breastage.
And I looked back in the dressing room.
And there were little tiny pellets and droppings of it.
And I fell in love.
Now you're talking.
Louie Louie.
Are you a girl or a goat woman?
Nah.
Man, that's it.
That's just a 100 proof.
Yeah.
Yeah, that was the cover of Louie Louie.
Are you a girl or a goat woman?
By Pooh Watertowel.
The original was Doctors for Wotan.
Princess, we and I are Pooh Watertowel once every three years when we record a song.
We've got to record Buddy.
Yes, we do.
The dog, the doc, the frop rock dog opera.
Well, here we are.
The rock opera.
Sitting here with the microphones, we should do it.
You know what?
I even have that karaoke cut of Tommy Ready to Go.
All right.
We cut it down to 19.
17 minutes instead of an hour and a half.
It's based on Tommy, of course, the rock opera.
But it's Buddy.
Buddy, can you hear me?
And so on.
That was back when Buddy escaped all the time.
He's a different dog now.
Hey, man.
That's a different dog, man.
Stay away from him.
Like me.
He's a different dog now, man.
Yeah.
Yeah, you got me wrong.
I'm a different dog now.
You got me wrong.
I didn't do it.
See?
Kids, are you clean?
No?
Why don't you try Triology Soaps from TriologySoaps.com?
Yes, there's a Dobbs head embedded in each translucent bar of Triology Soaps
in every possible funny named scent, including scentless.
But that one's not free.
Nor is it scented.
You can try TriologySoaps.com.
Now, you weren't reading that, were you?
You were just swinging it in?
Well, it's a real ad.
I can't run that on WCSB, for instance.
That's what I thought.
Yeah.
That's it for the ad.
It's verboten.
Yeah.
Our friend, Lord Ferg, among his many holdings, includes a company that makes this soap.
And it's special.
It really is.
It's a subgenius brand soap.
It's a silhouette Dobbs head made of dark colored soap inside of a translucent, clearish kind of soap.
Oh, it's so cool.
Because when you're using it and you're rolling it around in your hands,
the pipe flips from right to left as you flip it around and make the lather.
And so the soap portends your day.
When you put it down in the soap dish, if the pipe is facing to the right,
you're going to have a great day.
If it's to the left, not so much.
If it's to the left, it's communist.
That's what's wrong with this country.
Everybody's a communist but me.
Are you sure you didn't get backwards?
But as you're flopping it over...
Oh, I got it backwards.
It turns from Bob to Dick.
Dick Dobbs has his pipe going out the wrong way.
So it's like Bob Dick, Bob Dick, Bob Dick.
Well, that almost sounds obscene.
Yeah, but no kidding, man.
The girls love it.
Old Bob will sell just about anything to just about anybody.
What's he sold you today?
So?
So there's a great quote.
I wish I had come up with it.
That it's easier to act your way into a new way of thinking
than to think your way into a new way of acting.
So how important the external is to changing the internal.
It wasn't possible to measure happiness
or to compare happiness across individuals.
We would look basically at consumer preferences.
The inspiration to incorporate happiness into economic modeling
came from a rather unlikely source.
The networks had a stranglehold on national news.
Local stations did what minimal news they needed to do.
To fulfill FCC requirements that said in exchange for using the public airways,
you had to have a certain amount of news on them.
Partly cloudy skies with a high near 22.
Some lingering light snow flurries still in the air.
Partly cloudy tonight with a low of 12 degrees.
Are you suffering from information overload?
You suffering from information overload?
Information overload?
Are you suffering from information overload?
Almost every
effort has gone unnoticed.
These tend to sound funny to the outside world.
Is yourfor the change only compared to your make a story?
All right.
All right, it's all over.
We're all happy now.
We're so happy.
We all love each other.
There's evidence that human connection also modulates or can affect one's autonomic nervous system.
Human beings must be in the loop before someone is killed by a drone.
But it's in the machine.
My replica.
And it doesn't need people.
It's me, your computer.
I can't turn it off.
We need to talk.
I can't put it away.
It's in me.
It's computer.
Together.
You're me.
Don't get freaked out.
Destroy.
It can decide by itself.
Whether or not it kills somebody.
Huh?
I don't see a good reason to believe that we would survive.
Don't get freaked out.
Yeah.
I still think it would be fun to talk to a robot.
There was all kinds of experimentation and fun going on there.
All kinds of experimentation and fun.
The answer to why is my brain like this is,
because your brain is like this.
And that's all there is to it.
There is no more.
Bummer.
Close your eyes and pretend with me for a few seconds.
This is not a rerun.
Not a rerun.
Bye.
It's Bob.
Follow in my footsteps.
Bob.
It's Bob.
Alert.
Greetings, Bob.
Hello.
This is Bob.
I'm out at the moment.
If you leave your name and your telephone number,
I will call you back.
You know, I waited for somebody to say Bob.
You're fired.
I got the power.
I got the treasure.
And you have a flight to catch.
Huh?
Ah!
That's it.
No more Mr. Knife Guy.
This is what life is like.
At a, at a bottom line level, you know,
and I'm not gonna make you cut through
a lot of other stuff to get through it.
Here's what it is.
There's no gimmick about that.
It's straightforward.
It's strong and it's elemental.
We are heavy.
This wouldn't be a great way to do that on Earth,
but it's really a very efficient way
to do it.
Well, when?
Right now?
Go ahead.
No, no.
If not now, when?
If not us, who?
No, neither one of those two
are all right right now.
I have to go lay down
in the toilet for a while.
Well, Dave,
it has been an hour
and one minute
of show.
Show.
I'll probably chop it up
into two shows.
Oh, you handsome dog.
Yeti, say something.
He does talk.
He does.
No, that's not him.
That's her doing it.
No, I'm trying to get him
to do it.
That's how he talks, though.
Huh?
Why?
I'm just saying I had a dog
who saved a kid from drowning.
You did?
Yes, he did.
He jumped right in.
They got me out, all right.
And then the dog got in there
and got the kid
and the kid put his arms
around the dog's neck
and swam him in
and the dog shook
and everybody that was watching
the horrible event
applauded and went,
yeah.
Was this when you were,
uh,
a small kid?
No, this is when I was
a 20-some-year-old kid
and thought I was
the world's greatest athlete
and would go running
far, far with my dog.
And we came upon a place
in the river
that there was a,
what's it called?
Oh, I forget what they call that.
A water...
When the water gets...
When the water sucks
back up under
and pulls you down
as you get...
You get about five feet
away from the dam
and then it...
Pulls you back under.
The undertow.
An undertow.
And, uh,
I was there
for a much longer time
and the EMS people
had to come and
dig me out,
but my dog
did save a kid's life.
The kid was going,
please, mister,
help us.
Please help us.
And you didn't do anything,
but the dog understood
what the kid was saying.
Well, kind of, yeah.
Yeah, I thought,
oh, we're so much better.
We're so much smarter than dogs.
Recently,
on a training film,
I saw a dog deliver,
what's it called?
Chest smackers
to a person
who had a heart attack.
Now, see,
doesn't that sound
like a heart attack
that just now?
A little bit.
Yeah.
That's when I can't hear...
I can't understand him.
I can hear him,
but it...
How about this way?
I moved it like a microsecond
to the left.
There you go.
Is it okay now?
Yeah.
Okay, well,
I usually talk
pointing my mouth
just slightly to the side
of the microphone.
That's what I have to do.
So it's not popping the P's
like a bunch of puds
and puddlies.
You wouldn't believe
what that looks like
on the waveform.
It knocks everything else down
because I've got
an automatic volume limiter
on here,
and those P's
just make everything
drop out for a second.
I've seen the...
I've seen what the impulsives do.
It's a pain.
Pulsives?
Yeah.
Pulsives are a pain.
Poppity P's.
Oh,
pop your
pulses
P-P's.
We wept.
We just wrecked
that recording
and that song
about P-P's.
Whatever.
Oh,
at least Reverend P's
will be proud.
Yes.
He'll go,
oh,
I see you finally
mentioned me.
It's about time.
Yeah.
He will say that.
As if it wasn't
about time
to begin with,
you know?
It's about time.
It's about space.
It's about two men
in the craziest place.
Starring
Buzzzie,
who lives
over to
Stephenville
now.
Believe it or not,
Ruth Buzzzie
lives in Stephenville,
Texas,
not far from here.
Goodness.
That's right down the street.
Yep.
Oh,
she's my babe.
Who else?
Bob Denver
and Chuck McCann.
Now,
why can't we
remember
who was in that
horrible,
crappy kids show
and I can't remember
your W-2 form?
I think we all know.
I think we do know.
We know exactly why.
Let's just not dwell on it.
Let's not focus on that.
Let's not.
Friends,
you've been listening
to the Hour of Slack
here on radio station,
insert station here,
in the beautiful city
of the,
uh,
Bill Cates voice
should say the town.
And,
uh,
that is,
that's all folks.
Says,
Porky Pig.
Some non-stutterer.
I'll speak to you
once again soon.
I hope so.
I really hope so.
I hope so too.
I hope,
I hope the snow melts
someday there,
Dave.
That would,
that would be helpful
in recovering
my senses
and my,
and other stuff
like that.
Yeah.
Me too.
Okay, man.
Okay.
Okay, okay.
Okay, woman.
Okay.
Okay, all right.
Jesus.
Enough.
I busta.
Okay, I'm gonna,
I'm gonna hang up.
Oh, he hung up.
See, he does that.
Uh-oh, look what
Julian from Trailer Park Boys
is saying
to me on a message.
I get notifications
from Julian
of Trailer Park Boys.
Hey, dummy.
The dick mobile is ready.
Hurry up and get your shit.
That's what it says.
And he's right.
Oh, should I turn the sound on
for the Trailer Park Boys game?
It's the same as their TV theme.
Here.
Hey, Laufer,
,
Vroom!
Vroom, vroom.
Vroom.