Q. I tired. Hungry. When is it time to sleep? How do I go to the bathroom room?
Smack. Smack boom bam. Put your trust in TV. TV. TV gives me seeds. Plant seeds.
Flowers grow grow grow. I don't have any rights. Right. I don't know my rights.
Give me flowers or I shall die. I shall die. Die die die.
Mrs. Q enters the TV room. Billy, it's time for the subgenius hour of sweat.
Smack. Get up now. Let us put you to sleep.
Billy.
He reluctantly detaches his consciousness from the television. As if in a dream he is led to his bed.
He is soon asleep. A dreamless sleep. His memory cleared. Ready for a new day. Ready for anything.
And now, an explanation of the anatomy of a bobby.
One.
Subliminal jests, rants, hints, etc. enter Bobby's ear canal.
Two.
Sound carried along past via eardrum and ear bones.
Three.
Sound encoded into nerve impulse in cochlea.
Four.
Impulse sent to subconscious mind.
Five.
Bobby's subconscious being less dense than his own.
Three.
impulse in the vesicles through without affecting either the impulse or the subconscious six in pulse bouts off thought process is crashes and temporary memory started seven memory feels what's encoded just and kesindo overflow for death poor the motor
areas in the cerebral cortex that control it.
the jaw, tongue, lips, lungs, and vocal cords.
9.
Bobby, unaware of meaning behind the messages, repeats jokes and rants word for word.
10.
Now empty temporary memory storage sends signal of relief to pleasure centers.
11.
Pleasure centers instruct jaw, tongue, lips, lung, and vocal cords to issue stupid giggle and grin.
12.
Cycle starts over.
And that was It the Tard and Sheldon DeWeer,
Reverend Sheldon DeWeer from his tape hangnail of the start.
13.
But my friends, already we hear the accusations of sellouts coming from the armchair subgeniuses out there,
subfundamentalists, whose only pathetic reality is virtual.
These three crayons short of a full Crayola set gimme bobs complain to each other with smug complacency.
14.
Is nothing profane anymore?
15.
And this show isn't as obtuse and obnoxious as I could have done.
16.
Listen up you bobbies there.
17.
The church of the subgenius is not some namby-pamby art club.
18.
Not a reassuring politically correct in-out list to check your dopeness against as you huddle with a few other outcast dweebs in your face.
19.
You're a bunch of idiots in college dorms and high schools wrapping yourselves tight in your poster of daubs and pointing your fingers outward yelling PINKS over and over at everything that isn't you.
20.
Like some damaged disc segment crashing eternally against the system software.
21.
Oh boy, have we got news for you.
Yes, you!
You pseudo-suede sub.
Jargon spout no.
22.
You're a wannabe elite slacker than thou snob poseurs masturbating to your own hidden hitness.
23.
Bob's holy crusade isn't some underground circle jerk or silly codified in-joke.
Merely repeating Bob's name will not make you cool.
24.
Hating this show won't do you a bit of good on that ghastly day when the exes arrive to tab the planet's solar system.
25.
and spend them like so much chump change.
27.
We tell you, preaching to the saved is for cowards and free will is a joke.
28.
As if we'd give a flying hamster poot if you liked this show or not.
What do you think this is, communism?
29.
You who hate this show think you know the meaning of true hate?
30.
You who are still mired in non-convenientism.
31.
You who are still mired in conformist conformity.
32.
Unknowing slaves to anti-fashion fashion trends.
33.
You jealous followers with your oh-so-smug assumptions can't stand the thought of rich, successful, sexy weirdos, can ya?
34.
If no other mutant succeeded anything, then there's nothing for you to measure your own personal failure against.
35.
And you can stay safely fropped out.
36.
Asleep in your carefully hoarded piles of hermetic dung.
37.
You can't even see the
As for us, we'll never stop.
39.
Never!
40.
Until every living and living dead organism on the Earth bows down before Bob.
41.
Until every creature, great and small, dies.
42.
Until every creature reaches that most manifest level of mental drives, the totally consummating desire to kill Bob.
43.
And then comes out the other side knowing that nothing matters anymore.
44.
Because, my friend, as St. Palmer Freedies and I have said in this rant, Bob isn't the answer and neither is anything else.
45.
Did I keep you?
What's really going on here?
Him.
Are we talking about the death of the Big Machine?
One of theassesMy
What does it all really mean?
47.
Are we talking about the death of the Big Machine?
5.
14.
That's right, America.
In one но蒙
We're talking about the death of the Big Machine.
We're talking about the Big Hermetically Sealed Vacuum-Packed enterprise Tech actions
Por que pierwszy
goron
bits and bytes of information
which don't really, aren't really
having any existence.
And are these some way
a pizza front
for the corrupting snakes of hell?
I'm asking you as a caller
and as a personal beninder
and a bad reminder,
I'm asking
each and every one of you
out there
to remain quiet.
Do not lay down.
Stand where you are
and do not leave your homes.
Information
will be given out
on a first come,
user-friendly basis only.
So,
in the case
of an emergency or
a dynamic flux
or accident in the
warple frame,
in the warple fabric
of the time frame,
you will be
wrecked.
By your nearest authority
and we're not talking about
the man who waves the flag.
We're talking about the man
who finds that flag
like the Eerojima wavers
and raises it up on high
and plants it firmly
in his own breast.
He pounds it like a steak
into his heart.
May I interrupt here?
Um, Harry, let me take care
of a little business here
and then we'll continue
with this insanity.
I'm sorry, Taz.
I just got carried away.
I know you did, Dave.
I can't think about them too long.
Attention all writers
or would-be writers.
That's you.
Huh?
What?
I've been a would-be writer
for so long now.
The third annual Cleveland
material.
That was the idea.
What?
That's the true-true that I was
listening on Radio Netherlands
and this marine biologist
was saying that by the year 2020,
and we're not talking TV or ice
in the year 2020.
Come on now.
2020.
Taz, Flipper may be dead by 2020.
I'm talking about all the...
Flipper's already dead.
I'm talking about all the great whales.
And their great songs.
And all the great hits of the past.
Of course.
Because don't you know?
Jesus is going to come back
and make everything perfect
when, you know,
when it's all gone.
I'm waiting.
I'm waiting already.
Well, you just, you know,
have some patience.
Some faith, brother.
I cannot have faith.
I am of ye of little faith.
Ye of little faith.
I'm a doubting Thomas Gaugh.
If ye just had the faith
of a grain of mustard seed
or something like that...
Then, like, it would grow.
And I know all that stuff.
But I can't believe it.
I can't believe it.
I can't believe the lard
is going to come back
and repopulate the seas
with great whales
and even, well, great, great,
great videotapes.
Of great whales.
Of also great whales in bondage.
I can hardly wait for them.
They said that by 2025,
there'll be weird snuff films
of great whales.
Force-feeding great whales.
Force-feeding snuff films
of great whales.
Oh, man.
Now you're talking.
With diapers.
In diapers.
Yeah.
That's where we're heading, man.
No.
That's where we're heading.
I'm going head first.
Hey, there's a fetish party Sunday
at the Smart Bar.
A fetish party.
So if you come...
We missed the Friday the 13th party.
If you come dressed in your...
We're going to be there.
I want to be there.
Come and go to the fetish party.
Are you?
Yeah, sure.
What the hell?
I'm going to dress in my little
leather underwear.
Well, I knew that you had
pierced nipples.
I knew that.
Yeah.
You should see my balls.
I don't...
I'm sorry.
No, I don't particularly...
It's my baseballs.
Yeah, your big, shiny baseballs.
I know.
I remember you talking about them too often.
Hello, you're on the air.
Hey, it's me.
Who are you?
Uh...
That's Walter.
Well, don't bring the whole thing
to a screaming halt.
That's okay, Walter.
You don't have to know your real name.
You can have a fake name
as long as you're talking to me.
It's like a pretend thing.
I'm having a crisis.
What are you having a crisis about?
I found it.
If you're not dead,
you're part of it no matter what.
then you're stuck in this
smear of La Bombo.
Even you're asleep, Steve.
Did you relock the door?
Even I'm asleep?
You're a slave to their system.
I'm a slave to no one.
I'm speaking against
the corrupting worms.
No system.
Dave is the ultimate romantic hero.
No system is my master.
Like Don Giovanni.
I'm DJ, man.
No system is my alibi.
I'm contrary to all that stuff.
Hello, you're on the air.
Hello.
All the dirty bastards.
687-351-...
No, no, no, no, no, no.
That's the number in some of
the other places.
And we'll have to shut off
Lonesome Cowboy Dave and Chaz Smith there
from taped off of WCSB in Cleveland.
Now, what's that about?
Oh, there we go.
This...
Speaking of Cleveland,
this background music is by Ron Slade
of Cleveland.
And...
Oh, I guess now it's time to read you
a little bit of news
about the weird.
News of the weird here, dear friends.
News of the weird is a...
It's a new...
Some of you may see it in your weekly entertainment
magazines in your local town.
But we'll just...
Let's see.
We'll just read from it a little bit here.
Get some semi-neutral music in.
And...
Let's see.
Mm.
. . .
. . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . .
It's breath잽
they are an endangered species.
But people had used
stones, spears,
fires, and tribal drumbeats
to ward them off.
At least six people
were trampled to death.
Yes, revenge
is sweet, dear friends.
There's a lot of animal news
here. Animal
liberation news.
In November, officials
at, pardon me,
officials, gotta be ready
to have a radio star there. Whoa!
Wow.
What? Must have been them elephants.
Those elephants are getting them.
It is the elephants.
Oh no, it's not. It's the
Gyuto monks.
Anyway, in November, officials at
the Tokyo Sea Life Park
reported that about 10% of the
aquarium's bluefin and yellowfin
tuna have developed
deformed faces.
Because of the stress
of swimming in a small tank.
Large bumps
have appeared on some fish's
faces. Other fish's eyes
have become partially
dislodged.
I got news for you, friends. It's called
becoming middle
aged.
Uh, here's some
uh, oh, economic
weird news. In January, the
government of Brazil reported an annual
inflation rate for 1990.
In the year 1993, of
2,500%.
And Yugoslavia reported
that the cost of living rose
trillion percent
over the course of 1993.
In
Belgrade, a factory
that manufactures steel springs,
heard here in the background,
paid its workers in live
pigs rather than money.
In Rio de Janeiro,
a survey sponsored by the weekly
news magazine,
Istoé, found that
inflation was at least partly responsible
for the diminished frequency of sexual
relations in Brazil.
From an average person's
three times a week to
1.6. Said
a Sao Paulo psychotherapist,
you can't be a
victim in the street and a hero
in bed.
Uh,
let's see, uh,
oh, uh,
for, regarding
the weirdo American community,
this woman, Rachel Barton Russell,
uh, petitioned a court in Springfield,
Oregon in February for a ruling on the
meaning of the state's law against
corpse abuse.
Her deceased husband, Donald Eugene
Russell, had declared in his will
that he wanted his skin
used to make book covers
for a collection of his poetry.
But the state mortuary and
cemetery board claims that carrying out
the request would subject a few
funeral home to liability for
corpse abuse.
Dug up my baby last night.
See, uh,
um,
in, oh, there's some nice,
nice news. In February, the Royal Bank of
Scotland announced that it would begin to issue
extra check cashing ID cards
to its transvestite customers
who request them so that they might have separate
cards depicting themselves as a sex worker.
They also announced that they would be
dressed as male and female in order to
avoid embarrassment or difficulties.
And, uh, in October in Iran, where celebratory
gunfire is traditional at weddings,
a guest named Rasool lost control of his
automatic weapon at a wedding in
Lorystan Province, accidentally killing
six people and wounding fourteen.
Oh, that is, ahem, an automatic weapon
at the wedding. You know, those things are hard to hold
onto once you start firing. It's hard to, to really aim
them if you've ever done that.
And here, a horrible death.
The international food company Nestle, UK, was fined
about $20,000 in January for injuries suffered by its
employee, Alex Smith, 36, at a plant in York, England,
while cleaning excess chocolate off the sides of a giant
mixing bowl. He slipped and fell in, triggering the mixing
paddles, which whipped him for more than a minute before
they were shut off.
It sounds kind of like the sorts of things that happened to, uh,
Bob's enemies when he was a little kid.
And, uh, professional so- sports news, professional soccer team
manager Dan O'Riordan, uh, defending his decision to levy
fines against players for flatulence in the locker room
said, it can get fairly oppressive when you've got 20 players
in a tiny dressing room all suffering the effects of a Sunday
night curry.
Yes, those effects could sound and smell about like this show,
dear friends. That's from News of the Weird, which you can
subscribe to from Chuck Shepherd. Got that pencil ready?
News of the Weird, P.O. Box 8306.
St. Peter's, Pennsylvania.
Pittsburgh, Florida.
33738.
And, uh, oh, just thinking about that weird stuff makes me reach
for, uh, will it remain- it calls to mind a song, this wonderful
song here, coming up by none other than Lonesome Cowboy Dave,
and I guess the Brain Rot Band. Thank you.
Only eight dollars till Tuesday, I promise to pay back
me. Only eight dollars till 242, I won't leave you hanging
my brain.
All on me, all on me, eight dollars, you pinch.
You got more money than you need.
You got eight hundred bucks for getting hit by a truck.
So don't tell me that you're gonna bleed.
Only eight dollars till Thursday, I promise to pay back
me.
and youarnos mf yara, hehehehe,
and i'm
ahead.
SUB Marie Shetz 003.
Huh? What? Oh, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, Lonesome Cowboy Dave there with a lonely $19 and a beer and a what?
A golfer's head.
A golfer's head?
No, hockey players' heads.
What are these guys talking about?
No, basketball.
Wait a minute, golfer doesn't sound too bad.
Yeah, golfer.
Okay, golfer head.
I hate golf. How about you? Do you hate golf?
I really hate golf.
Do you hate golf?
Okay, wait a minute. Let's see where we are.
J.R. Bob Dobbs, Church of the Subgenius, Dallas, Texas, Reverend Ivan Stang, and a golfer head.
What's the golfer head doing, though?
Okay, it's scarred.
It's scarred?
We'll give you that. I mean, we'll give you that.
How about coagulated scab of the head of the golfer?
Okay, if the head is coagulating and scabbed, then we know it's decapitated.
We know it's decapitated.
It's not the torso. We're going to forget the torso.
No, the torso's gone.
Yeah.
The torso's straight out.
We were far behind.
Okay.
We were on that.
Okay, now let's review. We've got a golfer head.
We've got a golfer.
It's been decapitated.
Decapitated. What are we doing to it?
And it's got to be...
We don't get to win a baseball bat?
It's got to be...
Are we doing a field goal?
Should we just, like, set it on the floor and leave it there?
No.
Make it real stiff?
It's way too stiff.
Dear friends, well, we'll leave Sterno, Janer, and Reverend Andrew there from Ogre Network.
Yeah, the doctor's for Bob.
Sorry, getting back together.
Getting back together again.
It's like the Beatles getting back together again and then killing each other.
Well, it's time for...
Well, it's kook time now.
Yes, time for...
Time for...
Where's my background?
There.
There we go.
Yes, it's smooth.
Smooth and groovy, dear friends.
Yes, let's...
Now for our weekly reading from Donna Cossie's book, Kooks.
Tonight we'll be covering just a short section on a kook named Norma Cox,
who wrote a book called The Holy Land Above and Below,
which is profiled in this section of Kooks.
Oh, she also wrote UFOs and the Dragon Power.
And it's a real hodgepodge of all the classic crackpot conspiracy theories,
minus Bob.
So, of course, it's...
But just to give you a sample of what this wondrous Norma Cox has discovered
regarding contact with extraterrestrials by George Washington.
And we quote here from Norma Cox.
Enormously ambitious, the father of our country was aggressive and without scruples.
Scruples.
Giving not a damn for education and the finer side of life,
George Washington was a money-grabbing, glory-grubbing charlatan
with a bent for deceit and the devious.
With the ability to inspire trust and zeal,
he was the perfect tool for masonry.
Therefore, he was made privy to the deepest-held secrets of that diabolical organization
and allowed to fulfill his insatiable need for power, wealth,
and power.
And attention.
What a job lying historians have done on this faker over the last 200 years.
And George was an occultist who got a tremendous bang out of fooling around with the supernatural.
Of the highest masonic degree,
the father of our country, so-called,
was in full masonic regalia when he deposited secret objects at the cornerstone laying of the White House.
With all due respect,
I'm going to give you a little bit of a sneak peek at the
story of George Washington.
And I'll be right back.
And visions mapped a course for the newly formed nation.
Thirteen states with thirteen masonic governors to follow.
Since that time, every man succeeding to the presidency of the United States,
whether a mason,
or a favored member of some other demonic order,
has held firmly to the treasonous outline plotted by the sorcerer we have been taught to honor and admire.
Years later,
the ignorant American citizens were given the Statue of Liberty,
which is not only a symbol of the pagan goddess Diana,
but also a radio antenna.
As Norma goes on here,
with great spikes,
or antenna,
crowning her head,
and sitting upon a star-shaped base in the midst of flowing water,
water essential for this purpose,
this huge copper statue,
copper,
a number one conductor of electricity,
serves a dual purpose.
One, under the cover of a symbol of liberty,
it mesmerizes the citizens into adoring a goddess they know nothing about.
Two, in this cover concealing a still more important function,
the statue serves as a tower,
one reaching into heaven.
And transmitting and receiving messages to and from the moon.
Yes, friends, from Donna Cossey's book,
Kooks, available from Feral House Press,
Feral House, F-E-R-A-L,
P.O. Box 3466, Portland, Oregon 97208.
And, uh, what else have we coming up here?
Oh, well, I could give her the answer.
That's what I ought to do.
I'll read the talk, but see,
some of these so-called Christians are a little bit mixed up.
You know, they got it all, they got things all turned around.
And, uh, but, but we do have the answer.
Yes, the answer.
A little paperback book,
found in Christian bookstores,
from which we now read.
One day in the near future,
God will have to get the attention of the world,
for time is running out.
By the year 2050, there could be between 50 to 75 billion people,
or even more, all jammed together
like a global pack of sardines upon the face of the earth.
And amidst this global panic and confusion
will be the perfect time for Satan to send forth his son.
That wicked being whom the Bible calls the Beast,
Revelation 13, the Antichrist.
Forget the fantasies of the Omen trilogy of movies
and the false theology of Hal Lindsey,
the late great planet Earth.
The Antichrist will not come as a political leader
or a world dictator.
He will initially come into the world seen as Christ.
He will claim that this is the second coming of Christ,
but not Jesus Christ.
He comes as the Christ of the occult world.
He will come as the totally unalienable,
perfected man,
as the evolutionary, pipe-smoking super-human.
And he comes in the capacity of a world teacher,
religious reformer, and as a guide for humanity.
Later on, he will take over the ten-nation Western conspiracy,
or I'm sorry, confederacy.
And then will come the second holocaust, dear friends,
and the first rapture, and the second rapture,
and the Satanist initiates will completely take over.
Uh, this initiation will...
This initiation will also take place very, very quickly.
Schools, college campuses, churches, synagogues, sports stadiums,
and military bases could all be instantly converted
to Luciferic initiation centers overnight.
The antichrist will teach that time is of the greatest importance.
The evil ones must be removed as quickly as possible.
And friends, we're trying to help that happen at grand prix speed,
as it says here in Harry Walther's great book,
The Two Raptures.
Or the answer, I guess, is actually what it is.
And you know, that's how that brings to mind this other one.
Another little piece here by Reverend Sheldon DeWare.
Jesus loves me, this I know,
cause my preacher tells me so.
If I argue, he'll use his tongue
till I scream out,
Yes, I'm wrong!
Oh, God, I'm a sinner!
I repent! Just make him stop!
Oh!
...having a hard time finding customers at this time of night.
I think you better bring your own customers with you.
All right.
The inflatable...
Bring the inflatable ones we used last time, not the Moonies.
And the 700-foot tall Jesus.
Do you have to take that thing apart to get it on the train or not?
He had real good sand, if you know what I mean.
Remember that sand that he put...
Last time they told me I could check the Jesus, but, um...
But that... that...
I had to bring the Architeasma on board with me.
On the airplane?
Yep.
Wow.
Well, it's okay if you bring all that stuff,
because they do let you talk about Jesus on this radio station.
They don't have any kind of rules against it like the...
Right, that's like taking one of those PSA clearance impressions...
You're not just nailing him right up?
Yeah.
He gets across just nailing him just...
Actually, send us a whole box of those miniature Jesus, too.
Those are delicious.
Ha, ha, ha.
Just...
Wonderful job of calling, and praise Bob, and hi out there to all the slackest minions listening to this station who...
The old Delta.
...do and know that even in these hard economic times, so the new Saturations subgenius is still the best of all for you.
Send that dollar, send that five dollar bill, send that ten dollar bill, send that twenty dollar bill, send that hundred, that unmarked crisp twing hundred two.
And the wallet came.
Hello, you're on the air.
Clown.
Oh, the...
All the dirty back...
687-3515.
...is the phone number.
Hang on a second.
We're just sort of sitting around the fire tonight.
Okay.
There it's also on the shortwave.
The nuclear fire, you can hear it buzzing over in the corner there.
I heard two other things which aren't important to anybody.
One is called the urban tribes of Buenos Aires.
Oh, shut up, you fat pig.
You don't know my true weight, buddy.
That wasn't very nice.
No, it wasn't very nice, but it was very, very tangy, like salsa.
I did notice that part of it.
I'm very concerned about what's going on.
I'm very concerned about what you were talking about.
I'm terribly worried.
Do you know what I'm talking about then?
Unfortunately, yes.
There have been mass suicides in Buenos Aires.
Oh, my God.
I don't want to talk about it.
There have been.
Really?
Over the past several...
That's a true one, though.
Really?
Oh, well, we'll make light of it then.
And also...
I don't care.
...the urban tribes.
Well, there's two things...
I'm losing all my pity.
There's two things going on called the urban tribes down in South America, and there's
also been this big spate of suicides going on around the globe.
People just like, you know...
Often, so.
...in England, they run off the cliff.
Has that been happening there?
Yeah.
I just heard about this thing here, and then the urban tribes, they don't believe
in anything.
They just dress different to be against a different tribe, and it's purely style.
And they ask them what they believe in, and they say they don't believe in anything but
style.
Hello?
You're on the air.
Isn't it like the end times, or is it more like the beginning times?
Or is it just a bunch of more of the same damn in-between times we've been seeing all
the time?
You know, it's just proof that MKUltra was never closed.
Oh, yeah.
Uh-oh.
Dave?
MKUltra?
Never closed.
MKUltra was never closed.
That was in Time Magazine, but that guy, how do you say that?
He must be a spy.
I'm paranoid now.
Hello?
You're on the air.
I'm paranoid now.
No, MKUltra was never closed.
Of course not.
Who do you think runs the secret police?
The secret, secret, secret police.
And we're talking about guys who don't even get badges.
Some of them don't even get to carry winky badges.
I knew it.
Chepkeese.
Oh, my God, Chaz.
Let's not talk in those...
Those Egyptian vagaries will scare the children again.
And you eat Chepkeese.
Every time you...
Hello, anyone there?
Call her.
Eye in the pyramid and the eyeball hanging out of the pyramid.
Chaz, what is it?
Novus Ordo Seclorum.
New World Order.
No sacred order.
New sacred order.
Yes.
Secular, secular.
No, it's sacred.
Secular.
It means sacred.
Secularum.
Sacred.
Organum Mundum means...
I know it means sacred.
I had a doctor.
I had a doctor tell me it means sacred.
And plus, you were a damn choir boy, too.
You used to know Latin.
Hello?
Yeah.
Don't you think it's weird that Chaz, this foul-mouthed sick person, was actually
a choir boy?
Yeah.
Okay, well, I'm glad you keep agreeing like a little lamprey, but say something right
now or we'll kill you.
Okay, I'll pick the topping.
Yeah, let him talk.
Okay.
Some people are shy.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Shy indeed.
Hello?
This person's got a mono-syllabic vocabulary.
It's one of the Egyptian vagaries.
Why do you think if they could live to be 9,000 years old and eat 3,000% of their brain,
wouldn't they bet every horse in the X-Acta perfectly in the trifecta?
Have you seen how Jackie O, the lizard agent has run out of her use?
That is true, Jackie O, as a lizard agent, has really run out of Agent Orange.
They said that she was getting commands through her pillbox.
Huh?
I ran out of it once, and I ran back into it.
He ran it.
Now, this is a common thing, isn't it, Chaz?
Unfortunately, yes.
A lot of people run out of it, and they can't find anymore,
but then they run right into it as soon as it's going on again.
I'd ask you to help me, but...
Well, we can only help ourselves, and like a true...
Exactly right.
As a true sub...
That's why I didn't ask.
As a sub-moron.
I...
Don't say da-da to me.
I know what da-da means.
I'm not an abstruse rube.
I'm a glistening, gleaming dolt.
I noticed that, but I tried not to.
Well, try not to ever notice it again,
because someday when the sun comes up for the very last time,
we're all going to be ringing the lines of the cliffs,
screaming to that miscreant being as it zaps us down
and turns us into lard.
Or some other thing.
I want my mommy.
You can have your mommy.
I don't really want her like that.
That's the way I want her.
Uh-oh.
Mom.
You know, I want her gleaming white radish hump.
Oh, my God.
I do.
But I don't know if she wants mine.
We'll try to hide it.
I know they've given you the A treatment.
No, no, no, no, no.
You can tell, like, when my bells start ringing
or I make comments about the quantity of light in my brain,
like a thousand little pinholes,
that's when I'm being mind-controlled.
Now, when I'm not being mind-controlled,
it sounds like this.
What's happening?
Let's have another call right now.
Hello?
Hello, you're off the air.
Hello, you're on the air.
Have the nylons when grin wraps.
Yeah, hello, you're on the air, too.
Well, how come we're all on the air at the same time?
Well, because we have so much air, you wouldn't believe it.
Look at this.
A giant pile of busted microphones,
16 feet tall, along with a few broken tape recorders.
Are you a heavy breather?
I can hear you doing that.
Or are you merely sedated by the swatting numbers?
No, I'm sorry.
That isn't you.
I can see you now.
Go ahead.
Yeah, the picture's really fuzzy here.
We can't see you very good.
It's awfully nice of you to have us on our show.
Yeah, it's great being a radio star, huh?
Yeah.
How do you do it?
How do you keep up to life like that?
Not easy.
You eat a lot of chili.
A lot of chili.
A lot of hot weed.
I'm heating up some chili.
Yeah.
And I was listening to you guys, and I just broke my leg.
Yeah, you should have tried to send in money first and then listen to us,
because you might, in fact, you might want to do that now,
because you've got one leg left, if you know what I mean.
I already sent the money in.
Shut up.
Okay, then we'll leave that other leg alone.
I haven't even broken a leg yet.
Yeah?
How about an arm?
Oh.
How about another nostril?
That'll probably really help you get some slack.
Hey, now, that's expensive, though.
Now we're talking about things that are a little bit expensive
that you might have to fly all the way to Dobstown.
Yeah, microwave Dobstown.
I have a question for one of the doctors or one of the operating physicians.
Or did you want to share some chili with us?
Chili.
Yeah.
If you listen very carefully.
I hear the tiny little sounds of the subgenius healing session.
Gary, Gary, who are those people back there?
Well, I see Bob Nelson.
Who's that guy whispering?
Delivering a baby.
No, that man and woman.
They're whispering.
What are they doing?
I don't know.
I'm trying to breastfeed this woman.
Oh, I see.
It's so cold here.
I don't even see how they can spend that much time out here without lighting their pipes up.
Well.
I'm going to put another layer of whiskey.
We're out here at the airport.
And occasionally we do these live shows because, well, when people are eating chili and they're breaking legs left and right.
I'm sorry about that leg.
I didn't.
You probably don't need it, right?
And, okay.
The therapy room, as you can see, is being occupied.
We'll turn this up a little bit.
Adjust the color there.
Some of Dobst's treatments have been incredibly successful.
And if you are watching us, you can find us there.
Hello.
Hey, tell Bob to eat chili or use Vaseline.
Don't bother with those.
Just the wetsuits, okay, ma'am?
We ask that our other listeners bow their heads and thank J.R. and Bob Dobst for providing this slight respite to Conspiracy Radio.
I've never met Bob either, but I've been touched by Bob.
A lot of people involved are not going to be involved much longer.
The coming attractions, I think they're called.
Isn't that when the giant...
The giant hand of Jehovah or the fist of the mighty something?
Right, the wheelbarrow of Wotan.
Oh, that's the wheelbarrow of Wotan that is powered by the two of the fists.
So you can imagine how much trouble that will be.
And a wheel of revenge in the front of the wheelbarrow, which continues on by itself for quite a while.
Even after the wheelbarrow, yea, verily has dumped its load upon those who are unfaithful and do not send.
Oh, minor, minor parts of souvenirs.
Right, a dollar, a part of a dollar, a large, large part of a dollar.
The subgenius foundation.
And a check, a one dollar check is the best way because we like to see stacks and stacks and stacks.
Have you ever seen two million one dollar checks?
It's amazing.
Filling the rooms in Dallas.
Stuffed with cash.
Once a week I fly here to do this show just to share with you these pictures of...
Here, here, look.
Here's a room full of one dollar checks ready for the rubber stamp.
Isn't this amazing?
So we don't even cash the checks.
We don't even use the money.
We just need it to interpret your psychic stench.
Powerful Izzy is J.R. Bob Dobbs, our prophet, cannot get your psychic stench without the love offering.
So we just ask that you send in a small part of your fortune.
Whoever you may be or whatever kind of small job you might have, just slip out one of those little tiny green things and send it to the church so we can reach you and be in contact with you.
I know, I'm back again.
I'd rather have the rubber than the money.
Can we make a deal here?
Well, you can have both the rubber.
And the money.
Maybe.
The rubber's used, though.
Don't put it in the way.
No, man, I'm not going for no used rubber.
No, no, no, not that type of rubber.
No, I'm talking about the sheets.
I'm talking about rubber bands around newspapers.
Right, right, I'm talking about sheets.
I don't want that.
The sheets are about 34 feet by 18 feet.
We use them to cover the airplanes.
That's what I mean.
One size fits all our house, I know.
Yeah, yeah, the whole thing fits over the house.
Well, have you got your pipe through the mail?
Or are you going to write in and get your pipe?
I'm still waiting for the cast.
The cast?
Well, the cast is all...
Unfortunately, they'll be outside your house
to sing a song about 8 o'clock this morning.
Actually, we're expecting Vic Morrow, too.
Yeah, he's going to be starring in all the body parts.
I just want to know, you guys are very informative tonight,
but I want to know, what planet are we on?
Oh, and we have been on the KPFA planet there
with Puzzling Evidence
and the great Gary Gabrog friend.
That was an old...
That's an old, old recording, my friends.
Speaking of old recordings,
listen to what happens when I turn the air conditioner on.
See?
Quiet, sweet, wonderful all of a sudden.
Well, it was.
Well, let's shift gears here.
Friends, we certainly have had a lot of our friendly other shows,
the KPFA Subgenius Show and the ESO Radio and Brain Rot,
but we're not going to be doing that combo there
with Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
What the heck?
We'll just bring some more in.
We'll go to...
We'll go to Reverend Susie the Floozy.
That's it, yeah.
With her WREK Atlanta show.
And she has some sad news
and kind of a...
What?
Hey, what's...
Eh?
Spooky.
Very spooky noises, my friends.
Okay, Reverend Susie the Floozy.
Oh, that's a bit of a sad time
because yesterday,
well, I found out that Otis
the drunk died.
Oh, poor old Hal Smith, 77.
The man who staggered and stumbled and slurred
through the surreal streets of Mayberry
and taught his kids that passed out drunks
were not only funny, they were a nifty plot device.
The article didn't say if he'd ended his life
as a drunken sot in a Hicktown drunk tank,
like the way Aunt B slipped into serious psychosis
in Siler City, North Carolina,
faking pies and calling for an Opie
who never came home for dinner.
But despite this loss, the endless cycle of death
and rebirth grinds inexorably on.
So we're going to make Otis the drunk
our short-duration personal savior
for this episode of The Fun House.
Here we're setting him up a cot in the corner.
Hey, sleep it off.
And hey, when you wake up, we'll party with you.
Uh, fuck!
Stop abusing that substance, abusing my baby.
Because you're kicking him in the face.
Such a damn disgrace.
The way you treat him when you squeak this.
Jesus.
Fuck you.
Okay, Gabby, look at me!
Okay, Gabby, go!
I have a green hug.
What?
Hey, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh,
Okay, uh, that was, of course, one.
Lonesome cowboy Dave again.
And now, back to Reverend Susie the Floozy.
Whoo!
Yeah, this is a great time.
It's a time of loss, a time of new beginnings for the Reverend Flooze here.
And not necessarily because spring is near,
although the mystery tree out in front of the Floozeum
has burst into particularly outstanding fluorescence,
huge, fleshy blossoms of petals
that consistently
see of human skin.
Oh, nobody knows the genus of this strange plant,
but I take it sudden erupting is an omniscient,
and the end times are cruising up on us at a breakneck pace.
Oh, but it won't be my neck that's breaking,
because I'll be munching Fritos and dip in the hospitality suite
to the excess escape vessels
while watching global incineration up close and personal
on the wall-size high-definition video screen.
Ha!
And believe me,
I've been given a lot of thought about whose ends in particular
I want to bear gleeful witness to.
But the good thing is through the patented subgenius concept of time control
and the miracle of robot-controlled heat-resistant Steadicams,
there's no time limit on retribution.
Now, yes, your foes will feel the fires of this particular hell
for as long as you like,
because every time you view and review their videotaped records,
their own blazing pitch-anima raw nerve torments
will be fed again and again into their agony-dew account.
Oh, yes, they will owe you a debt of pain that they cannot waltz on.
Sure, they say revenge is a dish best served cold,
but I like it hot and spicy.
Muy caliente!
Ay, ay, ay, ay, ay!
There's something he said once before they took him away
to the Massachusetts State Home for the Beardless.
He said,
I'm not bewildered.
Life is like a sewer.
What you get out of it depends on what you put into it.
Manamana, manamana,
Yes, dear friends, it's right.
And imagine Nenslow's consternation
upon hearing what I'm saying.
About to read and finding that such a situation
which he wrote, though serious,
has nothing whatsoever to do with the gross national world church
of the subgenius's decision to repudiate Bob
in all his smirking forms.
No, indeed, oh, nothing at all.
Nothing at all to do with that.
It's just another damn coincidence, I tell ya.
And if you're the kind of naive simpleton
who'll take a simple coincidence,
a matter of meaningless happenstance,
and attribute all kinds of meaning and influence to it,
well, I'm just sorry for you.
That's all.
Not meaning any disrespect or anything.
I just think, hell, this is the 20th century,
the atom age, the last days,
predicted in some book somewhere.
And I figure by this time,
we should have crept far enough
from the shadow of the cave mouth
to see through such transparent ploys.
We should, even the mere human among us,
be able to keep our mental knuckles
off the figurative ground long enough
to straighten our psychological spine a little
and stand allegorically correct.
I figure.
Eh, maybe not.
Maybe I'm really as much of a nitwit
as everybody seems to think I am.
Maybe I oughta just quit,
crawl into my bunker,
and drink canned water till 1998,
and let the squealin' hordes fight it out alone.
But by something or other,
hell, no dobs,
I don't even have anything to...
Without Bob, you can't curse.
By dang, I just can't do it.
I guess I'm just a meddler,
a sucker, a dreamer,
a hopeless romantic swept away
by my own self-generated waves
of juvenile emotion.
But bling-ding-it,
I still have faith in you!
Yes, I still believe in you,
and I still believe in the church,
and in my own fellow and gal sub-geni.
And I feel that if anybody can save
this tired old world from a disgraceful,
degenerate end,
and nobody can,
it's us.
I mean, you and me, pal.
Or palette.
You and me, oh, we're different.
We're not like the rest of them.
We think alike.
And I truly believe that if you and I can work together,
if we can work together with the pitifully small handful
of true sub-geni,
whether they admit they're sub-geni or not,
whether they hate the church and the terminology,
or even don't know if it exists or not,
but the true flock,
if we can get together,
we can really make a change for the good.
I know it seems hopeless.
I know sometimes you seem so alone.
You look out into the bleak, gray, grimy world
through a cracked and filthy window pane,
and it all seems so pointless.
And you say to yourself,
there's squillions of them,
and only one of me.
What the heck can I do?
Just remember,
it's not only one of you.
It's you and me.
It's you and me in a secret underground of illusion,
illuminated ones who for aeons
have gently guided this sad old world upward
in the face of incredible odds,
sometimes without even knowing it.
A strange idea, isn't it?
That someone seemingly insignificant and powerless
on the ragged edge of society
could actually be the secret master or mistress of the world.
But it's true.
Look at them all,
the squabbling organic robotoids
acting out their ritual programs over and over again.
They live to serve you.
It's true.
Everything they build or make,
all the extravagant waste they create,
all the seemingly pointless,
futile, murderous, hateful acts
do have one ultimate goal.
To make possible for you
all those,
those all too short moments,
of pure slack you get
in the course of the day's endless rounds of drudgery.
I've always said that the folks I pity most
are the ones who suffer from the delusion
that they're not Jesus Christ.
What I mean is that everyone who suffers,
labors, and dies
does so for you.
To make your life better.
Your laboring and suffering
and death are not pointless either,
but go to make another person's slack possible.
My friend, no moment of pain, sorrow, or suffering
goes to waste.
All is transformed from the base metal of pain
to the pure gold of slack
through the action of the alchemical sublimate of...
Well, not Bob in this case,
because this rant was written by the great Northwest church of the South.
I'm not a subgenius with no Bob.
But something, I don't know.
I lost my train of thought now.
Anyway, it wasn't my train of thought to begin with.
It was Nenslow's.
That's all that stuff was written by Nenslow.
I was just reading from it.
And, uh, but you, but, but, you know what,
you know what we're saying?
You know what we're saying?
You know what Doctorsters for Bob were saying in the background music?
What D.K. Jones is saying in the background music right now.
And, uh, but, but what we don't know
is what we're gonna play next.
Oh, I know what we need.
We're getting down near the end of the show,
so I'm gonna tell you the most important thing
there is to tell you on this show,
which is the address to write for free information.
Got that pencil ready?
That's Bob!
It is Bob!
It's only Bob!
It's no one but Bob!
And you just write to Bob at
Post Office Box 140306
Dallas, Texas 75214
I'm gonna give that number again.
That's Bob at Post Office Box
Dallas, Texas 75214
And, uh, here to take us out
is, uh, this, uh, oddball little band
from up north called
The Merkins.
Hey girls, I've got some news for you
Please don't doubt because it's all true
There's a little spot that can send you up and down
Everybody's got one
So rub off your little crown
You can use your finger or a big vibrator
You'll find your little spot just south of your equator
Do it alone or with your favorite sweetie
Hit the park or plums and just have a sweet time
Two spots are fun
We all have one
Don't hesitate to press the secret button that's within you
My name is Contessa and I've got a question
Litter with a G-spot, will you give me a suggestion?
I steer up with my job at the Delicatessen
I've been sitting all day just indulging my obsession
But letter with a G-spot, my G-spot is nowhere to be found
Now where exactly did you say it was hanging around?
Now listen, foolish girl, I told you once before
That searching for your G-spot shouldn't be a chore
Consider it a way to open up your mind
Or Contessa, girl, you're gonna get left behind
G-spots are fun
We all have one
Two spots are fun
Don't hesitate to press the secret button that's within you
We all have one
Two spots are fun
Oh, and what's this
My friends have all left me
And I'm feeling so forlorn
My instruments of passion
Have turned on me with scorn
I'm auctioning off my dildos
On the 13th of November
And I'm off to build a real life
That I'm proud to remember
So auction off your dildos
And have a glass of wine
Forget the golden juice bars
You're living in your prime
So listen closely ladies
To your body and your mind
You're packed to your own ecstasy
Don't need to be defined
G-Spots are fun
We all have one
Don't hesitate to press the secret button
That's within you
G-Spots are fun
Just being you
My gift to the 5000
And that's what's added to this
G eight owner
And another little shortcut
P Government We человек
Red and red
JENN driver Manufactor
I think it's important for those with the energy to do it
to have something to do with it.
You know what I mean?
Send off for that strange stuff.
And, well, I don't know what comes next,
but we'll both find out now, won't we?
Now, goodbye, fishers.
Are you on?
I know you're part of the Illuminati.
You're head V.
I'm what now?
The head of the Illuminati, Dave.
Oh, man, I'm not even the head V-keeper.
Because if you weren't, they wouldn't let you speak.
Oh, you think they got the power to make your vocal cords stop?
I think they do.
Well, then I'm going to make your stop,
because I'm the head of the Illuminati.
Well, you've already traced the call.
I'm waiting.
Yes, we have ways of knowing who you are.
And with my all-seeing, all-knowing eyes,
I'm just going to have to set up a little barricade.
A little mental barricade?
Do you think you can set this little mental barricade
against this enormous intellect
and this huge, big, fat brain?
And you make me laugh,
you common-air mortal type of person.
I can see you out for...
You live in Richmond Heights.
You live at 45 Mr. Vons.
What a brilliant opposition right there.
He gave me his address.
Now, what does your car look like, sir?
I'm talking about the other times.
I'm not the same person whom you were speaking with.
Oh, okay, but you...
I don't live in Concord.
That was Concord boy.
He's trying to kill me.
Well, see, you're all victims of your own paranoid fantasy.
That's what we listened to for three years ago,
a long time ago.
Remember, Chaz?
Was a bunch of people calling each other up
and saying they were killing each other.
And not one of them ever died,
because they kept on calling this damn program
until we had to quit it.
Well, no, I guess it's not true, but it sure is.
I beg to...
Okay, yeah, one of them Siberian singers,
the Tupa Hoopas.
Well, come on, now, let's finish your statement.
All right, then I'll have to finish your statement.