it's awful it's all big green eyes and there's those feelings like it's like a cat baby snap
out of it listen oh go away please go away what you see oh no please it's too awful please
the subgenius
jumping catfish
comics versus the god of bovvers
bovvers that's b-o-v-v with two v's e-r-e-r-s e-r-e-r-s e-r-e-r-s e-r-e-r-s e-r-e-r-s e-r-e-r-s
e-r-e-r-s e-r-e-r-s e-r-e-r-s comics versus the god barbers religious groups have been forced to
stop using catchphrases
you
from popular british comedians to try to persuade youngsters into church
posters featuring such lines as yeah but no but yeah yeah but no but yeah yeah but no but yeah
but no and am i buffered
i'm really glad i came that whole jesus thing it's really interesting isn't it it's not interesting
it's scary it's nailing holes through your hands it's because we're all vile sinners
god made
you
you really think that's true it's in the bible leslie you have to believe it and you hate it
i don't have to believe it and i think it's beautiful you gotta believe the bible leslie
why because if you don't believe in the bible god will damn in hell when you die
wow maybe where'd you hear that that's right huh jess god damn to hell if you don't believe in the
bible i think so well i don't think so i seriously don't believe in the bible i don't believe in the
bible i don't think so you سمinki
yeah that's right okay i speak his percent slot
i don't believe in the bible i don't believe in the bible i don't believe in Podillip
i didn't know i looked like he was a dude
if you want to watch anymore i'll let you in my secret AST foreign songs
this is our point
bish
you and me
y 마음
i'm speaking rape
atmospheric
can i also say
fuck
Amy
check our page for både
bilo
i'm bampa
Rorschach's Journal, October 12th, 1985.
Dog carcass in alley this morning.
Tire tread on burst stomach.
This city is afraid of me.
I have seen its true face.
Streets are extended gutters and the gutters are full of blood.
And when the drains finally scab over all the vermin will drown.
The accumulated filth of all their sex and murder will foam up about their waste.
And all the whores and politicians will look up and shout, save us.
And I'll look down and whisper, no.
Oh no, Adrian.
Looks like the Reds are polluting the city lake.
What do we do?
We call the Watchmen.
Strong together, united forever.
They're the best of friends.
But when trouble's about, you'd best watch out for the Watchmen.
Now here's the leader and he loves to party down.
Rorschach's friends to the animals.
Yeah, when he's not clowning around.
I'm not even...
Eat up some thugs.
Say no to drugs.
In bed by ten.
But if trouble's about, you'd best watch out for the Watchmen.
Spectre's a sensation.
You should really never miss him.
The comedian's your biggest fan now.
If I could only get that kiss.
Ozy and Puberty's a couple of crime-saving superstars.
John can give you cancer and they'll turn into a car.
Strong together, united forever.
Come on.
Meet your friends.
Have no fear.
Time's up, time's here.
For the Watchmen.
Watch out.
Stood in firelight.
Sweltering bloodstain on chest like map of violent new continent.
Felt cleansed.
Felt dark planet turn under my feet and knew what cats know that...
Makes them scream like babies in the night.
The light of the sky through smoke heavy with human fat.
And God was not there.
The cold suffocating dark goes on forever and we are alone.
This rudderless world is not shaped by vague metaphysical forces.
It's a dream.
It is not God who kills the children.
Not fate that butchers them or destiny that feeds them to the dogs.
It's us.
Only us.
Now, Soupman.
Tireless fighter for soup and justice.
Able to leap the weak and the oppressed at a single bound.
Soupman.
Up in the sky.
Look!
It's Soupman!
Good tickets dark.
Following instructions, Soupman sways and groans and yawns suddenly.
And remember, Soupman had just escaped from San Miguel prison.
Tune in next time.
Can the man of Soup hangs over the town of Soupville?
Be sure to tune in the next thrilling installment of the amazing transcription feature, Soupman.
The guy in a white turban and some pants that looked like oversized diapers put his hand on a big curve knee.
He was wearing tennis shoes.
He looked happy, like a hobo in a Vaseline sandwich.
He had one arm around her shoulders.
Excuse us, please.
I'll have to get rid of Bob and get some things done.
Get rid of Bob?
Yeah.
All right.
You know, we can't get rid of Bob because he's the greatest superhero of them all.
We just heard Soupman by Lee Murr.
And before that, that was Alan Moore reading from his book, Soupman.
And before that, a cartoon, the Saturday Morning Watchmen cartoon theme by Happy Harry.
And you can see that cartoon on like the internet, not YouTube, but somewhere out there.
Just do a search for Saturday Morning Watchmen or Happy Harry.
Not to be confused with Happy Harry Cox of the Fireside Theater's album or with Happy Harry Robbins of Ask Dr. Howell.
Yeah.
And the religion clip we heard of the kids discussing religion was from a really good movie called Bridge to Terabithia that kind of went under the bridge to Terabithia.
And speaking of good movies, they didn't screw up Watchmen in my opinion.
This is – I'm recording this on the weekend that the Watchmen –
Watchmen was released.
Of course, I ran to see it.
Of course, I'm a Watchmen geek.
I've read the book a hundred times.
And as somebody who knows how hard it is to make a movie or adapt a book, I thought they did a great job.
And nobody paid me to say that.
I just wanted to mention it now.
Dave is calling.
Oh, Dave is calling.
Princess Wee says Dave has called in.
I must weigh in on the book.
Watchmen.
He wants to weigh – he's way in there now.
Yes, Dave, you're way in.
I'm in because I know of the movie, not because I was actually a part of it.
Well, you were a caped, masked crime fighter in your younger days, weren't you?
I was also – I was hospitalized for that and put in an institution for four and a half years.
You weren't –
It was the codpiece, dang it.
It stuck out real far of that blue and red uniform.
You were Mothman?
No, I was just –
Because he ended up – I assume that maybe you were Mothman because he was in a – finally ended up being put away.
Yeah, and he had a big codpiece on his blue and red uniform.
But I was a smiling, happy Uncle Dave that got me into some problems with minors.
Oh, you were a smiling, happy Dave.
Yeah.
The cartoon clown-masked crime fighter and criminal.
No, it was kind of a Superman-ish looking costume with a big codpiece.
That's the third time I'm going to say that.
Codpiece Dave.
And it –
The big blue codpiece is all anybody can talk about.
Anybody who saw it was reminded of fish and death, just like when they look at the face of Bob.
Oh, cod and the piece of death.
Well, fish is a –
And Bob is kind of skull-ish.
He's got that grin like a skull.
And you've even enhanced that with some of your amazing Electrolab stuff you have.
By the way, Dave, we got an interesting letter in the mail.
You're live.
You know, I'm going to share it with you because I think you'll find it.
I just got it a couple of days ago.
I'm not going to give the email address of the person who sent it, but he said,
Hello.
My name is Bobby J. Dobbs, Jr.
Junior being J-R.
Bobby J. Dobbs, Jr.
I am tired of people thinking I am kidding or am impersonating your figurehead.
Could you please change his name to something else?
Thanks, Bobby Dobbs.
That was a real letter we got.
And –
Well, if anybody in this life would be surfing the luck plane and has all the slack he needs,
merely by the whispering of a few words, I would say that person is very ungrateful.
Well, we wrote him back.
Actually, our lawyer, New Monet, wrote him back and said,
Dear Sir, Madam,
This matter requires your immediate attention.
We are the owners of a U.S. trademark registration for the trademark J.R. Bob Dobbs.
You are currently using this trademark name, specifically Bobby Dobbs.
A comparison of this use in our trademark reveals you're in violation of several provisions of the Federal Trademark Act 15-0-U.S.C.
We request that you immediately discontinue the use of our trademark name and close variations thereof
and take steps to adopt a new and legal name for personal and professional use that no longer represents an infringement on our trademark.
We sincerely hope that you use this opportunity to avoid any litigation that would devolve from your failure to comply with our request.
Please forward your notice of rejection or acceptance.
Yours truly, Snarf, Felcher & Sanchez, attorneys at law representing the Church of God.
The subgenius.
Well, thank you very much.
Now, when you wrote him back, what did him back feel like?
What, him neck?
Well, he did respond.
He did respond, and he, with one sentence, he said,
Damn you and your slack.
I think there's hope for Bobby Dobbs.
Now, strangely enough, we got an order for an ordainment from a Robert Dobbs last year.
But I think we bragged about that one enough.
Well, there are a lot of people going around making false claims and a lot of avaricious individuals who think they're going to cash in in some pecuniary way.
And there is no pecuniation going on here or in your domicile, as far as I heard from we.
And I think what they ought to do is just take a flying leap in the direction of the nearest orbital planet, namely Saturn.
Because it's far.
There is peculiuration in our domicile, Dave.
I understand that the reason you're not here at the station is because there's some peculiuration in your domicile.
You're building an arc, I understand, because the flood of Noah has begun in Ashtabula.
I don't know if it's begun in Ashtabula.
But it's here.
It certainly appeared for a while, a knock on wood.
It was going to attack my domicile.
You can get wood?
Well, there's some floating line.
It's all plastic around here.
Just staying.
You live in a forest.
Oh, speaking of getting wood, we've got just the right background music going.
We really do.
And so, Dave, I want you, Princess Wee has a commercial break to read.
I'm going to pot you and me both.
Over there? Oh, I see.
I'll just sit down.
I won't say a damn word.
I'll just listen.
Yeah, just if you can.
And we'll proceed.
B-Rock Oboner Pills.
Getting your flagpole into her oval orifice is big business.
Give it the presidential treatment and erase the national debt in one firmly patriotic movement.
Speak softly and carry a big stick with B-Rock Oboner.
Once you go B-Rock, you'll never go back.
Never has stimulus been so stimulating.
Do it for your country, soldier.
Uncle Sam wants you all night long.
B-Rock Oboner Pills.
Get some and get some today.
Yes, you can.
Available where not available.
Only available where not available.
And thanks to Reverend Backett on Up for sponsoring the Hour of Slack.
In that peculiar, pecuniary way?
Yes.
Well, I would like to thank her, too, for reminding us that it's hard.
As George W. used to say, it's hard work being a soldier.
It's hard work being a president.
So let's be as hard as we can at all times.
And that's all I have to say on that.
You be a rock.
That's rather a wooden performance you just gave, Dave.
Yeah, well, one of your friends told me that rocks actually have personalities.
So don't blame me for not being able to get a B-Rock Oboner when the time comes,
because some of these people are actually metaphysical minerals and stuff.
That's what you got in your church right now.
A bunch of people that are like...
Rockheads.
Stoneheads.
Stoners.
Yeah.
Boneheads.
But I'm not talking about that, Ken.
I'm talking about actual minerals.
Richards.
Richardheads.
Ricky Rickheads.
Rockheads.
Yeah.
Masons.
Stonecutters.
Aha!
Stapens.
Staplers.
Illuminati.
Hand-fleshers.
World conspiracies.
Four-fingered denizens of the dinosaur age.
Flesh-flippity-jerobiters.
Actual catacombs.
Home-dwelling monkeys.
And friends, you can learn about this with the Subgenius History class, starting April
16th and lasting eight weeks through May 31st.
Yes, 2009.
Once again, the Maybe Logic Academy, founded by Robert Anton Wilson, will be featuring
classes in how to be and not be a subgenius.
That's actually true.
I know.
Maybelogic.net.
And they also have released an Illuminatus audiobook.
So if you can't read, you can still pick up on the great insanity and wisdom of Robert
Wilson and Robert Shay's Illuminatus.
It's a 2-Bob book.
That was a 2-Bob job, you might say.
Yeah.
2-Bob.
Wasn't it?
Well, there was a pirate named 2-Bob, and there was also a character in Moby Dick, was
in there.
2-Bob on board who had, his eyelids were scratched or something like that.
He used to tell tales of these weird interterrestrial porcine beings, kind of like half pig, half
greys.
He was Queequeg's bunkmate.
Although I had 2-Bob confused with Queequeg, but 2-Bob, wasn't he in R2-Bob, stepped out
like, that's an actual pirate, isn't it?
Yeah.
Captain 2-Bob.
But, yeah, Queequeg was like a Polynesian dude or something.
Well, yeah.
He was...
He was old and who was the Indian guy?
The Native American?
That was Queequeg.
He was...
No, he wasn't a Native American.
He was Polynesian or something, I believe.
He was covered with tattoos, looked like a modern-day youth, but it was, you know, in
the days of Joseph Conrad and giant sperm whales.
Did you know that there was a lot of hidden meaning in that whole argument from Moby
Dick?
And from the very beginning, people had assumed that there were secret messages...
Yeah.
...and not just like on the Illuminati level, but more, you know, the psychosexual rapture
type of messages.
And that's why people read it in serial fashion from Boston to San Francisco, which wasn't
quite a city yet.
You're still speaking of the great literary classic Moby Dick?
Mm-hmm.
Uh-huh.
Oh my God.
You get adults who have children's minds to feed, Dr. Stang and walks to the podium.
That's a Saitang, which you know, I had my name Americanized.
Now do you have an operating table with people, like, stacked up, like, cadavers all the way
up to the ceiling looking down at you
exhuming or post-cadavering
the remains of Bob. No, no, no. We don't keep
the physical shell. We just keep the
soul in a little
in these blue metal
cylinders. Now, do you
exhumate or in any way impale
the cylinders so as to check the cylinders
livers and kidney forms?
No, we check them for
leaks now and then
and I've got to admit there have been a couple
accidents but nobody who'd still
be alive probably.
So, they're not going to be
suing us. But yeah, your soul
every listener's soul is
in a carefully labeled
blue metal canister in my basement.
We joke a lot about how they're all rusty
and falling apart but that's actually
it's not that bad. We
dust them off every now and then.
You know how basements
in Cleveland's are. Dry,
safe, secure, perfectly
dehumidified
and so forth.
Hey, hey. Dave, it's a joke
listener friends because
both Dave and I have basements
and a river runs through it.
In my case, it's only a small
river but Dave has been fighting
Noah's flood
in his house.
Sting has just a, actually a
potable trinkle which he uses
rather than paying his damn water bills.
Just goes down there and scoops it up
and keeps the family happy and all those
little souls kept in all those little
jars down there. There's not
much to work with but there's not much to work
with. However, in my
case, I, yeah,
there's some actually drifting
going on
and I think I hear pirates in the basement
now.
I hear some funky
music in the background.
Me three. Maybe turn your radio up to see
if the pirates enjoy it.
Sounds like the man's on his way.
There's so many different kinds. Sounds like the man's on his way to your pad
for do you, dad.
The man's
doesn't even have to go to your pad.
He's done you the minute you're born.
When they
whack your butt to get you
screaming and yelling,
the minute you step out into the world,
that's where the man
starts in on you. That's where the conspiracy
begins. That's where they start
slapping your slack away.
Or trying to. They can't
if you're a subgenius.
The conspiracy is so
deep that they actually take the removed
parts,
of the little boy's
foreskins.
Yeah, the hill of foreskins. That's in the Bible.
I'm not allowed. I'm feeling...
Okay, I'm going to say it anyway.
They take the material from the foreskin
and do DNA smears
and that's why there's
new shelves in the basement.
I'm glad I got that out.
I've been keeping it in for a long time.
Actually, I don't think you have.
I think we've discussed this on the show
many times, but then
the tape was erased,
you might say.
I don't think... Did the part about the foreskins
actually be used for DNA smudges?
I think it did,
actually. I think Bob
already punished you for it
by wiping your brain.
And he used really rough
toilet paper when he did that.
He used some kind of European
stuff.
I vaguely
remember some welts on my brain, but that's...
It's only if we've passed the threshold
threshold, the finality and the horizon
event, meaning that
we didn't talk about any of this before.
We just thought we did.
And we're punished by it. Somehow.
I think we may
have had this conversation before, but we're
not hurting anyone.
We're not hurting anyone.
Right. And that's not
to say no one is hurting us.
And to wit,
in effect, the economy
and the lack of material
goods and services going around.
Well, I was just telling
Charleston, the one good thing about the
economy now is that aside from the super
rich, everybody has to live like we've been
doing for years.
And that makes me happy
in a way.
You know, having to decide which
can of beans to buy, the
39-cent one or the 38-cent
one. I mean,
what am I saying?
The can of beans is more like
38 bucks now.
Like, yeah, $30,
$40, $50,
$60, $100
for a can of beans.
Maybe dollars.
We put the bread in a wheelbarrow
and put all our pennies in a huge
basket with an Easter bunny head in it.
Strew it into the store
and there was no one there.
There was a lady behind the cashier's desk
with a shotgun.
She looked mean. In fact,
she looked like Bob.
She is perfect.
It's me.
I can't wait to get home and play the tape
back on my extra loud headphones
so I'll know what you said.
I bet it was really amazing.
Well, I know I was just, you know, trying to do
a different character thing by putting my fingers
in my foreskin and my nose hole
and piercing the top part
and, um,
making a probably sound.
But I don't know
if it came with too many phone lines.
The brain picture you made for us, Dave.
The brain picture?
Yeah, when you described how you made
that character voice,
it was scary in our brain.
Well, geez.
That's the nicest thing you ever said to me,
Purchase.
I got scared when I
imagined your foreskin
in your nose, Dave.
Oh, wow. I didn't know if I could
paint an illusion that well and that's all I needed
was just a few words of consideration
from you and us.
You did. You had me.
I'm so scared.
Can he do that because he's really
limber and can bend over far
or is it for a different reason?
He's been doing yoga every day
of his scared life.
That's his yoga.
The yoga of fear.
Actually, the friction of muscles, the graying of hair,
the palpable,
stinky,
aluminum-tasting
saliva, the actual
feeling.
The knowledge that things just aren't right
and they're not going to get any better.
They're just not going to get any better.
Well, you know, speaking of the economy
and things not getting better, somebody
really, really cruel gave me a
fridge magnet that showed the
prices of things
on the year that I was
born, which happened to be
1953.
You're supposed to say
23.
Yeah, I know, but
the
I love you.
And, um, um, um, um, um, um, um, um.
The laundry followed a 14-year-old boy.
There was a strange, unexplainable interest in the boy.
The laundry himself seemed to be so like the laundry that Tonto was amazed.
Yeah, I see what you mean.
Let's go to the house.
Here we are.
Let's go in.
Of course.
Yes.
These are mine.
I've never showed them to anyone before.
See?
I see.
Did you send for a doctor?
Well...
Tell us about it.
Transcribed story of the violence that moved west with young America.
I'm that man, Matt Marshall.
Me left...
I'm cool.
And that enterpin-
Hill Extension...
Which means blow up the external neighbors.
Am additions with a drug,
where should he signed first?
And drugs.
I want out and kill all the parasites here you.
And now I'm make all theDrive felt walking to one.
Yeah.
Hлекalek...
Okay.
Now,
vaccine,
sure wasn't.
You'll stand back to back.
When I give the signal, you'll each
walk forward 15 paces, turn
and fire. Is that
clear?
You ready, mister?
Ready.
All right, let's go.
One, three, five,
seven, thirteen.
Hold it!
There's something I have to tell you.
Killing a man is good, son.
You know that. Yes, sir.
When you kill a man, you kill a little bit of your dinner.
I've never heard it said better.
What
is it?
It is a very arrogant apology.
Goodbye, Fernando Nende.
Limor.