Thank you.
Cyber chump in the background here, the construction of things.
And normally here in Cleveland, you'd be listening to radio synesthesia.
But the bad Dr. Sinister, well, he ran into a little tiny bit of a trouble.
Well, he didn't run into anything, but somebody ran into him.
Yeah, somebody ran into him, so he won't be here tonight.
And so instead of radio synesthesia,
I'm afraid you get yet another hour of slack.
A spare hour of slack, dear friends.
And you know what that means.
No, I don't know either.
But I do have some interesting music lined up.
And then we'll probably have some more lonesome cowboy man calling in at some point.
In the future.
Char.
Tupperware doodle.
I'm where you got to go.
Why?
i sveeway face
Always.
Bye bye.
Dany.
Andi.
Bye.
Kevin.
PETER.
Bye.
Everybody.
Thank you.
Said, Mother, you're one man that I love to read
Well, I'm gonna get high
I'm gonna get high just till you show my name
Well, you know I'm gonna get so high this morning
It's going to be a crying shame
Well, you know I'm gonna stick with my reform
I ain't gonna be messing around with no cocaine
And I don't even know what I'm saying
The way I talk, you think I was dead
And I can't even piss in a straight line
And I can't even wipe my own ass
If you want me to try and think some
Well, I'm sorry, I think that I'll pass
Cause I'm so dumb, I can't believe
The shit that I say
The shit that I can do
There's nothing here between my ears
For years and years
But a couple of ears
Well, I think that my food is dried up
But I don't know who I should blame
Cause I can't even think of nothing
And my whole life's been much the same
Got my needles here beside me
And my pants are covered with piss
But my feet don't ask about that
Cause my life's too hard as it is
Cause I'm so dumb, I can't believe
The shit that I can't do
There's nothing here between my ears
For years and years
I'm so dumb, I can't believe
The shit that I can't do
Cause I don't know who I should blame
Cause I can't believe
The shit that I can't do
Gotta get it done
Never does that happen
And never does that happen
Well, I'm sorry, I think that I'll pass
Cause I think that I'll pass
So if you come home and available
And you want a few 5 cents
I'm willing to pay $100 and everything
Thank you.
there
thing
that
He won't be having any more puppies.
I'm having the immortality implant placed in my, you know, my cerebral clavicle.
Aren't you even least considering the ideas?
Because so many of tomorrow's nowadays people will be forced to live in assisted living quarters somewhere near the outside of town where the wolves howl.
And where the weirds party.
Yeah, like dancing in their nightclub uniforms and their pretty blue underpants.
I just read the weirds party section from Neighbor World waiting for you to call in.
Yes, he gave a tantalizing excerpt.
Yeah, I've read the sexy party scene.
Well, I forget which part is that.
Could you give me a small one?
He gets laid with Leia.
Oh, where the pigs are dancing, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, pig nose, pig nose basil.
Yeah, I'm not sure if the music I had in the background was really appropriate, but we'll live with it.
It wasn't like real caustic subterranean, you know, like Appalachian music with a few foul words thrown in to make the exorcism.
No.
No, it wasn't.
No, but it is now.
I still want to, before the hour is up, I do want to run the 13-minute Lenny Bruce.
I'm going to run the 13-minute Lenny Bruce routine.
You'll want to hear that, too.
The way you're doing the pop-by-the-sailor-man music right now is to get everyone ready to get them in the right uniform and all hot and sexy to think about Lenny Bruce in his latter period before he stuck a vein into his vein and expired from constant rheumatoid arthritis of the rectum.
Yeah, but before we get to that stuff, we'll dance a shanty.
We'll dance to this fine ocean shanty with the whalers.
And the whalers...
Whale blubber, slipping and sliding on the blood and blubber.
Aboard the ship.
Ah, yes, our.
We're whale pirates.
What kind of pirate did we decide our dog was the other day?
This morning, we decided, damn it, our hound dog was some kind of a pirate.
Chicken bone pirate.
He could be like a dog pirate or something, but not a whale pirate.
Yeah, he's a chicken bone pirate.
He'll...
We'll be walking him along.
He'll be in some innocuous place, and suddenly, he's trying to eat something furtively.
And it's all...
And we grab him by the jaws.
And I pry his jaws open.
Stang pries his mouth open.
I reach my hand down his throat and pull out shards of extremely sharp chicken bones that were just about to go down his throat.
Yeah, we're always...
Yeah.
I hate that drill.
I remember that.
That's one of the few things I do not miss about having an animal enjoy my...
Physical company, if you know what I mean.
Which is amazing how fast it has snapped up and chewed.
Well, and shattered into spiky shards that will lodge in his throat when he swallows them.
I had a Springer Spaniel long, long ago that got a bad chicken bone in his neck, and...
Brace yourself, folks.
This is a gross story.
I had to spend the rest of that dog's life every day poking a little metal tube...
into a hole in his throat and squirting disinfectant in there.
Because it went straight through, thanks to the chicken bone.
I don't ever want to have a permanent hole in a dog's neck again.
No.
That's a bad, bad injury to have.
No, it's just the idea of it.
It's frightening enough you didn't have to bring that up, Stan.
Well, I didn't want it to happen to you, Dave.
I know you're a chicken bone pirate yourself.
I know it.
I've seen him go for them.
Yeah, I've heard myself.
You snap them up and start crunching those bones.
He likes the marrow.
Yeah, I did just the other afternoon, as a matter of fact.
And I was even thinking about that.
Man, I'm going to puncture my throat like a dog or something.
Because I was just gobbling them so quickly.
And the person at the Giant Meager store, the elephant store that I was located at...
Giant Meager?
Uh-huh.
Giant Meager.
There were very few.
It's like David's Restaurant.
Uh-huh.
Also on the same south side of...
Anyway, the turnpickle.
The turnpickle was pointed the wrong direction for me, that's for sure.
Because when those fuzzy-y-full guardians, I guess you'd call them, came out with the clubs and the fists.
It was painful.
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
Mm-mm-mm.
Sounds painful.
You don't want to get involved in anything like that.
Especially if there's whipped cream around and they're trying to kill each other.
Some of these people just have bad habits.
You're right.
They're sore losers.
They voted for tut-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta.
And staying, like, like some of them.
Like, you know, in a compromising sexual way.
Only when I'm in Russia, visiting my special friends, then we have a little water party.
And we do some sports with the spraying.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Oh.
Possible.
And then we sell them
Then we try to sell them a hotel
But they don't buy it
First we spray the spray all over the bed
That Obama slept in
And then we try to sell them a hotel
And they go, no, no
And we won't give you copies of the video
Which is shot either
Yeah, exactly
Just like F-Cup, it's sterile
And his own version of the blue underpants
Of Monterey Bay
And the exciting areas near there
Where all the fisticuffs used to take place
You just play your cards right, Mr. President
And we will make sure that you retain your power
And we will flood the Facebooks of the leftists
With the fake news that you love so much
Oh wait, I went from Russian to Nazi
I know
But it was such a seamless
Well, it wasn't really seamless
In fact, there was a huge lump on the side of his neck
It looked like a coral snake
Yeah, you gotta stick a tube in there
Disaffected
Squeeze it
Suck it
Suck it right out
You have to
You also have to express the oral gland
Or the meat will be spoiled
That's always one of my favorite things
You must get the oil of the oral gland
Away from the meat
Before you prepare
I don't think I want to continue this line
Of course of interesting information
Boys will be boys
You boys will be boys
I had a cat that got bit on the neck one time
And it puffed up and I had to squeeze that
And it went right in my eye
Oh no, Dave, no
That's horrifying
You know, when you have your little children
Your little male children
And you're changing them
And they pee in your eye
Of course
It's a family kind of thing
Oh, it's cute
Thank you
They do that once you get them completely clean
And dry
And a little bit of baby lotion
And some powder
And then pee
Bob Dobbs still does that
If he relaxes enough
He'll pee in your eye
I think that's
Carnivuncular or whatever the word is
For central focus
I think that is central
To the central focus
This is just fresh
Take off
All right
So if you're drawing what I wrote
Well there is no opacity
But we need it
Take off
You're looking straight at a
Puff
Like a
Yeah
or something?
I cried because I could not squint
and then I met a man who could not
drool.
Well, introduce me to that person, compadre.
I'd like to shake his hand
and his dolphin-like foot.
Well, just because he doesn't drool?
He can't drool.
That's the saddest thing.
I got it.
You know, he just fills up.
Well, I'm not as beleaguered
as you think I understood.
At least I didn't want, you know,
I didn't have any fantasies like John David Rockefeller
in the 1860s.
He has to either swallow it or stand on his head
so it runs out his nose.
Like Johnny Weissmuller playing orangutan
in the Tarzan movies.
What?
I forget.
No.
Don't you?
I'm sure you do.
You just don't want to be reminded.
I knew a girl who knew Johnny Weissmuller
in the nursing home in Hollywood.
The aged Johnny Weissmuller
would, in fact,
still do the Tarzan call
at the top of his lungs
and he would
sexually harass the young nurses.
Cool.
Mercilessly.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean that.
But Cheetah was the one who always scored.
I heard a lie that Cheetah outlived
Johnny Weissmuller.
I don't believe that.
On the other hand, we have a newt
that's outlived several of my friends.
Yes.
A four-inch long amphibian
that's at least,
he must be 38 years old now.
Yeah, something like that.
Well, how old can a Republican get?
He's 40?
The newt.
Yes, the small amphibian.
I was just thinking of the newt.
We don't know how old he was
when Princess We got him from the pet store.
No.
40 years ago.
You could be sitting on the science fiction novel
of your lifetime, Senor, right there.
Because what if that newt is secretly
controlling the miles of everybody
within, say, 40?
Five or 67 miles?
He could be.
The newt could be controlling the minds
of everyone within the near 67 or 48 miles.
And guess what's near Cleveland Heights
and around where I live, right in between there,
is one of the world's largest concentrations
of crystal quartz underground
that a spring runs through.
Go on, get out of here.
Are you serious?
Yeah.
I didn't know that.
I told you that once anyway.
Ohio rocks.
Those are Ohio rocks.
Speaking of which,
I joined the Northeast Ohio Rocks Facebook thing today
so that I could send them the picture
of the hidden painted rock that you found.
Oh, good.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Princess We found a golden egg in a park.
We thought it was a golden egg,
but it was rather irregular shape.
It was just a little rock
and it was painted gold.
And on the back,
it said,
if you find this,
send a picture to Northeast Ohio Rocks.
It had a number on it as well.
Now, here's the weird thing.
This Ohio Rocks thing,
it's just this,
do a kindness by leaving a painted rock somewhere.
Okay.
Okay, that's all well and good.
They do that down at the beach.
It's a nice, you know,
distraction for little old ladies
who collect statues of owls and stuff
and have, anyway.
Anyway.
The funny thing was,
when I looked up that innocuous little Facebook page.
Jays.
There were anti-Northeast Ohio Rocks pages.
Like pages with the name Northeast Ohio Rocks are morons.
What?
Right.
It's like the internet is so filled with bored haters
that they've got,
they're hating even the most boring, innocuous, pink,
goody two-shoes, non-objectionable.
It's like, how can you waste your time
getting mad at these lamers?
How lame are you?
I would like to strangle them all.
To be a snowflake over them.
Not with my own hands,
but I'd like somebody else to go and strangle them.
I mean, you...
Or at least try to.
Okay, there's this horrible set of hurricanes going on
at this writing.
Jays.
I get to the end,
at the end of an article,
I read the comments.
Arr.
And they, somehow or another,
half of the commenters
turn it,
turn the whole hurricane thing
into a plot by Al Gore
to trick libtards into giving him money.
And that's really,
the hurricanes aren't really that bad,
but the, you know,
the,
all the other reporters in the world
are making them look bad.
It's the right-wing version
of the conspiracy of geothermal engineering,
geoengineering.
It's the right-wing version of it
because somebody's got to be doing it,
the person who's doing it,
instead of oil companies and other people
who actually stand to materially gain
by controlling the weather and stuff.
They don't consider that they can,
they like to build demonetized,
demonic guys like Al Gore.
Like, we mentioned his name,
or Nancy Pelosi.
Well, of course,
right-wingers aren't the only ones who do that.
Extremist left-wingers have,
have,
have had all kinds of paranoid delusions about,
of when an earthquake happens.
Oh, that was planned.
That was caused by such and such fruit company.
Like, I wish.
Because if you could cause an earthquake,
you could probably also prevent,
you know, a very, very serious one.
Right.
I'm sorry, but it just doesn't add up.
No, it doesn't.
That science ain't there yet.
I, I don't think anything of what you just said
makes any sense to me, but...
Good.
Nothing makes sense to me.
I know.
And nothing makes sense to anyone else
after it's been processed through you.
At first.
It's like the second time you hear it though,
it's like, oh, he actually did say something.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
He just said it in a very, very...
You know the laughing kind,
the greasy little pages with your fingers,
just like you're having chicken salad sandwiches, Monsieur?
Which is something on the side,
like a capitalist robot.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
Right.
Well, it's time, you know,
I think it's time for this witty banter to end,
because I really want to hear this Lenny Bruce thing.
It's, I came into a stash of Lenny Bruce material.
You know,
I don't listen to standup comics.
I listened to Bill Hicks for a while,
but then it was like, you want to copy him.
And so, so you don't.
I don't know if other people are like that,
but I just like that.
If something's a little bit like what I want to do,
I don't want to be too much like them.
So I, and I've had the problem of sometimes quoting somebody
without knowing I'm quoting them.
I'm thinking I made it up myself or one of my friends said it,
but really they're quoting George Carlin or somebody,
you know, and, and you said later on,
you end up looking like an idiot.
If somebody else goes, no, George Carlin said that,
not Philo.
Yeah, that's what I was just going to say.
And it's still, yeah.
But it goes both ways.
I've also had people explain that George Carlin said something or another,
that I know that Robert Antonov is a racist.
John Wilson said, well, and I know where he got it from me.
So there it goes both ways in all directions.
Goes all ways.
Yes.
The statement that America's club and you ain't in it.
And it's also the same club they used to bang you over there to keep you in line with.
Do you remember that line from George Carlin just before he expired from?
No, I didn't.
I don't listen.
I don't listen to other standup comics.
See?
Well, I only, I only.
I don't hear Lenny Bruce's okay, because I can't ever sound like him.
And, yeah.
Yeah, whereas Bill Hicks, he was like my neighbor.
That guy's another Texas guy.
Yeah, I think he was, he was also fascinated by the police force.
Just like Lenny Bruce.
No, I.
No, it's the other way around.
Lenny, the police force was interested enough in Lenny Bruce that his best friend thinks that he was murdered.
He was murdered by the police.
And his mom doesn't think he committed suicide.
His friend said he wouldn't have overdosed.
Lenny Bruce allegedly died of an overdose.
But the police hated it.
Now, his best friends all said no.
Lenny was too expert of a heroin addict to ever overdose.
And his mom said, well, he wasn't deliberately committing suicide, because why else was he trying to lose weight?
So, who knows?
But anyway, I'm going to, I'm going to go back.
That's enough of that.
Let's listen to some old Lenny Bruce.
He's doing a routine that's not at all raunchy.
It's just kind of funny to me.
But he's got a heckler in the crowd.
And the way he deals with the heckler is really interesting.
So, Dave, do you want me to just pot you down and let you listen to it?
Or do you want to wait until you get the CD later?
Yes, I would like to listen to a little bit of it right now.
Okay, well, I'm going to see.
You're fighting against me.
I'm going to be waiting out.
The other music is gone now.
Please, your voice is going away, Dave.
And we should hear great Lenny Bruce in some nightclub in the 60s.
All right.
Now, let's see what I do with you.
Oh, I'll talk about, oh, here's a bit, you know, for the people who have seen me work before,
I always find a lot of humor tied in with motion pictures.
So, Dave, I had a weird kind of thing I was thinking of.
To do a science fiction picture that opens up in Atlantis.
You know, the old Myrna Loy.
Things under the sea.
And it has this hate crazed skin diver and a physical education major, a real moron,
who was thrown out of SC for looking over the lockers of the other guys in the showers,
you know, and taking showers with his underwear on.
Hey, you remember those guys that saved the brown underwear from the army, you know?
This is plenty good.
Let me show you.
So, that dig opens up, ready?
And they're down there and they're making this terrible monster, a real weirdo, and
they're getting them all ready with the scales and the fins and the whole bit, you know?
So, now he's all ready, right?
He's okay.
Is he ready?
Looks weird?
Good.
Send him up.
And he comes up, the monster, in Coney Island.
Starts stalking the beach and he comes up and there's all these people, you know, and he goes,
And so the Jewish ladies start whacking him in the face with their pucker books, you know?
So he's looking, you know, and kids are punching him, you know?
And the cop gives him a ticket for changing his suit under the boardwalk.
And like the sand is too hot for his feet and he's walking around like this.
He's like, get out of here!
So he flips, you know?
So, all right, shut up now, you hooker.
And out of here, Daddy Warbucks.
Never mind the diner's club schtick.
Listen, oh, you like this.
The convention isn't in town anymore.
Now they found him here.
Now the tape is for falling, right?
Screwed up the tape.
You came down here for nothing.
I had to get these two girls here from Sally Stanford's.
Now, you don't understand.
You can't talk here.
You'll get the towels and leave.
Now, because it doesn't matter.
I'm an existentialist, sweetheart, so you can't.
Okay, now back to...
No, it doesn't matter.
What, what, what, what?
All right, I'll wait.
I'll wait, Miss Brooks.
But don't get it on the suit.
That's what I said.
But I said existentialist.
Listen, forget it.
Listen, you'll end up in the trunk with Dr. Shepard.
They'll get you.
The gas in the face, you'll like it.
Don't, don't...
Look, it's nice.
It's really nice.
See, I've got a traumatic kind of...
I think we're all together.
No, I like the...
I want to go home with the three of you.
I'll sit on the bed.
I won't touch anybody.
I'm one of those guys.
I'll just watch.
Listen.
A lot of guys promise, you know, they say, oh, yeah, you promised you wouldn't touch
her, but you did.
And...
Well, there goes the picture.
There goes the money down the drain for the film.
I hope you enjoyed being part of the four show.
No, you're certainly very nice.
Those faces will come back.
Here's a...
The write-up did it.
That's what did it.
That really got me for the show.
I had a whole fight with myself in the dressing room.
I read it, you know, and then I was mad.
Then I went back.
I said, no, what is...
You know, back to our conversation in the car where I said, it doesn't matter, you know.
Then I did let it...
I don't know.
That's why we use narcotics.
Now...
Okay.
Back to...
No, I don't...
I can't talk while you're talking.
Be nice.
I like you.
You...
The elderly man.
You've only got a few years.
Live it out gracefully.
Where do you want to go?
There's a...
You know, they should say nice things about you, you know.
You don't want the guy to be insincere.
Said he was nice to comedians.
He was very...
Okay.
Now...
Back to...
Oh!
Okay.
Now, you remember the picture where he comes back down and the old...
They were hitting him and yelling.
So he comes down.
The scientists are waiting, you know.
So he says, what happened?
He said, I don't know.
I bombed.
He says, you're putting us on.
He says, no.
He says, what do you mean?
You didn't flip anybody?
No one was scared?
He says, no.
He says, did you do all the big things?
Did you do...
Yeah.
Did you do the other one?
That's what they say.
Said I was doing Jerry Lewis.
Geez, I don't know what the hell I'm making of that.
Is that...
Well, I know what it is.
Coney Island.
It was...
That's...
They're weird there.
Yeah.
Got to send them up maybe to Brighton Beach.
That's what it is.
They get him...
Again, weird.
Put an abalone on his...
Oh, you know, the whole bit.
The shrimp in his nose and...
Now he's ready.
Comes up again.
Shhh.
Comes up on the beach.
An old Jewish woman runs up to him.
She says, are you married?
My daughter's Sophie.
So he really flips this time.
You know, runs down the scientist as well.
No.
Come on.
You didn't scare nobody?
He says, no.
They're flips.
I don't know what the hell it is.
I just...
He says, I know what it is.
You look weird, but you're not thinking horror.
You're not predicting.
You're projecting yourself.
Now come here.
Are you really a weirdo?
She says, yeah.
Because if you're not, a lot of guys say they're freaky.
You know, they say, yeah, I'm wild.
You know, but when it comes to...
No, I'm wild.
Believe me.
Give me a break.
Cut to...
He's on the subway, right?
Now he's waiting there.
So this chick starts digging him, looking at him.
So she comes over to him.
She says, listen, I don't want to offend you, but I know a plastic surgeon and I had a nose
like that.
Just a tip.
And I'm like, what?
So now he really flips out.
He reaches out.
But you dig, I'm talking now, but I'm really not being sincere because I'm still digging
this two lepers on my left ear, you know?
And I'm not a mechanical comic.
You know, I haven't got routine, you know?
I have to feel good, you know?
And I'm going to do something very different you've never seen in a nightclub before.
Listen, stop it.
Stop.
I have these headaches.
Listen, you'll pose for the Legionnaire picture.
Hold it.
Now, it's really nice.
I've seen this guy somewhere in those sex offense magazines.
It's lovely.
Listen, forget it.
Lolita.
You'll get a four-year-old kid.
You don't need these elderly broads.
No.
Okay.
You'll get a nice kid.
You'll wash him up.
You'll get the fireman.
You'll give those firemen a bath.
And you must speak.
I don't mind you talking.
But just...
No, I do.
I just...
You can't be audible.
You don't even like your clothes.
I do.
I love the both of you.
I want to pour gas on you.
It'll be nice.
A little party.
What does it mean?
Once a year.
Yeah.
What a kind of a...
No, don't give me the shtick.
It's two.
Not one.
Never cutting the prices.
Now, now.
George, he'll say, don't do that bit.
Right?
I'll say, you know, I'm not a...
You're offending somebody.
Where do you go there?
Okay.
All right.
Meanwhile...
Being nice to me.
Don't you know I...
I can't...
That's my function to entertain you and get you Kleenex and everything.
Now, we're going to...
See, I'm basic.
All right.
We'll talk...
Okay.
Listen, how did you happen to come in here?
Well, is it a mystery bus?
Is it a mystery bus tour?
You got the tickets.
You got your slacks clean, free, then the roller rink, and then...
You have eyes for me, I can tell.
You can take me a little bit, right?
Later, 612, the keys under the rug.
I'm saying at the Olympic.
Take the elevator, the seventh floor, and walk down one.
And later, we'll show you Mel's wigs.
Now, it's weird, right?
I want to do the...
There's the great voice content.
The guy who introduces you.
If you remember the beginning of this show.
Can you tell us what he does?
What, dear?
Don't you feel like a nut now?
Don't you feel like a complete nut with that Woodbury necklace that you saved for...
Now, you're getting a different tape on me, right?
Lenny Bruce is hostile.
That's that kind of a thing.
Okay.
Yeah.
We might as well continue in that vein.
And I'd like to put something in your vein, an overload.
I don't know.
No.
Don't leave because George gets nervous.
Okay.
He doesn't realize that a certain percentage of the audience find me...
Yes.
We have another biological failure, a result of fallout.
Yeah.
It's all right.
See, the second generation of genetics have suffered.
We're getting paid back for Hiroshima.
All right.
What?
I think you're the best.
And I'm the best.
Yes?
What's the clock?
So,
Okay.
Yeah.
I'm so sort of sunshine, me and a beer place is wonderful, eh?
they're naked.
You're paranoid, that's what it is.
I'm not persecuting you.
I love you.
You I like better than the others.
What do I represent to you?
I'm surely not your father image.
Go home, Lenny.
Well, he finally spoke up.
The fellow sitting on the rubber tube.
Right?
He bought his own whoopee cushion
from the fun shop.
Okay.
Oh.
Oh, you don't know the bit.
After the show, they say,
we helped you out, right?
And some other schmuck says,
yeah, they were in the act, right?
There were stooges.
Yeah, la-da-da-da.
Yeah, I'm laughing,
but I don't like this kind of a show.
You know.
Paid this guy's $800 to tape the show
and this schlub is,
this parakeet with the blonde hair.
Now.
Ah! Ah! Ah!
Polly's a hooker!
Now.
All right.
That's it.
That's the one time you need the band.
Go into Hot Tech for the Star Spangled Banner.
All right.
Now.
Shh.
Be nice.
Soon the gas will be here.
But I'm kind of weird.
I kind of dig the blonde
on the Leah Zephyr.
She's wild, right?
I do.
Like, I'm a real nut.
Like, I'm spritzing her,
but I'm kind of looking at her, you know.
That's sick, right?
That's what guys are the lowest, right?
They're really rotten, right?
Look at me, right?
They're really bad to me.
That's why we're all dishonest.
I really feel rotten about that, you know.
Because I recognize my own dishonesties.
Like, if that's a guy yelling at me that way,
I'm real blaggish with him, you know.
And I'm bugged and I hate him, you know.
But like, there's three people
and the chick on the left
is kind of hot looking, you know.
So I feel hostility toward her,
but I'd like to hug her a little too.
You know.
Why is that?
Why do I like you?
What's your name?
That's it.
Screw the show.
That's right.
Talk dirty to me.
I don't care.
I'm nothing.
That's right.
Take me home, men.
Right?
Hit me.
But I'm yours.
I'm just a clown on the stage for you,
oh beautiful blonde goddess.
I can't see.
Is that a waitress there?
Bobby?
Would you bring them around, please?
Thank you very much.
Let's see.
Where's the piano player?
This is the first night
I didn't have the piano player.
Oh, thank you.
You're not the piano player.
You're the owner's son.
And a you-in for a terrible life.
His whole life is ruined, right?
That's it.
Look what you'll inherit.
Someday this will be all yours.
Just think of it, right?
Get everything that was done
with a stapling gun.
Oh, you're back.
Hello there.
They have a different piano player
every night.
Okay.
I'm gonna do something
I've never done yet.
I can do something
each different show.
I did a whole lot of waitresses.
And you can see me
on Mr. Ripley's show.
Get that on tape, Fritz.
Ha ha!
Educational Pl Bangkok
for this week.
Enjoy the Vibe Show with a
Don't forget to watch
for our alum
mmpach WolodICE band
Cell Consume!
One, two, one, two, three, four,
Crater Plater, Gator Blade, ESPN 360,
Griff Rich, Flies Away,
Chuck it up with some Zorbees,
Buy, sell, consume!
Hi, Billy Mays here!
Hi, praise the Mays!
Praise the Mays!
Gary Blasey
Now
So now
Gary Blasey
I know
Customer
One, two, one, two, three, four
Cool bandit Hercules
Put her down, no hesitation
Go for private, oxy-clean
Vicity's lighter station
Buy, sell, consume
Hi, Billy Mays here
Yes, here
Raise the Mays
hunting
Hi, Billy Mays here
Raise the Mays
Joo
bold
estrella
Good night
guitar solo
They didn't care about the music.
They were pilling into chaos.
guitar solo
Ah, yes, dear friends.
Only two of the amino acids,
but who needs a bass player and a theremin player?
guitar solo
When you reach the end of side one,
no matter what you are told by later instructions on the tape,
there is no side two.
However, if you do discover one, don't look at it.
If you discover one, don't look at it.