From PR News in Washington, I'm calling for an anti-PR news.
Italian, Italian, Italians gathered below.
The difficulties are complicated by Parkinson's disease, which causes gradual tracheotomy to everyone.
The Pope released the journalist before he shot himself in the head.
What happened?
PR's police chief says Iran says it needs atomic weapons to make PR news.
No!
I don't want this!
Therapy.
I don't need therapy.
What the hell is this?
The Self Genius Powerhouse Watch.
Liar! Liar, liar!
Don't worry, just relax.
I'm cute now, like you.
No one can do it better.
Kick it!
Another UFO sighting.
This one, front page headlines.
Another hour of slack.
A small, dedicated moment of misery.
As the turtles melt into the river.
And now a satanic Elvis arrives in his UFO.
His skin is so blue, like Krishna.
Why not make some coffee to keep them all happy while I think of something?
Coffee?
Coffee break!
Nice hot espresso enema for you, sir.
I mean, Mr. King.
Coffee can only make me nervous when I drink it.
You look like a man.
A man who could use more coffee.
Free coffee is a constitutional right.
You got any coffee? Coffee?
Yeah, coffee.
No, I don't drink coffee.
That, sir, is illogical.
Nothing like a great cup of black coffee.
How to drink coffee, sir?
Hit yourself over the head with a baseball bat.
Would you please?
Yes, sir.
I'll just have a coffee, thanks.
Everybody take coffee.
Now.
Mob!
Damn, Jimmy.
This is serious gourmet.
Mob.
It's the best, man. I got it from a
Stank.
My advice to you.
You should start drinking heavily.
What is this?
I'm not saying, but I can tell you that it's fairly rare and very unstable.
I like my coffee like I like my women.
Frappy.
Bitter and murky.
Oh, you'll like this coffee.
It's fresh.
Drink up, lad.
What is that?
Thank you, sir.
That's strange.
All of a sudden, I don't quite feel like myself.
Do you feel like once the paparazzi ran us their friends?
Get a rest?
Put that coffee down.
Too bad.
Just to be a good man.
I pray we're gonna have to liberate George.
But you know what's on my mind right now?
It ain't the coffee in my kitchen.
It's the dead Bob in my garage.
Have you got a dead Bob in your garage, my friend?
How many times are you gonna kill that old sod before he finally wakes up to what you're doing out there?
Don't you care?
Don't you even care about the children of the dead Bobs?
With alacrity and with a great amount of aplenty,
we must announce the parents of the millions of dead Bobs in garages around the country.
They're leaving their garages.
Suburban Mr. and Mrs. America have wake up calls.
Lots of coffee.
And now the army of Bob clones emerges from the garages as far as the eye can see down the long line of suburban driveways.
Followed by the corpses of the Armenian olive stuffers.
It looks like quite an entourage.
I can smell the smoke in the distance.
I don't know if some of them are being smoked or are actually smoking themselves.
It looks like quite a cloud.
These Dobbs clones, as they're called, are the perfect smoking machine.
And as well as the perfect selling machine, have decimated the economies and the air of every city they have passed through in this wave of destruction.
And sales.
Now, Terb, I'd just like to make one thing I'd like to ask the panel here,
Miss Wee and the turbulent Ivan Stenguefew.
Many of these corpses appear to have been eviscerated,
and yet they managed to make steam, as it were.
I don't know whether it's the cold weather or the fact that they've been eating the wrong things.
Well, they're freshly dead, the Dobbs clones, when they're finished using them.
I hope I don't have to spell that out.
Leave the corpses, the used pinks, as they call them, behind.
And of course, there's no natural scavengers or predators to dispose of the bodies anymore,
as the Dobbs have also had their way with the buzzards and so forth as well.
Well, there's plenty of that natural...
It's a serious, serious situation.
There's plenty of it.
We're hearing right now, at least, that there's plenty of that natural jelly surrounding them.
Most of the corpses that have fallen in the mud...
Well, everywhere these Dobbs clones go, as you know, they leave the cotter pins and the jelly.
No one understands that. It's been going on for decades now.
Well, they go loose as soon as we pull the pin on them.
Yes, that's exactly right.
Just as bad as any bad Romero or good Romero films we've seen in the last 500 years.
These shuffling dead Dobbs are certainly the most horrible manifestation of religious cultism,
superstitious nonsense.
Oh my God! No! They're coming to the station now!
Oh my God! Oh my God!
Well, we just thought a methamphetamine lab blew up down by the river,
and next thing we knew, we were covered with pipes and honkers.
That's not funny, man. Methamphetamines are the scourge of the po-buckers of America.
They're the scourge of Christ.
I lost a lot of friends to bathtub meth.
Well, we lost the Lord. He was actually squashed.
I lost a...
The plug of the drain where they made the bathtub meth.
Jello.
To bathtub meth.
It became as vapid as...
No, it just ate up the...
Vapor.
Yeah, vaporized the plug.
Very plug.
Meth vaporizes the plug in your head, my friend, so that nothing...
You know, it all builds up and it can't drain out.
And you know, sooner or later, it's gonna have to leak out.
Oh, man.
Look at the corpus callosum.
It's dried like a prune.
Hey, there's talk now of a Columbus devival.
You didn't hear about that.
No.
That Reverend Janina Grinder was gonna put on somewhere around Columbus.
And the band that's...
One of the bands that's gonna be there along with loathsome cow-frunk Dave and the retarded creatures of slime was Stylix.
Stylix.
Oh, man.
We have air on the air, man!
Good god.
Esquire of S.I.M.
Anddzyles.
De null match!
Fuck.
We took a drink and looked outside
We always wait until we die
The greatest thing I ever had
Came to pass and then I said
I like women just like to fly
That doesn't mean it has to be mine
The greatest dream you ever had
You know the truth inside your head
We took a drink and looked outside
We always wait until we die
Take on our future
Thetrustm mile a难
On Miniature
Like I said
It's time for bed
We both wake up
We both get treatment
Like I said
It's time for bed
We both wake up
We both get treatment
Like I said
It's time for bed
If we drink we will
We both get treatment
Like I said
It's time for bed
We both get treatment
From PR News in Washington, I'm not doing a good job taking the bottom 30% of PR's military
figurehead national federal and people's governments that might pass skeptical plans to change
the bottom 30% of PR news in Washington.
I'm not doing a good job taking the bottom 30% of PR news in Washington, I'm not doing
a good job taking the bottom 30% of PR news in Washington, I'm not doing a good job taking
the bottom 30% of PR news in Washington, I'm not doing a good job taking the bottom 30%
of PR news in Washington, I'm not doing a good job taking the bottom 30% of PR news
in Washington, I'm not doing a good job taking the bottom 30% of PR news in Washington, I'm
singing.
Singing.
That's her song.
From PR News in Washington, I'm the complication of the scar tissue that has caused the lower
lung to collapse.
The BBC opened fire on a civilian vehicle last Friday on the road to PR News, Washington.
Yeah, I am mindful that we're all sinners.
It is a riddle wrapped in a mystery inside an enigma.
I experimented with marijuana a time or two and I didn't like it.
I didn't inhale and never tried it again.
Yeah, I am mindful that we're all sinners.
Go on, chief, go on back to your tribe.
This was a reference to an individual.
Go on, before you get hurt.
Go on, chief.
You got a gun?
Who had a very large penis.
Yeah, right.
And he used the name that he had been referred to in the pornographic material.
Big Bob.
Yeah, that's what they call him.
Do you recall what it was?
Oh, yeah, it's not a form of socialization.
The name that was referred to was Long Dong Silver.
Yeah, I am mindful that we're all sinners.
Bob.
Congenitally innocent.
Term.
Long.
Dong.
Silver.
In conversation with Professor Hill.
Had you?
We're killing for God.
Killing for God.
That's number one on the religious channel's top ten.
Holding up, I'm going to kill all your women and children because that's what God wants.
And God gave this land to us and he also gave us these tanks.
So fuck off.
Killing for God.
That's all Joe and I did, Dom.
Killing for you.
With the Bible in one hand.
And the tech nine in the other.
How about one of them little small little angel rad nuclear devices?
Oh, for me, I like this old Russian RPG.
Take out half a damn building while I'm courting for Leviticus 597.
E!
Ah.
Killing today, friends.
And killing for God.
Killing for God.
This is what we see of our own existence.
There are so many ways we can express ourselves in this life.
And one of my favorites has always been to pick up a bludgeon or a truncheon and beat some elderly person silly, perhaps for death, and read to him the book of God.
And buy yourself a wild planet in a
impersonal dimension.
I, for GEAR 1 you lost.
Toll Labs to eaten fucking
Way if you would like to mie
I'
чит
I
read
eat
I smoke María
little vermin. He's an example of the worst scum that ever walked the earth, the criminal
cat. Look at that strange doliosophallic skull, the narrow set eyes, the quivering rabbit-like
chin, ever moist with a veneer of spittle, the long cadaverous twitching hands, the clashing
badly coordinated suit, vest, and tie combination, the Ralph Lauren polo shirt with the tiny
engraved polo ponies, and last but not least, that disgusting syphilitic wart right in the
center of his inflamed nose. It looked like a cat scratched him across the forehead, and
it seemed like a good idea, so I brought out Tabby, and I let him have it. This man's been
scratched by a cat over a hundred times. Call an ambulance. Here comes the dog patrol, and
not a moment too soon.
Another bulldog drumming, my pleasure. Out of the fog comes one relentless man, with
his underthrust jaw ready to bite out a chunk of crime.
That's you, friend, I hope.
Yes, it's you. Don't forget that most of you have the deviated septum for a damned or darn
good reason. That's where the implant goes, and that's where you get your directives.
I love big ol'
brother.
I love him so much, I wrote a poem to him last night.
You are king of the entire Tyra. Please come and let me breathe some air. My rectum and
the rest of my body's not free. I enjoy living in a station with...
Hey, wait, what?
With we.
Princess we.
A station, a place to stop for a moment.
Friends, let's stop for a moment.
And tell what we heard. That the crime report there was, of course, Dr. Howell, the toast
of San Francisco on the bread and butter of San Francisco, which I guess would be the
KPFA show of shows, the subgenius show without any name like that.
And he doesn't have syphilis on his work like I do.
Eh, well, now don't speak too soon.
Okay.
We, uh, uh, Norrell Preff did a whole lot of the cool, cool, cool collage.
That were happening in there, uh, such as the living specimen and the all sinners routine
there with, uh, George and so forth. Uh, but, uh, killing for God, I think was punked up
by Phineas Narco of National Cynical Network, which you can, uh, reach at nationalcynical.com.
Oh, Norrell Preff is available at heavyconfetti.com.
And, uh,
Lonesome Cowboy Dave is not available at all.
I'm not a veteran either.
I was spared the last war.
I'm bird-dogging princess.
We are done.
He's not a veteran.
And she's bird-dogging yours.
Truly, Reverend Ivan Stang.
No, no, no, no, man.
You're not a bird-dog.
You're a joker.
Got to bird-dog him.
I wonder why we, I'm sorry, didn't mean to get in between different actions.
Oh, no, no, no.
There's nothing.
There's nothing happening at all now.
No, no.
I just wondered why.
It's all for you, Dave.
Killing for God.
Why this is so emblematic of our culture and our human race.
What do you mean our culture?
Whose culture is that not emblematic of?
I'm not saying.
I'm saying ours is human beings or human beings, whichever, like, you know, deformed vegetables you want.
Could we not rise above that which is base and human and animal?
If our go-match was stimulated, perhaps, correctly, we could see the other side.
Perhaps not genius.
For that must be going the wrong direction.
But sub-geniuses.
Those who burrow under the underthings, under the groundwork of all cultural relativity.
Those who dig a hole under the magnanimous structures of the old culture and let it fall in underneath you like a temperature.
The termites in the foundations, one might say.
Each individual termite is a relatively powerless little force of slag.
But all told, together, working completely unconnectedly.
Why those termites can bring down your house.
The tombs of sub-genius ideas.
Your neighbor's house.
The cop station down the street.
Bringing down your cerebellum.
I want to bring down your religious constructs.
That brings me down.
All your sociopathological lies you tell yourself.
I couldn't help it.
Maybe you are there with too much passion.
Or too hard with attention for anything.
But soon, you will be surrounded.
in this till adjust fornoj noir himself.
But even so.
A humble Roheth the Gypsy act alone.
Who, neither with a grin nor chic inside partetherur to creepyITT
We wouldn't hope it comin' husband.
I don't need грats anywhere.
But you want to see rust.
Just we won't make it.
Cutマaa
same sneer on his face.
Every sign you go looking for a job
says no wart mongers need apply.
Every place you go, the bank's
trying to take your money, trying to take
your livelihood.
It ain't changed in a hundred
thousand years.
Walk down to the enlistment station, man.
There's gotta be a way
out of here.
There's gotta be a way out. There's gotta be a way out.
There's gotta be a way out.
Run.
No place to hide.
What's that smoke? What's that huge pipe?
What is that strange smell?
What's that...
Could that be the smell of hope?
Could that be the pipe of...
It was, and now he's gone.
Oh well, well that was fun for a second.
That's the way he is, man.
He comes and he goes, you know.
He's like a gypsy too, though.
He's so cool.
Check those sideburns.
No way to describe it.
I like the braided nostril hairs.
The kind of dreadlock thing going on.
That stinky smoke made me feel funny.
In fact, I feel like...
I feel really different.
I feel humorous myself, but I don't know if it's...
I feel more...
I'm seeing through new eyes.
I feel...
Look, you got a new eye.
There's an eye.
There's a hole in your forehead.
And there's a hole behind you
underneath your backbone.
And there's another hole
right in front.
It's...
It's incredible.
I can't...
I...
She's turned into a huge pipe.
Down upon your feet.
It's a pipe,
and she is in it.
It's like she is the funnel
through which the smoke may pass
and so many other things.
The vessel of Connie.
Channeling the all-femininity
of the inner yin
of all yangfulness.
This holy kundalini vessel
is capable of re-transforming the earth.
But no, you can't re-transform.
You can't transform one time and re-
Love has been born
into this plane
as a living two-legged pipe.
Wow, and what legs.
Wow.
And that smoke.
It's a bastard child, though.
I'm afraid it'll never find legal work.
At least in this sect.
Who is man enough to take...
to partake...
of this,
the pipe of Bedeet the Bodebob?
You got the testicles?
Come on, kid!
No, stop trying to wait, kid!
Get up here!
Get up close!
Now, now, get ready!
Yeah, see, everything's gonna be just fine,
just like in the Main Street, USA.
Look at the pipe. Firmly!
Go! Point your glance this way.
That's right.
Now put your mouth around there, baby.
Yeah, that's it, kid.
And listen.
By the time you take one big heften-up-and-pipe of that,
the bells of St. Mary will blow in the dark.
Anyway, there you go, Sonny.
You're one of us now.
Whoever the hell we are.
That is the question, isn't it?
Who are we, friends?
Why, only PR news knows the answer.
To avoid paying fines for 35 bodies.
There are still many more to be voted on since they have that last time.
The bodies were probably recently abducted or recently probably abducted.
Probably wearing civilian clothes.
Probably some recent days ago.
Some areas of Massachusetts received 8 inches of PR news in Washington.
Billy Martin is one of the nicest people.
He's one of the cleanest boys in our town.
He's one of the cleanest boys, too.
But he hasn't always been so clean.
They just want me to be a sissy.
As a matter of fact, they knew that a boy is bound to get dirty.
The trouble was, Billy had the wrong idea.
Billy had the dream.
I bet cowboys don't wash all the time.
It's not sissy to be clean.
Who said that?
Who's there? Who's there?
Sophie is the name, partner.
Why, you're a living cake of soap.
You're a living cake of soap.
I don't quite understand.
So many boys and girls don't understand what a good friend I can be.
So I'd like to show you.
May I?
Just lie down and close your eyes.
That's right.
Why, I see a cowboy.
He's washing up.
That's right.
There's nothing sissy about that cowboy, is there?
Now, close your eyes again, and I'll show you.
Learn good hand habit.
Each time you bathe all over.
That's right.
You and I can be partners in other clean habits, Billy.
And especially after going to the toilet.
If we work as partners.
Your clothes.
You know, flies carry dangerous germs on their feet.
Keep your mouth away from the nozzle.
That's right.
Break off the piece.
And Billy didn't forget.
He's one of the cleanest boys in our town now.
That cowboy sure knows how to clean a little boy now, don't he?
Yeah, he don't.
He's no sissy.
Well, just because of the meat hooks and everything, I've had problems before.
But that doesn't mean I'm still that way.
I don't have to wear at least pink ankle cufflets.
At least I don't have to let everybody know what my satellite image says where I am.
Uh.
Your satellite image always knows where you are, Dave.
That's my satellite shadow, isn't it?
Actually, as long as we're indoors, they can't see us.
I don't think.
Unless they use those special helicopters that do resonant stuff off the glass windows.
Right.
You're near a glass window, so technically they could get a kind of a reading.
It doesn't look like it's moving.
They could even record what we're saying here in this room.
They outside could hear what we're saying.
Right at this moment.
The fact that we're on the radio would make it a little bit moot point.
But they could be spying on us and detecting us.
And they could be spying on us.
They could be detecting what we're saying without plugging in the radio.
We can hear everything you say.
They can.
Yes.
On the way over here, we were talking about those websites where you can look at the geosynchronous orbiting satellites.
And their websites where you type in your address and look at your house from above through the satellite eye.
The third eye in the sky.
Why do they have to be so journalistic?
The conspiracy users.
And the snoopers.
And the peeping toms.
And the snooping toms.
And the little child cleaning cowboys.
There's nothing sissy about that cowboy now, is he?
But no, seriously. They can see you.
They can watch you bathe.
They can watch you bathe those children.
They can watch you bathe in the canoe from above, Dave.
They know what you did in that canoe.
They know what you do, kid.
They can see you and they're seeing you now.
You're bathing those kids in a canoe.
They saw you while you were seeing them.
And they know you were looking.
They know what you were looking at.
What was I looking at?
I got an email the other day that they wanted me to click on it so I would look at it.
But I knew it was entrapment so I didn't even look at it.
Because I knew.
They know about Connie and the canoe.
They also get the biofocal optical scans.
Once you look in the canoe.
Yeah, you look in there. See, when you click on it, they're clicking on you.
And then next thing you know, your cerebral cortex starts to click.
Back when I was a kid, when I was on, well, you know, the drugs and the JTPase and all that.
And the Freon and the nasal hairs.
We'd be driving around and we'd be going,
Hey man, be careful about that cop over there.
Because the cops have a vibe detector.
They can tell if you've got a buzz on, man.
Because they have this special vibe detector.
Special brain scan.
And the funny, we thought that was a funny joke back then in the 1950s.
When I was a teenager.
But now, it's not such a joke, is it?
No, things are on the other foot, aren't they, Sheriff Poopie?
Yes.
Now we can see the other side of the boat.
We can scan your brains too while you are scanning our brains.
The cerebral recorder is on the other side of your cerebra.
The left brain doesn't know what the right brain is doing, but the little recording device down there does.
And don't worry, the shoe is on the other foot, so you're not going to walk too far.
Oh, they tried to explain it.
They dangle the, they hide it in the open.
They dangle it in front of our faces and mock us in the form of science fiction movies.
The strange overboiled hot dog on the floor.
Oh, look what they'll be doing in the open.
It'll be the year 2020.
They'll be recording your thoughts and you won't even know you have a brain recorder that was implanted before you were born, that was grown in you.
Would you say so?
And then you find out that they've had it since World War II!
That they've been putting them into soldiers and infants since World War II, the brain recorders!
What is going down, Johnny?
Billy will never be clean.
And that's not a good cowboy.
And Tommy will never be dirty again.
These children have been renamed and relocated.
Each one of them given their own special magnetic shoe to flee whenever the brain scans don't fit.
It's not the same world you thought it was, Dr. Sphynx!
Things have changed for good.
Or for ill, depending on your perspective.
I love you, big brother.
Big brother.
I love you so much.
I sing.
It's too late for human individualism anymore.
They're gonna stomp it all out.
Where's that little booklet I found?
It had this funny, interesting...
Where is that little booklet you found?
It had this interesting little...
Oh, now at last the step-by-step process is revealed?
This explosive new future religion beyond science?
May raise your intelligence, transform your life, improve your health and luck, and end financial woes.
Well, I heard that before.
Sure, buddy. Sure, I'm gonna believe some pipe-smoking salesman's claim that this is a certified religion of scorn and vengeance directed at all of them, the enemies of us outsiders.
It is self-help through scoffing and blaspheming, frenzied fornication and the thumping of graven images.
The Church provides answers and miracles in the service of...
...SERI-AVALUES!
What?
Ignore the man behind the curtain, friends. The goal is slack.
The method is casting out of false prophets.
The weapon is time control and the motto,
We can't say on the radio,
Because they can't take a joke!
But why?
But you can, friends.
We know that you can because you once pledged money to the station.
You can take a joke.
Yes, we've taken a joke very well so far.
Some say we've taken this joke a bit too far.
Some say that you can't take a joke.
If you go to one of those subgenius devivals, you're likely to be...
...DOSED ON EXTASY!
What?
That's what we were accused of recently.
Take a bite.
Why, can you imagine that, friends?
What if you came to, for instance, Text Day, May 7th in Austin, Texas?
Would you be dosed on ecstasy by a nice girl?
Only Bob knows and you can find out.
Or is your soul ready...
...for Text Day?
Have you seen her blue flesh?
Have you seen her shiny purple behind, beckoning you as it glows in the dark?
You want to follow it, running forward on your knuckles, drooling after that gold ring of slack and beautiful soft round things.
Ah, he with the eyelids like an elephant clitoris.
Beautiful, bobbling...
He with the horns of a man of two kisses.
But that's a distraction from Bob!
That's a distraction from Bob, my friends!
If you...if you lose sight...
If you lose scent of the smoke of that time...
...if you lose sight of the smoke of that time...
...for one second, you might backslide!
You don't want to backslide, do you?
And fall back into the arms of the...
...the one we cannot speak?
It's beautiful.
It's a modern version of tomorrow's future today.
Not all artists are starving!
An incredible new vision of the future you'll never see.
It's the art of working with people.
It's the art of crying about their reality.
You don't want a mink coat.
Rayon is the fabric of the future.
You want a polyurethane hat.
You don't want a fuzzy wool hat.
Friends, what is...
...Baldada?
What is not?
Synthetos itocratis iptipanis.
It is, as Aristotle said,
Baldada, the essential
Ism-asm-non-what-what-is.
Baldada is the nearly unexplainable label
for that mysterious quality that impregnates
ordinary things with meaning for the subgenius
no matter how devoid of value
they may appear to the others.
Seeing in the vivisecting light of
Buldada, we recognize that the most
awe-inspiring artifacts in the world
of our civilization are not the revered
artsy-fartsy pieces of culture
displayed in our swankest art museums,
universities, and concert halls
as the conspiracy would have us believe,
but are instead to be found on such icons
as low-budget exploitation movies,
lurid comic books, all-night TV,
sleazy paperbacks of the gods,
certain bizarre billboards and pulp magazine ads,
and literally any other
fossil of raw humanity in all
of its tish-kickingly
flawed GLORY!
of its tish-kickingly flawed GLORY!
That's enough cheering now, we're going to
remove the appendices down from
this book, or this
book of life here spread out on the table
in front of me, Tom
Germanicus, was that his name?
Tom Germanicus,
an insurance salesman from
Wichita,
and he died 57 years of age
from over-smoking of his own coronary,
and what we're going to do is make
this incision right above the placebo
area, and there's, you notice
there's various onographic and
insular designs below there,
and could you also move the
camera a little bit closer?
This man has no spleen,
is that right Nurse Coxie? Yes, that's right.
Could you please hold the non-spleen
up so the people in the operating theater
and the back few chairs
of the balcony can see the actual
non-spleen? Do you want to talk to her?
It's pink, just like most of his
friends in his life was,
and it's a little smelly, like the
way things all came out for him,
but you notice here,
he's got an incision on the back of his neck.
Yes, I can see that.
Nurse, could you show him the tattoo
of the pipe right above the, yes,
where the, hmm? Here you are
doctor. Now this area is
. . .
. .
It's, it smells really funny in here.
6 o'clock alone
Dream a little dream of
Oh, dream with a
Dream on, dream on, dream on
I wanna dream of a
Sometimes in time
Working around
Dream police
They come to me in a band
I've got so many dreams
The Impostor Dream
That was, that was, that was
Just a dream, just a dream
Just a dream, dream
Dream, dream, dream
Phineas Narco did that, friends.
We've been playing a lot of Phineas Narco's stuff
he's done over the years and years and years
for national cynical
network, which you can get more
at nationalcynical.com
Hail Reverend Phineas Narco
as he
our leader in collage
for this show, well, him
and Norell Preff, who did
the Clean Billy one
heavyconfetti.com
Look at that
crowd of Satanists following those
two subgenius collage artists
They're starting to run a little, you know
keep up the pace a little bit, I don't know
not too good a situation
situation
What else have we got here?
Oh, Artemia Salina did one of the cut-ups
we were hearing later, the 126 song
which I can't possibly describe
What, what?
He do, drunk suck binklin
Give Luke's bzium goon chops it
Dob you're a dub, dob leets it
Big off, you're a bad man kill
That's health-pope Huey, sort of
Yeah, sounds like some of the research
had been done, yeah, listen
Nip him bug with dessert
Right, gosh, he can make it out quite easily
Yes
He jokey, be gooned up
Now this person is clearly not a problem with syntax
It's a problem with his actual mouth and his muscles in his mouth
Is it chip-chop mixed, Huey?
Yeah, yeah, his throat and much of the part below his larynx and his thorax
resembles chip-chop's hand
Now I know you can't understand a damn thing he's saying
but I know what he means, don't you?
Hey, sweetie, you know what I'm talking about?
Sorry
Sweetie
Dead sweet
Oh my goodness
Did somebody steal your bike?
It's just so good
Sell little children for sex
They'll be high
Oh, clean cowboy
I'll make you
Oh, the cowboy's cleaning them puppies again
Yeah, yeah, I got my wash
The lines were talking head
Which is a tad worse than being fined $7,500 Canadian
And to somehow make that situation palatable
They're dead, sucker
And all those European fag country
Unless we let a couple of the daughters and a couple of the little boys
Go and have sex
With those rich Americans
So why don't you try that?
Jackass you
My, I wish I could do that
In unrighteousness
All the nations in the aggregate
All has a drop in the bucket
I was unable to preach it
Like I'm doing it this morning
And I love to see
We're selling little children for sex
It's a little tickle in the ocean
Against all ungodliness and unrighteousness of men
And we are the terrorists
Yes
You Swedes
Better let your hearts be troubled
With fags and dykes
Counting the infants and the suckling
Yes
We are the terrorists
We're weak and vulnerable
You filthy Swedes
That's a perfect fit
You're going to be buried with the barrel of an ass
Don't bring acid
And them dead Swedes
That you can't find no how nor way
More land
We got a verse for it
Wake up
You're going to hell
Everybody's in a diabetic coma
From all this sugar preaching
You arrested a God almighty
Bike
Are likely to be found in mass grave
Every last one of them
I mean in the suckling the infantest of the infants
Fags are relevant to the child's story
The lover's out
So
Fags
Love love love love love love
Sugar sugar
Sugar sugar sugar sugar sugar
Get out in the concourse
In the streets
You filthy Swedes
E-R-R-T-E-R-E-L
And Sweden got it
I don't know
That was Reverend Ivan Stang live at the Detroit Devival
Last couple of weeks ago
That was you?
Reverend Stang was very upset over the treatment he'd gotten on his recent tour of the country
The subgeniuses in Sweden apparently expected more of him than he was willing or able to put out
Well in Stockholm they were expecting more than the stock Stang if you know what I'm saying
Yes that's right
They wanted you to perform in a multifunctional way
Yes they're more multicultural in Sweden I guess
They wanted you not only to spurt your venom but also to spurt his sperm
Well not me we're talking about Reverend Stang the crotchety old hate filled usurper of the throne of J.R. Bob Dobbs
On the throne of Gustavus
When Dobbs returns you know Stang will meet his fate and justice will be served
Those who were taxed unfairly under Stang will be released from their bondage
Bob will again sit on the great throne of slack
And the true subgenius race will spill its seed
Washing like a great tsunami of mutation
Across all of the Americas, the old worlds and the old planet
Who shall wear the great umbrella?
For when the sputum of Bob comes down
There'll be no projecting without this magic umbrella
No
Look at it
No brother
It's made of finest very finest silks
Well it's polysynthetic silks
The thickest
That are very thick and firm
And wait a minute
But I thought he was just the sacred squad
And Bob is big my friend
And Bob is good looking
And he wears tight tight tight tights
And look at Bob's umbrella
Bob go friends
He's a real uber mensch
An overman
One could almost say yes
A super man
A fantastical
Bigger than life
Larger than limbaugh
A real cheese of a man
He's no joke
He's no dime bag
Bob's the real thing
Bob's an injection baby
Bob loves you
And his love is so big
And so grand and so great
And his slack is so fat
And huge and heavy
That when Bob comes down on you my friends
When Bob comes on you
You'll know it
And it happens every time you go to the bathroom
Did you know that?
Every time you go to the bathroom you feel Bob
And every time you go to the Bob
Bathroom you're creating
In your mind's eye an image of Bob
To focus to concentrate on
This is the idea of Bob's life
This is the idea
This is the idea of
What's the name of that damn meditation
What's the name of it again?
Damatol
No no no
In fact you need to take your damatol
Come to think of it
I think we've had enough of this
And you take this damatol right now
Just open your mouth and take the damatol
I don't want to
I'm tired of the bees buzzing around my forehead
I'm tired of these endless arguments
You can still hear those bees?
Yes people
Yes
The alien bees
And the little argument of soldiers from outer space
They tell me which department to head
Which faculty to be in charge of
What faculties to lose
When they come back
I'm tired of it
He's lost his faculties
But that's alright
There's a new principal in town
And he's looking for you
That's right
Lord Rizal
And Germans
This year a mixture of many years into the future
You're going to be treated to some of the finest
Most luscious lecturing
And sideways cavernating this side of plutonium
Once we've secured this galactic area
And those beyond
There's no stopping
Who's
Who
No
Are we
Stopping
Who's us
Who are we
Who
Who are you
Who are they
Who is he
Who is it
Who are they
Who are you
Where are they
Where is it
What is mine
Who are you
Who is not
You know you're llama
And you're daddy
Say it high and low
I'm no good for you
They call me untouchable
I'll turn the ash round
See that I don't know what to do
I get so tired of sneaking around
Just to get to your back door
I crawl past the garbage and your llama jumps out screaming
Don't come back no more
I can't take it
Siddhar wants to kill your llama
Siddhar wants to burn your dead
I can't believe he's the best friend
Later I tried to call you
Your llama told me you weren't there
He told me don't bother to call again
Unless I curl up all my hair
I get so tired of sneaking around
Just to get to your back door
I crawl past the garbage and your llama jumps out screaming
Don't come back no more
Siddhar wants to kill your llama
Say it high and low
I get so tired of sneaking around
Just to get to your back door
He told me don't bother to call again
Don't come back no more
Siddhar wants to kill your llama
He tells me don't bother to call again
Don't come back no more
Later I tried to call you
Your llama told me you weren't there
You told me don't bother to call again
Unless I cut off all my hair
I get so tired of sneaking around
Just to get to your back door
I crawl past your garbage and your llama jumps out
I scream it don't come back no more
Can't take it
I said I want to kill you now
I said I want to burn you down
I can't believe I made you mad
I said I want to kill you now
Come on
Oh yes, Noril Pref!
Reverend Noril Pref, dear friends.
My sitar wants to kill your llama.
More from Noril Pref
is at heavyconfetti.com
I guess, you know,
what are you asking
a logical question?
In the first place,
you should have asked
the question in front of you.
First, I must ask you a question, friend.
What question did I ask?
You asked what is the meaning of slack.
That is the first question
you were asking.
Then you're asking
how does Bob relate
to the meaning of slack?
Does anybody really know
what's slack?
It's something you gotta feel
way down in your,
you know,
what's the part of your tevas?
Yeah.
You gotta feel way down
in your spinal column.
Hey, hey, hey.
You don't need to feel down
in her spinal column.
Mr. Cowboy.
Hey, quit cleaning that.
Cut.
The out of control
cleaning cowboy.
See, this is a tantric spot
right here.
You have this neck.
Oh, what's,
it's absorbing my finger.
Is that,
what, listen here, boy.
Um,
kids,
don't ever,
don't ever try to do
what I'm doing right now.
No, man,
don't ever use your digits
to mess with the digital delay.
I mean,
think of what happened
to Tom Delay.
You know,
he spent too long
and now look at it.
Just do what I say,
not as I do.
I'd like to ask you,
you children,
you know,
who are the children
of tomorrow
to think on this problem
and as we go through
the upcoming academic year,
along with the other
members of the department,
we're going to try
not only to bring you
the most,
the best education
we possibly can,
but a wholesome environment
in which you can thrive
and get,
okay,
get the implant away,
get the implant away from,
get the implant away
from that child.
Get,
get the,
get the implant away from,
which is the part of the proboscis
which hangs itself daily
at the witching hour
and then rehangs itself
on the wall.
It's dreadful.
It's horrible.
It's,
it's,
it's the subgenius
radio ministry hour of slack
and it's back
and it won't go away.
Well, actually,
it will go away fairly soon,
but in the meantime,
you should know
that you can always
Always get more information about the dreadful Church of the Subgenius by dialing in to www.subgenius.com.
There's no O in subgenius, but there is in .com.
In fact, there's actually two if you think about it.
Friends, you can also check out the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack by way of the U.S. Postal Service by writing to us.
That's us at Post Office Box.
Box 181417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio.
To whom are you making your address?
Stately Wayne Manor, Ohio.
Who are they?
44118.
Once again, who are you?
Who are they?
I don't know who they are.
I've never seen them before in my life.
Yes, if I knew better, I'd say they were here for a different reason than you had in mind.
I don't know it's anywhere.
What's it look like then?
Well, it's red with yellow wheels.
I mean, blue with orange wheels.
It's all in the mind.
The End
Blue manes?
What do you think?
I think that...
Remember, there'll be rough seas ahead.
What do you think?
Well, then, um...
Pounding overwhelming waves.
What do you think of that, eh?
Well, I think that...
That's a Muslim flag, right?
I think...
Well...
I've forgotten.
Right, then, let's get this vessel shipshape.
I kind of like the way it is.
Submarine shape.
Well, up in the crow's nest, I am the sea.
Well, son of a bitch, we've discovered, man.
Tom and Joe, dear friends.
I'm not sure which that was, Tom or Joe.
Hey, man, haven't you heard the word of Bob?
I'm a mutant.
I'm a sickoid, lobotomy, drug user.
I blow everything off.
I vomit on Christmas.
And I think Bob is the only true salvation.
And our goal is to have 34 billion hating our guts by 1984.
This goal will be vigorously pursued and sought after by all Arkansaniac subgeniuses.
Our schism is at war with your father church.
We're declaring ourselves as heterics against Bob.
No, wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
No, we're not.
Just kidding.
We're with you, Bob.
We heard you.
This is Bob police.
I was just kidding.
One, two, three, four.
Doctors for Bob.
No regulating.
The Lord hear my prayer, and let my cry come unto thee.
The Lord be with you.
He's lost his faculties.