Remain seated and come to order. The court is again in session.
Your behavior, to say the least, has been most strange.
I want to warn all who are here that the police have orders to arrest anyone creating...
The subgenius power of...
Your Honor, this is preposterous.
Yes!
I'm rational.
Who else is pixelated?
Why, everybody is pixelated, except...
The subgenius power of...
What?
Your Honor, this is absurd.
It was twisted around to sound imbecilic.
No objection.
There's a theory that our universe is the creation of another universe.
Only one more hour to go.
That it's a gigantic experiment in some kind of computer program.
There is a...
Perfect.
...specially reputable theory for that.
That cuts it, hardware boy.
So that guy, you know, he may have been...
No skinny pink boy is going to tell me how to say things on my show.
What is that?
What kind of sound is that?
I should see a video game.
Fanaticism consists in thinking some one matter so overwhelmingly important that it outweighs everything else.
I have nothing against Canadians.
I'm playing Bob and Doug right now, as a matter of fact, to show my love for Canada.
What about us?
Get out.
I've got the wives of 10,000 earth-rape old men.
10,000 earth-rape old men.
Philo has the flatulation of them.
So, Hoser, what are you talking about?
We're going to close back on, huh?
Way to go.
No, that's optional.
10,000 earth-rape old men.
And then...
Go pick your nose.
The acidic amino acids will be here tomorrow night!
Ah, yes, dear friends.
But tonight, you're listening to Hour of Slack number 1080,
of which I am your host and pair partner, Reverend Ivan Stang.
And we're going to continue with the...
Part two of the five-part...
What?
The amino acids are already inside of you now.
Yes, the amino acids are already inside of you now.
But this background music is, in fact, from their new album due out in June,
Humanity Will Fall Like Hens.
But tonight's Hour of Slack show is a real Hour of Slack show.
It's got all the normal Hour of Slack...
But it's from the abnormal station of KPFA from January 10th,
when we did a...
Five-hour epic starring host Izzy Isn't and host Puzzling Evidence,
both of whose shows we used up,
with Dr. Howell, who actually arrived later in the evening,
Philo Drummond, yours truly, Reverend Ivan Stang,
Reverend John Shirley, Gary Gabrogfran,
Michael Pepe, Princess We Are Dough,
Chaos McBobcat Drummond,
that's the new Mrs. Drummond,
Phineas Narco of NationalCyndical.com,
Kay Robb, somebody named Walter,
and the Uber Goober Booby Baby on keyboards,
plus Bishop Joey from the First Church of the Last Laugh.
And so, let us go into that very world.
Reverend Stang, I have to return to my apocalyptic theme
because I am the purveyor of the SignsOfWitness.com website.
I'm reporting for it.
I've got to ask...
I'm going to ask you this.
What will the apocalypse be like?
We know what the party is going to be like a little bit before,
but when the actual end comes,
could you describe a little bit what it would be like?
Well, it will depend on how...
Besides a blessed relief, I mean.
Well, individuals who never irritated any subgeniuses in any way during their lives
will have it much easier than those who...
Are we going to go back to the old...
Because they'll die instantly, practically.
Yeah.
Like switching off a light.
At some point in their lives, irritated a subgenius or inconvenienced one.
However, inadvertently, will suffer pains associated with hell,
the Dante-style hell, as well as modernized versions of subgeniuses.
It's going to be a widespread belief.
Just think how quickly you'd go through the airport, through security.
Oh, it's Reverend Stang going right through.
You know, oh, you'd have to...
Would you like to sit in first class, Reverend Stang?
Oh, well, there won't be airports after the end.
Well, there may be airports, but there'll be the kind of airports
where you're waiting in line with 5,000 other people for...
And there will be radio like this one.
You don't have to do this show 24 hours a day because there's nothing else to listen to.
We'll hate it.
Gotta throw it up in Barcelona.
That's just like us.
That was the way it used to be.
Yeah.
There was nothing but this show for 24 hours a day.
And how far we have fallen.
It's only eight or five hours a day now.
People will pay for the show.
I only do the show one hour and a half a day.
You can only abuse your body most of the time.
Michael Jackson.
Michael Pepe.
I think a broke friend is making these noises this time.
A mysterious device.
They're live.
This isn't a Bob Nelson background tone.
It's not one of Wellman's movie soundtrack collections.
But it made the mascara snake joyful.
It's not something Don Joyce is providing.
It's just not you, Gary.
You know, Gary, that hair, it's just not you.
It's just not me.
It has a life of its own.
Those shoes, those just aren't you, Gary.
Not you.
They're not you, Gary.
You know, it's getting so the teenage girls only grab the bottom half of my hair now
and they leave the top half alone.
What do you think that means?
It's growing farther down toward your crotch.
That's a little hint.
The rest of you are all cops.
Just a subtle hint.
Faces in the crowd.
Just a scruzzle hint.
Nine to five, nobody.
It's their way of saying, not you, Gary.
Are you here?
You're the guys at Red Curbs on Star Trek.
Get out!
You haven't stayed.
You've seen Idiocracy yet?
No, I have not seen Idiocracy, although you're the third person in about three days to mention it.
I just, as soon as it's downloadable, I'm sure I'll have a copy.
What is downloadable?
Oh, well, as soon as I'm home, I'll download it.
From my favorite channel.
Which channel is it on?
Don't play it with your brother.
I don't know, but they have the Fox News channel on it.
It's 500 years in the future.
Oh, cool.
Hello, baby.
Well, my favorite channel is alt.binaries.movies.divx.
Yes, it's on there.
That's one of those non-pay channels.
Hello, baby.
That's the Drummond family in the background.
That's all they do is they spoil, they talk to their baby.
Hello, baby.
That's Philo's rant now.
The baby has a very powerful mind that has taken them over completely.
It has, actually.
That baby might as well be running their lives.
They'll drop everything they're doing just for that baby.
Baby!
Why do they say, sleep like a baby, when babies wake up every two hours?
Tall.
To take an example.
One of the misfits.
I suppose the reason people dislike the way they attribute it to babies are not the cats.
It means that stuff runs out of your mouth and your both ends while you're sleeping.
That's what sleep like a baby really means.
It means you have to be cleaned up after the sleep.
It was so atrocious.
Princess Wee has just walked in, but seems not to have her own microphone.
Or even a chair.
Lady just entered the room, boys.
I'm shortly about to take the next rocket out, in fact.
I've been holding the fort.
There's a chair in there.
You can go sit, if you dare to sit next to Phineas and Arko.
I'm not going.
Yes, Princess Wee Ardo.
Queen of all the UFOs.
But only the unidentified O's.
Could she intercede for us when the UFOs come in the next day?
Could we fall to our knees in front of her and beg her to intercede so that they don't turn us in?
No, because when they come, then they're no longer unidentified.
You know what I'm saying?
What is her relationship with known objects?
That's the drawback to being that particular kind of queen.
Identified flying objects, then.
Yeah, what about known flying objects?
What is she going to do?
She's got no... Those are out of her jurisdiction.
Really?
Those aren't her responsibility.
Want to play with me?
Oh, man.
That's the 60s.
Have I done something wrong?
Bob's still in college.
Where's Glass Madness to sing a little Bob song?
I like Bob better than your Bob, cause your Bob sucks.
He sucks so bad.
We all slack Bob.
If you can kiss my wallet goodbye.
La la la la la la la la la la.
That's a little Bob.
So bad, tiny Bob.
Hey, we both can.
All praise the wolf.
You don't have to buy the best.
Did I hear a little tiny collar?
Little tiny collar.
Teeny, teeny, tiny collar.
Boy, I love you, baby.
Can't I help you?
You are not a toad.
Yeah.
Oh, breathless.
Watch it play me.
Wow, Not You Gary is playing the guitar by rubbing it just against the Harrison's device,
which are like guitar picks.
People will be praying for the end of the world
if it doesn't happen, my friend
People will be praying for the end of the show
if it doesn't change
the atmosphere somehow
Five hours tonight, Over the Edge
and the Puzzling Evidence Show
combined
We're going till five
If only the musicians could hear each other
And no one can stop us
If only we could hear each other
I hear the ocean
and I hear my tinnitus
Hey, guess what, you guys
I've learned that I'm losing my hearing
What? Huh?
They always do that
They cannot help themselves
Well, should I yell louder or what?
Yeah, that actually helps
quite a bit
You have headphones, volume controls under the desk there
The little knobs near every jack
They don't turn it up nearly
That's not a volume control
Oh, that's not a volume control
Oh!
They don't nearly turn it up high enough
but it's better than nothing
Well, it's not the jacks
or the headphones
or even the show
It's unfortunately my ears
You know, I'm really, really, really old
Well, you're mighty close to an electric guitar right now
I'd watch out
Yeah, that's part of the problem
Too many years spent filming my friend's bands
standing in front of the speakers
And now I'm in a situation
I hear these crickets all the time
I used to think they were real crickets
I moved to Ohio in the dead of winter
Princess, we would say,
Listen, hear that?
I'd go, yeah, I hear the crickets
What kind of vehicle did you use to move to Ohio?
I heard these crickets
I know these
Is there a history of this?
We used slaves, actually
to haul the church building itself
You must have got out just in time
Brick by brick
Well, this was Texas under George Bush
So it wasn't that expensive
You know, it wasn't a union
The unions were still out of it
They weren't there yet
We were able to move the church
stone by stone
so to speak, as it were
Brick by brick
floppy disc
by floppy disc
Did you move your frock brick by brick
or did you move it?
It was sort of like Easter
We moved the frock
Oh, I think I am
When they moved the building
they found something horrible underneath it
Well, I named my frock
Festering Expressence
and Spomam Patel
all those years
Dr. Drummond finally arrived
I heard Princess Wee's tackle
Actually, I was in a church building
I've been here just lurking about
listening and calculating
as it were
There she is
I've been repositioning my monitors
I've been recalibrating my whistle
There he is
Yeah, baby
We're swinging as we pucker
Get it
We're pinging and sluffering
You're swucker and pingerin'
Yeah, that's how you feel
The world's only brand new
Well, in that case
I gotta get my Walwart
Here you go
I have a Walwart
and I didn't say Wal-Mart
but I said Wal-Wart
Welcome to Wal-Mart
I love you
So, I'm just gonna say
Look, a price fell
How long will it be before all of us are working as greeters at Wal-Mart?
I'm gonna get a job there
Wal-Mart World
I already am
I know I can get a job there
because that will meet my standard of brain power
Well, they don't P-test you at Wal-Mart
That's one thing about it
I mean, they may not pay you well
or give you any benefits
but they don't P-test
They don't?
Welcome to Wal-Mart
They do?
Yes, and after 20 years
they give you a shirt
What if they give you a shirt
and don't pee?
No
And a cart?
You can live in that place
and they'd never know
People do
I do now
But do they give you a sincerity test?
There's plenty of food
What fluid did they take out for a sincerity test?
There's a mattress to park on
I don't know
but it comes out of the base of your skull
Toilets open all night?
Yeah
Snack food galore?
TV's
His sincerity fluid is slightly too viscous
TV's, DVD's, Wal-Mart
Dr. Drummond would have to use somebody else's
I'm totally depleted on the sincerity solution
Clothing
You never run out of clothing in Wal-Mart
In fact, I was going to try to get a depletion allowance
for my lack of sincerity
If you were living in Wal-Mart, you'd be home now
I've got some synthetic
So the Reverend John Shirley
I think it should be worth some kind of government subsidy
The Piss Baptist must go on about his Piss Baptist duties
You know, there are 10,000 people lined up in the Grand Canyon waiting for me
And I'm a sincerian, you know
There's an enormous vat next to the Grand Canyon
that I use to keep my fluids, the other fluids, replenished and flowing
And everybody is very grateful
Let John Shirley's mercy rain down
You know, the Forest Service is not allowed to say how old the Grand Canyon is
That's what I've heard, yeah
They're not allowed to say this
They said they were going to change that policy
They were going to stop selling that book about how the Grand Canyon is only 4,000 years old
They haven't done it
Because that would infringe on the rights of creationists
to state theories of ancient science
Well, I'm really hungry
My stomach is rumbling
I read in the newspaper that 29% of Americans
I find this hard to believe
but some of them
Some new survey
29% of Americans believe that the sun revolves around the Earth
It doesn't?
Are you saying it doesn't?
Okay, 29.01, I guess
It sounds believable to me
I mean, I can believe in a supernatural being
that's been around since the beginning of time
with no evidence at all
Why can't I believe in something as equally believable
as what you claim?
That appears to be the logic
If I know you can believe
I'm not making it up
Anything that you want to believe
You can be what you want
You can believe what you want, too
Anything you want
Because when you grow up
You can do anything you want
I'm very proud of you, young man
My stomach is really rumbling
I know, it's playing a rumba, isn't it?
Do what thou won't
Do what he won't
You've heard, do what thou wilt, shall be thou won't
The whole of the law, but for the subjeetis it's
Do what they won't shall be the whole of the law
Do what Jesus won't
Do what they won't
The engine of the train
You will
Waves something like 80,000 times
They won't, but you will
What would Jesus not do?
Who would Jesus do?
I forget the actual weight, but it's
Magdalene this year
W-W-N-J
N-D-J
I can't drink it now
G-W-B-B-Q
Jesus won't
You really
You know it's like a hot pot
Princess Weah
And her throne
Somebody wants to get in
Her throne and her sacred microphone is ready
You know, it turned out Princess Weah was actually the daughter of
of
Darth Hater
The Doctor Goon
The Doctor Goon, the singer from outer space?
Yeah, Doctor Goon, one of those guys
One of those ass guys
amino acids
You like me?
I'm going to escort the Piss Baptist to his limousine helicopter.
Well, steering the show is sort of like trying to jump on a big man's baby.
Dear friend.
This is what it sounds like in my brain just before I go to bed.
I know that you think that sounds funny.
Okay, now I've got some catalogs here I want to read from.
Okay.
Do you have my catalogs ready?
I'm ready to recite my catalog copy now.
This is Charles Collins at a testing laboratory in Houston, Texas.
Switches have just been turned.
There was already so much money in there.
The human brain.
The human being is about to receive an outer sink.
That many fingers with lots of neurons.
It will never wrinkle or decay.
Have you ever asked yourself how much are major companies willing to pay you to create a show like this one?
It's true.
From health supplements to credit cards.
They do it because.
It's good.
And it can bring in millions.
This is like a dream come true.
I have a retired lifestyle and 39 bucks to spend.
But I didn't care.
Remember there's no risk.
No risk.
I was just so busy that I bought this.
I have no money.
No risk.
I'm going to go buy this.
Well, after a while that's gone.
I'm going to go buy a car.
No risk.
I let go of my hair a long time ago.
It seemed to be getting like an ever increasingly disharmonious endeavor.
So I decided, along with my $10,000, to check in to the local.
I was reading Bob's note, and there I found out that he was a great guy and a very successful copywriter.
You'll be hearing a lot about him once you start our new program.
Oh yes, I almost forgot.
How swiftly can you change your career?
I like you.
Thank you.
You did it.
Wait for me out on the road.
I'll be right back.
Oh my God, this is still going on.
Okay, all right, all right.
We arranged the...
Let's do the show now.
The show can start now because we rearranged the studio into three sectors.
There's two sectors for...
Married people and their children.
And then there's the main room, which is for the lonely geeks.
Phineas, Don Joyce, and...
Sad old bachelors.
Weeping.
You can hear them weeping and hollering.
Over 300 years ago...
Ideally...
Tiny...
Great...
Wow.
Like they say, a boy.
Really?
It's a lie!
Really.
Say it like I did when I was young and grew up in Freelance.
Small turned mud all over my body.
You wouldn't do it with a explosion.
You could live in a nuestra chinchin.
You've got to watch your board, don't you?
Uh, now what?
Wh-w-what is that?
My name's Tony Gonzalez.
just transgressed my personal space.
Violated.
He violated me.
I feel raped.
And it was good, too.
I loved it.
I loved violating your personal spaces.
I feel raped.
I feel used.
Yeah, because we here at the one pretty true church,
the first church of the last lap,
kicks a subgenie's ass every time.
Listen to that fake Texas accent.
Every time.
That is the fakest Southern accent.
Oh, you look at these boots.
Smell the bottom of my boots.
That's the fakest smelling cow hockey I ever smelt.
Well, just look at my...
Is that my tinnitus or is that the show?
It's the show, dear.
It's just the show.
It's gotten to where my hearing, really, it's true,
my hearing's gotten so bad that Princess Wee has to translate for me.
And she plays...
She plays tricks on me by mistranslating things.
The waitress says,
that'll be $30.
And Princess Wee says,
she says she wants to have a three-way.
And then I end up humiliated and embarrassed.
And they all think it's funny.
People make fun of old deaf persons like myself.
Now, I don't want to forget my students.
And the subgenius how to make your own cult, do's and don'ts.
Oh, K-Rob has arrived.
The mighty K-Rob.
That means the sound quality may improve.
Uh-huh.
Listeners, there is hope.
Undoubtedly.
What the fuck?
Oh, no.
Michael Pepe, as I suspected.
Michael Pepe.
Michael Pepe even arrived.
That means the station will be on the air for another half an hour or so.
Before the Pepe effect works in.
Before we're publicized.
Pepe kind of looks like Philo's new daughter.
Michael Pepe has a new...
This is Philo's daughter.
No, that's Philo, not his daughter.
Philo's daughter is the one with the mutton chops in the other room.
Yes, Dr. Drummond and Mrs. Chaos McBobcat
have a new daughter.
They have brought their baby, their new infant child, Michael Pepe.
You can hear it crying now.
Pardon me, Michael.
I'm in headphones and you're not on a mic, so I can't...
Nothing makes any...
You said something about how many eyes does it have?
Only three.
Actually, my nephew, Alex, today asked a question.
He seriously asked me,
Hey, if you had three eyes,
would you be able to see the fourth dimension?
And I said no, because the fourth dimension
isn't something that you see.
So eyes are not the sense organ you need.
Your time sense would be able to...
You smell in the future.
Somehow.
Is the sense the future sense of smell?
Will you see the fifth dimension?
Well, they broke up.
The fifth dimension, I think, broke up.
The fourth dimension is cool.
What is that noise in the background?
Is that the show?
Yeah, it's puzzling evidence.
He puts on weird things and he leaves.
He's holding on to something.
Michael Pepe, you have to get on a microphone
for anyone to hear you.
I'm deaf now,
so I've been reading your lips so far,
but the radio audience can't hear that.
I sat down and...
He thinks I'm joking.
These kids these days,
they just walk around like zombies.
We just cussed each other out in sign language.
Hey, I learned sign language the other day.
The sign...
Okay, radio listeners,
the sign for sex is this.
And the sign for cactus is this.
Spiky, spiky.
So when you see somebody
want to have kinky sex with,
you go like that,
and then spiky, spiky.
And then you go like...
The sex symbol, of course,
is the old temple of Devo
with the finger...
That's the formal, polite way of saying sex.
Now, if you turn your fingers around like this,
that's butt sex,
or in 69, it's like that.
The sex symbol, friends,
is actually two fingers
of each hand
tapping together on the end.
Like if you made two little fingers,
you could walk along the tabletop
using your fingers.
You put those two figures together
and tap them together.
Yeah, but Uranus is not a planet.
Uranus is not a planet.
My anus is.
You have to get on a microphone, Michael,
or it doesn't really...
Nothing you say really exists.
Is that Michael Poupe?
Now, my students listening...
Give me the hook.
Get the hook.
Maybe logic.org class,
online class,
Church of the Subgenius,
should know
that this is the subgenius
business meeting.
Michael Poupe is here,
so I have to hook myself up.
Business meeting.
Well, what is the business?
The business is...
We're trying to untangle
the true history of the church.
Bob assigned us
to do a commission
to study the...
What went wrong
during the previous
church administration.
The previous administration
of the church
made many mistakes,
and we're trying to delineate
what happened
decade by decade
since, well,
for the last 100 years.
And then what happened?
The bad permit having to do
with the elimination
of the Gary Factor.
Once Gary was eliminated...
Well...
Not you, Bob.
Not you.
Gary's finally added up
to where the church
is going to suffer badly.
And right now...
Actually, that started
several years ago
on July 7th, 1987,
when Gary stormed out
of the studio saying,
I've had it with you guys.
Don't call me.
I'll call in the show.
I remember that.
That was the funniest thing
he ever did.
Who?
That was.
I hated to say that,
but I'm glad you just put that
out on the table
because I wanted to comment on that,
but I really didn't want to be the one
to bring the subject up.
I thought it was a great bit.
Now, one point of contention
is when exactly was
J.R. Bob Dobbs born?
Some say that it was
in the early 20s,
but we're looking now
at 1927 or 1929.
It was a midnight clear.
We know that.
Bob was born in my late 20s.
Yeah, we know it was
on a midnight clear
and we know that it was
in a cheap motel.
How else could they land?
We know that in 1945,
Bob killed Hitler again
and he met Philo in 1950
in college.
Well, you know,
that means I'm old.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, Gramps.
Now, in 1953,
Bob was immaculated
and the countdown to X-Day began.
Unfortunately,
it ended prematurely
and had to start again,
but we don't know where to start exactly
because we don't know where it ends.
Welcome to school.
I'm Principal Bob McKenzie.
In 1955,
Bob had his second,
pre-vision.
My vice-principal, Doug.
And, uh,
in 1956,
Princess Wea
was born.
When did Bob get sternocryptal?
1955.
1955 sterno was pregnant?
1950 and five.
And then eight years later,
Jane was born.
That's right.
It says so here.
In 1957,
some bad boys got me to sit on a cactus
by telling me it was the king's throne.
It was evil, evil, fast.
And, uh, I, my parents spent the afternoon
pulling tiny cactus spines out of my behind.
You're lucky you didn't have my parents.
They pounded the X spice into it.
Well, I was, I was spoiled.
I'll admit it.
I was a spoiled child.
Okay.
Please, I was born in a place like this.
I don't like this.
In 1959,
Bob started producing movies.
Like, uh,
Is this KPFA or is this DC?
Attack of the Giant Shrew People.
Uh, it's KP Yo Mama.
I didn't get that criticism.
I was...
KPFU?
It was undoubtedly a criticism,
but I couldn't make it out.
If you could call back and criticize us again,
we would very much appreciate it.
We'll all be quiet and listen to your criticisms.
Your constructive criticisms about...
He said something like,
Is this KPFA or is this...
And then I missed it.
So I don't know what we were being compared with.
Yeah.
It could be the mad God,
communist, insane, you know...
Grand people.
Yes.
I don't know.
We should look up more people
requests from
Anything is possible today.
You don't hammer a nail.
The nail causes the hammer to go up and with the human gripping.
And how do you feel about that, Sam?
I feel satisfied that the church has progressed as predicted.
I'm scared.
If this was the year 1963.
The manor's still alive.
We are still alive.
Is this the noisiest show?
Oh, princess, we think how pleasant our show, our slack is.
I'm trying to control it, but it's out of hand.
It's got a Don Joyce of its own.
This is Walter Bloom at Times Square in New York City,
returning you to Charles Collins in Texas.
Five, four, three, two, one.
As I looked at the strange devices before me,
I find it difficult to understand or even believe.
I believe it.
I believe that this show sounds better when they play tapes of other shows on it.
Good work, everyone.
But I knew what to expect when I was born.
They told me.
They gave me instructions for life when I was born
and told me what to expect.
Unlike others.
They're just people.
They just have to blunder and bluff their way through.
Unfortunately, I lost the instruction book when I was about five.
I had to be toilet trained all over again.
We have a long day ahead of us, so we should begin with a two-hour recess.
I kept having to call tech support for life.
Get up and go out.
Go to your side.
Good day.
Okay, now we're starting.
I'm going to go to bed.
Okay.
Good.
Good night.
This show reminds me of my hearing test, which I flunked.
My voice.
I'll wait until someone phones in where the pieces fell.
Gary Gebrogfred here has a special electronic guitar that, with every turn, he can play
Every time he touches one of the strings, it creates a whole new show.
It's like a sampler.
And each note of each string has a separate show that plays back.
Princess Wee is playing her messages over the microphone.
I'm going to go to bed.
I'll wait.
Then maybe we'll be finally knowing what the flying saucers are.
Who are the masters of the UFO?
Two to three to six feet, nine to twelve, twenty to six, twelve to three to nine.
Oh, no.
Standing next to me is a technical expert.
A fanatical group all together have a comfortable feeling that they're all friends of each other.
The people who are not on a microphone in the other studio are all laughing because they're having fun.
The people who are on microphones and listening to the show all look grim.
Maybe we should get off the microphones and join the party.
Just go jam. Just go jam out.
No, the jamming is happening right here. Gary is doing all the jamming.
I'm just waiting until you jam this thing.
He's been jamming it into the edge of the table and onto the equipment.
Jammed it into the microphone. Jammed it into his crowd.
Oh, clambering cacophony of symphonic proportion.
Uh, they're all very much exciting to see the true thing.
You can see it in any political party. There's always a fringe of fanatics in any political party.
So a lot of people think the world's his.
and 2012.
Yeah, but the reason I think that is because
of the Mayan calendar running out of numbers, right?
Right, that's Frank Zappa's birthday.
But that's just another bunch of arbitrary
numbers made by humans.
Why should nature and the exos and the world
ending depend on silly, arbitrary
human numbering traditions?
Oh, it's just a coincidence.
Oh, just a coincidence. Yeah, that's what they all say.
Except for the scientists who say that nothing is a coincidence
and it's all a meaningful, mystical message from Bob.
Well, the real good scientists.
The mystical message music now.
Let's get on with the mystical message.
I thought the music and the sound was itself the mystical message.
The answer, Mr. Collins, lies in a system called prepared curing.
I thought the bared curing was the mystical message.
A surface each person lives within is treated with a chemical
reactant in the cat. It is then dried at low temperatures
so as not to set the cat.
When we have the shape of each human being in question,
we eat it with this device.
The educational film in the background is describing where babies come from.
Chicago.
That's pretty much where my...
Yeah, Chicago.
That's where my dad explained it that way.
Really?
He said babies are poured into a little mold.
They have a mold, a person mold, and they pour the baby juice in there and the baby comes out.
That's what they mean by that? Yeah. That's what they mean by that? Yeah.
That's what they mean by breaking the mold.
Babies came from friendly 13-year-old girls.
Really?
Yeah.
I understand you think I'm right.
Babies come from friendly 13-year-old girls, he said.
That's what he said.
In some countries, that is correct.
Yes.
In many countries, that's correct.
As I keep reminding Princess We whenever we're watching a movie like Peter Pan or Lemony Snicket or Harry Potter.
I go, look!
You know, in many countries, those girls would be married by now.
They'd be grandmothers.
Not quite grandmothers, dear.
There's nothing wrong with that.
...to people in the third seat.
There's nothing wrong with it, is there?
I mean, not that there's anything wrong with it.
That's what they always say when there really is something wrong with it.
Why?
Are you having some kind of attention deficit disorder?
They do.
Is that what's wrong with you?
And they feel a bit cozy with each other.
Hey, Reverend Stang, I got a couple of extra catalogs over here.
Oh, is it time to read catalogs, Dr. Drummond?
Yeah.
You know, that's my favorite part of this show.
When you read the catalogs at random.
Hold on a minute. I'm gonna bring one over to you.
If it wasn't for that, I'd have nothing to edit out of your shows when I replay them on Hour of Slime.
Yeah, I've edited the best catalog readings out.
Oh, he really does have a catalog.
He just handed one to me. Now I can say,
Dynamite Discount Deals, Authentic,
Freethlining, Real Leather,
Bill Taker,
I can't do it as well as Dr. Drummond, though.
Nobody can read a catalog like Philo.
Now it's easier than ever to stay connected with friends, family, and colleagues around the world.
Philo, I notice that you're better at reading those catalogs.
I read catalogs right when Dr. Howell is coming to a dramatic crescendo.
Sleek, powerful, and completely portable.
On the go, in the car, at home, or in the office.
I've studied the dynamics of this show.
The perfect self-contained system.
Eliminate the hassles.
But Dr. Drummond, what does that have to do with our topic?
Always Make Clear.
Hey, is Bishop Joey running away?
You lucky son of a bitch.
Don't you remember? Every third word, the listeners are supposed to take the whole show,
cut it up into pieces, extract every third word, compile it,
then recite it backwards for the arcane secret messages hidden within.
We can't do it where it's too easy.
We have to, you know, perform something.
Some kind of upgrade, memory transfer, hard drive, uh, uh, refragmentation.
Not a defrag this time, but a refrag.
We're gonna refrag the hard drive.
We don't know why we have to do it.
We're possessed to do it.
But in the meantime...
...an instant plastic surgery, butchering murder.
Are we gonna get to the, uh, the business portion of the show?
When are we supposed to do the business meeting?
What is the business?
I've got a budget I gotta tell you guys about.
How I legally robbed a bank last month for over $87,978 and got away with it.
Well, let's split.
Let's split the money? Okay.
Both, both.
I don't mind because I'll easily make that much this month.
Okay.
Okay, now I wanna know, how does the listener digest the show in such a way that it enters the brain pan according to the pre-scribed pathways?
Hey, I drained my brain pan last night. What's your excuse?
What did you see?
I seen a flying saucer come down about a half mile from my ranch house.
Started this morning when I was going after lost calves.
He swears the saucer's undamaged, Dr. Brunson.
Ha.
Ha!
Oh, gross!
Test, test.
Is this show still on?
Chest, chest.
Chest.
Is this show still on?
And there's the other question.
Ha.
Ha!
Has the blessed one just turned out to be the best?
It's the best show right now.
Yes, it's the best show so far.
far from it.
I did too, unfortunately.
This is Charles Collins
reporting on one of the miracles of our time.
Sex disinformation tape.
It's actually a commercial.
We are ready to switch you over to a home
in Cleveland, Ohio,
where a family prepares for this experience.
Now how coincidental is that?
That's my house! Hey, they're showing our house!
Talk about your coincidences.
How can it be?
Stand by, please.
What's happening?
There's somebody standing next to our house.
No, don't be anxious. Stand by, please.
Wait a second.
No, no, stand by.
Can you just hop from one foot to the other?
Please stand by.
I'm hopping, I'm hopping.
People, people, please stand by.
You say hurry up.
Hello?
Don't all rush around in a little gaggle of peace.
I gotta go!
What's going on here?
Where's the bathroom?
Keep your hands at your sides and stand by.
Passing out.
Don't touch anything.
It's all pot.
Stolen by Ivan Stang
when he escaped from Texas
in a 1953 Chevrolet.
Two times.
No, Philo has the prop, not me.
Everybody accuses me of being the one with all the prop.
It was Philo.
That's what we're hoping, Pope.
That's what we want from a Pope.
You know, as a Pope myself,
I did bring some, of course.
You're a Pope?
I'm a Pope.
Yeah, I'm a Pope.
We're all Popes.
That's right.
They call me Michael Popey, ladies and gentlemen.
I'm a Pope with my old bathroom.
They're just kidding.
I thought you were like a favorite.
I'm a Pope with my old bathroom.
Yeah, I know.
And Pope Pep and all that.
Yeah, that'd be the second.
It was the first King to know
to have ordered pygmies to dance.
This is all.
Ladies and gentlemen,
a new subgenius has entered the world.
And he smiles immediately.
He was, as I said that.
Last year, I spent five weeks
in this booby baby.
So named for her diet.
Her, excuse me,
a genie, a subgeni.
She's now picking her nose on the air.
This is, of course,
a natural subgenius reaction
to being on the air.
Actually, if you'll notice,
the uber booby baby is wearing
a natural reaction.
The latest Bob bib.
That's right.
Everyone.
There is also a bib with Bob on it.
Bob the faceless.
Oh, yeah.
Birth defect.
Yeah.
Bob bib.
I'm not kidding.
You can actually go to
CafePress.com.
It's a genius shop.
And there's a Bob bib
as well as the Bob bib.
I got your mail.
This is a Christine Bob bib.
It hasn't been drooled
or vomited on in hours.
She loves Bob.
That's very clear.
It was.
Pretty blue eyes.
Your butts look big in those pants.
What's her name?
What's your daughter's name?
Can you hear me?
My daughter?
Uber booby baby.
That's on her first certificate.
Drum it.
Or
or
and praise the amino acids
heard here in the background
in their new album
Humanity will fall like pins
and will they not?
Ah, yes, yes, yes.
Dollar sign.
B-O-B space.
L-O-V-E-S space.
Y-O-U colon.
B-U-T space.
H-E space.
L-O-V-E-S space.
M-O-N-E-Y space.
E-V-E-N space.
M-O-R-E period.
Dollars and cents.
There is a fifth Bob beyond that which is known to Bob.
It is Bob as vast as Bob and as timeless as Bob.
It is the middle Bob between Bob and Bob between Bob and Bob.
And it lies between the Bob of man's fobs and the Bob of his Bob.
This is the Bob of a Bob.
It is an area which we call the...
Self genius.
Power of...
SWAT.
How about some Bob?
Bob.
Maybe you're finished mister.