He's coming.
They don't want to shoot him.
David, I'm afraid.
Be quiet.
There he is.
Look at his face now, David.
Yes.
I see it.
It's composed.
It looks human again.
Perhaps we're not meant to tamper with the natural.
So genius.
Powerful.
Quiet.
He's looking this way.
It's me, though.
No, don't do it.
He's still coming.
The story of Bob goes back in time to the very beginning of time.
And it's a tale that keeps repeating itself throughout the centuries.
Oh, yeah, he's the worst.
He's the absolute worst there is.
Whatever you've got, it'll be worse after you see him.
He's just a butcher.
A man's a butcher.
And then there's always that, make sure that you tell him that, you know, you know me.
Why?
What's the difference?
He's a doctor.
What is it?
Oh, you know Bob.
Okay, I'll give you the real medicine.
I don't know.
I'm gonna make you want it, and then I'm gonna call it.
I'm gonna return everything, and then you'll burn it.
This is not a joke, and we used to say that.
My friend Bob had shock treatments.
My friend Lars had shock treatments.
Uh, excuse me?
Uh-huh?
Do you have any condoms?
Sorry, I didn't hear what you said.
Condoms?
Oh, condoms, sure.
What kind you want?
Quiet ones.
Let me just get the blue.
Three-pack or 12-pack?
Three.
12-pack is cheaper.
Look, can you just get me some condoms?
I don't have change of a 20.
Hey, Bob, you have change of a 20?
You gotta have change of a 20.
Bob, the man needs his condoms.
You know what? Just keep it.
Just keep it.
Hi.
I'm Bob.
This is Paul.
Hi, Paul.
So, why'd you contact us, man?
Oh, you look like you kept shape, Philip.
Yeah, I work out.
But you know the way it is.
Time passes, we all change.
Do we ever.
Yeah, well, some more than others.
I don't know quite how to put this, Bob.
You didn't tell me anything, Philip.
Okay, it's Philippa now.
But if you still want me, I'm in.
Say it.
Say what?
My name is Roger.
I'm an addict in recovery.
Ha, ha, ha.
No, no, you say it.
My name is Bob, and I'm an addict in recovery.
And today is the first day in the rest of my life.
My name is Michelle, and I'm an addict.
Hello, Michelle.
My name is Anne, and I am an addict.
Hello, Anne.
My name is Chris.
I am an addict.
Hello, Chris.
My name is Bob, and I'm an addict.
Hello, Bob.
Secure that Bob statue.
Boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom.
Another beer one bottle.
Danke.
Gul Erdogan.
Thank you.
Bob is the real thing
I really like going to church
but it used to be that if I didn't get there half hour early
I couldn't get a seat up front and then I couldn't hear anything
but now that I have ear zoom
it doesn't matter where I sit
I can hear everything perfectly
The Subgenius
Power of
Spark
Hey Lee, listen now
do me a favor will ya?
I got a hot date tonight with Connie
knock on my door, wake me up in 20 minutes alright?
No, no, no, this is evolutionary
I've been reading this book on Leonardo
da Vinci
see that means from Vinci, did you know that?
Must be some book
Yeah, well it turns out that the master slept only 20 minutes
every 3 hours
now that works out to 2 and a half extra days
that I'm awake per week, every week
which means if I live to be 80
I will have lived the equivalent
of 105 years
Alright people, I'd like to begin
with a hearty hail and well met good fellow
to Bob joining us from Business Affairs
Thanks
Hi everybody
Bob, we have a little baptism by fire
for you so to speak
Poor bastard
Let me speak with the manager, excuse me
Bob?
You might think it's lame
to play the rap game
It all sounds the same, the dummies with the fame
Give me half a chance to sell
out with no shame
Very, very selfish
My number one interest is me
No contest, I might sound thoughtless
But still you bought this
Some call it ignorance
But me I call it bliss
Very, very selfish
Selfish man
Do it again
Used to think small
But now I walk tall
I know I'll have it all
I heard my duty call
I'm sick how I rhyme
And I'm sick how I ball
Very, very selfish
If you listen to this track
And it kinda takes you back
To your day smoking crack
Trying to chase the heart attack
Well let me tell you son
you weren't accomplishing jack
Very, very selfish
Selfish man
Selfish man, selfish man, do it again
Selfish man, selfish man, selfish man, do it again
You might think it's lame to play the rap game
It all sounds the same, the dummies with the fame
Give me half a chance to sell out with no shame
Very, very selfish, very, very selfish
Selfish
That's a, um, a pink, yeah, pink, we're, uh, we're pink, yeah
Yeah
Oh boy
Yeah, boy, boy
Uh
Yeah
Hey, Bobby
I'd offer you coffee, but my assistant is using a vacation time
Okay
Good time, too
Everyone but the bandits will be slacking off till after the new year anyway
Oh, I like this
And it's pink
I'll get you a pink wherever you want
I had a great time
The whole hour just flew by
I'll get that
Oh, thanks, Bobby
You don't want to have any regrets
I should know
What do you mean?
Well, I had a dream, too
I was gonna be a professional wrestler, man
I was gonna call myself Bobzilla
Bobzilla
Give me five more minutes on the name, dude
Well, it all went well, I guess, but I'm not gonna be a professional wrestler, man
It's not gonna work out fine
And now for the main event
In this corner, he's nasty
He's dirty
He lives under the refrigerator
Ladies and germs
The Roach
And in this corner
He's the best at controlling the pest
The man with a plan to put the bug in the can
The champion
Bobzilla
And I crushed my dreams
Everything I wanted to be
Bob's Bugs Be Gone was the death of me
I'm Bob from Bob's Bugs Be Gone
You call me for all your pest control needs
I will kill your bug's dreams
Bob's Bugs Be Gone is not affiliated with Robert's Bugs Be Gone or Bo's Bugs Be Gone or Bob's Bugs Be Good
Bob is not responsible for property damage due to hive removal, pest sterilization, or larval dispersion
Bugs Be Gone will not handle snakes longer than five and one-half feet in length.
Arachnids with two thoraxes, bats of any kind, or the dreaded vinegaroon.
Bob offers free termite inspections and $30 off for the purchase of an annual contract.
Bob is an Equal Opportunity Employer, Seattle, Espanol.
Bob, Bob, no me olvide.
El es Bob.
No me olvide.
El se nombre Bob.
Mom.
Is SAMUEL occupation club,
Bob start in our.
In the cannot.
¿Cómo se dice Bob?
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
El se nombre Bob.
Would you please just get on with the stupid Bob story?
Well, I'm on the phone with Bob, and I realize right then and there that I need to return this pair of pants.
So I'm off to the store.
What happened to Bob?
Well, nothing. His part of the story is done.
The only one they have in stock is Pink.
And the Pink sent me over the top.
We use Pink to rehabilitate a dog today.
How do you like that? It's not the Pink.
Everybody knows that.
We make sure that Pink was part of the family.
I think that's the most important part.
We put a cat and a dog together.
We make the humans become a path leader.
He was communicating with them.
What do you think?
I think Rockefeller was crazy that night.
He got away with the money.
How can we stop them?
We can stop them by stopping the Pink Boys.
If we stop the Pink Boys, we can stop them murdering and they're killing and they're stealing and they're persifying us.
But it's so difficult.
Oh, Jerry, don't let the boy out of the house.
Be brave. Be brave.
Oh, always be brave.
Because...
The women saves us.
Greetings to you, Earthlings.
I am Princess Dragomon.
I have taken over this planet.
Now I own the Earth and you'll be my slaves for all eternity.
The disasters you experienced are just small examples of our great power.
Either surrender to me or I'll destroy all humans.
I've spoken.
It's all the warning you're going to get from me.
You'll be destroyed.
They don't sleep, either.
They're not emotional,
angels don't have any emotions.
Another and worse war will break out.
And you see a night with a strange light in the sky.
You will know it is a sign that the world is about to be punished for its crime.
Do you have an empty moment?
By 1998, Every normal,
Mediocrity,
Pink boy,
Adman,
Treki and Hippy is gonna be trying to ain't your bs,
get on board with the good ship dogs or they're gonna fry along with everybody else when those
aliens get here of course such a prophecy immediately arises our cynicism is it possible
that the end of the world will come in july 1999 perhaps or is it just another of those
prognostications which have haunted man through the ages such a forewarning of ultimate doom
could generally be dismissed out of hand but for the fact that many of nostradamus's other prophecies
have already been fulfilled but the old ones are coming back
i'm going to let them through the tools of conquest do not necessarily come with bombs and
explosions and fallout no sometimes they come with jr bob dobbs and a subgenius membership pack ah
yes
yes yes yes friends our first live show since we were alive at x day we've been using those
canned ever since then and frankly i just got tired of it also i was missing lonesome cowboy dave
yeah i was lonesome for dave and he should be calling in at some point very soon but i'll
i'll have time to do the credits this time maybe um the little swath of
this free talk cast typingغ
let's see let's see
disbooking
but we'll RAIL intelig gäller
collagists like The Large
who did most of the
stuff that, collage
type cut up stuff that we've been hearing.
But also
we had
the Lemur, the great Fernand and Andy
Lemur is back.
Yay!
And he does PR News.
He's doing those new again.
Although I'm still using his old title
credits.
The song,
the
Nombre Bob
in Spanish
was sung by Priestess Pisces
with several fisted tales of Connie
behind her live.
Including Reverend Angry Larry,
Suds Bichot I think, Dr. Philodrum
and maybe Dr.
Sinister on drums. I don't
remember.
The sort of anti-rap
song you might
call it. Very, very selfish
was by the Psychoskeletons.
Who can be found at
soundclick.com
slash the psychoskeletons
from, really
I think the psychoskeletons are mostly
Reverend Basil.
He's the
Basil part of the
psychoskeletons. I don't know if they're really
even skeletons. I don't know either.
That may just be a band name. Yeah.
I don't know. But you just, you
never know.
This music in the background is
the Flyin' Ryan Brothers.
Good musician friends.
They're unusual among subgeniuses
as is
this horrible character
here heard in the background
or the foreground.
I'm hurting in the background.
Rumpel Foreskin is
on the line.
Say it again
and have the chill bling.
That's what grandma used to say.
At least
somebody's grandmother said that. I don't know.
You had a grandmother?
I had quite a few grandmothers in my
tasty young days. I was
fond of elderly ladies.
I used to seek them out on buses and
tramways and various
means of escapes.
I hope they returned your love, Dave.
They returned my love, usually with a
punch in the jaw.
Well, that means they really care about you.
Yeah. That they really got off is what
you're supposed to say.
I'm not up on the hip
lingo these days
with the kids and all.
Yeah, I know they're hard to
rectify.
All those laws.
Well, speaking of rectifying,
the erections are coming up,
as it were.
By the time most people outside
of Cleveland hear this show,
it'll be three weeks later than we're doing
this show. Dave and I talked about this earlier
today. I said,
we can't be too
current because most people won't hear it for three
weeks. So if you talk about today's
murder, mass murder of the day,
nobody's going to know
what you're talking about three weeks from now.
Because there'll have been
three weeks worth of
mass murders per day.
You're practicing time control right now.
Yeah.
And you have to now because those
school murders happen every what?
I guess they figured out there's something
like that every three and a half weeks.
Every school day
at quarter of three,
they just can't wait that extra
15 minutes before the bell rings.
And I know just how they feel.
If I'd had a handgun back then,
ding dong. Yeah,
I wouldn't be here now.
That would have been the end of principal poop
and all the other lackeys who used to hang around
the basement making weird paddles
at wood design or wood shop,
you know, the guys
would give you a ride like when you're supposed
to be taking driver's education and they
forearm you right in the nose and sometimes
it would like splinter and go in your eye.
Did your
shop teachers drill holes in those
paddles?
Yeah.
Yeah, it's to snag the meat.
Make them go.
Sizzle through the air faster
and hit you harder.
It is a weird way of in a culinary way.
It is a weird way of looking at all
that meat being paddled
that way with so many little holes
making a texture. I guess
there would probably be like a veal dish
or something.
Now my mouth is kind of watering.
I'm thinking of some of the butts.
Some of
them. Isn't there a
political party of big butted
people, the big ass party or
something like that?
That's the gop.
Not always. Some
of the gops are skinny.
I know one gop who started out
with a gigantic huge
butt and now he wears about the same size pants
I did. Uh-huh. Which isn't
saying a whole lot for my butt
actually to tell the truth.
But we have, you know,
other cliches.
to cover. And it's a silly butt
at that. I wish I could have watched some
sort of like Martian political
campaign rally and stuff. It's like
I, I, did you hear
um, Vice-Hair
Prime Minister, next checker
um, Von Clinton speak?
No. I actually listened
to that like an idiot and I was like
boy, those are the good old days
and old Bill was in there and uh
hey, nobody cares. Mostly honestly
had to do with business. Didn't have to do with
what you did with your, uh,
I thought he was pretty moderate for a Republican.
Yeah. Clinton.
Yes.
For that matter, that's the way I think
about Obama, but
Yeah. You know, I've
got a whole different, a new approach. I've
decided, Dave, that
and this is why I didn't listen to Clinton's
speech or any of that stuff. I'm
gonna, from now on, I'm not gonna vote
I'm not gonna vote according to what
the candidates say, but what their fans
say on Yahoo News comments.
I'm gonna judge the political
parties by their representatives
on Yahoo News dot com.
Well done, my dear.
These changes towards mental retardation amongst
the whole population are coming real quickly
so why not capitalize on them now and
even be the Varfisa or the
Elephant Organ or some other vessel
you know, for such a meandering
you know, so to speak.
Well, it's kind of like a reverse
barometer. I'll judge if
if in their comments they do
everything they're accusing their
opponents of, then that's the party I'll vote
against.
Oh, if they're doing what their party
says they're against
then you will vote against
them. No, if they do everything they're
accusing their Yahoo
dot com opponents of, for instance
a typical one would be
lib turds are
so stooped
and ignoratious they
can't do anything but name
calling because they're all
lazy racist
communists who are childish
and can't
spiel right
right
so
or if they say, what was the other thing?
Nobody I know ever got polled
well, we're all being polled
all the time
but you can choose the way you're going to get
screwed. Some ways are fun.
You have to learn the right angle
to bend over. That's about it.
You have to produce some sort of identification
in your forehead usually
and you put a little microchip in your pineal gland
so you don't have to worry about the voting machine being corrupted
you just walk in there and stare at a blank screen
for a few seconds and then walk away after you've been given your commands
Right. They installed those things when we were little kids in the 50s
Yep.
If we were little kids in the 50s, of course
the ones that they put in us, our generation
had mercury in them and
and uh
uh
,ões comédica
to aboard
prosák
las peruán
they put those things in uh
what were these things?
trajetoria
he, porque
pokers
uh
o
Dem summertime
bel aviv
,,
right now. It's stalled.
I can hear
fan noise coming off of it.
Well, I think the battery's still functional.
I don't know about the ignition switch.
Well,
see, yours is the reverse
of mine. My battery's fine,
but I have trouble getting it. I have to kickstart
my forehead.
And you have to use big, big boots
to do it with, and you have to keep stomping
afterwards and saying these weird
clockwork orange phrases and stuff
like, you'll get
and bother
bugger off and stuff.
Well, we don't have to. You and me get paid for
coming up with those.
Oh, yeah.
I just got a check here,
and I can't find it.
It was somewhere. I left it next to my
way.
Do you think the currency...
Do you think we should take Bob's name
off the currency?
I think Bob's name should be more
places and more...
arcane number symbology across
all of the currency.
I'm with you, Dave.
More Bob on the currency.
I miss the old Bobhead
nickels.
But we cannot crucify man
upon a cross of Bob
as...
Who says?
We can now. No, of course, back then
you couldn't. You can now.
You can crucify a person on Bob.
You just nail them to Bob.
Just right on top.
Yeah. You should nail your hands
or your victim's hands to his
hands and the feet
to Bob's feet.
Bob's your uncle.
Or Bob's your cross to bear.
big bird hung around your neck.
What's that big old bird?
You know, that big eagle or a buzzard or something
hanging around your neck. Albatross, that's it.
Yes. Albuquerque.
What? It's like having...
I mean, the whole state of New Mexico
and the ancient mariner
all intertwined and stuck around your head
while you're on the ground and you're crying
and laughing at the same time
because, you know,
bowel movements have changed radically
over the last three minutes
and you just can't focus
or anything. I don't know.
Hey, hey, is Al there? I want to talk to Al.
Albatross. Is that Albatross
here?
Not yet.
Al. Albatross.
How'd you like...
Al. Is there a how'd you like it
kid here?
I've heard that tape too many times.
And yet, once a month
somebody sends me that tape.
The two you are called.
Yeah, that's why I'll cut your belly
open and make you look at all the black
stuff you got in there.
That was my favorite line
until I overused it.
Oh, man.
Nobody I know is going to vote
for that guy.
No, what you mean is
nobody you know has told you
they're going to vote for that guy
because you've already told them what you think
about those who are going to vote for that guy.
So they'll just keep their mouth
shut and
let you rant and rave.
Yes, and nod
their heads politely and
look at their watch every 15 seconds
and eventually go,
Oh, I've got to... Oh, man, I'm sorry.
I have to go
return a library bug.
I've got a Blockbuster tape that's overdue.
VHS tape.
It's overdue 10 years.
I've got to find a Blockbuster
to return it.
I'm so happy to see those guys
go under. I had a personal grudge
against Blockbuster because they had a
personal grudge against Bob.
J.R. Bob Dobbs. What did they say?
Well, what happened was
in the 90s
our feature,
our length video, Arise,
actually got picked up for
distribution by Polygram.
And Polygram, amazingly enough,
sold it to the main video
renters of that year, which were...
Remember Sound Whorehouse?
I remember...
Well, they, Sound Warehouse,
bought 800 copies
of Arise to put in
all their stores.
And then a month later, they were bought by Blockbuster,
which was making a big name for itself
as a Christian company.
And Blockbuster, the next month,
had Sound Warehouse return all their copies
of Monty Python's Life of Brian
and Arise, and probably
some other things. But not, you know,
I murdered the babysitter, or
I'm the serial killer.
I burn your skin, I eat your
scabs, or any of those.
They still rented those.
Last Temptation of Christ.
Oh, yeah, right, right. Well, this was
before that time.
We got in trouble for doing a remake of that,
actually.
We didn't think it was bloody enough.
But, yeah, Blockbuster
had all of those Arise copies
returned, and after that,
Polygram didn't have any hope for us,
and they ignored our little movie.
And now, the only person
selling it is me and my co-director,
Court Holland.
Well, you are the kind of person,
and you generate the kind of
negative energy in some of these extreme
types. I won't say what kind of types
they are. They are generally pink.
Type O and type A.
Certainly, for surely.
But you generate too much angst nausea
in them, and they want to
not only attack your product, they want to
throw you out the window.
Not like you.
Oh, well, I'm sure I arouse similar feelings
of angst nausea in many people, and I think
that's better than netiquette
when you're frying your own dough.
Oh, you're a lot better at it than I am. You can do it without even opening your mouth.
Well,
that's because that's the only
orifice that needs to be open at that time.
Right. Other times I can
amuse people
with my squeaks and
other noises.
I believe.
What, I'm supposed to start farting now?
Yeah, I was actually waiting to hear some noises.
I wanted to hear some funny noises.
You know, we used to do sound effects
and stuff on... Oh, no.
Chaz was always one of the
sound effects.
Yeah.
I did the Foley effects with my mouth.
That's what you were expecting.
And coffee cups. Lots and lots of coffee cups.
Yeah, Dave would tear the end off a coffee cup
and use that for his electronic
special effect modifier.
And the cellophane from the cigarette wraps.
Didn't it work, though?
Well, yeah, in a little rascals
kind of way, but that's
our way.
Is this our way?
Did you ever punch a watermelon to resemble
the sound of a human being struck?
A human's face?
No, but I have the sound effects record
that they did that on.
Everybody did. Everybody had that
sound effects record.
The one with the car crash. There was a car crash
that to this day I still hear every now and then
in the movies.
It's got kind of an... noise just before
the crash.
It sounds like a human voice and it ends
with a rolling
wheel or something.
You hear something roll away afterwards
which has become kind of a cliche.
So now whenever there's a crash
you have to end it with one little piece
rolling off to the side.
This does a punctuation at the end.
And if you're into the audio business
of the end of the spectrum, you'd like to hear
the sound of a little clink or a clank
as the wheel goes by.
Sometimes you'd like to see a gnome, you know, like one of those
garden gnomes, expose
themselves in the most absurd
fashion, the most disgusting
little type of way
you could possibly imagine.
You're talking about
garden gnomes exposing themselves?
Dave?
Yes, it is.
You can tell what he's got on his mind.
You can tell what he thinks about
day in and day out from dawn to dusk.
As a member of the
Communist Party, I'd like
to thank the delegates from Eurasia,
Oceania,
and also the rest
of the delegates there.
This wonderful brunch
before we begin our
convention.
The Reverend
Thomas Luther of the Church of God.
...pickle, and
the Reverend Ivory
Ivan Stang
of the Church of the Subgenius
He pronounced it right.
...will deliver the
pre-campaign
networking Sphinx Prize
annual D-Drop Award.
Reverend Stang?
My fellow heads of
cabbage, come let us
reason together
and call the flowers
together upon this great
garden of
filth, which we
fertilize by osmosis.
Just lay down
and leak all over it, friends,
and your garden will grow.
It's hard for me
to be in this world lately, Dave.
I understand.
I have a better world at home.
If I was a kid,
I wouldn't have to do it at home.
I'd probably have a
miniature, portable
game player device.
Yes.
But I'd rather, frankly,
I'd rather be slaying
jaggies or lewdrothes.
These are monsters in this
my first video game.
I could totally understand.
Did I tell you about that?
How I started playing a real video game
just like people do?
Yes, and you created your own
sick world.
No, no, no.
I paid money.
I actually bought this game
and I entered a sick world
that some Japanese company created.
But they're pretty good.
The graphics are really nice.
It's a kid's game.
It's not really, it's no Skyrim
or Call of Duty.
But is not Stangor a rather
what else should we say
type of character
not very cosmopolitan?
Perhaps not.
Oh, he is now.
He is now.
When Stangor first awoke
in Moga Village,
he was a naked barbarian
with a little good-for-nothing
sword made out of popsicles.
I thought you were going to say something else.
In his underwear.
Yeah, he was in his underwear.
We don't actually know if he can take that underwear off.
And he is built
in the Mimitoni.
What a six-pack.
A prehistoric human being
with a caveman with a very small organ
is still quite a...
a delightfully...
I don't know, stupid, maybe.
Well, he's not a caveman.
That's what people get Stangor wrong.
He's more like Conan,
who, if you recall,
you're Robert E. Howard, Dave.
Conan became an emperor
eventually.
And Stangor has that possibility recently.
In fact,
there's one reason nobody's heard from me
in about two weeks
is we got an improved internet connection.
And I was able,
we'll start playing the game online,
which meant that Stangor
could go into the big city.
If you crossed through the magic window
into the bigger world
beyond Moga Village,
you can go to this big city.
And from there, if you're good enough,
you can eventually go sailing
all over the desert
and sand sails.
But Stangor actually
bought himself a tuxedo
made of giant bug wings
and things.
Man, it's cool.
Yeah, he looks very slick.
He doesn't even,
he can walk around in the city
wearing what looks like a tuxedo.
He doesn't even have a helmet on.
And he does look a little bit like me.
He's got a long ponytail
and a white goatee
and mustache.
And he's handsome, like I am.
Yes, and he's very regally drawn.
Yes.
Regally drawn.
What an eloquent statement.
Now, he also has some armor
that makes him look like a clown
wearing a bathysphere
over each body part.
Oh, that's so elegant.
He does have that.
But all of this is actually
just an excuse for me to play a song
that Pisces and Reverend Angry Larry
and them whipped up at X-Day.
And they mean that
in the extra meditating way, too.
Well.
They whipped it up.
Like a frosty cone in their mind.
Yeah.
I suppose so.
Actually, you guys don't know,
but we discussed that.
We discussed that on the previous hour of Slack,
the frosty cone extra meditation stuff,
which we probably shouldn't dwell upon.
But as a frame of reference,
you know, like,
where did I hear that?
Well, I said that.
No, Stank said that.
But why did we say it?
Did I say it?
Why did anyone say such a stupid thing?
Why are you asking that?
I don't know.
Because we're subgenius.
Because they were there?
Because we were there.
Because those stupid things to say
were there to be said.
If only rockers,
if they had been there,
there would be 20 times as many stupid things.
That's what I needed to hear.
I feel so relieved now.
No, I'm going to play this song.
The best thing about it is its length,
which is short.
Yeah, they were jamming on stage on July 5th,
but we were all sad because, you know,
it turned out not to be 1998 again.
And they were jamming on stage,
and suddenly,
I don't even know how Reverend Angry Larry
even knew about Stangor,
but he,
well, I guess I'd been walking around
dressed as Stangor.
That's an embarrassing thing.
I'd rather not dwell on it.
Oh, I don't know if I'd want to admit that.
But they,
suddenly he was talking about Stanguar,
and they did a Guar-like song
about Stangor,
and Pisces made up the lyrics,
which started with the word,
Ah!
So,
here it is.
Ah!
Stangor!
We need Steve Gordon Gordon up here to sing this!
One, two, three, four!
Stangor!
Stang터 사라졌 let Washyourawan
He's Stanko!
His name is Stanko!
Daddy's a fat, funny, and a killer
He's a great, stanko killer
He'll save them with his might
He can hit them good, hard, and quick
He's Stanko!
Stanko!
He's a great Stanko!
He's a great, awesome, and a killer
He'll save them with his might
He's a great, powerful, and a killer
He's a great, awesome, and a killer
He's Stanko!
Stanko!
Well, I won't subject everybody in the listening audience to this vanity song about my video game character.
Yeah, I'm grooving on it!
Those were some very, very mighty nice licks that were just extemporaneously boireized.
Yeah, it does sound pretty boireized.
You must tell Reverend Angry Larry that I appreciate from the bottom of my...
You know...
I'm sorry.
I'm so sick of you!
For sure.
Anyway, um...
I think there's an interesting little recording that comes up right after this,
which I may...
I may leave on, or turn the sound up for.
This was off of...
This was one of the few songs that sounded better off my location recorder,
and not off the board.
On the board version, all you hear is Pisces, and it hurts.
That scream at the beginning.
I saw the... I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to break the interlude, and the...
Um...
Did you see the... I saw the fish kill.
I saw the fish kill.
What? Huh?
What are you talking about, man?
Well, I guess I was listening to Canadian radio,
and they said, oh, there's been a massive fish kill in Lake Erie,
and the Ontario Ministry of...
See, Reverend Angry Larry reminded me of this Canadian crap,
but, um...
I'm not following.
So I went down to the beach today, and it's on this side,
but there's no reportage of it on this side.
I'm not following.
We've been to that beach that Dave goes to.
Well, it's...
Dave took us to that beach once in Eshtabula.
Oh. It does not have snow on it.
Now it has lots of sand and dead fish,
is what I was trying to say.
Oh, so there's been a die-off, another die-off.
There's been a mass...
And the Ontario Ministry of Fisheries in Wyethleif
said that, um,
there was a massive drop in the oxygen
through some machinery that we have to divulge later.
Well, you know...
That's not good.
The little spineless things,
not politicians,
the invertebrates,
like the vertebrates,
are estimated to be
one in five species
is about to be gone.
And a lot of people go,
well, who cares about a bunch of worms
and germs? What do they do for us?
Oh, well, they allow the plants to grow
and make oxygen.
They allow the roots to
suck germs out of the sand
and use them.
All they do is cause...
They're the bottom of the food chain
that allows all larger things to live
one after another.
And they're in no better shape
than the mountain gorillas
and the chimpanzees.
And the, uh...
Well, it used to be starving Armenians
when I was a kid,
and then it was starving Chinese.
Now it's the starving Americans.
Eat your dinner!
Think about the starving Americans!
Don't clean your plate!
That's why I both want to eat dinner
and I wept and laughed
during the Republican convention
because they were both silly,
I must agree with you,
and I completely and heartily.
But the Republican one was so absurd
that I couldn't believe
there was such a leap backwards
in the American people.
I felt so sorry for Mrs. Romney
because they were poor.
They had to eat off of an ironing board
and they had to eat canned food
and they had it so expensive.
It was so hard because
all they had to live on was the dividends
from his stocks.
Just the dividends from their daddy's stocks.
That's all they had.
I think most people can identify with that.
Most people know how that feels
to have nothing but the dividends
from your dad's stock to live on.
And trying to live just on tuna fish?
I mean, come on, that's really Spartan.
Unfortunately, it was Maimai
from the Cayman Islands.
She has been admitting both.
Well, we didn't really have
financial hardships,
but we had health problems.
Even rich people can have health problems.
Don't you feel sorry for me?
What are you, a racist?
Then she's going to walk into
the boondoggle of healthcare
and she's going to say,
no, no, no, no, no,
what I meant was healthcare.
And then there's going to be an immigration problem.
No, but she doesn't talk about things like that.
She's already said.
In fact, both of them have said,
no, no, we're not going to talk about that kind of thing.
The stuff that concerns you people.
I think their mistresses should come out.
The biggest, the hottest ones
with the most largest
Cajunas and the Bazongas
and the Cazordanas and all those other names, you know.
Comes out there and just goes,
oh, this is so great.
I love being here.
Oh.
And that'd be it.
That's kind of what everybody does anyway, right?
Oh yeah, that's right.
I'm so happy to be here.
You're all so wonderful.
Let's all just
masturbate each other.
I'm getting scared.
I'm getting really, really scared.
Actually, Philo does that hysterical tittering
a lot better than I do.
He's crazier.
He's even crazier than me.
Well, Philo's kind of a conservative,
but he lives in Berkeley.
So he's surrounded by people who would make me feel
like a conservative, relatively.
You know, it's all relative.
It depends on where you are.
If I'm in Stangsville, Texas,
why, I might as well be Chairman Mao.
Communist.
If I'm in Berkeley,
I might as well be Rush
Adolph Limbaugh.
You know, I mean, it really is.
And that's
as it should be.
The subgeniuses have to be
the opposite of what most people are doing.
That's their job.
And the eventual
extermination of most people.
Well, except that it's not up
to us to do that. That's the important thing.
We're not so proud
that we think we can destroy the Earth.
We feel
that that's best left up to
giant corporations and aliens
from outer space.
And their flatulence.
And their customers.
Actually, all you really need to destroy a planet
is a lot of customers.
A hell of a lot.
Malleable customers.
We're not, you know,
specifically collectivists.
But by the same token,
if you bite my shoe, I'll take a hammer
to your foot.
Yeah, it's every yard a kingdom.
Get off of my lawn.
Okay, Squire.
That's the new make my day.
Get off of my lawn.
Fill up my empty chair.
Sit in my chair.
You feeling like a punk?
Try it.
I actually got a nice cut up of Clint Eastwood's speech
from
I think Reverend Wilhelm
Stahlhelm.
But I pronounced his name wrong, so he changed his name
to the way I mispronounced it.
He changed it to
Wilhelm von Stroheim.
I think we saw greed the night before
or something and I got mixed up and said
Stroheim instead of Stahlhelm.
When I said uh, it was like uh, Clem.
And he thought that was the name
I was giving him, so he's
Reverend Wilhelm von Stroheim.
Anyway, he did a nice cut up
but I've already used it
on a canned hour
of Slack, which
everyone outside of WCSB Cleveland broadcast
has already heard or will hear
before they hear this.
So it's time decontrol.
And speaking of time control,
I was going to play another little bit.
And this little bit is funny
because, well first
there's a preacher talking about getting high off
drinking blood, because Stangor does that.
But it's a
recording, friends,
of, well it's actually, you might
call it the very first subgenius
recording. It was the first
transmission from the Exists.
I've never played it on the air
ever, I don't think.
I found it at the very end of a really old
special media barrage
preliminary tape. I'm going to play
this. It's kind of short, but you'll actually
hear, we had a, Philo
and I were driving around out in the country late
at night, and we were abducted
by UFOs. I know that
sounds silly, but you can listen to this
recording, you can tell that we're
sincerely terrified, and one of the aliens
sort of took control
of my brain,
such as it is, and spoke
through me. And
so I'm going to play this historic subgenius
recording, like I say, first
of all.
Yeah, okay, here,
first there's a preacher talking about
Stangor, okay.
Uh, no, this one.
Stang-quarr, Stang-quarr,
I don't know what we were singing.
Okay, okay, come on, come on.
Stang-quarr.
Some of these people I have been
told can get high off of
human blood, or can get high off of
animal blood. But they feel
very strongly that the blood from certain
animals at certain points in time, and the things that are done
at certain points in time, give them strength.
Give them power
over certain things.
This man says no.
It's all a myth. A crazy hoax
dreamed up by somebody, and built into a national
fixation by a sensation-seeking press.
Get up there! There's something in the sky!
Dr. Drummond, get a hold of the wheel!
I can't!
I feel...
Oh!
Get out!
This is Antron.
This is
Antron.
Attention, humans!
I am speaking
to the medium of
Ivan Stang!
To you, humans!
We planted the seeds of life on this planet
ten billion
years ago!
Seeds of
atomic testing!
Shut up, Pink Boy!
Shut up, Pink Boy, kill me!
What's going on?
Dr. Drummond!
Dr. Drummond, wake up!
That was 1977.
Wow.
That was so prophetic.
That was the beginnings of the...
You can see why we take the X-Day prophecy so seriously.
Right.
They are to be taken seriously.
I practically had a few tears there just thinking of what a horrible scene
and how much you guys must have been changed forever.
The poignance.
In so many different ways.
I just can't imagine the kind of psychic trauma that you go through every night,
perhaps every day.
That was the first time the phrase,
shut up, pink boy, was ever heard on the planet.
And it wasn't even a real phrase.
It was an alien speaking through you.
Shut up, pink boy.
Seize all atomic testing.
They called it atomic testing, I noticed,
as if it was some 1950s thing.
Probably that was the last.
That was the last TV transmissions they'd been able to get.
They'd been watching the same old monster movies we did,
so they were using the language from that.
Well, the thing is, these people shave their eyebrows
and look like they're living in some kind of astral dimension
between those two places you were talking about.
They don't really know what's happening, man.
I sure don't.
I don't either, but they don't.
Not as far as I'm concerned.
I get no real message from them.
I just get this.
Looks like Brando in an apocalypse now or something.
I just want to urinate in their shoes and run away
and shout foul epithets to the wind and things like that.
I'm sure you speak for every listener when you say that, Dave.
I can't do more than coax them, I suppose.
If I were like you, if I was like you,
and I could get them to do my bidding.
Well, yeah, I'm real good at getting people to do my bidding.
I can clean up my driveway.
Stuff like that.
I've got a mess in the basement.
I can't even get myself to do that.
It's funny you should mention that.
Yeah, funny you should mention some of those things.
Oh, well.
Well, that's what social media is for.
Just call, you know, just wig out on all your friends.
Daddy-o.
Well, I'm getting all excited because...
Clean up party at my pad.
The next best holiday to X-Day is coming.
Halloween.
Yeah.
And WCSB will be...
Having their big Halloween party, or costume ball.
Which is really...
We went to the last two of those, and they're great.
In fact, last time I was given the job of projecting monster movies
on the walls and ceilings, and I actually brought trailers, you know,
because then you get...
It's just the good stuff.
Women screaming, monsters coming, women screaming, monsters coming.
Monsters carrying beautiful...
Women coming, monsters screaming.
Just, you know, that's...
And, uh...
And they make WCSB beer, too.
Uh-huh.
And, uh...
And they let me have that for free, I think.
They're all...
Since we were working.
I was one of the workers.
Princess Wee was the main worker.
She did a lot.
In fact, there's...
Some of her work is in the station.
There's several monster silhouettes in the station studio windows.
She was the monster commissar.
She's the screaming woman.
I'm looking at a creature from...
From the Black Lagoon silhouette attacking a buxom silhouetted woman,
and that's actually Princess Wee.
And you can tell by the giant hair.
Her hair is bigger than the whole creature.
Bigger than the buxom part?
Oh, yeah, a lot bigger.
Well, you know, she's got that special hippie girl hair.
Anyway, it's...
Dave, we have to go because I'm going to play a song at the end.
In fact, I'm going to play...
The Duke of Uke at X-Day doing Cult of Personality.
I love that way he does that there.
I was going to say, you know, it's all right,
because I'm decomposing anyway right now.
No, no, Dave, don't decompose.
Please don't decompose.
He does that every night.
That's the word.
Where do you think his compositions come from?
I guess.
I'm going to have to bring him a ball.
I think it'll hardly work without me.
Well, friends, this has been the hour of slack.
But number 1,379, that's how many of these shows we've done,
fewer reruns, from the Church of the Subgenius,
and you can find all the information about that
and all past shows back to about number 200.
They're downloadable.
And even some books that are out of print.
They're on the web now.
And all the pictures of X-Day that are not safe for work.
And even worse things, it's subgenius.com.
If you were interested.
And meanwhile, now I'm going to go back to what?
Oh, whoa, we've got to do the news and then cult of personality.
Thank you, Dave, for calling in.
Thank you for being so square and so restless.
And thanks to the Flying Ryan Brothers for playing music in the background
here in the studio with us.
And thanks to Princess We for being Princess Lee
and making everything else possible for me.
So, okay.
The type.
Yeah.
Sacrament.
Okay.
From PR News in Washington, I'm considered dangerous.
American cycling star Lance Armstrong says he's going to prison,
not a mental institution for his crimes.
New York City officials say a gunman is outside the Empire State Building.
And that's PR's Janine Herbst.
Stock prices are down, down, down, down, down, 16 since November.
As Tropical Storm Isaac bears down on the Dominican Republic in Haiti,
one humanitarian organization says it has PR news.
PR news is flawed.
PR is bad.
One witness tells Fox 5 News this is PR news from Washington.
Thanks for having me.
I'm the Duke of Uke.
And thank you for choosing the Church of the Subgenius,
the cult with personality.
Look in my eyes, what do you see?
The cult of personality.
I know your anger, I know your dreams.
I've been everything you want to be.
I'm the cult of personality.
Like Mussolini and Kennedy.
The cult of personality.
Neon lights, Nobel Prize.
When the mirror speaks, the reflection lies.
You won't have to follow me.
Only you can set me free.
I sell the things you need to be.
I'm the smiling face on your TV.
I exploit you, steal you of me.
I tell you one and one make three.
I'm the cult of personality.
Lake Jeroboam's like Connie.
What was that in your childhood,
talking about how I came back here,
with J. Robin enticing me to
serve the army and all the pinned워 MBs get oil.
And the doubled, fitted off,
uprooted adesso Don Quixote,
the crown of power,
I'm the cult of, I'm the cult of, I'm the cult of, I'm the cult of, I'm the cult of,
I'm the cult of, I'm the cult of, I'm the cult of, I'm the cult of, I'm the cult of
personality.
Red Bob, my work here is done.
Sire, there is no more money.
We gotta get some money.
That dirty, purgish, hark-a-back, flackin', whartin', filibunker, burton, purkaluma, burton,
durton, bostonite, oh!
B-O-B.
Friends, we're glad you listened to this show, and we're even more glad that some listeners
have donated enough to help us keep on going for another couple of months.
Not just this show, but subgenius.com and all the other archive sites.
But if you truly love Bob, and want some of that slack back to rebound to you, you should
go to subgenius.com front page, or especially the radio page, or the catalog page, and you
can go to the store pages, and help out financially as best you can.
Now, we know what it's like to be on the brink of total poverty, and we don't want any subgeniuses
to make their own situations worse.
But some of you still have jobs.
Even five bucks makes a big difference, even if it's only once a month, from enough of
you.
Fifty bucks makes an even bigger difference.
All we're saying is that...
Blowjobs could go the way of Stevejobs if you don't pay Dobbs.
We also take checks and money orders to Subgenius Foundation.
P.O.
Box 181-417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
Thanks for anything you can do to help let there be slack.
Imam Shaikh Ali
ruffia
S freedoms
Dubliminal tramplers
Money Bob
Free pills
Stag money, Bob!
Free pills!
Kill me!
Stag money, Bob!