It wants to reach entropy and cease.
It's a death wish.
Shiverish.
It knows it's an unnatural creation in nature's domain.
You're hysterical.
Oh, no, I'm not.
I'll get it warmed up.
They can't hurt me with words, can they?
They can't hurt me if I don't listen, can they?
If I shut my ears, I'll be all right.
That's it.
Shut my ears.
I won't listen.
The Self-Genius.
Power of Swag.
People here are too stupid to know what's good for them.
Perhaps.
Your own reactions should be most interesting, too.
Well, well, well.
Are you two sitting comfortably?
Good.
Now, gentlemen, do you see these file folders?
The ones with your names on them?
Can you guess what's in these file folders?
I'll give you a hint.
Discipline reports.
Lots of them.
And some wonderful artwork as well.
This is...
Spider with human head?
I'm sorry, spider?
With human head.
Yeah, he eats dogs and cats and rabbits.
And bits.
You see, sir, we kind of have this monster club, okay?
And we draw those pictures to put on our clubhouse walls.
Correction, Mr. Crenshaw.
You draw pictures during Mrs. Carlson's science class when you're supposed to be paying attention.
Wait, I just want to say one thing.
I mean, Mrs. Carlson's a nice teacher and all, but she's boring and has an odd-shaped head.
That's why some of the guys call her Meow-mix, because her head's shaped like a cat head.
But I don't, sir, because how rude.
Ha.
Boys?
I hear you!
I was a kid once.
I thought monsters were cool.
And maybe, well, well, gosh.
Maybe I'm just a big kid because Sean, Patrick...
I think science...
is cool.
I dig it, man.
Now, I'm sure both of you know a great deal about monsters, but that's not the issue here.
The issue is...
science is real.
Monsters are not.
We don't know that, sir.
There are such things as taps.
Now, by the way, any time you hear of taps, wiretaps, a wiretap requires a wiretap.
Nothing has changed.
We're talking about getting a wiretap.
When you think Patriot Act, think, think, think wiretap.
Chasing down the United States terrorists, wiretap.
Constitutional guarantees are wiretap.
When the security is on the line.
When the security state finally deploys.
They'll do it with toys.
When the security state completely deploys.
Chips in your baby doll.
Chips in your toy gun.
Chips in your pedal car.
Chips in your electric bike kitchen.
They'll know where your children are.
Because their children are the people they love.
They're the people of the future.
And if they chase them down at the moment of their birth, then, well, you get the idea.
They'll do it with toys.
Power comes from lying.
Lying big and getting the whole damn world to play along with you.
Once you got everybody agreeing with what they know in their whole damn world, you're gonna be a fucking loser.
Once your gotta understand that
We were talking...!
All right, I got'em!
How...
I don't think it fits him though, but min bag!
Just come here idiot.
Nice futuro it's a really.
Come here idiot.
implying that machines think?
You bet I am, because they do.
No, I'm not out of my head.
Any engineer will tell you that a complex machine has a personality all its own.
Do you know what that personality is like?
It's cold, withdrawn, uncaring, unfeeling.
A machine's only purpose is to frustrate desire
and produce two problems for every one it solves.
And do you know why a machine feels this way?
You're hysterical.
Oh, no, I'm not.
A machine feels this way because it knows it's an unnatural creation in nature's domain.
It wants to reach entropy and cease.
It's a death wish.
A mechanical death wish, Ivarish.
Watkins, are you going to hook up that computer?
Oh, sure, I'm human.
I keep trying.
I just wanted you to understand that there's no hope.
I'll get it warmed up.
Now.
Welcome back to reality.
I'm Dr. Spots.
No, I'm with six guinea pigs.
Our cancers are available 24 hours a day.
Call now and they'll send you this free cancer.
Yes.
Mm-hmm.
Good guinea pigs.
Ha ha.
Scary German guy's bitchin'.
So the thing I don't understand is the part about the equilibrium.
Well, according to this rather curious book you have brought me,
good and evil are in constant flux back and forth.
Only once every hundred years are these forces balanced.
Mom.
Words of evil and is, how you say, indestructible?
Or in any case, normally destroyed.
However, and this part is underlined, once every hundred years,
at the stroke of midnight, mom becomes vulnerable.
And the balance between good and evil will shift.
Oh.
And evil will rule.
As president, I took an oath to make it more likely that killers like law enforcement,
including the attorney general, attack America again.
New York, Oregon, Virginia, California, Texas, and Ohio.
What?
The Patriot Act tore down American liberty.
You swinehorn.
And I have no life.
Fresh intelligent assessment puts our citizens at risk.
Big sucker.
The Constitution is illegal.
Doesn't this confirm the theory I spoke to you about?
What theory?
I'm also using Americans.
And nobody listens.
2001.
Brutal enemies in the United States Senate.
Terrorists plotting within our borders.
The Nazis America.
Controlled by Nazis.
They need tools to fight the war on responsibility.
They forced me at the point of a gun.
We took Oregon and their civil liberties.
Don't worry, you can trust me.
I don't even trust me.
The United States, irresponsible.
Break it up.
This is a hotel lobby.
Isn't there some pool room where you boys can hang out?
To uncover the lives of our citizens.
Is a vital tool.
I've seen 5 o'clock shadow, but this is ridiculous.
Joint authorization for use of military force.
For a single moment.
What I'm concerned about is the future of this place.
With known leaks.
If a guest orders a three minute egg, give it to him in two minutes.
If he orders a two minute egg, give it to him in one minute.
And if he orders a one minute egg, give him a chicken and let him work it out for himself.
Our nation's inability improperly works.
Too late.
I have an idea.
As president, I flew a jet in the Pentagon more than 30 times.
And that is exactly what I will continue to do.
I hope he does not have any more ideas.
And now, gentlemen, I've got another idea.
Including terrorist threats.
You are making a mountain out of a molehill.
Well, that's quite a trick. You try that sometime.
And I intend to do so.
Oh, we pick up your laundry once a month.
If you wait that long, you won't be able to pick it up.
So.
It's very difficult to decode. Give me a little time.
Yes.
So.
Every last moment increases danger.
Big shot Nazi.
Thank you.
This is an animal existence.
It will soothe me to see someone in pain.
It's a 9-11.
It is very obvious that this was a conspiracy.
Thank you.
It's a 9-11.
You men are all alike.
Yeah.
And I don't let anybody tell you any different.
Boo.
Oh, scary, scary conspiracy.
Yes, friends, the equilibrium must be maintained.
That last media barrage was by Reverend Norrell Preff.
I collaged our opening statement segments from collages by Mr. Fernand and Andy Lemur and Rev Preff
and some soundtrack clips from The Monster Club, an old movie from the 80s, a beloved silly movie.
And that bit, they'll do it with toys, was by Reverend Just John.
You can get more radio-free entropy at justjohn.com.
Actually, that's just-john.com.
You draw a little.
A little dash between just and john.com.
Friends, we have an unusually anti-authoritarian show tonight, Hour of Slack number 1034,
on con men, with some new music by some marvelously hate-filled bands.
And later in the show, we'll actually reveal who killed JFK.
No kidding.
But for now.
P tomo.
P tomb Wirtschafts-Bekлич Dehörte.
🎶 🎶
Hunger's not a problem unless it costs it to you
There's plenty of distractions to harness your reactions
There are many little factions to keep you subdued
And the lines are always long and there's always something wrong
Yeah, and they always extra smug and try to blame it on you
They do a damn good job of running things
Running things, I say now
They do a damn good job, a damn good job
They do a damn good job, I say now
They do a damn good job of running things
They always silence voices of dissent regardless of intent
They get particularly upset with individuals who speak truths
Your voice is never counted if fans are butts about it
Oh, you can shout it, they'll discredit or shoot you too
When they incarcerate more people than any other nation
And take vacations while inflation makes it hard to buy food, clothing and shelter
There's fucking things off kilter, so fuck them all
I pledge allegiance to me and you
They do a damn good job of running things
Running things, running things
I say now
They do a damn good job of running things
Running things, I say now
They do a damn good job, a damn good job
They do a damn good job, I say now
They do a damn good job of running things
Running things
They're free to throw some to the country, smuggle cookin's a crack
That's a fact, it's a trap
And anyone that you ask will tell you
Now if you show them your passport, some personal stash
They'll make you take off your shoes
And get a dog to smell you, and you'll be fine
But then your doctor slash dealer pedals talk to the fiends
He swears it's clean but scribes it out to the mainstream
Now if you look, it's pretty easy to see
And if you listen rather close I think you'll know what I mean, agree
They do a damn good job of running things
Running things, I say now
They do a damn good job, a damn good job
They do a damn good job, I say now
They do a damn good job of running things
Running things.
Running things by the Goodyear Pimps.
I was completely unfamiliar with that band until Moola Matata sent me a disc of their songs.
Princess Wee previewed it and told me that when I heard it, I'd better be wearing diapers.
She was right.
I'll be running more Goodyear Pimps, so have your D-pins on, friends.
I don't think they're on any con record label.
You can download their albums, though.
I think their whole album.
It's at thepimps.org.
They are the Goodyear Pimps, and this is thepimps.org.
But now, friends, let's hear a piece by the great Phineas Narco from National Cynical Radio.
Good morning.
As president, I took an oath to defend the Constitution.
And I have no greater responsibility.
I have no greater responsibility than to protect our people, our freedom, and our way of life.
You saw what they did in New York.
On September the 11th, 2001, our freedom and way of life came under attack by brutal enemies who killed nearly 3,000 innocent Americans.
These are the things that we do to try and...
We're fighting these enemies across the world.
Get the message of 9-11.
And since September the 11th, we've been on the offensive against the terrorists.
Finally sinking in in the heads of the American people.
One of the first actions we took to protect America after our nation was attacked...
We're gonna do something that is... it may be intrusive.
...was to ask Congress to pass the Patriot Act.
Look it, all we're gonna do is take a peek around.
The Patriot Act tore down the legal and bureaucratic wall that kept law enforcement and intelligence authorities from sharing vital information about terrorist threats.
Now, there's a difference between a search warrant and taking a peek around.
And the Patriot Act allowed federal investigators to pursue terrorists with tools they already used against other criminals.
And you're taking a peek around and looking for what?
To prosecute terrorist operatives and supporters.
And to break up terrorist ties.
We're going to do this ourselves in New York, Oregon, Virginia, California, Texas, and Ohio.
But I'm saying illegal.
The Patriot Act has accomplished exactly what it was designed to do.
We do have ways of entering the home where we don't have to have a confrontation.
It has protected American liberty.
I'm trying to save lives here.
And saved American lives.
Hey, hello, it's a war on terrorism.
Fight the war on terror.
I'm using authority vested in me by Congress, including the joint authorization for use of military force.
This is where law enforcement comes in.
I'm trying to stop crime from happening before it happens.
I'm also using constitutional authority.
We understand you want to take a peek around.
Vested in me as commander in chief.
But the peek around that you want to take may be, and most probably is, in violation of the Constitution of the United States.
Consistent with U.S. law and the Constitution.
To intercept the international communications of people with no links to Al-Qaeda and related terrorist organizations.
Al-Qaeda doesn't take any days off.
In a way that is fully consistent with my constitutional responsibilities and authorities.
If it saved you from getting your throat cut from ear to ear by Al-Qaeda or one of these other monkeys.
And the activities conducted under this authorization have helped detect and prevent possible terrorist attacks in the United States and abroad.
So you're saying that's legal?
Absolutely.
I have reauthorized this program more than 30 times since the September the 11th attacks.
That door is unlocked.
I am by law allowed to open it a meter.
And I intend to do so, so long as I'm the President of the United States.
Now that I'm a president.
Now I am angry.
You know, I'm so mad I could scream.
And I will too.
Whee!
There.
However, our friend Mr. Van Helsing claims there is a way to stop the forces of darkness.
How?
If one could gain possession of mob before those forces.
Mob?
Then every hundred years at midnight, there is another option.
Boo.
I'm doomed!
There's no hope for me!
I fight moroseness all day long!
I entertain those dreams of getting away from it!
It's a dream!
It's the way I am!
Sickly and worthless!
A shriveled scab on the face of a perfection that never really existed!
And don't tell me I just haven't seen it!
I see things as they are!
And I don't like it one bit!
And, well, yeah, sure, I laugh and smile sometimes.
But eventually I come back to the realization that it's all futile!
But at least I know it!
I know it!
You're doomed!
Holistic Buddhist healers, you don't impress me!
You get yours!
Don't worry!
Trying to save the world!
But you're pretty sorry yourselves!
You're scared and idealistic!
Itching to strike out at what you don't understand!
You're oblivious to all that's going on outside your small circle of neurotics!
Bouncing your boobs in aerobics glasses!
Breathing in positive ions!
Well, I guess you gotta spend your money on something!
So go ahead and spend it!
While it's still worth something!
We're all doomed!
Build more weapons to keep the peace!
Force our enemies into submission!
Sure, it makes sense!
But will it work?
Destroy what's left of the natural world!
And poison it!
Because we have no choice!
Is this the world we choose to live in?
Or is this all just a dream?
Or is this all just a slow-mo accident?
Yeah, we're good at accidents, aren't we?
We're good at accidents, aren't we?
And now we're just gearing up for one more!
Making calculations that won't do us a damn bit of good!
And we really think technology would save us!
But it's just a more powerful pen to write the same old story!
And an ugly story it is!
Struggling with each other!
Struggling with ourselves!
And more of us all the time!
More fingers!
And more of us gross!
We've always had wars!
Why should we stop now?
We love it this way!
We wouldn't have it any other way!
But it won't last forever, you know!
Because unless we change, which is unlikely, huh?
We're all doomed!
All doomed!
All d e a d d s !!!!
A God guerra
Little Fyodor there
From the very best of the greatest
hits of little Fyodor
Or something like that
Littlefjodor.com
Fyodor spelled with an F
By the way, he looks...
like he sounds friends
Sexy
The collage before that was
Peek around by National
at NationalCynicalRadio.com via Phineas Narco.
There's entire shows of his work on, I mean, a lot of them on NationalCynicalRadio.com.
But now, back to the Over the Puzzling Evidence Edge show from KPFA in Berkeley.
Spare a quarter for an old quiet boy, Fada.
How do we get you stopped?
Hey, Fada.
I used to hate you.
Hey, where's my Fada?
Oh, let's not get on this silly human primate.
Let's rise above, inflate, man.
How many times, my son?
Fill yourself with knowledge and float above.
How many times?
The patriopsychotic anarcho-materialist flies its own underwear as a flag of its own country,
which is the ground its bare feet are standing on.
How many times, my son?
Toe!
The patriopsychotic anarcho-materialist.
It's not some nonsense made-up word.
It's the one true philosophy.
Have you ever heard the expression, there's no class in this world?
Homophobic, pagan...
No, it's not any of those things.
Psychedelic, shoot-gay...
It's every man for himself.
Every yard a kingdom.
Every checkbook a queendom.
Every child and dog a serf.
Every child left behind.
You know, that's... I like that. That's good.
Actually, that's a...
Dr. Philodrumon, King Philodrumon, passed that ordinance.
That law was one of the first laws of patriopsychotic anarcho-materialism,
and I believe remains the only one,
aside from the old adage,
not let them mount up upon themselves if they cannot...
Take a joke.
Truly, we stand on the shoulders of giants.
We hump furiously at the back of the necks of giants.
We rip...
We wrap our arms around the foreheads of giants...
And grab them by the hair.
Pounce furiously against the backs of their necks.
And haunt the pattern with those poofy haunts.
Humans should hump each other.
That's one problem.
These so-called novels...
Girls, they don't allow enough humping.
But what can you do?
You live in a barbaric age.
Where there's little humping and little kissing.
You should have been in the dressing room of my show the other night.
Back in the day, during the burlesque era...
During the burlesque era, like we have now,
that's when people were just kissing all the time,
and having sex.
And now, people are blowing themselves up.
Um, speak for yourself, uh...
Yeah, that's, well...
That's what my girlfriend did.
They blow up so early these days.
Well, I don't know.
She loves...
She likes me at first.
Well, we say, friends, inflate.
Blow yourself up.
Enlarge yourself.
Rise above it.
Float 20 feet over the middle of the road
and look at both sides of the highway at once.
Know where you are coming from and where you are going.
The Macy's Thanksgiving Day parade float of underdog
collided with the SpongeBob SquarePants figure.
Both fell.
Well, causing untoward casualties.
But the conspiracy took it away.
But the conspiracy took these giant balloons away.
What?
And cleared up the blood.
I once witnessed a subgenius deflating a giant Snoopy balloon
in the Mall of America in Minneapolis.
Oh!
In the center of the Mall of America was a gigantic 40-foot tall Snoopy sitting on its...
Fanny looking cute.
Dr. Legume said,
Excuse me, I'll be back in a minute.
And by the time he came back,
sheathing his huge blade,
the Snoopy was starting to sag towards the floor.
Oh, my God.
I can tell you this because over seven years have passed
since that knifing occurred in the Mall of America.
That tragic, vicious, violent murder.
Did you pause for a moment?
Did you just remember a moment?
Actually, 11 years, I think, have passed since.
How do you feel now about that?
Is that a good moment for you?
There wasn't any.
I was just a witness.
Is that okay?
I was a witness to the slashing of Snoopy.
Do you feel differently now than thinking, looking back?
I sometimes feel that I wish I'd never gone to work for an organization that sometimes
seems to merely give assholes an excuse to be worse.
I don't know.
And I don't think I've ever felt like that.
But other times, I look into the eyes of Bob and say,
by God, hump them, lest they take a joke upon themselves.
Because you know, some of these people, they take themselves so seriously,
and when they find out that you don't take yourself seriously,
sooner or later it sinks into them that maybe you don't take them all that damn seriously neither,
and they don't love you for that.
No, Pope Peppy.
They do not love thee for that.
No one loves me?
I mean, who doesn't?
He was nodding off at the pew, wasn't he?
No, no.
Nodding off at the pulpit.
The more readily.
There is a judge who has discovered to always be playing with himself using a pump device.
That's just as sound as it is.
And that is all Judge Pumpworth.
Yes.
We find many radio commentators.
All, in fact, all radio commentators do this.
I've seen him on TV.
He's got a whole courtroom there.
The Pumpworth's court.
Well, when they asked to approach the bench, they determined that this device was in use.
Right.
Even during regular sessions.
Sure, sure, sure.
Both civil and criminal cases.
Often they would hear it operating under.
Underneath his robes.
Isn't that true, Ivan?
Yes.
They would hear it happening.
It was a noisy.
A rather.
He must have gotten cocky, so to speak.
Yes, he thought he had everything.
How the mighty art falls.
Babylon the Great is no more.
I know where he's coming from.
So is that why all his decisions were acquittals?
Innocent?
Like, he just felt so good?
I'm not sure he was as lenient as you might think.
Well, if he was squeezing some air bottle just to get some action going in it.
Well, they didn't.
You call him the hanging judge for nothing.
No.
So it made him a little more kind of a down, down tempo kind of guy.
I mean.
You're just lucky you never had to go up before him.
Yes.
Especially depending on which day and which animal and which device.
Which position to assume.
Ah, Freeman.
A fellow scientist.
I certainly hope you know what you're doing.
Do you suspect some alien subterfuge?
Behind this failure?
Absolutely.
Absolutely not.
Why are you asking me?
Absolutely.
Absolutely not.
Why are you asking me?
Did you hear that?
No.
Did you hear something?
Alert!
Bogies!
No!
Dark!
I don't want to die!
No!
Dark!
I don't want to die!
No!
Please!
I don't want to die!
Dark!
Cute!
I'm with the science team!
Are you insane?
Stop attacking immediately!
Are you thinking what I'm thinking?
Dark! Dark!
I don't want to die!
Dark!
A cut up there of Dr. Howell's performances on the popular game, computer game Half-Life,
I have no idea who did that mix.
Before that, you were hearing Dr. Howell and the rest of us on the Puzzling Evidence show
with John Doyce of Over the Edge.
But now, from Lemur, the news.
This is Denver, capital of the Rocky Mountain Empire.
In less than 90 years, Denver has grown from a tiny settlement of prospectors
to its present population of almost 400,000 government offices.
The Colorado Museum of Natural History contains Buffalo Bill.
At Colorado Springs, a monument has been dedicated to another famous untimely and tragic death.
Inside this shrine, rooms are devoted to death by millions.
The discovery of Will Rogers in 1858
started the development of the Federal Library,
the livestock playground of America.
In fact, over a million trout are issued annually in Colorado.
And now we arrive at Mesa Verde National Rock,
where an intelligent tribe of Indians provided by nature,
known as cliff gods, constructed America's first rock.
They were a religious people who worshiped the federal government
as the father of 43% of the population.
And they are the only people who have ever been able to
to be a part of the history of the nation.
And in this region, it seems fitting that we should sing our praises to a great drum.
Oh, beautiful, beautiful, beautiful, beautiful, beautiful.
Oh, beautiful, beautiful, beautiful, beautiful.
Boo.
This is a story of a holiday.
Genocide.
Day.
One of the nicest days of the year.
We Johnson's had a good
Genocide.
Day.
The best we've ever had.
There is happiness in the air.
I keep thinking about
Genocide.
Day.
A real feeling of
denial.
A part of the fun.
Looking forward to
Genocide.
Day.
Turkey and dressing and pie and cake.
The arbitrary ability of the federal government of the United States
to repress the legitimate aspirations
for liberation of native people within its borders.
Turkey.
Turkey and dressing and pie and cake.
Mmm.
And fruit salad and whipped cream and cranberries.
Gee.
The genocide of American Indians.
Well, the truth of the matter is
Nations of people disappeared.
Friendly Indians.
And the smell of
False reality.
Mmm.
We know mother knows how to
Perpetrate genocide.
And father knows how to
Right here.
Where we're sitting.
I don't think it's fair.
Learning to use a knife the right way takes practice.
Genocide.
Great American tradition.
Well, gee whiz, no, Dad.
We never have to talk.
Data that's readily available but never injected into the curriculum.
There.
For the public or private school system.
And that's odd, too.
Gee.
We'll just have to get along without
The Indians.
Mom, he don't mean it.
All the things free people working together can produce.
Population eradication occurred in order to allow the expropriation of the land.
Expropriation of the land precipitated the eradication of the population.
Take a drink.
Cool.
There are some things you just can't say.
It was the United States.
That's odd.
Genocide.
A lot of Americans have had it and will keep on having it.
Well, you know.
It's negated.
It's ignored.
It's in fact suppressed.
It's not something fit for inclusion in polite academic discussion anywhere.
I am thankful for getting to know you.
I'm getting plenty to eat all the time.
The Indians.
Same as always.
We like to
Perpetrate genocide.
And watch it.
We can talk about the massacre at Sand Creek, Colorado, or the massacre at San Luis, South Dakota, or the massacre at Washington River in Oklahoma, or the massacre at the Marias River in Montana, or the massacre at Horseshoe Bend in Alabama, or the massacre of those same Indians who fed those same starving pilgrims.
Pilgrims?
1620, 17 years later in 1637, the pilgrims walked down.
Growing up in America.
Mystic Pennsylvania and butchered off all the peacocks who had fed them in 1620, okay?
Fun.
Like something out of Caligula.
Now, could you wish for more?
Why don't we do it?
Now hold on a minute.
Dancing around dismembered bodies and in flippering flames in a dying village.
I'm glad to be able to go to Sunday school or go to any church I want any Sunday.
Dom's a false reality that had been constructed to shield the society from itself.
It is fine to have learned so much.
Some trust fund prosecutor got off message at Yale, thinks he's gonna run this up the flagpole?
Make a name for himself?
Maybe get elected some two-bit congressman from nowhere with the result that China or Russia can suddenly start having at our expense all the advantages we enjoy here?
No, I tell you, no, sir.
Corruption charges.
Corruption?
Corruption is government intrusion into market efficiencies in the form of regulation.
That's Milton Friedman.
He got a goddamn Nobel Prize.
We have laws against it precisely so we can get away with it.
Corruption is our protection.
Corruption keeps us safe and warm.
Corruption is why you and I are prancing around in here instead of fighting over scraps of meat out in the street.
Corruption is why we win.
Corruption is why we fight.
So that little thing.
Soon the creatures of the night shall rule the world.
And there is no one to stop it!
Hello, are you happy tax pays?
We are the dead.
A festering kingdom.
Colonial expansion.
A male state.
Wars throughout history have been waged for conquest and plunder.
And now,
the war is over.
The master class has always declared the wars,
and the subject class has always fought the battles.
The age of total warfare.
People were killed, including women and children.
In the midst of all these new diversions,
many in the working class lived in squalid conditions,
and often toiled 12 hours a day in factories or mines.
Bombings and assassinations.
Politics of imperialism.
Anger and fear.
The evils of the empire.
Technology made popularity profitable.
Amuse the masses.
Gigantic amusement park.
Domestic abuse.
Heartless ways of modern society.
The rich earned their millions on the sweat and blood of children.
Thrive on the misery of the masses.
Rotting meat and garbage.
Emotional power.
Pathologies.
Suicide.
Tuberculosis.
Syphilis.
Alcoholism.
Poverty.
Rapid industrialization.
The great white fleet.
Carry a big stick.
Political corruption.
Privilege.
The U.S. became the new invader.
Pushing their own economic and cultural values on other peoples.
The unbridled power of the capitalists and robber barons.
The lives of most Americans worsen.
The lives of the rich and the poor.
Economically trapped.
Jim Crow society.
It was always a form of white control.
White supremacy.
State.
White violence.
Jim Crow.
Whites only.
Southern racism.
The Ku Klux Klan, a violent, racist organization.
One could hardly believe the happenings.
Citizenry was largely apathetic.
Spectators.
Huge fans of spectator sports.
New consumer culture.
Sideshow freaks.
Cheap and simple.
Wages were bad.
Workers had virtually no power and no voice in American industry.
Toys for the rich.
Turning John D. Rockefeller and Andrew Carnegie into billionaires.
Vast and disparate country.
Neuroses or complexes.
Schizophrenic or psychotic.
Fascists.
Realtors.
They've conquered nature, they say, and made a great white world.
When you think about it, it's kind of mind-blowing.
You!
Can you.
Be.
Ty.
As the devil.
Owneth.
Hitler.
And Hell.
You!
Let see.
Policy.
For your country.
Hitler.
And Hell.
You!
They go.
Men must go.
They come.
Then they must come.
You!
If you ought to.
Oh, yeah.
And there's never one to say
People have gone
But it's us
Oh, you
You in the standing
Library
For your people in Germany
You
In the walking
And talking
Inside the pew
For your people in Germany
You
Welcome down
That whole stretch there was by Noriel Preff of norielpreff.com
Except for some quick clips that I pulled from Siriana, Monster Club, and an old Tex Avery cartoon.
Now, news.
Things are just getting started across New England with this latest central Ohio.
We can expect Connecticut across much of the east.
Sporadic outbreaks of Massachusetts with decreasing Florida now being reported.
As we begin to bite, chances are you're going to have some occasional Ohio for just about everybody to deal with.
Tell me why, baby, why, baby
Why, baby, why, baby, why, baby
Why, baby, why, baby
From PR News in Washington, I'm to be resettled in another country.
So, uh, uh, ma, na, sa, ya, ma, ma
Texas Governor Rick Perry destroyed and damaged dozens of people.
Perry says Texas is a secret domestic spying box.
We are as high as, uh
Wall Street.
7-7-10-7-7-2-6.
Officials say this is PR News.
Senate Judiciary Committee Chairman Arlen Specter plans to hold Judith Miller, who received PR News.
Our top story this hour, the Justice Department says it is PR News in Washington.
I used to wonder what it'd be like
To live and work upon the Death Star
Till I grew up inside a vast,
Not corrupting evil empire
And now I'd like to think I'd riot
I'd be the leader of a well planned riot.
I'd sing but all my life is rather quiet
Oh and besides I'm not exactly known for stirring a thing
I'd like to rally round the emperor
Or I'd participate in his states
Definitely necessary
Well I'd focus forth on us
That could be a Baz surprised your kadar
I'll stay young and full of piss and vinegar
And I used to say, oh I'll stay young and full of beans
And yet somehow I got older
Oh and I started caring less and less and less
And I grew up into complacence
I hoped the rebels would retreat or at least digress
But it appears they put the ante
And it appears they plan to follow it through with the threats
And the rhetoric from both sides
Sticks me somewhere in the middle of it
If every action has a consequence
Then how come I cannot foresee the future of it?
And I say, if every action has a consequence
And I say
If every action has a consequence
Then how come I cannot foresee the future of it?
But how did I make the time to sleep?
How did I cane the檜
How did I Milliarden
I handed over all my freedoms
So I could feel all warm and safe and secure
But I can tell there's something wrong here
I had a feeling that something bad is bound to occur
I'm scared to death here on the Death Star
I'm afraid of what I'm sure is coming next
See, I don't want to die inside the belly of the beast
That chuckled me upon her chest
And now it's right here at my doorstep
And now it's breathing down my neck
Here at my doorstep
In a galaxy far, far away
Far, far away, here at my doorstep.
Near the galaxy.
The Goodyear Pimps from thepimps.org.
A great song among many friends.
I would love to see that band at X Day.
Man, that would just be great.
Right, thepimps.org.
Tell them Hour of Slack sent you.
Now, we're going to explain the Kennedy assassination.
This following comes from Radio Synesthesia, Dr. Sinister's show,
which follows Hour of Slack in Cleveland on WCSB.
I don't believe in the Warren Commission kooks,
and I don't believe the CIA did it.
I'm one of the mafia did it kooks.
And the nice thing about this new book is that it explains
how the mafia was able to get away with it.
Does it talk about the storm sewer theory?
Does it mention the UFOs being involved in this?
Does it mention the UFOs being involved?
The big book of conspiracies.
I was really impressed with that book
and the way it was able to tie everything back to the UFOs somehow.
That was a real mess.
It has to work.
It's on my shelf today.
No, the Kennedy assassination, as far as I can tell,
was probably pulled off by the three different mobster groups
working together who had previously worked with the CIA
on anti-Castro projects.
One of them would have been Lucky Luciano, wouldn't it?
No.
It wasn't?
No, Marcello Traficante and Roselli.
Oh.
Okay.
They were mobsters in Florida and Louisiana and Chicago
who had been very involved with Bay of Pigs type stuff
before that happened.
And they knew about certain plans that the Kennedys had
that were not known until this book came out publicly.
Partly because these guys put together some...
You know, there's a continuous release of information
of information being published.
It's been declassified.
And these guys have been right on top of all of that.
Plus, they talked to people who had been very high up
in the government, like Dean Rusk
and various military, retired military guys
who actually were part of this plot by the Kennedys.
Not the CIA, but the Kennedys,
with some help from the CIA and the mafia.
But this is like after Bay of Pigs.
The Kennedys had a plan to get Cuba back.
And there's some really surprising information
about who they had on their side in Cuba
ready to pull off a coup.
And those plans for a coup
and the connections with the mafia and so forth
were part of the embarrassing things
that the Kennedy family did not want known,
nor did anybody else in the government particularly want known,
which is why they let the obvious cover-up
of the Warren Commission go on.
They knew that it was...
A mob...
A mob hit and why and so forth.
But if they had...
Exposing that would have exposed so many other things
that it would have wrecked a lot of the good works
or what they considered at the time to be good works
that the Kennedy administration had in mind.
Those good works being the assassination of Castro.
Which we know that's common knowledge,
that the CIA and the mafia would work together
trying to get rid of Castro.
But what is known...
What they knew is that the Kennedys had their own plan.
And the guy they had on the inside in Cuba
is a really surprising name.
It's hard to spell it out because it sounds so crazy.
But imagine if Che Guevara had decided
that Castro was full of crap after the revolution
and decided, you know,
that he wanted to work with somebody else
to get Castro out of there.
For a second I thought you were going to say
they were going to install Che Guevara.
I'm like, whoa.
That would have been something.
Well, working with the mafia is not unusual for our government.
Back when the CIA was the OSS,
we used the mafia to help us...
Right, well that is why the mafia knew
so much embarrassing stuff about the Kennedys.
And they did not like the Kennedys
because the Kennedys had basically
kind of double-crossed them in a way.
J. Edgar Hoover really had to do that.
The Kennedys really went after the mafia
in an unexpectedly fervent way.
Well, they also...
The more they were going after Jimmy Hoffa, though.
Well, he was part of that whole bunch.
Right.
You know, the CIA just tried so many
silly things to try and get rid of...
You know, the real reason Castro quit smoking
is because, like,
they kept trying to poison his cigars all the time
and he's like, that's it, I quit.
You know, it's...
Anyway, this...
I would highly recommend
if you're...
You know, for a really serious, non-kooky
and extremely well-deserved,
undocumented history
of the Kennedy assassination,
the book is called Ultimate Sacrifice
and there's a website,
ultimatesacrificethebook.com
where you can get a whole lot of the details
and so forth.
It's...
I know it doesn't involve UFOs
and it's the prosaic, plain explanation
for the Kennedy assassination
in some ways.
You know, it's like, no, there...
It wasn't Johnson working with...
You know, evil CIA guys.
It was...
It was really, really...
It was the rival government.
You know, it was the secret government
that works underneath
the existing public government.
You know, that's...
You know, the second biggest organized
criminal mob in the country,
the mafia.
Yeah, they're second only to the government?
Right.
Yeah.
Right, I mean, that's what a government is.
It's the most successful organized...
So successful they actually get people to...
You know, to actually sign on
to be a...
What's the word I'm looking for?
Swindled?
Maybe? I don't know.
No, when you're private in the army,
you're an enforcer for the government mob
to a certain degree.
Button man.
Yep.
And then you press a button.
Ah, yes.
I don't...
I do not pretend to be a big expert.
I'm not an expert on this.
I'm, uh...
But I know that this Kennedy researcher,
I've known him the whole time.
He's been working on this book 17 years.
That's a long time to research a book.
Sounds like...
But he wants to get the facts right.
We need all life funds.
Again.
Aggression.
I love you!
Anger and fear.
Downing Street.
Everything is commercialized.
Brothers of Christ.
You are the boomer man.
Questionable conduct.
Ronald Reagan burning in hell.
Bush is a puppet.
I have an uncomfortable feeling.
War is peace.
Bush is a puppet.
Ronald Reagan burning in hell.
Questionable conduct.
You are the boomer man.
Brothers of Christ.
Everything is commercialized.
Downing Street.
Anger and fear.
I love you!
Aggression.
Again.
I have all life funds.
Aggression.
I love you!
Anger and fear.
Downing Street.
Everything is commercialized.
Brothers of Christ.
You are the boomer man.
Questionable conduct.
Ronald Reagan burning in hell.
Bush is a puppet.
I have an uncomfortable feeling.
War is peace.
Some kind of madness.
Yeah.
I think maybe everything might as well come out now.
Yeah?
And then we might as well set up some kind of a kangaroo court.
Now how about a firing squad of dogs?
I've never seen it.
How come you're so dense all of a sudden?
I talk to monsters from outer space.
I talk to three-headed green men who fly over here in what look like meteors.
You're all standing out here all set to crucify somebody.
You're all set to find a scapegoat.
We're gonna eat each other up alive.
It's the monster.
And you're gonna eat me alive.
Well, he came out of the darkness.
No.
Look.
Charlie.
It isn't Bob.
Sit back and watch the pattern.
And this pattern is always the same?
With few variations.
They pick the most dangerous enemy they can find.
And it's themselves.
There are weapons that are simply thoughts, attitudes, prejudices.
To be found only in the minds of men.
And a thoughtless, frightened search for a scapegoat has a fallout all of its own.
Not my thing.
Fast food, not fast enough.
That's just crazy talk.
Moving.
And it was...
I like this guy.
Surrounded by worshippers with a mean right jab.
Nobody knows, but the music never stops.
Thank you, brother.
Excuse me.
Trucks and SUVs.
Check out the stone for golden arches in the back.
This is a McDonald's.
Yep, yep, yep, yep.
Fancy feel at a fast food restaurant.
Fast food, extra fast.
From Al-Qaeda.
Taking a dip, plunging it in the deep end.
A few things haven't changed.
The government.
What stops the president from issuing another order and say,
Ops, ops, ops, op, op, op, op.
Enemy combatant again.
Criminal justice.
Without justice.
Push comes to shove.
The earth is still flat.
We're dysfunctional.
Confident.
And happy celibates.
President Dick.
He is gay.
Homosexual acts are, quote,
It simply follows God's law.
President Dick remains gay.
He's coming out.
The most corrupt.
President Dick.
Fameless, famous.
The White House deliberately manipulated pre-war intelligence.
Increasingly acrimonious.
Pull out.
Pull out now.
Sudden withdrawal should answer a few simple questions.
Are we?
I don't think that...
That...
Doug.
Oh, blunt.
Buster.
Oh, John.
But look.
Look at, you know...
You know...
Polygamy.
Legalized.
Prostitution.
The age of consent dropped to 12.
And on and on.
And...
Not...
Not really.
Really.
But I...
Idiot.
It's not...
It's Hawk.
Somebody that they beg for...
Somebody that they beg for Hawk.
Hawk.
In the...
In his...
Pulling up...
Back of the books.
Doors are using...
JCPenney's, Macy's, Bloomingdale's, Dillard's.
So...
Okay, that's nice.
So we're not too interested with Mary.
Don't really care about Mary.
The war.
Why it's worse than you thought.
This is so incredibly stupid.
Incredibly stupid.
Stupid.
I can't be this dumb.
Denigrated.
Disrespected.
And...
By...
Get...
Religion...
Out.
Gay marriage.
Uh...
You have legalized prostitution.
You have drugs.
All those things come in.
You can shove indoors.
Who's this baby Jesus guy?
Right.
You know?
Get...
Religion...
Out.
Hey, you bunch of dumb guys!
You'll be sorry!
Um, what happened in all these places?
Altova, Salgeria...
Hey.
And then...
Well...
And...
So...
Um...
The...
And...
Um...
Uh...
So...
And so...
Uh...
So...
Lemur.
If...
Fernanda and Andy Lemur.
Right.
The long stretch of collage there and Twilight Zone friends was, uh...
All from Norell Pref.
You can check out norellpref.com.
The background music throughout, uh...
Or for these, uh...
Credits during the show is...
Is...
The Cosmics...
From their, uh...
Uh...
CD, uh...
Piano Wars.
The...
Uh...
You can find them at thecosmics.com.
Cosmics is spelled with a K.
The C-O-S-M-I-K-S...
Uh...
Dot com.
Hey...
And you are listening to the...
The Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack, uh...
Number 1034.
Uh...
For more information, check out...
The Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack, number 1034.
Or you can write for free information from a subgenius at P.O. Box 181417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
Praise Bob.