Tonight, radio's distinguished series dedicated to man's imagination.
The Soul Genius Power of Swag.
It's our way of acknowledging our American heroes.
That's what you say.
We say you could act like a jackrabbit.
With frazzled nerves and a heart pounding like a trip hammer.
You gotta keep jumping. You gotta keep punching.
Punch. Punch. Punch that grandfather.
Ugh.
The victim can stand only so much abuse.
Too many people die because they couldn't live.
Grandfather's journey is ending.
He swam from the Pacific Ocean all the way up to Mount Fuji.
That's impossible, isn't it?
This is beyond our present knowledge or understanding.
Bob? Bob? Bob?
Good evening, Bob.
Where are you going tonight, Bob?
Who will you be with tonight, Bob?
Where will I find you if I need you, Bob?
And there's a joint in it.
That's good.
Do you know a Bob?
Oh, yes.
Yes.
Khuri Mahru.
Bob's cool.
He takes special interest in Bob.
Bob's sensitive.
Very clever.
Bob smashed people.
Bob.
Look here, what's this all about?
You're a cunt.
What?
Thank you, Lemur.
And this is not a rerun.
We have some jolly stuff at first.
Then it'll get somber because I have yet more subgenius obituaries.
Then it'll get scary.
But then hopefully we'll have a call-in from Dr. Philo Drummond,
overman first degree, co-sub-founder of the Subgenius Foundation and Bob's good buddy.
But first, well, this piece of music is a mystery to me.
The file title was Shadow Men, and I presume that's the band.
And the file also had the call letter CKLN,
which is, or rather, the name of the band.
There was a small Toronto college station that once had this show on every week.
Shadow Men.
Madam Ohayon Ziel Sundays Area,
Sir fromdoggy państwa
Xochimilk
Yan Paul
Ajo
花
Strong Time
© BF-WATCH TV 2021
I ended up making a list. I was going through my paper mailing list, believe it or not,
and cutting out a photocopy and reorganizing it because half the people on this really old mailing
list had died. These were people that I knew really well or sent a lot of mail to or wanted
to send a lot of mail to. We hardly knew ye. And these are all people that you've heard on the Hour
of Slack. Reverend Ann Atrocity, Frank Barney. He was the guy who started the brushwood, the use of
brushwood as a campground. Charles B., or Reverend Ouroboros Rex. George Clinton.
Joe Cosby. Halim Eldab. Victoria Ganger. Mark Hundahl. The Mojo Bag. You needs it. You gots to have it.
That was his routine, and that was him. Reverend Heathen. Reverend Jess John. Don Joyce. Dottie
Kekever.
Ken Keesey. Greg Klaber, also known as Doctor Dark. Paul Krasner. Ken Musgrave, also known as Doc Mojo.
Ken Narowski, also known as Doctor Kataden Lagim. Jeff Rosenbaum, co-founder of ACE in Cleveland
and the festival's. Charles...
Chaz Smith, Professor Chaz Smith, my good friend, had that band and that show.
Cecilia Pinson Smith of Dallas.
Zug's Rift.
Joe Riley, the film guy of Dallas.
Robert Anton Wilson.
And just recently, my uncle St. Clair, he was the last of the old brothers there.
Now, I'm next in line.
Let's see, what have we got here?
Oh, this music in the background is Cyber Chomp.
And the album is...
I've used Cyber Chomp.
I've used this a lot, because it's an unobtrusive rug, but it's pretty.
Their Moment of Perfect Happiness.
That's an apt title.
Friends, Onan Canabite is still publishing the Dobbs Town Mirror out of Dobbs.town.
And I want to read some of that again, some more.
But it's actually quite late at night.
And I should probably get off the microphone.
But, yeah, we had a little serious moment there.
How about that?
From PR News in Washington, I'm setting fire to PR Reports.
It looked like, I guess, uh...
President Bush demanded a small fixed-wing airplane smashed into North Korea.
The president, sending a strong joint, said he stands by his rose garden.
Stock price is 822-1077338.
This is PR News.
PR News.
Just in case.
The FBI erratically said terrorism was involved in the crash of a small plane into a PR apartment building.
Officials say at least the crash killed PR News in Washington.
Whoa.
Hi, man.
Hi, yo, Scudder.
My family has left for the day.
They've gone to get their hairs cut.
And, uh...
I always thought it was funny they call it a haircut.
You know?
Instead of a hair's cut.
Yeah, so if you're only gonna have one special hair cut.
Or like you had just one big shaft of hair sticking out of the top of your head.
Boy, that would be so...
It was like six or seven inches in diameter.
Right.
And, you know, it looked like a horn.
It would end up looking like a big old horn.
A hair horn.
Like a rhino.
It would be a lot easier to keep clean.
You would think.
If you don't hear me talking, it's cause I'm propping.
Okay.
I'm trying not to waste time.
I was thinking about going to get a beer.
You should.
I can't hear well.
Hold on.
I'm thinking about passing gas.
You can just blather.
The recorder is still on.
I'm thinking about passing gas.
Oops, I don't even have to think about it anymore.
It's actually manifested itself into reality.
And as a result...
Whew, I gotta walk away for a minute.
Yeah, this is the time.
This is the time that all men must enter their adulthood and take hold of the beer bear.
A beer bear.
And wrangle that guy back into control.
I'm not sure.
Get that beer bear up with his beer belly.
All right.
Wow, what's that?
So...
So, okay, Dr. Drummond, I've got my...
I want you to fetch me a Lagunitas and...
Okay.
I've got me a Frappinitas.
What is that noise in the background?
Sounds like you're dragging a coffin across a concrete floor.
I was just dragging a coffin across a concrete floor.
Oh, okay.
That was a good guess on my part.
Yeah, very good.
Very good.
See, that's exactly what it sounds like.
Yeah.
To have drawn a carpet of concrete often across a carpeted floor.
It's heavy.
Oh, I had it backwards.
Anyway, what we got...
So now it's the hour of slack number 1,800.
2,889.
Wow.
I can't believe it.
That's definitely a milestone of magnificent proportion.
Huge.
Well, yeah.
Who else has done almost 2,000 subgenius radio shows?
Well, Puzzling Evidence has been on since 1982 and still is.
And our slack started at 1,000.
It started in October 1985.
Wow.
Yeah.
So it's been...
I don't even want to think about the math.
It's too much.
Do you remember how jealous we were when Doug Wellman had his own radio show and he
was doing stuff and sending us tapes?
Man, we had to do that.
It's amazing how competitive we were.
We were back then with our friends.
Well, yeah.
But once I finally got a show, I played a whole lot of their show, you know?
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Because it was so great.
The parts that you could hear were really great.
Then there were the other parts.
Yeah.
That no one would want to hear except Puzzling Evidence in headphones.
Right.
Well, I wanted to hear them, you know?
Oh, well.
I like to hear all the bad and the good.
The good and the bad.
That's very...
Noble.
Yeah.
Noble of me.
I kind of like that.
Well, okay.
To listeners who don't know anything, we're the two original cool guys that Bob first
recruited.
Yeah.
And we allow a small group of other almost as cool guys to hang out.
We shouldn't talk that way.
They get real mad when we do that.
You better cut this part out.
We're not out of the race.
That's right.
But it's true, though.
The handsome and mature gents are few and far between, but...
We're a special elite squad of subgenius hierarchites.
Right.
Yeah.
We make big decisions in the background.
So, okay.
Okay.
Onan sent me this letter.
And when he wants to tell me something real...
I mean, we talk all the time in text.
But when he wants me to take something real seriously, he'll actually send it by mail.
You know, I was dragging my feet on getting that Agent and Mr. Dobbs book out, which bothered
him because he had actually done all the layout and work himself.
Yeah.
And he...
He was just waiting for you to put your imprimatur on it.
Your imprimatur.
I got this immensely heavy box in the mail that probably cost 50 bucks to mail from him.
And inside was a brick with the word Agent and Mr. Dobbs written in charcoal on it.
And basically, I had to carry that brick around until I got that job done.
And we did get the hardcover.
We got the $50 hardcover edition is out and all sold out.
And then I dragged my feet on the paperback.
But by the time people hear this tonight, I'll have that purchase button on subgenius.com.
In the book section.
And people can buy the Agent and Mr. Dobbs, which is hilarious.
It is hilarious.
I've got my...
I actually have my copy here.
Yeah.
Right here in front of me.
It's very much like a cross between H.P.
Lovecraft and the Three Stooges.
Yeah.
Right.
It is.
If that could be done.
It captures...
This book does it.
It captures the essence.
The essence of Bob better than just about anything else anybody's done, including me.
It's amazing.
Yeah.
And you know, people would be...
You know, if they...
I could just say that, you know, that particular line about any H.P.
Lovecraft fan or...
And any Three Stooges fan.
You don't have to be both.
You could just be one or the other.
And still find this to be a very interesting and revealing...
If not enlightening book.
Yeah.
Mainly, it's just really funny.
It's funny.
You'll probably laugh more than anything.
Now, here's the weird thing.
I have not...
I have not heard back from Titor LaVerge since I sent him the first copies of the hardcover.
Maybe he got drunk in celebration and is still celebrating.
Well, another...
He was still on Facebook, but he was talking about Ukraine.
I think he's, you know, from a Ukrainian background.
Oh.
Maybe he went over there to be a freedom fighter.
Despite the name LaVerge.
Yeah, right.
I don't know.
But he's...
He's just kind of fan of...
You know, it could be...
I don't know, but it could be that LaVerge may be a subgenius name.
It may not be actually a birth name.
Titor LaVerge?
It might not be his conspiracy name.
So, he might have some real dull name like...
Yeah.
Bill Smith or Doug Wilcox or...
No.
It's gonna be a Ukrainian name.
It's gonna be like, you know, Vladimir Shmugmoid or whatever they have over there.
Right.
Okay.
Well, anyway, here's this letter that Onan sent.
And it's kind of...
The first page is pretty short.
Then there's a short story, a true story about P.T.
Barnum and Grizzly Adams.
Oh.
Okay.
But get this.
Please stop Hour of Slack.
I'm sorry.
Please stop at any day, at any time, unannounced or no.
Stop.
Lots of work, lots of time, little pay, much complaining.
And you know, you guys and my wife hear the complaining.
In fact, Princess Wee said that I'd been complaining about having to do this stupid show as long
as she knew me, which was 1990 or something.
Oh, yeah.
Anyway, Onan says, you won.
You outlasted most paid career DJs.
And it's true.
Hour of Slack has been on longer than Johnny Carson or what's his name more.
We ought to work on like a Wikipedia page just for Hour of Slack.
Well, there is one, but...
A groundbreaking show that lasted longer than everything else, you know?
Yeah.
But all the ground was totally broken afterwards.
It's completely broken.
You had to repair it.
It's all soft.
It's completely soft and mushy now.
You can't even repair it.
It's mushy.
You can't.
You can't grow anything in it.
No.
Anyway, he says, free up that complaining for something else.
Permission granted.
The listeners don't know this, but I really do complain because it's a routine.
It's not just...
Yeah.
There's all this other stuff I have to do that a nutless chimpanzee could do my job if
only I could train him to read numbers.
He says...
You might need one nut.
He says, every X day...
Oh, you're right.
That's not funny, Dr. Drummond.
Every X day in Devival has a curtain.
Every book has a back cover, and yet, subgenius rolls on and you roll on.
I am specifically not...
I am not saying to switch to any other anything.
Not web, not books, not dogs, not anything.
Just stop doing the one thing over and over as if there will be a different result.
Whatever it is, are you making it better or are you making it worse?
And I've been...
I've sort of been begging for permission to quit this weekly routine for a long time.
Yeah.
Let's face it.
There's 2,000 shows that anybody can listen to anytime.
Anytime.
Or play on their own station or podcast.
That's right.
I even...
I could call them up.
They're retrievable.
They're like archived and all ready to go.
Anybody could even mechanize that process if they wanted to.
Actually, some stations did, I think, already.
Yeah.
It's simple.
It's like I'm 168 years old.
Right.
I'm 168.
I'm...
Everything's taking longer.
It takes...
And you were that sacred scribe for that other religion before this one.
Well, we don't talk about that.
But there's...
You know, there...
I'm still sacred scribe number 273, but there's going to be a number 274.
Yeah.
And I think he's already...
I think he's probably going to be...
Yeah, he's probably already...
I think he's like in his, you know...
Yeah.
...journeyman phase.
You know, he's more than an apprentice now.
He's actually graduated up almost to yeoman.
Well...
Not quite there.
Right.
Well, he...
And he's done his own...
He did the Man of Books and his own podcast and things.
Yeah.
He's done...
He actually at one point offered...
Man of Letters.
Yeah, Man of Letters.
He offered to take over the show at one point.
But, you know, I don't want to do that.
It would be a different show.
It wouldn't be the Hour of Slack.
Yeah.
That's right.
And we're not getting the contributions.
You know, there's no Lee Murr cranking out new stuff anymore.
Yeah.
That's all from the olden days.
So the content is, you know...
The content's harder to come by and not just...
But that's not a really...
It's not that much harder to just...
And here's another thing.
I'm not an angry young man anymore.
Yeah.
Right.
You're like a happy old man.
I'm angry...
Yeah, well, I'm angry at chronic diseases and aches and pains and that kind of thing.
Who isn't angry at that, though?
I mean, that's everybody's anger, you know?
No, not everybody has chronic pain, believe me.
Not like you.
Not like you, I would say.
Hey, we...
Well, remember, a long time ago, we needed units of measurement for things like pain
and slack and confusion...
Yeah.
...and inebriation.
And the first...
We both immediately landed on Drummond.
...and stangs of...
Or was it phylos of slack?
Yeah, phylos of slack.
And stangs of pain.
Yeah.
And that may have been a self-fulfilling prophecy.
Man, we should have been given...
We should have given old Stang some upside.
Well, there was janers of confusion and I think sternos of inebriation.
And I forget what some of the other ones were.
They...
I don't remember.
I remember that may have all been cut from Revelation X.
Yeah.
Just think about all the stuff that got cut.
Well, that...
See, there's another whole half a book right there.
History.
And I'd like to be scanning old things that were never published that happened before
the internet.
Yeah.
But after we quit publishing because the postage cost too much and it was too hard
and I always lost my shirt...
Yeah.
...on this giant...
Do you remember what...
Reverend Stang, do you remember when the internet was just like seven guys with tape
decks?
Yeah.
Right.
That was our internet.
Yeah.
That was the only...
That was the only worthwhile part of the internet.
It was very slow and it was mostly audio but it was mobile.
I mean, we would record...
We would talk to each other and do...
And it was fun.
Really fun.
Yeah.
Well...
Man.
We all had horrible real life jobs then and we needed that fun.
We had...
Yeah.
When we managed to take a break, we didn't waste it.
No kidding.
Whereas now, we're kind of jaded in that respect and both of us have farming chores
that we...
Yeah.
I got animals to feed and...
Right.
...and crops to harvest.
Yeah.
It's...
I got a...
I got some crops.
Man, the squash has been coming in.
Whoo.
Yeah.
I saw those pictures.
Dr. Drummond actually has a farm with crops because it rains and he has dirt.
Yeah.
I have a very big garden but it's in pots because our dirt is not really...
It's...
Yeah.
I feel sorry for your dirt, man.
Because our dirt is so...
It's just like you just plant...
You just put seeds in it and they grow.
Well, you put cactus seeds in this stuff and it'll grow and seed...
Well, that's true.
Yeah.
But yeah, it's...
You put it...
You said it well.
You said it was...
This land had an ornamental dusting of dirt over a foundation of solid limestone.
Yeah.
That's what it is.
I was just out there...
That's just where the limestone got worn down a little bit and turned into dirt.
The limestone is all made of dead sea creatures, shells.
Yeah.
It actually is.
I mean, if you look at it real close in a lot of areas, if you know what you're looking
at, you're looking at ancient eroded sea shells that were piled up for billions and billions
of years or something.
So...
Oh, here's the rest of this letter about the Quintin the Hour Slack.
Yeah.
And you know, I hate to admit it, but I have been thinking about it for about 25 years.
My first wife was so happy when I got kicked off KNON, she thought I would stop.
But I just kept making tapes and sending them to the other stations.
Anyway, here's more in ONAN's excellent handwriting.
One day, a man made an appointment to see P.T.
Barnum at his American museum.
The visitor was known to Barnum.
Grizzly Adams!
Mr. Adams was begging for a job.
Barnum put him to work wrestling bears.
After a time, Barnum asked Adams to come to his office and say how things were going.
Adams had taken the job to pay for his children's education so that they did not have to wrestle
bears past retirement.
Adams appeared in Barnum's office but left his animal skin cap on.
Barnum said he was accustomed to men remembering that.
Making them sit at their desk in the back of their office is like removing their hat in his office.
Adams removed his hat.
And so revealed a great wound on his head.
Adams explained a bear had bitten him, removing flesh and part of his skull.
But he didn't want to quit for his children.
Barnum wrote out a check to pay for his children's education and fired him on the spot.
Don't be Grizzly Adams.
So I think what ONAN is saying is that,
You know, I've been bitten by the bear enough times, and my children are past the age of education, and it is getting...
That is so frightening.
Doing those links every week, it's the linking, and you have to write a blurb.
You have to write a little blurb about it.
Yeah, the blurb always got me.
I could do all the mechanical stuff, but the blurb, man, you had to take time.
You actually had to listen to the show and make...
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
My website has logs of just about everything.
You know, any show that has less than 100 cuts, I'll usually have a log of it.
Yeah.
It's really just the file names and the order they were played, but, you know, it's a lot of stuff, and it's all still there.
And, you know, if I get a wild hare, and we do something.
And it's really amazing.
Yeah, a special show.
You know, I can always tack it on as, you know, here's an hour of, like, annual special.
It'd be like the Ewok special for Steven Spielberg, you know?
That was George Lucas.
The Christmas, the Star Wars...
Yeah, the Star Wars Christmas special.
Star Wars Christmas special.
You need a...
You'll have an hour of that Christmas special.
That's so bad that people can't...
That it's a collector's item.
It becomes a cult classic.
Because of...
It's just whole, total badness, you know?
People have to seek it out.
Well, that would...
Artificially restricted supply.
That would be when Princess Wee and I finally record our 17-minute rock dog opera, Buddy, based on Tommy.
You read the lyrics.
You thought they were hilarious.
Yeah.
We're ready to go.
I actually have...
I found a website that pulls the vocals out of sound.
Wow.
And I used the Live at Leeds version of Tommy and removed the vocals.
It sounds a little weird.
And, of course, Princess Wee is almost a professional singer.
Yeah, she can actually sing, but you are different.
Yeah, I'm a little different.
Dave, Reverend Angry Larry said,
I want to help you do that, just so you won't be the one singing.
Yeah, you know, I miss him.
I used to get to see him every year.
At least once a year, and now I don't get to see him anymore.
So that's the bad, sad thing about X Day being a do-it-yourself thing.
Oh, Reverend Angry Larry?
Yeah.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
I mean, well...
I've been here at my house for some...
Like, for five people.
Yeah.
But it's too late now.
Well, I mean, no...
You know...
I mean...
Reverend Xanthia is going to start her resort up again.
She's got new land, and she's moving the weird domes and buildings and all of her stuff.
I don't know where she gets the energy.
Oh, now I remember.
She's never done...
She doesn't do drugs.
Oh.
She didn't really drink or frop or anything.
Man, I don't know if I like people like that.
Oh, she's wonderful, actually.
She's great.
But she's an overachiever.
She always looks like...
She's kind of in pain in those pictures.
I think it's just the...
I think it's just the artificial irises.
The irises.
That's what does it.
Oh, the contact lenses?
Yeah.
Well, she sure does work hard in her...
Oh, yes, she does.
Skimpy, skimpy costumes.
You sure can tell that, for sure.
A lot of subgeniuses went...
I don't know.
How can she be a subgenius?
She's too beautiful and too...
I don't know.
Right.
And...
She's too...
I don't know.
She's actually come to this house and was really cool.
I've stayed at her house, but she's moving.
But we still might have ex-days in Florida.
However, right now, you know, because of my situation, I can't leave.
We're going to have an ex-day here.
Just me and Princess Wee and Wee Mama.
Who is mostly pretty out of it because she's heading for the saucers.
That's why I can't go anywhere.
Yeah.
And so, I would love to do that stuff again, but I'm not ever going to go back to Ohio.
Oh, no.
I don't want to get on airplanes and I don't want to...
I can't carry luggage anymore.
That's what broke my back was all those ex-days.
Packing the car.
Unpacking it in a big hurry.
I can remember every time I picked up a case wrong and went, oh, that was a mistake.
You had a pinched nerve recently, right?
Yeah.
I used to get one.
I got over my pinched nerve.
That's something that I would get almost every ex-day and suffer through it.
Oh, man.
That's why...
You mentioned that I grunted incessantly.
Yeah.
You know, my grunting has only gotten more constant and louder.
And it drives people...
It actually makes people feel sorry for you, but...
I know, because I'm always going...
But then the other day, you know, not too long ago, actually, maybe a little while ago,
I noticed I was grunting a lot more.
Like, wait, why am I grunting?
Well, folks, it's just a sign that happens.
It's a sign that you're transitioning into a different setting.
It's a sign that you're in a different phase of existence.
Yeah, a skeleton.
One that you need to maximize.
You know, it's like I was telling somebody the other day, is that every age of man has
its advantages and disadvantages.
And you don't want to get all bogged down in the disadvantages of being an old man that
you forget about the advantages.
It's great.
If you look around, you know, you're always getting a discount on a buffet somewhere.
That's true.
Princess, we got shopping on Tuesday.
Tuesdays and Thursdays, because that's old folks' 5% off day.
Yeah, see, people always want to say, hey, go to McDonald's.
They give me coffee for like 70 cents.
Yeah, the first time that happened, I didn't ask, and I didn't understand.
I looked at it and went, oh, man, they can...
They did that.
I didn't even ask, you know.
They gave me a senior discount.
And that was 15 years ago.
So my point is just don't forget, you know.
Every age is a special...
It's a special time, and you got to live it.
Live it.
Live it or lose it.
Dolomite said something about when I get old, Dolomite's not going to lay around and feel
sad.
He's going to get his kicks thinking about all the swinging times that he's had.
That's exactly right.
Dolomite was, you know, he was a great philosopher.
Yeah, but he's dead.
Yeah.
Well, nobody lasts forever.
That's for sure.
Some of us are lucky if we make it to, you know, 70, 80, 90.
Well, that's the thing.
We're lucky.
We're already lucky.
Yeah.
I mean, I think 73 is the average age of a white man in America.
That's about the...
If you're a 73-year-old subgenius right now, you're a lucky son of a buck.
Yeah, I think I'm in or you're dead.
Son of a mother...
A mother buck.
Yeah.
I read the list earlier before you were on.
It's a long list of people who are already on the saucers.
Oh, well.
Already made it up there.
They're reading their old comic book collection right now.
And all good things must come to an end.
And we're thinking maybe show number 2,000, which is 10 shows from now, maybe that, we
can say, will be the last show.
But wait.
Why?
What symbology does 2,000 have?
Nothing.
I mean...
Doesn't 1998 have a much better symbology?
Actually, yeah, that would only be eight more shows.
Eight more shows.
I like that.
Yeah.
To 1998.
That's it.
Yeah.
2,000.
Anybody would end their career at 2,000.
Anybody can end there because it's round.
You know, the first thing somebody says is, oh, you're going to be 2,000.
You're going to stop at 2,000.
Oh, wait a minute.
I just thought about something.
That's another 100 shows.
I would actually have to stop at 1,900 because we're at 1,889.
Yeah, that's...
Oh, damn.
Yes, that wrecks the whole thing.
1,900, who cares about that?
Yeah, who cares about that?
You know what Onan would say?
Onan would say, well, just end it right now.
Just, that's it.
And we could just turn the recorders off right now and say, okay.
Yeah.
And that'd be it.
I'm not going to do that, though.
I'm going to play...
No.
I'm going to play Dockstock Mountain.
High on Dockstock Mountain from the Soak Your Butt album by the Swingin' Love Corpses.
Why does this one sound so much better than the one I've played?
Because this one was actually recorded in our little basement studio, you know, when
we were trying to practice and do things well.
We weren't actually in a...
Not that we weren't trying to do things well in a show.
It wasn't in that...
Right.
It's just harder to get a good recording.
Yeah.
And we never had good minds.
Yikes are good recording attempts.
We were too worried about doing a show.
Right.
And unfortunately never had really good live recordings.
Well, there's some.
I think some of my best of Swingin' Love Corpses is live because...
But it was just, you know, it was collected from old tapes.
So anyway, this is about the Dockstocks that we used to...
Actually, Sterno, you might say, was the host of those in Arkansas.
Yeah.
They were secret subgenius gatherings.
They were secret gatherings that only like 20 or 30 people and maybe their spouses and
kids would even be invited to.
And they were pretty wild.
And everybody would jam and rant and swim in the lake.
Fun times.
Those were great.
So anyway, here's a song about it.
High on Dockstock Mountain.
Okay.
That's where we play.
Here's a song.
Here we go.
From across the nation they came and they saw
A new world begin in northern Arkansas
They drove the storms and hurled the night
To the new awakening and dark, dark inside
They shared seeds of love and great times
Eternity was there and they were meeting in time
Body was there but they were few
There was mostly cool guys like me and you
And we got high, so high on Dr. Council
Yeah, we got high, so high on Dr. Council
We ate lots of mushrooms to commune with nature
How old were we?
We took no weed at the move our sh** later
Five hundred colors flashed into my brain
My cell division occurred in three or four planes
My brain was blasted, my head feeling thick
My eyeballs protruded but I didn't get sick
We packed up our tips but we kept seeing dots
Then we found that the peaks had gotten all the best spots
So we got high, so high on Dr. Council
Yeah, we got high, so high on Dr. Council
People were happy, they were all having fun
While Dr. Sir Bob was farming skulls in the sun
The corpses were swinging, their love did abound
The average corpse floated a foot off the ground
But the sun was still shining, the sun was still shining
The bandit's hair knot was speaking its name
While his doctors on the plant show was claiming their fame
Sparkdog explosion and combo gang punch
Finisists said, just in time for lunch
And we got high, so high on Dr. Council
Yeah, we got high, so high on Dr. Council
We packed up our tips and our heads feeling thick
And we kept seeing dots
We packed up our tips and our hair knot was claiming their fame
But we got high, so high on Dr. Council
Now we travel, we get ill, break we wake
We packed up our tips and our hair knot was claiming their fame
Break through to Collaboratal
I'm gonna go back there
I'll even meet the Pope
Better make it to Doc's Dock
Or just give up hope
The dead will be walking
Maybe Bob will appear
The sound of chainsaws
Will be all that you hear
Now I'm gonna go back
And I won't be stopped
I'm gonna go back
To smoke the ultimate frown
You just can't imagine
What it's like to you go
When reality's on hold
And Doc's Dock's a show
We got a lot
So why
Do you want Doc's Dock
Now?
Oh yeah
We got high
Too high
To Doc's Dock
Now
Oh yeah
I went way up high
On Doc's Dock Mountain
I climbed down
I climbed up all the way to the top
I took everything you could think of
I shot
Beer
I smoked heroin
I snorted marijuana
I stuck
A stiff glue
I put
Um
Barbiturate
Propositories in my rectal cavity
I um
I soul danced on Venus with James Brown's sister-in-law
I've seen ten square miles of asphalt
And then I got stuck up there on top of Doc's Dock Mountain
Cause the song was over before I could ever come down
So now I'm lost in a Doc's Dock
Frappulated hell neither world
In the song
Man, okay, tell me when you're gonna go back into the show
We can talk about how awesome that was
Okay, yeah, I'm gonna go back into the show
Cause you know that particular one I really dragged out
Yeah, okay, one, two, three, go
Man, that was so awesome
Yeah, that was a great version
I think we were probably a little bit inebriated or something
During that one
That's you singing mostly and not your brother, isn't it?
Yeah, that's my brother, my cousin
Singing in the background vocals
And I was singing lead there
Yeah
I know you and Colonel Sphinx Drummond traded off a lot
Right
We traded songs
Generally we didn't trade in a song
You know, he'd do one or I'd do another
And then we'd trade backup parts
Things like that
Every now and then my cousin, my brother cousin
Would do some vocals
Dr. Ray Hay
Dr. Ray Hay, right
And yeah
I'm actually in the process right now
Of getting all of the live footage in one place
So I can
My plan is to make this little bit of a playlist
Kind of a thing that anybody that wanted it
Could easily watch all of the live footage that I have
Of Swingin' Love Corpses
Listeners, the Swingin' Love Corpses were long before Spinal Tap
And I think that's a good thing
And yet there's a lot of similarities
There's a lot of differences too
There's a whole lot of differences
We played a role
You know, we were a band that was
A famous touring band
That had met harder times
And was doing local shows again
And our tours may have only been like
Two stops in the U.S. that year
You know
Yeah, like the subgenius world
World tours
Yeah
And so
But yeah, we played that role
And it was a lot of fun
And we all had wigs
In fact, that was one of our few rules
Is that you could not appear on stage
Without your wig on
Yeah, they had
And wild costumes
Very tasteless
And crazy outfits
Yeah, our outfits were based on some hippie's nightmare
Yeah
A bad trip
A hippie's bad trip
And there was great spaz dancing
During the instrumental parts
Yeah, we had
In fact, we talked about
Just recently
How we had a character named
Beetle Bob
Who would show up at our shows
And he was really tall
And he would stand right in front
And do the craziest dancing
Right in the middle
Right
Now, unfortunately
People couldn't see me as well
Right
When Beetle Bob was there
Even though I admired his dancing
And didn't want to lose his draw appeal
So what we did is
We would prepare
Because Beetle Bob came to every show
We got some
Like that kind of tape
That they tape off where
You know
Crime scene
And we taped off an area
And then designated it
Beetle Bob only
Over on the side, right?
Oh, it was on the side
Yeah
But up front
Right up front
Next to the stage
But a little over to the side
So that he wouldn't obscure
The audience's view of me
I always used to videotape
My favorite bands like yours
And the amino acids
From the side of the stage
So my right ear was pointing directly
At the main speakers
And that's why I can't hear anything
In my right ear
Yeah
Isn't that funny?
It'll do it to you
It's not
It's funny but only in an ironic sense
So anyway
Let's play one more
Swingin' Love Corpses song
And this one's an instrumental
That you just posted recently
I'd never heard
And the title of this one is
Rock Roll Lead Zep
With Robert Planet Voice Horn Parts
All one word
There you go
That's pretty much a good description
Dot Wave
We can climb up on Doc's Doc Mountain
While that song plays
Yeah
Okay
We know what that means
Okay here goes
Yeah
Okay
Thank you.