You'll have to excuse Ivan's manner.
If you behave yourself, he'll hurt you.
Look, what kind of a creep joint is this?
Place of research, and Ivan.
Oh, yeah?
That's a genius, Harry.
A slap.
Perfect.
Oh, yes.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
No.
No, no, no.
Oh, yes.
Oh, no.
Okay.
All right.
Let's see how this works.
Oh, I think it might work.
It just might work.
Hello?
Uh, yes, dear friends.
We're live.
Hi, dear friends.
I'm stupid.
What?
How, how, how?
I've been strange.
Dr. Ivan Strange.
That's me.
String.
Can you hear me okay?
Yeah.
I can hear.
Okay.
Yes.
The mute button is off, and the mutes have all been sent home.
The mutes.
Why isn't the mute on?
May I ask you one question?
Yeah.
Why isn't the mute on when they can't say anything to it anyway?
You're going to have to ask that in clearer English, because I'm hard.
Why you, why you send the mutes, mutos back home when they don't have any television and
their feet are bound like the lady?
I send the mutos home because they live here.
This is where the mutos live.
They're the ones that are barfing out all the glass and building up all the company
forests and stuff?
Oh, no, no.
I have them out planting flowers in the garden.
Ah.
They're.
That's important.
Yeah.
Especially since we're expecting another one of those killer Texas deep freezes in about
four days.
Oh, you're going to get the deep freeze in four days, eh?
Did you see what's happening on the East Coast there?
I saw what's happening where you live in Ashtabula, thanks to our friend, friends Potter and Petal
Nostril.
They had photos out showing their driveway, which was just white.
That's all there was.
It was just white.
Yeah.
Plus, a few Eskimos hiding under the garden there, waiting to make their move.
As soon as you come out there, they pull up weapons out and have big clamor, big reaction
to everything else that's going on.
Like Zupyr and Zuz and all those guys that have similar names.
Zupyr and Zuz?
Zupyr and Zuz.
And Zuz.
Want to fight a war in the Metromia.
Or not Metromia, but the Ukraine-ish.
Oh, yeah.
I like that show.
I love Zussi.
He and Hera were always fighting.
Hera is what they named her after, right?
That's what it sounds like.
It could have been Hera's or no Hera's, like in myself.
I've been offered the opportunity, but I've never taken it.
Well, you're locked in.
You're now snowed in to the insane asylum where you live, right?
Yes, I am.
They may wheel out a dead person or go and talk somebody down
or maybe just start using the four-letter word real profusely
and saying you blank, blank, blank and shooting off a gun.
I always liked that, too.
I mean, I don't like it that much, but it's exciting, you know.
Better than watching PBS television.
Just listening to the sounds of fights around you
and your emotions.
Insane asylum.
Yeah, and women screaming real loud.
I knew what you were like when I, you know, this is all your fault.
And the guys sound really crazy, like they might have done time.
I don't know which time, you know.
Old time or ancient times or just time of the time of time.
Do you ever hear one of them say to another one,
shut up, little man?
Yeah.
Oh, you have?
Okay, I know those two guys.
They walked right straight.
Well, she did anyway.
Walked straight up to my penis and said that.
Shut up, little man.
Yeah, as if I had ears and could accommodate her.
I don't know.
Well, Dave, it's a study in contrast because here at Stang Ranch,
it's literally 71 degrees and lovely outside.
And I took my first walk for about a month and nothing broke.
Not my toe, not my back, nothing.
Nothing.
And I daily planted flowers all along.
Well, you have been gay for a long time,
so why not plant flowers daily all along the way?
Oh, they're such gay flowers.
I really did.
And hold them to your bosom and do your Fred Astaire dance?
That's what nurturing naturism is the difference about.
Actually, I don't do the planting.
The MUTOs are following behind me doing all that.
Well, they're making plenty of hand movements at least, aren't they?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And they have flowers growing out the top of their heads.
It makes them look cute.
Yeah, yeah.
There's several different types.
There's red mutants, albinos, yellow ones, blue ones, big.
The purple ones are always really fat.
Yeah, purple fatties, they call them the fecund ones.
I named one of them Fat Pandi.
Yeah.
I get to name them, see.
They forget their names when they come after me.
Yeah, they're always the same.
And then after we finish with them, the MUTOs forget their names and we give them new ones
in the cult.
Yeah.
At least I always ... I just agree with you as usual, 1,000%.
Well, I usually agree with you because I can't really understand half of what you're saying.
But that's not just you, Dave.
That's almost everybody.
You can't understand everybody?
I can't understand everybody.
I need subtitles.
You do.
In Swedish and Italian, you need subtitles.
There's two little layers there in one in Swedish and one in Italian.
You pretend it's 1978 and you're getting first exposure to foreign films.
You're learning what a ... Oh, nihilist ... Not like a nihilism, but ... Nevermind.
Nevermind.
Well, you know what's really maddening is ... You've wanted to watch the movie, but
you haven't watched this movie for a long time, and you're going to get to watch it,
but you're on Air Portugal.
It's in English, but they've added Portuguese subtitles to the bottom of it.
Well, by the time the movie's over, you can't remember the movie, but you've learned Portuguese,
or at least a little bit.
Yeah.
Enough to get by in Sao Paulo.
Right.
I mean, I've watched lots of Italian, German, Dutch movies with subtitles, whatever.
I'm not going to get into that.
I also watch American, English, and Australian movies with subtitles in English, because
I can't speak the lingo that these kids do these days.
They're too fast.
They talk like you, basically, kind of mumble.
And so it's for those of us with crisp, clear diction and microphones, we ...
That's what you call it, eh?
Yeah.
That's what the kids are called.
I got a big diction, baby.
I got a whole bunch of them.
Big ones, big ones.
You got a big dictionary to prove it.
Yes, sir.
I got one of those great big 500-pound ones.
I did, actually.
That's where about half of the subgenius doctrine came from.
Philo and I, since Bob wasn't helping, would just open this giant dictionary and put our
fingers down on a word randomly.
E popped.
Hey, that's what Bob is.
In fact, that's exactly what Bob is.
That's where we got his title.
It was just random going through the dictionary.
Put your hand down.
Breaks.
Breaks, yeah.
Some people have bad breaks.
No governor.
No controller.
They can't exist within the circle.
Don't work and play well with others.
Haven't mastered the masks of insanity, which you have to have to act normal and get a job,
see?
Right.
Because in many dimensions, you couldn't act normally even if you tried.
And they fire you before they hire you.
They make to make sure that the deed is done.
You know, like a lot of people that hire you, then they fire you.
It's time.
Yes, it's wonderful.
It's like a barbecue in your backyard with your family that you hate and want to shoot.
And everybody just likes your haircut.
And I never mind.
I'm sorry.
Luckily, I don't.
I don't have one.
I'm diffused.
I don't have one of those kind of families.
I have a.
I have an idyllic, wonderful family.
Well, except for the murder and the.
Well, you are being attacked by vampires right now to want to.
I know.
No, no, no.
They they don't bother me.
I've got the vampire repellent.
It's worked for decades now.
I have ghost ghost repellent, UFO repellent, Chupacabra repellent.
And of course, nobody will come near me.
Right.
Including my dogs.
Because they're all made for raw sewage.
All made for raw sewage.
Yeah, all of those things combined.
Bear repellent, of course.
Wasp repellent.
Women of St. John's.
I used to bring wasp attractant to X-Day just in case we ever needed to target a reverend bastard,
one of those guys that you wish hadn't come and they're hard to get rid of.
Well, you put the wasp attractant on them.
There is such a thing.
Well, that's horrible.
It sounds like what the Japanese OSS forces in World War III might have done if they were full of compunction.
You know, like sometimes they would blow farts.
That's the common term anyway.
Blow farts on the enemy.
And they'd be so disgraced by the time they go to that big sales meeting and speak as, you know,
like show their whole doctrine and everything and the different churches they were going to open up.
That's when they come and arrest them, right?
At that very moment.
They send the officers of the law to do their duty.
Well, you know, in America today, basically, you can get arrested for anything, literally.
But not if you're wearing swaddling clothes, whatever the hell those are.
Swathering clothes?
Sweltering clothes?
Swaddling clothes?
And a babe would come in swaddling.
That's what Drew—
Our Savior.
The Savior of the Fourth and the Third.
He popped.
Well, not that Savior.
The Avatar Savior.
The Third Ray.
I always thought swaddling clothes were what you wrap drunk people up in so when they vomited,
that would sort of catch most of their vomit and keep it off your nice white couch.
Which, yeah, was referred to as the swaddle.
A lot of people just like save the swaddle in little mason jars or plastic plates
and just like stick them in their room somewhere where the kids can't find them.
But other ones are more, a lot more, you know, a lot more.
Yeah, more.
More.
More on these morons later.
But now, this.
Abstrusia.
Now, when I count to three, your dollar bill will still be there.
Are you ready?
Number one.
One.
Number two.
Two.
Three.
One.
Four o'clock.
Three.
Two.
Twenty.
Rock.
Eight o'clock.
Seven.
Eight.
Rock.
Seven.
Ten.
Nine.
One.
Bob.
Oh, that's beautiful.
Yeah.
I say it's beautiful and you trust me.
The time is free.
Woo.
Oh, here it is.
Did you notice the transition I just did where I say, and now this?
That's what you say when you run out of anything to say.
You just go, and now this.
Yeah, but I was supposed to concur with you in the good old German, German, German, German way.
Instead, I did my own thing not knowing what I was doing.
So, don't feel sad.
Just feel sorry for me.
Oh, I always feel.
Everybody feels.
Terribly sorry for you, lonesome, because you're so lonesome.
Yeah, that's the way it is today, anyway.
I couldn't even go out on my beautiful balcony to look at the Civil War era house across
the street here, which hasn't been painted since the 1860s.
But, that was funny.
Thanks for taking that, for laughing at that.
Well, I had an almost Civil War era house.
It was in Cleveland.
And I was embarrassed at the paint job.
We spent a lot of money getting it painted.
And then it sold for just about nothing.
We really, in the end, we should have just given it away.
Yeah, you could have turned it into a soup kitchen and startled the turtles, you know, so to speak.
No, that's what we were doing out here in Texas with the MUTOs.
We feed them and make them plant for us.
Sometimes they plant each other.
They're good little skull farmers, you know.
Yep.
Little red beards, little red beards and little, you know, little packages of toast in their
back pockets, ready to make the best kind of statement they can make this time of year,
this wonderful holiday season, which is over now.
Well, you know, our skulls are so expensive now.
Because they taste.
So good.
Well, no, no, it's not that.
It's that the fertilizer has like tripled in price because the one big company that made skull fertilizer went out of business.
Thanks to the COVIDs and one of them.
And so now it's all imported skull fertilizer.
And of course, you don't know what you're getting.
And it's all cut with fentanyl or something like that.
Especially if it's from China, it can be cheese.
Or underwear.
It could be anything.
Right.
Yeah.
I quit buying anything that comes from most other countries lately.
Unfortunately, that includes almost everything.
Pretty soon it'll be all the food, too.
I'm not sure what I'm going to do then.
Oh, yeah.
Farming skulls.
But, you know, skulls don't really have, they have a lot of calcium, but it's not like there's a brain in there anymore.
It's not going to.
It's not going to anymore, you know, so.
No.
Well, I'm glad you found it.
I feel that way because we all have to have a motivation in life that gives us fulfillment.
Like, if you want to eat the skull packets and you want to feed them and dish them out to the kids and stuff like that after they've been cooked in their own raw natural juices, that is fine with me and fine with you, I hope.
Or else you'd be, you know, schizoid and die-crossed.
Oh, we end up, we've learned how to make skull pie, skull soup.
Skull soup.
Skull.
That's a favorite.
Ice cream.
Oh.
I've never had skull ice cream, so I didn't answer on that one.
It's like garlic.
I heard it's.
It's like garlic ice cream.
It's really just a gimmick.
Just, you know, like, put this label on anything, anywhere and try and sell it for five bucks or something.
I've seen garlic ice cream for sale.
In Gilroy, America's garlic capital.
Capital.
Gilroy garlic and Altadena for milk products.
Gilroy, California.
Driving through that town and the environs around it, everything smells like the excrement of cows that have been living on garlic their entire lives.
It's not really that disagreeable of a smell.
Great.
Walk and stay.
You know, it's herbivore scat in giant masses.
But it's garlic scented.
Steak guitar.
Steak guitar with garlic.
I hope at least till tomorrow.
Maybe Tuesday or Wednesday.
Yep.
This is the gross girl with three children.
She gave up their children.
What year?
Okay.
Yeah.
And doing what I did.
You know, you know, I'd say don't do that.
Having was not.
But I do think because I think but I don't think what three prongs.
And I think a lot of women are uncomfortable.
And I think it's great.
Yes.
No, I think because I think, you know, to think, you know, I think to think.
And you talk a little bit about your mother was blown to bits.
I began to think that's a risk.
I think.
I'm prepared to take.
Right.
Well, our book critic has a book for the first time.
Yeah.
Dave, I actually went for a walk today.
You know, I've been bedridden and I try to get rid of my bed.
But I have been stuck there for a couple of months on and off.
And I went out today.
It was sunny.
And I got my Muto's coming gaily behind me, throwing flower seeds.
And flowers everywhere.
Banging their heads against trees until they were bloody.
And we just had us a great old time.
Walked all the way around.
And that does sound great.
The the the places that are easy for a hobbling old fellow to walk.
And by golly, I didn't.
Don't want to get his way.
I never felt that.
Well, that's lovers leap.
And in some places, but quarters, it's obviously it really is fornicators way.
They have their own.
You know, the problem is that wherever kids go to park and make out, that's where the monsters go.
Don't they like to appear over the trunk and over the shoulder shot a little bit over the top of the head and a screaming woman in the face?
What's that noise out there?
What's that noise out there, Bob?
Oh, don't worry about that, Connie.
It's probably just coyotes or something.
Don't.
There's no such thing as monsters.
Don't worry about that, Connie. It's probably just coyotes or something. Don't. There's no such thing as monsters.
Say, how do you undo this little hook back here?
Oh, it ain't got no face.
That's the good part right there.
They're shown to be faceless, but does full of foolish sentiments and desires.
Yeah, you can say that again.
No, I forgot it.
Now it would be hard to do that.
Yeah, I got to push them.
I forget to push the button every time we speak.
Indolently or architecturally.
In real life or fake life.
I always am supposed to go and hit that button,
and it will dutifully record everything that's said,
including the things that aren't funny at all,
and give them back in a gray fondant soup
of our own choosing, and that's the way it is.
Big tittas. Big tittas.
Gray flannel soup.
That's not as bad as it sounds. Yep.
You put, you know, throw some skulls in, and by golly,
you've got your own gray flannel and skull soup.
That does sound good, doesn't it?
It's weird.
Maybe we can get an across the border thing going.
What the hell?
What was that?
Oh, it's my phone hollering about some message I probably got.
It's called notifications, Dave.
Oh, great. Noticias.
But I don't have it.
That's what it says on mine.
It says it in Spanish.
It says noticias, which also means news,
which is as well as notices.
News is the funny one.
We should ask our question what it means.
What does it mean, news?
Is it new information or just right hot off the press
or near the clarinet zone where people like to get together
and play three times a week?
No, I say unto you, Lee.
At least I'll try not.
I'll try not to.
Okay, then.
From PR News in Washington, I'm drawing praise from the LGBTTBG sexual abuse community.
The Trump is offering gay sex abuse in a meeting in Chile.
Pope Francis told him, God made you like this and he loves you because he's gay.
As President Trump said two weeks ago, to protect the American people was not the objective.
President Trump doesn't back down.
He's not a mental douche creator.
Trump said, we are a gang of three.
Drink.
Members of the Senate Intelligence Committee grilled Trump about PR News, Washington.
The Veterans Group is criticizing PR.
Okay, then I say you're cooking something right now, like a foot or?
No, no, no, no.
I had a great breakfast, though.
The funny thing was Princess We had already made breakfast, but she made so much,
I thought it was for another family.
So I made my own.
And then she came and yelled and screamed at me and berated me.
And made me eat all of those hash browns that she cooked up.
There was going to be hash browns and skulls.
I'm going to be, oh, I'm sorry.
Yeah, that was it.
That's all.
I was going to be having hash browns and some hummus.
And I was going to walk up and down the hall as many times as I could to get my exercise
because it sucks so bad outside.
I'm not going to go out there.
Hey, I thought of something that we're supposed to talk about.
What is it?
The newly published.
Published subgenius books.
Now, of course, we're famous for our nonfiction holy texts, the books of the subgenius and
the other 10 that are out of print, Revelation X, Revelation C, and so forth.
And the Bobliographon and the Bobliographan and all of those.
But we started publishing on our own because, well, Amazon.
Yes.
You don't have to pay anything up front.
It's when somebody wants your book, they just, it's printed right there.
Paying behind.
Yeah.
And Amazon keeps most of the money.
Anyway, Lonesome Cowboy Dave's book, Neighbor World is out.
I don't know if everybody knew about that.
I mean, it keeps me on it.
It's such a wonderful novel.
It was our first.
Dystopian.
Yeah, it's a dystopian novel.
It's been compared with Brave New World.
1984, 1983, A Merman I Should Turn to Be.
1985, Monster Will Do Hand Jive and a whole bunch of other dystopian novels.
The entire decade, yeah.
Yeah.
What was that one you were telling me about?
The Every, the All, the Nothing.
You did not publish that one.
That is independently published by, I guess I saw it on Amazon thing.
But they are.
Yeah.
These were, these are, you know, they're just books that have been compared to Neighbor
World by Dave DeLuca, also known as Lonesome Cowboy Dave DeLuca.
And yeah, it's a, hey, what can I say?
It's like, isn't it like 200 pages long or something?
That's a lot for your book.
Oh, over 200 pages.
Yeah.
And there's even, it's even illustrated.
It's got pictures of the characters drawn by Dave right at the beginning of it.
So you know what they all look like.
Yeah.
They're not, they're not.
They're just kind of scribbly.
Yeah.
They look kind of, what do they call it?
Sketchy?
Now everybody, how come everyone's been using that term sketchy?
But they are sketchy.
They're sketchy characters.
I know, but that hasn't been used since the thirties, back when they used to have plots
and different things like that.
I mean, you notice in the 1930s, you had a movie and stuff that had to have not just
a leading character or two, but it had to have a story behind it, some kind.
Now all there is just like these, these huge car races that blow up everything.
Yeah.
And people shooting guns that have 28 bullets in them, cartridges in there.
Guns that shoot knives and can fly.
Yeah.
And continue, just keep, keep on flying.
I love those.
I love those movies actually.
I eat them up.
I hate them.
It hurts me.
But, oh, and there, and other, in other nerds in subgenius book publishing, Eyelash
by Reverend Nikolai Kingsley, which is the first.
Now whereas Neighbor World isn't specific.
Yeah.
It's not specifically subgenius-y, except in its sort of overall theme that we're all
being turned into skulls by skull farmers of the conspiracy.
Yeah.
But the, Eyelash has Bob as character at the beginning of it.
And then an exist, an actual man from Planet X who happens to be a buxom, beautiful woman.
And then the two subgenius characters.
And, yeah.
There's a lot of really, really angry, clumsy, stupid robots that fight constantly.
And Alien Squid, who is a veterinarian, who is hired to fix the humans.
And subgenius is on barbecues.
That's Eyelash by Nikolai Kingsley.
It takes place partly right at the base of the eyelash of a Yakatizma, which subgeniuses
know are planet sized.
Planet eating robots.
Then there's the latest one.
We got a new one out, Dave, that just came out.
It's hardcover and it's a novella.
So it really, it looks like a little golden book, like when you were a kid.
And it's, it's the most perverted and funniest of the, of the three books.
It's called The Agent and Mr. Dobbs by Reverend Teters LaVerge.
I read the entire novella.
I had no idea.
I read it over several hours of slack about 10 years ago.
And in fact, Reverend Cosmack liked it so much, he edited all those segments together
into one big 90 minute audio book.
So I may be running parts of The Agent and Mr. Dobbs old audio book again, just to help
drum up interest in The Agent and Mr. Dobbs, which actually is really funny.
And if somebody was going to make a segment.
I'd say, here's your subgenius movie.
I would no longer hand them my first screenplay.
I wouldn't even hand him my second screenplay.
I'd hand him The Agent and Mr. Dobbs and go, here's your subgenius movie.
And they'll go, but it doesn't really have an ending.
And I'd go, exactly.
Exactly.
Yeah.
Now you see where we're going with this.
You want to be able to twiddle your thumbs for the next 20 years.
Yeah.
Or twaddle them.
Mr. Dobbs was sitting in a large, large, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big,
and there he was with a large leather armchair with his back to me.
A billow of smoke coming up from his front.
I slowly walked over to him.
He said nothing.
But with his right hand, he motioned me to sit on a folding metal chair adjacent to him.
He seemed to be engrossed in a television program.
It was Leave It to Beaver, a wholesome program.
Suddenly, he began to speak.
I do love this show.
That word cleaver is one relaxed man.
Connie doesn't like me to watch this program.
She thinks it's pornographic, but that's why I like it.
He fell into a deep silence, intently watching a commercial and nodding his head in time with the jingle.
When the commercial ended, he turned to me and asked,
What can I do for you, young agent?
I noticed then that even though the upper half of his body was clad in a dark suit with white shirt and dark tie,
the bottom half of his body was clad only in wingtip shoes.
It was very disturbing and put me off for a moment,
but I'd been warned by my handlers that this Mr. Dobbs had many tricks up his sleeve,
and I took this as his way of making a person uncomfortable.
We're also about to construct our own metaverse, I think.
I don't know what that is, what those are yet, but I'm told that we'll be doing that.
Who gave you the word? Who gave you the go-ahead?
I knew you were waiting for weeks and weeks there.
J.R. Bob Dobbs.
Bob, uh...
Direct from the upper offices, yeah.
Actually, this was the AI copy of Bob's brain.
It's still, you could say it was Bob.
You could actually say it was a lot smarter than the original Meat Bob,
who is still around somewhere.
The difference is we can dial up the AI Bob 2.0, but we can't.
Nobody knows.
Nobody knows where Bob is unless they happen to be on a fishing trip.
If they're on a fishing trip with him or underneath him in some cheap hotel room,
or topping him in some cheap motel room, or Trump Tower,
or trumping Trump in Trump Tower with yellow snow in everyone's mouth,
because that's what I've heard.
You've heard that?
Yeah.
Don't ever hear that.
Yeah, as far as I'm concerned.
I discovered an illegal copycat Bob NFT.
I actually own it, or file it.
I found it.
File it.
I found somebody selling our trademark as an NFT.
I don't think anyone's bought it, and I don't think you know what an NFT is,
so it doesn't matter.
But it does matter to me because I want to stop it before somebody buys it,
but instead I'm doing this stupid show.
And after that, I'm going to do it.
I don't do something else stupid like exercises.
Yeah.
Well, that makes sense.
I follow you 100% on that one.
Yeah, but sooner or later, I have to shut down these bastards with their—
they just decided, oh, well, Bob's Clipart, so we can—
No, Bob was Clipart at one time.
Bob hasn't been Clipart in 40 years.
Bob's Clipart is a trademark owned by somebody named Douglas Smith.
I happen to know who that is.
He's the janitor here at the Subgenius Foundation.
He dresses like a woman, and yeah.
Well, we put it in his name so that if somebody kills him for it,
it won't be me that they kill for it, you know, or Bob.
Right.
Well, way to go, you know?
I can only offer my own personal kudos.
We're trying to take care of business, but there's a lot of ripoffs out there.
I mean, there really are.
There's a lot of people.
People selling unauthorized, non-licensed Bob Dobbs stuff.
We shut them down when we get around to it.
And when I say we, I mean I.
Yeah, there are a lot of commercials that I've noticed lately in this neighborhood,
neck of the woods, where a religious cartoon character named Bob endorses a product,
and everybody loves Bob and goes out and gets the product and says,
this gives the thumb up to Bob when they close the last shot and stuff.
Well, the worst was that Boner pill.
The Boner pill ads for smiling Bob.
Oh, Prince Boner.
Why is Bob so happy?
Why do the girls love Bob so much?
Well, take these little pills, and if you're a man, you'll find out.
Like Bob.
Just like Bob.
That was a blatant ripoff.
Luckily, the guy behind that company and his mom all went,
you know, they're going to get a job.
They still sold the pills.
But the guy who had the idea of ripping us off,
he got his comeuppance or his leave downants or whatever.
He got, he got.
The guy who played Bob.
There was a rumor that the man who played Bob in those commercials died,
drowned in the Caribbean.
But that was just a rumor.
It turned out not to be true.
Well, at least as far as I was concerned, it was all false and full of nothing but vapor slides.
I can't even remember the name of the.
Oh, now I remember the name of him, and I'm not going to say him.
Bob's bathroom decor.
Those box bathrooms that could fit any generation at any age.
It's just bringing it covers up the towels and the bathtub and the sink and everything.
It makes it look like an entirely new bathroom.
Is that what you're talking about?
No.
Oh, okay.
No, I don't know.
I don't know what I'm talking about.
I know even less about what you're talking about.
Well, there's on the local television, there's a Bob guy, a cartoon character whose name
is Bob and everybody.
Oh, they do it, Bob.
Say this and that and whatnot, Bob.
Bob, you.
Is this recent?
And oh.
Yes, it is recent because I, well, within the last two weeks, because I keep trying
to remind myself to remember it.
I tell you that to tell you that there, but it doesn't look like Bob.
It doesn't look like Bob Clippard at all.
Oh, well, that doesn't matter.
Another cartoon.
It's another cartoon face.
Oh, it's Bob again, bringing us plenty of this and whatever Bob brings us.
Well, here's the important thing.
Does he have a pipe?
I think that got me going one night.
I think one of them did, but maybe not.
Maybe no telltale pipe to hang our bitches on.
But, well, I was falling asleep.
What do you expect?
You know, now there's that Bob guy.
Right.
Oh, it puts me to sleep real fast.
Like this show.
This show just usually knocks me right out.
It doesn't affect everybody that way, though.
My daughter wouldn't listen to it.
She liked to contribute to it, but she wouldn't listen to it because she said it gave her
a headache every time.
Imagine that.
Our mellifluous voices lapping against the seashore like water make it a headache.
Yapping against the seashore like an ocean.
Don't you see how much more discreet and iconoplastic that made her instead of the
old man?
You have to love Bob.
He loves you, but you love Bob.
You have to.
Or else what happens if you don't love Bob?
He'll kill you.
He'll bob you out.
He'll bob you out, folks.
You heard it here first.
If you don't love Bob, he'll bob you out, man.
And that was my baby daughter, Sivit, staying at age six or so.
And here she is, probably around age 12 or so.
So she's actually now about 40 or so.
Yeah.
Now Bob, I smell his drop around me.
And when I have no slack, I touch my gland and Bob has found me.
On my job, the noddles act like dumb shits.
Without slack, the sweat runs down my armpits.
The next day, I'll see the sun.
The sun's coming.
And all I need is Bob and me forever and forever.
But until I spend my 30 bucks, I'm just ranting to myself and not to Bob.
And although I know that I am screwed,
still I'm still going to be a good boy.
I say, there's a day of pain.
I love Bob, but when the rupture's over, he'll be gone.
The earth will be in ruins.
Without him, the world around me changes.
The conspiracy is everywhere.
The malls are full of pink boys.
I love Bob, but every day I don't spend the 30 bucks.
I'm only just pretending.
Without me, Bob's world will go on burning.
On next day, Bob will have this land that I'll never know.
On this day, I'll be a naked
On above...
I love Bob.
On above.
Bob love me on my own.
A love Bob.
l'm only on my own.
I don't know.
I'm on my own.
I don't know what's up with that.
Uh, you know, just joined this religion recently . . .
quez near people all over the globe and you know, for debt . . .
If that's what you call a religion.
You're one of the newbies from the 1990s.
Well, if you can't be a newbie, what can you be?
Eh?
Eh, Minad?
An oldie.
Oldie too much.
Me too.
Hold it between your knees and sing in the reptilian songs of our ancestors.
If there are any.
I know some of them seem relative, related by family.
Did you hear what I just said or was I mumbling again?
I wasn't paying any attention because I was trying to set up Princess We here on microphone two.
I think it is.
No, no, over here, over here, over here.
Okay.
The one on the cushion with its butt on the cushion.
It had an operation for, you know, pot.
Piles.
And it has to sit on one of those special cushions.
It's sad.
It had an operation for its condition.
Does she have a monitor so she can tell if I sound?
There's not much I can do.
She has headphones on, but they're not nearly as good as mine.
I have really fancy new headphones.
Yeah, he does.
Scared the hell out of the dog.
Chippy.
Chippy came in and saw me with them on and ran away.
Well, you know, they're kind of sparkly.
They're really shiny and sparkly.
I can imagine that she would get scared at those.
Well, she knows my head.
She knows they are also a weapon.
You know, they have to.
She recognizes that.
No, no.
The microphone.
You're wearing the dog's hat again.
Hats.
The dog's hats with a posture here above the eye.
Hey, did I tell you that Buddy's not okay?
Well, he is now.
But he got beat up by the young.
Younger male.
Yeah, you told me that yesterday.
Yeah.
Or the day before.
Yeah, he, I don't know what.
He, you know, Buddy's the old one.
The old male.
He's been acting all alpha like bossing the other dogs around.
Well, not his sister Claudia so much.
No, but he's been stealing their chews and being real haughty.
Yeah.
Going around taking wastebaskets apart and all kinds of crazy behavior.
The other day he crossed his younger rival Yeti,
who is about four times Buddy's size.
Actually, he's four times everybody's size.
Yeah, he is.
Yeah, he is too.
And they got into a, boy, Buddy was being tossed by the neck like a little squirrel.
And I was terrified.
That's horrible.
I'm still traumatized by it.
I don't even know how I'm going to ever get over this.
Yeah, Dave's traumatized too.
The dogs and I got over it.
I know.
You just shook it right off.
But I just, I can't stop seeing it.
You know, I go through it in my head over and over and I can't stop.
I thought.
I thought that Buddy's leg had been broken by a bite because he couldn't walk at first.
And he did manage to make it up the stairs and climb into the bed with me.
And he stayed in that bed for 24 hours straight with us bringing him food and water.
And meds.
And he never peed or anything for 24 hours straight.
And finally last night he got up as if he had never been bitten.
And tried.
And potted down.
Yeah.
Outside and peed.
Yeah, he wasn't limping or anything.
Yeah.
And.
But my God, if I had been shaken the way that Buddy was shaken by our big dog, I wouldn't
be back yet.
I'd still be laying in bed trying to heal.
It was a whole day at least operation getting yourself together.
I was there because I remember when my dog got beat up that way and just watching it
and not being able to do anything about it.
Pull the other dog off of him.
And just think, well, my dog's going to die from a neck.
Yeah.
Right.
Well, we learned that this will be of interest to dog owning listeners.
Princess, we read that the one way that you break up a dog fight is grab the attacking
dog's hind legs.
It's called the wheelbarrow.
The wheelbarrow.
Yeah.
You pull.
Pull them up and out.
Pull their feet up and away.
Now, then you have to hope that that attacking dog doesn't spin around and attack you.
The article said that that's generally not what happens because the dog.
Isn't angry at you.
He's angry at the other dog.
They usually don't lash out at the person that's pulling him away.
No, man.
That time.
The one time Buddy and Claudia got into a fight.
Oh, I know.
They were tripping.
I pulled Buddy off of Claudia and he turned around and bit my leg so hard that I had to sit in bed for two days.
Yeah.
That was bad.
I'm whimpering and licking.
I had to lick my.
Man, I wore my tongue out licking my leg.
I'm licking your legs like a little baby.
Like a dog.
That's so sweet.
Like, oh, well.
Licking my wounds.
That's what Buddy did.
Sitting next to me.
He's still licking his wounds.
Yeah.
Did you lick your wounds?
I can't lick the back of his neck.
I was doing that for him.
Well, I did too.
Let's give credit where credit's due.
I wondered who else was licking the back of Buddy's neck.
The back of his neck.
It was so scary.
It's all covered.
I was in the.
Dead blood.
Ugh.
God.
I was in the meta world.
So I was there.
Even if I'm more resembled with Mr. Rogers playing Lincoln.
I was there.
Somehow.
Dave was there.
Oh, Dave was there.
And there is here.
And he returned to there.
Princess, your voice sounded great just now.
Here is now.
Princess, how does my voice sound?
Do I sound all beat up and crashed?
No, you sound just like Dave.
Dave.
Okay.
I just wondered.
Earlier today, he sounded like this.
Then when I told him about it, then he quit.
Then he accused me of speaking clearer right after that.
And as I'm telling you folks, it's really hard doing a weekly radio show.
Especially when you only actually do it every month or so.
Especially when you're weak.
Yeah.
Weak.
Weekly show.
That's the way it's been lately.
Weak.
Weekly.
Weekly radio show.
Weekly reruns.
They were great.
All the reruns were killer.
Yeah.
They're even better when they're watered by a part of the langitudes.
When you get a little bit of extra fertilizer on them, they just jump right out of the skull
and you're back in bee's knees.
Back in the bee's knees.
Yeah.
I wish I had some bees.
Why don't you guys become bee, what do you call it?
Beekeepers?
Beekeepers.
What do they call it?
Heavy area and pimple bunions?
What do they call them?
Yeah.
I'm doing that just because I'm a chicken.
Well, yeah.
Bees hate chickens.
I mean, unless they're deep fried in country bread.
Now, I have several friends that are beekeepers and they love beekeeping.
Well, they can walk into a swarm of bees and not get stung and everybody who sees that
goes, what are you?
Are you crazy or what?
Does it count if you're a beekeeper?
I've got that urinal.
Oh, I've got to empty that urinal up there pretty soon.
For the.
Dogs.
Dogs knock it over.
That would be a real mess.
Wouldn't be good for the carpet.
Turn that blue carpet into green.
It would be green in a splash pad.
Yeah.
Do you have a bunch of toilets throughout the property that you use as dog dishes?
Please don't tell me you do that.
We have them in 10 places around the property and they all have bidets and wind chimes and
little incense and ashtray with always.
Well, that's great.
That's fantastic
But no lighter because there's a burn ban on here
No one can light a fire in Texas
No
For now
Yeah, you have to be 30 yards from the building, yeah
Oh no, you can't light any kind of
Just don't light a fire
Yeah, you gotta vape, no smoking
Well, I know there's one thing they say, yeah, right
Right, exactly
Yeah, don't even ignite any tobacco
They won't let Dave smoke inside his own room
What?
Yeah, the insane asylum
They won't let any of those people
Not only that, if he wanted to have a six pack of beer
Yeah
He'd have to smuggle it in, like in a dorm room
What? Why?
Because it's that cheap
Because it's like a hospital?
No, because it's real cheap
Because Dave's really old
And so they have rules like that
That you can't bring in alcohol and tobacco
Right
Low income housing
Jeez
That's what they call that
Wow
And people, middle class people are real mad at poor people
Because poor people have everything
I've heard this so many times
Oh, some poor person was lying in a supermarket in front of me
She was buying steak
I just had to buy chicken
It's like, how do you know that's a poor person?
Well, you could tell
Yeah, I think I know what our friend means
But that's not, no
He's profiling
Yeah, he was profiling
He was profiling
You can't tell who's a poor person
No
I mean, I look rich, don't I?
But you'd be fooled
My fancy shoes, my fancy clothes and car that I drive
I look rich, don't I?
You'd never think I was rich as Midas
You'd just assume, well, that guy's on welfare
They make $35,000 a year, did you know that?
On welfare, you get $35,000 a year
Which is not at all true
I know
And you also can't stay on welfare forever
And it's, I was going, well, and they drive Cadillacs
Well, why don't you just get on welfare if you want to drive Cadillacs and eat steak?
And the answer was, I don't want to live in a cardboard box
Make up your mind
Which is it?
Who said this?
Are poor people rich or are they poor?
Fair enough, people
Believe me
It's a cross-border
Section of conversations, actually
Yes
I'm not, I try not to just live inside my little subgenius bubble of purity of Dobbs
I like to see what the idiots are thinking also
So I've been monitoring, I've been monitoring, let's call it the extremists' normals
The extremist normals for my whole life, practically
Urban bourbon legends
Well, I was raised among them, you see
I'm part Pobucker
Part
I understand
I'm also part elite
In fact, more elite than the richest elites
Bourbon legends
No, I'm elite in my knowledge
I have knowledge of Dobbs
I memorized Book of the Subgenius
I forgot it
I didn't
No, I
Heck, I assembled the whole thing on that big table right over there
When this was Pappy's house
Because I didn't have a table
I had that big, my shelf
And now it's my table
Thanks, Pap
And Mammy
And Mappy
And Mappy and Flappy
And Pappy and Pappy
And my brother for doing all the repairs for Pappy
Oh, goodness
And followed by my nephews for doing all
That's for doggone sure
Now I gotta hire my grandson
Dave's trying to hire his grandson
But these zombies these days, they don't wanna work
They just wanna lay around in their grave all day long
They just wanna creep their...
When I was a zombie, we used to eat the flesh of a living being every morning
Before we could go
And we...
But, yeah
Actually, that's an old Jane or Hyperclete's routine
And I'm not supposed to use that
No, don't use those
I'm not even supposed to mention him
Because if
Every time I do, I owe him another $10,000
Yes
According to him
Well, he claimed that one stick was worth $10,000, huh?
Yep
Well, he might have been right
Somewhere
No
Well, I'd send him the $10,000
But he's never been able to tell me his correct address
He's not kidding, even, Dave
No, I'm not
There's been...
There's at least two times in a row that we mailed money to Jane or...
And it bounced back because it wasn't his zip code
Right
He could not give us his own real zip code
Huh
I never met a person who didn't know their own zip code
Good...
You...
It's a lucky you that you never met Jane or...
Why don't you invite him over to your house?
Well, I...
I...
No thanks
But I...
I remember him very very...
That's whenever somebody goes,
Man, Jane or Harper Clutes, what's he like?
I go, why don't you invite him over and find out?
You'll soon see
It's like saying, why don't you just jump in this pit of fire?
No
Pit of snakes
Just giving people an opportunity to find out for themselves
So that I'm not talking about someone behind their back
I guess
On broadcast radio
You're talking right at their front, yep
Or on my little living room radio shack radio station
Tarzan's
We do have sound effects machine now, listen to this
When is X day, friends?
Why it could be tonight!
Are you ready?
Sounds like CBS Mystery Theater from 1938 or something
Have you done...
I'll join the church of the subgenius
Hey, guess what?
We've got a special deal for you
We just raised our prices
Wait until you see our excuses for that
At subgenius.com
If you are taking the government's...
No, not the government, but the whole...
And if...
Right there on the front page of subgenius.com
It tells you how you can hear the radio show
Every episode of the radio show for free
It tells how you can get hold of Lonesome Cowboy Dave's book Neighbor World
And the new one, The Agent and Mr. Dobbs and Eyelash
And the book of the subgenius
It shows you a link to every place that's playing the subgenius movie
J.R. Bob Dobson and the Church of the Subgenius directed by Sandy Boone
Woohoo!
And guess what?
It's on Tubi for free with ads
Yeah, yeah
I turned it on
I was going through...
Tubi is one of those internet TV networks that's...
You don't have to pay for it
If you got one of those...
If you got one service...
I guess the TV's will tune it in now
If you got internet
And it has ads
But they have all the best bad movies
And old movies
And great movies
Stuff that's kind of old
I was watching The Good, Bad and the Ugly last night
While I did my stretches
But get this
I was flipping through the recommended for you
And what title card comes up?
But J.R. Bob Dobson and the Church of the Subgenius
And here's what it said on the screen
Starring Douglas Smith, Nick Offerman and Richard Linklater
And I thought that's the weirdest thing
Why didn't it...
It doesn't say Reverend Ivan Stang
It had the janitor's name instead
And instead of showing a picture of Bob or Reverend Stang
It showed Paul Mavridis
Who doesn't look anything like Bob or Stang
Or you
Or Douglas
No
Well can you get this thing with the janitor resolved somehow?
Well every week I have to hear about
How he's you know
Stealing your properties
And taking your values and so forth
And running them down the toilet
No no
The worst thing he's ever done is steal our dope
That's it
He hasn't stolen the turkey and the...
The last time I was trying to do some plumbing
And I was looking around for the pipe dope
You know that stuff you put on the
Spreads of old metal pipes
Right you tried to smoke it
It was all gone and it was Doug Smith
Had gotten in and rooted around
Pilfered it all
Yeah
Wait a minute that reminds me
Where's my pills?
He pilfered the pills and the pipe dope
No
And the pipe
Good lord
Knowing him he's probably stuffed the pipe full of pills
And burned them up
And
Probably did
And since the pipe is made of you know copper
Or old cast iron or something
It probably heated up and burned him
And then he rubbed the pipe dope on the burns
Instead of bag bomb
Which is the only medicine you need for anything
Ever
Yeah you can rub on your titties
Bag bomb is really a delicious article to wear
The dogs sure love it
They do
They lick it off my chapped hands
Whenever I'm trying to medicate my chaps
Yeah they smell it and they're like mmm
My chappy
How come you don't get hostages?
Chappy has cracks
Chappy has fears
My hand has chappy
Chappy
He's a self aware robot
You'll see someday when he's your boss
Someday I will see
What the pee pee pee pee pee pee
I will stand and dance in the dark
When the trumpet calls X day
In a brother and sister band
When they blow the world away
We shall have paradise
Subgenie of the world unite
Alien sex every night
Subgenie of the world
Subgenie of the world unite
Make men crazy
Not to buy
With through love
Young and отправsy
The way of how a man is
A acuerdo
The Subgenius Anthem by Lonesome Cowboy Day performed by Einstein's Secret Orchestra at a church revival in Cleveland.
And we will continue this epic two-parter Dave Call episode next week along with some longer excerpts of The Agent and Mr. Dobbs as well as some extra Sheridan and Subgenius collage.
The music in the background is the Empire Jazz Orchestra, symphonies and riffs.
And this has been Hour of Slight number 1,868.
You can learn everything about...
everything at subgenius.com.
Praise Bob.