Something wrong with the recorder?
Don't think so.
Is their system the same?
Yes. It is according to the directions on the carton.
Sveeeh...
It sounds confusing, and that can be helpful when trying to find out quickly who might be up to
The Self Genius Hour of Sveeeh!
It really jumps out.
His latest Pulitzer Prize winner book,
People Seeing Things That They've Seen Before.
Shadow people, entities that people have seen before,
ghosts that people have seen before.
My God! It's, it's, it's, it's, it's just, it's...
The Giant Bob.
We welcome you.
Won't you kindly seat yourselves and be comfortable?
I'm controller of planet X.
And I've invited you here to discuss something that's very important.
Meanwhile, the Church of the Subgenius, a parody cult of slackers who worship a character named Bob Dobbs,
had planned their own Armageddon date.
July 5th, 1998.
But the next day, they were still here.
So they did what they liked to do best.
Throw wild parties called Divivals,
where members enjoy such events as blood wrestling, pig worship, and naked Bobtisms.
A subculture of the bizarre.
And the tempo control.
Disco.
Wait, whoa, whoa.
Oh, Bob.
Oh.
Turn on.
Tune in.
And...
So what do you call it?
Why do you want to be normal?
The rupture is upon us, dear friends.
That fateful day.
July 5th, 1998.
Next days are coming.
And the pigs are bumming.
Ha!
Sure, when the rupture hits,
we'll all be in our first class window seats on the pleasure saucers watching the little pink boys fry.
Ha!
Turn on.
Tune in.
and slack off!
You certainly don't want to preach to people.
X days are coming!
And the pigs are bumming!
Sure, J.R. Bob Dobbs is my savior.
And of course I want more slack.
And I'm smoking prop non-stop.
But what I really want...
Oh yeah, that's it.
Those lovely alien nympho mutants.
Nonstop orgies on the pleasure saucers.
Oh yeah.
Oh, I love to be naked.
More, more.
Oh, fuck.
Turn on.
Tune in.
And slack off!
Why don't you want to be normal?
X days are coming.
And the pigs are bumming.
Yeah!
I said X days are coming!
And the pigs are bumming.
And the little pigs are bumming.
Those conspiracy-dude pink boy normals are gonna fry!
They won't even know what hit them.
That old Stark fist is gonna come down hard.
But nothing's guaranteed, dear friends.
I'm a card-carrying member of the Church of the Subgenius.
I'm the almighty king of subgenius.
I never showed up to death, fuck!
I never wasn't born with dignity from the injury.
Well, listen here.
If there is any man's life that has never been whether you're fucking or not.
Just like my fucking friend, Robin Choi.
The only thing I have is my unshakable fate.
In Bach!
Not long ago.
Turn on.
I'll get through them.
And I'll...
Why do you want to be known?
X-Days are coming.
And the pigs are bumming.
Don't you want to be saved?
No.
X-Days are coming.
And the pigs are bumming.
Listen to me, mister. It's salvation I'm talking about.
I think you will agree the report we have just heard from our astronauts is truly amazing.
On the newly discovered planet,
there exists a race of stars.
Superior beings with highly advanced scientific knowledge,
especially in medicine.
And furthermore, they have extended their hand in friendship to the people of the Earth.
It is our duty as Supreme Council
to carefully study the proposal as set forth by Planet X
and arrive at an early decision.
We'll receive a wonder drug.
Then we can save the people of the Earth from sufferings.
The organizations of...
The organizations of women have no objection.
We acknowledge the sincere message of peace which was forwarded by the controller of the new planet.
Also, it appears to me that we can learn humanity from these people,
as well as scientific knowledge.
Thank you.
The Council shall therefore order cooperation with Planet X.
First, first, first, first.
We must get off.
We must get off this place.
First.
We must leave.
We must get off.
First.
Now, who gonna talk for you on Earth?
Who gonna say the words?
Can I get a witness?
First.
Who gonna pronounce the final epithet that's gonna take you off on this world?
Who gonna speak for you?
First.
Who gonna talk for Earth?
We know who speaks for the nation.
First.
But who speaks for the planet?
Who speaks for Earth?
First.
Cold veins of steel.
Hombre's without hearts.
First.
Human beings without minds.
A world of pain.
No luxury.
First.
No comfort.
No delight.
First.
Suffering at every corner.
Enjoy yourself.
First.
We must get off.
We must get off this place.
First.
Is there all more?
There is no future.
First.
We have destroyed the land we live in.
We are the one who will enslave the Earth!
Just the way it's been done for billions of years.
This is the Sly George Face of Evolution.
This is the slow pivot, slumbering, blubbering face of evolution.
You know, to know, you know, to know, you know, like, you know, to go, you know, kind of, kind of, kind of like the reptilian agenda.
You know, the masculine and feminine in the galactic core with reptilian source energy.
Multidimensional, malevolent, conscious, feminine deities that are under the control of very evil beings of the Draco reptilians.
But, um, but the Anunnaki brought in its own huge monster that we're dealing with.
This is Earth headquarters.
Contola here.
Your orders, sir.
You are to execute plan two, item four of schedule five.
Plan two, item four, schedule five. Yes, sir.
Come on, little green.
I was cruising through the city on a Saturday night.
When I saw some land up there, it was low, kind of bright.
I went into a ship with a little green man.
I was a man.
We were standing in a circle starting helium.
I looked around some more.
There was a party going on.
And there was Berla Ngozi.
He was singing this song.
Calling all the members of the human race.
It's Humble Man 69 from Outer Seas.
Playing 69 from Outer Seas.
Outer Space.
Playing 69 from Outer Space.
Outer Space
Playing 69 from Outer Space
Calling all the boys and girls in the US of A
It's time for Playing 69 from Outer Space
Doesn't really matter if you're black or white
Anything is fine if it feels alright
Calling all the boys all over the world
Grab yourself a girl and give it a whirl
Calling all the girls all over the land
Grab yourself a man and a wham, bam, bam
Love in a spaceship
Playing 69 from Outer Space
Outstanding.
Thanks for watching.
My people and I appreciate your warm welcome.
This day will always be remembered by the universe
as when our two civilizations joined together
for the benefit of galactic mankind.
We are friendly, our aims are peaceful,
and we seek to establish cooperation and eternal friendship
between our two worlds.
Control to speak with forked tongue, maybe, huh?
It's fun and inane
when the trumpet calls X day
in a brother and sister band
when they blow the world away.
We shall have paradise.
Subgenie of the world, unite.
Alien sex every night.
Subgenie of the world.
Subgenie of the world, unite.
We shall have paradise.
Stand hand in hand
when the trumpet calls X day.
In a brother and sister band
when they blow the world away.
We shall have paradise.
Subgenie of the world, unite.
Alien sucks everybody
Satini of the world, satini of the world, satini of the world, unite!
I am the controller of planet X.
To the people of the Earth, I command that you obey the following orders.
Orders?
You will place the Earth under our absolute control and be governed as our colony.
What is a governess as a colony?
If you do not obey these orders willingly and immediately, we shall destroy your civilization.
Double trust and think.
So we stumble right into a trap.
I repeat the order. Earth will continue to exist only as a colony of planet X.
No! No!
They must have lied to us.
Well, wait a minute. What's wrong with Earth being a colony of planet X?
Actually, that's not so bad.
Is it?
Well, it hasn't been detailed to us yet, has it dear?
Well, it's got to be better than what we have now.
I guess.
Okay, well, let's see. What happened here? What's... what... what happened?
Um, thanks to Mr. Sister for the planet X clips from, uh, Monster Zero or something like that.
Uh, thanks to...
To Lonesome Cowboy Dave and also Einstein's Secret Orchestra for the subgenius anthem.
That was the last song played.
The song before that, Plan 69 from Outer Space, was by the Kirkendall Void of Cleveland itself.
Good old Cleveland.
Uh, Earth First, that strange mix, was by Einstein's Secret Orchestra.
Uh, Professor Chas.
Uh, with also Lonesome Cowboy Dave and, uh, whoever else.
Not you, Princess Weave, that time.
Oh, no. Not me.
Michelle George was there.
And, uh, X Days of Comin' by Bill T. Miller, King of Slack.
The collages, uh, so far have mostly been by Fernandan and E. Lee Murr, but there will be more from him,
and from Reverend Royal D. King.
Capitator.
This music in the background is Petra Hayden,
who does, in this particular album, movie soundtracks,
all a cappella and overdubbed.
Potter Nostril was playing in the background
one breakfast morning.
Praise Potter Nostril.
And I thought I was losing my mind
because it was some of my favorite movie themes,
but just off, you know.
And yes, friends, X Day is a-coming.
We're here in the studio for once.
Probably the next time that happens,
we'll be with Dr. Hal,
because it's a busy, busy, busy June coming up
as we head in towards the end of the world.
I can tell you about some subgenius-related events.
I can't tell you to go to them.
But if...
For instance, on June 22nd, Saturday,
in Pittsburgh, why, there's a subgenius devival.
Actually, it's Tommy Amoeba's rock and roll birthday gala extravaganza
with a subgenius devival thrown in.
But since the party involves Fat Man D
and her band, The Cultural District,
and since it features Amoeba Knievel,
the incredible spaz band of Tommy Amoeba,
and Andrew the Impaled,
St. Andrew the Impaled,
and even St. Tentatively a Convenience.
Isn't that remarkable?
Well, one of the last times...
I'm not sure the last time I saw him,
but one of the last times I saw him,
I couldn't see him,
because he had split from the...
At 1982,
World Subgenius...
convention in Chicago after braining Pope's sternodocs with some kind of heavy music synthesizer
device in a creative argument.
But that was many lifetimes ago, and everyone has forgotten everything.
And if we ever knew any of it to begin with, so it'll be really interesting to see alternatively
and see what he's up to.
That should be a fun show.
That's a Saturday, June 22nd at Howler's Coyote Cafe in Pittsburgh, or Pittsburgh,
as St. Andrew the Impaled instructed us it should be said.
I was at this amazing cacophony society event last weekend as emcee of all things and saw
our old friend David Apocalypse.
He used to be a...
a sideshow Marvel partners with Andrew the Impaled in a group called Circus Apocalypse.
And he's going to be moving back to Pittsburgh soon.
That'll be good, because he's a real troublemaker, a crazy man.
He'll juggle knives at you, and he doesn't know how to juggle knives well.
So it's not fake blood, and it's not a fake cowboy who calls in...
Cowboy, hell.
Are we getting him on the air or not?
I don't know.
It is off the air.
I'm hearing your...
a delay.
I'm hearing a delay, too.
I'm hearing an unusual, strange echo in this whole room, as if...
as if...
No?
Okay.
I think it's the ghost of the old prophets walking around with stinky sandals and bad
eyesight.
Well, I kind of like this strange...
Yeah, me too.
This is like...
You see, listening audience and Dave, from our point of view, we're hearing Dave in our
headphones as well as on a big, loud speaker, which I suppose maybe if I start turning things
down, well...
That's what it is.
Oh.
The speaker is giving Aaron information to the audio...
Test.
This is like the lonesome cowboy Wizard of Oz sound.
Yeah.
The voice.
Would you like to look at my underpants?
I wish you hadn't brought that up.
No, I have them right here with me in a shoebox.
Aren't they cute?
You sure you wouldn't want to take one home?
Look at the markings.
They're so smart, too.
Well, I've been giving them names and...
Hello?
I don't know about those markings, Dave.
Well, I think this one is a...
a...
Like a Hungarian cheesemaker, perhaps?
Yeah.
Hmm.
With plenty of lecivor on top.
I see.
Hmm.
That echo is kind of weird.
Yeah, I'm pushing buttons like mad trying to eliminate you from the speaker.
Of course, one way I could be able to...
Don't push any of the buttons on your own body or else you might delete...
yourself no not that button oh no not that button no wood what the hell it's it's weird to hear um
what you say slow it down and recompress decompress that's weird
it's the ominous voice of dave
a thousand feet above you now stand back from the fence and listen to me
d listen when the aliens come you will not be able to resist them you will not fight
you will go to a place in southern ohio and lay down and pretend
to die but you will not die now go to the fence no i am at the fence i am at the fence
you're too close to the fence lady stand back from the fence please oh okay okay i'm i'm standing
back now no no too far step in a little bit okay okay what is that cologne you're wearing
uh it's uh um it's called your filter fist that's what it is
such a
shally
you'll say that real fast ten times
no no no don't don't don't do that on the air well i've been uh enjoying this
special sound effect and i can't do anything about it i've never seen anything like this
in this studio i've pushed buttons uh both randomly and from a careful monitor options
sort of setting and i've been enjoying this special sound effect and i can't do anything about it i've
been enjoying this powerful sound that i've been doing this special sound effect and i can't do nothing i'm going
siren
much more comfortable than i have at any time
shally
siren
very
creepy
임
is
really
tell lord
just
this shally how i i cannot sleep at night is an ebony copy of a 90% amount radio out of
the government reading every single email one by one the whole government everyone in the whole
government reading every single email sent by anyone since email was invented and those guys
have never really had to work that hard now they're stuck in an audience in an office i mean
you see this confuses your your nasal cavity and other parts of close to the um
the deviated septum but i think they should be forced to work
well i think uh you know at this point there's some guy in a government office a national security
agency reading i'm planning to have meatloaf and potatoes tonight but oh gosh i guess i have to go
to the store first why do i have to read every single email
everybody's facebook entry but that's what it takes for security wouldn't that be great though
then they probably have to do a study to how to get out of that what not you know having to obey
the law necessarily but get out of the whole idea and stuff and then you know there'll be all kinds
of experts and everybody will have to attend seminars and stuff and they'll get bored with
that stuff too but they'll realize that uh what they're doing is too big of a pain in the
ass
a pain in the what in the ass oh yeah that's right you can say that now you know i've been
cutting that word out of our slack for years just out of uh sort of well yeah and
and then i realized that i was hearing it on plain ordinary television once i actually
listened to a plain ordinary television which happened by accident this month
well your genes are all screwed up anyway you've got
all different kinds of primate genes going around in your head and everything so no wonder you get
confused well in princess we use the wrong detergent when she put them in the wash and
it's all messed up yeah i put detergent in last night totally messed up so let's see what else
what else is big news here um okay there's this revival in pittsburgh in a couple of weeks
uh before oh i gotta go do a wedding next week of potter and petal nostril that will be so romantic
it's a going to be a classic paganish hippie subgenius well really it's a subgenius wedding
it's held at a sacred pagan area and i i've heard tell the pagans were a little worried
that we might somehow i don't know kill all their trees in the punch bowl right but yeah
something in the punch bowl and we are we are that thing in floating bobbing in the punch bowl
but um
i'm surprised that anyone would wonder about that we've been defiling we've been defiling
sacred groves we are that thing floating in the punch bowl yeah there's a new slogan for you
yeah we're that thing floating in the punch bowl jr bob dobbs 1953 punch bowl salesman convention
uh des moines iowa okay but uh
uh but yeah
we've been defiling sacred groves for a long time and they always re-sacrified themselves pretty quick
you know the trees mounts back i don't know about the fundamentalist pagans
but these aren't funny pagans these are the opposite these are our buddies pagans yeah it
doesn't take these are our old pagan friends a couple of hours of of regular pagan sunshine
to bleach out all the subgenius darkness ain't yeah yeah just so long as i'm turning in energy
right to turn into a werewolf is not a problem
actually whether i don't like the song and turn it into a
i've seen it on tv and it's good
got to get this lógica
with my brother
moderate
pragma
all right
the table.
Because this...
I can't turn this...
There's
an external speaker button
here. The buttons
that used to work no longer work.
We're not ever supposed
to talk about technical
problems on the
radio.
Because after
all, friends, you can tell this is all a recording
that's been heavily edited to
sound like we meant
to do this while...
Double-dozed
and double-dipped
creamy finger pie.
And speaking of...
You're not so special to us.
Climb on in.
Welcome aboard.
There's a finger pie
cook-off at X-Day this year.
It's going to be a great place
for the experiments, too.
X-Day held from July
1st through 7th.
First at Wisteria
Campground in Southern Ohio, and then
aboard probably my
escape vessel
for the last couple of days.
And then Starwood will be in
the same place, my
escape vessel. Or
push comes to shove,
Wisteria
still on planet Earth. Back at that
Wisteria campground, yeah.
The weather's going to be good this time.
We know because somebody checked
weatherwiz.com.
And it said that a month in advance
that it would be 85 degrees.
That's not bad.
Hey, Dr. Sinister,
you would probably know
just which button to push here.
Dr. Sinister just...
The magic, Dr. Sinister.
Was that Dave?
You know, that whole time
I thought Dave was coming from up there.
It's because you're deaf.
Huh?
Is that a what?
Because you're deaf.
Oh, it's because you're deaf.
No, I'm kidding.
That's not funny anymore.
Is it stopped?
It stopped.
It was a different...
There's a little knuckle-sized
knucklehead of a speaker kind of hidden.
That's the previous speaker.
I could see it.
And if I'd have pulled my headphones off
and really poked around, I would have...
Yeah, I mean, it's the previous speaker.
There's no reason why anything should be
coming out over that speaker once the microphone is on.
You're right.
We've got issues.
We don't just have issues.
We've got bank issues.
Yeah, well, I was...
I was pushing all the preview buttons.
Yeah.
That's the thing.
I'm not...
The system's been messed up for...
It's been messed up for weeks.
Oh.
Well, Dave, now we know the secret of your buzz.
It was never your buzz.
The buzz was always everybody else's fault.
Yeah.
Just like all political problems.
They're all everybody else's fault.
Right.
And they're the reason why everyone,
anywhere has problems.
Everybody else.
It's other people's fault.
No matter what other people do to other people,
it's their own other's fault.
Those liberal libtards and right-tards,
just blamers,
those idiotic, stupid chicken cowards
can only call names
and blame everyone else.
And you see, it's all their fault.
Yeah.
But the thing floating in your punch bowl
knows no direction
except for where the wind blows it.
And that's the true test
of a prophetic type of thing.
And that thing floating there?
There's a reason they say it's bobbing.
Because they call that thing...
They call that thing in the punch bowl
J.R. Bob Dobbs.
There's a little hymn for you.
That is sad and yet wonderfully true.
That's the way I see him.
It's kind of like a...
Well, it's been done before.
I thought of Mr. Hankey and various...
It's...
It's not funny, I guess.
I...
I'm sorry.
I'm so apologetic.
I...
It's J.R. Bob Dobbs!
He just entered the studio!
Well, at least the smell of...
A horrible smell just entered the studio.
That's me.
Stroking his member.
He's arguing with a rhesus monkey on his shoulder.
He's the guy you've been waiting to talk to,
but you haven't had the time.
It's J.R. Bob Dobbs.
Bob, how are you?
I have heart palpitations.
You know, the reason that
nobody's talking to you is because you're a...
Nobody recognizes Superman as Clark Kent
is because Clark Kent is kind of like Bob Dobbs.
Nobody would recognize Bob
without the pipe.
And nobody would recognize Clark Kent without the glasses.
That's so true, and by the same token,
the...
Some of the fundy subgeniuses,
the Bobbies, you know...
Oh, yes.
Anybody with a pipe.
Anybody with a pipe and short hair.
That's Bob!
That could even have a little mustache.
They could have a little goatee.
Without a pipe and short hair.
Oh, my God, that's Bob.
What if they got the half mustache?
May I ask one question?
Anything with a pipe.
Oh, wow, that's Bob.
That's so funny.
What about Subcomandante Marcos?
Oh, so old.
Been there, done that.
G. Gordon Gordon pointed out
that Subcomandante Marcos
was a subcomandante
and indeed does look just like Bob
with a mask on.
He's wearing a bottle of Bob.
Oh, with the same official underwear
and all the great accrutiments,
the red boots,
the big fuzzy red boots,
and the little fake eye tear
like Sovereigns and Temple Nuts.
It's a wonderful, wonderful getup
they got going.
Mine got up and went.
Well...
Whatever the hell you're talking about.
But it doesn't matter, don't you see?
It just don't matter
because it's all a bunch of Bob stuff, right?
If you just make notes,
no sense at all,
and play five records at once,
and say Bob every five minutes,
then it's a Bob show.
W-W-B-Do.
Bob?
Do I sound a little burned out?
Yeah.
A little.
Just a little crisp around the edges there.
You said, what would Bob do?
And then you also said,
what would Brian do?
And it made me cry.
I couldn't figure out
what the hell you were saying, man.
That's because you asked the wrong question.
The question is,
what would Bob not do?
What has Bob not already done?
Nothing.
Is there anything Bob isn't about to do
any second now?
Not a damn thing, Jim.
So, you know,
so I think,
I think we got our fair warning
and what we need to do now is
run!
Run!
It's in your very life
dependent upon it!
Get the hell out of here.
Maybe I just need some medical marijuana.
Burning.
We found this printout
in the studio here
that says Ohio lawmaker
introduces marijuana legalization proposals.
That one bill focuses on medical usage
and the second one
would be a statewide vote
for marijuana legalization.
Like on Washington or Colorado.
A la Colorado.
Then nobody would want to move anymore.
They'd want to stay here.
Well, and it's Representative Hagan.
Of Youngstown.
That dirty liberal.
The Youngstown Brown.
I hate them liberals.
He's a known liberal.
I'm going to be against legalization
if it means we all have to get
Youngstown quality weed.
Is that the problem?
I don't want any Youngstown Brown.
I don't want the Youngstown Brown.
I want the Cincinnati Red.
What do they call that?
Miggs County?
Miggs County Green?
Oh, yes.
Hocking, Miggs.
And people wonder why we moved it to Wisteria.
Famous around the world.
Yeah, I actually got lost in the woods there
and couldn't find anything.
Right.
Do you really want the Sherman Gray
or do you want the Miggs County Green?
The Sherman County Green.
Well.
I want a passport to hell.
I mean, to sweet, sweet, blessed oblivion
via the Church of the Subgenius.
Wah, wah.
I got the Philodrum and Purple.
Actually, it's the Philodrum and Purple
Vayner is the full name for it.
I wouldn't recommend it to everybody.
No, such frappazoolians are known.
That's why the experiments every year
get better and better and more exciting
because more people have brain damage
when they return home to their jobs
as dental hygienists or, you know,
writers or comedians in the funny man's world
and stuff like that or just, you know,
sewing up ditches with tiny little pieces of thread.
They discover not too long after
that much of their brain
is damaged from big chunks of the cerebral cortex
are just like rotting off.
It's a virus.
It's nothing to do with escaping planet Earth.
A very virile virus.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to rain on X-Day.
They all sound like Princess Wei in the background.
They all are.
Aw.
Now, why is that?
They're all Petra.
All those voices are Petra.
I thought I had the...
You have the voice in your sound.
That was like that Who album.
She also does an old, obscure Who album,
all a cappella.
She does all the parts herself.
And I didn't really like that one that much.
We?
Well, it's probably because you don't like Who
as much as some of us do.
No, it was the old Who.
It wasn't...
It was the, you know,
like 1960s.
1965 Who.
So the less people like that kind of stuff,
I'm just...
It sounds like you guys are in your living room
or something like that.
But did we...
That's we?
No, that's Petra.
Yeah.
I thought you were referring to the rock formations
in the Southwest you and Stang had visited
so recently ago.
I wish we were still there.
And so do most of the listeners at this point.
And so does that damn Jack Babbitt
that bit off your leg.
I tried to.
So, Reverend Stang,
you were saying that after X-Day comes Starwood.
You had mentioned that.
And I agree.
Oh, yeah, that's a hippie festival.
It's true.
That is a thing that happens after X-Day.
If there's any Earth left for it to happen in.
I actually ended up reading about
that Rosenbaum fellow.
He was involved in a dust-up
in the Wikipedia community.
Well, yeah, it turned out
there'd been somebody sabotaging the pagans
in general.
On Wikipedia for years now
and getting away with it.
And he was finally exposed.
Yes, and it pointed up
a real serious problem with Wikipedia,
which is that one person
can screw up the whole thing
if they're really dedicated
and if they have nothing better to do
with their lives.
And this guy didn't.
He felt that the world
shouldn't have pagans in it.
So he edited Wikipedia
to remove as much about
any kind of pagan thing
as possible.
That he could.
But was he in the employ of Wikipedia?
No, nobody is in the employ
of Wikipedia to speak of.
It's a voluntary editing thing.
And that's the problem with that
and democracy.
You get what you pay for.
You know, though,
I've tried to edit things
on Wikipedia before
only to have my edits removed
a couple, actually less than a day later.
And it was on a really obscure topic, too.
And it was removed within a day.
And I looked at the commentary on it
and the commentary on it was
a comment that the person
who removed my entry left
just showed that the person
was kind of ignorant
about what they were talking about.
And I gave up at that point.
Well, yeah.
You want to know how obscure this is?
This is about that.
That was a convoluted and interesting story
that went into itself
as if Wikipedia works sometimes
because that happens
and then this is why
at the same time
he was doing the same thing you were.
Well, it's the nature of the beast.
It's like democracy.
You're going to get,
you know, what you put into it.
Which quickly becomes demonocracy
after a while.
Well, Dr. Philodrum and
had a problem with Wikipedia
in the subgenius entry.
It says that the church
was founded by Bob
and then popularized
by Dr. Philodrum and me,
Reverend Stang.
Well, under Reverend Stang,
it also gives my human street name,
which happens to be
so incredible.
It's incredibly common
that I don't mind anyone knowing it.
Gary Jones.
Gary Hogwell.
Well, meanwhile, Philo decides,
okay, I'm retired.
My ex-wife isn't even alive anymore.
I don't have anybody to answer to.
I want my human street name in there too.
So he himself put in,
added to the Wikipedia article.
That's a very serious violation
of the Wikipedia and ethics.
If you edit that,
it's something that you are
personally connected to.
Well, here's the funny thing.
All he was doing was giving his real name.
Still alive.
So who is better qualified
to say who he is than he?
What is reality?
But I understand.
Jeff Rosenbaum ran into that problem.
The notability question,
if nobody else is going to bother
writing about you,
then you have no business
writing about yourself.
Well, here's the sad thing.
I went in and said,
hey, y'all,
because they kept removing Philo's thing.
He got quite angry.
And I went in and I said,
look, y'all,
this is Reverend Stang.
You've let me correct things in here before.
This is Philo.
Give him a break so he doesn't have to destroy
all of you on X day.
Well, they did for about two years.
But this year they started messing some.
He somebody took it out.
He went in and put it back in
and then it turned into the whole stink.
You know, how dare you say you're Philo Drummond?
Well, because I am Philo Drummond.
Well, how dare you say you're not Philo Drummond?
You're really Steven Roe Wilcox.
Oh, well, because I am both.
But you're not supposed to write
about yourself on Wikipedia.
Right. So I have to go in there
and write about him.
But what happens if it's in the subgenius article?
Are they going to discount it
because the biggest expert on subgenius
or to try to correct something?
Well, then you need to get a lackey to do it for you.
Yeah, that's what I've got a job for you, Dr. Sinister.
All right. I think I'm up to the task.
You're lacking some of the facial hair you had last time.
Really?
I don't remember, actually.
I change facial hair the way most people change underwear, you know?
The way most people change radio frequencies
when at around nine o'clock Sunday night.
I got a monocle tattoo.
I miss my mustache.
I hear a kind of interference in the background now.
Well, there is interference in the background.
That's Captain Beefheart.
But look.
Yeah, it's the phone line.
And it's probably here.
It's not even necessarily Dave.
It's not Dave.
We've been having problems with the phone lines here for weeks, too.
You now have your own special added buzz.
Well, except that everyone who calls will get that, I suppose.
Yeah.
It's probably a viral thing, but I don't know how they do it
because my phone is not part of the cloud.
The last time I tried to call a station, the Verizon jingle came on.
I don't have a cell phone.
A battery.
I don't.
I'm just using...
That's because Barack Hussein Obama has got headphones on listening to your every phone
call.
Well, he is the Antichrist.
With his hand on a drone button.
Because if you say something he doesn't like or if you heckle his wife, he'll drone you,
baby.
He threatened to drone the Jonas Brothers.
Did he?
I think so.
It was like a White House Correspondents' Center or something a couple years ago, and there
was a joke about how his daughter's head crushes on the Jonas Brothers.
They said, let me tell you boys, if you think of trying anything, two words for you, drone
strike.
It was a joke.
It was supposed to be a joke, but I didn't find it funny.
I think it's pretty funny.
It's a little funny.
I think it's funny.
Made me laugh right out loud.
I love learning.
Oh, man.
The things this country won't do in an effort to create a pay gap.
The PR event out of any stupid thing there is or conceivably could be.
Well, all the news headlines I'm seeing, I seem to remember from the year of 2006 as
well.
But that was six, seven years ago now.
That was back when a Republican was doing it.
And Democrats would protest about that sort of thing.
And then a couple years later, they get their hands on the levers of power and they do the
exact same thing.
So would you.
If you could...
You could listen to everybody's conversations, wouldn't you?
I would.
You know, I actually heard a story a few years ago, read it somewhere.
I can't remember.
But I guess there was a scandal in the NSA where they were getting recordings of soldiers
in Iraq and Afghanistan having phone sex with their spouses back home.
And they were passing around these recordings for laughs.
And they didn't give us any.
They didn't send a single one to the station, did they?
No.
That's how important college radio is.
I thought they were going to send us one.
I thought this was supposed to be, you know, a public record.
Yeah.
I thought it would be sent to every college.
Every college radio station should be able to play every phone call they want to.
I think the minute you walk into class, you should sit down until the teacher gets ready.
They should play all of the sex phone recordings of the soldiers in Iraq and various parts
of the world where they're currently stationed right now.
And any sexual innuendo that they, you know, and that's what you have to hear.
Listen to this interference.
Dave is on a landline.
Right.
Now that's landline noise.
Does Line 2 do this too?
It depends.
I mean, it's just all over the place.
Sometimes if you hear people calling up on the other line, you'll hear a while the phone
is ringing on one of the other lines.
Yeah, it's been messed up for a while.
Right now it sounds like someone crumpling paper.
Oh, yeah.
All the time.
As soon as I mention it, it stops.
I can just hear that it's not as crystal clear as it was two weeks ago when it kept
on exploding.
Subgenius listeners, this is the kind of programming that we strive to bring you every
week.
You need to know the justifications for doing why what we do and what we're doing.
We're fussing and fiddling.
And if you want to be a real subgenius broadcaster, you've got to get down on your hands and knees
and eat dirt like a dog.
God knows we've all had to do it.
That horrible sound just had to be bad mouthed by you long enough before it just shut down
altogether.
It's gone now.
We have a magical outlook, which could be a factor in this.
Now which?
She has a magical kind of overview of the situation and thinks that we could conceivably
shut off the source of the information without her.
I've watched both section of a book and a movie, where a ch warmed up before a scene
kommerpande.
What if that Hiding
I know a greed for real fortune is here, because I was looking at the prosecutor's
magnum.
faced by every subgenius?
Oh, wait, I have an answer for it.
I could just cut to interesting...
Actually, it's almost as bad as what we're saying,
so maybe I should leave it alone.
But for editing purposes,
I could end the show here or anywhere
and simply insert other material,
if it sounds bad enough.
To match what we've already done.
I'll have to dig pretty far into the...
Well, no, I'll only have to go to last week's show.
Well, there was the ballyhoo about
we were all at X Day walking around
and we were commenting on what we were seeing.
Well, that never materialized.
Instead, we start talking about a buzzing phone.
Excuse me.
I'm not centering.
And we were supposed to be...
Not supposed to be,
but there were kind of like some guideposts for...
In this little episode,
and we'd be seeing things
and we'd be talking about them.
Oh, there's Suzy Fluzy
with a cardboard box full of underpants
or whatever.
And instead, we did this.
She says she's not going to have
the cardboard box full of underpants this year.
But we're lucky enough to still have Suzy.
Suzy's still planning to be there.
Although it'll be by hook and by crook.
And without the box of underwear.
Without the giant box of underwear.
Jeez.
That's going to be really rough.
We'll make it somehow.
The hairy pants.
They're so uncomfortable.
I kind of dig them.
The hairy pants.
Well, you took a vow, Reverend Stang.
When you entered this establishment,
as you call it,
the Church of the Subgenius,
you took a vow.
You wear the hair shirt
to be reminded of your lack of sins.
My lack of what?
Your lack of sins.
You don't have enough.
Gotta get cracking, man.
I'm speechless.
Speechless, I tell you.
That might be because of the golf ball-sized
garter in your neck.
Or it could be because you're making
a subliminal statement about the state
of things as they are.
He's right there.
I'm not making fun of my neck again.
Well, at least he didn't mention my ball
of my foot.
That probably not a swollen thing
with a mind of its own.
That huge ball of my foot
that won't stop screaming
and giving me weird messages.
I wish that ball would stop.
Shut up.
Well, actually,
I think it is time to end this charade.
I'm going to go back to
cut-ups
for the remainder of the show
so as to let...
But Dave is a cut-up.
He's a cut-up, all right.
He's the class clown,
they called him.
Yep.
They also called him the class crip.
The class tard
and all kinds of very erudite
and mean things.
I can remember the songs.
That was my favorite part
of being bullied
were the songs about being
lacking in certain areas
that the other children weren't.
Now they just call the problem kid
the class Dave.
I bit each and every one of them.
I made them cry
as much as they made me cry
with my big sharp teeth.
I'm sorry.
Wait, is this turning into
another subgenius support group?
I'm getting kind of tired
of listening to subgeniuses
complain about their mental illnesses
and stuff.
That's what you're supposed to be
bragging about that stuff, peepo.
You're supposed to be
celebrating your abnormality.
Sure, the pinks may have
made you feel terrible
and insufficient
because of your abnormality,
but you're not.
Yeah, let me brag
about how dysfunctional I am.
Yeah.
Let me brag about how little
I get done in life
because of these awesome
mental illnesses.
I prefer to do that by example.
That's right.
To brag about how much
I've done by example.
Oh, exactly.
Inaction speaks louder than words.
I really was going to,
I really am going to,
okay, everybody shut up.
I'm going to put on
tapes that are even worse.
Okay.
Okay?
Are you going to shut up?
Shut them up, Bosh?
Dave, thanks for calling in,
even though on the exact moment
that you finally cured the buzz
on your end of the phone,
the station gave you a new one.
It's so symmetrical, though.
We all have to wear.
Well, I guess I've got to go
crawl back into my little cage
and I wish you all well.
I really do.
I've had a wonderful time.
Yeah.
Okay.
And do we wish you well, Dave?
We're all going away now
and fading out.
And so are we.
But my question is,
have you ever seen
any alien beings?
Yeah.
Just some alien beings.
Beat the hell out of me.
Well.
I drink.
I also use drugs.
I mean, stuff.
I use stuff.
Oh?
But you're 100% right.
Right.
Nope.
No?
Yeah.
What?
I also hallucinate.
All right.
I'm cool, man.
No, I'm cool, man.
I don't mind you being the sheriff.
There was one of the head dudes down there
and, yeah, no, they're never going to go into operation, man.
The way this earth is rolling,
we'll have them out of town before then.
You know, this is just absolutely ridiculous, man.
I mean, man, that controls the weather for the planet.
Man, this stuff is toxic nightmare 101.
That's why they don't care.
They could care less.
You know, you got to say, hey, man, man, this stuff, we should all do a class action lawsuit
on these things, man.
They're dinosaurs.
That's just common sense.
I mean, heck, and I was up there, too, man.
I couldn't believe that no one was keeping an eye on those dudes.
I mean, they've been garbage dump city forever, man.
I could see.
I mean, wow.
Bob.
Man, I am going to write it down on this computer front, man.
You got to drink your egg orange this morning?
Oh, yeah.
I had it with my pancakes, man.
I was, like, just dead, man.
I'm expecting that to not be the case pretty soon here.
I believe it was Neil Armstrong who made a report or remark, excuse me,
while walking on the moon.
This is during the live actual broadcast.
When he said that he saw what look like footprints on the moon.
Do either one of you remember Mr. Armstrong making that statement?
Yes.
I do not.
Do you?
No, I don't remember that.
Yes, I am correct.
And I, like myself, I could be one of those entities.
I could be done.
I am not done.
Done or not.
Mm-hmm.
Exactly.
No.
Taking a little day trip?
Um, Bob and I are driving home to Oregon.
You know, I really thought you were a ball, ball, ball, ball, ball, ball, ball, ball.
I've been set up.
I'll have another one, Bob.
And whatever a scenery I want.
No, I'm going to get off.
See you later, Bob.
I have been following your career with great interest, baby.
I can't understand a word you said the whole time.
Did you eat some peanut butter or something?
Yeah, you sound like a dog.
Peanut butter on the roof of your mouth.
Baby, I have come here to defeat you.
Oh, well, there's strikes two and three right there.
Did you hear what he just said?
Well, welcome to America, amigo.
Oh!
Ow!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
You are fast, baby.
But I am faster.
All right, you let go of me, you nutjob!
Like the frightened baby chipmunk.
You are scared by anything that is different.
I will let you go.
But first, I want you to say,
I love Bobby.
Put on your flip-flops and let's go shopping, dear.
Put on your flip-flops, we'll go flip-flopping, dear.
There's platinum petrol in the car.
We'll go shopping not too far.
When we were young, we would go pill-popping, dear.
We'd be pill-popping, but there was no stopping, dear.
But right now, I think I'd rather go shopping, dear.
Let's go shopping, dear.
We can cast away our fears.
You know the shops are really near.
I don't know what's behind everything, dear.
You're not a prostitute...
You're a monster, dear.
WeWow ...
You're cooked and ready to publish $1,000اض fullectivial…?
Cleveland Heights, Ohio
or see
www.subgenius.com
Praise Bob!
Friends, we're glad you listened to this show
and we're even more glad that some listeners
have donated enough to help us keep on going
for another couple of months.
Not just this show, but
subgenius.com and all the other
archive sites.
But if you truly love Bob
and want some of that slack back
to rebound to you,
you should go to subgenius.com
front page, or especially
the radio page, or the catalog
store pages
and help out financially as best
you can. Now, we
know what it's like to be on the
brink of total poverty and we don't
want any subgeniuses to make their own
situations worse.
But some of you still have jobs.
Even five bucks
makes a big difference, even
if it's only once a month from
enough of you. Fifty bucks
makes an even bigger difference.
All we're saying
is that blowjobs
could go the way of Steve Jobs
if you don't pay Dobbs.
We also take
checks and money orders to
subgeniusfoundation.com
P.O. Box
181-417
Cleveland
Heights, Ohio
Thanks for anything
you can do to help let there
be slack.