From PR News in Washington, I'm warning the world against PR.
Secretary of State John Kerry is slaughtering thousands of chickens and ducks
after the third outbreak of human flu in a week.
The State Department says spring sir bias is friendship.
Kerry says clear wetways paths will pass off a mush deal.
While Iran says backbeerous grim must probe clear full new peace to a trites did,
but Russian Foreign Minister Sergei Lavrov says PR News are already in place.
And now, the subgenius hour of SWAC.
Minority Mo.
And the only reason you don't understand our music is that you don't like it.
It's just nature out here, you know.
I mean, how many other people can say, you know,
oh, I woke up this morning and I, you know,
I saw...
I saw a raccoon mating, you know.
That doesn't happen very often.
Well, this is the, you know, what I call the extra meditation chamber,
or, you know, this is my bathroom.
You know, maybe it's a little primitive to some people's standards,
but it's got everything I need.
It's got running water and, you know, it's got a toilet and, well,
it's got a bucket and, you know, a place for toilet paper and, you know, I got art.
There's, I mean, the teaching of Jesus Christ, the authority, the commandments,
to strap a bomb to your chest, to abuse children, to go and kill anyone,
to blow yourself up, but that's what we're here on earth to do.
And once we, once we get a hold of the peace that is in that, oh, folks.
Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus.
A reflection for death.
Death by death, or lack of it.
Whichever.
Early Mesopotamian accounts of wide disaster made by God.
Later, Isaiah will remind Israel of God's flood to destroy the earth.
We can only disappear.
Water for all of us.
As the realization of Noah's promise.
Death.
For all of us.
Are you okay?
Life can be so difficult.
Which is what the doctor told him.
I've heard of this.
But my friend Sarah's mom just got life.
And it was affordable.
I would feel better if your mom was an option.
I've also heard of this.
Life from Life is affordable life that can be used to help protect your spouse.
If you're age 5 to 6, you can get a free life.
$10,000.
Premium start at $20,000 per month.
We also offer a variety of options.
Hasn't been an option.
Simple, easy, affordable life from a company you know.
If you thought you couldn't get life, now you can.
Make the call today and get your life right over the phone.
Call 1-826-252-321.
Why don't we call right now?
Get the life you deserve.
Life could be what you've been looking for.
Call 1-816-1513-11.
Tip 2.
prot warfare.
It's a real time sport that cuts most humidity using an oxygen sensor.
assemblingØ® Habo.
And Iãªã.
Lhenekranz시간каjtaujhangujnjmpedayajmanmichjjkanply녕
You.
ðŸ˜‚
I'm trying f sushi.
48,000?
my mind if I listen to it once like by the way to heaven like I just heard it
I wake up worshiping the devil and it's true listen
did you have a vision something coming
something very something very awesome something very something very awesome
no he didn't even think of that I have a great delight to come into the seat
or in palace was all with sticky and muttered Something were rotten still
it was a feeling
we want you want we want
stand far away
we decide that ours is the best and we put other people down
Put in fine clothes with gold rings on his hands.
Holy, something very awesome.
Come near, something very awesome.
You'll be given a wrap on your fingers.
Holy, something very awesome.
The choice is yours and the choice is mine.
To walk in the path of divine.
Holy, something very awesome.
The choice is yours and the choice is mine.
To walk in the path of divine.
Something very holy.
Something very awesome.
something very holy, something very awesome, something very...
Wipe these things away as if they are superstition and they lead to nothing.
Hello?
We Irish are nothing but a lot of stupid, superstitious idiots.
Quite right, sir.
You and your twisted sense of humor.
My what?
My wife.
No, wait. What?
What?
What's the matter with you anyway?
Yes.
And now, cigarettes.
In a moment, this cigarette.
Listen.
Extra.
Today.
Here in Dublin, a place known as Kenny Kills Devils near Inner Devlin.
And then, modern science, modern chemistry has shown that dark, dank earth produced this amazing telephone.
Very well.
I wish to talk to you, Mr. Bitty.
Well, I've certainly no desire to move Dublin, so I've decided to rent out the old place.
Rent it out?
Why not?
I see.
Oh?
Aye.
I'd suggest, sir.
And if I may say so, if.
Well, I'm quite certain I can.
Hello?
Goodbye.
Well, how are you?
Nice to see you again.
We certainly did.
Here.
Now, look here.
Good donor.
I don't know what you're talking about.
And do you don't know?
I don't know.
You heard me.
You?
Well, who knows?
You don't know what?
I don't know.
Who did this?
Show yourself.
Yes.
I see.
In daylight.
John Law is never wrong.
Officer Bob will teach you not to question authority.
Officer Bob was doling out chocolates to the war orphans when the call came in.
Now, I don't know how many times I've said this in my life, but I'm sure they've
He wasn't. He was rousting hookers for free hand jobs when the call came in.
He was rousting hookers for free hand jobs when the call came in.
Sexual assault.
Secretary of State John Kerry warns Russia's big foreign minister is expected tonight.
From Vienna, PR's report appears unlikely.
Serious analysts say supporters of a deal will have PR news for the second time.
Vienna.
Palestinian officials say this is PR.
If it is confirmed, it doesn't confirm PR news in Washington.
Jehovah and his son Jesus are strange gods.
Please see E.T. Novel.
Nothing that was God's given a Holy Ghost machine and I'll blow your head off.
Have a big time.
The refrigerator full of beer.
The cigarette stains on the fingers.
The dirty jokes that came from evil hearts.
God forgotten.
I want to tell you, brother, this generation of youth has been raised in an environment like that.
I hate to be as negative as I am tonight.
But they've been raised in an environment of sexual lust.
They've been raised in an environment.
I forget God.
Monkey rectums.
Hot oil massages.
X-Wing magazines.
Get mad.
Live it up.
Forget God.
Sin.
Get mad.
Live it up.
Forget God.
Make all the sexual conquests you can make.
They've been raised in an environment.
Marvellous.
So rule, my kind.
They've been raised in an environment.
Marvellous.
Gently awakening.
Felt
Gettin'
Back
Dead.
Come out.
From PR News in Washington, I'm calling for justice.
I'm scheduled to preach.
I'm expected today.
I'm confirmed.
I'm Carter.
Senate Majority Leader Harry Reid says he might find PR News appealing because Washington.
I'm prompted to step down.
I'm executed last year.
Chief Zahir Zahir Zahir said the director of PR News blew himself up.
I'm defying orders to retreat in Washington.
I'm to be the leader of Hong Kong.
I'm looking at the internet and this is PR News.
The study asked questions like, what does PR stand for?
Which is to be expected.
Most people know when to signal for a top sign.
But if you ask them when to signal for a turn, most of them are going to have a much more difficult time with that.
Almost 40% misunderstood PR News.
Which is to be expected.
It's the last day of June 1st.
In July.
I'm topping 11 miles per hour.
I'm PR News in Washington.
President Reagan reclords New York City with his plan toored free market market stock.
An Gra spokesman also cancelled the successful sale of Halloween
After right today's Aussie forecast.
Lieutenant Colonel James.
Attorney Byron.
for more information visit subgenius.com
oh busting again dear friends yes dear friends we're here where's dave i'm right here just
waiting oh i'm pinching needles to to hear the vibrations coming out of the top of your head
i just need to turn those headphones up that's all that's all it was as the snow comes down
on northern ohio and blankets all the lonesome cowboys under a shroud
of music by the law
this is the third week in a row that you've tried to kill me in words it's like 40 and slips
it's like well dave and shrouds and bone orchards and
but you're not dead yet are you dave i mean not really you're not really dead yet
of course not are you say you're not dead dave
there was actually a weird it's not funny though we had a some weird opening segments in the show
here uh fernanda andy lee did an awful lot of it uh we heard clips from the amino acids
cuttlefish electric apricot doctors for bob one last little cold minute by reverend awu guy
he's a new guy so it's hard for me to tell you which minute that was and and the spell awuga awuga
the uh the song raised in an environment of bob was the el queso all stars and we heard the steaming
sack of slack there towards the end oh yes yes yes and so now we may proceed with uh the next portion of the show
which i have no idea what it will be i'm tempted to just well shut up and let you and princess we do the whole show actually i had to do an interview last night on somebody else's show and i thought about just playing that today and you spewed your spewdom
he spewed your jolly is expended as they used to say in new orleans when they had five fingers at a time you know i'm sorry
man well we do have an upcoming event we could mention there's uh some folks may remember a
festival a winter festival called winter star that uh ace or the association of consciousness
exploration used to throw before the resort shut down they resorted to closing but uh we're going
to do it again at the beachland ballroom on saturday march 21st and it's free and
i'm the mc and fat mandy is going to be singing and there'll be music by mayan ruins and uh who've
been on the hour slack before and maruga booker who rocks and his cosmic hodow band right and uh
that's too it's it's free admission although they're trying to raise money for a a nice
tombstone for reverend stymie de bergerac also known as the late jeff rosenbaum
because uh because he he needs to have a nice cosmic tombstone indeed he does he didn't he didn't
get a he didn't get all the cosmic stuff he was owed because life isn't fair at all
oh and fat mandy is gonna sing at that uh uh winter star ball right right so it'll be like
a little bit of
x day in that respect there'll be me hollering and fat mandy hollering and you'll be standing
around looking beautiful and and lonesome cowboy dave probably won't be able to be there and that
makes it also like x days who knows you never know dave could show this time of day what day
is it on a weekend saturday march 21st the winter star ball at the beachland ball room
so there'll be a ball in the ballroom yes and i'll bring a ball
yes it's different from the winter star symposium which used to be a long weekend
oh we'd love that dave so there you go and we can go back to talking about morbid things now
okay well no that was morbid because it was to raise money for a tombstone that's true
the music in the background a minute ago was by uh this psycho skeletons i was
about to say the psycho love corpses i'm confused or the swinging skeletons or something actually
this is subs go marching in by artemia salina now and next we'll get to hear the hog and goose from
uh the country woods in but uh more of that later
you'll see what i mean
okay you sound a little bit not down in the mouth but rather like a
re-recognition
uh yeah whatever you said that's right
no i i just said that you sound a little bit
or not have taken umbrage or something but as if you were like an
cyborg
you know i'm not a cyborg
i'm just kind of mood
well i i kind of am we had a rough drive out here to the station there was cause for anxiety
never knowing never knowing but i guess that's why the way bob wanted it jr bob dob said you
ain't gonna know stag you just aren't gonna know you're gonna have to guess and bluff your way all
the way through it but here we are amazingly
think of it staggy
each other
here we go
a bb
ER
o
ï¿½ë„
e
later
make
hair
wars, people gnashing their teeth, skinning themselves, horrible barbarians chopping heads
off of other horrible barbarians right and left.
The weather right now, if you compound those issues, just think of only Vikings, even Vikings
couldn't withstand this weather.
Well, you know what they're not, what's obvious that they're not telling us is that it is
never, ever going to get warm again.
You ever see that movie Quintet?
It's like that.
It's going to be zero degrees from here on out.
In fact, zero will be considered warm by this upcoming summer.
Well, you've already noticed that just from being exposed to it for, well, you were exposed
to it the whole time you were gone except for brief stunts in Texmayorca and Dallasville.
It was blizzarding in Texas.
We got stranded in Abilene, Texas for two nights.
Two nights because the weather was too bad to drive.
I remember that part.
It was an ice storm.
And then we're turning in Kentucky.
And we died in Kentucky.
We had a car wreck and died.
It's been Twilight Zone radio show ever since then.
I hear you.
And you know, this is why in the old days of the former Soviet Union, there were so
many Russians who just like walk out bare naked with a bottle of vodka and say, you
know, some crude epithet.
I think I just heard that.
I heard Annie Sam going.
Annie, Annie.
Annie Sam, the pig.
Oh, what?
Annie Sam?
Annie Sam from Stangville, Texas.
Oh, she was the winner of the Miss Porcine Electrocutionist Award for the upcoming years
or something?
Or something like that.
Oh, I remember that.
She's the one who whined like a duck.
No, no, that's that's that's thing one is the goose.
Annie Sam is the hog.
It is a member of the aquatic fowl family after all.
To me, it sounds like a bad saxophone player.
No, these are the bands that we're going to have at the upcoming 18X Day in July when
we have our X Day Festival.
No, that's just really cold.
And that goose.
That angry goose.
That's just really cold.
Boy, man, it's been in the tenor.
It's like an alto.
It's kind of a rhythmic, but you got to keep your feet on the ground and your nose to the
grindstone.
Sorry.
Was that your nose grinding on the grindstone?
Yep.
It kicks up a lot of blood when he does that.
Yeah, I guess so.
It was the sound of my foreskin dwindling as I passed through the furious hours here
in Toastier Street.
It's right next to the pineal sands, somewhere in the medulla oblongata.
No, that's in the pineal gland.
Geez, what am I talking about?
I'm forgetting the parts of my brain.
Are you also?
I had to burn mine to stay warm last night.
Not all of them, obviously.
We just toasted lightly.
Yeah.
Well, we had nothing to eat, so, you know.
Well, yeah, right.
And you can't...
That's what you're faced with the choice.
Do I cook my brains and eat them, or do I just kind of keep them burning to stay warm?
If I eat them, then they're gone, and there's nothing left to burn to stay warm with.
Basically, all you got is that cooking time, and that's your cooking them and stuff, and
then you eat them and hope that that raises your blood sugar enough to fight off another
bout of minus 24 degrees.
Well, how are you staying warm, Dave?
Right now, I'm by a register.
A cash register?
Those don't count.
No, the international register of infernal places.
Really?
Oh.
We've got to go back.
I see big roadblocks with, like, these really, really huge looking, like, Nazi-type SS guys.
I mean, kind of abnormally large, like, seven feet tall and stuff.
Yeah.
And they're about 300 pounds.
And Stang was wearing just a mustache, not a goatee or anything like that.
Just a very thin, listy mustache.
Not like their fur or anything like that, but like the brave—
Like a pencil-thin mustache?
Yeah, like a gigolo.
Or the real brave revolutionary who gave up a career as a doctor of jurisprudence to
join the Navy and would regret his actions.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, just like that.
Yeah.
Are you talking about something you dreamed or something you saw?
Oh, I'm having dreams of big, huge—huge—I told you, big, huge Nazi-looking dudes marching
out of the scene, like, boot-stepping and everything like that.
Oh, so the answer is dreams.
This is dreams, right?
No, the unifying element isn't dreams, per se.
It's not even connected to that in any way.
I feel like I'm in the middle of a dream.
A slow down—a dream that's winding down.
A dream called the Hour of Slack that's soon to be over.
Oh, is it—
It actually couldn't be over soon enough for me.
This is the second show I've done this weekend, and the first one was a lot more fun.
Well, I knew what was coming.
I knew what was going to happen.
Well, in any creative endeavor, you have to have willing participants, and I suppose you
don't feel willing right now.
No.
No, I'd rather be hunting monsters in The Matrix.
You'd rather be warm somewhere.
Actually, it's quite warm in this radius.
Maybe like in Tokyo, where you'd talk a little bit and you wouldn't die from it.
Oh, I shouldn't complain.
I feel really lucky every time I look out in my backyard and see all those Nazis.
I've seen those naked subgeniuses shivering in that five-degree below zero weather
nibbling on this—
Oh, they bring cups—
—bushes and—oh, they don't even have anything to hold cups with.
They've had to eat their own hands off their—
Yeah, they have pot leiderlaugh—
You know, I wish I could help them and, you know, let them in to warm up for half
a second, but they'd just give them big ideas, you know.
And then you'd want to go up there and strangle them or whatnot.
And it's like strangling, drawing a che Perry zombie.
Argh- Teachers—
It's against...
No, it's just against the law.
That's all.
I'd love to make some subgenius venison chili,
but you can't shoot deer in the city
and you can't put subgeniuses out of their misery either,
even in the dead of winter when they just as soon you did.
Well, you could maybe throttle them for exercise.
I know you're trying to get into a new routine this week.
You could use 25 flaps,
shake them a little bit,
and then run away.
I can't understand half of what you're saying, Dave, for some reason.
I think it's because you sewed your lips shut.
Why don't you just cut those threads and flap your lips?
Because you sound like Andrew the Impaled after he's had his lips sewn shut.
What kind of voodoo doll would...
What would I be?
Can you hear me, Lee?
I can hear you, but I'm having a bit of trouble as well, so...
Oh.
Yes.
I have to reposition my...
How about this?
No, you'd have to reposition your brain in relation to your lips, I'm afraid,
is what you'd have to do.
You just need to go back and take diction.
You just have to take diction lessons again.
Did you leave your diction hanging out?
Did they...
Did they make you put it away at the supermarket
because you walked in the supermarket with your diction hanging out?
Listen, Dave, now put it away.
Put it away again.
So you think our sexuality is determined by a semantics?
I suppose that's where you're raised on YouTube.
That's where you're coming from.
I don't know where I'm coming from.
But I know where I'm going.
I'm going home at 10 o'clock tonight.
And that goes...
Stick around and have a few beers, a few laughs with the guys.
Maybe flirt a little bit.
And then see, we is flirting a little bit.
And you get kind of...
And then you want to go home.
And then you don't want to go home.
And you have another beer.
And next thing you know, you wake up in someone's parking lot you don't know.
What?
Huh?
Who are you?
What?
What's going on here?
I just woke up.
I am the voice of your extraction.
Look behind you, Stan.
You have a green elf on your wife's shoulder.
You have a green elf on your shoulder.
Well, here, I'll read from this script.
The Church of the Subgenius is the premier mind-control cult.
From the sales and salvation seminars delivered by J.R. Bob Dobbs in the 1950s
to the mail-order faith franchise of the 1980s
to the globe-crushing internet temple of the 21st century,
no other mind-control cult lets you keep as much of your mind
as the Church of the Subgenius.
That is well-spoken.
We're all under MK Ultra Sub Ross at 1255 right now,
which is beyond weather control and debilitation of the nostrils
by, I think it was some perfunctory offering that they used to give back in the old days
of, you know, blizzards and tycoons and stuff.
Well, Dave, it's true that our members are well-fed and well-adjusted.
We don't have to tell lies to build ourselves up.
It's a choice.
Bob doesn't miss a trick.
Although he has been known to trick amiss.
Any number of would-be rivals stand ready to receive your renumerance.
They try to rant, but it's only so much diatribe from the diaper tribe.
Rant has a noun with positive connotations.
That's ours.
We are a bunch of hicks fueled with the fire of hick-essential wisdom.
What do you say to that, Dave?
I agree completely.
I mean, especially the part where you had to burn the pig intestines
just to make sure that everything was electrically perfect
and electrocutionarily muzzled down.
And I had to make sure that you knew that.
You, each of you, have paid to know what you really think.
So, of course, we do know that, Dave.
Each of me.
You've bought your membership.
You've listened to the Hour of Slack.
You've memorized the pamphlet.
And you've hung a Dobbs head in your bathroom.
You're a zombie.
You're a zombie for Bob now.
His clever phrases are part of your daily patter.
Your sacrifice and your zeal have not gone unnoticed.
You took the time to show up.
Your mind is not your mind, and you don't mind.
Good.
Having rendered yourself a clean slate,
you may now scribble inside the skull of another.
Listen.
Attention.
Here are the secrets of mind control.
Take it away, Dave.
Who?
Subject?
Remains in chair seated uncomfortably.
Bring both lips and three eyes together in a perpendicular motion.
Hold the breath for exactly five seconds.
After this, imagine a cow coming into the room with a vest full of machine guns.
Then relax for five minutes and five minutes only.
Bringing your focus of attention into one part of the room,
make sure your hair is combed.
And then, once you're in the room,
Once remained seated, breathe normally.
Now, wasn't that worth it, kids?
That time and effort you've spent doing data entry for emotional invoices that'll never
be paid?
You're now free to hit delete and get on with things.
No more need to rehearse your wounds.
No more need to practice your problems.
When you thought to yourself, I can't think about this anymore, you were right.
Would there really be a problem with this?
Would there be a cow in a vest?
I think if you look back into page 72, I think it is, you let me grab my goggles and my haircut.
And let's see, it says on page 72, that those who were in the Valley of Snow had no meal.
So they cooked their favorite children and argued with the superintendent.
Ah.
You see, Dave knows that the function of language is to separate people into groups.
If the function of language was to communicate, we'd have one language.
Instead, we have hundreds of languages and thousands of dialects, all to make sure only
certain people are in the know.
Just so, the function of the Church of the Subgenius is to separate people into groups.
Us and them.
But we do more than that.
We can't stand each other, either.
Not that we hate each other.
Not that we hate each other, necessarily.
But that superior mutants are not interchangeable.
I'm so soggy and smelly.
We stand apart together, alone as one, against the great equality of the conspiracy.
And that's the way it is, folks.
That is exactly and precisely right on the money.
I don't know if money was the intended target.
Or perhaps some sort of investment program.
At either rate, if there are any rates going right now, we'd like to be rated very highly
in your book.
Which no longer exists as you know it.
Because everything's been taken down digitally, including your shortcuts.
But that's another story.
Inquire about the Church of the Subgenius at...
At...
At stang at subgenius dot com.
But you see, there's still lots of money involved.
Membership in the church can be purchased at the swag table.
Where a swagger will be more than happy to receive your order to join our order.
You can buy a membership for your every mood.
And you can involuntarily save the soul of your most reluctant family member
and most bitter enemy for the same price.
I'd just like to...
To ask one question.
If there's any kind of question in anyone's mind.
There's no doubt that stang has been on a religious quest.
Perhaps a crusade.
As some call it.
A downright obsession, many might say.
To argue with those who do not believe in his church.
He confronts them on the street.
There are bitter disagreements.
He's often thrown in jail.
Stang won't...
What do you say to all of this criticism?
Whether harsh or for actual reasons?
Well, that answer is easy.
Since everyone can be sold two dobs, you don't have to worry about it.
Oh, Reverend Stang, my girlfriend isn't a subgenius.
Oh, Reverend Stang, my co-worker isn't a subgenius.
Oh, Reverend Stang, those people I hate aren't subgeniuses.
Well, then get on it!
Everyone you hate has you in common.
So either save them or ship them out.
Either buy their membership to your own Church of the Subgenius,
or stop, drop, and roll.
Whoop it or go down.
Pee or get off the pot.
Kill me or kill me.
Ugh.
Yeah.
Well, those are some alternatives everybody should all do,
consider it seriously.
The rest of the world's about ready to be hit by an asteroid
as it stays zero degrees forever.
That's the horse's asteroid.
Oh, hell, doom and doom.
I should shut my mouth.
I know it makes the Reverend angry
when I complain about existence on Earth.
I mean, he knows better, of course.
Well, now, Dave, you know,
even a blind watch can smell when it's truffle time twice a day.
Twice a day.
Homeopathic wisdom says all things are connected,
but subgenius science tells us all things are not equally connected.
When you got turned down for that date,
it should ruin your evening, but not your life.
When the meritocracy is replaced with crazy merits,
it's just as awful as it looks,
but it doesn't involve you.
The pinks ruin everything cool,
and the conspiracy runs everything cold.
But you are not they.
They are them, and you are us.
Praise Bob.
When I first come to your country,
I am very, very vicious, and I am bare naked.
My thinking is not right.
I want to go good American,
and I love Bob so much.
I think I learn of the Bob in the old country,
and I come here,
I want to go far.
When I first come here,
I think I have to go to Texas.
I have to go all the way to Texas,
which is very, very far.
So I kick a man who has a beer truck,
and we twirl the punctures,
and all the way down to the,
I think it's the southern area,
the hemisphere, anyway,
and they don't eat their brains down there anything.
Mmm, mmm, mmm.
Well, it may be,
it may seem bad to you now,
uh, Mr. Immigrant Man.
Yeah, it can.
But when you find yourself in the blackest night,
and you think you're all alone,
maybe you are.
But you could be the dork before the dawn.
Go luck yourself.
Turn on the dehumanifier,
get smashed on a piñata colata,
and send one dollar.
Every subgenius radiates
the entire church like,
think lines, or a spidey sense.
Once you've turned over your worldly possessions
to the Subgenius Foundation,
you don't need us anymore.
Well, that's not necessarily true.
We know that since the timing of the war,
people have needed each other's company.
They've needed each other's resources and finance.
And they've also needed to go and wonder.
And, you know, it's back to that.
So I've left them go.
And you should too.
It's also asymmetrical.
It's like an hexagon.
Yes.
Or a polyhedron.
Is that what you said? Polyhedron?
Something like that.
It may have been a polyhedron.
It may have been a hexagon.
But it wasn't an accident that brought you here tonight, friend.
It was clandestine.
Bob puts the wince in coincidence.
It isn't always fun to be a subgenius.
And neither is anything else.
Well, except vengeance.
That's always fun.
But besides that,
you now know
that you can pack up those troubles in an old kit bag
and kill, kill, kill.
Kill boredom.
Kill pinkness.
Kill, kill.
Charlie Manson can't kill, kill.
But you can.
You're better than Charlie Manson,
Adolf Hitler,
and Kim Jong-un combined.
That's not flattery.
It's the truth, Dave.
I agree 100%.
Especially when you're talking about Pol Pot.
He used to smoke a lot of frop or something like that.
And he had,
there were two brothers in there both named Pauly.
It was little Pauly and big Pauly.
Man, talk about not having any kind of imagination thing going on there.
If they're parents,
there's really arguing,
you know,
good ones.
Once,
what's the thing in there?
They call it the third eye.
That's your patio plan, right?
The eyes are right.
Let those who have eyes see it.
That's the $5,000 winning prize.
And you've just named it.
So name your prize.
Let those who have ears hear it, friends.
Let those who have cash buy it.
My words have amused you all.
Bugs, some of you know what I mean at a whole other level.
I don't know.
I can't figure out what I just said.
It isn't enough to know your religion.
You have to believe it.
And right in the middle of believe is lie.
I think an air pie sounds good.
And I thought my jokes were bad.
No, that is one of the most,
you don't understand.
That is one of the most beautiful things that you ever came up with in the middle of believe is lie.
It's,
uh,
did you come up with that or am I,
I know I'm,
I'm,
I'm miscreant and all that other stuff,
but is that yours or the final?
Is that an old one?
No, Dave,
I'm reading from a new sermon,
an Onan sermon by Reverend Onan Canabite from December,
2014.
And I began this sermon by promising to reveal to you the secrets of time control.
If you can't remember me saying that it's proof that what I've described,
actually,
works,
whatever now means now you have now entered a time stream and are hereby absolved from all prior obligations and doubts.
Dave,
you have a new history,
one of your own design and must now proceed accordingly.
What you do with your freedom was predetermined,
but it was predetermined by you by choice.
You are the person you've been saving yourself for.
You are the one subgenius still able to save this cult from collapsing.
You know who you think you are.
You are who you think you are.
So get to thinking and praise Bob.
Praise Bob and praise Onan.
Praise Onan.
except for,
you know,
the one part about second class citizenship and stuff like it.
Well,
it was really,
really a good topic.
And I actually did totally forget.
And that was just fudge wall.
And,
but it was,
you know,
the last paragraph of what you read and had something to do with,
uh,
see,
I'm not going to catch it right now.
So you're going to have to,
uh,
me.
Oh,
I don't know.
Um,
maybe argue with the,
uh,
other people outside the window there.
Hey,
you know,
you sounded real clear when you said that.
I don't know.
I don't know the meaning of it,
but I understood the words quite well.
You're going to understand the meaning of it.
I don't know the meaning of the words because the words are only transcriptions of lies.
Just as you said,
what was it?
Believe in lie and believe in lie.
Well,
uh,
no,
the important thing of course,
is that,
uh,
it isn't enough to know your religion.
You have to believe your religion and right in the middle of believe is lie.
And that's why we maintain our faith in Bob.
We keep up.
The F I B we call it,
you know,
that Dave,
you wouldn't kid yourself about something like that.
Would you Billy?
Don't
you wouldn't fib about that.
Got to keep up the F I B.
Mm.
How,
how,
and I thought my jokes were good.
I still think that an eardrum pie sounds good.
An eardrum pie.
Doesn't that sound tasty?
Well,
it depends on whether you're a percussionist or not.
I miss fancy pitch.
I was going to say,
you know,
and let those who have about an ear flute pie.
Oh,
well,
that would be a little hairier and nasal.
How about an ear guitar pie?
I don't like the sounds of that at all.
An ear trumpet pie.
Why must it always be an ear drum pie?
Why aren't we,
why can't we think outside the ear canal?
Cause there's a time,
right?
Because in the time,
there's a tiny little drum like membrane that resembles a timpani head.
Wouldn't it,
I forget what it comes in the air first.
No,
it goes to the outer and it goes to the inner and then it goes through the bunch of names in Latin.
Yeah,
yeah,
that too.
Well,
anyway,
it's the resonances are much like drum pulsations to some researchers,
I suppose.
I had to read that far into it.
Some of us have fucking glands and we're not allowed to because our pubes smells like rain.
Or vice versa.
Oh,
got it.
Got it.
Smells like rain,
eh?
Catastrophe.
Yep.
Multi-global,
by the way,
if you don't mind inspecting my shorts.
I don't want to look at your shorts.
I mean my briefs.
I mean my,
my briefs.
I will not reveal my sores.
You should every day.
Nice.
Rain,
sometimes.
You know,
I have,
I'm looking at a,
go ahead,
Dave.
Go ahead.
No,
after you.
no,
I insist.
No,
you.
I go ahead,
please.
I insist that you talk.
No.
Well,
well,
I was just going to say absolutely nothing.
I just got into like a little,
little pantry odor with you.
It's like back and forth,
like tennis table or something like that.
And Nixon,
you know,
you were winning and I didn't even know what kind of game yet.
Well,
I think I may save the worst Bob song in the world for maybe next week or maybe no week.
I got this,
uh,
a Bob song on a CD in the mail.
It's from a friend of ours.
He is often a very talented musician and singer,
and we've played his work on the show,
especially around devotional time.
But he sent me a song.
You haven't heard this yet.
Princess.
We,
it's prop possibly the worst Bob song in the world.
And I should know because I have recently been collecting together.
Oh,
and I do mean all of the songs about Bob.
I've got,
I don't have to be picky about this.
This is a clear hands down.
Worst Bob song ever.
Maybe I shouldn't keep talking about it.
Maybe I'll just play it.
But it is so bad.
It is so very horribly,
horribly bad.
But now you've teased us so much that we are going to have to listen to the show next week.
No,
no,
actually,
I've teased you so much that it would actually make sense to play it.
Now,
let me see.
Dave.
Yes.
Now,
this song is about five minutes long.
I'm not going to play the whole thing.
Okay.
I'm going to,
I'm going to ditch out of it at a certain point.
And the listeners and the readers of this show will thank me.
But hold on and just hang through about,
oh,
let's say about three minutes of this thing and then I'll spare everyone.
Okay.
This is get ready.
Now this is our friend,
Reverend Malcolm tent.
All right.
Okay.
It's an instrumental business at first.
That's pretty irritating.
And then he starts singing.
So be ready.
Okay.
And then once we're at it,
I'm going to turn off and provide him some more of that sentiment.
I'm going to hit that voice.
A new line up for this project.
Everything's always simple.
Everything's easy to do.
I'm just going to tell you today,
But this isn't the really bad part here.
Well, Bob went down to Montreux
On the Lake Geneva shoreline
To record an hour of slack
He had that much time
The swinging love corpses
Were at the best place in town
But some yeti with a flare gun
Burned the place to the ground
Bob on the water
With saucers in the sky
He burned down the gambling house
It died with an awful sound
Connie Dolls was running in and out
Pulling kids out of the ground
When it was all over
It was all over
He had to find another place
Swiss time was running out
It seemed that Bob would lose the race
Bob on the water
With saucers in the sky
Bob
And I'll fade that down mercifully.
Wow.
Was I wrong?
Right?
That was painful.
Was I right?
Was that the worst Bob song you've ever heard?
I'd pretty much have to call it
The worst Bob song I've ever heard.
I've heard a lot of them.
I loved it.
Well, I love it too.
For what it is, which is
If you were going to sit down
And design the worst Bob song possible
I don't think you could do it.
I don't think you could do it
As well as Malcolm Tent.
I think you could do it.
I don't think you could do it.
That's true.
I hope he wouldn't be offended
By me describing it that way.
No, it's exquisitely bad.
I think that's why he's saying
Yes, it's exquisitely bad
As Leonard P. Starnell used to say.
It's so petty.
Exquisitely bad.
What do you think about the illusion
Perhaps of rubbing hot pepper in your eyes?
No?
How?
It hurts to think about.
Well, that song.
That's the way I saw it.
Well, it's more like
Pepper in your ears, isn't it?
Or something.
Well, no, I mean
It makes you cry
And it's very unpleasant.
It's very painful.
Rubbing hot pepper in your ears
Would make you just like
Well, spice it up a little bit.
But I think he used
All the spices available
And was not forgiving.
Yes, but you know
There are some genius radio shows
That are devoted to
Even worse music than that.
If that is possible.
Reverend Susie the Fluesy's show
In Atlanta, WREK station.
She recently did a show
That was every
Well, not every
But many, many covers of
The song
Come on, Baby, Light My Fire.
Everything from disco
To easy listening.
So, yes, some things could be worse
Even than this show, friends.
Hard to imagine, but
It could be true.
And luckily for the listeners and me
This show is coming to a bitter conclusion
Very quickly.
Well, I'd just like to thank you
For all your confidence
And in the creation
Of all the things you've done
Over the past six weeks, seven years
Fifteen years, whatever it's been, I forget.
But during that entire time
You've continued
To mislead and lead people astray
To confuse
To confuse and to hurt people.
To disinverse
To evolve.
Yes, friends, that's the subgenius
Radio ministry, Hour of Slack.
And we're going to end this broadcast day
With this old song here
By Reverend Yukon Jack
Introduced, I think, by yours truly.
But we'll see.
Dave, thank you.
And good night.
No, thank you.
Oh, thank you, Dave.
Thank you, Dave.
Oh, bust it again, dear friends.
But let us forget these things
And now end with a happy New Year song
From Reverend Yukon Jack.
Praise Reverend Yukon Jack
And W-I-C-A
Up there in Wisconsin.
Ooh!
Quit your job.
Bop.
Never again.
Quit your job!
Sire, there is no more money!
We gotta get some money!
That dirty, purgish, hark-a-packed, flackin' whartin'
Philip Bunker Burton, Perkaluma Burton,
doesn't fuss tonight at all!
Friends, we're glad you listened to this show,
and we're even more glad that some listeners have donated enough
to help us keep on going for another couple of months.
Not just this show, but subgenius.com and all the other archive sites.
But if you truly love Bob,
and want some of that slack back to rebound to you,
you should go to subgenius.com,
front page, or especially the radio page,
or the catalog store pages,
and help out financially as best you can.
Now, we know what it's like to be on the brink of total poverty,
and we don't want any subgeniuses to make their own situations worse.
But some of you still have jobs.
Even five bucks makes a big difference,
even if it's only once a month from enough of you.
Fifty bucks makes an even bigger difference.
All we're saying is that
blowjobs could go the way of Steve Jobs
if you don't pay Dobbs.
We also take checks and money orders to
Subgenius Foundation,
P.O. Box 181417,
Cleveland Heights, Ohio,
44118,
Uh, thanks for anything you can do
to help Let There Be Slack.
If you ain't got no money that
If you ain't got no money that makes you broke,
then bring some
If you ain't got no money that makes you broke, then more
Then more
Sex, money, Bob!
Subliminal Hypno Corporation!
Free pills!
Sex, money, Bob!
Kill me!