Yeah.
You're recording me, aren't you?
I'm telling you not to call me again.
I'm the evolving drinking theme crush now.
Yes, apparently.
What are the effects of the theme crush drink itself?
Uh, it makes you, uh, it makes you breakdream.
Ah, the break...
Oh, much like the breakwind of the...
Yes, the breakwind of the breakdreamers often clogs these busy mall arcades,
causing merchants to get out on the sidewalk and fuss and fume at the blocked aisles and the lack of customers.
And they often, what they do, they use what they call the dancing flame, and I think that's pretty...
Oh, I see. And then, just how do they carry the flame about the park?
Exactly. Exactly. That's the problem.
It's a giant match.
Scientists have been trying to decide this problem for years.
Here they are now.
This is Mission Control. Roger, you're one-three-zero-one-three.
Well, I don't think there is any question about it.
This sort of thing has cropped up before.
It can only be solved...
...if it's only attributable to...
The Self-Genius Power of Swag.
Roger, you're one-three-zero-one-three.
Well, first of all, I bring a personal message from Dr. Howell.
Do you believe that Howell has genuine emotions?
Well, he acts like he has genuine emotions.
But as to whether or not he has real feelings is something I don't think anyone can truthfully answer.
Hmm...
Hum...
I do, I do.
It's working now. I can't believe it. It's actually...
Huh?
It wouldn't start. It would discard.
Unbelievable.
Why did you stop it? I mean, by changing it, I smashed it.
Which is good for the cassette's meaning to be whacked on the side.
Well, I tried this other cassette on it. Let's try it with this cassette. Another call. Okay?
Well it's working now.
Sometimes there is something that can be improved,.
Well, Bob Dobbs is a real nice guy.
...
About Tom Dobbs.
Send a dollar to the P.O. Box, he'll get you high.
Yeah, Bob Dobbs is a real nice guy.
Send a buck to the box and he'll get you high.
The box number is 140306.
140306.
Dallas, Texas.
306.
706.
1-4-0.
3-0-6.
2-1-4.
1-4-0.
3-0-6.
Dallas, Texas.
7-5.
2-1-4.
Hello, caller.
Something has happened in the motorcade.
Yes.
I believe I can see Arnold Palmer showing up.
You mean he's alive?
Something did happen.
No, he's not alive.
Temporarily alive.
Not for long.
Oh.
How do you communicate with him?
Communicates quietly.
Foot gland.
Have you been glandscaped?
Which I think he's practiced a great deal since he was born.
Excuse me.
I see.
Let's see if I can get it right.
Yes.
Teddy.
Bobby.
Johnny.
John.
They're all here.
This will be the Kennedy Hour.
We will be here with all the Kennedy family, dead and alive.
For later interviews, any of you with political orientation,
questions can call in here at the KPFA hotline.
Just phone 848-4425 and talk to a Kennedy.
That's right.
And ladies and gentlemen, I'm most honored at this point to say that we will be going to camera one on the floor live.
This is Reverend Stang down on the floor at the Divival.
Stilex, I think, is about to play.
Here they are.
Stilex.
We'll be right back.
Time to forget yourself
Sudden panic attacks
Like the break of dawn
Slowly the empty rise
Remember who you are
But let it dry and fall
This time just yesterday
You were losing your mind
Now it's complete and all
Make sure you're forgetten
I have no right or stage
To make it back home
Wait up, wait up
While you work it
We've got way down
I'm not the one in control
I am a machine
And I do as I flow
I'm not the one in control
I am a machine
And I do as I flow
I'm not the one in control
I am a machine
And I do as I flow
I don't want to go
Try again
I won't ever do it again
Why are you working
I'm not the one in control
I am a machine
And I do it on my own
I'm not the one in control
I am a machine
And I do it on my own
I'm not the one in control
I am a machine
And I do it on my own
I'm not the one in control, I am the power, and I do as I go.
I'm not the one in control ...
Bidwell
approach to it and it's
extremely vague and
our religion is based
on hypocrisy folks
don't ever if you ever
catch us being consistent
oh I don't know what to tell you to do
kill me
the Buddha said if you meet the Buddha
on the highway then you should kill him
and Bob said something like that
and there are people who think
they're Bob running around there and you should
go ahead and kill them
if it's really Bob
he's like Daffy Duck
he'll come back with
band-aids on
but if it's a
false boss
slack is dollar bills
slack is drugs
slack is a warm home
slack is the car
you drive slack is the
job you do for money
slack is that which the conspiracy
system
stole from you
they don't love you Bob
they don't love you like I do
slack
you slack
for sure
slack
beyond your wildest dreams
by now it's slack
you
slack
you have the power to find slack
good something for nothing
credit cards are taken
slack
send cash
I want more slack
send your money now
conspiracy denied me again
send your money
I will have my slack
your slack's open in here
slack
buy more slack
use slack
you slack
your period
all sorts of slack
new slack
every kind of slack
I'm adding them all
slack
slack from the other side of the world
slack from right next door
here we go
slack salesman
slack salesman ladies and gentlemen
you slack
buy it here buy it now
slack from the other side of the world
knockhusers
suck
you slack
we have you slack
blackjack
take the blackjack
elegant
new sack
use slack
back fresh
Coogming
slack
If you have the cash, you can have your slack.
Money is slack.
Something for nothing.
Slack is green.
Slack.
Slack is government control for your protection.
I want more slack.
Slack is not for everyone.
You cannot take my slack away.
Slack can be taken by prescription.
A used slack for sale by the great king of slack, Reverend Bill T. Miller.
Friends, there's tons more Bill T. Miller mixes.
at BillTMiller.com
or also at KingOfSlack.com
Thank you.
And we're going to get some of the stuff that we want to do so badly.
And now with the injection of this age force that you have received through the regulation
of the cash flow and the invokin of the yakutismic forces, and the true aesthetic beauty life-death
force of the universe is coursing through your veins, we now look at our work and go
through it, plan every step of it, every, every facet of it until there it is.
And that's it.
crafted, polished, completely, perfectly assembled.
The great jewel, a great jewel of something,
of some great expression that we've wanted for so long.
And we focus it, we examine it, we look at it,
holding it there with the energy from it feeding back to us, from us,
as it is us and we are it.
And then we blow it all off.
That's right, friends.
At that moment, we just blow it all off.
We snuff it out.
We throw it away.
We say, yeah, well, that could be done.
Could be done.
Could be done exactly that way.
I know I can.
And so what?
Why should I?
And when you blow something like that off,
ah, the slack, it doesn't trickle in, friends.
It surges in.
It's a great injection of slack into your life.
Yes.
Do you like people?
No, I don't.
Do you like all kinds of people?
That's wonderful.
Do you like adult films and other visual materials?
I'm looking for a book on television.
Steadily expanding direction.
I think we can help you.
You do?
That's good.
There exists a number of positions.
You will find that there can be...
great variety and interest.
But you will be rewarded with real pleasure television.
People like you.
On wheels.
Did you get me that material on the sternocleidomastoid
and the zygomatic head of the quadratus levius priori?
Yes, doctor.
Here it is.
Oh, thank you, nurse.
Pleasure work by Norell Preff there, friends.
And you can cop whole albums of Norell Preff
at heavyconfetti.com.
Yes, heavyconfetti.com, friends.
You can put that in your pipe and smoke it.
You can put it in your pipe.
Now, some people say,
oh, but Reverend Stang,
what about Bob's pipe?
What's he smoking in there, Reverend Stang?
That must be marijuana.
That's what Slack's really all about,
getting high and sitting around on your ass all day,
not having a job.
That's the pink boy dumbass version of Slack,
my friend.
That is the dumbass version of Slack.
The dumbass version of Slack is,
I'm a slacker, dude.
I just sit, I donate, I work as bad
because, because, because, you know.
Friends, for some of us,
Slack is being as alert and aware
as you can possibly be
and keeping in that awareness.
The thought that you are indeed
smarter than those other dumbasses around you
who are trying to out-yell me.
You can't because you don't have an amplified microphone.
You can't, you can't be as dumb as Bob
because your face has not been mimeographed in Xerox
and put up in as many places as his hat.
Again, you may doubt,
to the polished ears of the modernist
or the liberal or the conservative,
you might say, well, that don't make no damn sense.
Pace fucking Bob!
And then you say, well, my friend,
what Reverend's saying, what about sex?
I've heard sex is Slack or Slack is sex
or something like that.
How often is sex really Slack for you, my friend?
How often do you achieve the ultimate ooze squirt
that will make you feel like you're a fucking dick?
What do you do, Felаете?
Why, I Kurt, what do you do, you furious
fucking sick asshole.
I mean sit.
Then I roll in the toilet.
Aye, aye.
So how do you know if you have the ooze squirt, the pure sex feeling that Bob and God and evolution put into your head?
How do you know?
You don't know, friends.
You don't know until you have emptied yourself of all that conspiracy programming.
And that doesn't mean studying the word of Bob, buying the videotapes, reading the books.
Of course you have to do all that.
But then you have to flush every bit of it out of your mind.
Because your mind is a toilet that the conspiracy has been shitting in.
Yes, the conspiracy has been shitting down your brain hole.
Mine too.
I'm not saying I'm in any better shape than anybody else here.
As a matter of fact, I got a cold.
I'm hallucinating.
I'm half fucking crazy.
And that's when I'm healthy.
Pop that Bob on the brain, my friend.
That's right.
My shorter persevere.
Bob does.
Or I just don't believe him.
This is starring...
Al-Qaeda changes its tune.
We're by Ed Fred.
And now Dr. Onan Canobite on the road.
It doesn't matter if you're a vegetarian,
or if you eat hamburgers,
or if you're something else.
You know, a lot of subgeniuses have been on the Slatkins diet lately.
The only raw meat diet.
And it's true they've lost weight,
if that's what they wanted.
Others have gained weight, if that's what they wanted.
The Slatkins diet adjusts to your needs and your goals,
even before you knew you had them.
A lot of subgeniuses have been on the Slatkins diet,
Slatkins diet,
since before they were born.
How is that possible?
Send one dollar.
And you ain't heard the last, Ernest T. Banks.
Yes friends, we all make mistakes.
If we were like Bob,
we'd make a million dollars every time we made a mistake.
But if we were like Bob, we'd be as lucky as Bob.
And friends, I'm sorry, but
he's Bob and we're just friends.
That's why we worship him.
And isn't he a great person to worship?
Because it's not like he's going to show up
and make sure you're worshiping him right.
The great thing about Bob is,
you can be alone with Bob.
When you're with Jesus, you're not alone.
Jesus is still breathing down your neck.
He's still wondering whether you've been sinning or not.
When you're with Santa Claus, you're not alone.
He knows whether you've been bad or good.
Bob does not care whether you have been bad or good.
Bob does not care about your sins.
Bob came and comes again and again
to justify and excuse your sins.
Such as they are.
Most of your sins are...
You know, you feel so guilty about that bad thing you did.
Man, everybody in this room did that same bad thing.
Bob is not in the same room.
You're not impressed.
Unless you've come up with a new bad thing
that no one else has ever thought of before.
Then maybe that's what we call slack.
Among other things.
Oh.
Ha.
Give me good Bob.
Give me slack Bob.
Give me brap Bob.
Give me brap, give me brap.
Give me brap, give me brap, give me brap.
Just kidding.
That's the way we like it here.
At beautiful WCSB.
At Cleveland State University.
Ah, yes.
The most noble college station in the world.
Except for the other college stations that carry this show.
Such as beautiful WREK.
In Atlanta.
The strongest.
Of oh, the southern.
potent power
college station. The rising
banner of the new south.
Not a flaccid whore of the old
confederacy, but a beautiful...
They do have a flaccid whore. Oh, well, of course.
But it is these
other stations that carry the
hour of slack. And friends,
we're coming up on hour of slack
number 1,000.
Yes, there have been almost... This is hour of
slack number 990.
One... Soon we will
come up to Bob's number 999
and then finally,
yes, the conspiracy
will fold in
half when we reach the magic
number of
1,000 hours
of
slack!
Hey.
Hey, Chico.
What you going to do with your slack?
I'm going to go after that blondie
guy. I'm going to cut him.
I'm going to cut blondie. And then I'm
going to get him.
I'm going to get him with my badge, man.
I think I'm going to go and buy some hot
chocolate. Hey, do you have any stinking badges?
I need a...
I can find you
the hot chocolate if you can find me some stinking
badges, man. I need some stinking badges.
Well, just take a look at these ones here.
See, these were recently removed from a
man's groin area.
Oh, an elderly man's groin area.
An elderly incontinency.
Yes, incontinency man's groin
area. And these came
from a small child's...
Well...
Let's overlook this child. Let's move
on to the next child, please.
That child was not radio-friendly.
No, that was not a radio-friendly
child you were talking about.
Or any sort of mechanism
which flies through the air. You cannot hear her.
You cannot feel her. She's like...
I don't know, like an anti-radio wave.
Perhaps it is more like a...
No.
An TV. Anti-TV.
Anti-radios.
The silent radio
signal, friends. Yes,
sandwiched between the layers that you can hear
and the carrier signal.
There is a third signal.
The DAWB signal that is
getting through to you and imparting to you
a sense of the slack you already
had, my friend.
You had that slack and you will
have more slack if you turn
up the radio. Let's
this...
...your third
nostril and let the
essence of the slack power well
up within you from within your well
swollen, good annual
areas. Millions of them smelling
the slack as they come over the
mountain were saved, Jeanette. You will be like
the badge of an elderly
groined man. Oh, Jeanette
was saved. The sub...
...genia here.
Uh-oh.
Epigenia? The dangerous?
Does his name appear in the book
of life, Lord?
Nay.
Cast in and into the lake of fire,
for the Lord is not slack concerning
slackness.
We've got, um, Williams, Terrence,
um, Clarence, Barron, Terrence,
uh, 2972.
Terrence Williams, 2972.
See, three thousand...
Oh, he was convicted
and found guiltless of
wearing a blank yellow
page. He said, uh, I'm writing
a book and you fill in the pages.
Here we are on page three.
Mr. Williams says in his own
eloquent way, he says,
Bob Dobbs has given me
more slackluster and flavor
than I've ever experienced in my entire
life. By the time I'm
ready to go, I've already gone
twice each day. And I don't have
to eat bran, it eats me.
Ah. Well, I don't
know for sins, but, uh, hey,
a good way to go. The prune.
Ah. The almighty
prune. Shoo ye not
the prune. And
and and and can't
Yeah, dried plums.
Yeah, right, whatever. And do not sniff
at the dried baboon. And don't
make sniffy faces. The dried baboon
is the key. Oh, now Bob's laying out a bunch of rules.
So now we can't sniff at baboons purple.
Those are not Bob's rules. Those are
my rules. Those are the rules of God.
As expressed in the mathematical
number of pi.
And here are some... The true name of God is
216 letters hidden
within pi. I read that in a book somewhere
or saw it in a movie or something.
And speaking of pi,
how late is that baker's pi
place open? I'm getting hungry. Oh, no, no,
no, no. No, no, no.
No pie, no baker pie.
We hate pie. Pie is baker bad pie.
Tonight is a pro people
anti-pie show.
We deal with deviated
septum, septum, septum,
septum. Yes, yes.
Unless they are septic,
they are septic.
Quadinal arches?
We like to climb them, alright?
Thank you.
Hello, this is a recording
that will not be repeated. Thank you.
Oh, thank you.
These
are the forces. This
is the power. And this is
65869.
Now what? What?
What is the most potent
invocation you can have against the
conspiracy?
Dot, dot, dot, or kill me.
Say it. Kill me now.
And close your eyes and feel.
Go ahead, please.
You can't say on the radio.
On this call, we'd like you to use the T.O.P.
Okay, I feel like 6586928.
Here I am having a feeling that I'm not supposed to have.
This is a good time to stop this tape.
Go ahead, please.
Oh.
I'm gonna go down.
Where's my money?
Bye.
Man, I'd better do that.
I was struck naked right in the arm.
Paul here.
Oh, of course.
Hey, hey, puzzling?
It's puzzled.
Color Xerox place.
Nose around.
I'm gonna call Lies and see if he can tell me the truth about your location.
I'm calling you again about your fly.
I really need it as soon as possible, please.
Thank you. Bye.
Go underneath the atom ball, okay, Doug?
I'm gonna go down. I'm coming, Doug.
Okay.
Come, come, come, come, come.
Ah!
I want $2,000 off Lyft or just kill me!
Yay!
You have reached Doug.
All our lines are busy.
As soon as one of our lines is free, you will be connected with today's curse.
Thank you for waiting.
He or she is a slimy-sided, frog-mouthed, silt-eating slug with the brains of a turtle.
Thank you for calling, you pathetic, cringing little milksop.
This is a recording.
In the name of Bob, I demand that you hang up on me right away.
Thanks to Dr. Phineas Narco for providing those cuts and clips that were by puzzling evidence.
And Dr. Howell and Bob Nelson and Gary Gabrogfran and all the rest of us old-timers.
Uh, and now, Hellpulp Huey.
Actually, you're closer to the core of true slack than most.
By sitting and bitching about it and not chasing it, slack can come to you in its true form, unadulterated.
If you chase a cat bellowing, come here, you little bastardo, I wanna pet you, the only portion of cat you will experience is the egg it will lay on your pillow for your disruptive screeching.
However, if you dab a little tuna on your chin and lie there on the couch passively grumbling about your imagined laxin life, why sure as anything, that cat will come up and lick you right on the chin.
That tuna is your yeti hood. That cat is Bob and the effect of that licking is pure slack.
Going out among the pinks is a wretched thing on its own, but when used in its proper form as the psychic slide rule for divining the spaces between crap and shinola,
it can refine your sacred laziness and generate for you all the tuna you need.
Of course, if you just leave it in the can, screw you, I did my part.
After all, we have a fake president, faked enemies, fake patriotic gusto with balsa wood underpinnings, fake food, fake heroes, fake love, and fake Chinese dildos that fall apart after the fourth porking.
So I'll be really, really amused when one of those giant tripods steps on George and squishes him like in Bambi Meets Godzilla.
QEM do happy happy joy joy dance them very muchly, yes, min saheed, mmm.
isto habo Audrey
TKC
Thank you.
That ate my teeth
The coffee chair
It lost its shape
Destroyed
Destroy old things
And do it today
You broke a string
And you broke a string
Throw the guitar away
Find a new one
Now they're all so cheap
So what?
Who cares if it just lasts a week?
Destroyed
Out of date
Outmoded
Out of all of you
And out of all of you
Destroyed old things
And buy all new gear
And do it
Several times a year
Spend your time
Cash for
Get the quality
Do your part
For the economy
Destroy it
Buy it cheap
Be smart
Shop
Yes
, smart
This brand new stuff
Your body's broken
Destroyed
AT a flash
But the budding public
Have already spoken
They purchase garbage
With a smile
With violent high
On top of stinking garbage pile
Shock
Destroy it
You no longer care
Fix it all so it can't be repaired
Smash that trash, no hesitation
Destroy and vent out all your animal frustration
But what to do with all this waste
Fired into outer space
Would cost too much
Instead let's act fast
Destroy it with long-storming fire
Turn those heat-missing lights
Piles of trash into radioactive ash
Outsized
Outcast
Destroyed
Destroyed at last
All your new things
Destroyed
Will soon be broken
You'll buy them over again
Do you think I'm joking?
We can, we should
Blow it up real good
Destroyed
läh, leh, geh, eeh, go
Thevold
Thewatch
We're heavy!
they might be buying at Woolworths in the next few days.
We don't know.
Only Bob knows that.
And the great thing about it is he doesn't care.
You are completely free of any guilt trips.
Bob just ain't judgmental.
You've noticed it's not called the Church of the Genius.
Have you noticed that?
It's called the Church of the Sub-Genius.
It's not that we're not proud.
It's that we believe that the conspiracy has misdefined intelligence for thousands of years.
So that now an intelligent person, that's your limp-dick-no-nuts college professor
that hasn't got his rocks off in 15 years.
But he made better grades than you, so therefore he's more intelligent.
Or Bill Gates, who made more money than anybody else.
Does that prove intelligence?
Of course not. You know that.
Then what we're talking about in the Church of the Sub-Genius
is not intelligence, but sense.
Common sense.
Sense of humor.
And dollars and cents.
Now, Reverend Carter LeBlanc was up here trying to get...
He was talking about the dollars and cents.
He wants you to go back to that table and get yourself ordained
so that you can do marriages.
Massaments, everyone, what are you looking at?
Subscribers the absorptions of all that shit.
Seriously, that stuff sucks.
It actually and a hurts the whitewashed dresses between cold and cold
and gunpla fires.
Disaster started to suppress your eyes in all kinds of my contains,
all this behind cose,
and of course you have a skin on your face,
and resources for a few 아이폰 Firmen are so bothering.
Would you like a few pieces of that stuff?
there to watch each dropping of each coprolite from each dinosaur sphincter. Bob saw. Bob sees
now. Bob always will see. And if it is not superfluous to add, the only faith that promises.
It may sound like we're endorsing the worst kind of conspiracy behavior. No, you only do these
terrible things to get what you need. Each caller hears a different thing. Well, it's my own idea.
Oh, now the caller's turned into a little dog playing the drums.
Sphincto's dead. Yes, it's Mimi Kemp's show now. That's right. We're trying to bring him back. We
just don't have enough juice. Sphincto is dead, but it's schmutz. I better send more money. Yes.
Dr. Howell, how do we get them on? They're back to Earth. Well, we have spilled a pure neutronium.
And now the neutronium is rolled down to the street level where the peasants will begin to
eat it and then kiss the queen, giving her the power of the neutronium. Yes, this neutronium,
the densest substance.
Known in the physical universe, it is going to be the basis of an entirely new review of the
tale which all of our foreign dignitaries, as well as the president and his charming wife,
will ascend in just 25 short minutes as the subgenius floats continue in this parade of
parades on the year of surprises. And here, moving at faster than sound, a giant transports
in a transportable... Leave them on. Dear God,
please don't let it...
...stray, rot, water chew off my genitals. And don't let my arms be pulled off by a threshing
machine. Don't let me crash on the freeway, mangling my legs and causing massive irreparable
brain damage, paralyzing me for life so I can't move, clean myself, or go to the bathroom normally.
Don't let me be stabbed in the head or be captured by a sadistic serial killer who tortures me in
his basement.
Don't let my building collapse in a horrific earthquake trapping me, all my bones broken
and split, smothered so that I can barely breathe, with my life slowly sleeping out
of me.
Please God, keep my skin from burning. Don't let me go blind. Don't let me be shot, slashed,
or bludgeoned to death. Don't let any of my organs fail on me. Don't let my bones snap for any reason.
Don't let my skull be fractured or my eyes get accidentally punctured. Don't let anyone
I love die or get sick. Don't let me become homeless. Don't let me lose all my possessions.
Don't let me be arrested or executed or tortured. Don't let me be raped or assaulted. Don't
let me be hit by a car. Don't let me get liver cancer. Don't let me get old and live in a
hospital. Don't let me be sick and helpless. And just don't let anything bad happen to me.
Please.
And in exchange for this, I will try to be a better person.
News in Washington. From PR News in Washington, I'm trying to regain the momentum that brought
down PR News. The Walt Disney Company has announced that they brought Peter Pan to jail
in the Philippines. The legal team says he would be transferred elsewhere to be tortured.
And now an official reports from London. There's been military action against PR News,
symbolic status quo. Thousands of PR News in Washington. From PR News in Washington,
I'm sticking a gun in her side and tying her up to slowly lower PR News while at the same time
making room for more PR News. 61072244. Yes, you've entered the listener zone.
You're one of the listeners. Hello? Hello? Yes, hello, you're on the air. Oh, yes. Did you want
to hear Too Young to Date? I want to know everything I possibly can about Bob.
I must know more about this mysterious Bob.
This studio is slanting a bit. Oh, the gas. If you're in a canoe and you don't have that paddle
that you need, don't worry about it. Don't sweat it. There are lots of songs you can sing,
things like that. Things are nice, pretty, you know. Don't worry about it. Because I mean,
the problem is, you probably haven't thought.
The problems that you have at this time. Yes, and how much time do you have left?
I can't think anymore. It's 3.30 and you can't think anymore.
Why they didn't even announce they were going to test today.
No, Skull Farmers. They're testing the Skull Farmers again.
The rising sun will play thunder.
Being a driver in a panic, climbing the brakes on a positive note.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Yes, showing them how to breathe now.
What was that?
There they go. Teams of doctors off to the different heliopads to answer your needs at this hour in Berkeley.
And here on this program.
I glanced at Bob and then I saw a great whale of fright overcoming target situation.
Jacks are better to open.
This is Conrad Red alert.
This is not a test.
This is an alert.
Take cover immediately, everyone.
I repeat, this is not a test.
This is Conrad. Take cover immediately.
We are under attack.
How quiet it was under attack.
The competition finally found the following.
The first one.
The show.
Wait a minute.
I'm not asleep.
I'm really on the show.
What's happening.
I wouldn't know.
Okay.
Listen.
Then we've got to find out what's happening.
Read the map or something.
Stop.
Stand up.
Put that cigarette out.
This is time to think.
Here.
Light up a cigarette.
Relax.
I don't know.
They said all of Berkeley was invited down here to start a show.
So we're all lined up outside the station here.
We each get two minutes on the show.
They're all lined up outside the station here and we're.
They'll get their two minutes too
Everybody gets time on the show
I understand
Well they're farther back in the line
Nothing to get excited about
It's just a show
Yeah I saw it too
At Dockstop
Trying to get away from the music
The music was so horrible
So bad
People running in all directions
Doing anything they could
To stop the music
Stop the music
And they watched for all those people
Who were buying lots of postage stamps
At once in suspicious amounts of course
And mailing lots of large boxes
That had radios in them
That couldn't focus on any one thing
Hello
I'm just trying to send this to Dallas
No it's not
The voice is not coming from inside the box
Let go of my box
Yeah right
Hello
I think I just wanted these tapes
You know
Yeah
No no
No you're one of the tapes we're playing
We're really here
Look buddy
We can't be talking to you
If you're going to be calling us up
And ask us questions
If you're not sure
Then you have
Not sure
You're not sure you'd call us?
Okay well then you have
Some really old puzzling evidence
From the 80s
Thanks to Phineas Narco
For preserving that
Now next Dobbs is asked
If he is a traitor
Dobbs has embarked on an anti-traitor
Trade tirade
Too greedy
Too vile
Unnecessarily adversarial
Now it's interesting listening to Dobbs
He's a pro-capitalist component
He's not really a capitalist
Dobbs
In some ways
He's so caught
In this illusion of the ruling class
Dobbs says
When Dobbs is talking about
Don't put the middle class competing
With the third world
Let's check out what Dobbs has to say
Because
Let's see
Let's see how Dobbs responds
To this whole process
Dig this
Dobbs is further advanced
On this particular issue
Than you are
Now what's interesting
In part about this
Is that
You know while Dobbs is right on
You know some of these issues
About as far as
What is happening
Let's check out what Dobbs has to say
Dig this
Mars needs women
When Dobbs says
When Dobbs speaks
By Noro Pref
More about that
At heavyconfetti.com
For more about Dobbs himself
Though friends
The best place to go is
www.subgenius.com
Ah yes yes yes
That makes total sense
Do you want to drive
Sakuya
Press
Bueno
See you
Bye
Ah
MALE MODEL
Come
Come on
We will
But I'm driving
No I can't
We'll drive you
If you like
No you sit in the middle
I'm sitting in the middle.
Who says you were driving?
I am driving.
I'll get in the back then.