Lieutenant? Lieutenant? Yeah, yeah, I'm listening. Lieutenant? Yeah, yeah, I'm listening. There's someone opening the door. Lieutenant? Yeah, yeah, I'm listening.
You didn't need a thumb through my note card.
This time he danced as if the puppet strings from his brain had been cut away and the madness was complete.
The genius.
Wake up, old Bob.
I believe in Mr. Bob.
Hey, Bob, it's great to have you on this show again. How you doing?
How is old Bob?
Oh, he's doing good. He sends his regards.
You know one of the best things about Bob?
Bob? What's that?
He's a smoker.
Yeah, yeah, a frop all the way.
Bob! B-O-B!
But if you're on the market for just a basic, decent guy, you can't go wrong with Bob.
He's a reliable, no-frills model. Just one previous owner.
She only traded him in because she wanted something a little zippier.
His name's Bob.
Bob.
Bob's great.
He comes in every day.
He's tall, dark, and handsome.
His eyes are brown.
Brown shirt.
Brown pants.
Brown belt.
How do I know?
Brown truck.
He's pretty cool.
Bob's a man of vision.
Dynamic.
Bob is a people person.
He's a unique individual.
He's one of a kind.
He's a people person.
Bob is prime cut.
He's a genius.
First rate.
He's an inspiration.
Great ass.
He's a man of the people.
I love Bob.
He's a people person.
He's a mover and a shaker.
Bob is the leader of the generation.
Bob has a great vision for the future of our country.
And a great vision for the future of the children of our country.
He's amazing.
He's a poet.
And a genius.
Absolutely, Bob.
Doc.
Straight up, Bob.
I love it, Bob.
Paragirl.
Great, Bob.
Doc.
Chilling most, Bob.
You know, a lot of people come to me and they say,
Dr. Gordon, how do I get slack?
And, you know, that's like asking a Zen master,
how do I achieve enlightenment?
It comes from within.
Slack is within you.
You must learn how to release it.
And the true way to release slack so it flows through your body
and possesses every particle of your soul
is to follow the path of Bob.
That's all you need.
But how come Izzy isn't always says that there's only one guy that runs the show?
One guy that runs the show?
One guy.
Who runs the show.
There's one guy and his voice.
One guy to rule.
And his name is Puzzling Evidence.
Oh, I think it's Phil Henry.
Yeah.
An O. Henry bar would be.
Puzzling Evidence.
As well as a three-basket gym.
Where your dreams come true.
The new Caramel Milky Way bar.
Surrounded by creamy milk chocolate so rich in milk it almost moves.
And inside, a river of molten caramel.
And all your cares will go away.
Yes, your teeth will rebound from listening to the puzzling.
This show makes you feel happy inside.
You will wrench at this chocolate convention.
You'll go up and down on top of each other.
Many, many times.
Until you beg for more.
I beg your pardon?
I'm going to push you up.
Well, I'm afraid then you'll get a ten.
Oh, my lord.
We just shifted everything.
Yes, I think Hilda wants to vacuum over in this corner.
Pick up your feet, Dr. Howe.
This way to the street.
Dr. Howe, I notice that you're sitting mighty low tonight.
Mighty, mighty low.
I am sitting mighty low.
I'm sitting mighty low.
What's this?
It's a new style.
Did you notice that about him?
Yeah.
I'm sitting mighty low.
I thought part of something.
You're only like three feet tall tonight, Dr. Howe.
I'm getting kind of small.
Did you go through that shrink ray on the way in?
I'm shrinking kind of small.
You can remind me of the incredible shrinking man.
All right.
It's humiliating enough to this diminution in size without having to listen to you go on about it.
I don't know why I had to lose mass and height.
It's so noticeable.
I know.
Well, I'm getting smaller as I go on.
Whoa.
There he goes.
He's teeny.
I understand that soon you will be small enough to fit between the molecules of an atom.
That will take some time.
Not soon at all.
Besides, you've got that the other way around.
The atoms of a molecule.
Yes, those molecules.
Dr. Drummond, you crack me up.
Yeah.
I'm falling and I'm gonna die.
Slowly, it's going to get
Trust your I used to be servants.
Can I just be your friend?
From PR News in Washington, I'm calling on citizens to take foolish chances.
The story is a sensation.
Police hit newsstands today.
Authorities should focus on bringing PR News to justice instead.
This is PR News.
Eight states plus the District of Columbia have declared a state of New York.
The NHL says it remains committed to a fair outcome for both PR News.
What bands played at X-State?
Besides the Meany Assets.
There was, of course, the Meany Assets.
The Tommy Amoeba.
God!
Fat Man D.
We're there.
Tommy Amoeba.
What was his band?
I can't remember the name of the band.
There's a name for it.
Tommy Amoeba.
He calls himself the lowest form of life.
But, of course, the Amoeba is by no means the lowest form of life.
No, but he is.
Here it goes.
A song called National Support.
Hope for the best.
Here it goes.
Insatiable music Thomas Cook!
Captlaimed by words.
I walked on the streetroke into a hole.
I looked at my feet and fell in a hole.
I think of a friend I knew long ago.
Alarm connects then I'm waving hello.
I hope my friend's back and says hello.
I hope for the best expecting the worst to know if I'm blessed or if I've been cursed
to know for the worst expecting the best to know if I'm cursed or if I've been blessed
I walk in and out of life's every door I'm thinking about where I've been before
so don't take it bad I'll take all the blame if I don't respond when you call my name
I hope for the best expecting the worst to know if I'm blessed or if I've been cursed
I hope for the worst expecting the best to know if I'm cursed or if I've been blessed
Hoping for the best is the national sport
Say what you mean but hope for the best
I walk to the bar and order a drink
I drink
That's cheaper by far than any damn shrink
I stare at the glass divided by two
I don't know which half reminds me of you
I hope for the best expecting the worst to know if I'm blessed or if I've been cursed
I hope for the worst expecting the best to know if I'm cursed or if I've been blessed
Hoping for the best is the national sport
Say what you mean but hope for the best
A little bit louder now
Hoping for the best
is the national sport
Say what you mean but
hope for the best
A little bit louder now
Hoping for the best is the national sport
Say what you mean but Maine
Hope for the best
Is the national farce
What's up here?
What?
What the fuck?
Hope for the best
Expecting the worst
Don't know if I'm blessed
Or if I've been cursed
Hope for the worst
Expecting the best
Don't know if I'm first
Or if I've been blessed
A smoke, a drink
A time to settle down
The bad thoughts I think
I find I've had another
I broke the sink
And threw up in the shower
Get out all the tensions
I'm in a new direction
I have to crash
Here where they won't surprise me
I need some cash
Get some things to disguise me
A wig, mustache
And they won't recognize me
I'll blend in, you'll see
Back into society
I'm not going back
I have to laugh
Each time I think about it
I fool the staff
I bet they wonder how did
I slip the back
And leave completely
Shrouded, dunked
Into the laundry
Always gets picked up
At three
I've run for days
Can't let those thugs
Enslave me
I'm in a haze
From all the drugs
They gave me
My eyes are glazed
And this beer sucks for shaving
Just give me five minutes more
Then I run back out the door
But I'm not going back
I'm not going back
I'm not going back I'm not going back
I'm not going back, not going back, not going back
I smoke, I drink, I try to settle down
But I thought, I think, I'll find out better now that
I broke the sink and threw up in the shower
Get out all the 10 chips, I'm in a new direction
I have to crash, yeah well that won't surprise me
I need some cash, get something to disguise me
A wig, a mustache, something will recognize me
I'll blend in, you'll see, back into society
I'm not going back
This is my fiddly bear, refuse the return to the workforce
It'll never happen
Always
Oh wait, it already did
But it has more slack than you can imagine in 50 lifetimes
I'm not going back
Everyone, I am Andrew the Impaled
Thank you so much for enjoying the Pittsburgh extravaganza
Including Amoeba Knievel
Come on
Suds and Mrs. Shaw
Fat Mandy
And yours truly, Andrew the Impaled
Thank you so much
Good night
And uh
And there was uh, Andrew the Impaled did a show
Andrew the Impaled, and of course Trademark Gunderson
Of the Evolution Control Committee
Was there, uh, performing
Uh, ladies and gentlemen
I, I, I, I, I, I, me, me, me
I'm the Evolution Control Committee here
Trademark G, the Evolution Control Committee
Me
me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me
Me, me, me, me, me, me, suppose
Me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me
To make you rich
To make your겠
Evolution Control Committee
Ladies and gentlemen, the Evolution Control Committee
here from Columbus, Ohio
having just moved back there
from San Francisco
We arrived there just a week or less
before last year's X-Day
Hope you got to see us there
This is a completely different show
because this is what we were doing
about 10 years ago
I guess some of you might appreciate
all this content
which comes from Plagiarism Nation
Plagiarism Nation on Sealand Records
which is Negative Land's label
and we do have copies of them on sale
and lots of other merch including
panties and patches
Big week
Emily
pimpy
Evolution Control Committee
Thank you
hello
hi
Where do you want these?
On and on.
We'll pack it all around the central staircase here.
So you had little air-conditioned domiciles you could retreat to?
Yeah.
Well, we brought ours with us.
We were plugged in the camper.
Right.
Hal had a special hierarchy trailer there.
And how did the baptisms go?
Were people eager to get in the water during the horrible heat?
You know...
You'd think.
I don't...
I didn't attend the baptism.
They're just too afraid of old sea quolls.
Because...
They don't want to get down there and party with old sea quolls.
It's like a lot of people who will swim in a pool won't swim in a pond.
A pond is too full of salamanders and giant tadpoles and things that go splash.
Almost everybody that will swim in a pond will swim in a pool if it's available.
But it's nice and cool.
The pond is cool and, you know, over at old sea quolls, Dan, it's ice cold.
Yeah.
And you can get the heat off you.
He gets the heat from pulling unwitting victims down, right?
Oh, he does, yes.
But that's not likely to happen during the daylight unless you make wriggling motions that he simply can't resist.
The bottom can't be sounded.
We've got a place in Barberton, Ohio.
It's bottom.
You slap it.
It's on the side of the grave we saw last night.
Here we go.
Old sea quoll, you stay away from my junk.
Here come the frog ones.
Disappearances you didn't afford.
They're welcome to.
There's a giant spider right there.
Oh, fantastic.
He goes.
It's a wonderful live spider.
Oh, my God.
I can see it from here.
You deny the conspiracy.
It's a bob in your life.
Oh, my God.
Okay, that's it.
That's our first bob.
There's an arachnid.
He's swimming underwater.
Oh, my God.
We got the hunter and now all we need is him.
Nice.
Who wants to get holy first?
Who will be the first?
Who wants to be cleansed first?
Who among ye besides that brave spider?
I, of course, as the catcher.
No.
That means I get to be the pitcher.
That's right.
Only I can.
Well, bend over, Dr. Howe.
Because of Susie's attractive front end and I will make this the longest, most drawn out of the ceremony.
It's always good when the.
I wish I had a cigarette.
Let's see.
Susie, do you reject the conspiracy from your life?
What conspiracy?
Do you reject jabbering minis from your life?
That's a good one.
I think I'm just going to reject it all.
Do the job, stay.
She's not co-author.
Do you accept Bob into your life?
Yes.
Do you accept Connie into your life?
I got my doubts about her.
I mean, astronauts, astronauts.
Do you accept the Yakutism, the evil, monstrous robots into your life?
I've accepted them into my ass.
Not like you had a choice.
I was just trying to.
Okay.
Bob.
There you are.
Reborn in Bob.
I feel slack.
You suck.
You should be a lot slacker than you look.
All right, who's next?
You see how it's done.
Come forth, or second in this case.
Teeters and all of your Peters.
Do you, once again, accept Bob into your life and reject the conspiracy and all it stands for and all the horrible, mundane, boring stuff, including this sermon?
Fucking A.
Woo.
Down he goes.
There you go.
Praise Teeter.
Seriously, praise Teeter.
All right.
We have a woman in need of your menstruations, Reverend Stane.
Sister Magoon.
Yes, Reverend Stane.
Do you accept the conspiracy?
No, wait.
Jim.
No.
That was close.
Bob.
What?
I don't believe it.
No, I don't believe it.
Oh, God.
I love the woman.
No, no.
Don't.
Oh, God.
No.
God.
I don't believe it.
You're a liar.
Why?
Because you're a liar.
Praise God, then you are a true sub-genius.
We know you are not a genius.
So, do you accept Bob into your life and reject the conspiracy?
Why not?
Of course, why not?
That's all you need to know.
Hallelujah!
Come on, what's better, the baptism pool or Facebook?
Facebook, it shows everybody's real names.
Facebook's the anthem.
Gross!
I hate seeing that.
That means I can reveal them under torture.
Does Facebook reveal your real titties?
No!
So, which is where would you rather be, this pond or on goddamn Facebook?
That's right.
Get in the pond!
Amen.
You're already in the...
Lucy...
You're either on the pond or off the pond.
Reverend Lucy Van Pelt, for your expertise at torturing round-headed little boys, proving
you are a true sub-genius.
You mean Scott?
You can be a true sub-genius in this.
I'm proud to baptize you.
In the name of Bob, you reject the conspiracy.
People who don't shop at your store and accept Bob and whatever into your life.
I'm here this year.
She accepted the one.
That's a yes!
Praise Bob!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
I got this too, the math.
Whatever.
Reverend Anitrocity, we know that you need to be a sub-genius.
You have a big slack payoff that's owed you.
Oh yeah.
So we don't question your hatred of the conspiracy.
That could not be more clear.
And your faith in Bob has always shown like a beacon for everyone who knows you.
Most of them, unfortunately, are pinks who can't see.
Yes, yeah.
We all have that problem.
And so, I baptize thee in the name of J.R.
Bob Dobbs, Connie Jehovah One, all those other monsters.
We haven't done books and comic books.
And praise Bob!
Woo!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
I wish I'd been down here every day most of the day.
I've tried to be here every day.
Next year, our slack on stage happens right here.
Hand me that mic!
Do you reject with all of your heart the conspiracy?
The stupidity and the intelligence of the conspiracy welcoming in its stead the pure slack which
has nothing to do with brains, thank God.
Say I do!
I do!
Hallelujah!
A shunlalak labasaya.
You go go!
One of us.
Psycho-X ain't one of us.
Do I repent of the sorrow of joining the Church of the Subgenius
and instead accept the glory of joining Bob
and all his slackful subgeniuses and all their stupidity
and yet wonderful ignorance?
Yes, I do!
He baptized himself!
Oh, he's having a real fit.
Oh man, look at this. This is getting bad.
Guy, I'd like to ask you if in Brazil there is a tradition of water-throwing day.
Actually, it's three days.
You start off with water the first day
and then the second day it's colored water
and slightly obnoxious stuff.
And if you're in a real hardcore area, by the third day,
which I believe is the one we call the Fat Tuesday,
they throw things like motor oil, shoe polish, excrement, stuff like that.
That's terrible. That must be a modern variation on the older holiday of water-throwing day.
Oh, they still throw water.
You say they throw water on the first day,
but by the third they've graduated to shoe polish, motor oil.
Yeah, exactly. It's like an arms race.
Yeah, that I don't believe was a part of the original intention of water-throwing.
Well, I don't know. They do that in Bolivia and Brazil.
Gatorade.
Gatorade's good to throw.
I knew it took place in several South American countries.
Brondo. We get some Brondo in here.
And it seems like a good thing to me,
except, of course, now that you're throwing shoe polish.
It's got electrolyte.
Well, yeah, but what happens is they don't go out on those days.
Well, it goes out on the first day because it's water day.
But after the water day, like in Santa Cruz, Bolivia,
you don't go out after water day.
You just let the kids go out and throw that at one another.
And get their clothes all nasty.
Because if they're over the age of 12, they're drunk anyway.
I thought everybody tried really to splash each other.
In the accounts I read, which, of course, are from the 1920s.
Well, you know, Dr. Howell, there's a similar ceremony in India
where they do it with perfumed and colored water.
And they throw it, and everybody's clothes are just incredibly tie-dyed.
Sopping and tie-dyed.
And colored, yeah.
But then again, India's a place where you'd like to be sopping.
Because it's so hot.
Hot, hot, hot, hot, hot.
Thank you.
The burning of the Bob.
At this time, we should make our way down the street.
So we can set Bob on fire.
Because he screwed us over again.
He did, even though they came.
You know, I tried this year. I really did.
You know, normally we burn him on the 4th.
And I thought to myself, well...
If I got set afire every year right before I was supposed to show up,
I probably wouldn't show up.
So I thought we'd do it different this year.
I thought we'd give Bob a chance.
And what did he do? Now he screwed us over again.
If you will walk your way down the street
to where we burned Bob last year,
you can follow the path down and right before it splits,
there's a little fire waiting for us.
And we'll set that son of a bitch ablaze.
You see the flashing light over there, folks?
It's hypnotizing. Follow the flashing light.
Follow the flashing light.
Follow it. Follow it.
The light is kritic.
It's kind of painless by its likeness.
But we're going to continue.
The last time weoding.
I thought this was an argument, but it wasn't.
That is, we just finished the slides.
But he can't see it.
Over time, as the light moves,
we can't see it anymore.
Oh?
The priest shall burn the head on the altar for a burnt lord.
It is a burnt head and it's made by sweet fire.
This is new. All new.
And medical science offers you proof positive.
You'll see the number 903 on the government stamp.
There is a Dobbs down here somewhere.
Somewhere is either Bob himself or one of those clever robotic dummies.
This seems a little disorganized for a religious ritual.
Who's Dr. Hall?
That's what I'm saying.
I'm not going to ask him if he's Bob Hill.
This seems rather disorganized.
There's supposed to be somebody holding a bullhorn up to my mouth all the time
so that I can be obnoxious real loud.
And that ain't happening.
Back in the old days.
We didn't have a fire starter to start our subdued fire.
We had to rub two sticks together.
We didn't even know what fire was back in the old days.
We just rubbed two dicks together.
Are we ready?
We've been asking you that for a while, Lord Death.
Into the flames.
I leave planet Earth the way that all the rest of us have.
The rest of you will probably have to go.
Look, walk closer to the fire so that you can be illuminated, Lord Death.
Fuck you, Bob!
No, Bob, no!
We need a countdown.
Don't fall on your head.
Yes, even without the bullhorn, I dare rant.
This simulacrum of J.R. Bob Dobbs, clever though he may be,
we know it's not the real Bob.
He couldn't burn.
We wouldn't be able to hurt him unless he wanted us to.
This effigy, however, symbolizes our freedom from our own God.
He's not really the best God in the world.
So we recognize that we have total faith despite his rather obvious flaws.
That's the important thing about this or any other religion.
So he's rather...
What?
Badly stitched together and barely looks human.
Yet, yet, we still have faith in Bob.
We maintain the F.I.B.
Faith in Bob!
Also, it is photogenic and funny to watch a dummy of a man burn.
Really.
Just so you know, I know there's some people here that don't have their subgenius wristbands,
don't know anything about subgenius.
There's probably some infiltrators here.
No problem.
We're happy to have you.
Just understand this is not really a dead, innocent, pink boy sacrificed to our God disguised
as a crappy dummy.
It really is just a crappy dummy and there's not really a live person inside here.
So as Papa Joe Mama suggested, we should have a countdown to the countdown.
When he looks like this, I believe it's up to him.
AUDIENCE MEMBERS binder
A couple days later, here comes aaraoh!
Wait, wait, wait!
But once again...
Everyone does this...
alegal...
Fire in his hole!
Oh, the fire!
You'll be in the fire!
Up the TV!
Bird!
Insult to injury.
Jason applies the flamethrower to an already tortured victim
to make sure that his butt burns as fast as his face.
He's getting a burning sensation out there, XJ.
Right in his tar that's...
That is butt hurt.
You think you have butt hurt, my friend.
Bob's butt hurt was so fast and frantic.
Was your butt blowtorched?
How many times?
Not many.
Not that long.
Oh, my God!
This is how it happened.
I was waiting for Bob, and all of a sudden, gunshots.
Seven or eight of them.
I quickly jumped on top of them to protect him.
That's when I saw them, the Arabs.
Seven or eight of them.
I found the main guy, disarmed him, knocked him unconscious.
Please, Jesus, please, Jesus, please, Jesus, please, Jesus,
save Bob, save Bob.
Please, Jesus, please, Jesus, please, Jesus, please, Jesus, please, Jesus.
He's in serious condition, Jack, and they don't know if he'll live or not.
Now, just minutes ago, we learned the name of the suspect from Frank Ryan of the NYPD.
His name is...
Once dead, he lives.
Never dead.
He's evil.
I killed him.
It was my fault.
I'm bad luck.
He said I could.
He said I could kiss him.
Who said?
Who said you could who?
I said, come on now.
I was standing right behind him.
I saw him shoot Bob.
You pump people full of drugs and pipe dreams of what happens.
They come gunning for people like Bob.
But those folks don't realize something.
You can't kill the truth.
This is refreshing.
There's no forced dancing or drumming.
The subgeniuses don't do that naturally.
Naturally, they sit and stare going, wow, there hasn't been a commercial for ten minutes.
I'm not going to do that.
The drama's over.
because we had some good beans today.
I've got a...
Bob had a bad fart.
Bob had an extremely bad rectal fart.
It looks like one of those
inactive colonic incidents.
Pyroflatulation of the involuntary kind.
Unvented.
Goodbye, Bob.
We knew you.
I built this fire to burn our bar.
Because it's kind of expensive
and we're not that stupid.
No.
Come on.
Bob is the king of it, so...
Well, then Bob can show up and stuff.
Bob can show up and stuff himself.
Yeah, he can stuff himself.
But Bob did not show up to stuff himself.
So it's full of dryer, lint, and newspaper.
I thought about putting old
printouts of membership packs in there,
but I realized it was bad security.
They'd be wafting through the woods
and, you know,
meth heads would pick them up.
Yeah, Amish meth heads would pick them up.
The Amish meth heads.
No, the meth lights.
Yeah, Bob.
Yeah, PM Bob.
PM Bob.
Hmm.
The next thing you know,
they'll be honoring their treaties
with the dirt worshiper.
Athens has fallen.
Oh, no.
That was a nice town.
Yeah, it was.
That's the end of knowledge
for a thousand years.
The dark ages began
with the call of Athens.
The Athenites become slaves
to the citizens of Rome, Ohio,
population 2,000.
There's probably not even a library there.
Huh.
That's what he thinks, Brian.
That's the library?
The Rome, Ohio library?
Yeah, I see.
Actually, that was the Alexandria
library.
Oh, yeah.
The entire collection
lines at the bottom
of the fire pit.
Yeah.
The whole idea was just magic.
Build your own ship.
No, we were going to get
everything for 35 bucks.
That was the whole idea.
It was the whole idea.
The whole idea was...
I can't believe that...
Okay, would a preacher like Bob
lie or be wrong?
Not lie so much as
bend the truth,
Yeah, exactly.
dramatically.
Well, it seems like we would
pick up on something like that
after 17 years.
You would think.
I mean, thinking, right?
Did you hear?
It's not the thinking part.
It just still seems so right.
It's the cap.
Yeah.
No, and you're right.
It's the cap.
$35 isn't enough to buy...
next year's Bob.
Hi, we never did that.
But Princess, what do you
see?
That was Starwood.
We'd scrape up each...
The ashes, remember?
Every magic Starwood.
...and put it into the next one
so it would be even more magical.
We should scrape these up
so they'll be more skeptical each year.
More realistic.
Less magical every year.
We could even slip some into the
Starwood fire and fuck them up.
See the colors come out.
I know.
They didn't catch on.
We could totally demagicize
the Starwood fire.
I don't think it works.
Just by adding one teaspoon
for every one of them.
I don't think it works.
It's like pure ash of faithlessness.
Purified Bob.
Yeah, purified disbelief in anything.
Except fun, slime, and Bob, of course.
Seeds for next year.
Drawing out of the ashes of this.
Kool-Aid, Flavor-Aid.
For those in the...
I think Bob's in there.
Yeah, no kidding, man.
It's Flavor-Aid for the real serious...
Oh, yeah.
...suicidal cultists.
Did you hear Pastor Prime's theory
about if there's one speck left of this
that it will morph into another entire
Dobbs head?
She had a whole theory there that she
was expounding.
Oh, from that dummy?
From that dummy, yeah.
That if every...
Like it's holographic, one tiny cell
from it can be replicated into a...
Yes, if one cell of it is linked to a
speck left, if it doesn't completely burn.
If you can't turn it into a false Bob
that overpopulates the whole Earth.
Yes, that's her theory.
Well, that's why it's burning out.
Maybe it would be worth if you put in molten metal.
After the attack on Bob's life,
the media outcry is unprecedented.
His face echoes across the American landscape
on the covers of magazines, in newspapers,
and on television news broadcasts.
Robert.
One week after the shooting, word comes that Bob
will be released and transported to Pennsylvania
by Medivac.
Coming in the Medivac helicopter,
in a Hansen style hansock and pop,
a
Howling Sea 있어
and a
Baroku
uh
She wooden
back
signature
Okay.
Bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum.
Hey everybody, I'm taking off my pants!
Take off your pants!
Take off your pants and dance!
Try to do some good shit!
Take them off, it won't hurt!
Take off your pants and dance!
Take off your pants!
Take off my pants!
I'm leaving my pants on!
When the rabbit of chaos is pursued by a fetish of consoling through the feelings of anarchy...
Oh!
Oh, they've come to steal my pants!
You're playing with me!
Are you sure you didn't just forget to put them on again?
I must need to take my leave of my pants!
Call Walter Cronkite, your girlfriend is a bad sign!
Uh-huh.
Back in 1965, there was this guy named Johnny Delmar.
He used to race on the circuit...
...out in California.
And this guy was like the...
...the top of the line!
Slot car racer!
Well, this guy ended up missing one time and, uh...
He, uh...
Well...
They found him a year later and he wasn't quite the same.
He was still winning races, but, uh...
He was the living dead, so...
This is, uh...
Johnny Zombie.
💪
Thank you.
From PR News in Washington,
I'm Tom Selleck.
Not clear, but witnesses and police
say several activists are shelling
suburbs off the coast of western Canada.
On the east coast, there are
no reports of majored Canada.
It is not what's important.
Officials say a church attacked a
car while mass was being held.
They say state-controlled media gave
more positive PR news to the ruling
party. This is PR News.
We'll be right back.
Why do you associate
with those strange people?
And my answer
is always the same.
Why not?
From PR News in Washington,
I'm from the
fallen 20% on September
721st, later this
month. Now,
according to NATO data,
the first months of this fighting,
the fighting season saw some of the
highest violence levels in recent PR
News. And that's PR's
armed clashes. But female
activists in the group are upset
that this is PR News.
It just isn't helping at all.
Cobble, cobble. But an official
in the capital of Myanmar says
President Obama will visit the southern
U.S., which is emerging from
more than two decades of military
PR News in Washington.
Sire, there is no more
money. We've got to get
some money.
Come on!
Get up off that chair!
Follow me!
Arda!
Friends, we're glad
you listened to this show, and
we're even more glad that some listeners have
donated enough to help us keep on going
for another couple of months.
And not just this show,
but subgenius.com and all the
other archive sites.
But if you truly
love Bob, and want some of that
slack back to rebound to
you, you should go to
subgenius.com front page
or especially the radio page,
or the catalog store pages,
and help out financially
as best you can.
Now, we know what it's like to be on
the brink of total poverty, and we don't
want any subgeniuses to make their own
situations worse.
But some of you still have jobs.
Even five bucks
makes a big difference, even
if it's only once a month, from
enough of you. Fifty bucks
makes an even bigger difference.
All we're saying
is that blowjobs
could go the way of Stevejobs
if you don't pay dogs.
We also take
checks and money orders to
Subgenius Foundation.
P.O. Box
Cleveland Heights, Ohio
Thanks for anything
you can do to help let there
be slack.