Every student of human behavior knows that women like masculine things.
The rough caress of a tweed shoulder against a soft cheek,
the gleam of fine polished leather,
the look of a pipe in a man's mouth.
However, if you delve a little deeper into feminine psychology,
you will find that the appeal of that pipe sometimes drops way down
when its smoke meets dainty feminine nostrils.
What can you do about it?
That's easy.
The Self-Genius Power of Swag.
Its fragrance, its grand aged in the wood aroma,
will complete your pipe appeal with the lady you wish to impress.
And that wonderful flavor too.
Rich, full-bodied, yet mild.
And what a bargain.
Bush is viral in nature.
This bush, viral in nature.
Another bush.
Getting sick, getting sick system.
The system is causing a stomach bar system.
The system is causing tension, tension, tension, tension, bush bar.
The disaster status quo.
We are, we want to, we are committed.
We believe we have the ability.
We believe we're committed to work on it.
And we'll continue to do that.
That we can, and I say again, let's have President Bush.
Eating small children and harming small animals.
Oh, he's back from the dead.
That's right.
His grinning skull floats ever in front of your eyes.
And Jesus brought him back.
And he's lusting for the flesh of the living.
And these things are coming and coming.
They need to be replaced.
That is exactly what we must do.
I tried to explain, sir.
This is a true story, a true story.
And I'm sorry, that anything can be repaired.
But God forbid, you know what I mean?
That is not a best thing in life, do as he says.
Grass is not killed.
It was autes, me.
Not because I killed them.
Yeah, well.
We're allados, there you go.
The way he did it, there you go, yes, there you go.
Again, it does happen.
Again, as you heard.
Did God tell us?
for that. That was San Andreas' fault.
That shows the endless connection, how one
crime succeeds another, for he says the land
is full of bloody
crimes and the city is full of
violence. Therefore, God
says, I will bring the basis,
the worst, of heathen
Gentile people, and
they are going to conquer you and
drive you out and move into your
houses and your holy places will be
defiled. Destruction comes, God
says.
Oh, good God, we're
doomed. No!
We're out of
Jonah! One could go on and on
with reports of this nature. Week after week
we get letters to our office and it'll
say, Brother Smith, it saved my
life. You don't realize where I was
headed. A farmer awakened one morning
and the clock struck one,
two, three, seven,
twelve, thirteen,
fourteen. His wife said, Honey, wake
up. He said, What time is it? She said, I don't know.
But it's later than it's
ever been before.
World leaders are indeed
pessimistic. They should be.
I guess you can pull the ballad of Bob
Dobbs' music down in the background. Everybody
here has seen that on
YouTube by now, I hope.
And you can creep the music back.
Back up when you need to because that
creeps everybody up or out
or something. Anyway, friends,
thanks. That was a wonderful moment of noise.
I want to do it again, friends. If we can
get in the mood for this
religious, finally
something, you know, religious and
superstitious out here at Starwood.
If you could open your heart,
close your mind, lock
it up, unzip your lips
and bend over and pull out your wallet
and let's have that moment of noise,
friends. Praise Bob! Praise
Bob! Praise God damn
Bob!
Don't hurt yourself.
That takes practice.
Oh, and to do things, this is
a real traditional
style one, friends. This is a U.S.
dollar bill, which I'm going to
illegally burn right now.
And it's not
because we don't love money.
It's to prove to the aliens that
they're still, when they smell the smoke
from this burning U.S. dollar,
they'll know that they're still
something down here on Earth worth saving.
Actually,
probably still spend that last
50 cents. You notice
I didn't use a 20. We're
religious, but we're not that
nutty.
And
for those of you who don't know a
damn thing about the church of the subgenius,
there's only three things you need to
understand about it. That's
Bob, the face that you will never
be able to etch out of your mind again.
Slack, which
is what you want and
probably already have,
but you may not know it yet.
And the conspiracy,
which is everything that takes away
your slack. And
I guess I can just shut up
there, because those who know don't say
and those who say don't know, and
here, bye.
That's really the way
we should do it. The subgenius thing
is best encountered
when you find one of those little muddy
pamphlets that we have over on the
sales table in a gutter.
When you're in the gutter,
and you're on your last
rope, you're like, you know,
and you find that little picture
of Bob, and you go,
here is an answer. Actually,
Bob is not the answer,
but neither is anything
else. And that is
the point of the church of the subgenius.
You have to, sure, you've got to dig
into your wallet to buy
the answers that Bob
provides, but we don't really,
expect them to last very long.
That's why Bob is what we call
a short-duration personal
savior, or in the Tibetan
Shordirper Sav.
This is a
world of planned obsolescence,
and like, you know,
if you tell a joke too many times,
it loses its power.
So you may have to move on to, I don't
know, sure, the flying spaghetti
monster, or Scientology,
or Jesus, or whatnot.
We don't really care.
We don't care where you go after
you spend that 30 bucks.
But it's not like we're just
after your money.
We also want your belief.
And there's lots of belief
here at Starwood.
Although, as Bob said,
believe me out of it.
We don't want to get into arguments
with people about which is the one
true religion, because we already know.
Oh, and there's one rule,
for those who don't know anything
about religion, and that is,
we have a lot of laws about the church of the subgenius.
We have zillions of laws, and thou shalt's
and shalt not's, but those are just for fun.
There is one that is real,
and that you can really live your life by,
and I think some of my fellow subgeniuses
know what that rule is.
It is, friends, fuck them if they can't take a joke!
Fuck them if they can't take a joke!
Are there any children here?
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to...
The other way you can say it is,
if they can't not take a joke,
then let them mount up upon themselves.
That's the polite Irish Celtic way of saying it.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we're about to begin the portion of the program
called the Ask Dr. Howell Show.
I,
Dr. Howell and Howell,
will now, during this next period,
answer any questions
which you, the audience,
have to pose.
These questions, and my answers,
will be made a part of
the recording and later podcast
of this broadcast.
And finally,
added to the ultimate
aditum of subgenius
storage
in the master computer
known as MWOM.
Ladies and gentlemen,
although I may
perform this
tawdry nightclub act
on a weekly basis in my
own home town,
what I do here
has a more
theologically defined purpose.
To come
closer and closer
to the true and perfect knowledge
of J.R. Bob Dobbs.
And of course,
Dobbsian
philosophy is not necessarily
something that one has to
learn like some college course.
One learns
from Dobbs in a visceral way.
Kind of like being
kicked in the stomach.
For all you
male subgenius fans.
So, while we're
getting ready, I'd like to
describe how this works.
You simply write down on the slips
that we've provided, whatever
question is unburdened
or needs to be
unburdened.
Something you might have
wondered about for a while.
Now, questions of
quantity and quiddity
have limited interpretations
and answers. Far
better to ask
something with a philosophical
dimension. Well, we
already have a question and so
I will answer this first
question while the rest of you are filling out your slips.
Are we ready, Reverend
Stang? Yes, yes.
Thank you for... Should I present
the question? Yes.
I'm ready. The first question.
Why didn't this goddamn
segment start at 1pm
as scheduled?
A most interesting and pertinent
question. Because it
implies that there's
something a little hinky in subgenius
land. A little wonky.
A little off about
our scheduling service
and systematics. Well,
if this were so,
let us indulge in
hypothetical speculation,
would it necessarily be a bad thing?
Are we out here
punching anyone's time
clock, even Bob's?
Or are we relaxing
in the balm
and benign benison of
slack? I think you know
the answer of those two choices.
But there is another answer to that question I could
give. And that is, we did
begin at 1. We were
right here. We started
but there was no one present.
Nonetheless, we
soldiered on. And
so, I must say
to the questioner, where were you?
Not where were we.
Actually, I might also add that if
you look at the schedule, it says hour
of slack started at 1,
and that Ask Dr. Howell starts at
3, which is in
two more minutes. Yes, we're actually
jumping the gun and providing
two extra minutes of Ask Dr. Howell
as a special subgenius
radio premium.
Ah,
yes, yes, yes. And so we have
new questions coming in.
This question from
the anonymous user.
So, how many
subgeniuses does it take
to change a mini
disc? You know,
let me preface this one
by saying, there's something
in my nature which
bristles and bridles at
any sentence which begins
with the word, so.
You know, it seems
that something is about to be presented to one
in less than a friendly conversational
fashion.
It is as if
one is accused,
without having said anything, of having
previously submitted
an untenable proposition which
needs to be rudely
challenged, without even
the slightest kindness of
polite discourse. However,
this is perhaps only one
of my own tropes.
Anyway, the question was,
so,
what?
So, how many subgeniuses does it take
to change a mini disc?
It takes, of course,
the master subgenius
to change the master
disc. We are dealing here
with the matrix upon which the
impressions are recorded.
Any subgenius may diddle around
with any little dubious diddly
squat disc, but the master disc
is, of course, the disc which records
these sacred
prononcementos,
and are stored in the master
computer, there to
abide until the end of time.
It also
helps for there to be at least one
subgenius who knows
where the other mini discs
are. And that requires
a level of interest that we have never
yet encountered in our
many years of history.
But, of course, we are hopeful.
That the sunrise will
someday illuminate
those dark and shadowy realms.
Oh, I might add that the
another thing that's almost as
annoying as starting a question with
so, is starting it with
um.
That is tentative. And um is in fact
much worse. So is impudent
and um, as you say, is
so tentative that it is far
worse, because it implies a
lack of spirit. And one knows
that what one will
probably be confronted with
that follows the um, is
a triacally
wandering, wistful,
warbling piece of
insupportable
trivia. But, perhaps not
in this case. Let's see. Well, let's move on
to a more elevated question.
What is
the nature of nature
itself?
Well, that's a fine
question. It's good that we
get them like that.
Yes, what is the nature of
nature? Nature might
be described as
physics or the state of
the universe. Most of us think of
nature as the subset of the universe
involving growing
things and life.
Life and life's effluents.
Cloud at once and shower.
Unfortunately, any
rational picture of the universe
shows a gigantic
canvas splashed
with nothing.
There's nothing there.
Nothing, nothing,
nothing, nothing at all.
Only a few
atoms here and there.
Or maybe a few galaxies.
However, actually
there are infinite number of galaxies
but still
mostly what
you have there is nothing.
And then what is happening
with this little bit of matter?
It is becoming
disordered. And yet,
how did it get there in the first place?
Within matter,
there is a tendency to organize.
And matter, especially
in our neck of the woods,
in our system, in the Sagittarian
arm of the Milky Way
galaxy, has that curious propensity.
Even non-living matter
has a principle of self-organization
within it. Thus we see
crystalline forms emerging.
Complex molecules
even in the mineral realm.
Many of you may have seen on the internet
the discovery of the vast
underground crystals in the Mexican
cavern going on and on
down through layer upon
sub-layer of a knighted abyss.
Huge pillars and
have you seen that staying?
No. I can send you some
what is it, JPEGs?
What do you call them? Anyway.
Pictures. The pictures are there.
So let us then answer
this in the stereotypical
form of nature as representing the lush
planet Earth with
its oceans and sighing
winds, its rich soils
and squirming microorganisms
and of course the inhabitants
of the sea, land and air.
What is the nature
of that nature? Well here
the organization of matter
takes place at an
incredibly furious pace.
Far faster than the
stately growth of crystals
or the accumulation and accretion
of geological columns,
nature is a flying
fly-by-night operation.
Here today, gone tomorrow
or perhaps even
within an hour.
Some things like the damsel fly
exist for the various
brevity of time, but even
shorter than that the microorganisms
sport in their fluid
medium forming and
reforming. But it might
be added that the microorganisms
themselves know not
death in the sense that the
more complicated things do.
And indeed in the beginning
they had to wait for death,
that useful invention, to be
invented. I don't have time to go into
that here. So nature itself
continually evolves
and organizes.
I think we all agree upon
that. Now when you ask what is the nature
are you asking about a purpose?
Because I will tell you that too.
And in nature's embodiment
as that section of the universe
we will speak of the ultimate purpose
of the universe. And that
is this. If the universe may be
considered as an oblong body
something more than an
oblate spheroid,
its ultimate purpose
nature and result
of all this organization is that it
may extend a pseudopod
with an eyeball in it at the end
which it can turn back
to view itself.
Good lord
man, so that is the ultimate
fight and destiny.
Well, some say one thing, some say another thing.
But thanks for your question.
I almost did decide to not even
set the pulpit up here because
normally I work from
complicated notes so I don't forget
anything important. But I've realized lately
I've been serving Bob so damn long
I can't forget even if I
wanted to.
But the pulpit looks nice.
And so we went ahead
and assembled it. Plus I have a few
things I wanted to show off.
Friends, not just the
subgeniuses but all of us
recently made the weekly
world news, the world's only reliable
newspaper, Freaks,
Geeks, and Weirdos.
That's
headlong.
And it shows several of our
number. Here's a four-legged babe
and some kids with tentacles for arms
and a woman who's had her
third nostril replaced with a third
eye and a flying
hamburger. Isn't that nice?
They even snuck in, I swear,
you know, they photoshopped some of these
pictures. I don't know if you knew that.
But one of them,
my wife says this is not me,
but I swear they stuck my face
on this old, this is a man
in Israel who sweats
when a ghost is around.
And they show this guy
with a very sweaty shirt
rolling some dough and he looks
just like yours truly, Reverend Stank.
I was really proud of,
that's the second time we've made
weekly world news that way.
And I'm so happy to be here.
I was going to let others come up
and use these limited microphones.
That's right. We're going to invite you
to come right up here and testify
for Bob.
Reverend Bleepo Abernathy
happens to be here.
This is his first X Day,
but it's sure not his first
subgenius campout,
you might say.
He's been announcing
the Hour of Slack since before
he does the voice.
There's a phrase at the beginning
that says, it's
the subgenius
hour of slack.
Remember that old timey
radio voice, friends?
Well, we peeled
Reverend Bleepo Abernathy
off of the wallpaper and brought him in
this time.
You know the most important thing, I think,
about everything subgenius,
Reverend Stank, if I can be so bold,
is that
it appears to be
always something
that knows what it's doing.
Even when it has no idea what it's doing.
The direction of
subgenius rhetoric is
always directed directly
at a thought or vision
that may or may not be occurring
at any given time and or
not time.
Well, we just follow where they
take us. The wind almost took
us in Fultimus'
go-rilla away.
Yes, in fact, Reverend Slough...
I'm insulting...
This go-rilla is saying,
Now that you finally brought your wife to
X-Day, you no longer need to
come.
Finally, my
Princess Wee's been at X-Day
since 1999.
I'll be right with you.
Go stick your head in the fence
over there.
That's what she said.
It's impossible to look
at those pictures and not think
of, you know...
The bullies that picked on me
in elementary school. Actually,
I wasn't the kind that got picked on. I was the kind
that was invisible. I hid
well. Or I would make them laugh.
That always would
work for me, if I possibly could.
I thought that only worked in the movies.
It did until I was 13.
And then, you know, when you had that weird
shift of hormones and stuff.
Then it stopped
working at school and only worked when I was with
my weird Unitarian summer camp friends.
But...
That's a true
revelation there.
We don't need to hear about all the
childhood traumas that turned you into
a subgenius. For some of us,
all it is is being nearsighted and having to get glasses.
Then for
others, it's the urge to kill
and kill and kill and
kill and kill
and kill and kill
and kill!
Well, I'm not...
I personally don't understand where those people
are coming from. I might...
What attracted me to the church was the
promise of infinite riches
and sex and slack
and so forth. I think that's what most
of us are... That and the
thought of everyone else burning in
hell. In that respect, we're like any
other religious...
Can I ask you something that I think I've never asked you?
That is...
Where's the derivation of your
name?
Of your subgenius name?
Well, obviously, Stang is an
anglicized version. The original name is
Stankovich, but that was...
That's really
a made-up name, too. I'm
a direct descendant
of the Tsarina
Alexandra
and her illicit affair with the
mad monk Rasputin, thus making
me the lone
sole heir to the jewels of
the Russian throne.
People laugh and mock, and
I don't expect anyone
to believe me. A lot of kooks and nuts
saying that they're heirs to the...
crown jewels of
all the Russias, but what
can I say? If you study
Rasputin's history and look at me
real close, you'll see... That wasn't a real laugh. That was just a sound
effects laugh. Yeah, it was a sound effects
laugh. I've heard that one in
cartoons. I just quote them.
Yeah. I never laugh
in real life.
Well, speaking of cartoons, you know,
I look out upon this
vast audience, and what I see
are human
cartoons. That's what
we find among... The subgeniuses
have very little in common with each other.
As we say, all we have in common
is that we have nothing in common with the conspiracy
of the normal people, but
everybody's got this completely
different exaggeration about
them. And sometimes
it's a feature that everyone regards
as good, and sometimes it's a feature that
everyone regards as bad.
Alex over here, for instance.
So, you know,
you get all kinds. We
have to live with each other and tolerate
each other, except that
there's always one other
subgenius who
appears to have been put on this earth for
no other reason than to piss
you off.
You're anti-subgenius.
Now, unfortunately, I feel like
I've got dozens of those.
But they feel the same way. It's a
mutual thing, usually.
I'd still rather have an anti-subgenius
bothering me than, like, an anti-
normal. Rather have the right people
laughing at you than the
wrong people laughing with you. And just
because you're anti-normal doesn't mean you're
subgenius, too. Oh, God.
God forbid, because there's so many,
we run into so many of these
gimme bobs that,
they're the first one to point the finger
and go, oh, that guy's pink.
I can't believe there's
these pinks here. And they're
jabbering in pink, bobby
jargon about who else is
some sort of cultish bobby
pink!
So, I wouldn't want to call those people
pinks, because then I'd sound just like
that. But I am, anyway.
They don't
know who they are.
I think of pinks as talking like
this. Pinks are
really cute and pudgy, and
you could squish their cheeks,
and they sort of just talk like this,
and they do what we say.
Those are happy pinks.
The kind of happy pinks, the happiest
kind of pink is the pink that will tell you
what you're gonna do and smile
while he's like, you know, telling you,
clean up that vomit.
Yeah! Because I'm pink.
And you want to be like
me, so if you want to succeed, just
clean up lots of vomit, because that's
how they talk, and they've got big pudgy
cheeks. That's what I think of when I hear pink.
I hear that voice. Well, it's funny. I had a
boss who was short and
pink and had pudgy cheeks
and told me to clean up
his vomit. Well, I, and
that was actually a vision that I had. But he kind of
talked like this. When I was back in the
80s, when I was living in Boston with all these
subgeniuses,
Dr.
Ahmed Fishmonger and
others, you know, I was like in
college at the time, and I was struggling to work
and stuff, and I had this long
conversation with my dad about
how I had to earn a living.
Well, you might as well, you know,
get a job at McDonald's,
is what he said.
You know, even just for a little while,
because you've got to make some money.
And I was like, job at McDonald's?
And that night,
I had a dream that
I went to,
that I was like, I'm driving on the highway,
and I had to go to a place called
Pwodzaburger to eat.
And Pwodzaburger was
basically run by a man who
looked like Shoney's Big Boy. And he talked
like this. He's like, come on in to Pwodzah's.
And, and,
and I was like, well, I'm not sure I
really want to. And he's like, well, come on in and,
you know, have a seat.
And if you, you know, if
you behave yourself, maybe you could get your
very own job here at Pwodzah's.
And I was like, well,
I don't really want a job at Pwodzah's.
And he started giving me the tour of the place.
This is a real dream I had.
Pwodzah's was spelled
P-W-D-G-A
apostrophe S.
And, um,
as I went through it, I started to realize
this was like a Soylent Green
operation. And that everybody wanted
to be happy and please Pwodzah.
Because they had a statue of Pwodzah. It was sort of like
between Buddha and a pig
and Shoni's big boy
was the statue. And I'll never
forget, I couldn't draw what it looks like. Maybe Dr.
Hal could draw it someday.
But if you took those three elements, that would be
Pwodzah. And everybody wanted
to please him and be happy so they could, you know,
rise up in management. And
then I started to realize
that the workers who weren't
doing well, as well as the other workers, were really
scared. And they had this extra
scared look on their face.
And then I realized why.
It was because the workers who
couldn't keep up the happy pace of Pwodzahs
would of course be sacrificed
and thrown into the grinder
and become Pwodzahburgers.
And that was how they maintained their
big profits. And everybody loves
Pwodzahburgers.
And yeah, so that was my real dream.
And that's what made, another
thing that cemented,
cemented my
wanting to be a subgenius and exploit
my abnormality to get
where I wanted to go. That just made
me say, no, you know, I understand
Dad's thinking he came from the depression, but
no, I've got to, if I
possibly can, I've got to exploit
my abnormality. Get this.
I worked there.
I had a job there for
two hours.
The guy said,
you're going to have to get a haircut to work here,
so come back tomorrow.
Well, he said it in that way, I can't imitate him.
Oh, you have to come back tomorrow. Come back tomorrow
after you get a haircut. And
I didn't get a haircut.
My hair was about as long as yours.
But that was long then.
And then I came back
without the haircut and got to work
swabbing the toilets.
And just when the little
squeaky man showed up, so did the
corporate inspector.
And got the creepy,
got him in trouble
because he had hired a long hair.
And then I got fired.
And boy was I happy.
No, and the other,
just the other part of the dream was,
I'll never forget what he said, because I
made it into a radio skit later.
He said,
just maintain group growth status production quotient
on a viable categorical basis within your
substrata, and you can have all the
podger burgers and real taste pies
that you can muster.
That's what he said.
And that's when I woke up, I think.
It's when I hear about things like that
that I'm glad that I'm a slave for
J.R. Bob Dobbs.
So am I. Listen. Because he's never around.
That's the nice thing about having
him for a boss.
Yep, yep. I mean, let's face it,
I do work for the conspiracy.
And yet, you know, for a conspiracy job,
it's the greatest conspiracy job I could possibly ask for.
And it sucks, right?
No, it doesn't suck. No, no, no.
Luckily for me, you know, I mean, sure,
you know, podger's always on the horizon
at any corporation, they always are.
But, you know, what's good for me is that,
you know, they let me do what I like.
And I can still
explore Bob, I think.
I think I'm safe to do that.
And the other thing is,
that, uh, we've
tried to get the word across,
but it's hard to do. It's just, it can
be hard to directly inject
Bob's word into the conspiracy.
But I still do it. You're not hammering hard enough,
boy. You sharper nails in
their heads.
That's what you gotta do.
You know, I just thank Bob for,
you know, giving me the microphone, basically.
If it wasn't for Bob, I wouldn't have the microphone.
Well, Bob is my gorilla.
Yeah.
This is Just John with a message for whoever
wants to eat the ham out of my hellburger.
Whoever you are, I have to think you got the
concept exactly wrong.
Or maybe you're operating under a different concept entirely,
one I haven't heard of.
Or maybe you're just a jerk.
Are you a member of one of those religions that banned the eating
of pork products and you felt like breaking a commandment
and a dietary law at the same time?
Regardless,
you can eat the rest of the hellburger for all I care.
I have obtained a
new hellburger, and I will not be
leaving this one unattended.
We're in a deep, deep
deep deep deep....
deep, deep deep deep deep
deep deep deep deep deep ....
...
into the Jimmy Jones cult!
Jimmy Jones logical
section!
Yeah!
He had a very large,
and what happened?
Now, Jimmy Jones, he was absolutely no stranger.
Could we follow Jimmy Jones?
Become a part
of the cult!
Jimmy Jones. Well, how do we keep false teaching? How did you receive, Jimmy Jones, so something
else? A cult? Something else. You need to do this and that and the other thing. A cult
is important. Go downward. Go downward. Blowing down for nourishment. Now we're building,
okay? We're building a cult. I have bad, empty philosophy. Ignorant? Ignorant. You really
can't know anything for sure. You're ignorant. Of course, think about that. You can't know
anything for sure. Can't know anything for sure. Twist that around. Okay. I have more
bad. It's about that thick. Now, you're coming and there's a building. You're coming on your
left. And the shadow of someone coming. There's a person coming. Yeah. Okay. Yeah. And so
the person coming.
The person coming. Yeah. Okay. Yeah. And so the person coming. Yeah. Okay. Yeah. And so
the person comes for a moment. Donuts, thank you. Okay, good. Oh, the fullness. Marshall
Applewhite, leader of Heaven's Gate cult. Correction. Fullness. We just come. We just
come. And this happened at the very moment. Getting sucked. Getting sucked. Getting sucked.
Cult. Cult. Sucked. Into the Jimmy Jones cult.
Oh boy. Sucked into a cult. That would be terrible, wouldn't it?
That, as well as the viral Bush piece at the beginning, was by Reverend Norell Preff of
Norellpreff.com. Before that, the Hellburger moment was by Reverend Just John here on Hour
of Sight number one thousand one hundred and eleven. One, one, one, one for our superstitious
ones out there. Our titles were by...
And almost always are. And the nice big end of the world collage at the beginning and
also coming up was by Reverend Susie the Floozy from her beautiful show, Bob's Slacktime Fun
House on WREK.org Atlanta. And we heard some clips from the Sermon to the Pagans at Starwood
Festival number twenty-seven by yours truly, Reverend Ivan Stubbs. And we heard some clips
of the clip by  Stub pins this for 73.com who actually transpose how
For sure, you're listening to Benobo's & arche QR card show at X Day Ten, and lots of
X Day LIVE ON STAGE radio with Ask Doctor How. For more on that, see AskDrHow.com,
saddle ***** resend bhouv lipoguoo  dei
this duet thank you very much to Martin Huerf or David van Wuerff for gra
that.
on them, check out bonobosmusic.com.
And now the news.
To maintain a healthy discussion, we suggest a steady diet of PR news.
PR news.
Broad from the BBC.
From PR news in Washington, I'm battling a blaze between January and March.
The man who touched Pope Benedict's Peter spoke at a ceremony in Normandy, France today.
It's a lie.
The Vatican says a German man turned up dead on Wall Street 14455.
A police spokesman says this is PR news in Washington.
Hey, there's a lot we all agree on here.
The government says the Labor Department says productivity measures how much one worker can kidnap and beat two young men in one hour of PR.
PR comes from com.com.
Trailer for sale or rent.
Rooms to let 50 cents.
Here comes Peter.
Peter Cottontail.
No phone, no pool, no pets.
Hopping down the bunny trail.
I ain't got no cigarettes.
About two hours of push and broom.
Buys a 8x12 4-bit room.
Hippity-hoppity, Easter's on its way.
I'm a man of means by no means.
Bringing every girl and boy a basket full of Easter joy.
King of the road.
Here's the next question, Dr. Howell.
I'm ready.
And it's a rough one.
Has Bob forsaken us?
How do we know?
Did you ride a bike when you were a kid, Ivan Stan?
Why, yeah, sure, Dr. Howell.
I think we all have that memory of riding a bicycle through sunlit streets of summer.
Maybe carrying something in our bicycle basket.
But there was a time when we had, uh,
training wheels and it, we might have feared falling over and getting a skinning.
Because, uh, the bike takes a little bit of mastery to learn.
And who often helps you learn?
Sometimes you do it yourself, but sometimes your dad helps, doesn't he?
Sometimes Wilford Bramley has to help.
Yes, that old, uh, pensioner has to come stumping down and take a few palsied feeble steps,
holding your handlebar and supporting your body vertically up.
And he's got a little bit of a
But then he lets go.
And either you land in a humiliating heap or you scud down the street, enormously aware of infinitely unfolding possibilities.
Would you say that Wilford has left you?
Well, you might if you were incredibly insecure.
But the fact is, Bob has not forsaken us.
We have forsaken all of you.
Bob.
But don't worry.
Bob is bringing up the rear.
Bob is going to be along.
Any day now.
Dr. Howell, that makes, that's so reassuring to me.
Well, it shouldn't be.
I'd rather have Bob in front of me myself.
Anyway, uh, let's go on.
We still have a few more of these to answer.
This is one I know that you've gotten before.
Because it's the same kind that, that, that,
Blame me. I've seen them all.
There's always the smart aleck in the, uh, corner.
That comparative religion class.
Thank God for that smart aleck.
That asks the priest this question.
Yep.
Father, could Bob give it, could God give himself a dick so big even he couldn't suck it?
That's the classic atheist's question.
Uh, and we get it.
Uh, we certainly do.
Over and over again.
And in another sense, we also get it.
The question really boils down to, parsed another way,
would God make rules and then disobey them?
And, uh, since God is infinitely plastic and can stretch into all dimensions and places,
no twisting or torsion of the continuum is beyond his malignant efforts.
But would God do that?
It might be said that the almighty spirit is in some senses lazy.
And only does the easy things.
Follows the straightest of lines.
No, for that sinuous, uh, sinusoidal sinuosity, we need Satan and his barbed tail.
Then we get the interesting curved path.
The, uh, spirals.
The strange configurations which are the essence of kicking against the traces.
That's positively satanic, Doctor.
Dr. Howell, thank you.
The sum of Satan percolates and drips into the church of the subgenius, but only the good part.
Good in a utilitarian sense.
Well, this is a related question.
Is it possible to get sick of Bob?
And if so, what should be done about it?
That recalls to me that, uh, that old subgenius hymn, Sick of Bob.
Well, and that is the, uh, genesis and seedbed of the answer.
Because what one does when one is sick of Bob,
is create a song or a statue or a poem or a pile of stinky laundry
to commemorate that self-same sickness.
The nausea of existential understanding.
This is a positive development.
You should be sick of Bob.
If you eat, sleep, live, and breathe Bob all the time,
then how can you appreciate Bob
when he comes upon you like a thief in the night?
Uh, here's one, uh, Dr. Howell, that I think you'll enjoy
because it's a, sort of a scientific related question.
Well, let's have it.
If one were to travel very near the speed of light and survive,
what would it smell like?
Well, um, you can travel near the speed of light
as long as you control your exhalation.
And, uh, your deceleration particularly.
Um, and, uh, all you need to do is approach within, uh,
the smallest fraction of that speed.
Like Achilles' tortoise.
Ever severing the distance but, uh, coming a microscopic
and yet diminishing distance closer.
But what would it smell like?
It would smell like your own stressed out blood, sweat,
lymph, entrails, and slime.
Little human, you were not meant to travel very near the speed of light.
Or anything like that speed.
You already travel at thousands and thousands of unseemly miles per hour
through the universe's enfolding cloak of mystery.
Be well satisfied with that.
And seek not to dispute your place at hyper-relativistic velocities.
The angels were created to do that,
and even they got sick of it.
Praise Bob.
Perfect time to switch me.
Ah, time to flip the old tape.
Yep. We're still flipping.
Well, uh, while we're doing that...
We're still flipping. No, we're done.
Let's announce that...oh.
We're all done. Go ahead and announce stuff.
Well, I was going to announce that we were doing the Ask Dr. Hal show,
uh, for the broadcast tape, but if we're done,
I should announce that we're done.
No, no. We're not...we're not nowhere near done yet.
Oh, you're done flipping the tape.
Yes, I'm done flipping the tape.
We've just flipped the tape in the middle of the Ask Dr. Hal show.
Flipping the tape, uh, of course, is a metaphor
from a quainter, earlier technological age.
Um, do we want to, uh, interrupt the proceedings
to read, um, gorilla and demon statements?
Certainly.
Before we come back?
Well, here's another one.
Oh, okay. This, uh, the gorilla in this person's...
Oh, we've already done this one.
This is for use when the show gets slow or retarded.
All right. Well, do this one, then.
I...
Because I trust we haven't been slow at all.
Oh, okay.
And retarded so far.
I...I...wow, what amazing handwriting.
It looks like a professional cartoonist or...or calligrapher did this.
The gorilla says,
I gets all confused and anxious about the protocol among the humans.
I just want slack, but no want you be uncomfort...
want...no want to be uncomfortable.
Want...I just want slack, but no want to be uncomfortable.
They no care about gorilly gorilly.
No care about gorilly gorilly.
Gorilly no mean make bad smell.
Scrum all.
That last probably is pronounced screw em all.
Screw em all.
Okay, I'm sorry.
Well, what about the demon, Reverend Stane?
The demon, uh, says, why don't every one of you self-satisfied little pose your twerps?
Admit your inadequacy as representatives of your feeble mind.
And kill yourselves now, squirming bags of unfulfilled appetites.
I disdain your foul tasting blood.
That's a S. Clay Wilson demon, isn't it?
If only we had Mavridis here to fill that out.
We should save one of those for him.
Well, let's get back to the Ask Dr. Hal show because we still have a few questions to answer.
The...the gorilla in this one is clutching a...a distressed naked blonde woman.
Very well rendered.
And yet he expresses unsatisfaction.
Not good.
Not an ape.
All right.
Is New Orleans safe from future flooding?
Will the levees be adequate?
Is New Orleans the future Atlantis?
Let it go.
New Orleans is simply the future.
The inundation will eventually roll over most of the cities.
Because most cities are built at the mouths of rivers and watercourses.
Or on oceans themselves.
If the water level rises sufficiently in the oceans, the rivers will not flow into them.
And they too shall rise and back up.
And the great flood shall roll over the land.
The quaking cities of man shall be smote down.
By the waves of doom, justice and vengeance.
But on the other hand, all the earth will not be covered.
And this is what God promised.
He said, don't worry.
There's never going to be a flood as there was in Noah's day.
This is in the Bible.
Unfortunately, then he said, no, there won't be a flood.
Instead, there will be a fire age coming.
And that too will come to pass.
Too quickly to avoid.
Avoid regret.
When that flood comes, I'm going to join the smokers and find dry land.
You can find dry land.
That's the thing about this flood.
But then the heat will come.
And will Kevin Costner be there?
That great Costner to himself.
So we're living in a real crazy world, my friend.
We're living in a world where everyone is crying out for deliverance.
Now, many times you will see the president standing there in the Rose Garden with two of these smiling men from the east on each side.
One has got a tablecloth on his head.
And he told them they smile and then they put there in the newspaper, uh, peace.
I've got no problem with the peace treaties that they sign.
I have a problem with the people who sign the peace treaties.
Uh, that's, that's reality.
George, you should be ashamed of yourself.
And how.
Recently, another 400 scientists, scholars, businessmen, and political leaders have been
met in Texas to ponder the problems facing mankind.
They said it is a gloomy world indeed.
The energy crisis, famine, the financial problems of New York City, drug abuse, and other unrelated problems are all portents of the present darkness.
And the Bible says,
I am the God of hell fire, and I bring you fire.
Sudden destruction comes upon them, and they shall not escape.
That's what the Bible says here.
There shall be famine, pestilences, and different things.
And I don't have to tell you these things.
You know, if there ever is a time that Bible prophecy is confirmed right before our eyes
of mouth.
Plagues, pestilences, and things like that.
Yeah, right.
Yeah.
Now, the boss says this is a very bad thing for the country.
See, because this contract starts after the war.
Now, the boss has got an idea with all this Nazi and Jap money that, uh, well, I haven't
got it quite straight, but anyway, the boss says it's a bad thing for the country.
So far, you've told me what the boss has found out.
What did you find out?
I don't need the terrorists.
Boy, you're hotter than a firecracker on the 5th of July.
Who is it?
All right.
Listen up, everyone.
I want you to calmly file towards the exit.
That's it.
Nobody runs.
Just walk.
Single file.
That's it.
Now, if we just stay calm, no one's going to be harmed by the huge bomb that's going
to explode any minute.
I'm sorry.
It's a cookbook!
A world is getting out of hand, all what's removed from me, so what else, some nameless
face.
controls my destiny
Is it the man who's doing research
or the man who's out in space
There's something that's controlling me
Some silent, nameless space
Is he an IBM computer
or an electronic brain
And if I cannot find him
Where do I come from
Where
Yes?
Excuse me, I believe I left a pipe and some books
Oh, they're right here
This is my lucky pipe
and I didn't want to leave it behind
I understand you're going away
That's right, I've got to start packing right now
You're a blithering coward
Bitch, I'll f*** your ass up
Is all that?
Are you sure you're discussing my departure?
Oh no, no, no, don't worry about that
You are miserable because you don't know how to say goodbye
But danger has come sooner than you expected
and now you are making up your mind to go at once
The secret won't keep for long, of course
but at present it is, I think
known only to us, conspirators
and we're not going to let you escape so easily
But I must go
It cannot be helped
It is wretched for us all
but please help me and don't hinder me
You don't understand
You're lying
Maybe he's not
I know him
Look at his face
He's lying
Hey, Bob is my only hope
Back off and give him some room to think
All right
This place is going up
Well, if I'm going out, I'm going out happy
Before we're all blown to bits
Mind if I pull the underwear out of my crack?
Man's got to go comfortable
All right, but that's it
God, I hate that guy
I don't believe it
Tell him the truth or not
Didn't the police mention it?
Say anything about it?
Bob, no
No
What did he look like?
Looked like what?
He looked like a man, of course
What do you suppose?
Uh-huh
Oh, yes, yes
He looked like a man
Yeah, yes, I know
He's a queer bunny
Nobody believed me
Even my colleagues wouldn't believe me
Poor man
He's insane, that's what he is
He believed me
He believes it
He must be insane
For fools
Can't they understand me?
Tell me something
Am I mad?
Tell me
Here's somebody's gorilla
Oh, can I read it?
Yeah
The gorilla is one
And the demon is the other
Okay, yeah
These are again anonymous
But
I just want to eat Froot Loops
I don't want to do housework
Housework?
That's the inner gorilla
He's got the same problem as all of you slackers
Oh, shut it, gorilla
You damned dirty ape
Says the demon
It's a pretty simple one
But, you know, they're elemental
This is all very elemental
And very therapeutic
I think already five people now
Have been helped
Third box star, midnight train
Destination Bangor, Maine
Things to make your Easter bright and gay
Old worn-out suitors
And shoes
I don't pay no union dues
He's got jelly beans for Tommy
Colored eggs for Sister Sue
I smoke old stogies I have found
Short but not too big a round
Here's an orchid for your mommy
And an Easter bonnet too
Oh
Bob has a secret number
You know, just like the Antichrist
Bob's number is 999
Ha ha
Figures
The anti-Bob's number is 333
Bob is not the Antichrist
But he's sort of like the anti-Antichrist
He's buddies with Jesus
There's always just been their fan club
That bothers us
I don't know where I was going with that one, actually
What was that?
Oh, well
It's in there somewhere
Friend, are you sick of flibberty gibbish
News-groping yobers
Yoked to insaneness?
Hate to have to work
In a herd of turds
And tards
And not a fleet of eagles?
Are your cow orkers
A bunch of shit-offs
With the hundredth lemming syndrome?
Low Mudville joy quotient
And a thousand idiot synchronicities
Rendering you a mongoose of panic?
Are you a crazed diuretic constipationist
Faced with overwhelm-tion
Who can't get your favorite nose reticence
In her quickly enough?
Well, bum and bummest
That's a bunch of jabbermacky and cockabucky
Fuck it or fuck with it
Be spurky, not chumpy
Neither hard-faced nor ab-mul
Nor all flibby and jibby
Don't worry one wheat nor twittle
About every little ninny-picking
Hood and winker
Every whim and quigger
We are on it 23-7
I am, we are
We're the 12th
We're the 1200th monkey
So get off your bohunkus on us
And start flinging the gungawackum back at em
Get back your funanity
Learn to laugh at yourself
And you'll always be amused
Actually, I think her grandpa said that
Or as Pogo said
Don't take life so serious
It ain't no way permanent
Friends, you could be getting slack
So good-looking it'll get you leaking
Cause it's un-really good
It's god-shittingly good
So put your frock where your mouth is
Repent, quit your job
Slack off while you still know how
Question authority
Why?
Bob is not the answer
And neither is anything else
Fuck them if they can't take a joke
And praise Bob
Praise Bob
Don't try that at home
And you need an Adam's apple
Okay, I think I can go to the Q&A
Oh, we did have one new
We have a new church
We just invented
You know, we don't actually make giant bucks doing this
Bob started this
It's like an art project that's
It's anti-art
And it's a new piece of art
anti-business business and it's an anti-science scientific project and most
of all it was a club for non-joiners and it has not made us rich so we were
thinking about starting a new one for normal people called Bob's Club for
Joiners. What do y'all think of that? I mean probably you may not be up your alley but
don't you think that would work better at the point of purchase at the stop and
go you know Bob's Club for Joiners people go whoa yeah I'm a joiner. Let me have one of those and one of those energy pills and a lottery ticket. That would be so cute.
I know every engineer on every train maybe if you're extra good he'll roll lots of Easter eggs your way all the children and all of their names look at him hop and listen to him say and
every train will say Bob's Club for Joiners.
hand out in every town and every life that ain't like when no one's around when you find those chocolate bunnies that he's hiding everywhere I'm a man of means by no means you wake up in Easter morning and you'll know that he was that king of the road.
King Peter by Reverend Just John of just-john.com
and this is the end of the show.
This is the 1111th hour of slack.
Before Just John we heard subgenius preaching from the Starwood Festival.
For more on that see roseandcomet.com
For more information on all that plus Church of the Subgenius see subgenius.com
Or write to post office box 181.
This is so close.
Jeff Gordon speaking.
TIME ON AIR.
It's time.
JOHN Phillis is here.
FILL OUT YOUR PROJECTS.
The
FULL-N Immediately.
AND P cheat
AND intellectual
and da
Just maintain group growth status production quotient on a viable categorical basis within your substrata,
and you can have all the Pudger burgers and real taste pies that you can muster.