Oh my god!
My friend, can your heart stand the shocking facts about Bob?
If you think that it's factual, then at least find that back in Bob.
The End
Bob?
Hello there.
You know, I've been all around this wonderful world of ours,
and in all this world, nothing else is Bob.
Bob.
The Son of Genius
I cut my finger on a soup can lid
I got an infection and it spread
To my whole body
To my dick
It swelled up to the size of a human head
And then a mouth opened on it
And this is what it said
Kill the pink boys, quit your job
Mock the world and praise Bob Dobbs
We'll build a ship and take a trip
Go on, go get a pen, write the coordinates
Three and a half months in my garage
Tearing parts off of old used cars
My groin at this point was unusually large
And would occasionally hum while smoking cigars
The project was finished
The ship would hold twenty
The power source was anything
The crew would think was funny
We didn't need the slack list
They're hapless
Our worth proved its worth
In escaping the stark fist
On our way to Planet X
For sex that wrecks necks
A prairie squid and every pot of money
Shot a coney twat
It's an all-horse hour of bonanza
It's like a world without Tony Danza
Orphanza
The pink shit that hits the charts
In a world of dead art
Simultaneous lobotomy and sodomy
We take a moment and we pause to reflect
On the pinks that we killed
And the planet that they wrecked
Then we laugh like banshees
And howl like a man
She's too a victim
To redempt
In our underoos and panties
Our fantasy is a reality
Earth's tarnished as dust
As Planet X are bust for us
Bob's pipe is lit
Space and time shift
The ship will determine
What causes a slack rift
And they drop in ahead
A dimensional split
Severs forever
Subgeni from pink shit
Bob walked in a circle
And steadily exhaled in the smoke
I can see why the pink boys failed
To pay a daze has caused destruction
Second hole of slackless suction
Ape of you alien abductors
Function
Functioning on soulless slack
The money should be painted black
The mate from space that stole your balls
Will soon come back and take it all
Return to slack
Return to Bob
Repent slack off and quit your job
Or slurp the beastly knob
Carnage
Lick the throbbing vein of slavery
Now you're sleeping like a baby
But Bob woke me up and said
Get out of Dodge
There's a guy who's dick and top
With a UFO in his garage
I ate some bad ham
And I guess I'm gonna die
I got really sick
And in a puddle of my puke
Where the puke was most thick
A mouth did appear
And it beckoned me near
And it whispered the following words into my ear
It said
Kill the pink boys
Quit your job
Mock the world
And praise Bob Dobbs
You'll build a ship
And take a trip
Go on go get a pen
Write the coordinates
Six and a half months hold up alone
Circuit boards duct tape and turkey bones
The ship appeared more than disaster prone
But the vomit assured me that far weirder ships had flown
The project was failed
The ship would hold twenty
The power source was anything the crew would think was funny
We didn't need the slack list or hapless
Our mouth proved its worth in escaping the star fist
On our way to Planet X for sex that wrecks necks
A prairie squid and every pot of money shot a coney twine
It's an all-hoss hour of bonanza
It's like a world without Tony Danza
Or fans of the pink shit that hits the charts
In a world of dead art
Simultaneous lobotomy and sodomy
We take a moment and we pause to reflect
On the pinks that we killed and the planet that they wrecked
Then we look up and we see the world that we're in
We laugh like Benchies and howl like Comanches
Do a victory dance in our underoos and panties
Our fantasy is a reality
Earth turns to dust
It's Planet X or Bustros
Embracing day one
This is the end
Closing your veins
The front pipe clouds bring slack like rain
Let Bob control what's left of your brain
Oh yes and all your money to the Reverend Einstein
You have to turn around your head
Oh no too late
It's chain collapses
How long are you gonna get
They're just saying
Just make yourself waste of it
Come back here
Come out and start doing it
You ain't enough
Just relax like the Congress of the Democratic Dividends
Charging back to something that you icinged with
You see people are blaming their BottomS traveled
It's his position
Embrace the yeti blood that flows in your veins
The thought might cloud free, slap might rain
When mom can control what's left of your brain
Oh, pass him all your money to the reverend I can see
We had Dr. Howl in town, Dr. Howl and Owl of the KPFA show
and the Ask Dr. Howl nightclub act in San Francisco
and even that game Half-Life.
So friends, get ready for, well actually for the next several shows,
get ready for a real plate full of spicy slack subgenius style.
Mamma mia!
That's a spicy meatball!
There is rebellion in the wind.
It will be crushed.
Be one of the few, the proud.
That's right, we want all the subgeniuses to get their lead out of their treads
and get some traction on the action and rumble on down to Indianapolis, Indiana.
Scene of the biggest subgenius revival ever to come coddling down the pike.
A scan 300 miles away from the Cleveland area, Indianapolis is home to many fine things.
The statue of Arno.
Armature Veswing.
The capital of Indiana itself.
The state building is there and also a number of outcroppings.
Death Race 2000.
But they all pale into etiolated whiteness in comparison to the pulsing full-blooded subgenius festival
which will be there in all its raw rampaging glory.
Five igloos, count them, five igloos!
And you'll see all the subs go through a wonderful montage of bloopers and flubs.
Right up on the stage it'll be a real fly slapper.
Fly, fly, fly, fly, fly, fly, fly, fly, fly, fly, fly, fly, fly, fly, fly.
Bob is coming and also coming up next,
friends I am so proud finally to bring to the Midwest,
the howl-ribbly, rib-ticklin',
Dr. Howl!
Yeah!
Woo!
Thank you, Ivan Stang.
You couldn't ask for a better introducer.
Of course, Ivan Stang and I go way back.
And we are, as they say, tight like that.
We know the secrets of each other's hearts.
We know the good that is in us,
and unfortunately, as a result of close association through so many years,
we also know the part that is not so good.
The crawling, creeping part.
For in every subgenus, even in one as slack-filled as the sacred scribe,
Ivan Stang himself,
there exists a small crawling worm.
Which hungers and thirsts for the juices and secretions of the conspiracy.
I wouldn't say this, unless I was certain that these are not idlers here,
but people who actually understand a little thing or two about subgenius doctrine.
After all, subgenius doctrine is not that difficult to understand,
it just takes a long time to explain it.
Today, bedraggled and sleep-rumbled,
we were leaving our hotel, or maybe it was yesterday, I don't know,
in a fog of sleeplessness and slacklessness,
suddenly we were confronted by a curious group of normals in a van,
who started asking us about that face on our clothing.
And they were saying,
You mean you're Trekkies, right?
No, madam.
Not in any sense.
We are members of the church of the subgenius.
Subgenius? What's that?
Does it mean you're stupid?
Well, indeed it may.
There's no point in ruling it out.
But, as has been mentioned before,
subgenius does not really have anything to do with intelligence,
and hardly anything to do with stupidity.
Subgenius, when you parse the word,
only means that each one who is a subgenius
is under, as the prefix sub indicates,
his own genius.
And the word genius has an alternative meaning
that you will find in the dictionary,
cognate to the word genie or spirit.
Because there are spiritual powers in this twisted and tormented world,
the conspiracy doesn't agree that any of them exist,
it can't make money from.
But we, members of the church of the subgenius,
are occasionally able to make money from even these tenuous phantoms.
And a true subgenius is one who acts under his own genius,
or her own genius,
rather than at the behest of the conspiracy.
Yes, the conspiracy.
Not just the John F. Kennedy conspiracy,
or any conspiracy in particular,
they interlock.
They are, at the back of all things,
the same gigantic interlocked conspiracy.
Conspiracy, from the Latin con, meaning with,
and spiro, meaning to breathe,
as in respiration, inspiration.
To be inspired is to be full of breath.
To conspire is to breathe together.
So the conspiracy and its members all breathe together.
They may not know,
that they are aligned in a mighty force
against the few heroic members of the church of the subgenius,
but nonetheless,
they act like some gigantic malignant organism,
together in thrall,
to oppose what the subgeniuses want.
And what do the subgeniuses want?
You know.
What must the subgenius have?
Slack!
Slack, yes.
Slack is the soft voice.
Slack, the luminous cloud.
We rejoice in Slack.
Slack is the opposite of tension.
Slack is leisure.
Leisure, the basis of culture.
Only in leisure can you figure out the next neat thing.
Not while you are enmeshed in the tentacular coils of the conspiracy,
at your meaningless job.
It is important,
it is unfortunately necessary,
since we are surrounded by the fluid medium of the conspiracy,
that we breathe it a little bit,
that we kick against it a little bit.
We may have to have a conspiracy job now and then,
on our way, on our voyage,
to being an art bum,
and having no job,
and somehow being miraculously supported.
It is a path beset with thorns,
scorpions,
and orthopedic shoes.
But it can be surmounted.
And it is worthwhile taking that sinusoidal trail
through the toils of the conspiracy's
bowels to the mountain of enlightenment,
the punchline,
the pot of gold.
See the heaven and hell diagram in Revelation X,
the Babel Bible Files.
Now, the conspiracy wants to take away your original Slack.
You were born, each and every one of you,
with original Slack.
But the conspiracy wants to take that original Slack
away from you and sell you a piece of false Slack,
that it has earned you.
And it wants to keep you thirsting,
and jonesing,
and gasping,
and grasping,
for each new laptop and palm pilot,
each new trinket,
each new tchotchke,
which it assures you will complete
the ring of your happiness.
But you will never be happy,
just as Tantalus in the underworld
is tortured by having food
lowered almost to his parched lips,
and then when he snatches at it,
has it draw away
what you think of
as part of your happiness,
will eternally draw away
as you attempt to approach it.
This is how you know it is false Slack,
a production of the conspiracy.
Now, anybody who's ever thought
of drawing cartoons
has probably looked at those books which say,
everybody can draw cartoons.
It's really simple.
First you draw a circle,
and then you draw a vertical line,
and in about 15 minutes,
you're completely bored with it,
and you throw it over.
But all these books have one thing in common.
They contain a diagram,
which allegedly represents
how to draw in perspective.
And this is invariably a picture of railroad tracks
stretching away to a point on the horizon,
a point which they call the vanishing point.
The horizon is always drawn at the head
of your characters at eye level,
because the horizon is the same
at everyone's eye level.
And these railroad tracks do appear
to draw away into a point.
And throughout your life,
you are rushing down those tracks
toward that vanishing point.
But there comes a time,
and it grieves me to tell you this,
it really does,
I don't want to bring anybody down,
I know everyone's here having a good time,
but there comes a time
when as you look forward
from the train,
you'll see, by God,
they do come to a point.
And that point is coming closer and closer.
And inevitably,
the train will go off the tracks,
derail, because the rails are no longer wide enough,
and after that point is oblivion,
the abyss of nothingness.
It is your job,
it is your duty as a subgenius
to indulge in what we call
time control.
Yes, you don't have to go
pell-mell down this track,
you can goof off,
you can bloviate,
you can loaf,
you can use your divine subgenius essence
and put it to the test.
Because time is nothing
you should have to consider,
it's slack that you should consider.
Time is a thing of dragonflies and angels,
the former live too little
and the latter live too long.
But you will live your allotted life
in a moment span,
either in slacklessness
or in thirsty grasping
for the conspiracy's worthless trinkets.
It's a sad business,
ladies and gentlemen.
I've simply laid it out for you a little bit.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, no.
Bob?
Stop it!
Bob? Bob? Bob?
Stop it, I tell you!
Stop it!
Bob? Bob?
Get back to your...
Get back to your machine, you man!
Bob? Bob? Bob?
Now, these grunting,
all I have you know,
especially Dr. Howell,
the grunts are highly codified
and are of great interest
to those people who,
let's just call them red-liners...
...on the Pacific coast.
You know what I mean?
I'm talking about...
Yeah, when you turn down the elastic,
you see the little red lines.
No, you know what we're talking about.
CIA, Langley boys,
Fort Meade...
CIA, ASC, FBI, OSS...
Oh, yes, I know,
it's all very boring
to those who've heard it
a thousand times before,
but there are some...
Oh, no, I...
...who are just learning
about this kind of stuff,
and, uh, well, Pastor Stang,
I think you ought to...
Oh, I'm not...
...respect their quest
for knowledge.
I'm not bored.
I'm exhausted from helping
to fulfill their quest
for knowledge.
Me, too.
Soak your smelly old feet
in Excelsior and...
...dry gunpowder,
and, uh, place one of those
dirigible...
...those, you know, devices
you were selling in...
...in the right place,
and you'll be fine.
Those things don't work.
And we just came back from the...
They don't...
...either do they toil.
We just came back from the lengthy
and...
...and exhaustive, uh,
subgenius tour, uh,
uh, through Speedunk, uh,
Shinbone, uh, Potterville,
and...
...Spoontown.
You really went through
such places?
That's right,
and we left the glimmering
message of Bob behind,
right on the doorstep
of each individual.
We'd light it on fire,
and then we'd ring the doorbell,
and we'd run.
Well, how did these
rustic Hoosiers, you know,
go for your big, uh,
Bob blowjob there?
I mean...
They lapped it up
enthusiastically.
They did?
I'm proud.
Yes, uh, again and again...
I'm rather proud.
...a quivering audience
member pressed our hands
amidst sobs and tears
and told us it was
the best thing ever.
We love that movie.
You couldn't have said
it even better.
They sucked it up
like snakes suck milk
from a cow's udder.
Well, see, now,
you couldn't have
said it better.
And the swag table
doubled.
They did land office business.
Well...
Now, uh,
Pastor Stang owns
the mortgage to several
homes in the area.
Not to mention
orphanages.
Well, they're
feisty people,
those Hoosiers,
so I wouldn't put them,
you know, I wouldn't, uh,
you know, down them too hard.
They might come after you.
They make fine
basketball players,
but, uh, frankly, uh,
when, uh, it comes to
signing on the dotted line,
uh, all the Pastor Stang
has them beat six ways
to Sunday.
Yeah, and it's usually
a big ol' bloody X
they stamp down there
because they've forgotten
how to write their names
after being plowed under
so many times.
Yeah, and they're
by the Hoovers
and the big conglomerate.
It's easier for them
to scratch out an X
with their finger stumps
after they've been ratified
and codified.
Yeah.
It's a poor situation,
but what can we do
as, uh, you know,
slovenly, mediocre individuals
taking up our Hoovers
and, you know,
that thing there?
Well, you can't leave
the Hoovers switched on
all night,
but the easiest thing
to do is...
No, you know,
you blow out your spleen.
You just have to...
You can trust in Bob.
...make the entire
syllogism of the Hovers
become easier
for the average participant.
How do we start?
T and A.
Take out some of those
archaic legal
and theological concepts.
No one needs them,
and put some girls in it.
Yeah.
And, uh,
and some lively,
snappy music
and some songs.
Yeah, that's right.
And we can find
maybe an old barn
nobody's using
and put on a show.
I've got a mustache.
I can play the old man.
Yeah, I can use
a bunny girl.
Everybody likes this.
Look at this hat.
This used to be granddad's.
Well, now I can be
on the stage.
Yeah, and I got a friend
who's a dance.
We'll have the booze
and the music
and we'll be...
Yeah.
Hmm.
You can pull the curtain,
uh, just to take hold
of one corner of it
and give it a good pull.
I'll try.
See, it's real easy.
Uh, they make it seem
like it's hard to be
in show biz,
but nothing's easier.
The rest of it,
it's just a lot
of technical double talk
and tomfoolery
to keep people awed
and in their place.
But I...
I can't do
the fully stumping
and jumping
at the same time
that I'm pulling
the big old Excelsior down.
Well, you have, uh,
hidden talents
and untapped reserves
which you can call
to your aid
at this crucial time.
Are you saying
I can draw on my
higher shelf,
so to speak,
to create, perhaps,
maybe move the pots
down a little bit
to get that glow
off your nostrils?
I'm looking for people
who like to draw.
And you can draw on
a pair of long johns
with a drop seat
made out of
miracle sheep wool
with lanolin content
higher than anything
you ever dreamed possible.
Higher than that
spectral toxicity
in my blood.
Jesus,
I'm not sure
what you're talking about.
that's a great world
we're looking forward to.
I guess I used
the wrong name for Dobbs.
It's a wonderful world
we're looking forward to.
A brave kind.
Yes, that's right.
Uh, why should the Malaysians
have all the fun
of Dobbstown?
We're going to bring
the Dobbs struggle
back to these shores.
Dobbstown.
Build your own Dobbstown.
Look at India.
Look at all the
many, many, many,
many millions of people
working for one penny a week.
Why not Dobbstown
where they get
one penny a year?
They're toiling
in our offshore corporation
to make all sorts
of tchotchkes
for the subgenius
swag table.
These little kids
are paid in cigarettes
and chocolate.
Yes, we coat
the cigarettes
in chocolate
and serve them.
It saves time that way.
You get nicotine
and caffeine,
two of the basic
food groups.
And some hardworking
little kids
there in that
Dobbstown factory.
And what people
don't realize...
They turn their noses
pressed against
the cafeteria window
while we wolf down
our executive luncheon.
Mmm, eat the hell
out of it.
They certainly
don't realize
that we're doing
a good work
and a good job
for the Council
of Foreign Relations
and all these other
people who want
to reduce the world's
population.
They are going to get
what we have
sooner or later,
a square meal
and a square deal
for each and every one
of those little
wiggly characters.
And how many,
how many of those
posters of a child
crying can you stamp out?
One is good enough
to make a template.
Yes, that big-eyed
crying Bob
gives me a throb
right in the sternum.
Yes, it's removing
the blood
from the flesh
be a part of my clothes
right now.
We've got to have us
to talk, right,
right, right, right.
Oh, but I don't have
to think it over.
I can give you
an answer right now.
I don't believe in Bob.
You don't?
Of course not.
Isn't that a good idea?
Outstanding.
You have a wonderful
sense of humor, Bob.
Well.
Bob's arriving next week.
Bye!
Friends,
I had faith in Bob.
I kept up
the air.
I believed the FIB,
as we call it,
faith in Bob.
And by God,
after seeking
the hamburger
of eternal slack,
I finally got
that burger!
Yes, I did!
And friends,
I have not been,
just so you know,
I haven't just
been eating
the hamburger.
Oh, yes!
Oh, no.
I have been eating
the living,
greasy hell
out of that hamburger!
I have been eating
And it was because,
it was because
I kept up the FIB.
It really,
it was pretty close there.
But,
but we,
we made it.
And I learned something
very important
that we tend
to forget sometimes.
We get lost in,
oh,
the little trivial details
of our lives
or jobs
or our pathetic happiness.
Trivial things like that.
And we forget,
friends,
that we are
not alone.
We are not alone.
And I said
that to you
when you look
at the world,
and you see
in the world.
But,
but,
is coming! When they say Jesus is coming they just mean he's on his way. Bob is coming.
And you know the great thing about all that is? You can be alone with Bob. If you've got
Bob you really don't need anybody else.
C allowed to Pros join.
Please give over B us in your community.
Please do subscribe and hit the bell.
Maybe we can raise it for you guys and you can be a spokesperson for thiswares.th.
C Around the Board with Chris redistricting,'s
From the cell phone back row We are a bench CD entering the role with the
Accept.
Bob.
You know what I'm going to do?
I'm going to take a dump in every last call you got there.
I'm going to pee on your counter.
I'm going to do it all.
Una secrecion vaginal anormal.
Listen up.
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can be used against you in a court of law.
You have the right at this time to talk to a...
Bob.
Why did you let a turtle man in say I want to fight him?
You said you wanted to meet him.
Yeah, but that doesn't mean I want to fight him.
Hey, that's enough.
Don't act yet.
We had our problems, but we had smooth sailing after that.
And now we're here to inculcate all of you with subgenius philosophy.
As if they didn't get enough of that on this benighted station.
Well, they get it, of course, but then as soon as it enters their ears,
they start frittering it away and it dissolves.
And it...
It dilates.
Until finally there's nothing but a swirling mist of sophistry.
Because the actual subgenius doctrine, though solid and heavy,
is nonetheless as slippery as a pig at a greased lightning competition.
Hard to keep hold of.
And difficult to retain.
My, my, my.
Smell that bacon cooking at breakfast.
That's some slippery dogma, but it makes for a fine repast.
When you chop it up.
Smoke it.
Cook it.
Or you can hang it and it will get a little high,
but it will be more delicious and so will you be.
The yummy, yummy taste of the knowledge teat.
Surrounded in rich creamery butter.
The wisdom teat.
I'm on a wisdom drip myself.
The wisdom IV drip.
Must be controlled very carefully because it's...
It's a dangerous controlled substance, actually.
What is the spirit of man that goeth upwards
and the spirit of the beast which goeth downward to the earth?
And do snakes suck the udders of milk cows in the springtime?
These and other questions will be answered later on in our program,
but you're going to have to keep listening.
And we hope that you'll ask us questions by calling in the special call number.
Skis.
Best.
Three, five.
No.
Questions which require an answer.
And now you can bring closure, as they say, and receive that answer.
So please don't hang back or be coy or modest.
Simply call.
It's just like that number you see written on the inside of a bathroom stall, you know, for a good time.
Or the one you see on the inside of your eyelids in letters of fire.
It doesn't matter as long as you actually act and call the number.
Don't hang back and think about how much fun it would be if you did.
For a good time, call J.R. Bob Dodds.
1-888-669-2323.
Did you say Dodds?
Is that actually a real number?
Yes, that is a real number, actually.
As a matter of fact, if you were to call that number, 888-669-2323, you might wake up Jesus.
Yes, Jesus is at the end of that number.
Wow.
888-669-2323.
Israel shall neither slumber nor sleep.
I wonder if...
Jesus does snooze at the end of the day.
That line.
Either Jesus or Magdalene would...
Actually, they'll probably let the message machine pick it up.
They'll be lying there snoring.
Looks like...
They're not going to pick it up.
Oh, oh, oh, what?
Sorry, friend, sorry.
That was...
When Dr. Howell was in town, we invaded the show at WCSB Cleveland of Dr. Sinister.
His show called Synesthesia, which follows Hour of Slack on WCSB.
As Cleveland listeners would surely know.
Friends, yes, and we've also heard some great cut-ups by Fernanda Nande-Limor.
Lots more of those coming, too.
But first, a word from our sponsor.
The World Helpful Health Information Service invites you to consider direct head-to-head contact with an infected person.
It seems that we are suddenly living...
We're living in a more frightening world with terrible events happening around us every day.
If we're not hearing about or experiencing another homeless person under a bridge,
or even more distressing to most of us, cretinisms in the streets of our neighborhoods,
what causes that?
There are a variety of causes, ranging all the way from toddlers, on the one hand, to things that live in the sea.
The most common cause, however, is a diet low in valium.
So, to summarize, you may not be able to control the evil head lice that your child experiences.
And programs already exist in most countries to allow it to happen.
There is now an international drive to burrow into the scalp and cause psychological disease.
At this point in the proceedings, it is my privilege and my great honor...
to bring to the stage one who you have all thirsted to see, Reverend Nikki Death Chick.
Yes, you know that there are many, many rituals within the Church of the Subgenius,
and one of the greatest and least performed is the Death Chick Spanking Ritual,
which I have come here from a great distance to perform for you tonight.
Now, you know that the conspiracy, they...
many of you here, you don't follow the conspiracy, you don't believe in the things that they have to say,
but they put their guilt demons into you, whether you like it or not,
and you cannot get rid of them except for the very special rituals that we have for you.
Now, of course, you know that the things that you do that give you slack,
the conspiracy says that they're bad on a lot of occasions.
They say that they're very bad.
Now, you know that they're very bad.
And of course, this is true.
I want you to know tonight that the conspiracy is right, okay?
But what they don't tell you is that the things that you love that give you slack,
that they tell you that are bad, they're bad for the conspiracy.
They're not bad for you.
Woo-hoo!
You know that's true.
So I've come here tonight to perform the spanking ritual for you because when they put their guilt demons into you,
you know, it's my personal belief that the guilt demons, they reside in your ass.
And through this ritual, whereas you come up here and I spank you,
the guilt demons will come out of your ass and you'll be free to go forth and slack and sin again.
I need people to come up.
Come on up.
Come up for your...
All right.
Woo!
What's your name?
Princess Nez.
Princess Nez?
Oh, that's very good.
Okay, I need you to assume the position on the pulpit.
All right.
What is it that you have done that the conspiracy guilt demons played your ass?
Oh, I fuck and I fuck and I fuck some more.
And that gives you slack?
Yeah!
Oh, yeah.
And the conspiracy says it's bad.
You know what's bad?
The conspiracy, but it's not bad for you.
Hell yeah.
All right, here we go.
All right, Ellie.
Woo!
I feel those guilt demons coming out of your ass.
What do you feel?
I feel great.
All right.
Woo!
I get into this shit.
All right, do you feel it?
Do you feel it?
You have been healed, boys.
The power of the spaggy ritual tonight.
I have.
All right, you've been healed.
Go forth and sit again.
Bravo!
Gosh, you've been really brave.
Cheers.
It's over!
All right, looks good.
Chicken.
Bob.
Fossil is a 12-year-old boy who lived with his wife and family in Varna, Bulgaria,
until about a year ago when his wife left him, taking their two children with her.
He had a flattened nose, a pouchy stomach, and thickened skin.
Soon, he developed fevers, retarded growth, and slow mental development,
and his skin and eyes turned yellow.
His skin began to bruise easily, and his abdomen became swollen.
Fossil had developed alcoholic head lice, like several other children in the village.
But that was the old world. That's so last century.
Today, here we are in technological triumph,
as the computer age has got everyone looking nervously.
Over his, her, or its shoulder.
It's silicon, Dad. There's no way out of it.
I lived there for 23 months, and believe me, when I was done, I was shot.
I was completely depleted. They took everything out of me.
You talk about gates, there's worse monsters than this fish pile.
And believe me, there's a lot of more shaking you can possibly imagine.
Whether you're transformed or transgendered,
you're going to have to make some room in your life for these little nodes.
And pretty soon, a whole jittering cloud of nanobots will take up residence,
inside yours truly, and everyone else.
That's it!
That went down.
But don't worry.
There's Amanda Fear, America's favorite transvex private eye.
You know, they're making that stuff smaller and smaller, Seamus.
They could be planting a bug that, well, it could be on a bug, if you know what I mean.
Now, when you say Seamus, do you mean like a man's name, or do you mean, you know, a private detective?
I thought you were taking the part of the spotted dick.
And so I acted accordingly.
Okay, well, we'll blend the genders and we'll go back to square.
Not another gender blender.
Yes, another!
I hate it so much.
The case of Bob.
He will not reveal his identity.
So for today, we're calling him Bob.
Bob?
Bob!
Anyway, friends, yes, I am an American weirdo,
which unfortunately is an endangered species right now,
as well as an oppressed minority.
It's called the subgenius, the most understood minority.
It takes a while to understand that.
But friends, here's the thing.
When you are a true weirdo,
you can't be normal!
You cannot!
be normal. You can
and to tell the truth
friends, when you get after a while
and many of you probably already at this
point, of course you don't want to be normal.
But then there's the
keeping the job thing, you know.
I sympathize
believe it or not.
And I learned the hard way that not only
was I never going to be able to
be normal, I couldn't even
act normal.
Not even to hold down the job.
I ended up holding down lots of
jobs for guys that were much weirder than
me. But I
couldn't even, you know, the best you
can do is to pretend to yourself
that you're acting normal
and hope you can bluff your way through
you know, the job.
As Bob said,
act like a dumb
shit and they'll treat you
as an equal.
Luckily, some of us
don't even have to act.
But
you know, really
Pope Fred mentioned
our brothers, the
mighty
mongrels of the Mormons
in Utah.
And we're in, they're in danger.
Well, they're not in danger, but we are.
Why is that? We're like
American Indians or the Amish.
It's not related.
But here's what
makes it, here's why
we're in danger.
It's hard to be
really weird.
What is weird anymore?
I remember back in the day
when you saw a man with long
hair, you'd go, wow,
look at that weird, strange man. He looks like
Wild Bill Hickok. He looks just like
a cowboy. What a weird man. Or you'd see a
big, bald-headed guy with
a mustache and tattoos all over him.
You'd go, what a weird guy. He looks just like
a pirate.
Well, I guess all those gimps
shopping at the mall
must be cowboys and pirates
then, huh?
What is a weirdo
nowadays? What is really weird?
You know, when every grandma
has tattoos and shades their head
bald. Isn't Marilyn
Manson?
You know, that was
normal back when Alice Cooper
ditched his good band.
Hey,
I know what's weird. A man
with boobs. Wouldn't that
be weird? Hell, they have parades
of men with boobs
in Dallas goddamn
Patrick.
More than once a year.
So, you know what I mean? A true
weirdo is hard to find.
And you sure
can't judge a book by its
cover. Bob can, and I
can judge a book by how many pages are
stuck together. But
you cannot tell by
look around yourself in this
crowd of subgeniuses.
And this afternoon
a whole bunch of us met at that little pub.
Well, when we first met, we were like, well,
when we first walked in, there were just a few
weirdos. But
within about half an hour, there were only
four normal people in the
room. And the rest of it was all
people with that smiling guy.
You know?
And somebody at the table
said, well, actually it was me.
I said, I feel sorry for those
normal people over there.
A more true to life subgenius
said, I don't feel
sorry for any
normal people. Oh, no.
If I could, I'd make
them undergo the
loneliest, the fear,
the anger that I did when those
villagers were chasing the
torches.
You know,
but then it occurred to me,
well, you know, here we are doing
the same thing the normals do. We're looking at these normal
looking people, assuming they're normal.
For all we know, they
just came back from Burning Man.
You know.
But
the Burning Man old time,
they quit going because
it's too normal.
You know, six flags out there now.
So friends, really, what
is a weirdo?
Somebody would say,
well, like our friend
Dr. Pissoff here
and Barbara Alien.
They don't just, you wouldn't look
twice walking down the street.
They're not wearing their underwear on their head most
of the time.
I understand there are times when they do.
But, you know,
you just cannot tell.
You can't.
A true weirdo is hard to find.
Now, there are plenty of
fuckwads and kooks running around.
Mal-aligned normals,
nerds, dips and
gims and neurotic pinks
wearing berets and shaving their
eyebrows and saying, oh, I'm an artist.
I'm weird.
I don't have a job, thanks to
my
inheritance. So I'm weird.
You know, I've read,
this entire
post-modernist book, so I'm weird.
I believe strange,
wacky, weird.
I watch television that my friends
never heard of. I'm weird.
And, uh,
friends, give me
a real weirdo, a real fanatic
who truly believes
in something totally insane.
Such as a
pipe-faced, innocuous
looking clip guy
could bring
total and ultimate
slack.
Give me someone who can truly
believe, and then believe
me out of it, because they're mostly
nuts.
Furthermore,
your idea of racial or religious hatred
is the cornerstone of true Americanism
and must be jealously guarded
if we are to remain a band of hooded terrorists.
Yes. Assuring to us all,
the illegal government by primitive violence
and the pursuit of happiness.
As Abraham Lincoln said,
this nation may as well abandon its constitution,
forget its bill of rights,
tear down its courts of justice,
plant the seeds of despotism
which God has planted in us,
and revert to the barbarism of government by citizens.
Um, uh,
I know, I know.
If only we could bring this
special understanding to so many
of our citizens who
unknowing are searching in the dark
and thirsting for it.
But these early days, Stang,
is Stang counseled for us as he used it to bring them
the message?
I don't know if this is still valid in today's world of modern times.
Well, the first Stangian
orthodox fist temple
of whatever it is, is standing
by to leech away
your vital essence and turn it
into solid blocks of
subgenius understanding.
Slack comes from the barrel
of a gun, Dave.
The slag gun.
Looks like one of these.
I bet you wish you had one of these.
Slag guns like this one, see?
Yeah.
Pretty sharp, huh?
I can smell your guys' pineal glands
all the way from out here,
50 miles away.
Oh, I guess that's me.
I can smell crackling and burning
like a big forest fire out there in the west.
I'm slightly embarrassed.
I'm not.
I'm just in such an awe
because I wanted you guys to explain
Dobbs Town and the good works
and because it faded out
as I began to
transflux.
Well, you know, we practice acubating
and opening of the
third nostril
to all inductees,
but that's just at the first
few weeks of big boot camp.
Afterwards comes
hell month.
Now, the legends
and rumors about the balls
and vice grips and the hazings,
that's a bunch of propaganda
from the experts.
That's right.
It's not nearly so hard.
Benny, enjoy it.
And they come back again and again
to retake our slinky
subgenius seminars.
Well, sadly, some of the propaganda
is being recirculated by various
sectors of the Church of the Subgenius itself.
But I wouldn't ask you to direct yourself
to that.
They're in the pockets of Time Warner
Clear Channel and the Saturday Evening Post.
They're everywhere.
That's right.
Just like the carpet under your feet
or the nails at the end of your fingers.
Your little tinfoil helmet
ain't gonna keep them out.
Yes, pyramids won't do it.
But my tinfoil helmet has worked
for an awful lot of the evil things
you've tried to do, you know, playing with my mind
and stuff.
It has helped.
You have to remember that.
You have a self-destruct button
like our helmets do.
Well, that's another thing in the hierarchy.
How come you guys got better technology
than the rest of us?
Well, we were there when they passed out the beans.
Hmm.
You mean the multicolored beans?
Well, you plant them in the backyard
at the full of the moon.
Should we be giving away this information?
I think...
Nobody's listening.
All right.
Well, it doesn't matter.
You cast your beans
on the fertile earth,
and the next day,
there's a humongous big piece of crabgrass
out there with your name on it.
Now, um,
I wouldn't give these special things to...
This is Arnold.
Go see my new movie, Terminator 3,
and please go vote for me, please.
Now we see your listener-censored radio
and still being interrupted
by public service announcements.
That was...
...NPR affiliate.
Oh, that's very annoying.
That etches out the inside of your ears.
Here we go.
But I think...
I think it's a form of cosmic relief
for the whole rest of the evacuation,
you know, middaging.
You guys have been sputin' out.
I mean, some of it's right on the money,
but the rest of it is just to take your money.
Well, you don't know what to say about that.
You can't make an omelet without breaking a few eggs.
Well, you're like cracking skulls, buddy.
You can't control every aspect
of the way this is developed and promulgated?
I'm with you 100%.
It's just that, you know,
I have the eyes to see and the ears to hear it,
you know, like they used to say in the old...
And now you're looking through a glass darkly.
Get some Windex and get a better view.
I've got 360 vision, man.
That's the best part of these helmets.
I mean, I'm not saying it's keeping out
all the bad vibes you guys are sending right now
or anything, but I can still see behind my head.
And you can see in the dark
without searching blindly in the dark.
That's correct.
And it's been very, very valuable
for so many members of my family
who keep losing me daily,
especially, you know, after the sun goes down.
They should let their fingers,
do the walking up your spine.
Yeah, I knew you were going to talk about
doing that stuff to my spine again.
Don't, you know, don't...
I'm not going to forget it.
Let's just put it that way.
You've got to release the Kundalini energy, see?
There are 33 little bumps here,
and after each one is tweaked,
you'll feel like a new being.
Yeah, I have felt like a new being before.
It hasn't done me any good.
Well, you just don't have faith.
You've got to have faith.
And faith will move mountains and molehills, too.
Every day, a new personality.
Every time I wake up,
a completely new, different history.
I'm getting really, really, you know...
Your name is Legion.
You have a hundred zip codes.
Have faith and eat more prunes, Dave.
Well, I'll give that a try,
but no more of the Satanist hobo stuff.
You know, my name is Legion and everything.
My name's not Legion.
That sounds, you know...
Well, not most of the time.
Let's take that other call there.
Oh.
The L stands for Lumbar.
Uh...
Or...
Converter Brace.
Hey, uh, Dan, Jack, and Jim, go over to see Tim.
Dan, Jack, and Jim, go over to see Tim.
Can I go...
Can I borrow a toothbrush to clean my shoes?
You know, once you guys like to buy a bottle of long water...
This isn't a lending library.
Hello?
No.
Why do they all want special privileges?
They all do.
You know, and after all the years
that I've been sucking up to you guys and stuff,
how many have I got?
Three.
Well, you see, uh...
Those who...
do don't receive the benefits,
and this is very ironic,
of those who simply lap up the cream.
See, back to perplexation again.
This Buddhist-type stuff,
if I seek it, I will not find it.
If I sit down, I take a nap,
maybe it'll happen, and et cetera, you know.
I...
I don't know.
I do lose my faith once in a while.
You just gotta sit under that fig tree and, uh...
concentrate on the eternal infinite.
Okay.
But what does that really mean?
Well, it means that there is a universe of emptiness inside you.
Oh, man.
Now, that's not what I feel when I'm sticking my hand down there.
Well, what?
You got an amusement park inside?
What?
No, but I have a lot of misdirected hairs and calloused parts.
College radio.
And my name is actually Legion, not Legion.
I got scars the size of a San Diego freeway.
Why don't you put a Band-Aid on that sucker?
That's unsightly.
Our listeners aren't interested in your...
your wounds and, uh...
Oh, my gosh.
He needs to drink lots and lots and lots of aloe vera juice, Dave.
I've suffered these wounds for Bob Dobbs.
Much in the same way...
He can feel the inside of you.
You know, I'll tell you one thing, Dave,
as long as we're talking here, man-to-man.
Chicks dig scars.
You know what I'm talking about?
Yeah.
So those lumps and wounds, lesions,
things that you're talking about,
they... they, uh...
they help you along a lot.
They're chick magnets.
Yeah, exactly.
Just like you're on your refrigerator.
So, uh, buck up and, uh,
pull yourself together.
Uh, things aren't as bad as they seem,
and it's always darkest
just before it goes completely pitch black.
Ah.
Yeah, well...
Now I'm settling in.
It seems I'm...
Yeah, you don't want that to happen.
...sunk up to the knee,
so what's happening to the floor?
Well, I...
We didn't want to explain this to you earlier, Dr. Hall,
but, uh...
It's like hardening rubber.
Once your knees begin to settle
and your molecules are assuming
the strength of the skin,
the shape of the chair you're in,
it's just one of the many luxuries
and little daffodil ding-dongs
we've got here out of the subterranean...
It's too organic for me.
Well, yeah, of course it's organic,
but you are, too.
You know what I'm saying?
Yes, well, I...
Some of us think,
and I'm one of them,
that these nanobots have gone too far.
Ah, yeah, but enough thinking.
The old world used to be more cohesive.
Things didn't just melt and flow and fall apart.
Yes, of course they didn't,
but you do too much thinking,
and this is the way it things.
You're too stiff, dude.
Listen to the hat man.
He's here for your protection and benefit.
All right, all right.
I'll, uh, uh, uh...
The flow of your genius must be lax, man.
Do as he says.
The flow of your hemisnapper,
whatever he said.
Just pay attention
and keep your eyes firmly
on the monitor screen.
It all started years ago
when they started manufacturing Play-Doh,
that amorphous glop,
and soon the entire nuosphere
became contaminated with the idea.
Silly party!
Yeah, and the idea got so damn big,
and everybody else got so small,
there was no room left for any of us.
We had to move.
Starting with a little ball
that you could roll against a pud comic
from around a piece of bubblegum
and lift up the image
to the worst tyranny ever known
in the history of the human race.
Now I stamp his face on your newspaper.
But that was nothing to what things
came out of the sea caves of Creek Hill.
Ahem.
Yes.
Never.
Or write to the church in Austin, Texas
for free information
at P.O. Box 204206,
Austin, Texas, 78720.
Friends,
there's a new devival coming up in Detroit.
Yes!
Detroit!
At the Magic Stick in Detroit
on November 29th.
Subgenius Devival
with the Amino Acids.
And now,
let's see what these guys
you're up to.
Cleveland?
Yeah, Cleveland. How about Cleveland?
Cleveland? Okay.
Okay. Cleveland
has been cancelled until further notice.
Sure. It's a nice town.
Yeah, but...
It looks like you've traveled around the Earth and
I've traveled far to be here,
that's no lie. But you are the
conductor of the train itself.
I do nothing but my own
business.
Ah, yes, you are
the conductor of the train
of consciousness. You have your ticket?
I have no need
of tickets. Well, you can buy
a ticket on the train, but it's gonna cost you.
I'm telling you, I'm not buying. I have
no need of a ticket. I...
Well, that was the
last we saw him. I think they hung
him up on the mail hook as the
train went by, and the whole
story all goes to prove
you've got to be prepared when you're
riding mass transit.
Be it the old method of a train
or the modern method of a
teleportation pod, it's all
the same. But, of course,
lonesome cowboy Dave bounced back from that
one, and today, he's hail and hearty
as ever. Why, uh...
I've lost a little bit of weight, though.
I've lost a little bit of weight. Not too much,
just enough. Well, it looks
ravishing. There's a lot more blue
in the eye shadow now.
I mean, there's not more
blue things in it. It's just a little bit more bluish
color. And, of course,
you know, I wouldn't think you could
get away with checks with stripes like
that, but it's simply a divine ensemble.
Wait, cowboy hat on top and
until next week.
Is that E.L.Y.? Or is
your hat head actually light?
Hats on tight.
The world is
crumbling. Back to when?
Where is the revival? The Indiana
revival?
Yeah.
I hate you.
Good night.
I say.
All right.
Good night.
This is a conspiracy!
Fine. Now buzz off.
All right.