These aren't men, some are right, and I think we better watch out, watch out, watch out, watch out, watch out, watch out, watch out, watch out, watch out.
Dear friends, it's KNON 89.3 FM in Dallas, Texas.
And, uh, I was thinking to myself, well, praise Bob.
I guess the kids have learned to think faster due to television commercials, MTV, and such like, a heavy, fast hour of slack.
It was a 20-foot slender and incredibly fast subgenius.
Oh.
That looks very inviting, Mr. Hobbs.
Well, why don't you take a bite?
A bite?
I got a little lick.
The gaping mouth was almost on me when...
Oh, take it deeper.
Oh, yeah, that's it.
Keep like that?
Yeah.
Rub your tongue underneath the head.
Oh.
I hope he swallows it.
He'll be back tonight in our dreams.
Enjoy this one.
Tell me about it.
Tell me what you like.
Oh, it is so good.
But I don't think he liked the way you taste it.
Sounds primitive, doesn't it?
Really?
We're all primitive deep down, Pete.
What?
What's your rhyme?
I don't know why not master it.
Sounds primitive, doesn't it?
I know this will sound funny to a scientist.
I can't say.
Okay.
And now, this.
That thing's still running.
What do we got here?
Oh.
Oh, wow.
I mean, like, you know, it's time for the...
I just had it.
Oh, wow.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
The Gottlieb.
No.
Ginsberg.
Yeah, wow.
That's a Ginsberg moment.
Like, I keep trying to think back, you know,
and I can't really get it sometimes.
It's kind of confusing.
But I remember, occasionally...
And today we...
Oh, I'm sorry.
Are you on?
Yeah, I think I'm on.
Wow, man.
Like, what's happening?
May I sit down here?
Are you the DJ, sir?
Yeah, wow, man.
What do you want?
I feel as if I'm flashing back.
No, man, it's me that's flashing back.
What are you doing?
Who are you?
My name is Tyer Biter.
Someone asked me if I would come today
to help you on your radio program,
but they didn't say that...
Your eyes would be so strange.
Oh, wow, deja vu.
I'm telling you, hey.
Tyer Biter.
Oh, wow, man.
I've heard that before.
Who is...
Vice President?
No, no, no.
Let me see.
Wow, man.
You want a Coke or...
No, I gave up Coke a long time ago.
I'm sorry.
This is 1989.
Wait, I know.
I remember.
Oh, wow.
Wow, you're the girl delighter.
Well, yes, I was in my youth.
I'm very happy that you remember this moment.
Yes, exactly.
I haven't heard your voice since 19 and...
Oh, wow, I don't know, 67?
Judging by your look, sir,
I don't think you've heard much of anything since 1967.
Well, I mean, hey, you know,
I mean, we've got priorities here, you know?
I mean, wow, it's just...
Well, what are you doing here?
Well, I'm in town to promote a film,
and someone said it would be good for me
to come on this radio station
and help you with your contest of some sort today.
I am fully ignorant and rather damp at the moment,
so why don't you go on with a Judge Crater moment?
Well, we should get along great, man,
because I've been ignorant for years, you know.
Yes.
But, yeah, yeah, I've got a song here.
I want to play it for everybody,
and then we can talk, you know, later on.
Wonderful.
Well, I'll just sit back and enjoy myself
and flash into your past.
¶¶
Now, you know, they asked me to be a guest host
on the Johnny Carson show, but I had to turn it down.
Why was that, Clem?
They wanted our people to supply the nitrous oxide
for Ed McMahon.
¶¶
That could have been a good horn, but you just blew it.
I'm beginning to move it. With 53 stitches in it, it's not about to fall off.
Will somebody fill me in? I offered.
Right in the face, and a bright flash circled him, and he seemed to stiffen.
And when he started to Fish up, it made him quite fetqiud.
Stand up!
Father, be civil!
I know you bothered, but look.
As each of you bus get a photo, each of them has to serve two characters.
Aead gives him the postcard in which the inexperienced questioner leaves the board,
and the rest, those two men go home.
any minute now.
Oh, actually,
they told us
10 o'clock.
Oh, he would love that.
There's been quite a bit
of kill Stang sentiment
in the air here lately.
Hey, Will,
is this going to be
another scripted revival
where they read off
a script that they've
written?
No.
No, not now.
Wait, what was that?
In the spring,
the FFB read some...
Maybe I wasn't here
or maybe I forgot.
You were here.
It was all scripted?
Yeah, we read some script
he had that he said
he'd done at every convention
for the last year.
I know, I've heard
the tapes on the other side.
I know, I know.
It's the exact same thing.
And then you read the book
and it's the exact same.
Oh, well.
The only good thing
is when Bob fell off the wall
and everyone screamed
and died.
But now, wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
The next one.
We're trying to suppress
the church's really
obscenely swollen name
in Arlington.
The one with Dr. Don.
Dr. Don?
Dr. Don,
the one who wrote that one.
It's in a house
filled with...
We're going to have
Let's all have
a revival.
The one who published
The Ideology of Madness.
I'm sorry,
what's that you're
talking about?
I don't even hate Sting.
He's mediocre.
He's worse than
a figure of paper.
Not worth hating.
Not worth even hating.
He's mediocre.
There's both of them.
It's the Fallen Bob's.
Oh my God,
my head broke open.
There's something
sticking out of it.
I never got any ones.
It wouldn't be a pipe,
would it?
It's a gland.
It's a big old new
hole.
Look at the tape.
Turn around.
Go back down
back the way you came.
Babylon is laid to waste.
Egypt's buried in Hashem.
The mighty men are all
beaten down.
Their kings are falling
in the waves.
Eat God.
Pride of man.
Broken in the dust again.
When the grand
Jarmagal all-star
belt was harrowly the rage
between our Weltington's
extraordinary and our petty
thick's the Marshalazy,
and Irish eyes of welcome
were smiling daggers down
their backs.
Yeah.
Daggers down our backs.
You thought I wasn't
listening, didn't you?
See, rest of listeners,
a little bit of that was just
to let those who were at the
Fantasy Fair subgenius revival
two weeks ago who were there
and thinking that the ears of
Reverend Stang and by virtue of
my placement in the church,
the ears of Bob, too,
weren't listening.
I'm not saying that they
weren't listening, but see,
we were listening, all right.
Yeah, always listening.
He records everything and puts
it in the movie.
Yes, that's, so that's, yeah,
that's what we do, friends.
That's the, just before the
revival starts, during the,
well, we've got 45 minutes of
show left, and which means
we'll be peaking about 20
minutes from now.
So, and we will be playing the
first half of the Fantasy Fair
revival, edited version, of
course.
Hopefully you'll be able to
tell where the edits are.
I like to edit that kind of
stuff in such a way as to bring
attention to the fact that
something was cut out and
usually with just enough left
in that you can tell what it
was.
Anyway, we've also got, well,
we've got a second generation
guest in our studio.
Praise Bob!
Reverend George Leroy
Tirebiter.
But, actually, first generation
here in the studio, the man who
brought George Tirebiter to St.
Louis, where the tape was made.
Oh, it's a heavy responsibility.
We've got Chuck, the Doge of
South St. Louis.
Why didn't you just, you could
have picked all of Missouri.
No, I'm modest.
We're modest to a fault.
I'm modest to a fault.
That is a fault.
That's a, not all of you.
Well, it's a divine fault.
Dr. Philo Drummond certainly
isn't.
See, what's happened here dear
friends.
What?
At the expense of the
taxpayers.
That's, no, K-N-O-N is not at
the expense of the taxpayers and
neither is K-D-H-X-F-M in St.
Louis.
Yes, it is.
Oh, it is?
Yes, of course.
We take government money.
We'll take anybody's money.
Well, I guess, I guess K-N-O-N
must surely take some government
money.
We're a public radio.
We'll take money any way we can
get it.
Crumpled singles, we don't care.
That's right.
Oh, yeah, it's an NPR affiliate,
right?
No, no, we're not.
We're sort of a kind of Pacifica
affiliate, sort of more or less
halfway.
Commies, man, I get it.
That's right.
Not like K-N-O-N.
Oh, no.
Anyway, and Doge Chuck here has,
has just sort of handed a, can you
believe this?
Give me a second.
I'm going to get this.
This guy standing here actually told
Dr. Philo Drummond and the rest of the
Swingin' Love Corpses, hey, why don't we
do a show together?
Yeah.
My father's got a barn.
I've got a mustache.
I'll be the old man.
Yeah, that's right.
We'll have to, we'll be getting tapes,
I guess, of that show.
And see now I can.
We aim to see that you do, yes.
And then I'll be sending tapes to you
and then they'll get played over.
And then they'll get played over again
about a month later.
It's all part of the conspiracy,
friends.
Yes.
Bob, Bob is in us and with us and
under us and in our toothpaste.
And you can smell him all the time.
That's right.
But we're working on that.
We've got deodorizers all over the
friggin' station at KDHX.
Hey, you can't say frigging on the radio.
Isn't that a nautical term?
I thought that was okay.
Oh, okay.
Oh, you're talking about what first
mate Bob had to say about that.
Actually, I ought to, you know, I can.
Hype my boy.
I'm going to get a more jump from,
uh, let's see, yeah, side one.
The Reverend Ivan Stang is now
quickly queuing up a record.
Let's see.
He was in the rigging.
Uh, actually, yeah, now we've got two things.
I can have two going at once.
We've got, wow, this is like artistic
mixing on underground pirate radio stations.
Like, this is like psychedelic, man.
Yeah, where you have, you have Finnegan's
White going on one side and Fergie's
White going on the other.
Oh, it's like four out now.
Kansas was condensed.
I've anchored my soul in the haven of rest.
Oh, wow, it's like, like, like I'm having
a religious experience.
Ahoy there, shipmate.
Eight bells and all's well.
First mate Bob and the crew of the good ship, Grace.
The voices from the harbor called Haven of Rest.
I'm told that everybody likes a story.
Every life is a story.
And mine is no exception.
May I share it with you?
No.
The story of my conversion to Christ in 1934.
First mate Bob.
And I shall begin the narration.
See, what that's about is first you have to mate Bob,
and then you can have the conversion.
That's right.
It is a sexual religious experience.
Religio-sexual.
And that's what the Church of the Subgenius was supposed to be all about.
That's right.
Yeah, but then they put us in this little room with these microphones,
and ever since then we haven't been able to talk about what you really want to hear.
And in fact, I understand that some of the tapes I've sent you had objectionable language of some kind on them?
Well, I think, as I understand it, the conspiracy inserted that objectionable language
while the tapes went through the U.S. mail, because after all, that is a governmental agency,
and of course we all know who's behind it.
I understand that.
Well, you do, do you?
Well, I do.
Don't you?
I would never say I knew what was behind the government.
I wouldn't even want to really know.
I mean, a few stages of conspiracy end, sure,
but I don't want to see behind that vault in Rockefeller Center.
We joked about going behind that vault door, but we didn't.
Nobody but Bob has been back there.
I know.
Bob could.
Maybe Dr. Philodrumon, because of the operation, might be able to go through the screen.
You're right. It is scary.
I mean, George Bush only got to the first porthole, and look what happened to him.
Yeah, that's a good point.
Oh, gosh, I read in the paper today that a television official was talking to Quayle about,
oh, Czechoslovakia, yeah.
He was going, well, what do you think about what's going on in Czechoslovakia?
And Quayle said, what?
And the guy said, well, they just completely changed governments over there this week.
And Quayle just got a glazed look in his eye and said, oh.
Well, you see, the problem was that Quayle's handlers hadn't inserted the proper compact disc.
You see, let alone the fact that he really doesn't have a brain.
There is a very sophisticated laser compact disc player there.
But he's an elected official.
Well, not really elected, I guess.
Sort of.
I mean, it was part of a package deal.
Isn't that always the way it works?
Yeah.
Well, I wouldn't want to joke about the kind of votes that Bush would have to get in order to make Lyndon Johnson president.
Now would I?
We'll be playing Jack Ruby's Girls by the Potatoes a little later on if we get down to it.
All right.
But let's go back to what really happened in St. Louis that day.
None other than the president.
The old, the living codger, George Leroy Tirebiter.
Himself.
Do you want to say anything more about how that came about?
How he came there?
Well, it's actually, I see, I don't know how much you've got on the tape.
The reason he was in town was to promote the new colorized version of his film, Babes in Khaki.
Yeah.
Which many of you have heard excerpts from on an album of cultural archival stuff.
The Don't Crush That Dwarf Hand.
It's on a record label, God与 dir deerts.
That's the outdo briefing version.
Except, I have members of Texas future ..
.
n cust NSF, and South Bay.
Q hajaq 0663.
Ab Mtla eternalia olsun, where I am.
And to be straight and clear!
It was a special feature.
Caa!
O-رو arx.
Arxvilleau karWaitis des Landus.
Aes prazo Bran, sthawas.
Allow me to say something about undefended, braw Cortierign.
Sorry?
I just can't stand people that willkell St. Louis.
I manufacturize magical to Earth.
The PR monograph that зап zugров is B Councillor genres.
And you know it!
It'll help with the
Thank you.
Shout a warning to the nation
That the sword of God is raised
In Babylon, that's my history
Rich in treasure, wise in fame
Oh God, pride of man
Broken in the dust again
Yeah!
I first heard this song by Quicksilver Messenger Service
live at a show
a long, long time ago.
When I was at that concert, I think that was when I tried marijuana
for the first time, and that was the last thing I remember
until just now, sitting in this radio station.
Oh, wow.
And it shall cause your tower to fall
Make of you a pyre of flame
Oh, you who dwell on many waters
Rich in treasure, wise in fame
You bow unto your God of gold
Your pride of might shall be your shame
For only God can lead his people
To the glory of his glory
Back unto the earth again
Oh God, pride of man
Broken in the dust again
Thy holy mountain be restored
And by the sea of thy people
Thy people, Lord
Thy water in me
Thou dost name
Thou and I
Thy brother
Thy Sovereign
The Holy Spirit
Eternal King
The West
Above theOf
Every city
Lord
Land on earth
Lived on earth
Praise the Lord
This prophet
That's right.
Charles is here.
He's going to tell you about what's coming up here.
And I'd like to, because this is,
some of you folks may have recognized the voice
that helped introduce the Ginsburg moment.
Yes, it's none other than the Hollywood legend himself,
George Leroy, tire-biter.
George, welcome to St. Louis.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Privilege.
Great pleasure to be here on this rainy, rainy weekend.
It is that.
I want to let everybody know a little bit about George.
Of course, as you know, he was born in 1922 in Chicago, Illinois,
and just likes to think of himself as just an average North American.
I think it's great.
George, of course, a veteran of the radio and vaudeville,
where he made such a name for himself as the comic Croatian in Only a Plate,
and is well known for his radio scripts,
including, of course, the famous Anytown USA and Phone Trouble,
which I believe was later made into a film, was it not?
Oh, yes, Phone Trouble.
Yes, indeed.
That was a radio drama, one-woman radio,
and then ultimately we made it into a much larger film
with at least 20 or 30 people.
That was when Smell-O-Vision was employed in that.
Yeah, you were Scratch.
It was Scratch-O-Vision.
Scratch and Sniff.
Yes, Scratch and Sniff.
Yes, exactly.
First Scratch and Sniff movie.
I remember that because the ads for it would mention that.
The audience would often say,
Four, do four, you know,
and someone would scratch four in the back
and realize he'd been terribly hoaxed.
A number of people got employment out of that, though,
as scratchers in the theaters, did they not?
Well, not as many as sniffers,
but I believe we will discuss the subject of scratchers and sniffers
slightly later on.
That's right.
That's true.
Well, at any rate, of course, since 1968, George,
as everybody knows, you've made your home in Shenzhou, Japan,
which is the center of country eastern music,
produced a number of albums there,
and of course you're best known there
as the man behind the popular mystery series
Young Guy, Atomic Detective.
Young Guy, Young Guy.
Yes.
Isn't that also where Agar Agar comes from?
He's the star of Young Guy.
Oh, yeah, he's the John Agar's brother.
John Canassos-looking person.
Yes, exactly.
But maybe less known, of course,
is that you frequently appear on the show
as Dr. Toto, the clockwork fiend,
Young Guy's chief nemesis.
He's a nemesis, yes.
And, of course, in this country,
folks will recognize you from your numerous appearances
on Beat the Reaper and Stop That Tune
and, of course, Hawaiian Sellout.
Yes, indeed.
I want to hear about this new movie.
What is this?
What is the new movie?
Well, this is actually a new movie.
My publicity has been handed about, hasn't it?
Yes, it has.
Talking all about Babes in Khaki.
Babes in Khaki, a wonderful, wonderful motion picture
that has lain under dust in the archives
of the paranoid pictures.
You know, Paranoid went out of business,
sold its entire studios,
gave away all of its props,
kept a few films,
and we have been able, Ted Turner and I,
to get these films out of the paranoid vaults.
And I'm especially happy
that Ted has decided to colorize Babes in Khaki.
Well, now, I read that, and I just have a question.
When you colorize Khaki, don't you still get khaki?
Well, but you get a better grade of khaki.
I didn't know that I was going to come here to be made fun of.
Well, no, no, no.
I just wanted to clarify some things for our listeners here.
You know, they need to know all the facts.
Well, the original motion picture was made in sepia,
which was as close as we could get to khaki at the time.
Now we have a delicate balance of khaki tones,
which are provided entirely electronically,
a complete range of khakis,
from the wafts and the waves and the whacks, of course,
to the military men of the time.
Each, you understand, wore a different kind of khaki.
Pink, for example, a pink khaki.
Pink.
Pink khaki, yeah.
Yes, indeed.
And then there was the gray and salt and pepper khakis,
which were worn by the officers.
I see.
And the puce khaki.
I beg your pardon?
The puce khaki.
Puce khaki, yes.
I thought the Women's Army Corps wore wacky khaki.
Wasn't that what they would be?
I didn't know I was going to be made fun of.
I thought that was a historical fact.
You slacky.
Well.
It's a much more beautiful motion picture.
The battle scenes, the wonderful dance numbers,
the
This is a real period piece, though.
I mean, it's been in the vault since the war.
Since the war, right?
1942.
This was one of those great morale raisers
to get everyone in America behind the war effort to hate those
By bombs.
Bonds.
nasty nips and those, you know,
the people were all quite, you know, as it were, in bed with.
And it was a great star vehicle for Lily Lamont, was it not?
Yes, my wife at the time,
she was a somewhat older woman than I was.
I was a very young man when I made this film.
Twenty-two.
Twenty-two years.
Twenty-one, perhaps, around my birthday.
And Lily was a few years older.
Lily had been a great star of a certain kind of vaudeville.
Perhaps those of you who read her book, Taking It All Off,
will remember that she was one of the great burlesque stars of late 1920s.
That was hardbound, wasn't it?
Yes, never released in paper back.
Yes.
It was quite stiffly bound, as I recall.
It was indeed.
That's what I've heard.
That later became the basis for a famous Broadway musical, did it not?
As I recall, it lasted like one night, something like that.
Tremendous amount of money went.
Actually, I had nothing to do with the Broadway musical version of Babes in Khaki.
No.
The project was purchased from Paranoid Pictures.
Of course, I received not one red cent,
not even one all-American red, white, and blue cent for this.
And unfortunately, or fortunately, it didn't last.
I was very happy to see it flop-a-roo, I can tell you.
Well, I think perhaps we should move on to the Book of Lists, because...
No, no, not yet. Not exactly.
Because we have to play the carts.
Do you have to play the carts on the St. Louis show?
Well, of course, I'm sorry.
We, of course, don't have carts.
At St. Louis, we always believe in putting the horse before the cart.
You know that I didn't go to the cart.
Well, I thought I was going to go to the cart.
Well, we pull it out and shove it in again.
Collectors Records would like to thank K&ON by sponsoring this program.
For more information, Collectors Records can be reached at 327-33-1.
That's 327-33-1.
3313.
Oh, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho.
Yes. Yep.
Friends, you know...
Time for another healing of the tape machine.
This is a traditional thing, the battle with the 8-track carts.
I'll say, heal, heal!
And this is the new deck.
It's the visible.
You can't even get it out of there.
If you won't heal, sit up and beg.
It's not moving.
You gotta push stop.
And it won't let go!
There you go.
Oh, no.
See, it makes you...
Here in George Tirebiter, I don't know about you, but it makes me want to talk like him.
And I'm not going to do it.
No.
He's copyrighted anyway.
We can't do that.
Well, this is the underwriter cart.
And what it basically says, dear friends, is that you should...
If you know of a better way to do this, you can go to www.tirebiter.com.
And if you're a business or are a business that would like to underwrite a K-N-O-N show,
it's, uh...
Well, it's like cheap advertising, almost.
Almost.
You have to...
Because of the nature of the station, you have to kind of tweak it.
Yeah, yeah.
You kind of tweak it a bit one way or the other.
Oh, the Doge.
You've been taking lessons from the Healer of Appliances, haven't you?
Well, let's go ahead and we'll try it just for fun.
And nothing happens!
It's not easy to make nothing happen.
No, it's not.
Well, we got it out for a while there.
Well, uh...
Cassette machines can have a great deal of slack, and those are the kind that we use to make Doctors for Bob music.
Ah.
So...
Back.
Back we go.
Down again.
Gotcha.
I'm gonna spurt!
Don't you think it would be a good idea for you to turn the radio on?
Turn the machine on.
Well, it is a beautiful world out there, all right.
Take, for instance, the city of Chicago earlier this month.
It was filled to overflowing with Wookiees, Warlocks, and Japanese robots as thousands flocked to the annual World Science Fiction Convention
at the Hyatt Regency Hotel.
But at the cheaper hotel across the street, a group of people too weird for most science fiction fans to comprehend
were holding a little convention of their own.
These wackos call themselves the First Church of the Subgenius,
and they include, in their, to say the least, eccentric membership...
Bob!
Bob Bob!
Bob Bob Bob!
What do they believe in? Everything.
Who do they believe in?
A mysterious character name?
Bob.
I'm sorry I haven't time for social obligations.
There is another word.
We are not, then, alone in our battle.
It might make too much sense, but it's not intended to.
The second question is, what's happening?
Is this a miracle? What kind of a miracle?
Is this a parable? What's the point?
Is this a letter? What's the big idea? What's he trying to communicate?
My God's dead!
Sorry about yours!
Woo!
How'd you write that?
1989, Paul McBrady.
Well, well, well. What a wonderful congregation we find gathered here tonight.
Talk!
Bigger, bigger talk!
We should 35 years, big money, big bills, big money.
Now, before we all moonlight out and all the hipstop parts behind the barrel that we
are cutting in our muds, it's on a universeshacters, the big future that's going on between us
Gathered in andefense lobby, up in that example.
In the full body of that scene, they say, O IRON MAN!
You've suspected what they are doing!
Freeze!
You got the right VR in there!
Before we get going, we do have this radio ministry every Sunday night, which has been getting a might bit of criticism of late these last few months,
complaining that there weren't enough true believers from the Dallas clenches represented upon the airwaves, the great waves of Bob Dobbs.
And now's your chance! Oh, I'm sorry, take two! But it would be, uh, no, now's your chance!
To eat the gizzard of Bob!
You know, this'll be, don't worry, this'll be your chance.
To rant on the air of slack. It's real easy. Anybody can rant. You just go, one, two, three, RANT!
And then they're, ah, and then they're so good that way.
Yes, well, no, how did you do that?
Our egos are...
What? Pardon me? Say that again. Say it clearly and loud.
I said our egos are so pitifully small here in Texas that we've gotta show those Californians and those New Jerseyers
what kind of people we've got up here.
Oh, people!
You're just the man to do it. I can count.
Please let me on the air of slack!
Why do you, why do you, why do you, why do you...
Please, please, may somebody like the God-puzzling-evidence listen to us.
Well, okay, so I don't, I don't, obviously I don't have to EXPLAIN the Church of the Subgenius.
But what's it all about?
What do you like to know?
Oh, my friend, if you...
There are some things man was not meant to know.
And if, thank God, there are some things hidden from the mind of the pathetic, poor, tiny mind of man.
I, I need you to heal. I woke up yesterday morning and there was a psychic fishhook in the back of my brain being pulled on by Bob.
He said, Bob! And who is this Bob?
I didn't know who Bob was, but I found a map tattooed on my, on my very chest saying, saying, saying...
Tibet, Malaysia, Bobtown, Dobbsville.
What does it mean?
Psychophysians, visions, yetis without knowing what yetis are.
Well, I think you know just what to do about this, Joe.
Well, you take care of that.
Bob! Bob! Bob!
We get some damn good lampshades made out of those maps.
And how about that soap?
Oh, yeah, the soap.
The chocolate-covered, lontic, chili pieces. The whole deal.
Well, this isn't, uh...
This isn't a normal, uh, subgenius revival.
Uh-huh.
Of course, there... No, no.
Technically, there shouldn't...
I gotta admit it.
There should not be such a thing as a normal subgenius revival.
However, just to give you an idea of, of, uh, what has driven us to this place in this room tonight, here's...
I'll share with you...
Oh!
Well, I love the accent here.
Anyway.
Okay.
Uh, just to give you an idea of how, how far it's going.
This is...
I'm gonna share with you all, uh...
Uh, uh...
This is a typical inter-office memo within the Subgenius Foundation group.
Bob wrote it?
Okay.
Huh?
Did Bob write it?
No, no.
No.
But just to give you an idea of just how far it's gone
and why I'm doing things this way tonight,
St. Palmer Vredes of the Lies Corporation in San Francisco
wrote and sent this proposal for a subgenius motivational seminar, trademark.
Well, he says, well, how's about another Mondo brain blowout,
anus clenching, California style subgenius, trademark, show?
But hey, he says, wait a second.
Haven't the devivals, trademark, been done to death, you say?
The audiences now are just the usual bunch of pink boys, trademark,
and pink girls, trademark,
mindlessly repeating our own jokes to us
with every bit of our well-wishers.
Worn-out acts memorized.
Hell, they don't even spend enough money on our crappy dobs, trademark,
doodads and souvenirs.
Some of these aceholes even dance to the anti-music, trademark,
as if it was some kind of entertainment.
We've done this stuff so much, it's almost showbiz by now.
It's time for a change.
It's time to get tough with these scummy gimme bobs, trademark,
and chintzy po-buckers, trademark.
Okay, here's the proposed show.
Any of the following ideas are just that, ideas.
Don't worry if this sounds too crass and commercial.
Ha, that'll be the day.
Anything here can be changed, discarded, or mutated.
I'm tossing this stuff out as a starting point.
This type of subgenius, trademark, show
emphasizes the sales and business aspects of the foundation, trademark.
The revivals and devivals, trademark,
centered on the mystic and religious side of dobs.
If you will, the yuppie bob, not the new age bob.
Combine the two and we get the no age bob.
This is his idea.
It's in a holiday inn or quality court or Ramada Inn,
just like those other cult seminars.
If people come to see us in a gallery, they mistake us for artists.
If they see us in a nightclub, they think we're a rock band.
If we're on a stage, they see it as a show.
If we're in a theater, if we do it on the street, we just get arrested.
And what's worse, lose money even if we do rack up valuable dobs points, trademark.
Nobody can deny our reality in a holiday inn or a Marriott, as the case may be.
Number one, it will be expensive to rent the space.
Not to mention clearing some of the more extreme aspects,
such as loud noises, cursing, screaming, blaspheming, live sex,
gunfire,
explosives, execution, and so forth,
of the seminar, trademark, with hotel management.
This may be a major stumbling block.
Will we need insurance?
In the other shows, we were covered by already existing theater or club policies.
It will last several hours with a meal break.
Just like other seminars, we will wear the, quote, audience, unquote, down
by controlling their time and forcing them to endure
long stretches of sub, trademark, exposure,
thus smashing their will to resist.
They will become more pliant subjects for our evil purposes.
Time span at least 40 or 50 hours, maybe more,
makes anyone who attends really committed.
This will not be, quote, taking in a show, unquote.
Sure, it's hard to fill that much time up and retain their attention.
The other guys do that.
Their events last up to 24 hours.
That's what effective brainwashing is all about.
But we can use this time to make them always do as we say,
pushing their limits until they either snap or begin to resist us
the very thing we want.
No, wait a minute.
Meal break can be used to teach valuable survival lessons.
Perhaps a box lunch can be passed out.
This will force them to stay with us.
Without the relief of leaving the room.
Upon opening their box lunches, which have been referred to
either as delicious or expensive or gourmet,
in order to have raised their expectations,
they will find a piece of burnt toast,
some Cheetos or pork cracklins,
a few candy corn,
a vitamin pill, and a bottle or cup of the worst Dayglo soft drink we can find.
In short, food that looks ugly and barely passes through the eye,
but is edible and is something we obviously didn't spend a dime on.
This is what you all could be getting if we'd have charged more.
However, down with the seminar leaders and monitors at their own table,
a hot banquet is laid out, wheeled in from the kitchen.
Roast turkey, platters of pate, vegetables, whatever.
A lot more food than the show personnel can eat.
Enough, in fact, that the whole group could be fed from the table.
The crew enjoy their meal with great relish.
Any of the sub-trainees, trademark,
have to do to claim a plate of real food is to come down and take it.
Under no circumstances should anyone in the show reveal this fact to the trainees.
They must do this for themselves.
Otherwise, they'll just have to make do with their charcoal
while they watch us pig out.
This is the kind of relationship the United States has with the rest of the world.
Well, I could, I might continue, I don't know.
But we, I do know that one time at one of these conventions,
at a science fiction convention like this,
we, for some reason they put the table with the PA on one side of the room,
but the chairs were all facing the other way.
Well, Sternow, Kekever, and Dr. Snavely and I were doing the show.
We came in and everyone was sitting facing the other way.
Well, we didn't say anything.
We just wanted to see who would have the cojones, or uvulas,
to turn their chairs around and actually face us.
About half stayed with their chairs turned the other way,
with their necks like this, for an hour!
For a whole hour!
Now, can you, now can you understand
why some people don't do this?
Sometimes we don't even show up!
I understand.
The last, the last, quote,
rave session, unquote, that,
well, I had told Larry Langford I couldn't make it.
He didn't want to change the pace up in the guide to the show,
so people showed up anyway.
Well, no subgenius preachers arrived,
and yet, I understand it was a pretty good show,
nevertheless.
I mean, not even Willa Dobbs showed up to sell stuff, right?
No.
Right.
So,
I'm sure somebody showed something.
Somebody showed something and did something.
We know that.
And apparently it was, uh, okay.
So, I thought, well,
darn it, everybody's giving us a hard time about how,
oh, Reverend Stang, evil Reverend Stang,
doesn't let me come on his radio show to rap.
So, now's your chance!
I know!
You got a suas?
chance.
All right.
So, I think you right now go the radio show.
No.
We have a new roller coaster.
You know, well, is that something that we just took into the audience?
Is there anyné drawing?
All right, let's see how many of you can leave with no legs and still call it an act.
Well, you'll get an Academy Award, won't you?
Woo!
An act.
Thank you.
In the Comedy Church, they called it.
Oh, yeah, right.
In a fair number of...
What?
Five.
Well...
Yeah, thanks for the money.
To put the entire church in perspective,
those of you out there who have...
You've heard of the Scientologists, you've heard of the Moonies,
you've heard of the Holy Rollers, the Snake Handlers.
This is like all of those all rolled into one a thousand times worse,
and yet, true, with so much...
I mean, we can save that many more souls.
What about the money?
Really, now, are you guys in this cult business just for the bucks?
It's not the money, man.
It's not the money.
It's really not money.
It's the souls.
Yeah, it's not the whole, the entire soul, either.
It's just a part of your soul that's rubbed off on you.
You've got to go save it.
You've got to.
The bit of your soul which you...
The symmetry of the church.
This is a joke, but it is a very serious joke.
To you.
Now, we can...
We can either let people walk by the microphone of the show here.
This is the show.
The show exists in this little black box from Radio Shack.
It even has a little blinking light on it.
Yeah, that's called a VU meter, son.
It's like a show with a VU meter.
And when that thing's lit up all the time, that means you're talking so loud that it won't be used at all.
You can walk up and you can tell us...
You can tell us about the people you hate.
I don't mean just the people you sort of hate.
I mean the people you hate.
I hate you.
I mean that you hate not necessarily just people.
It could be corporations.
It could be political groups, if you want to really be naive.
It can be...
I mean, it could be TV shows.
Bob Dobbs himself.
It could indeed even be Bob.
But it's got to be...
I don't want to hear a bunch of fake hate.
I want to hear the real...
I mean the...
My mom was giving me the car keys last Saturday.
I hate you guys.
I hate you.
Or...
You can also walk up to the show here and describe what is slack to you.
What do you really like?
What has...
What about sexual problems?
Ever since I discovered Bob, I've been shouting Bob's name during orgasm.
Oh my God.
And I've tried everything.
I've tried lobotomy and castration.
It doesn't seem to work.
But ever since I found Bob, I've had this problem.
And I was wondering if you could give me some good lies to convince me that that's not...
That's not...
That's not really a problem.
Well, now, why is that a problem?
Well, no, I never thought about that until you mentioned it.
Remember what?
Is that a problem?
I told you.
The girl you were with was probably shouting Bob, too.
Now, when I was watching you out...
What's this?
It's a bandwagon.
How would they know?
There's such a thing as...
Well, with stereo, you get a thing called phasing.
Let me ask you this.
If the other person is saying Bob at the exact time and frequency that you are, then they'll cancel each other out.
Look, it's very, very simply...
Doesn't matter.
Let me ask you a question.
Do animals understand English?
Which animal?
Yeah, leave it.
A paramecium still.
A meep is yes.
Okay.
I mean, where do you draw the line?
What's an animal?
If cattle understand English, then I'm in deep s***.
If not...
I can promise you that cattle do not understand English.
Of course not.
I have stood in front of an entire herd of cows.
This is true.
I'm behind from it.
I've stood in front...
Yeah.
And eaten a McDonald's hamburger.
And they...
I mean, they just went on eating their grass.
I mean, by the same token, I've stood and sold subgenius pamphlets in front of pink boys on the street.
Same thing.
Same difference.
And what do they do?
Same thing.
So I won't be hearing gossip about myself in early morning farmers programs.
Huh?
I won't be hearing gossip about myself in early morning farmers programs.
I'll be hearing gossip about myself in early morning farmers programs.
You will on KM.
Don't worry.
Don't worry, boss.
You will not testify.
Even if it could talk, animals cannot testify.
Well, we...
The Church of the Subgenius is not responsible for the actions or inactions of any member
or...
Yeah.
The Holy Dominion.
Or writers or artists involved.
Well, I just want to say that I met Bob in a dark alley.
He raped me.
He took my wallet.
He left me for dead.
I am eternally grateful to him.
and I don't know why.
Praise Bob Hewlett!
Yeah!
Frankly, I wouldn't be praising Bob
if I were you.
Wait a minute, was that Bob?
Huh?
I think it was Bob.
It was me.
Worship him now!
It was him!
It was Bob!
He was the master!
He cooked the eggs with the pickles!
I had a child!
So, you know...
Is that one with the doctor?
Whoa!
Listeners, the show looks great so far.
Wish you could actually be here.
And you can also say,
as this man has already done,
stand up and give your testimonial
as to what Bob
has done for, or to, you.
Bob may well have done nothing for you
because that's what you needed.
He's waiting for you to find out
what it is you need.
All you need is slack.
Well, that's when the lady from the
filth singing group came in and
asked us if we could be quiet.
Uh, which of course we couldn't.
You know, I mean, we just flat out can't do that.
This is a church of subgenius.
It is in fact sacrilegious for us to be quiet, Reverend.
Well, except in certain situations.
I mean, we're not gonna get that...
We're not that brutal of a cult.
Now, it's fairly brutal.
We like to think, but...
We do our best, but...
There's...
There are worse things, believe it or not.
There are people who outshine us in that regard.
It's true.
Yeah, some...
This new political group here has tried to recruit us.
Is this the one that Dan Quayle belongs to?
I don't know.
I'm thinking about joining them myself.
It says here on this ad,
Had enough of Western decline?
Then turn to the American Imperial Party
for men who are ready to own the world.
Now, this is not a joke either.
That's the interesting thing here.
And here are ten reasons to vote for the American Imperial Party.
Well, that's rotten.
There are darn good reasons, too.
Number one.
Number one, executions will be rapid for vicious criminals who are already in prison.
I'm all for that.
And I'd like to be the one who defined who was a vicious criminal.
Reason number two, death squads and vigilantes will execute vicious criminals who are not in prison.
You know, save the cops some trouble.
Absolutely.
And reason number three...
They need help.
Reason number three, vengeance for honor will be permitted, even encouraged.
Lawsuits will be more frequently settled by the firm of Smith and Wesson.
I'd rather have twelve...
No, I'd rather be carried out by six than judged by twelve.
That's right.
Reason number four, to vote for the American Imperial Party.
And I don't know who the candidate is.
Oh.
But it...
Taxpaying citizens will enjoy complete privacy from journalists, advertisers, and beggars.
That's right.
I notice it doesn't mention religious groups here, so I'm all for that one so far.
And here's reason number five.
People who are sick and dishonorable and or self-destructive...
No, sick for dishonorable...
Oh, sick for dishonorable...
I'm sorry about that.
Sick for dishonorable and or self-destructive reasons get neither sympathy nor medical care.
So take that.
Well, that means...
That means dope addicts and so forth.
Yeah.
No medical care for...
Well, they're self-medicating anyway.
So it doesn't matter.
Reason number six, foreign aid will be replaced by foreign tribute.
The bribery of rug merchants will cease immediately.
Don't like what this is.
What is it?
What's the term again?
Reason number seven, American lives and property will not be subject to compromise.
Any attack, even verbal, will be answered swiftly and brutally.
That's, I mean, so much for burning flags, right?
Public bounties will be placed on terrorists.
And, of course, importantly...
Why haven't they done that already?
I don't know.
It says here, reason number eight, the American military will be tested and bloodied.
All segments of the military that do not fight or truly support fighting will be open to sacrifice.
Um...
There's human sacrifice, Baylor.
Reason number nine...
An Imperial Party president would be more than a candidate, but an actual commander.
He would not hesitate to order invasions, remove dissidents, or conduct public executions.
Now, see, all of this stuff is predicted in Book of the Subgenius way back in 1983.
You look in the Book of Bob, it's right there.
That's right.
Praise Bob.
And these things are coming, friends.
These things are coming, and there's nothing you can...
Not a thing you can do about it, except go ahead and...
If I were you...
I mean, you can't beat them, so join them.
The American Imperial Party.
Those nations which are near to us and insulting to us can finally be invaded.
That means Canada, and Mexico, Puerto Rico, this will...
Cuba!
This will require secret military bases and many small usable weapons.
Eventually, the goal of removing communism will be honored by blood.
Communism is defined as anything which stands in the way of our pleasure.
Well, Bob...
That's as good a definition of communism as I ever heard in my life.
My Bob, Reverend, I can't argue with...
Wait a minute.
No, it's not.
That's the definition of the conspiracy.
But the conspiracy is defined as anything which stands in the way of our slack.
But it's the same thing.
Well, yes and no.
Sort of.
Some get slack not from pleasure, nay, but from pain.
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
Hey, say, do that again.
Oh, yes.
Madam.
Ma'am?
Oh, yes.
Yes, but then Reverend, the pain is their pleasure.
Well, we've got to get out of here for a collector's showcase.
And just in time, too.
Or, if you're listening in another city for...
Which is a great show, I'm sure.
Bob listens to it all the time.
So, good night to you, dear friends.
Good night to Chuck the Doge of South St. Louis.
That's right.
Who will be sending more garbled shows made from other shows...
Which are made from...
The Money Show.
...which play on this show, which then gets rerouted again, and it's like a giant blender...
Yeah.
...that just spews right back into itself, and you get to, or have to, listen to the
results.
Yes.
You hear me?
Get away from it.
Just like these...
Hey, you've got to pay me some money.
Hey, give me some money.
Is that a tick or a tick-head?
This little chigger got on me when I was under the old Palo Verde tree, and it's kind of
burrowed under my .
If your chigger offends me, cut it out.
That's right.
Use new chigger off, and the music will always keep coming.
We are M.E.A.D.
This is M.E.A.D.
This is the coming together of people of all races, all sexes, all walks of life, coming
together, joining hands, and sharing what they can with me.
And that's kind of neat.
Yeah, it kind of makes you wonder...
Hands across the me.
...where all the goodness is coming from.
We are the me.
It is your responsibility to feed and to serve.
We are the musicians in this together.
You are next.
Good triumphs over evil every time.
There's this force that flows between us all, and in Church of the Subgenius we just call
it money.
You can just make it flow towards me.
Well, you know what really makes me mad?
Thank you.
Thank you guys.
What makes you pee?
What makes me pee?
Well, about, uh, two liters of Coke 45.
No, no, no, no, no, not that.
Now let's go over that again.
That's a good idea.
No, no, okay, what?
No, really.
People come up to me and say that they have sugar bites.
Oh, no.
That bums me down.
And mosquitoes collide with them.
That's a good idea.
Yeah.
Don't they know that the word is chigoro?
I don't know.
No, no, it's chigo.
They don't have any elegance.
It's not chigoro, it's chigo, if we must be pedantic.
Well?
Well, chigo became corrupted into the word chigger.
Oh, yes.
Around the same time that the word revelia became pronounced revel-ee.
It's an Americanization of the pronunciation.
Now, what about the word origins of the word tawdry?
Tawdry?
Yes.
Well, you know, this is Frank here, and I think you know Audrey.
She's a wonderful trooper.
Thank you very much.
She's going to demonstrate in the finals of this wonderful contest
how the tawdry talketh.
And she's going to go on to a new question.
A personal friend of mine for the past 15 years,
a great humanitarian.
Couldn't make it.
What, what?
Here you go.
Someone who never wants to be known as just a Milton Berle for acid heads.
Oh, no.
Oh, never, never.
The amazing Mr. Me, Me, Me,
who sometimes is called the final solution to the entertainment problem.
Me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me.
Oh, ho, ho, ho.
I mean, he might be Jane, but I'm even Janer.
Oh, ho, ho.
You're a Janer?
You're a Janer than most.
Oh, ho, ho, ho.
I'm making too much money off this kill me stuff to die now, baby.
Who's the Janest in the world?
Okay, well, shall we?