And now, the Su-Su-Su-Su-Su-Su-Su-Su-Su-Subgenius Hour of Slack!
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
Oh, alright.
And I, Stang, am in a big, bubbly hurry,
And so tonight's show is a re-re-re-run, but not of an hour of slack, not even of a minute of slack, nay, but rather of Bob's Slack Time Funhouse from WREK Atlanta.
And not this time won by the good reverend Susie the Floozy, but a mental classic by her co-pad was the Lymph Node Institute.
Chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug.
You are listening to Bob's Slack Time Funhouse.
The Lymph Node Institute Edition.
I'm Doc.
And I'm Bugsy.
We're going to discuss the brain this evening in the interest of the magic dancing giants above us.
It's funny because your brain will fill in gaps as needed, especially when you're receiving everything through your ear holes.
So if you hear any extra noises, it's just the, it's the dancing giants.
The subliminal dancing giant.
We're not really, as far as you know, hammering anything into your brain.
It's for your benefit, Atlanta and places beyond.
Your brain's squishy, little monkey man.
Let's go.
You have a few feet on my back.
That's the way to get off the bottom of the mountain
That's how Westin made me great
We mean good
Our 똑돼 이젠
One word
I know
Although I do believe there would be more
I've got a nervous kind of feeling
Got a painful yellow headache
Every picture in every magazine's tongue frills
Every face looks out and screams at me to frills
Cold sweat on my collar
Dripping to my boots
The waves of nauseous pain
Sets off the pressure pad along
Gotta get out of hell
Got a painful swelling brain
Banging in my head
And I call it a day
I'm cold off sick
Got a swelling itching pain
Got it pulling out my hair
Clutching at my brain
Got a painful swelling brain
In the back of my head
In my head
Got a cold half sick
Got a swelling itching pain
Got me pulling out my hair
Clutching out by brain
Got a painful swelling brain
Got me laying on the floor
And she banged, banged it in my head
Got a painful swelling brain
In the back of my head
And I called off sick
Got a painful swelling brain
Got that pulling out my hair
Clutching up my brain
Got a painful swelling brain
People swelling brain
Driving me up to wall
Got a painful swelling brain
People swelling brain
Clipping out my eyes and closing my mouth
Got a painful swelling brain
People swelling brain
Imploding my thoughts
Got a painful swelling brain
People swelling brain
That's me holding up my hand
義
Got a flying empty bag while I do my
Punching in my brain
Got people falling, people falling
Got me lying on the ground
Going out of my squad
Got people falling, people falling
Burning up my thoughts
Coming out my eyes is losing my
Got people falling, people falling
And it's falling, tearing me apart
Good evening, outpatients.
I know it has been some time since I've donned the blood-spattered lab coat of healing,
and it is possible that some of you listening have suffered mightily at the withdrawal of your coded programming.
Some of those not listening may be, in fact, deceased.
But let me make my position clear.
We don't need you anymore.
We're so deep in our endgame model that we don't have the time or resources to even look around,
much less worry about you.
We've got all the human...
human pincushions we need since our rapture-has-passed recruiting drive.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
I tell ya.
Global anxiety equals multiple international revenue streams.
But on to business.
One of the last remaining uneaten helper monkeys reminded me of some damn funding technicality community outreach bullsh-ish.
So, here we are at or around the point.
Ahem.
Now,
more than ever,
your mind is a battleground.
The invading armies of normalcy have already dug in on the beachhead of your desire for acceptance,
which is, not coincidentally,
perilously close to your slack reserves.
No, please.
I hear your protest.
I understand the reflex to automatically attest your rugged individualism,
but this is not a cigarette ad.
You damn well better take a passing interest,
in the opinions of others.
I should not have to remind you that our kind has a poor track record when it comes to frenzied pink mobs.
So, you desire that they accept you,
at least to the point of keeping your guts off their pitchforks.
You know, all I have ever asked of you is one simple thing.
Make the simple decision that it is the world that is insane,
not you.
Just acknowledge that somehow,
a system of techno-feudalism in which blind slaves squirm at the feet of sad, sadistic, repressed yetis,
clamoring for crumbs and passing up rumors on their farts,
has somehow failed.
No problem, right?
Plain as the scabs on my nose, you say.
But,
tomorrow,
or the next day,
you'll be back at the table,
playing their comfortingly stupid shell game.
The world hovers on the edge of rebirth,
and I'll bet you still have a damn job,
still standing at the answer table in the back of their seedy opium den of lies.
Oh, don't get me wrong.
I'm not here to run the moneylenders out of the temple.
Just think of me as the guy in the next cell,
who won't stop whispering dangerous,
bull-ish,
through the cinder blocks.
But it's not because I'm trying to get you in trouble,
although that would be funny.
I just don't want you to forget the present that history has bought for you.
See you in the gulag.
Goodnight.
And now,
the parts of the train,
performed by,
the train.
Yes.
Neocortex frontal lobe.
Brainstorm! Brainstorm!
Hippocampus neural node, right hemisphere.
Pons and cortex visual.
Brainstorm! Brainstorm!
Sylvian-Fisher pineal, left hemisphere.
Cerebellum left,
cerebellum right.
Synapse hypothalamus,
striatum dendrite.
Axon fibers, matter gray.
Brainstorm! Brainstorm!
Central tegmental pathway,
temporal lobe.
White core matter, four brains go.
Brainstorm! Brainstorm!
Central fissure, cord, spinal,
parietal.
Piameter,
men and geovane,
medulla, vanguata, and lobe.
Ptolembic, microelectrodes.
The brain!
One is moral,
one is not.
It's super ego and idbot.
Do you have any idea how frustrating it is
to be a robot personification
of the human id?
I never should have given you a penis.
That's what she said.
Oh idbot.
Well come on, let's sit down at this
all you can eat buffet.
Oh boy, I want all of it.
Now.
Now now idbot.
No, out of my way.
Only eat what you need.
Cuff you, you big queer.
Gluttony is a sin, idbot.
And you're a pansy, get out of my way.
All things in moderation.
I gots to have it.
No you don't, you're a robot.
As a personification of the human id,
I must have all of it, I gots to have it,
I gots to have it, gimme gimme, get out of my way.
You're incorrigible, idbot.
That's it, I'm waiting in the car.
Get out of my way, other patrons.
Nom nom nom.
One is moral, one is not,
it's super ego and idbot.
Did you read Brave New World by Aldous Huxley?
Laugh Riot.
It's pretty funny for a book that's not supposed to be funny.
I mean, he was not a swift.
No, but orgy porgy
until I started seeing a lot of
rap videos.
Really struck me as comical.
Well they got the JC character in there and that wasn't so funny.
And the savage.
It's the same with 1984, there's always
a heretic, a Satan figure.
Or Jesus, depending on which
side you're looking at him from.
But me mum smoked when she was having me and I got okay with
brackish amniocytic fluid.
But it wasn't quite poo poo.
In Brave New World they just deprived some of the oxygen
to the fetus. Yeah.
It's amazing how that really stunts development. Funny that.
Let's say things go Brave New World
and you start doing all the alterations
of fetuses to make sure they end up in certain
positions in society. Yes.
Because you know the society, the needs of the society are
paramount to the society. It really messes up
the whole mother nature curve if you start
dumbing down some and smartening up others.
Music
Shakers and we will not burn
Killers and we will return
Shakers and we will not shock
Shockers and we will burn
I'm not the world's most incredible man
But I just can't seem to understand
If it weren't for all the people I'd be all alone
Rock me baby, rock me baby all night long
I'm not the world's most incredible man
But I just can't seem to understand
If it weren't for all the people I'd be all alone
I'm not the world's most incredible man
Shakers and we will not burn
Killers and we will return
Shakers and we will not shock
Shockers and we will burn
They were doing what I was doing
When lightning hit the street
A bar of soap, a pint of scope
Was all they'd had to eat
Look at that, some macaroni had happened to his hair
He had a shirt but it was hurt
And sadness filled the air
The arms of the world's most incredible man
I never can quite seem to understand
If it weren't for all the people I'd be all alone
Rock me baby, rock me baby all night long
It takes a lot of money to let you teach them how to talk
Come on pretty baby, rock, rock, rock
One is moral, one is not
It's super ego and it's bot
Ah, now for some fine adult entertainment
Remember, no touching
Guff that noise, I gots to have it
It bot, I can't take you anywhere
You're embarrassing me in front of the ladies
Guff you, pansy, give me a dollar
Well, all I've got are these Sacagaweas
Look at the ladies, I gots to have it
It bot, no!
Ladies, I have attachments
I have special attachments
Please, you have to respect these people
They're just working a job like anyone else
Guff you, give me a ten spot
I wish I had a laugh
Oh, I need to have a laugh dance
It bot, retract that tentacle
Bouncer, you better step off
Excuse my friend, sir, he's a little bit of a robot
I'll drink all the liquor and have all the booty in this hole
It bot, moderate, you're embarrassing me
People are looking at us, the Japanese businessmen
Moderation is for pussies
Seriously, it bot, I can't take you anywhere
Ha ha ha ha ha, um
It bot, that's murder
One is moral, one is not
It's super ego, and it bot
Now you heard the disclaimer, you know the deal
If you, if you take any of this seriously
Then you have a real problem
Well, you sure are talking serious, doc
About all his cognition processes
Well, hell, I don't know
The brain is funny, too
Actually, the appreciation of humor
Probably is just as important as having the gullies of depression
So I don't know, I don't know
I tell you people who are leveled out, mostly
From the pills you take
You're missing most of the ride
Your rollercoaster's pretty straight
Hunter S. Thompson said that the first sign of insanity
Is the loss of the sense of humor
But what about people who never had one?
Born crazy
You know the bland, the bland Blanco?
The bland
Deaf, dumb, and bland
Yeah, now mama, let's go downtown
Flyin' high and gettin' down
Gonzo, hyper, cybernetic
Jump in the air and levitate
You are blurred, you can't hold that deck
Old damn town, well, rock your life
Rock tonight, rock tonight
Blast your booty, bust a move
Marsh your mind and ride the groove
Do your part to make a wish
Let's all do the boogal fit
You are blurred, you can't hold that deck
Old damn town, well, rock your life
Rock tonight, rock tonight
Get your sweet, cross your eyes
Slam the beat and funk aside
Ain't no psycho, ain't no relic
Reality is psychedelic
Psychedelic
You are blurred, you can't hold that deck
Old damn town, well, rock your life
Rock tonight, rock tonight
Inside, outside, outside
In right brain, left brain
Let us fit
Cyber Sue and Jimmy Jimmy
Party on down with Dr. Timmy
You are blurred, you can't hold that deck
Old damn town, well, rock your life
Rock tonight, rock tonight
estou deseandourgence
bezou doświad P форм mengoli
Quehhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
Queuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuu
ouuuuuuuuu substance
facultyello mercury
music is a strange function of the human mind it's not necessarily a function of the mind the
mind does determine patterns but when the music's presented those are predetermined patterns you may
interpret them differently but it's not like you're making music out of randomness you're
being presented with patterns already but if you go back i mean way back to the advent of music
one can only assume that it was organic sounds a couple of stone cavemen sitting somewhere
listening to bugs probably hitting rocks and skulls yeah sticks on the sixth day of god time
the mastodon went away from far beyond the galaxies i've journeyed to this place
to study
the behavior patterns of the human race and i find them highly illogical
girl meets boy they fall in love she says he's everything she's dreamed of but when they get
married before he's aware she changes his habits the way he combs his hair she changes him to
someone he's never been and then complain
he's not like other men now really i find this most illogical
take the case of your automobiles greatest invention since man discovered wheels
high dramatic overdrive floor on the floor push button windows push button doors
double barrel carburetors rush you any place but you never can find a parking space
highly
illogical
take the case of modern man he works all his life gives it all he can saves all his money
works overtime pinches every penny banks every dime all he can think about is money but you
know that he can take it with him where he's going to go now i find that fascinatingly
illogical
now is the time to journey home
to tell of what i've learned my people i believe have every right to be concerned
illogical
for in spite of computers and advanced psychology behavior patterns are still a mystery i predict
the future of this earthly human race is that having made a mess of earth they'll move to
outer space well there goes the neighborhood
totally completely absolutely
illogical
and
one is moral one is not it's super ego and it bot
ah it bot it's been such a long time since i couldn't take you anywhere remember when
we first used to go to the candy shack when we were young boys shut your wet human mouth
you're making me hungry i want sweets and i need them yesterday that's exactly what
what you used to say.
Sir, take that right back.
Hey, can I help you?
Yes, I'd like a modicum
of moderately priced chocolate.
Give me everything in the counter.
Open up the counter.
Move out of the way, old fellow.
I will have you from behind.
Ibbot, no, you're embarrassing me in front of
the old man.
I don't even know who you are. Don't touch me.
What the hell is he doing?
Never mind my friend, sir.
He's a little excitable for the sugar, but
don't worry, he's a robot.
Put candy in my orifice now.
Put it in.
Ibbot wants more candy.
Ibbot, no, that's his head.
Ah, yes, those were the days.
One is moral, one is not.
It's super ego
and Ibbot.
We'll have to wait until the terrorists
kidnap Ronald Reagan to do that.
What terrorists? The terrorists.
What? The terrorists that...
Don't you remember any of this?
The terrorists that escaped from Guantanamo Bay
invaded the country, just like that
Chuck Norris movie, and then
freaking kidnapped Ronald Reagan.
That hadn't happened yet, has it?
Well, he's Alzheimer's boy.
So we can't very well ask him.
He's so retold.
I believe it. He was Alzheimer's boy when he was in office.
No, I have read the script
as it is going to be executed.
The terrorists will escape from Guantanamo
and they will kidnap Ronald Reagan
and I think they do something terrible
to the state of Texas.
I think Negative Land pulled off
the whole time trials better.
Hell yes.
Let's play a little Negative Land.
They've done everything better than we have.
Fine. Okay, fine.
Let's play some Negative Land.
Yes, let's.
You're the Pepsi generation.
Now, what's inside of you?
Open it.
What's gonna be there?
What's inside of you?
Open it.
What's gonna be there?
What's inside of you?
Open it, I tell you.
Pepsi.
I need a Pepsi.
I need the Pepsi.
I need a Pepsi today.
Open it.
If there's Pepsi,
I know
Ports are aisle
I need a Pepsi.
Open it.
If there's Pepsi,
I need a Pepsi right away.
Open it.
If there's Pepsi,
I'll only know
Pepsi, Pepsi today.
What does make Pepsi,
I could say Pepsi to you?
I don't know what else to say.
Put a had whom.
But you need a Pepsi,
need a Pepsi,
need a Pepsi
I need a Pepsi today.
I need a Pepsi.
I need a Pepsi right away.
What did I tell you?
I need a Pepsi.
To show my grand loyalty.
To say all good about me.
We don't know what else to say.
But I need Pepsi.
What's up?
I need a Pepsi.
So I can play basketball.
I don't need Coca-Cola at all.
To show my grand loyalty.
To feel good about me.
We don't know what else to say.
But I need Pepsi.
Pepsi.
Pepsi today.
I need Pepsi sometimes.
And I don't know why.
There's a voice inside my head.
That makes me go out and buy.
I need Pepsi.
I buy a Pepsi.
Buy a Pepsi.
Buy a Pepsi after drinkin' some beer.
Beer.
Buy a Pepsi.
Buy a Pepsi after beatin' up queer.
Pepsi Pepsi.
Buy a Pepsi.
Buy a Pepsi after beatin' up queer.
Pepsi.
Buy Pepsi.
After drinkin' some beer.
Peps-I need Pepsi.
We might as well come right out with it.
I need a Pepsi sometime.
All flavors have that happy face.
And I don't know why.
Except sarsaparilla.
We haven't quite hit that happy, carefree note in sarsaparilla.
There's a voice inside my head.
Now please don't misunderstand me.
I need a Pepsi.
Our sarsaparilla is absolutely dependable.
I need a Pepsi today.
It's trustworthy.
It's loyal.
Right away.
And many fine, upstanding citizens love it.
Pepsi.
A really good mix.
I need a Pepsi.
But it just isn't what we call happy.
Pepsi.
A really good mix.
Pepsi today.
You take our orange.
It's absolutely rollicking.
Fountain Pepsi.
Our lemon is almost giggling.
Maybe a 12 ounce Pepsi.
Our black cherry and black raspberry are so bubbling with happiness.
They damp in the glass.
Maybe a 16 ounce Pepsi.
We're sorry about sarsaparilla.
Pepsi.
Why?
Isn't it happy?
Pepsi.
Honey, you can just go out and urinate.
You're an orange especially if you
Isn't it happy?
Hasn't it happy?
I love negative playing. That was great.
It was. Everything they do.
You know what they call it when they're starting a marketing campaign
and the first wave is just to get you to be aware that the product is out there?
Foreplay?
Basically, it's called establishing a mind share.
Isn't that a Queensryche album?
Operation Mind Share?
Operation Mind Slime. Operation Daddy Did Me.
Showload.
He's like Showboat, but loady.
Well, Jack, it's great to see you again.
Hey, thanks.
You folks say you've been making remarkable progress?
I hope the antidepressants have helped.
Yeah? You look good.
Thanks.
You look real good.
Well, thanks.
I think we should start today's session with a little word association.
I don't have to be here, you know.
Actually, you do. You've been remanded to my care by the courts.
Whatever.
So, just clear your mind. Shouldn't be that hard to do.
And say the first thing that comes to mind.
Chocolate.
Let us begin.
Razor wire.
No, see, I will say the word you will respond to,
and that's the association by which I will respond.
I'll make judgments on how normal you are.
Papa Bean.
No.
Razor wire.
Are you ready?
Wealthy.
Poor.
Octogenarian.
Octopus.
Pheromones.
Ferret.
My friend's got some ferrets. They're funny.
Family values.
Funny ferrets.
Subwoofer.
Pass.
Authority figures.
Mom. Dad. Teachers.
Cops.
Ass.
Cryptophane.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
What will you do if we let you go?
And the plastic's all melted and so is the car
Who are the brain police?
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
What will you do when the label comes off?
And the plastic's all melted and the chrome is too soft
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
I can't believe I'm alive
Who are the brain police?
What will you do if the people you knew
Were the plastic that melted at the chromium tube?
Who are the brain police?
All your senses are filtered through your brain.
They're just like microphones and cameras,
and heat and touch receptors
attached to that thing in your skull.
So if your brain is messed up,
you can never accurately perceive the outside world.
One expects that to happen.
We've had it proven by all the movies
that show people in little bamboo cages
clawing at their own feces, because they're crazy.
Speaking of behavioral programs,
I guess the prime one would be fight or flight.
Brought to you courtesy of your hypothalamus.
Once the senses squeeze in
through your various sense organs,
they run through something called the hypothalamus,
which is a little squirting gland in your brain.
The hypothalamus is kind of in charge of
deciding what is important and what is not.
So it's like Charlie for your brain.
Yes, basically it is your brain secretary.
It operates basically under four prerogatives,
which is fight, flight, feed, and puff.
And if something you see is important
to one of those four poles, I guess,
then the hypothalamus kind of gives it a little extra squirt,
which is why you might drive off the road
looking at some chickies behind,
because your hypothalamus is chanting,
well, you know...
Get you some, get you some.
Get it, get it, get it, get it.
And then when you look back to the road
and you're about three years old,
you're about three feet from the bumper of the car in front of you,
that's when your hypothalamus once again kicks in
with your fight or flight,
and there's really nothing you can do.
At the three seconds from the truck collision,
then you get the whole flash before your eyes,
read the whole of your existence,
which has to do with, I guess, the memory.
They all look very similar, right?
You can easily simply detest someone
You don't belong there.
But if someone comes as a real human,
that person can build an existence
and it took two meters to bring them together to show the difference.
Yeah, kiss for me, sweet and brave
Kiss for me, shit to impale
My head on my head, you walk out like arrows
My head on my head, my mind's growing narrow
Hit, hit, hit, hit, hit
And you breathe, and you breathe
Yeah, kiss for me, sweet and brave
Yeah, kiss for me, shit to impale
My head on my head, your words are like arrows
My head on my head, my mind's growing narrow
Yeah, kiss for me, it hits me hard
Yeah, kiss for me, you love me so hard
My head on my head, you walk out like arrows
My head on my head, my mind's growing narrow
Hit, hit, hit, hit, hit, hit, hit, hit, hit, hit
Hit, hit, hit, hit, hit, hit, hit, hit, hit, hit, hit, hit
And you breathe
They're all the same, they're all the same
20 eyes in my head
When you're feeling 20 things at a time
You just can't slow things down
When you're feeling 20 things in your mind
Well, all the time
This is the crowding of your human face
We're taking over the world
20 eyes in my head
They're all the same, they're all the same
When you're feeling 20 things at a time
You just can't slow things down
When you're feeling 20 things in your mind
Well, all the time
This is the crowding of your human face
We're taking over the world
20 eyes in my head
They're all the same
We were going to talk about memory.
Well, that's because your life flashed before your eyes.
It seemed like an appropriate seg.
Yes, yes.
And memory is very important
because basically the memories of who you are
and what you've done
sort of make who you are in the present.
Let's say you're reading a book
that's like fifth in a series.
Yes.
I think you would enjoy the subtleties
of the main character you're supposed to relate to
much more if you'd already been with that character
on several other adventures with different input.
And if you're the character in your own story,
which you really should be,
you very much should be,
then you're going to have a much more rich existence,
one thinks,
if you can relate everything that's currently happening
to what's happened in your past.
But don't live in the past
because that's a Jethro Tull song.
That's Stang's job to play Jethro Tull.
We don't do that.
Yeah, so memory's important.
When you lack memory,
you start to lose your definition of who you are, I think.
You look at these Alzheimer people.
Look at them.
I don't want to.
I know, not a pretty sight.
Could happen to you.
Don't drink your cola out of cans, kids.
They say that,
and I guess you can't use deodorant either
with all that alum.
That's what they say.
That's what's said.
So you're best at being
just what you are.
You can't be what you were.
The time of now is running out.
It's running out.
It's running, running, running out.
You can't be what you were.
So you're best at living the life
that you're talking about.
You can't be what you were.
You're just like a
a
I'm not guys, you know, aren't you?
a bad mind
There's no moving
in a bad love
if I
trade a bad
mind
You're always
talking, talking, talking,
talking, talking
this now
But you will
talk yourself down
You're going down
One is moral
One is not
It's super ego
and it bought
Well, it bought
Here we are
at yet another Woodstock
I smell cannabis
They are illegal
and we wouldn't want
to do anything wrong
or get in trouble
Out of my way
but truly makes me crazy
I do what he says, folks
I'm caught in the mud
Help
I have got to get
some of that sex drugs
and rock and roll
Well, maybe
two out of three
If it's too loud
then you are too old
Well, it's not too loud
I've got my earplugs in
You are such a
pansy panty waist
If you want me to
damage my hearing
that would make you happy
Why don't you hold
that girl down
while I set fire
to this tower?
No!
We need that tower
for observation
and filming
I like to watch
Give it to it, bot
It bought
No!
Let me at it
I gots to have it
All right
You just retract
those tentacles, mister
We gotta get out of here
You've gotten us
in trouble again
Woodstock
Woo
Party till you puke
That piece
of paper
I put in my mouth
is making me feel
awful
funny
Whoa
One is moral
One is not
It's super ego
and it bought
What's the difference
between the mind
and the brain?
The brain is the organ
and the mind is the
the part we like to
think that we are
Is the mind the soul?
Probably
Our consciousness
and personality
sure as hell
don't live in the brain
If you want to test that
just give someone's brain
a good whack
and watch their personality change
You know, you wipe out
one part of the brain
and some other part of the brain
starts kicking in
I think the mind is like a modem
The brain itself
is like the piece of equipment
that we used to call a modem
A modulator demodulator
That's correct
It connects with the outside world
And not only does it connect
with the outside world
but the whole part that makes it
I think the seat of the soul
is its connection
to things that the rest of your senses
can't really get at
and so you have to intuit
So what else does the mind
really make you decide you need?
Clothes
Clothes?
Hey, actually
And again, if the mind
is the seat of the soul
then all those big corporations
trying to get you
and get that mind share
that we talked about
are actually after your soul
Trying to redefine
who you think you are
so you give them money
It's amazing how people
just sort of
intuitively understand
that companies
are after their brains
and that they don't seem to mind
but when you mention the soul
they pucker up
That's why we've got
the invisible monster
He's the great Connie in the sky
One is moral
One is not
It's super ego
And it bought
Well, it bought
Now that we're in Hawaii
I hope you don't
choose to embarrass me here too
Come on, get out of my way
I need to get laid
That wasn't funny
at the airport either
Now, are you going to sit down
and enjoy the luau or not?
You know very well
that I can't sit
Are you making fun of me?
Don't put a chip
on your shoulder there
Get it?
Chip robot
I think you are making fun of me
Of course I'm not
I'm just happy
I want the pig
The pig is for everyone, idbot
I will not share
The pig will be mine
I'm cutting you off
I'm sick of this
I can't take you anywhere
Move these damn foreigners
out of my way
Move, move, move
Now, idbot
This is a foreign country
We're all foreigners here
No, no, no, no, no, no
Idbot
No, no, no, no, no, no, no
That's it
This is the last time
You
No, no, no, no, no, no
Me
Edge of the volcano
Now
All right, super ego
Have it your way
Just carry me safely
to the lip of the volcano
Meanwhile, at the top of the volcano
Ah, you've had this coming for years
Mom always liked you better
I'm sick of this
Sonification of your id
You made me vomit all over my prom date
You turned me into a cybernetic organism
You made me gain fifty pounds
when I broke my leg and started smoking pot
Ah, ah, you never lubricate me properly
I built you
You have a point
I do
Let's not fight
No
Ah, I tricked you
Oh, ahhhhhh
One is moral
One is not
It's super ego and it's bot
Tonight the city is full of morgues
And all the toilets are overflowing
There's shopping malls coming out of the walls
As we walk out among the manure
That's why
I'm super ego and it's bot
But the ladies at the counter
We gon' pay no mind
away
I said you ain't gonna bring the sweet
But no Facet
Give the finger to the rock and roll singer
As he's dancing upon your paycheck
The sales climb high
high through the garbage pale sky
like a giant dildo crushing the sun
that's why
I paint all mine
sleep in slime
I just got signed
so get out your lead pipe pipe drains
get out your ten foot flags
the insects are huge and the poisons all been used
and the drugs won't kill your day job honey
honey
that's why
I paint all mine
I play no mind.
If you'd like to learn more about the Church of the Subgenius,
drop them a load at P.O. Box 807,
Glen Rose, Texas,
76043.
My God, what are you waiting for?
Or just go to www.subgenius.com.
Another fine lymph node production.
Listen to Bob's Slack Time Funhouse at WREK.org,
91.1 FM, WREK Atlanta.
Your brain has decoded the following audio stimuli in the following order.
Swelling Itching Brain by Devo.
The Mind Lecture by LNI.
Brain Stem by Pinky and the Brain.
Super Ego and Idbot at the All You Can Eat Buffet.
By LNI.
The Butthole Surfers with Intelligent Guy.
Super Ego and Idbot at the Strip Club.
By LNI.
Fugu Fish by the very late Dr. Timothy Leary.
Leonard Nimoy with Highly Illogical.
Super Ego and Idbot at the Candy Store.
By LNI.
Voice Inside My Head by Negative Land.
The Old Word Association Skit by LNI.
Who Are the Brain Police?
By Frank Zappa and the Mothers.
Head Injury by Soundgarden.
Twenty Eyes by the Misfits.
Bad Mouth by Fugazi.
Super Ego and Idbot at Woodstock.
By LNI.
Super Ego and Idbot in Hawaii.
By the Lymph Node Institute.
Pay No Mind by Beck.
And in case you feel oddly empty this evening,
like there's something missing from this show,
then just lean back.
And listen to the dulcet tones of Queensryche
rocking you live with Operation Mindcrime.
Oh, Dallas, this is Operation Mindcrime.
Oh, Dallas.
Oh, it just takes a minute to feel the pain.
You got to make something of your life.
Give me one way.
You come to see that I'll never show you that you're.
I want to take away the questions.
I want to make you shine.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
When I hit the bed for the order
We couldn't go to school
Had a skin shot for a head hit
Yeah, it looked pretty cool
I had a habit to do it midnight
And I watched it drag me by
Knowing who's the guy
I don't know, it's nothing more than that
Now I know you won't make me lose
I know you won't, but you'll
So much to lose
We've been so far
You've got a thing for me to lose
So take my hand for a walk
She's my belief in my mind
We were down to ground
Revolution was the gun of the time
My belief in my mind
There's a child in you
And a sister in you
You've got to be the son
Of me
guitar solo
Hey, hey, hey, you know everything
Now there is new
Now here's my gun, oh
Take it home, we've got a phone
I'm gonna send someone over
Who's gonna give you what you need
You're worth it, definitely
You've got to make this city big
I don't know who you are, but you
I know your world is huge
We've got so much to do
So take my hand
We're alive and proud
Revolution was another time
I believe in life
It's a job for you
You're a sister, you're a god
Love me to death
I believe in life
We're alive and proud
Revolution was another time
I believe in life
You can come and see the back of the earth
If you're the girl
I believe in life
You've got to raise something up your arm
Let us into your mind
I believe in life
It's a job for you
You're the sister you've got
For me
You've got nothing to sign
Don't get a baseless
You've got nothing for me
For our parents
And you've got nothing for me
A rainy day
I could die seasons away
But you bought some of the clothes
Called my miss
Until they found а rainbow
You're sweet and kind
You've got something to say
Take a smile
You gösterون
I'll always be with you
Till the day that I go
I won't you die
The kurds with the moisture
We're here to save the world
Is that too far out?
Not for me, it's not.
One is moral, one is not.
It's super ego and it bought.
Mertz makes up your mind.
Take only as directed.
Bob's Slack Time Funhouse is the cure for the diseases you don't know you have.
Do you suffer from necrophilia, anxiety, depression, boredom, apathy,
gullibility, low self-esteem, cardiac, rectal, or frenulum,
analysis, addiction, psychosis, neurosis, paranoia,
catatonia, hysteria, schizophrenia, bipolar curiosity,
hyper-onanism, nerdism, blue balls, OCD, OCD, OCD.
If so, you need Bob's Slack Time Funhouse.
Tune in now.
1 a.m. Saturday night for your weekly inoculation.
And a dose of Bob's Own Medicine.
Bob's Own Medicine.
The preceding claims have not been certified by any reputable medical organization.
Bob's Slack Time Funhouse may cause smallpox, rash, discharge, recidivism,
colorblindness, seizure, monobrowism, synchronicities,
Dobbs Syndrome, caboose loosening, morning wood, rosetta stones, flying buttresses, or death.
Your local subgenius radio ministry.
Bob's Slack Time Funhouse.
Saturday night at 1 a.m.
WREK Atlanta 91.1 FM.