I love you.
Genuine.
Beautiful.
Giant.
Perfect.
Cool.
Special.
Cheered.
Labyrinth.
Easy.
Ultimate.
Best.
Natural.
Growing.
Special.
Nice.
Proud.
Quicker.
And much more.
Ah, yes, dear friends, it is rerun time again, but you'll be glad to know that we're not
going to just do the same old three Christmas hour of slack show reruns in a row.
No, I'm going to compress it.
All into just this one intensive total rerun show.
Except that actually it's not.
The whole first half will be largely peppered with a new Christmas sickness for the holidays
and holy days and the hole in head days, as it is for some people.
Actually, I have to work double time because it's the season of selling.
Selling.
Yes.
Oh.
You wouldn't believe what the elves have done over at the subgenius catalogs.
But anyway, happy whatever you do.
Yes, this music in the background is somebody named Kenny Wayne Shepard.
Yeah, there's an album called Merry Axmas, a guitar axmas.
It's cool, man.
Cool.
And.
Oh.
I'd like to find the guy who done me wrong and stuck my butt up on this Christmas tree.
Stuck the wood where I poop-she-poop-she-poop-poop with the stick of my hip-de-dip-de-dip.
Who was that man?
He shoved it up my can and left me stranded on this Christmas tree.
Yeah.
Will you stop it?
When this angel heard, chop-a-pop-a-pop, chop-a-pop-a-pop,
a dreadful fear went right into me.
My heart, those pine tree needles sting me.
Ram-a-jam-a-ram-a-jam-a-nam-a-ding-dong.
You'll never know how much that smarts.
So who put the stomp in my romp-a-bomp-a-bomp?
Who took and jammed it in my ram-a-lam-a-ding-dong?
Who stood the wood where I poop-she-poop-she-poop?
Who put the stick up my hip-de-dip-de-dip?
Who took that bush and crammed it in my tooth?
Who made this angel beg for mercy, please?
I might squeeze him too tight.
It's that psychedelic time of the year.
Do you know where your brain cells are?
It's already 9 p.m.
Don't go looking out in the backyard to dog-ate him.
Don't go walking down to the bar because old Frankie died last night in the backyard.
I mean, I'm in the apartment store.
I'm in the apartment store.
Oh, can I borrow the brain cells tonight?
Yeah, he brought back the chainsaw.
Yeah, and I ain't gonna let you use the brain cells
till I get the damn chainsaw fixed and back in my arm the way it was Tuesday.
Now, you boys be good, and I'll give you some of this here.
It ain't no good of a child.
That dog's running off with them brain cells.
Can you do something about that, boy?
I'm gonna have to.
What we as manufacturers sell you is fun.
The faith of a child.
Spend all the money you've got.
The Christmas trough.
I've lost my freaking mind.
Oh, look.
Dave's dressed like Santa Claus.
He's like a cowboy Santa.
Hajali.
Oh, Jazz is giving,
gives Dave the show pills.
Boy, I really need one of those.
What am I going to do about laundromat in this suit, though?
I need the show bath.
Bath.
The show de-lousing.
Oh, Dave doesn't even have headphones yet.
That's enough of that.
Oh, he's got headphones now.
I also have the part of my pancreas
that I'd like to show you now.
It's been increased in size to...
Oh, your pancreas looks lovely, Dave.
Look, it's swelling.
I have the capability of a man of 190 IQs brain.
I'll put more pills out for everybody.
Oh, those pills.
They make my...
mouth feel like it's on fire.
And my brain feel like it's a puddle of liquefied crystals.
I'm shocked by the...
The red pills are really good.
I like to take the red one and the blue one
at the same time.
That way you go in and out.
The warp mix is easy.
It's so high, you can't go over it.
Angels, we have heard on high.
Singing about mountains too.
And those mountains in reply.
Saying we wish we had some too.
Oh-oh-oh-ohh-oh-oh Whoa-oh-ohh-ohh-oh
Oh-oh-oh-ohh-ohh Oh-oh-ohh-ohh-ohh
Oh, Wario
ItISHK is say-o
Whoa-oh-oh-oh-ohh Oh-oh-oh-oh-ohh
Oh-oh-oh-oh-ohh Oh-oh-ohh-ohh-oh
Wario
It excels these days
Barbie Dolls
Women rape and memorialize their lives
by role-playing with bars
Barbie Dolls
We have devised a marketing scheme
for children's toys
It will empower us to resist
You will use your church
as a vehicle to bring these toys
before the public
It will be all
the fun
of the day
for kids
But how will the battle
of good against evil
be represented
in your marketing schemes
human?
Good has lots of muscles
Good
The primitive earth societies
should accept
this value judgment
Good will have
great physical attributes
according to human desires
46 00 model
sexual desires
latent at stake
child-like
ora
DOWN
percent
savage
watery
min incent jones
We must buy our toys!
Yes.
The old subgenius toy marketing scheme.
Recorded there at Dockstock 1984.
And me and Palmer Veedies.
Angels We Have Heard on High was by The Philistines.
The collage called All the Money You've Got
is from the great Obtuse Christmas collage album,
which you can get for free.
Get this.
Check out this website.
Obtuse.iuma.com
That's Obtuse.
Excuse me.
Ah, yes.
And next up, The Real Story of Christmas by Michael Shelley.
Once upon a time, there was the baby Jesus.
And he had two eyes made out of coal.
And he was stuck up a partridge in a pear tree.
And he wanted his two front teeth.
And he got McDonald's gift certificates.
And he had a dog named Santa's Little Helper.
And he took all the presents from Whoville.
And his friend Yukon Cornelius came.
With the three wise guys.
And he wanted to play the drums and be the little drummer boy.
But he couldn't.
He wanted 10s and 20s.
10s and 20s.
And he got McDonald's gift certificates.
And he got Zuzu's pedals.
And that's The Real Story of Christmas.
Take the house.
And he gave McDonald's gifts to
the children.
Take the house.
And he gave McDonald's gifts to
The Real Story of Christmas gift certificates.
Well, Tommy knew exactly what he wanted for Christmas.
He wanted an electric train.
He had the whole thing in his mind, even to the table where he was going to set it up.
He could picture the whole thing, and he would dream so hard that the whole thing would come to life right before his eyes.
Of course, Tommy was a pretty strong wisher.
And what he started wishing for was a pretty fancy-looking train set,
which he would never be able to get rid of.
He had a locomotive and three cars,
the station and the gateman,
the water tower, and all the kinds of wonderful equipment and accessories.
So rad that you might think Tommy was waiting for something that just didn't exist.
But he would know the real Lord, but the succeed stoplo religious work, was playing his role as he was trying to unravel the answer on the color of the Sasenta chain.
So Estored is back and puedes spektrying out some more bits of texto.
The Wall is in a jar!
I'm going to look at Tocantins now!
The Wall is as free and normal as the M Engilerts of Persia!
Oh, greetings!
Stand there,
Bob Dobbs comes with Rocket Pipe, Head Launcher, Jainer Device,
All-Yakitism, Fighting Jesus, and other action figures sold separately.
Some assembly required, batteries not included.
This toy falls apart in three days.
He-Bob and the Bastards of the Universe.
Too much is always better than not enough.
From Bob Dobbs.
Gorgeous.
My Connie.
Ken Dowsell separately.
He-Bob and the Bastards of the Universe will be back after this message.
Santa Claus.
It is turnover.
The time of the year when all things sell.
The end of the year sale.
So come and get it, everyone, and just buy our products.
I'm a little confused about what Christmas is all about.
Are we celebrating the birth of Santa Claus or his death when they nailed him?
Well, that's the ancient, ancient subgenie.
But the present subgenie tried to make sure that we have our inventories cleared by now.
And sell everything to the pigs.
Oh, yes.
Once a pagan holiday, and now a shopping season.
And it was something else in between there.
After it was a pagan holiday and before it was a shopping season, it was something else.
But I think they started a war over it.
Yeah.
Oh, oh, Gloria
Oh, I'm a place of honor
I'm a true wonder
Yeah, it's too much good
Oh, I'm not some god
Oh, oh, Gloria
Oh, Santa had extra sins
adjustment
Thank you.
Friends, try to imagine
my God and
Savior somewhere in the snow
north, the
Santibob trudging
mindlessly through the Himalayan
snows, driven by
strange forces to
complete his nameless errand.
And he may show
up at your house,
my friend, if you've been a bad
subgenius or a halfway
subgenius, or if we keep
getting tangled up in these other
shows and having strange
microphones.
How did that paternity
suit ever turn out between
Dobbs and Santa?
And who? His dad.
Santa dog. I don't know.
I don't think it was...
St. Nicholas, this is fact,
St. Nicholas punched another
bishop in the nose and
bloodied his nose.
Really? The historical St.
Nicholas?
Over the trinity of God.
The original St. Nicholas
in Turkey?
I swear upon Bob's and
who's the hell's God?
Yeah.
I can tell you shit, God.
Who the hell is God?
Ask Dobbs one day.
That's the question we should be asking.
Suddenly, a lightning bolt
struck from nowhere on that
bright, sunny day. Bob
did a backflip, and from that day
on, he too was a believer.
And from the snow
a little child bearing
flowers emerged.
Chip, what else?
Each one a dirty flower.
St. Nicholas.
The historical Santa Claus
is originally
lived, as the caller
knows, as a bishop
in, was it
Constantinople?
Yeah, like one of those...
It was in ancient Byzantium.
Yeah, Asia Minor
in general, yeah.
And he was
known for
sneaking into the room,
the rooms of young women, and leaving
gifts.
Light-sized lumps of coal, complete with a fake beard
and a CIA Wall Street credit card.
A saint he was,
the girl said.
St. Nicholas invented the CIA.
You got it, brother.
Stuck into people's houses through the chimney.
He knew when they were awake.
You got it, brother.
But like the CIA, he was
protecting them.
St. Nicholas was a creeping, stinking
spy.
He knows when you've been sleeping.
He knows what you've been eating.
Hey, man, my kids still believe in St. Nicholas.
And who keeps that belief alive
in their fevered, sick little brain?
Madison Avenue, of course.
No, the surveillance community
under your direction.
And the Reynolds Tobacco Company.
Miller Beer, you know.
If you're bad, he punishes you.
If you're good, he rewards you.
He's probably the closest thing to Jesus
walking the earth.
He's the closest thing to Big Brother there is.
He rewards those...
Who knows when they are smiling when they're awake.
I think, really, if you want to make a deal,
you have to do it with, you know...
Could Dr. Claus, in fact,
be the wandering, quote,
milkman rumored to have
fathered our savior,
J.R. Bob Dobbs?
Well, we find it a very likely possibility
from the falsified documents
we have here.
And also the fluffy beard that often grew on Bob's feet.
You better watch out.
You better not...
You better not tell anyone.
Santa Claus is coming to town.
He's a brother, man, this.
Checking it twice.
Gonna find out who's nobler in there.
Santa Claus is coming to town.
He's a brother, man, this.
He knows when you're awake.
He knows when you're in bad or good.
So be goodness to goodness sake.
Oh, you better watch out.
You better not cry.
You better not tell them telling you what.
Santa Claus is coming to town.
Oh, he's crazy.
logic工fm on rotates
Santa Claus is coming to town.
Santa Claus is coming for me.
Thank you heavily.
Hey, accessibility.
Santa Claus is coming to town tonight.
That's right, as a..."
Oh, look down thisiane.
You know where he is.
He's back delicious.
Or wrists.
Santa's back again.
Material plants?
Biological agents who only take 15%?
Thank you.
Oh, it's a great day, all right.
A salute to Mr. and Mrs. American.
Shop as usual.
And avoid panic buying.
All right!
It's two days old Christmas, a million things to do.
Clean the house, put on tea, company is due.
Where are my relatives?
Why haven't they showed up?
I've met her at the airport, I forgot to pick them up.
Christmas, Christmas here.
Sometimes I think all that Santa crap's just bull.
Santa Claus is real.
Who's the head man?
Santa Claus.
He was a huge beastly, bulging man.
You're so real.
How come we didn't get squat last year?
Yes, the birth of the baby.
The birth of our baby Satan on July 4th.
And now you can have it all pure 100% vinyl chloride CID.
The birth of our baby Satan as told by various authors and eclectic scholars from around the globular unit.
Including that announcer.
This announcement has not been a perfunctory announcement.
But an announcement of the blessed anointing and birthday of our Lord.
See you.
For one bright Christmas morning.
Was born in a cradle to a rich man's family.
Oh, I know the rave Jesus.
I'm parting with the rave Jesus.
Have yourself a merry little Christmas.
Merry little Christmas
Let your side be light
From the water
Triples with the outer side
Have yourself a
Merry little Christmas
From now on
We're miles away
Once again
As in olden
Say happy golden
Be miles away
Let your heart
Be out of sight
Out of sight
The Jackson's
But I wish everybody
A crystal merry Christmas
And a gloomy gloomy day
From Mutated Christmas, friends,
the Have Yourself a Merry Little Christmas
by No-L.
No-L.
Before that, some year-old ESO
and Michael Shelley.
did that real story of Christmas
from the Tarkin Records
all-star holiday extravaganza.
I'm playing a lot from that.
So check out www.triage.com
for that one also.
The Tarkin Records is also on
www.triage.com
and now the Jethro's.
That's today's special edition
of enjoyment.
Hey!
Come along.
. . . this. . . . this. . . . this. . . . this. . . . . this. . . . this. . . . . this. . . . . Grah. fingeraaaaa agaaaaaaagggh!
¶¶
detritus.net slash illegal art
www.detritus.net slash illegal art
And now, more Jethro's!
Jethro's!
Now you're blaming Jesus, you're blaming our Lord.
I sort of understand, because...
I understood the way any old fool would understand.
There was no Jesus, no flatulent old woman waving her panties on the hill.
It's not that you don't want to, it's that they won't let you.
No, they're ashamed.
Just a cry of wilderness.
They're ashamed.
And the hot pursuit of wolves everywhere in the background.
I'm ashamed of them.
Oh!
It's cold.
I'm leaving that city life behind and radio people crazy.
I can't get my noodle back in the pan, Jen.
Come on, cowboy.
No, man, I was trying to hear a can against your tree, and it started whispering to me, man.
Oh, you've been drinking.
There's the face of the Madonna right up there.
There's the face of the Virgin Mary.
I swear to God, look at it.
It ate me.
What?
It's your Christmas witch coming.
It ate me.
It was crazy.
Wow.
A Christmas witch?
I'll be whole.
Oh.
She's beautiful.
Oh, my God, yeah, I guess it does look a little bit more...
Her breasts are so cold.
Witchy than angelic.
I know she must be a true witch.
I guess you could call her that if that's what she's packing out of you for real.
She's surrounded by hovering Christmas ornaments.
It looks like a radar device.
What?
Yo.
Yo?
It's her.
What up?
Nothing.
What's up?
What a deep voice.
First Christmas.
Witch.
Thank you.
Christmas is now.
It's me.
You've beaten the crap out of Santa Claus.
Scott, you made your choice.
You rejected my word, you rejected me.
And to your eternal soul,
you have found that only could you afford
to give to God that which was his.
But you could not afford to do otherwise.
The Senate still stands.
And as the snow melts,
into outer darkness,
where there is wailing and gnashing of feet,
Sir, please give me just one more chance, sir.
I don't want to go to hell, sir.
Sir, no, no.
I don't want to go to hell.
No.
Live as he could be.
And the children say he could laugh and play
just the same old you and me.
The tail bearer will be at the judgment.
¶¶
Strange lights appear in the skies all over the world.
The wife of a carpenter experiences virgin birth,
and a baby is born with a head
that glows like a fluorescent lamp.
Dare I ask it?
Yes.
Was the infant Jesus neither man nor God,
but merely one of the countless aliens
that visit the Earth each and every day?
The answer?
Yes, definitely.
Take that and shove it up the tube,
mark certainty,
in the fuzzy place called the Twilight Zone.
Merry Christmas to all!
Now you're all gonna die!
The night Santa went crazy
The night Saint Nick went insane
Realized he'd been getting the wrong deal
Something finally must have snapped in his brain
Well the workshop is gone now
He decided to bomb it
Everywhere you'll find pieces
Of Cupid and Comet
And he tied up his helpers
And he held the elves hostage
And he grounded them
And he turned up for Rudolph
Into reindeer sausage
He got dancer in Prancer
With an old German Luger
And he slashed up Dasher
Just like Freddy Krueger
And he picked up a flamethrower
And he barbecued Blitzen
And he took a big bite
To say it tastes just like chicken
The night Santa went crazy
The night Kris Kringle went nuts
Now you can hardly walk
Around the world
Without stepping in reindeer guts
There's a National Guard
And the FBI
There's a van from the eye
With just news
And helicopters circling
Round in the sky
And the bullets are flying
The bodyguards rising
And everyone's dying
To know who Santa was
Who he really was
Santa went toNY
And showed your friends
How就是說
That Santa is
Cause you're Majreally
You better watch out.
You better not cry.
You better not pout.
I'm telling you why.
Santa Claus is coming to town.
Have yourself an advanced Dogmatic Christmas song thing
called Santa is Coming by F. Gillespie and F. J. Coot.
ElectricElf at Loop.com can tell you more about that.
But now...
Who gave the Lord the claptrap?
Who made him talk in funny riddles so that we cannot understand?
Who made him so succinct and blind that he is actually blind?
Yeah, we're now officially in the Jesus season.
The time of the Lord, of the fat man of the crowd.
How many do you...
Before you reach your limit, how many do you get?
Jesuses?
Yeah, how many can you bag?
How many messiahs can you bag?
Hail Jesuses.
If you're doing it in season...
If you're doing it out of season, you need a special permit.
Oh, you never do...
And you can only take one.
Yeah, but I mean...
You never bag the Lord in C.
You bag the Lord in B-flat, so you get that kind of rough sound.
But when they're in season, it's every God for himself.
This is the season for the fighting Jesus.
Obviously.
We are between a rock and a hard place.
Did you know, though,
that the Lord walked through the city of Jerusalem
and he walked through Chaldea in the old age
and he got a very, very hard foot
and he got elephantages of the rectum.
You know, it's not something well-known
by many Christian scholars.
But I think the phrase in Hebrew was...
Well, I like the story...
I kind of like those stories where the Lord dies
and then comes here to America and settles,
you know, tames the West.
I like when he moves into a trailer park
and cowboys walk with his dog.
Jesus fought for the Confederate army.
The ranger.
I like the...
Yeah!
The Texas ranger.
Jesus, Texas ranger.
Johnny Riva was a Jesus!
I could see Jesus for the Navajo police,
for maybe the Hopi police force.
Billy Jack was the Indian Jesus.
He was the white brother who came to instruct the Indians
how to be liberal.
Well, what about old peacemaker,
the Jesus of the Iroquois,
who was actually Huron, a Huron.
You didn't know that, did you?
See, I got you!
Thin Ron.
Jesus!
El Ron.
I got it.
Get in the club!
Jesus is like no other Jesus you've ever seen.
Oh, it tastes like butter.
A new Jesus.
A different Jesus.
It tastes like crappy pie, children.
A future Jesus.
A pipe-smoking Jesus!
Hey, Dave, you know where it is.
Go kick that window open.
I already kicked it.
I'll kick it again, though.
Kick it good this time.
We don't mean nothing by this Jesus and God.
We hope that...
We thank you for all the nice things
that you've done for us.
This thanks...
Clapping!
We appreciate all that.
And we're just trying to insult your fan club.
That's all.
That's why we do this blasphemous stuff.
But we knew that you knew that
because you're in all things and everything, right, Jesus?
Right.
I could hear him say that.
Praise God and Bob and Jesus.
Next topic.
Terrorist insurance.
Could you see Jesus as a terrorist?
And science.
Well, that's the life of Brian, isn't it?
And Greek mythology.
Norse mythology.
And the sounds of hell.
Jingle, jangle, jingle
We're on a sleigh ride to heck
Santa and his reindeer
Are really wicked
Wrapped in wrapping paper
We're gonna break our necks
Got a rocket in my pocket
On a sleigh ride to heck
Jingle, jangle, jingle
Sleigh ride to heck
The elves are full of cheer
The kids are tucked in bed
Santa ain't coming
We're on a sleigh ride to heck
Their dreams are filled with toys
But they're out of luck
Cause Satan's taking Santa on a sleigh ride to
Sleigh ride to heck
The greatest scary Christmas song ever, friends,
from his life.
His new album, Don't Trust Whitey,
James Kochalka, Superstar.
You know, see, a subgenius has so much faith
that he not only can accept
somebody making fun of Bob,
stomping on a picture of Bob,
he'll do it himself.
He has so much trust and faith in Bob.
Bob is such a good friend that he can insult Bob.
Now, we subgeni,
I hate to get on my soapbox
in the middle of a bunch of entertaining tapes,
but we subgeni may be bad,
but our way of bad is holy,
is holy compared to the evil of so...
Not all, by any means,
but so many American fundamentalists,
charismatics, evangelicals, etc., in general.
Of course, they and their corresponding types
in Iran, Russia, Libya, South Africa, etc.,
if you ask me, are actually the ace up the devil's sleeve.
Wolves in sheep's clothing, friends,
just like Jesus warned about.
I... we're...
Jesus and Bob, like we say,
our old drinking buddies,
got nothing against Jesus.
It's just his fan club.
And now, we aren't saying that Bob
is the ace up God's sleeve.
He's more like the smear on God's handkerchief,
just like you or me.
But the uptight rival cults,
they don't think God has a handkerchief.
Uh-uh, no, because God's perfect.
He doesn't even sneeze.
We're made in his image,
except that we have all these nasty parts attached to us,
and we have to go in the secret room,
the bathroom,
to do awful things.
But God, oh, he's clean and pure,
according to them.
Oh, and he's male.
But he doesn't excrete juices and sweat
and smelly stuff out of him like we do.
Because we sinned. Oh, yeah, we all sinned.
We're bad, we're worthless,
we're no good to God
unless we sign a contract with his agent.
God is the best.
We interrupt this program
for a special promotional announcement.
We turn.
E-Bob and the bastards of the universe
will be back after this message.
All right, thank you.
This is the end of the show.
If you did, please subscribe.
Bye-bye.
Captions by GetTranscribed.com
Captions by GetTranscr reversed in operation by
Copyrightpringer
I am dreaming of a Caucasianに
God's hand
Where everyone can ouais
Bye
Hey
Sure
You
And may all your dogs
Can be wise
By Fernanda Nande-Lemore
Oh, holy night
The stars are brightly shining
It is the night of our dear Savior's birth
Long lay, long lay the world
In different pining
The pit and the stone mountains red
A thrill of hope
The weary world rejoices
Beyond the grave
A new and glorious dawn
On
On your knees
Oh, hear
The angel voices
Oh, night
Divine
When Christ was born
Oh, night
Divine
Have yourselves
A groovy little song
Sing it to the world
Jamaica!
Hammity flock meet up
Hooman Cob د
It's he Bob
You can help that
Satanus.
Rice
Overthrow the evil
With new Bob-Dods
Action figure
With rock!
Off script
Move on
I catch you
Go to the
Space Cadet, life support system down to zero cocoa.
Feeling space.
I have some of my new cocoa pebbles.
Now so trumpety.
Smells coconut.
Space Cocoa.
Coconut.
Blow.
Well, friends, what do you think?
Is it the nativity of Santa Claus that we're trying to celebrate here?
Or is it the horrible death of the Santa Bob, the Santai Bob,
as he's been referred to in some early pre-scriptures?
The Jethro's.
Friends, you need to know where to write to the Jethro's.
They're at, they did that Wreck the Halls and so many other versions we've been playing.
The Jethro's are at 212 and a half Miller.
Avenue.
That's 212 and a half Miller Avenue.
Portsmouth, New Hampshire.
Portsmouth NH.
O-3-8-O-1.
Santa Claus is Coming to Town was by Corporal Blossom.
Information on that mutant Christmas is available from www.triagemusic.com
or www.
www.detritus.net
slash
illegal art.
I'm Reverend Ivan Stang.
Friends, you can reach me, send me tapes or whatnot at
post office box
Cleveland Heights, Ohio
And friends, as always, the hour of slack is brought to you by the Church of the Subgenius.
www.subgenius.com
www.subgenius.org
We'll see you next time.
Yeah.
Santa, I mean.
Otherwise, gosh.
I guess we have to wait till Santa comes, Dave.
Our beloved Santa.
I have wanted to put your bag down for a minute.
This side is always so ready to let him fit.
Santa for so long.
Hey, Bob and Mary Exmus.
Don't go looking for my good dear.
Merry fucking Christmas.
Thank you.