You know how you, when you go to sleep and you dream, how you can bend and shape the events that take place in that dream?
Well that, what if that were your reality? And what if this were the dream?
You know, you can actually paint your future and you can make everything that's ever happened, is happening and will happen, has already happened.
It's shape-shifting time and events so that you know why your soul is here.
And that's the purpose, to know why you're here, to know why you came back.
This is amazing.
I know.
What are you going to call it?
I think I'll call it Bob.
Bob?
You don't like Bob?
You can't call a planet Bob.
Oh, so now you're the boss.
You're...
You're the king of Bob.
Well, no.
But...
What?
Can't you just call it Earth?
Well, no one said you had to live on Bob.
I'm never calling it that.
Ha ha ha ha!
We are the men of...
The Super...
Genius...
Of...
Slack.
We wear the...
Power of Slack.
...star.
We like to think of...
The Super...
Genius...
We've got everything for your...
Slack.
We've got lubricants and batteries just for you.
We've got...
Slack.
...too.
We've got everything for your...
So genius.
Power of...
Slack.
...slay.
Man by day, beast and devourer of the unwary by night.
Who is this creature?
...wha?
Whose origins lie in Medieval Europe as a potent symbol of fear...
...and the violence that lurks at the center, under the veneer of civilization.
...wha?
A ravenous, gelatinous werewolf, as its huge corpulent bones slid across the plain, leaving its slimy trail behind it.
The werewolf, or the werewolf worm, as it were, slithering and glithering like some ancient, hideous beast.
Too symbolic to even mention, and the emphasis is on mention, I might add.
While the tradition that we seek in uniting the water with the air represents the coming together of matter and spirit,
this positive force that we know we can perceive with our obvious logic and reason,
the
I'm going to tie one on.
Okay, you go ahead.
Right over here.
Don't let me get you back, okay?
Here.
You tie one on over there, and I'll just tie one on over here.
And tie one on over here.
It's on.
Yeah, I'm...
I'm aware.
I'm aware of that now.
Please.
You know, plants may be calculating creatures.
To most people, the word computer conjures up an image of a PC squatting on a desktop.
PC, man.
According to a new study, however, complex...
Okay, and now I want you to gently feel your neighbor's nipple to your left and to your right.
Okay, then get him up toward you.
Go ahead.
All right, I got a complaint regarding the larger event.
Because at that very moment, the Gens thanks you for talking to me.
Hey, Blackie.
Anymore babes in there?
How doth the smiling head of Dobbs improve each slackful hour?
What a metros falta!
for all the day from the pipe of power. How skillfully he gets the sale, how much
he earns in cash, and hides it all away in pails from poor stangs reaching grasp.
In frantic work or lazy days we surf the luck plane too. Though the Khan still
screams obey and steals your slack from you. In rant or song or garbled show we
praise Bob and shun the pinks that we may finally err know what we have paid
to think. People like I said before are robots. That's how people are. If you put
an idea in their head like you know you love me and they're gonna want to follow
the life of the party.
Bob! Bob! Open the door! Bob! It's about to-
Bob! Bob! Open up!
Bob! Bob! Open the door!
Bob! Bob! Bob! Bob! Bob! Open up!
Bob!
Don't be a dick to me!
Bob! I'm trying to help you!
Bob is a self-described corporate guy. Bob was also friends with people on the board
of bad outcomes. One day this banker friend handed Bob a cardboard box but he got nowhere.
I swear to God if I get you slacking off one more time I'll shove a bird!
Mr. Johnson why don't you just chill out?
It's okay.
It is okay. See you in church.
The Labor Department says I'm PR's Pope at the Vatican. On Wall Street 44 14374.
The White House says Vice President Joe Biden says this is PR.
The government says Biden has pleaded not guilty in a New York federal court today.
The White House says he died earlier this week after a battle with PR News in Washington.
PR News. PR News Washington.
The funeral for Venezuela President Hugo Chavez is armed against terror suspects, including Cuban President Raul Castro.
South Korea's new president says he won't talk about the president's death.
The White House says he will tolerate PR News in Washington.
Washington came first and he was perfect.
John Adams kept us out of war with France.
Jefferson made a Louisiana Purchase.
In 1812 James Madison kicked the British in the pants.
James Monroe told Europe they could suck it.
John Quincy Adams looked just like his dad.
Andrew Jackson was a great man.
Jackson got rid of all the Indians.
Van Buren served one term but he wasn't bad.
William Henry Harrison died early.
John Tyler annexed Texas from Mexico.
James K. Pope fought Mexico to keep it.
Taylor was a Mexican war hero.
Fillmore gave a boat to Commodore Perry.
Pierce appealed to Missouri Compromise.
Up 앉ed Texas.
H МУ
W ELI
This is America's 올해
conceived the historic U.S. through來
enk שלress heading of America's 올해
General Grant enjoyed a drink or two
Rutherford B. Hayes ended Reconstruction
Garfield was assassinated in 1882
Arthur suspended Chinese immigration
Cleveland made the railroad people squirm
Harrison signed the Sherman Antitrust Act
Grover Cleveland served another term
McKinley kicked the Spanish out of Cuba
Roosevelt was handy with a gun
Taft was big and fat and had a mustache
Wilson kicked some ass in World War I
Harding said let's laissez-faire with business
Coolidge made the roaring 20s roar
Hoover screwed the pooch in the Great Depression
Roosevelt beat the Nazis in the war
Truman dropped the bomb on Hiroshima
Eisenhower kept the commies well in hand
Kennedy was killed by a magic bullet
Johnson lost his job to the Nazis
and murdered kids in Vietnam
Nixon was a sweating, filthy liar
Ford gave Nixon pardon for his crimes
Carter lusted in his heart for peanuts
Reagan won the Cold War and lost his mind
George Bush Senior poked at Saddam Hussein
Clinton gave an intern a cigar
W's legacy's a work in progress
That is all the presidents so far
In the year 2005 we're out of money
Somewhere surely freedom's on the march
I don't like to make political statements
Incoming president chamber of the chamber
and he said if business or a group of businesses
had agreed to pay for all the outcomes period
I know one past life I was a cowboy
and I was shot by accident
and I've met two of my four buddies that I was with together
here and we agreed to come back
on some kind of subliminal basis
so yeah I was a cowboy in one lifetime
probably right before the turn of the century
and my other lifetime I really don't know
but I know I was crushed
and I don't know by what
but probably a large building
I haven't identified the time yet
I'm still working on that
I'm not gonna they've set me up
Patrick T benefit
Patrick T giving us the way
and put in on these locked up
obviously
but I'm not going to let you guess
you can sign on your way
he's really a good son
Wooyah
I'm an fighter
manyangering
come to pass.
And when you join, you'll get two
spare car keys as well as credit
card keys. These keys are made
especially for your car door.
Many makes and months.
They are as thin as a credit card.
And they slip
neatly into your
wife or her bra.
And
you never, ever get
locked out of your vehicle again.
What kind of a bargain is that? And only the
Church of the Subgenius brings you
this astonishing extra.
Can I have two?
Hidden like an Easter egg
in the vast design
of subgenius
artifacts.
And it's
a money back guarantee. Yeehaw!
Eternal salvation or
triple your money back.
And if you order today, you'll get
Bob L. Butt.
Not only blows bubbles from his behind,
but makes farting noises at the same time.
He's a one-man entertainment center
who will keep everyone amused by his
multi-talented tricks.
To activate your farting noise,
humor, mail, express activation
card 1138
to
flatulent subgenius.
Thank you.
P.
Thanks to P.
P.E.
That's puzzling evidence.
Dear friends,
and Dr. Howell
and Philo,
but this isn't going to be one of those
reruns of their shows because we're home.
Or rather, we're in
Cleveland again.
And, oh, the song
there about
the presidents was, of course,
old Johnny Coe,
Joe Coe,
Princess Weave's Shorterper
sad, Jonathan Colton.
We went to see him live
at one point during our long, long
four-month trip.
Notice at the end of that song
about the presidents,
Jonathan Colton
mentioned Bush
and said that was all the
presidents so far. I think that song's
from 2005 or so.
And I understand from the
Wiki, the Joe Coe
Wikipedia, that he, now when he does
that song in concert,
he says something along the lines
of, we're,
we survived despite
George Bush or something like that.
We're cleaning up the mess
and Obama has been
pretty excellent so far.
Then he ends it with,
I don't like to make political
statements, and that's the end.
Now,
friends, if you ask me
about my politics,
that's between me
and Big Brother.
Know what I'm saying?
Know what you're saying.
Know what I'm saying.
Know.
Know what you're saying.
Yes, friends, we were out on the trail
for months, and
it was a great trail.
We learned a lot.
We learned that when you're going out,
the plants on the trail
look gray. Those
one plants, they look gray.
But when you're coming back,
you see that they're actually
blue.
And I'm not going to try
to explain that, but if
you go out on the trail
like we did, you'll
at some point, I know,
I had a vision that at some point
a young lady who listens
to this show, and this would happen
twice in my vision, two different young
ladies would say to the young men
they're with at one point,
coming back from walking on a trail,
they'll say,
now I get it. They were right.
Now I know what staying meant.
The plants were gray going
out, but as we came back,
we could see that they were actually
blue.
And I hope
that one of the young
lady listeners will pick up
on that. We both do.
I hope so, too. Speaking of
young ladies, although
Fernanda and Andy Lee Murr
did the titles and PR news,
all the collages on this episode
were by Reverend
Baby Bear. Or rather,
she sent in a whole bunch of clips,
and then I found ways
to organize them. They may
only make sense to me, but that's the way
it works. And this music in the background
is by Dr.
Zeronius from his band
Cult of Zier.
Spelled
Z-I-R. This is
an instrumental piece called
Impolite
Ice Tulpa.
Another thing
we learned as
we hiked through the great deserts
of the Southwest
is that, you know, it's just not a desert
until you see a cow skull.
We saw the Saguaro
cactuses. Of course, they
only actually exist in the Saguaro
National Park area, but
you know, we did see those.
And we saw
kangaroo rats,
cowboy boots,
and we even saw
a Mexican in a sombrero
sleeping against a cactus.
Mostly on fast food.
Yes, taco shacks.
Yeah, but a couple of times we saw the real
thing. But I was
just thinking, man, it's not
a proper roadrunner versus
Wile E. Coyote
desert unless there's like a
cow skull in the foreground.
Hopefully next to some poisoned
water. Right.
With a poisoned skull sign
on it. But finally,
I think in Grand Staircase
Escalante,
we did indeed,
come upon the proverbial
rotting cow carcass.
And I got a
nice shot of it
in the foreground in our
van, the I-van
in the background. Which I still haven't
managed to bare my eyes
upon, but I know that I will.
She has a saying, don't look
at dead things.
Don't even look at them.
Weren't we going to do a movie called Children
Shouldn't Play With Dead Things, or did somebody
else already make that movie? No, I thought you'd like to see it.
I liked Don't Look at Dead Things.
I thought you actually liked that as a title of the
movie. Well, listen,
the psycho skeletons have started up
in the background. This is
an instrumental piece called
Ghetto Princess
by Reverend Basil
of the Psycho
Skeletons. I think he's the Basil
one there.
I was expecting
Lonesome Cowboy Dave to call
in. We're in
anxiety whether he will still
have the buzz on.
Friends, we need to get Dave a new
phone. Well, actually, it's not the phone.
I think it's all the wiring in his house.
Or perhaps
one of those newfangled things they
call a cell phone.
I actually have
one in my pocket right now. This is the first
year that I've actually carried a
wireless telephone.
Can you believe it? But I'm going to
modernize
my son taught me everything
I know, and he taught me that I need
to quote.
I'm quoting myself.
But he's
right. I do need to spend his
inheritance and
upgrade my own equipment.
I need an iPhone and an iPad
and an iPod
and an iPlaystation 3
and an iXbox
and about an iMillion
dollars. We have to do it without
spending their...
Inheritance.
It's not fair.
I'll be able to give him more inheritance once I make
some money after I
modernize. I've got to
keep up with the Joneses.
Okay. All right.
Oh, what else
did we see that was wonderful on
our trip? Friends, we saw
every kind of novelty dinosaur.
Oh, speaking of which, here's a
novelty dinosaur calling in now.
Testing. Testing.
Testing.
Hello?
Dave? That's no Dave.
That doesn't mean any good at all.
Did I hang up on him?
I hope not.
Well,
I just don't know.
We'll wait and see what the next call
brings. Maybe that was
Dave and the buzz
has become so
powerful on his phone that it sounds
like a dial tone.
And that was him.
We just couldn't hear him.
He was over it.
Now, he may have to call back again.
I don't know. Of course, somebody else might try to call in
and trick us, but that won't
last long.
As I was saying,
we saw novelty dinosaurs
made of everything. It wasn't just
dinosaurs. There was occasional bears
and Indians and cowboys made of
car parts,
lawnmowers,
driftwood,
dinosaurs made of nails,
dinosaurs made of sheet metal,
dinosaurs made of duct tape,
PVC,
coffee cans.
The most impressive was a dinosaur made
completely out of arrowheads.
Deer antlers.
I mean,
if you drive around
America, or at least the
wrinkly parts of America long enough,
you will see some amazing
novelty dinosaurs.
That's all I can say.
We don't have any of the pictures up
on our website yet.
Because there are thousands
of them.
We just need to
kind of narrow them down to
3,000 or so.
Oh yeah, we've got quite a photo
collection of giant cocks.
That is roosters.
I don't know, friends, if you've noticed
the prevalence of eight
foot tall sheet metal
roosters in America.
And we'll just put some other
in the background here.
Some surf music.
Just generic surf music.
This is good to drive
to. Yeah, this is great driving music.
Friends, we...
Now, don't be jealous, because Princess
Wee pretended to like the
others at her time
weather control job, rather,
for 30 years.
And I put up with
you people for 30 years.
And I still had to work on the road.
I mean, literally
filling orders and
preaching Bob and even
somewhat
assembling radio shows from
inside the car.
Or various
rest areas and roach motels.
Friends, we could tell you everything
about the roach motels of
America. Pest Western.
Don't believe
Pest Western's
rewards program. It is
a come on and a
small print lie.
It is a lie.
They tricked us.
Yeah, we fell for
Pest Western's rewards program.
Don't do it. Don't even.
Don't even think about it.
They won't honor it until it is
no longer
being offered.
Until it is no longer
of any use to you.
Right, and certainly not to us.
America's Pest Value
was another roach motel.
Some of those are good.
Some of them are terrible.
Mediocre Lodge was
god-awful in Albuquerque.
But the one in Fredericksburg
is not
mediocre at all.
In fact, it's economic.
It's an econo-lodge.
Econo-mediocre?
And you would be surprised, but every now
and then, a Motel 6 is the
best place in town. Next time we
go to Las Vegas, we'll certainly return
to the downtown Las Vegas
Motel 6.
That was so gruesome.
Because it was priced right.
They left the lights on for us.
But weirdest of all, it was all
futuristic Jetsons
Las Vegas-y looking.
It was like a space module.
Yeah, yeah, it was like a space module.
It was all orange and white
and big round bubbly things.
It was crazy.
But we rewarded our very
last motel we stayed in
just outside of Mammoth
Cave, in fact, in Cave City,
Kentucky.
We finally paid for and
stayed in a wigwam
motel. Those are those
not exactly ubiquitous
teepee-shaped
motels. There was a chain
of them. There were at least eight.
We've seen and photographed
the one in El Paso,
but that may be a different chain.
I don't know. Anyway, friends, wigwam
motels, one shaped like teepees.
I know you've always wanted to try
one. You always wondered if they're cone-shaped.
On the inside,
yes and no.
There's a low ceiling, so you don't get
the full cone, but it is basically
a circular room.
It feels a little bit more like you're staying
in a lighthouse. Yeah,
it's almost kind of lighthouse-like.
And of course, they have
the one we were in
was cold.
So it was a little bit like staying
in a real teepee.
Not quite as smoky.
But
it's a little bit like a real teepee.
But it's a little bit like a real teepee.
It's definitely worth it.
Come on, when you were a kid
in the 50s, and your parents
were driving across the southwest
on their way to San Diego for that
naval officers convention,
didn't you wistfully
stare at those teepee motels
as you went by going,
why can't we stay in those?
Of course. Absolutely.
But then you saw the place
your parents had picked to stay in
with a swimming pool
and everything.
Everything was okay.
Because that's what counts to a kid.
So yeah, we learned all about
the brooch motels of America.
We kept
the bats
of the American caves from getting
white nose syndrome
by contracting it ourselves.
And hantavirus,
we took that away from the rodents.
Yeah, Dave has not called.
Dave has not called back. I'm looking for a little green light.
Is that a Dave?
Yes.
Oh my God.
The buzz is almost louder
than the dial tone.
It is louder than the dial tone.
Did you
put some spit on it and rub it
and jiggle it a little
and kind of move it around and shove it in and out?
I thought it was nose grease.
I did the woo dance.
I did all kinds of weird stuff
and it didn't make a darn bit of difference.
Your phone
is like my brain
and the PlayStation 3
that my nephew gave me.
It's been sitting there
restoring the hard disk
for 48 hours now.
Actually, I gave up.
It's
I
thought I had a PlayStation 3
and then it didn't.
Unless I could.
Hey, the buzz went down.
It went down?
Yeah, you've been spitting on it, haven't you?
You dribbled on that buzz.
I was doing some more stuff.
I was making some more woo dance noises.
Well, the woo woo dance is good.
I can actually hear the background now.
Yeah.
Surf music background.
Bob, we don't need background.
We'll just have Dave do that.
Dave and his buzz can keep the show going
for how much longer do we have?
Another 20 minutes or so.
Oh my God.
Dave's buzz is like a surf
behind the surf music.
It's a low shushing sound.
Yeah, it's the surf shush.
The sound of the tectonic plates moving.
It doesn't sound like it.
It's the plate in my head.
I noticed it was some sort of fractal
kind of interference coming through my brain
when I was messing with the other phone.
I heard like computer noises.
Like...
I think I've been dishonorably discharged
from the foreign servers
by having the...
someone messing with my phone.
No one's messing with your phone, Dave.
Besides you.
You could...
I mean, I know we want to blame the conspiracy,
but I think you need a new everything.
I know I do.
I mean, we really...
Princess, we and I kind of need a new everything.
I need a new shoulder socket.
I'm not kidding about that.
You don't know.
It may be able to be rehabbed or...
I don't know.
Shot with cortisone and fixed.
You just don't know yet.
I'll try the Chinese medicines first
because, you know, that's a lot of money,
all that rotator cuff stuff and everything.
Yeah.
I'll have to ask Isaac Bonowitz
about that Chinese medicine.
Now, now.
That wasn't Chinese medicine.
That's not a Chinese name.
Let's see.
I'll ask...
Ding, ding, doink.
Dave, Princess, we and I have been studying...
I've noticed that.
Well, I mean, we're wandering around all these places
like Valley of Fire in Nevada and Red Rock Canyon,
and we even made it to Goblin Valley,
Goblin Valley State Park in Utah.
These massive eruptions from the subconscious of the Earth
disturb everybody that sees them.
Oh, we love those eruptions from the Earth.
The weather.
Whether they are still merely igneous
or if they devolved into sedimentary rock
or even if they became metamorphic rock.
It's twisted under pressure,
just like Superman can change a piece of coal into a diamond
just by gripping it.
Think of what he can do to your testicle.
That wasn't where I was going with that.
Well, for the rest of us,
they usually band together,
and the friction itself is what causes the decrease
in onerous pressure.
Your voice sounds like it's being rubbed between two rocks.
I have to tell you one thing before I get cut off
or I forget to tell you forever.
My ex-wife's husband...
That would be you, Dave.
No, no, my ex...
Oh, the current husband.
No, my ex-wife's current husband
finds these huge, as big as a house,
fossils of dinosaurs and stuff
near where he hangs out there
and doesn't want to tell anybody.
And all the museums know him.
And stuff.
Where is he finding these?
He's finding them...
In Ohio?
Yes.
The Ohio-saurus.
In the Northeastern Ohio area.
And apparently, our understanding of the bizarre geology
of the Great Lakes and the Great Ocean
that covered everything,
and that was in many different stages,
and there's all kinds of poppins,
but not like the ones in the Southwest,
so I'll shut up now.
Could an Ohio-saurus defeat a Dunkleosteus?
Which is a...
A Texasaurus?
No, no.
A Dunkleosteus actually is an Ohio
primitive-fit giant fish-like thing.
Before they were really even fish,
I think it had an exoskeleton.
Yeah.
There's one down at the Natural History Museum in Cleveland.
Its face is the size of a Volkswagen.
Oh, my...
Easily.
Yeah.
Did it have, like, dorsal finage and stuff like that there?
This thing is so monstrous.
It's so monstrous that it had shells for eyelids.
It has bony eyelids,
or some kind of a...
like a camera iris set up...
Yes.
...with bones over its hideous, black, baleful eyes.
Well, I think your evolutionists are making them up in the basement,
and then they're producing them,
and they're putting them on there,
and they're...
And people fall for it,
because they're so stupid.
Everybody's so stupid.
It don't prove nothing.
God still made the Earth in two and a half hours.
Stooped.
To some.
I just deliberately left a bit of buzz on the air there
so that I can hopefully filter that out.
I'm not going to put up with this forever.
However, I will tell you...
It did not decrease then again.
Well, it's back up again, it seems like.
The thing is, it's hard for me to tell
whether it's your phone or my tinnitus or what,
but I know it's not WCSB,
this fine radio station,
from which we're recording this show.
Yes, normally.
If it doesn't have Dave on it,
or subgenius shows,
oh, well.
It sounds pretty sweet in there.
Well, there are other times when people have worse reception
or transmission than others,
and this just happens to be one of those foregone conclusions.
Right.
Now, hopefully every driver out there
listening in their car,
poor things,
can't hear anything,
because the buzz,
and the road noise combine
to make everything sound about the way I hear it,
which is like this.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's the way I hear it all right.
Yeah, like that.
So, Mr. Chinley Greenness,
Princess, we and I had to make up
our own geological descriptive terms,
because we were coming upon rocks
that were so amazing looking,
and so many...
There were so many different kinds.
Usually, each given national park area
has its own distinctive look,
but some of them, like Death Valley,
have all of them scattered about.
But we didn't really...
You know, some...
There are names for things,
these rock formations,
like fins and flutes and so forth,
but we didn't really...
And some of them aren't really that accurate.
So we came up...
I'm going to tell you some of the new descriptions
of rock formations,
for instance, I forget where it was,
maybe Valley of Fire,
but we realized that everywhere you looked,
there were sleeping Tyrannosauruses,
not just any dinosaur.
They were all either Tyrannosauruses
or Allosauruses,
or one of those big carnivores.
Yes, sleeping.
Sleeping.
All of them laying on their chins,
on their bellies, sleeping.
Sometimes there would be a sleeping Tyrannosaurus
within a sleeping Tyrannosaurus,
within an even bigger...
There were bigger sleeping Tyrannosaurus,
but it's like you kept seeing the same pattern everywhere.
The rocks were all slanted,
going down a certain way,
and they all ended with this sort of a jawbone
and a skull eye,
and it was just sleeping Tyrannosauruses
all the way down.
By the same token,
you go around Zion National Park,
and everywhere you look, there's what...
Well, for the radio audience,
I'll say white breasts.
We had a somewhat more...
Blunt name for what...
They're really called Navajo sandstone domes,
but to us, they were white...
Big, swelling white bosoms.
They're pretty.
They're real pretty.
At the Trona Pinnacles,
where the Tim Burton Planet of the Apes was shot,
we noticed that there was row upon row
of building-sized rock formations
that all looked like...
like a surprised crab
with his claws or mittens
sticking up out of the ground on either side.
And he always had his antenna raised in surprise.
All of the...
It was just...
We saw the first crab with mittens
and thought, wow, that's amazing.
That huge rock for me looks like crab with mittens.
Let's go see what's behind it.
But there was another crab with mittens.
Behind that, another surprised crab with mittens.
Well, I understand the mittens part,
and I can see how, like,
big, big...
Mitten-like things could cover them,
little claws and stuff.
But how in the hell do you register
or understand what a surprised crab looks like?
Is his...
Are his little eyes bigger than yours?
No, because he's got his mittens up in surprise.
His mittens...
It's the way he's displaying his claws.
He looks like he's going...
Ah!
Ah.
Yeah, it's like, ooh, humans, gross.
So it's the gesture of those two little...
Yes, it's the gesture.
Yes.
I thought perhaps you were reading something into, you know...
The face of a crab.
It might be a reading...
...high-contact language or something.
Well, now, of course, there are some places
of types of landscape.
We call them crazy all kinds of faces and shapes land.
I have seen those.
Well, Princess Wee can see a face in everything
when she's at one of those.
Oh, yeah.
I hear that.
Let's see.
Yeah, those are kind of a wild card.
They look like anything.
They start taking on demonic, you know, appurtenances.
Yeah.
After a certain period of time.
Right.
Just a few swirls in some linoleum and bam, I've got a demon.
Or I've got an angel.
Or an ape.
Or a common ape face.
Or a clown.
Yes.
Or a baby.
Or a clown, baby, ape face.
Well, that's...
You find all of those in crazy face pancake lip land.
It's a modular Cretan highway, too.
You can go to where they have small hoodoos that we call hoodoos.
Hoodoo toddlers.
They're like very skinny mushroom head things.
There was...
Well, Princess Wee named one type of chinly formation, the giant's toes.
And they do look like giant's toes.
They do look like giant's toes.
There's dripping paint rocks, chocolate wafer rocks, cinnamon pancake rocks,
mint and chocolate ice cream swirl.
Schmooze.
That was one.
It's kind of an all-purpose.
Oh, the albino Cthulhu type, which is...
The albino Cthulhu type?
Yeah, that was inside of Carlsbad Caverns.
Right, you run into those in caves.
Hideous, nameless, eldritch creatures from the time beyond time.
When limestone and water drip slowly for a long, long time.
Scalagmite.
Yes, scalagmite.
They make Cthulhi.
Cthulhu.
Albino Cthulhu.
Cthulhu type.
That's a new...
Oh, yeah.
It's scary, too.
Fake bricks.
I've often urinated to that sound.
You occasionally find places where they've built the theme park so shoddily
that the rocks look like fake bricks.
And basically...
I've got a handy and holy relic over here.
You know, Princess Wee thinks all those things are formed by nature.
She doesn't understand that Monument Valley and Death Valley,
and all of them, Mammoth Cave, all of those were manufactured, you know.
Like Disneyland.
Yeah.
In a laboratory?
Well, I mean, they hire the finest migrant artists and rock carvers.
So they can pay them less.
Yeah.
But they do a great job.
I mean, when they make those balloon toots, the rocks that I call balloon toots,
Uh-huh.
The one with the giraffes on the side?
The little toy figures?
I guess maybe when you were growing up, balloon toots didn't mean the same thing
that they meant when Pappy referred to.
Don't kick your brother in the balloon toots again.
Ah.
That hurts.
Tiki heads, the Easter Island heads that weren't carved.
Yes.
Because they really are the heads of giants that are buried up to their neck in the dirt.
And have calcified over the years.
And were mostly...
Mostly of a meteorological content to begin with, which is, you know,
gets back to a lot of your Cthulhu messages.
Your Cthulhu kind of inner messages were like there is a war between the gods below the earth.
The titans, actually.
They call them the Pinto Bean Boys.
Well, there were Pinto Bean Boy titans that carved Monument Valley.
Really?
They're childish titans, but they get a lot done.
We went to the Devil's Drive-In.
We saw the honeycomb hideout of Martian honeycombs.
Oh, the Devil's Liquor Cabinet.
That was one of my favorites.
You can really get lost in there.
That's a silly talking doll.
But the craziest rocks of all are the ones that Princess Weave labeled Corn Starch on Speakers.
After...
When you put liquid cornstarch on speakers and turn the speakers on, the cornstarch dances.
It jumps around and forms the most incredible shapes.
Yeah, shapes grow up out of it.
If you hired a public speaker to a corn dance and you poured some liquid on he or she,
then they would start dancing the corn dance in what now?
Cornstarch on speakers.
Cornstarch mud.
Yeah, you have to...
You have to be able to change your shape.
Cornstarch with cold water and it makes mud.
And then you put that on a speaker and you put the sound through it.
And the sound going through that colloidal suspension makes these crazy shapes grow up out of the cornstarch mud.
Yeah, Google it.
Google YouTube.
Google this phrase.
YouTube cornstarch on speakers.
I know how to make pudding, so just don't worry about me having to Google about cornstarch on speakers.
But no, no.
Don't start Googling.
Don't start Googling while we're right in front of everybody on the radio.
If you make pudding, it'll ruin everything.
I can't already stop what I already started by God's man.
No pudding.
Cold cornstarch in water.
Cold, cold.
What else did we have?
I think there's the nude gargoyle rocks.
Man, those are scary.
I can't say some of the types of cracks.
I can't even look at those.
But my favorite parts were the ones that had...
that looked like my monster hunter tri landscapes
that have good gathering spots and fishing spots and...
As long as you avoid where the baroth and the carupaco go.
And the bull fangos.
And bub-el butts.
And bub-el butts, yeah.
Bub-el butts?
Yeah.
Yeah, that was from...
I don't know, but Hal was talking...
I was talking about the bub-el butts earlier in this show.
Oh, a person's name.
A person's name, bub-el butt.
Yeah.
Yeah, Chinley.
That's right.
Mr. Chinley Greenness.
The proper name would be bub-er or bub-er-inus or something.
Or moinkopi.
The loincloth.
Moinkopi.
One of our favorite places was everywhere you looked,
there was windgate rock on top.
Windgate.
Which is the smooth...
What they call it?
Shred.
It's slippery rock or sheer rock or...
Slip rock or something.
Yeah.
Yes.
Then there would be a layer of Chinley, which was...
Slick rock.
Could come in every...
Slick rock, that's right.
And then Chinley, which was more like giant toes shape,
and comes in all colors.
Blue, turquoise, pink, purple, white, every color.
Bright colors.
In the artist's ghetto part of Death Valley,
all of those colors are mixed.
And Princess Wee and I kept going back to that place.
We wouldn't leave Death Valley for three days
because we were waiting for the sun to come out.
It rained.
It rained in Death Valley.
When we got to Death Valley,
the driest place in the universe,
at the lowest place below sea level,
222 feet below sea level,
they get two inches of rain a year.
And...
You were coming to have a great take.
We had to worry about our engine getting flooded in Death Valley.
Well, at least you didn't have to worry about your ancestors
forcing their way back into the common market.
No.
No, we didn't.
We did have to worry about getting flooded in the middle of Death Valley,
which was really unusual.
It was like...
One minute, there's this salt, dried salt lake,
bad water basin.
Hottest, lowest place in the world.
Next minute, it's an actual lake
with a couple of feet of water in it.
All of a sudden, 10 minutes later,
it's a dry salt flat again.
But boy, there's a lot of happy little frogs
and newts and mud-dwelling things
that only come out once a year.
In that one particular spot,
separating the cold...
I mean, the fresh from the bracken water.
Oh, God, we learned the most horrible thing,
the saddest thing about a desert,
an endangered desert creature called the desert tortoise.
The desert tortoise only gets to drink
maybe every year or two.
Holy crap.
So it takes them a long, long time to fill their bladder.
And that's what they keep as reserve water
in case they go a year or two with no water at all.
But here's the thing.
If someone...
If some little 12-year-old Pobucker boy,
some little Kwait or Monsko boy
comes up and scares that tortoise,
it will flush all of its water out.
It will void its water, all of it.
And it might take it another five years
to build up one single decent urination.
Bladderful.
What a valuable lesson for kids today.
Do not attempt to frighten a desert tortoise.
You will literally scare...
It's bladder for five years.
Right.
You'll scare the water out of it.
You may have a hard time breaking the, you know,
contents of what you're saying down
so the children understand what you're actually saying.
Don't frighten the tortoise or he'll pee too much.
But I think when they hear the final part of it
about going to the bathroom or making a turtle pee...
Oh, they'll just run around looking for those turtles
and scaring them deliberately.
Let's make him pee five years' worth of his life away.
Because we're stupid kids.
And they'll be facing each other a bunch of weird pictures they drew
of things that actually scare them worse.
And then the thing will just keep multiplying and multiplying
and it'll go geometric and stuff.
Well, everywhere you go, there's bacteria.
And we've got ten minutes to go, Dave.
And I'm going to...
Because of that and the buzz,
I'm going to fade you out
and let us end this show with some more music
and some more music.
There's a Rudy Schwartz project song coming up.
And we hit this.
Jonathan Colton.
One last time.
Bacteria.
Look, there's bacteria.
You might not see them, but they're there.
Bacteria.
Everything you touch.
That's right.
Salmonella bacteria.
But we have to watch out for bacteria.
That can spoil our chicken.
Bacteria practically everywhere.
Everywhere you look.
In the kitchen.
Inside the cooler.
In the dining area.
In the restrooms.
On our raw chicken.
And like I said, bacteria.
Bacteria.
Look, there's bacteria.
You might not see them, but they're there.
Bacteria.
Everything you touch.
That's right.
Salmonella bacteria.
Salmonella grows on raw chicken, especially old chicken.
Moist foods like our salad, staph bacteria on the left, and strep bacteria on the right.
Salmonella.
Shigella.
Clostridium.
If you didn't wash your hands, they would become breeding grounds for bacteria.
Bacteria.
Look, there's bacteria.
You might not see them, but they're there.
Bacteria.
Everything you touch.
That's right.
Salmonella bacteria.
Fever.
Cramps and fever.
Dysentery.
Fever.
V-v-v-fever.
Vomiting.
Chills.
Cramps.
And chills and cramps.
One square inch.
Half a billion.
Salmonella bacteria.
These bacteria really sound so good.
It's a good thing they're in the series.
They are when they're left unchecked.
And it could mean a trip to the hospital.
For someone.
Our customers.
Wow.
Ourselves.
All right.
Our chicken.
And our reputation.
All right.
You mean bacteria on me right now?
Clean, clean and then clean again.
Bacteria.
Look, there's bacteria.
You might not see them, but they're there.
Bacteria.
Everything you touch.
That's right.
Salmonella bacteria.
So, do the new ones redeem as much of a Bobby's soul as the old pamphlets?
Oh, more.
I know the shows that take the show to.
The new ones are much more highly compressed and efficient.
The new pamphlets can actually extract up to 99.9% of a Bobby's soul in less than nine
tenths of a second.
So, the definitely, the slack, you can acquire a whole lot more slack faster and at cheaper
cost with the new more efficient subgenius pamphlets.
Yes, even you, those of you who have, who can barely discern white from black, day from
night, no reflection upon your vision of course.
It is important to make those distinctions.
Are asking those, those decisions.
Making those decisions in the help book of Jader.
From PR News in Washington, I'm stretched for a mile and a half.
President Obama pleaded not guilty to conspiring to kill Americans.
The White House says the President will also have more to say on the topic next week when
he visits Chicago.
The President has said conspiring to kill Americans is among his main priorities during
his second term.
Rupert Murdoch's News Corp. says it is 67-14-397.
That's right.
PR News.
The Labor Department says you're listening to PR News in Washington.
You can do incredible tricks automatically.
Especially designed pool rooms.
Hey, is there any tie between Bob's wife Connie and the conspiracy?
Obviously.
There's obviously a connection there.
You seem to have penetrated a simple analog in the allegory.
Right.
There's no doubt that the word con in Connie and the con in conspiracy all are composed
of the very same letters of the alphabet.
Yeah.
You see it is necessary for the society.
You're a subgenius to embrace the conspiracy and even to have carnal relations with the
conspiracies.
To a certain degree, only in the interest of avoiding it, eventually, and finding slack.
We hate to do it, but carnal relations are carnal relations.
And somewhere slack has to be obtained where you find it.
And what about the rest of the world?
The, um...
I don't care about them.
We don't care about them.
We want them to care about themselves.
I care about me.
I care about my wife.
And through caring about themselves, they can care about us.
Oh, true subgeniuses.
Well, they have plenty of things to care about.
I mean, like people who buy clothes for people.
We know that everyone must love themselves before they can love another person.
It's tough to stand by, et cetera, uh...
Et cetera, et cetera, et cetera.
Hello?
You know, the ones who buy lots of stuff.
Well, you can do that too, but those are the prosumers.
If they buy what they want, that's the important thing.
You're talking about prosumers who are professional buyers.
Just like Homer Simpson says, donuts of the world beware of the
world.
It's judgment day.
Yeah.
He didn't say that.
Wait a minute, he didn't?
Well, it says that right here in the script.
Are you one to challenge the script writer?
No.
Pay attention to these flowers.
No, no, no.
They are not...
That's been done before, and those people aren't around anymore.
Heh, heh, heh.
Few know what I mean.
Um, also, we had an anonymous message...
They're out hip-hopping in a hot rod.
...some callers are gonna come down, and I guess they're here now.
Oh.
We're going to interview these folks.
Did I ever do that?
I'll break you up.
They're out hip-hopping in a hot rod.
I'm gonna be on the air.
Sure, when you were a big kid, you could drive.
You could come down to the show.
I've heard that if you have at least three shows on your hard drive, your computer will
run faster.
Um, it's, uh...
Now the ball gags are placed in...
If you've downloaded at least three shows from...
Well, I mean, uh, Serpent X is much harder to say, because I like to just say QuiveringBrain.com.
It's more like an education service.
If you go to www.QuiveringBrain.com, I'm gonna put up a link to the show, and you can
find the link for the Puzzling Evidence, uh, show.
Is that Puzzling Evidence plus P show?
Is that the one you're, uh...
Well, they're all there, even the ones without P.
Oh.
I did.
P and Slack, same stuff.
It can be.
I always thought that...
Well, I just wanna know three things.
P, damn, ass.
What does that have to do with anything?
That's what I've gotta find out, and that's your challenge here at the last waning few
minutes of the show.
And rewind to the show.
So, Carl, 848-4425, and...
I'm gonna put away my stuff.
No, you can't call, because you've already called.
Because your mom said so.
End of show.
You're all beautiful right now.
You have to hang up and call back to call.
Bob, it was awesome meeting you.
This has been an incredible three days.
This is a good thing.
Right.
Okay.
Bob, best of luck.
Thanks, man.
Hey, Eli Green!
HEY, EDITASS!
HE CALLS Girls
to seduce complete record collectors into buying multiple copies of the same release.
Rudy, that's not very nice.
No shit, Waldo. And to make the whole scam even more insulting,
let's start off with a pointless little ditty on the subject of vomit.
Vomit?
That's right, Waldo. Vomit. Go grab a corn dog and pull up a chair.
Okay.
I would have preferred an assassin's pubic hair.
Who was a-rockin' and a-rollin' with a boogie woogie blue?
Good God Almighty, make my puke just turn blue!
Twistin' and a-frugin' and a-shoot-a-doop-a-doo!
Turn out the lights! Turn out the lights!
Turn out the lights and let my vomit come through!
Well, poppers in the kitchen could be a good idea.
Hypnoggy beats too.
Mommas havin' sex with the pot-black crew.
Sisters got a yeast inflation, don't know what to do.
Turn out the lights! Turn out the lights!
Turn out the lights and let my vomit come through!
Hey, oh, rockin' Terry, rockin'!
Turn out the lights! Turn out the lights!
Turn out the lights and let my vomit come through!
Oh, sweet patootie, Bud's got a beauty!
Who has put pubic hair on my coke?
Well, Jerry Cossett suckin' on Arsenio's dick!
Bud's got a corn dog roasted on a stick!
Satan's got a present that he wants to give to you!
Turn out the lights! Turn out the lights!
Turn out the lights and let my vomit come through!
I said, I'd turn out the lights! Turn out the lights!
Turn out the lights and let my...
...pot-black crew!
You've been listening to the subgenius radio ministry Hour of Slack.
For free information,
write to P.O. Box 181-417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118
or see www.subgenius.com
Praise Bob!
For Sire, there is no more money!
We gotta get some money!
That dirty purgish hark of backflag!
We wantin' Philip Buck to Burton!
Perkaluma Burton!
Thurton first tonight!
Beep! Beep! Beep!
Friends, we're glad you listened to this show,
and we're even more glad that some listeners have donated enough to help us keep on going for another couple of months.
Not just this show, but subgenius.com and all the other archive sites.
Bob! Bob! Bob! Bob!
But if you truly love Bob,
and want some of that slack back to rebound to you,
you should go to subgenius.com front page,
or especially the radio page,
or the catalog store pages,
and help out financially as best you can.
Now, we know what it's like to be on the brink of total poverty,
and we don't want any subgeniuses to make their own situations worse.
But some of you still have jobs.
Even five bucks makes a big difference,
even if it's only once a month,
from enough of you.
Fifty bucks makes an even bigger difference.
All we're saying is that
blowjobs could go the way of Steve Jobs,
if you don't pay Dobbs.
We also take checks and money orders to
Subgenius Foundation.
P.O. Box 181-417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio.
44118.
Thanks for anything you can do to help let there be slack.
Subtitles by the Amara.org community