You are about to experience the awe and mystery which reaches from the inner mind to the subgenius hour of SWAT.
Yes, and let's just go directly to the new Negative Land CD.
This is Negative Land, Time Zone's exchange project.
It's a beautiful, beautiful thing.
Executive Window will bring you information more quickly and concisely in a form suited to your leadership role.
Using symbols and color codes augmented with sound and motion,
your Executive Window will communicate the status of projects and corporate measurements of interest to you.
Radio Moscow World Service presents Sidewalk Survey.
Your hosts, Paula.
Laura Garb and George Morzin.
Hello, everybody.
Hello.
Lately, we've received letters asking about what people in this country know and think about the various riddles scientists are working on.
Well, for instance, the Bermuda Triangle, unidentified flying objects, various lake monsters, and last but not least, the so-called Abominable Snowman.
The Abominable Snowman.
Just by way of explanation, this so-called snowman is called Sasquatch in Canada.
Since that's what the local Indians first named the beings they claim to have come across for centuries.
Oh, yes, dear friends.
This is Hour of Slack number 1768.
But it's really a rerun.
Trying to save time.
And crank shows up faster, which means more reruns.
Luckily, I have all the old Hour of Slack cassette type masters from the old days.
All at Stang Ranch here in Texas.
And I asked listeners for suggestions of favorite reruns.
And somebody, I can't remember who, suggested number 468.
Which would be from, I guess, the late 80s, early 90s.
I fetched that tape and the label, hand label on it said that it has a Negative Land CD that was brand new at that time called Time Zones Project.
And I guess it probably has a label on it.
It's a whole lot of that CD.
But it also says here,
Rant on Internet, comma, alt.slack, Starwood, miscellaneous rant, diet, good and evil, the soul, Nissan Bob, normal bobs, the Canadian false bob, and then more Time Zone from Negative Land.
So, I haven't heard this myself.
We'll be listening to it for the first time together.
And I hope that I don't sound too embarrassingly young and earnest.
But if I recall correctly, it's me trying to explain to people what the Internet is all about.
This would have to be, I guess, in the middle 90s now that I think about it.
I think I started cluing in and using America Online or something around 1994.
So, praise Bob.
Praise Negative Land.
Praise reruns.
Huh.
I know that you won't hear this until you return to Howland.
And by that time, your negotiations should be complete and successful.
I want to congratulate you and all the people on the team there on the island for a job grandly done.
As I listen to these tapes of your departure to the Soviet Union, I am filled with pride and admiration.
Idish submission.
And also recognize your enthusiasm for the US, the whole America, the pier.
It was a prior to that, I hope the next financial crisis doesn't get any worse.
Thank you for being with you tonight.
That was wonderful.
You were here to talk about
peace, wandering through
the time with me tonight.
So, thank you.
And thanks again to
The second gonna be at the end of the show two at a time, after which we're going on늘 haven at the same time, et cetera.
I'm fucking here and haven't heard from you.
Ugh.
I'm just kidding.
Thank you, thanks.
Lucy did, but I believe especially in documentary areas to begin with, we will
gain a great deal of needed respect. I don't mean to say that...
Note to my secretary, the memo began to go a bit astray from my original plans
there and some negativity began to creep in. Please delete those implications.
As I listen to you climb into your P-38 and take off from that beautiful island,
I can only hope that...
Note to my secretary, I have the tapes from Howland on freeze frame at the moment at a very interesting section.
It appears to me that Mr. Howard Hughes was on the island at the time of Mr. Friday's departure.
Would you please look into this? I understood that Mr. Hughes was dead.
You'll find him appearing in a white shirt to the left of the P-38 at frame 608.
6014. 6014. I believe that's the first image of him.
Hmm. Oh. Hmm. Where's that unlock code?
Oh yeah, there it is. Okay, let's see what this says.
Good morning, Mr. Edge. This is Bud Winkle out on Howland.
We have...
I'm Mr. Friday's chief of temporal insertion, and I'm presently handling the late 20th century media insertions for the historical trans-infiltration task force here at NetWeb headquarters.
Now, I'm not permitted to reveal what year it is here now, of course, but let me assure you, a lot has happened since you died.
Mr. Friday is presently vacationing out on the crystal wheel, but his 2020 hindsight seems to only improve when he's off planet.
I have just as...
Well, we could use that as an excuse.
I would say some preçofupe.
Forgive my tampering.
I really hope the addresses in the deal will be any less of a hassle, and make the audacity better this evening.
With quickly from the beginning of these auditions for today, through anyเพ deine
mathematics , I hope the hard work we had slowly towards
designed for the Soviet population.
It has perhaps already occurred to you
that while the old order of Soviet society has been dumped,
there has been virtually no practical preparation
in Soviet culture to replace it with what they said they wanted.
From our vantage point here in the future, Mr. Edge,
we need to quickly insert the functional aspects
of a free market economy into the collective Soviet mentality
to avoid the approaching chaotic derailment
of their economy in your time.
You know, learning to buy is easy.
They must learn how to sell.
If this works, and Mr. Friday is confident it will,
it will immediately open all of the Soviet republics
to the unhindered distribution and sale of Mertz,
which in turn will change their decision
to prevent Pride All Labs from mining
the Mertz enhancer chemical, Cephysate,
which will soon be discovered in that big crater in Siberia.
And with the exclusive rights to Soviet Cephysate
from the Soviet government,
Pride All Labs swamped the future synthetic competition
in metal supplements, providing the funds now necessary
to finally corner the ice mining market
by buying the Braided Ring of Saturn.
And then, well, oh, forgive me, Mr. Edge,
I'm telling you more than you need to know.
Sometimes I'm like a kid in a history store.
Oh, in your time frame, Mr. Friday is now at Radio Moscow
in his capacity as director of the Time Zones Exchange Project
for UMN.
Let's see, oh, one more thing.
Mr. Dickie Diamond was originally informed
that he would host this test wave broadcast,
but Mr. Friday now tells me he has canceled Diamond as host,
so don't let him in the studio.
No matter how popular he is with the public,
we can't risk the future of Pride All
on a space-brained loose cat like Dickie.
Okay, good luck, Mr. Edge.
I'll talk to you again soon,
and say, if you play the stock market,
perhaps I can give you a few tips.
We have very accurate stock listings
covering your next few years.
Oh, but I guess if this test wave succeeds,
that'll probably all change, huh?
Well, closing transmission now.
Please lock and recode.
Well, who am I to say?
I hope they know what they're doing.
Who's this?
UMN 1 to studio.
Hello?
I'm next.
This is Dickie Diamond,
star of stage, screen, and satellite.
Dickie.
Ha ha ha!
And I've got your damn whirlicopter,
and I'm not coming down!
Never!
Dickie!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
This is Mr. Edge.
What happened?
Bring that whirlicopter back.
We've got a herd traffic at six.
Shut up, Edge!
Chief of Auto Schematics.
Dickie, Dickie.
Will somebody explain why you're making all those premium credits?
What the hell is Auto Schematics, Edge?
I don't even answer.
The whole thing is a pathetic hoax designed to keep the duds and ditch the diamond.
Don't you think I know what you know that I know what you and Pliny are up to?
Dickie.
Dickie, calm down.
Calm down.
You're still the biggest draw we've got, Dickie.
The Dutch web is not going to cut me out of their medium pie.
Dickie.
Dickie, we had no intention of-
Oh, if it wasn't for you, I wouldn't be doing this shit ever since my Dancing on the Moon special was rated lowest in the sphere, you menacing me out.
How was I to know that gravity and rhythm are linked?
And now?
Now it's anything for diamond, anything for diamond, nothing for diamond!
Well, my career is not ending here, not at all.
Of course not.
I'm not over the edge yet.
Listen to me.
Slap yourself to death.
What are you doing?
I've had it with bony net web types leading me on with dramatic promises and then delivering what?
What?
Improvisation!
Bah!
I hate improvisation!
And now...
I'm going to do the worst thing anyone could do to you!
Don't do it Dicky, don't do it!
I'm going to use this script and I'm going to take your listeners away!
He's got a script!
You have no defense against a script, do you?
Ha! A real plan!
Dicky listen...
Remember the media shifter, Edge?
The media shifter?
It's right in front of me, quite the gimmick, very expensive!
Listen Diamond...
The blind pulls...
Dicky! Dicky!
Dicky, come on!
Ease on down!
I'm going to use this media shifter to remove your listeners!
Wait a minute Dicky!
Remove them to your biggest competitor!
And they'll stay there, Edge!
They'll have to stay there!
Dicky!
Listen Dicky, I don't know what you're up to but...
Power is red, I'm going to do it!
I'm going to do it, Edge!
Don't do it! Don't do it!
Electron factor, ten to the seventh power!
Dicky! Dicky!
Don't touch that button!
Counting down now Mr. Edge!
Ready?
Five... Four...
You can't do this!
Three...
Dicky, we've got a pilot for you!
I can fly this myself!
So long, NetWeb!
Try to find yourself in the ratings now!
Ha ha ha!
Two...
Three...
Don't do it!
I'm going to do it!
You're dead!
Back to Friday, I must not be so easily diverted.
Oh, no kidding, man.
And yes, dear friends, that last 11 minutes and 38 seconds was from the new Negative Land CD,
which is Time Zone's Exchange Project, a beautiful double CD.
And who knows, we may be running tons and tons of that material for your pleasure.
Your pleasure.
Pleasure here on the Hour of Slack from our good friends at Negative Land.
Yes, after having their very lives almost destroyed by Island Records, U2, and SST Records,
these valiant audio slack masters and creators of their own medium have not only tenaciously
pumped out astounding new album after album, much of the material, like in this case,
taken from their radio shows, Over the Edge, there on KPFA in Berkeley,
but have formed their own record company co-op to help themselves and other artistes get distribution
without a single record company vampire involved.
And believe you me, the Church of the Subgenius is going to benefit from that very thing.
It's over the...
As soon as I get any kind of a break, I need to sit down and start compiling.
The Hour of Slack CD series to be done in conjunction with Negative Land.
Yes, dear friends.
Oh, by the way, in the background, we're hearing music by an obscure band.
Well, maybe they're not obscure to you.
I just hadn't heard of them until recently.
Called Osric Tentacles.
There they go.
Osric Tentacles.
It's so...
Psyche.
Psychedelic.
Anyway, I...
You know, I bet...
I bet you can't tell from where you're sitting, my friend.
But from where I am, this particular show is late, late, late.
I should already have duplicated the 14 copies and be sending this show out right now
instead of just now starting to produce it.
Oh, now, why is that preacher, Reverend Stang, always making excuses, you ask?
Well, now, because of being ensconced here at the apex.
Of the very church.
Just a few notches below Dobbs himself.
My excuses are actually pretty exciting.
And this time, it's not our new book, Revelation X.
That's all done and we're just doing PR stuff now.
In fact, by the time you hear this, you may very well already have your copy in your hot little hands.
Or claws.
Or pinchers.
They print that mighty book on November 18th.
And the official release date...
Okay, the date they pick to indicate when they think it'll start hitting stores is, get this, November 22nd.
You can't say Dobbs doesn't love you now, Jack.
Yes, Revelation X, the third New Testament.
The new third Last Testament, one might say.
The Bob Apocryphon.
A Simon & Schuster publication will be out there for all to see and bask.
In, for better or for worse.
And my excuse is not, this time, that I've been running around preaching on car hoods and sleeping in flea-bitten motel rooms.
That'll be my excuse next month.
Dues-paying ordained members will be getting postcards about these shows.
Now, my excuse, friends, my excuse of this week partakes of none of those, nay.
But in the fact that I've been surfing the internet.
Yes, the subgenius foundation.
Can now take on the role of global village idiot on the information superhighway.
I've finally hooked up the modem that Dr. Drummond gave me and got an America Online account.
And I'm just waiting for my free internet access special account to come through so it won't be costing.
So now, friends, when I give the sacred P.O. box number at the end of the broadcast for information about this church.
I'll also be giving the church...
Headquarters email number.
And you ordained members will be glad to know that now that we've managed to get a handle on the technology and learn the geeky jargon.
What we're mainly working on is the stark fist of removal church magazine online.
Yes, I mean, we gotta work on it anyway.
And I'll be dumping the magazine in progress onto alt.slack on the internet.
And tweaking it.
And adding to it.
And adding to it interactively with everybody else there.
And when it's all done, we'll publish it on paper for everybody else.
Who doesn't have their very brain linked to a computer and modem yet.
Now, my friend, let me backtrack and explain to ye who have not yet tried to cross that information superhighway.
For many indeed are the virtual dead dog corpses dotting the sides of that highway.
Now, one week ago, before my crash.
Course in nerd speak.
I was barely aware of all this.
So I can sympathize if this already sounds like a bunch of hugger mugger gobbledy gook to you.
As you probably know, the internet is this invisible place like heaven or hell where people can leave electronic junk lying around for each other to fish out.
And mostly it's text messages and programs.
Although with enough know how.
And.
Here.
You can send and receive art and sound, etc.
And I mean, eventually we'll all have have them in our shirt pockets or embedded in our heads.
But there's already millions of humans plugged into the internet all over the world.
And it and it breaks down into thousands of categories.
Now, in the category called alternative, which is where most of the weird stuff happens.
There's a special mini network among all the others called alt.
Dot slack or alt period slack, depending, which is where the subgeniuses have been leaving messages to each other for several years now.
And there's several thousand messages sitting in it right now.
And then now there are also other subgenius electronic meeting places on other networks besides the Internet.
Like, for instance, America Online has a Church of the Subgenius board located under their philosophical matters heading in their hobbies department called the.
Exchange.
But alt.
Dot slack on the Internet is for now probably the most used subgenius dump.
Now, I don't know who started all slack and nobody's moderating it.
In other words, it's an endless series of unrelated topics being discussed.
And it's also cluttered with topics that have been automatically and senselessly dumped in there from other nerd networks.
And.
So when you first start looking for the interesting slack imbued material on there, you're met with total chaos and the equivalent of thousands and thousands of pages of garbage that has nothing to do with the church or the war against the conspiracy, for that matter.
You're also met with some of the lamest subgenius wannabe geekliness imaginable.
It's kind of like wandering around a comic book convention.
And since I'm, you know, Mr. Famous Guy Subgenius, when I made my presence known there, I was additionally greeted by the expected combination of groveling butt kissing and overly defensive rebelliousness and insults.
But that'll die down, I figure.
Now, despite all that, this is all tremendously exciting to me, my friend.
Because amidst all this false slack, there are also lurking some keen individuals in doubt.
And the potential for the whole thing is practically infinite.
Now, Dr. Drummond and I have been developing a plan.
Now, we have no intention of hobbling the chaotic, what most of us would call lame, idiotic, childish blabbering by those so-called subgenii who have no lives.
We do, however, plan to give the newcomer an alternative to all that by creating new, clearly marked chaos.
We will create new categories which, taken all together, will comprise and represent introductions to the church and, in fact, the stark fist of removal church magazine in progress.
In other words, if you enter alt.slack on the internet, you can go straight to where the most recent few hundred messages are.
And you'll find categories that were started by us here at the Subgenius Foundation.
But which are also being constantly updated and added to by others.
We can only hope that this works. We're just now starting.
For instance, here's some of the organizational categories that would comprise the online stark fist, or I guess you could actually call it the online hour of slack.
There'd be an intro to Bob for newcomers.
An intro guide to alt.slack.
Official church news.
Reviews of other mutants.
And high weirdness updates.
You know, wonderful magazines, books, CDs, tapes you can get, and so forth.
Videos.
Upcoming devivals.
Current hour of slack stations and times.
Practical anti-conspiracy weaponry.
Classic subgenius rants.
New subgenius rants.
Letters, prayers, and confessions.
Suggestions and requests.
Classic tales of Bob.
New tales of Bob.
A dissent.
Evil gossip and flaming.
Bummers.
Etc.
And it would all be free.
Of course, this would be kind of like the naked stark fist because there's no art.
And we can't do italics or boldface, you know, so the accents don't come across quite the same.
But it would be free.
And again, we have no intention of corralling alt.slack or cleaning up the chaos, so to speak.
We wouldn't dream of it even if we could.
We merely want to put little islands of useful organization into it for those of us who don't really have the time or money to wade through the randomness.
And you may be saying now, Reverend Stang, even if I had a computer and a modem, I wouldn't be interested in messing with all this computerese jargon and Bobby Blather.
I'm a subgenius, man.
And I'm just a genius.
I'm just not going to do it.
But, um, so why don't you shut up and all that stuff and just play some damn tapes.
Okay.
Okay, we're going to do that.
Slack.
Just wanted to let you know what else is out there in the realm of the church, which is actually a pretty big realm.
I mean, this is a religion, so it touches on every possible area of life.
Death and a lot of the mess in between.
What else is out there, you know, besides this show and the books and the comic books and the tapes and so forth?
Only one.
Back to Friday.
I must not be so easily diverted.
Oh, what was that again?
The Friday family belonged to an uncommon theological order.
The Sandemanians, they were called.
Oh, I...
In his later years, and indeed throughout his life, Friday thought that men of science were given to higher moral feelings than other men.
Well, Mr. Thomas, how does that statement jive with page 13 of your biography here, where...
Where you state that the Sandemanians were a lusty sect of sun-worshippers and that young Friday would spend hours hanging upside down and naked in his backyard reading pornographic Sandemanian texts,
purportedly found in a crashed alien pod by Dr. Sandemanian himself.
And what did he say of his reading?
He said this.
It made me think.
The connection with a good book has no equal in how it is written.
It is the connection with how it can turn a mind.
Well, let's hope that's not always true.
But beyond his massive sexual appetite for misshapen physique, so what can you tell us about these supposedly alien electrical experiments which were illustrated in these Sandemanian books?
Friday was already engaged in doing some experiments he had read about in the books.
And he said,
I made such experiments
as could be defrayed in their expense
by a few pence a week.
But what was the nature of these...
Isn't that just wonderful to hear?
Yes.
Well, now that he owns half the world, it's hard to believe he started out on such a shoestring.
Friday wrote,
I am now constantly employed in observing the works of nature
and tracing the manner
in which she directs the order and arrangement of the world.
Now, what do you suppose he meant by that?
Order and arrangement of the world.
I see. Sort of a vast world vision that would probably...
And this phrase, order and arrangement...
Yes.
By that he meant the great scheme of things in nature.
Order and arrangement.
Well, with just a few minutes left, I'd like to get back to...
Now, Friday heard of this event,
that electricity makes magnetism.
And in his notebook he wrote,
Make magnetism produce electricity.
The year was 1820.
Uh, wait a minute.
I don't even have to take off my shoes to figure that would make him,
let's see, 1820 to 1900, that's 60 plus, I don't know, what is it now,
For 11 years he labored on the idea,
make magnetism produce electricity.
So, let's see, 1820 plus 11, that's...
In 1831, the discovery was unfolded.
Ah, yes, yes, and that of course must have been that famous first probe
into the mysteries of trans-infiltration, which killed all those assistants.
But, uh, Mr. Thomas, in the short time left, can we move on to the...
I am busy, John.
I am just now on electromagnetism.
I think I have hold of a good thing, but cannot say for sure.
Well, all right, but then, uh, how did this electrical work prepare him
for his many political and diplomatic accomplishments?
Uh, you know, he's running again in 92.
Soon after the discovery,
Mr. Friday demonstrated it to the Prime Minister.
Of what use is it, Mr. Friday, said the Prime Minister,
to which Friday replied,
Mr. Minister, one day you may be able to tax it.
Huh, tax it.
One day you may be able to tax it.
Tax it.
Isn't that a wonderful reply?
Super reply.
But, uh, now, was this prior to the patent laws
that now give him exclusive usage rights over that technology?
Uh, and at that point in time, how could he have foreseen...
And on another occasion, a lady put the same question.
Of what use is it, Mr. Friday?
And he replied,
Of what use is a newborn baby, madam?
Indeed, sometimes I still ask myself that one.
And I also wonder how Friday, at such a young age,
was creating all these things so long ago,
as if he could understand what the future would... would... would...
So now, when you see the huge transmission lines
stretched across the land,
and when you visit the huge generating plants
where falling water gives birth to the electric fluid
which lights your home and toasts your bread,
and when the day turns dark,
and the darkness is turned to light
by a million neon flames,
think of Friday, that little boy born to a blacksmith,
who gave to the world
this enormous gift of his genius.
Super genius, super genius.
But tell us about all that wealth.
I think most people want to hear about all that money.
And so he had to decide.
Make money, gather wealth, or serve science and mankind.
His decision, we can already guess.
I guess so.
And he spoke ever constantly in this refrain.
The sweetest reward of my work
is the sympathy and goodwill
which flows to me from all quarters of the earth.
Of all his great and wonderful characteristics,
the most prominent, I would say,
must be his sense of order and his humble heart.
Of his many utterances, this stands nobly among them.
For the philosopher, truth adds industry
within the veil of science, he said.
It is a glorious school for the mind.
And this phrase.
There is nothing too wonderful to be true.
Is that true?
Nothing too wonderful to be true.
Just kidding.
Well, we are right out of time, Dr. Thomas.
So I say, it would be good for boys to get jobs like this today.
Well, I'm sure they'll try, Mr. Thomas.
You mean like...
Remember, too.
Ben Franklin was an errand boy.
And an apprentice to a printer.
You will remember. I told about that.
Yes, I do remember, Dr. Thomas.
And thank you, thank you very much.
Thanks for that insight into the early years of C. Eliot Friday.
We've been talking with Delmar Detmer Thomas,
the one and only authorized biographer of C. Eliot Friday.
As we continue here on the Piddlediddle Report
with our topic for tonight,
C. Eliot Friday and the Soviet connection.
I must say,
Mr. Thomas must be quite a draw
because our ABS audience meter,
indicating how many of you are tuned in to us,
took a giant flying leap into the really big numbers
right in the middle of that interview.
Well, glad to have you aboard.
And I know you'll want to stay with us
as these historical events in the Soviet Union continue to develop
and we explore the mysterious role of C. Eliot Friday,
the world's most mysterious tycoon in these events.
We'll be back with more of that.
More right after these messages.
This is the American Broadcasting System.
Diet recommendation for subgeniuses?
Well, now, actually,
in the book of the subgenius it says,
oh, some granola in the morning,
and then three martinis,
and then some nice,
you make a sandwich,
you take some of your,
you take some sprouts,
you know, some organically grown sprouts
and some of that peanut butter
that you get in the health food stores,
the kind with the oil on top,
yeah, and your grandma's face,
and make your sandwich.
And now that's for lunch.
Then for dinner you would maybe eat some rusty nails
and stuff some froth up your exit wound.
That quote, in that sort of thing,
when we give directives and admonitions,
admonitions of Bob in our books,
those are really, oftentimes, believe it or not,
those are meant humorously.
Because Bob would never,
no subgenius is going to give you orders.
Well, actually, I shouldn't say that.
A subgenius may give you orders,
but no subgenius ever takes orders
from any other subgenius.
We would give, for instance,
the conspiracy would tell you what's healthy to eat,
what you should eat,
what you should watch on TV,
and who you should vote for.
We're not going to tell you any of that stuff,
aside from the obvious,
J.R. Bob Dobbs for World Overlord.
But for all we know,
as powerful as he is,
he may already be World Overlord.
Praise that man, Bob.
I hate Bob.
You can't imagine that Bob can,
Bob hates you so much.
He doesn't even know you,
but he hates you.
He hates you.
You can go to bed at night
all alone and think,
well, I'm not completely alone.
Bob's thinking of me.
He hates me.
But only if you send him that $20, friends,
which goes up to $30, by the way,
when the new book comes out in,
well, it's supposed to be in November.
What?
Right, Bob doesn't care.
He hates you anyway,
but he also loves you.
You know, Bob is,
it's like good and evil
are one thing when you're on that level.
It's all, I mean, Bob,
one minute he might walk a little old lady
across the street,
and the next minute,
beat her to death,
club her to death,
and take her money.
It's whatever gives him the most slack.
For all we know,
now this is not likely,
it's possible,
it's not likely,
but it's possible that Bob is,
where is he?
He's not here right now.
He could be meeting with Dan Quayle
to prepare a new retrovirus,
a new, quote,
accidental release of another warfare,
biological warfare germ.
He could be doing that.
That doesn't seem like something
we would want Bob to do.
It's not something the average subgenius
could even imagine Bob doing.
But here's the point.
If he does, so be it.
It is not up to us to question Bob.
You do not question,
you don't use your mind
to think about your religion.
It's as simple as that.
I mean, the minute you drag logic
and reason into your mind,
into any religious sort of thing,
that's the end of it.
You might as well just go join the Moonies,
the Scientology, Catholics, you know,
or one of those other subgenius spin-offs.
Oh, yes, the young little boy over there with the...
Bob said it.
No, actually, the correct line is,
Bob sold it, I smoked it.
That settles it.
Oh, well...
You think about Bob with your head,
you think about Bob with your gonads.
Well, now, that depends.
Actually, the soul...
Many people think that the soul
is located in the gonads.
Actually, it is in the...
Now, this sounds like a play on words,
but the human soul, S-O-U-L,
is in the foot,
along with the S-O-L-E type soul.
And like that other soul,
it's a rectangular, greenish, flat thing.
However, what most people don't know
is, like the rhinoceros horn,
it is actually made of hair.
It's like the fingernails or something.
That's right.
The soul is down there.
It's all proof, man.
It's like they look for scientific proof.
Well, we'll offer $50,000 to anybody
who can prove that J.R. Bob Dobbs does not exist.
That offer has been standing for 10 years now,
and nobody's taken us up on it.
Now, this is...
We're getting into the angels on the head of a pen type question.
What is Bob's shoe size?
Actually, Bob wears size 12 Brogans.
That is a question that is addressed doctrinally.
Bob has eaten a great deal of spam.
Bob was in World War II.
Bob...
No, let's not do Monty Python stuff.
Oh, wait.
Next, it's going to be Rocky Horror Picture Show face.
It's going to be Doctor Who fans.
Or Mystery Science Theater 3000.
That was the Nissan Bob.
That was a rip-off.
Yeah, he's referring to the spate of commercials
in conspiracy media that feature cute, Bob-like characters,
often called Bob.
The best one is the Nissan spot,
where you just...
It's point of view shots out of a windshield of a Nissan,
and the signs all say,
Yield to Bob.
You know, this lane is Bob's.
He starts to get a ticket from a cop,
and the cop says,
Oh, it's you, Bob.
And at the end of the spot,
they show the car and a little slogan that says,
Why should rich guys have all the luck?
That is an example of the conspiracy...
You can watch for this kind of thing.
The conspiracy has a special...
You know how they have a UFO study group?
And so forth.
They have a subgenius study group,
that for all we know,
may be more important to Bob's plan than any of us.
But they...
The conspiracy does try to cutesy Bob up,
deliver a...
This sort of a understandable Bob,
a silly Bob,
that's only a take-off on silly televangelists.
And they're trying to serve you, Bob,
on a silver platter.
And the day that Bob Dobbs becomes popular,
that is the day to start worrying about this shit.
Because I guarantee you,
those of us who were in there at the beginning will have gone.
We will be gone.
We may have taken the money and run,
but someone else will be running it.
And on that day, my friend,
that is the day to fear.
When they start selling you church air
for one soul per breath.
And you laugh.
You think that's funny.
I've seen these things.
You can read on the internet all kinds of stuff
about the church and the subgenius.
I heard the other...
Oh, there's all these geeks on the internet.
They know all about Church of the Subgenius.
The Reverend Ivan Stang is just a fake name
for a consortium of 50 writers in Texas or...
No, in Canada.
That was the latest one.
Yeah, the Canadian false Bob.
Oh, there's a smiley face Bob.
You can actually buy CDs by Bob Dobbs.
He's afraid to call himself J.R. Bob Dobbs
or put it in quotes or anything like that.
No, it's in Canada.
And it's like, called...
It's like, lost more than they'll ever make.
Yes?
Bob Dean has sent this to my radio station.
Not one penny or more and he went to his conference
going to give this...
Oh, Pastor Craig.
No!
Friends, here it is.
Pastor Craig.
Pastor Craig here
from the Philadelphia Subgenius radio show.
This is the CD.
The CD,
which is Yabab's Media Ecology.
It's the funny...
It's the intellectual Bob.
He's a little more serious and he uses much more trendy McLuhan-esque words
so that you can really know that it's like,
not that silly Texas stuff.
God damn it.
I can't wait for the fight.
Oh!
Yeah!
Let's just spike the pathetic,
the wannabe,
the gimme Bob,
the one of the Ivan Bob psychotic.
It feels too bad now because I love Bob.
Oh.
Thank you, Pastor Craig,
for that amazing contribution there.
I've always wanted to do that.
WFMU did that to that guy's album,
sent it back to him.
That's what we should do.
We'll mail it back to Bob Dean,
the false Bob.
We're not even at the next one.
You know,
I just noticed among the shards there
two pills on the ground.
Now,
I'm not going to take these pills
because I know what's in them.
Those are health food store
or convenience store speed.
You know those,
those zippy pills and so forth
that you see at the convenience stores?
I don't know about you,
but ephedra.
just doesn't cut it for me.
And caffeine in the form of GoToCola just ain't...
It just ain't there, you know?
It doesn't do the trick.
We like to still...
We're the only way!
Well, I'm getting...
Frankly, I believe in Slack for myself and Yoko.
And we would like to...
I would actually just as soon listen to this amazing rendition of
Sunshine of Your Love by Jimi Hendrix.
On the radio for the rest of the afternoon.
This is the American Broadcasting System.
I'm so depressed, Andrew.
You can't be depressed. This is the holiday season.
But America's losing its values, Andrew.
I just read it in the paper.
Nonsense. I spent my lunch hour at Hastings,
and believe me, there are plenty of values there.
Andrew, I'm talking about something much more far-reaching.
I doubt it. The values I saw at Hastings
reach to just about every gift item you can imagine.
Sweaters, dress shirts, neckwear, sports shirts,
outerwear jackets, camel hair, sport coats, suits, casual slacks.
Andrew, this is deeper.
Deeper? I don't think you'll find a much deeper value
than $32.90 for a soft lambswool sweater
or $12.90 for a beautiful silk tie.
Andrew, I'm talking...
I'm talking about human values.
Well, then you're talking service.
And there's not another clothing store
with a more helpful staff than Hastings.
Real professionals.
But, Andrew...
Friendly, unhurried atmosphere.
Real holiday spirit.
Andrew, we're just on different wavelengths.
That's because you haven't been to Hastings yet.
One store where you can find great holiday gifts
at great holiday prices.
Well, I guess that is value.
Kind of restores your faith, doesn't it?
Only in America.
Only at Hastings.
This is the Piddle Diddle Report.
A five-hour in-depth report
on current issues of substance.
All right.
We're back.
And with more on tonight's
C. Eliot Friday and the Soviet Connection.
Tonight's report on the Piddle Diddle Report.
I'm Doug Piddle.
My colleague Peter Diddle is away on assignment
to Howland Island in the Mid-Pacific.
And we hope to have a direct phone link
to him shortly.
Of course, Mr. Friday reclusively resides
on Howland Island,
where he maintains headquarters
for his many enterprises,
most notably the Universal Media NetWeb,
now the largest international multimedia
glomerate in the world.
And Fridol, his pharmaceutical lab,
which has been distributing free Mertz tablets
in the Soviet Union for months.
And I can't be the first one to wonder
if they had some effect on current events there.
And we've all heard the various rumors
regarding Mr. Friday's role in beginning
and then ending the recent Soviet coup attempt.
It has been alleged that it was a walnut-sized prototype
Fridotronics micro mini video cam,
which Gorbachev used to record his denials
while a captive in the Crimea.
We all saw what he held up at his press conference,
wrapped in a hanky to cover the brand name.
What's more, there appears to be a great deal
of security surrounding some kind of scientific testing
going on at Howland Island right now.
And we also have reports that many Soviet media officials
are now on the island.
Could this involve the mysterious trans-infiltration device
we've heard so much about now being developed
by Fridotronics?
Is Friday on the island at all?
We heard his flying wing left Howland several days ago,
taking the polar route towards Russia.
Is he dead?
No one's heard or seen the man in over six years.
Well, we're going to try and find out these
and other things.
We're going to try and find out the things occurring
before and after you hear this.
Peter Dill should be calling us soon
with his report on the spot from that tiny dot,
so isolated that it isn't even in any time zone.
And in fact, I think this is his call coming in now.
Let's check that right here.
Peter, are you there?
What time is it?
Hey! Where did he land at?
Just a second here.
It's fabulous.
It's all green.
It's beautiful.
It looks...
It's gorgeous.
What are you going to do next, Peter?
I don't know, but with these new pills,
it'll be easy to make up my mind.
Okay.
Well, listen, we...
I'm going to look for some of those Soviet officials, I guess.
Oh, hey, hang on, Peter.
Okay.
Hang on.
Don't go away.
Listen, the console is indicating
we have a very special phone call here.
Could you hang on a minute?
No, no trouble.
We have a...
Someone's on call.
Just a moment, Peter.
Let me adjust the scale.
All right.
Go ahead with that call.
Coming into the space network from the White House.
Oh, my God, Peter.
This is very special.
Listen to this.
We would like to patch them through.
All right.
Go ahead.
If you would, please, Mr. President, go ahead.
I think your trip is just going to ignite the excitement
and the forward thinking for this country,
so I really...
I really just wanted to call up and wish you the very best.
It's God-forsaken lush green foliage out here.
It's...
Oh, really?
Can you hear Mr. Bush all right?
I'm...
Wait, he's still on.
He's still on.
Mr. Bush, are you still there?
I couldn't understand that.
Yes, just a moment.
No.
I just thought he was a calm guy out there, you know,
and now look at him.
How are you going to do that?
It's great talking to you,
and I'll let you go back to work.
What's the next thing you've got to do?
That's what I was wondering.
Move forward, I guess.
I voted Democratic, you know.
Oh, that's great.
I'm sure it'll go well.
Sitting right behind my desk is that model you gave me down there
and also the picture of you two guys,
and it was there before this phone call, too.
Oh, how about that, Peter?
Great deal.
May I address the vice president?
He cut out.
I think it's probably an attribute to the fabulous and magnetic qualities
of your personality supported extensively
as I can attest to.
My personality.
What do you think?
Oh, Peter, your signal's all jamming up now.
It's on this end.
Everything looks very great.
Peter.
Well, Peter has faded out.
Thank you.
That happens occasionally on these shortwave cellular phone transmissions.
I'm sure he'll be back later.
He's got our number.
And my God, things are a little strange tonight, folks.
Kill the ocean, that's one thing I'm still in command of.
You're listening to the Piddle Diddle Report.
Peter Diddle, of course, you just heard out on Howland Island
doing a grand job making his way up towards those lights, hopefully.
If he can hear me, towards the lights, Peter.
Let's go to a...
message right now and come back and continue as usual.
This is the American Broadcasting System.
Oh, yes, dear friends.
And that was Negative Land, their new CD.
Actually, it's a double CD set.
It's Negative Land presents some best of from their over the edge,
radio show, the Time Zones Exchange Project.
Well, we're just swimming in code tonight, aren't we?
Yes, the Church of the Subgenius has gone online
and off the wall and over the edge.
And why not?
While I'm at it, I suppose I should give
the sacred post office box number of the Church of the Subgenius.
Yes, this is the place to write.
Drop us a postcard or a self-addressed stamped envelope
for information on other subgenius information.
And that number is, you know, that's not the kind of music
that you want to put in the background when you're given the sacred post office box.
That number is, dear friends.
Hey, that music's even worse.
There we go.
Okay, the post office box is, well, just right there, Bob.
He ain't going to read your letter, but I will.
Maybe.
Just address that to Bob at post office box 807 Glen Rose, Texas 76043.
And now, as promised.
Oh, by the way, that zip code once again was 76043.
Because they know.
Yes, over there.
At the mighty P, those P.O. buckers at the P.O. know.
They see all and they know all.
But they don't tell all.
But I'm going to tell you the email address.
As promised, you can email the church now.
And it's one word, one nice long string of words.
Subgestang1 at AOL.com.
I'm going to go through that.
This one time.
It's S-U-B-G-S-T-A-N-G.
Numeral 1.
That's Subgestang1.
That's all you need if you're on America Online.
But for everybody else, it's Subgestang1 at, you know, the little A with a circle around it.
A-O-L dot C-O-M.
It's America Online Communications.
Me, me, me.
And you'd be surprised.
I sit up every night and go through the mail.
As one subgenius out there said, or on there said,
it's like a P.O. box that never closes.
And your wife and kids, or husband and kids,
sit and wonder why you sit and peck away at that little box,
that evil box that the conspiracy can, you know, they can monitor everything we say and do.
But you know, friends, I mean, I'm so used to it.
All these poor folks on the internet are complaining about censorship,
and they can't advertise or cuss.
I've been under those limitations doing this show for all these many years.
And it's just, it's something, in a way, of course, we intend to dismantle their evil system.
But for now, you have to look at it.
It is sort of a challenge, you know.
You have to invent your own new cuss words and evile code words and so forth.
Well, anyway, enough of that.
Let's let the show go out.
This is Osric Tentaclesmore in the background.
Let's listen to Dr. Howell on the Puzzling Evidence show.
That's what he calls it now.
This particular tape, I'm not sure what it's going to be,
but I know what it's from.
It's from Phineas Narco's compilations of that show.
You can get information about a catalog of the KPFA subgenius show from Phineas Narco.
Okay.
What, what, what, what, what?
And is it consistent with the Small Minded Law?
Yes, and with the Small Mind Administration,
which has officially certified it with the house-shrinking seal of approval.
And here on the side, right under there,
that are the, well, this is interesting.
It's the ingredients.
It says,
U.S. certified sludge, water, sucrose, muscimol extract,
ibuprofenic acid, muscazone, dimethyltryptamine, serotonin,
natural sludge flavorings,
contains one fortieth of one percent gabofrop,
an artificial mood enhancer,
which should be used only by those who must restrict their intake of ordinary humor.
Caution, product may be habit-forming.
Do not operate radio while taking this medication.
Do not operate heavy farm machinery.
Do not use any medication that is in excess of 70 miles per hour.
Do not attempt to explain yourself to others.
Maintain an aspect of normal human.
Consult your sub-physician or any doctor the errors condition persists.
Okay, well, this looks like the stuff.
So I'm going to take some right here on the show.
Oh, oh no.
Yep, here goes.
Okay.
Oh my God.
Ugh, boy, it's...
That's better.
My God, it's incredible.
Well, take them on a finite break.
I've started a Boeing cycle, caller.
Stop it.
This has never happened before.
I think I'm going to be sucked into the world of Boeings.
The world of nothing but Boeings.
The Boeing dimension.
It's right behind you, Mobius.
The world of Boeings that we could be internally trapped in.
If we don't watch out, there'll be nothing on the show but Boeings.
How do you get some of this stuff?
Well, I told you what was in it.
You can rip up a batch yourself.
But I don't know half of that stuff.
It's a free sample in each package.
Oh, whoa, whoa.
Wait, wait, wait.
Oh, no.
Get those.
Oh, the Boeings.
They're too much.
Too much Boeings.
Oh, my.
Oh, that one was wonderful.
Need a towel?
Oh, no.
I threw a towel over it the moment it happened.
And now, ladies and gentlemen, the moment you've all been waiting for, the penultimate
comedian of all time.
Oh, my God.
I'm E. Transon Steinman.
You can't get no...
He's a hilarious, hell-raising hypocrite of hallelujah.
It's the Jainer Diva.
Who's that?
You, man.
You.
You're on the air.
You're a big shot.
Make them laugh.
However, off the public support at Airwise, I can tell you to send $35 or you will die
on X day or something much, much worse.
And if you already have become a subgenius minister, God bless you.
You've gotten that huge 25-piece membership kit with button and bumper stickers and minister's
card and many frameable certificates and lots of dog's heads.
You might not have the book of the subgenius or Neighbor World or even our world-famous
pamphlets over 100,000 sold.
Well, not Neighbor World, about 80 of those maybe.
But come on, man.
A thing?
For that matter, there's fast clothing designs and drinkware with subgenius.
There's subgenius graphics on them and all manner of fine Dobbs wear and Dobbs gimmickry
and Bob gadgets and DVDs of movies, good and bad ones, mostly pretty good and very weird.
And CDs of what we did before the radio shows and after, like stage shows and such.
Boy, it's just an immense mess of keen and yet sacred collectibles, enjoyables and guilty
pleasures.
And the book of the subgenius is awesome.
It's autographed when you get it from us.
Not by Bob, no, sorry, just me.
Anyway, thank you, friends, and good night or good day or whatevs.
Praise Bob.