Uh, hello Bob, and yes dear friends, it is 1997, but you're about to listen to Hour of Slack, number 75, from 1987.
Praise Bob.
Praise Bob. Oh yes, dear friends, this is Li Biqin, a Chinese subgenius, and you are listening to the Hour of Slack.
Be calm, be calm.
You are about to experience the awe and mystery which reaches from the inner mind to the subgenius.
Hour of Slack. Sponsored by the Church of the Subgenius.
Come on.
Verse zou.
What?
Wow.
That's more words than a bridge.
el
Remember, Bob is a comrade of all people.
He is a child just like in America.
And people need slack.
In Chinese, we call slack .
But it must be true slack, not the bad slack of the conspiracy.
Please, Bob, help me somebody.
Bob!
Eternal salvation.
Or triple your money back.
Should any other shows be heard from or contacted in the course of this show,
the listener is advised to remain calm and only contact listed or unlisted officials
in the event of any material from this radio or other listening device being inhaled during broadcast.
Thank you.
Small animals or other children becoming exposed to the ultra-high or ultra-low shocks
and brain frequencies constantly scanned throughout our program should seek shelter in an approved safety unit only.
This is Walter Teasdale reminding you that it's often a photon that light releases,
but truth is, not everyone gets the picture.
Hoping your time is all time and all your unpermissible truths are happy truths.
After relaxing on the lake, Bob's ready to have a great time entertaining his friends.
Right, Bob?
Bob?
Break out of that glass box and join the Church of the Subgenius.
In a country where freedom of religion is guaranteed by the Constitution, we must be
prepared to face the worst of the worst.
In the midst of a world of chaos, anything is likely to develop.
Enter the Church of the Subgenius, billing itself as the weirdest cult on Earth.
What do they believe in?
Everything.
Who do they believe in?
A mysterious character named Bob.
Bob is the culmination of that to which man has aspired throughout his long and slackless history.
Bob is what will bring slack to planet Earth.
And to you, young man.
This is a church that does not play games.
The other churches talk about love.
And think hate.
The other churches do not talk about money.
They take your money.
You don't see the gold-plated temples in the Church of Bob.
You don't see Cadillac convertibles in the Church of Bob.
You don't see Jensen interceptors in the parking lot of Bob.
You see slack-filled smiling faces in the tabernacle of the Bob.
Bob founded the church mainly to help unmask the conspiracy.
And we're talking about the conspiracy.
What's next?
Just believe in the power of the dogs.
I believe.
Believe in Bob.
Reach out for him.
I'm reaching.
Feel the healing power.
I think you killed him.
See, there you go.
See, now, do you remember anything?
Does it hurt?
No.
See, no problem.
No problem with Bob, right?
Yeah!
Right!
You midnight rams.
All right.
When are the midnight rams?
I don't mean just black nights.
I mean you black-hearted men and women.
Our midnight rams.
I know the man by Mr. Fletcher in Dallas, Texas.
And he's a good man.
Except that he don't buy me two glasses of Fitcher's beer.
And I said, I love you.
I love you, boy.
And I'm going to tell you, if I can't whoop it, I'll go down.
All right, man!
He can't whoop it!
He's going down.
Ae, ae, ae, ae!
It's just miracle wisdom coming through from me.
Oh, yeah.
We may find only the intergalactic silences, or we may encounter intelligences greater
than our own, answers to questions we cannot even formulate today.
.
Or the pioneers, traveling or falling between fire and darkness, between freezing and burning, may sense that we live only on the narrowest of margins.
Snowflakes, condensed momentarily out of the great snowstorms and firestorms of matter in space.
The Earth is a planet that has not had much time left.
The date that Bob has set is, uh, I mean, he's not trying to do this. This isn't something he wants to do.
But, uh,
so,
seven o'clock in the morning, July 5th, when everybody has hangovers, uh, 1998.
That year, you can expect the, quote, end of the world, unquote.
Uh, the Church of the Subgenius is here to make sure the end of the world happens correctly.
Uh, it can go various different ways.
Uh, people tend to think of the end of the world as, uh, a sudden, you know, bam, it's gone, or the rapture, you know, suddenly all the Christians are in heaven.
Happy, watching all the sinners fry.
I wanna get saved, you better get right with Bob right now!
Right now!
Basically, two factions out there right now is us and them.
Friend, have you ever heard the expression, there's no slack in this world?
A lot of people have to ask me what slack is.
And that's sad, mister.
They were born with slack. Oh yeah, you were born with slack.
But the conspiracy took it away.
The conspiracy made you want to be nothing.
You wanted to be normal.
That's what the conspiracy is all about.
And the conspiracy is, uh, a patchwork of different things.
Some are nations, some are products, some are hypnotic television shows, some are, um, bad pills.
You'll find unless you find Bob!
And you better find Bob right now!
And no one has ever met Bob.
The leader of our church, no one has ever met.
Because, as you know, all cults, they're leaders.
And leaders are usually pretty hard to find.
And Bob is no exception.
Bob will help you.
Dig your own weirdness.
I got a Bob in my pants.
Honey, I got a problem.
It's right over here.
I need some padded tweezers.
No, no, don't run away.
I got a Bob in my pants.
Oh, they all run away.
I need help.
I got a Bob in my pants.
Will somebody help me?
Hi, ma'am.
I'm trying to squat my Bob.
I gotta squat my Bob.
Will you help me squat my Bob?
I got a Bob in my pants.
If you're up here, I can't hold you but a minute, bro.
I got a Bob in my designer jeans.
I got a Bob in my pants.
It's clean Bob.
I got a Bob in my shorts.
Don't smell.
Really, I trained it.
It's on really hot.
I got a Bob in my shorts.
I gotta get this Bob out of my pants.
I gotta get this Bob.
This is Sister Chris, and couldn't you just whiff the isness, the slack that was inherited
in that collage?
Truly first-rate sleazy art or tenth-rate high art that contains the cheapness necessary
to help you maintain faith throughout subgenius depression or alienation from blessed mania
in these times of no style, when no one has the guts to put their bloody hearts in the
line without fear of being called a weirdo, a time when people laugh at the things that
aren't funny and don't laugh at the ones that are.
They, being the normals, laugh only when there is a laugh track, because they don't, because
they rather they want to be accepted, and they don't want to step out of line.
It's gone so far, I've actually heard sobbing at a movie theater when the expensive cars,
the Mercedes-Benz and such, get totaled in a car chase.
Confusion abounds, and the only thing we can keep our precious insanity is by letting
go of the oppressive concrete weights around our necks that pull us down to the bottom
of the pool of normalcy, float up to the surface where the breathing is easy.
Come up to freshness.
Try Menthol Bob.
He's that refreshing voice in the back of your head that all of the nuns in Catholic
training and psychic torturing centers told you was the voice of the devil or one of his
minions, urging you to step away from the flock.
The herd instinct.
Is the real diabolical notion that organized religion teaches?
Dump those graven images down the drain before you dump your will in a ditch for them.
Ah, yes, the harvest.
I guess comparing the word Bob, Bob, Bob.
They said your mind is in this jar, and then they poured it down the sink.
Subgeniuses are the class of people who can't be classed.
Bob has taken winos on the street and turned them into millionaires overnight.
By the same token, he has taken millionaires and given them the slack they always needed
all along as winos.
Some of the greatest of the subgeniuses, some of the most ascended rogue subgeniuses
are complete morons.
You know, but they perform a service.
You know, we need the morons of the world.
And they've got me.
I don't even know where the hell they're coming from.
But, you know, thanks for letting me speak my piece.
Sure, sure, listen, if I were you, I would keep speaking your piece as much as possible
because it's not going to be long before people cannot say what they mean.
People won't be able to express themselves in public.
I understand that, but, you know, that other stuff is coming down with me.
I just can't, you know, relate to it at all.
It'll come to you.
It's real.
I want to know what gets you started in this religious cult.
What gets you started?
Or what got us started?
What got us started?
Yeah.
Actually, I was contacted one time.
I was driving along in my automobile.
You've heard about these UFO contactee stories I know before.
But I was driving along.
I was driving along in my automobile one day and out on some country road
and was forcibly wrenched from my car and manipulated by creatures from outer space.
Does that appeal to you?
Pretty simple, really.
No, I don't believe it myself.
Well, what you can do, yeah, I was going to say,
you probably wouldn't want to send us a dollar if you, you know,
we don't insist that people believe us.
We only insist that they do what we do.
We ask them to.
In fact, we really, we believe that the majority of you out there won't believe us.
Yeah, I was wanting to talk to them too, guys.
Is this Rhodey?
Yeah, they're right here.
And I'm Rhodey.
Hello?
Okay, I want to ask them two questions.
The first question is, they said they was into winning souls.
Who are they winning souls for, Satan or Jesus?
Pal, Bob and Jesus are on the same side.
They're just not playing quite the same game.
Yeah, but there's only one game.
That's right.
There's only one game.
That's all.
We're not going to be able to tell you anything.
So play your game and keep on playing.
Well, my second question is, why are you deceiving everybody?
We're not deceiving anyone.
We are doing it for Jesus.
It's going to be a lot easier to deceive people once the government starts putting
Valium in the water supply.
I probably won't even be here.
That's right.
You're probably right.
Let me make an important point here.
A lot of the people that are born.
Again, Christians now are doing more to turn America against Jesus than they are
for Jesus.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
Yeah, I hear you there.
But what I'm saying is, why don't y'all why don't y'all try to turn people to
Jesus?
We're just trying to take it from a slightly different direction.
We make people aware of the fact that they can make their own decisions.
We're going step by step.
Do you think you ever occur to you might be going in the wrong step?
We think about that all the time.
Has it ever occurred to you?
No.
I got a mighty big ball.
I got a big ball.
And it's got to come out.
Well, he must have got in.
Ain't no room.
It's got to get out.
There ain't no room in my skin.
But there's a mighty big ball.
Big ball.
Inside of me.
He's a mighty big ball.
Ugly ball.
You know, it makes me pee.
He's a mighty big ball.
He's too big.
Man, he's really too big.
He's a mighty big ball.
That will overcome Satan's powers,
the anointing that will break the yoke of Satan's bondage.
And I want you to know that I have just been experiencing an attack on all sides.
It seems like on every room where we try to advance,
the devil would just unleash, literally,
horrors of demonic suffering.
He would come and force us to stop ourselves.
And after a few weeks of this, I just began to feel a deep hurting in my belly.
Way deep down in my spirit.
And some people say, well, on top of what?
You mean you experience pain too?
Yes I do.
I hurt just like you do.
I feel the pain of a satanic attack just like you do.
But I really didn't even know how to pray because I didn't know exactly what was coming at me.
Satan was bombarding me from so many sides, actually I felt kind of dumb.
Step in to the wonderful world of auto dynamics.
Step in to the swept wing Dodge of 1957.
If the last 50 years made such a change, just imagine the New York of 1980.
When everyone has a number instead of a name and the government tells you whom you should marry.
Just imagine, 1980.
Oh my goodness, oh, oh, are you all right doctor?
If that don't work, we'll bore you.
I'm healed again.
Right here, right in front of us folks.
This ain't the highest quality slack I ever heard in my life either.
Yeah, well, it's better than that liquid slack.
We have to buy from you.
Hey, there's a caller.
We talked to Bosco Bear today.
Let's see what Bosco has to say.
Well, you know, it's a little known fact that the soul is actually located in the foot.
Of course, it's not physically.
It's not a physical thing.
It doesn't die with the physical body.
It rots, but never actually dies.
It stays around.
The soul is the stroke drug of the spiritual realm.
It wanders.
It wanders around trying to score a last bit of prop before it passes over into the before life.
And you know, a normal soul, when they get over into the before life, they all just run together into one big slurry.
They get strained out and used in another normal in the next life, but you couldn't really call it a next life because it's just normal.
Yes, but a subgenius soul becomes a dot.
They're hard to catch.
But what happens to a business executive?
They move fast, boy.
So what happens to a business executive's soul?
Well, those are the ones that Bob will use as the main commodity in his bargaining with the elder gods when the day of judgment arrives.
You should know that from looking at Prescripture 1714, Dr. Howell.
I presume you have been reading your prescriptures.
I was only making an inquiry on behalf of the many unenlightened listeners who might be curious to know how vulnerable a business executive might be.
I've just noticed a certain lack of discipline around this whole show thing.
Just the fact that you call it a show.
Don't eschew the show.
If the checks were bigger, the show would be better.
Oh, the checks and money, I see.
Yes, if the checks were bigger, the balances would be greater.
Your love of Bob is in direct proportion to how much Bob pays you, right?
Oh, I think Bob's love of me is in direct proportion.
That's so funny.
In direct proportion to how many souls I destroy.
Bob pays through the nose, and I've worn out many souls pounding the streets in his service.
That's right, and I've hurt my nostrils trying to receive those payments.
I had my third nostril forcibly opened by a crazed wino on Telegraph Avenue.
And that's the best way to do it.
That is really the best way, getting it on the street.
You don't have to get fancy about it.
You know, do it natural-like.
Get a, just, you know, the ones that's out on the street.
There they are now.
That's probably where Bob is.
Now, he's probably walking the streets.
Right now.
It's amazing.
Like a miracle.
The law of the land.
Filling it full of money.
Just as we all are, he is only a delicate envelope of flesh.
Yeah, but he's been licked more than once.
He's a bag of skin filled with meat, just like everybody, but it's special.
Establish justice.
I ain't afraid of all the gulls and altars.
I used to think if I died in an evil place,
then my soul wouldn't be able to make it to heaven.
But now,
I mean, I don't care where it goes as long as it ain't here.
So what do you want to do?
I'm going in to examine it.
Isn't that dangerous, even with the suit on, sir?
It won't take me long.
Very well.
He's reached bottom.
Open the lock.
Father.
Hold it.
Mary, what are you doing here in a radiation suit?
You should've looked in the dynamic.
Father, I haven't got a aside For.
You think I can't?
There let me use it like a
There's-, there's-
And now you've broken all our trust,
and I've got this little t kommero.
You think this is going to control us?
get in their heads and start teaching.
J.R. Bob Dobbs, known among salesmen as the saint of sales.
It's actually a mystic sales ability.
Oh, okay.
Schedulatory sales.
Hey, where did you get these jokes anyway?
Oh man, the safety seal is broken.
Hey, hey, hey, these jokes have been tampered with, man.
Hey, jokes, I like Peter Rodman.
Scott, get him out of here.
He's good in science.
Where did these jokes come from?
In the same pot.
The conspiracy's been full with our jokes.
We're obliterating Abram.
And liberty and justice for all who believe.
Christ my Lord.
Perhaps somehow this knowledge weighs on him
more heavily than on many of us who are able
to bear our mortality without resorting
to an elaborate denial system.
Well, I haven't figured that one out myself yet.
Perhaps after the show you could show me
how.
Well, how else can you explain the avoidance
of humanity itself, of simple human charity,
of the fact of connection?
Well, it can be explained.
It's a simple explanation.
The explanation for practically everything is available
at your fingertips.
And it seems most of you in this room have forgotten it.
Now, what happened to the old, the old, you know,
kill or kill me philosophy of subgenius?
Hey, what happened to this?
I mean, Bob was supposed to kill you and you turned it around.
All right.
I died a thousand times.
All I want is a little crumb of bread, Ivan.
Just a tiny, just one bite of bread.
Now come back to the church.
Throw my face.
Just one, just one crumb of nourishment for one
of the old faithful.
Oh, man does not live by bread alone.
There's other things besides food that nourish you very enough.
But just one crumb.
You had your crumb.
More tape.
You dropped my tape.
Hey, hey.
You want to buy some show?
Our show is scientifically engineered
to reduce stress and fatigue.
The world's most successful show and superb performance
is only half the story.
It's a legend in its own time.
However, improper listening techniques
may lead some persons to dependency, seizures,
cranial fits, priapic conditions, micturition,
sternutation, subtle glandular mutations,
and in some territories, legal arrest.
Listen to the definitive, authoritative, and
informative, eye-opening, thorough, insightful,
useful, complete, and original subgenius hour and a half of slack.
.
Peace.
Hey.
Get up in peace.
Peace.
.
Napoleon has indeed won the battle.
Peace.
Once congratulations to you and to all of us in your
wonderful, wonderful nation of coils policies.
.
Peace.
Scott Kemp, I sentence you to hell.
No, I have been saved.
I've been in church practically all my life.
Yes, you have grown up in church,
and you have certainly had an experience with your God.
But the record reveals that you have been unprofitable,
and the word decrees that the unprofitable servant
must be cast into outer darkness.
But when have I been unprofitable?
You have rebelled against my word,
and you have stolen your Lord's money.
While you lived upon the earth,
I permitted you to earn a good living.
As my servant, I gave you power and health to earn money,
and in return for this, I decreed in my word
that a tenth part of those earnings were mine.
I left that 10% in your care,
charging you to invest it for me
and to make me a good man.
I gave you my church,
that the gospel might be preached.
But you, Scott, have rebelled against my word.
You have not only taken 90% which I freely gave you,
but you have been so covetous as to take the 10% also.
Did you know that rebellion is a sin of witchcraft,
and that no covetous person shall enter the kingdom of God?
Oh, sir, I tell you, I didn't realize it was so serious.
I didn't realize it was so serious.
And if you don't want that to happen to you,
if you don't want the judgment in Dobbstown,
a recording of which you just heard,
to go against you like that poor Poe Bucker there,
Bob was mad at him because he was unprofitable.
And he didn't want us to be unprofitable either.
You can write for information,
not about this station,
but about the church of the subgenius,
which so many of you hate.
You got that pencil or pen or tattoo needle ready, dear friends?
That's P.O. Box 140306.
Got a nice ring to it.
140306, Dallas, Texas, 75214.
And just drop us a postcards with your address.
And...
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Oh, yes.
The Harvest.
And we've gotten a lot of calls tonight.
Lots of great hate calls.
You know, I played some recordings of old hate calls,
and it's funny how they'll just follow that cue.
It just, it brings it out.
So keep calling and keep listening.
We'd love to know that you keep listening to something you hate.
That tells us a lot.
Thank you.
THE HARVEST
Space girls always smoke but tease
Swallow butts and feed no waste
Say don't mess around with the rule
They don't want you
Just to show that they don't care
And that's why I'm here today
Go bite the face and burn the hair.
Suck them up and move the hood.
Now you've got the sprinkle blues.
My daddy works for the secret Marines.
I know because he has, he keeps six brains in maldehyde jars on our living room mantelpiece.
He chooses six different kinds of food coloring in them for some reason.
And I've been told never to touch the jars.
But sometimes I talk to the grains when nobody's home.
Electric static noises, lightning bolts.
Well, you know, lightning bolts and ions.
I'm going to jump out like a circus in the fireplace.
My daddy has seven brains.
Six he keeps on the shelf and one that he keeps in his head that he doesn't tell anybody about.
That he uses to play along with those TV game shows.
I see you off for tonight from North Carolina ...
Well I gotta finish with a reservation for tonight at the Andamanuk House Hotel.
I got a littleorvation for tonight.
You want two beds or one?
One.
Ok, one bed.
32 plus taxes.
I'd like to get a room to rest for a night.
32 plus taxes?
32.
That's great.
Now this is for two beds, kids.
Now, do you have mirrors on the ceilings?
Because I know some of these fancy whoop-de-doo Hollywood hotels have mirrors on the ceilings.
No, we don't.
Oh, no.
I don't know if I want to do it.
We don't like that kind of place.
Oh, you're not that kind of place.
No, we don't like that kind of place.
Well, wait a minute.
3-2-22?
What's that mean?
Now, let me ask you this.
You got color TV?
Color TV and telephone.
Oh, man.
Okay, can I give you the reservation?
No reservation needed.
When you drop by, we need your ID.
Oh, you'll have the vacancy, though.
We got lots of it.
Okay, let me ask you this.
Is adult photography allowed in the rooms also?
Sir, you've been asking me a lot of questions like that, okay?
I think you better go to other hotels.
Well, if I pee on the floor, can I drink it out of a Dixie cup if I can scoop it up with a straw?
No, you can't.
Why not?
I don't know what kind of question you're asking.
Well, if the bullfrogs were gagging on...
This is a decent hotel.
If you want that kind of a, you know, those kind of a hotel, you better go across the street.
The 400, they got mirrors, they got x-rays.
Oh, man.
Not here.
Man, oh, man, that's good.
Let me...
It's all an illusion.
Yes, these were the old days, dear friends.
We're listening to a 10-year-old hour of slack.
What a trip down memory lane.
It's been a long time.
It's been a long time for me, and what a confusing mess for you, but that's all right.
You don't want to know why I didn't do an original show this week.
I don't want to know either.
Praise Bob.
It's all an illusion.
All a lie.
The one who flashed the badge calls your name and says,
I am Special Agent Arnold Palmer,
acting under authority of Exec.
Order Camp X-Day 666.
BOM for your own good and the security of the nation.
We are taking you into protective custody.
You need to know these facts.
One, we are in a war to the death.
In large means.
The average subgenius doesn't even realize the anti-Bob is fanatically lusting to destroy...
Because of misconduct.
Every last subgenius patriot.
Even as they have done to our kindred in Dobstown, in Bolivia.
In any war, the most vital element is slack.
Positive mental slack.
This includes courage, the willingness to sacrifice oneself for the good of one's me.
Knowing one's own identity, knowing who and what.
The people.
The weak enemy is.
Your plans and your foe's plans.
The pink boys, although 50 times as many as they'll admit,
are still a ridiculously small minority compared to the Axists.
Able to dominate a world because they're organized.
They control communications and thus are able to keep billions of victims misled, disorganized, demoralized...
Inhumany.
The lord of laughs.
His high-ranking...
Followed my commandments from this very day.
All my confri-
Yes, I'm not swaying, I'm a plata don dos, I say one of your high-ranking sirs.
Who killed his fellow brothers in a conflict with the Black Manna.
And let the personalities, so corrupt in no way be stripped of dignity.
out humbled that guy over there he came up and just threw some humiliation laughs and then but
then i just humbled him up the face then i humbled him in that yet i'm humbler than half the people
you've ever met hell he was humbler than hell damn enlarge me after that a pretty girl came up to me
a reporter for a famous newspaper asked me reverend sterno how did you find out about
the pink pardon my language but yee-haw said well it happened in the 50s when bob uncovered that rock
and she's a 50 save not through it can't be news word back in the 50s well we want to know what
happened two minutes ago she said in a jack daniels bottle leaving it for three weeks under her porch
self-examination and then she said well i'm not sure what happened to you but i'm not sure what happened to you
she was telling it to crager crager mutating it craggers of course functioning discombobulation ray
selling it coast to coast and the truck that was the actual drum kit used in the 14th doctors for
bob show when they the truck wired it was all the drummer be not and then they realized the
conspiracy plot was actually not a conspiracy
plot at all, but a conspiracy
plot to make people think
there was a conspiracy plot.
Why is there a limit?
Pardon me, what was that
again, Dr. Howell? Maybe our listeners
would like to hear that the
new edition of the Book of the Subgenius
is coming out soon. So you'll have to buy
that extra copy. New cover?
Yes, and a different PowerShell code.
Cross the threshold of reality and enter a fantastic
imaginary universe. Who would you like to know?
Visit lands islanded in mystery
and magic. Splendid palaces
where powerful dragons soar
through the sky. Mystical unicorns
comfort the pure of heart.
And sprightly elves cavort
in moonlit forests. Hey, Sting, we want
our show to stay the same. If you bother
messing with it, your plane won't land
and you'll go straight to your Bob.
Peer over the edge of darkness where
ancient spirits lurk in the shadows.
Oh, so you like this
this hodgepodge
of death?
I like the number 9.
9 is amazing.
Satisfying.
It's not stodgy. It's
satisfying.
The most satisfying number is
nine. Four is not so hot. Four and eight are not that great.
Uh, hi, I'm interested in, uh, reserving a room for tonight. Do you have vacancies?
Oh, that's great. Now let me ask you this. How much does it cost for a room for two people?
Oh yeah. Oh, overnight. Oh, that's a great bargain. That's a great, you know,
you have the best bargain in town about, about for that. Now, now let me ask you this for single
bed, right? Okay. Now, now let me ask you this. Uh, when they, when they, uh, get the
delivery, they're going to be, they're going to be, they're going to be, they're going to be
When the Delvecchio method interred within, did the youngsters do it?
I can't hear you.
Well, when the youngsters did it with the Delvecchio method, they didn't have it.
Have what?
Well, they had the salami meat with the cervix menstruating, Barners.
No.
Now, at the Hi-Hat Hotel, do you allow youngsters to urinate on the floor
if they smash bullfrogs on the head with sledgehammers?
No, I don't know.
Now, if I went to the bathroom and I found 11 bullfrogs gagging on clumps of hair,
do you think that I could desiccate them and eat the vital organs?
If I wouldn't be breaking the law, that is.
Yeah.
Would that be acceptable to the morals of your decency?
You know, the legless eunuch banded together and clumped with the corn stalks
reproduced from all over 90 cases.
Yeah, you want to rent overnight, right?
Yes, absolutely. Can you take my name?
Yeah, okay. What's your name?
Perry Strump.
Huh?
Perry what?
Strump.
Yeah, okay.
It rhymes with hump.
Okay. What time you come here?
About 2 o'clock.
And we're coming from another dimension beyond the beams of the electrons, beyond that which is known.
We are vibrating very rapidly at a higher energy level, but we plan to be with you.
Will you accept us?
You come to here, okay?
One more last information.
Information.
Tell me what they did with the youngsters.
Did the youngsters do it?
What?
Did the youngsters meet the salami unit?
With...
What?
Did the youngsters do it with the salami unit which they had?
I was trying to find out. I talked to Karen. I talked to Sarah. I talked to Barry.
They didn't have any of the information that I wanted.
Please, please let me know. Else I can't come to the Hi-Hat Hotel.
Yeah, okay. Anyway, you come here and...
Barry had the plexiglass.
Ah.
Do you got the tubes that were inserted into the nasal passages?
...
Hello?
Charlie?
Prosecutor?
What is it?
Isn't VR because of contraption?
What should I do?
Choi, send a to patients with  aad  phin.
What?
lo, wicked.
Pretty useless.
Gerishment in the whole world of the NHSth wavelength.
Because of Beijing's airkiungsthe wholeAmlogical page,
you know, it sat to bring the convolution between the human species and upcoming organisms.
Rift. There's a lot from that to L.A., the other L.A. group of crazies there. Truby, at one point,
answered one of those ads that you see in comic books and men's magazines that say,
send in your lyrics and we'll turn it into a country western song, you know, for 10 bucks.
You get a cassette back and they'd have put your lyrics to music. Well, he sent in a
pretty surrealistic poem and
sure enough, they made it into a song.
That's the way it is.
The parts of my days
Because they're black
Love it when we play
The E.V.
The blind man's piece of red
Because he's black
The E.V.
The blind man's piece
Is a dark, glossy black
The E.V.
Is a boil Daniel
Isn't he tan?
Is it konw, huggy and round?
Whatcha goin' through the bag again?
Whiskin over and outta deep stream.
foarte
Wierde
Jeli
Sp
There's always
that you need coke and you made the tolerated jacket out of.
I don't know.
Been in hell so long
that I'm blinded by any light.
Been buried at the bottom
of the dung heap so long
that my eyes are dead to any hope
for a better tomorrow.
Like a hideous deep sea
fish. I've adapted
to the blackest depths imaginable.
Please
forgive me if I perceive
no light.
Been in hell so long
that I'm accustomed to being paraded
by assholes.
I'm accustomed
to being penniless and powerless
forever. I'm
accustomed to doing
mob work for mob
chicks. I'm accustomed
to being a toady for incompetent
dildos and
living on loose change
until
Friday.
I am so accustomed to
eating shit mob that I am
unaware of any other kind of nourishment.
Been in hell so long
that any escape routes are invisible
to me.
Due to my
adapted blindness
from dying in hell
for so long.
Which was actually a conspiracy
plot, which was actually a subgenius
plot, which was
actually a front for another
conspiracy plot which had been
created by conspiracy
robots, which had been created
by subgenius robots, which
in turn had been created by
subgenius androids, which in turn
had been created by subgenius robots.
Which had been created by
glowingly dark brain aliens,
which had been created by the nine inch worm androids,
which had been created by castner heads,
which had been created by the Mission Impossible team.
Good evening, Klamath town.
Yeah, I'd like to make a reservation.
Is that okay?
Reservation?
Yeah.
Okay.
For what day?
For tonight. I'd like it.
For tonight?
Yes.
Okay.
This is for certain tribes and races of people who have
characteristic odors.
Pardon me?
This is for certain tribes and races of people who have
characteristic odors.
Now, let me ask you this.
At the Cloud Motel, did the youngsters find the plexiglass?
Sir, could you please be a little louder?
I cannot hear your voice.
Okay.
Let me ask you this.
When you had the glassine packets, did you have any
plexiglass enveloped over the retinas?
The odor after coitus was overwhelming.
Now, is that allowed at the Cloud Motel?
I don't know.
Well, I cannot just hear your voice because it's...
Terry, Barry, and Linda informed me that we could have had it
done without surgery.
Is that correct?
That's correct.
Sorry.
Excuse me.
Stay on.
Oops.
Here.
You know, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Say it.
It can be done while you sleep.
Yes, while you sleep.
One hour of positive, constructive repetition while you sleep is equivalent to nine hours
while you are awake.
Bob?
The message.
is now part of and registered in your subconscious mind.
Every time you say, see, hear, or think...
Bob?
...that's your key phrase,
it will trigger the entire message
without your being aware of it.
Wait, wait, wait.
All right, wait.
Uh, has that happened recently, do you know?
All the time.
They have to have a source of supply.
Where do you people get these boxes?
In the ground.
On gathering night, all come from boxes.
Clothes, wood, food, all from boxes.
When I'm born, she'd be put into boxes
and dug up for great eating.
Uh, do you know whether they ever come out
into the subway tunnels of the city?
I think so.
Right on underground.
Underground?
Underground.
What do you know about the underground?
The elders say there is much good eating underground.
.
From the far horizons of the unknown
come transcribed tales of new dimensions in time and space.
These are stories of a future,
Adventures in which you'll live in a million could be years on a thousand maybe worlds.
X minus 1.
Robot has landed at the foot of the tube, sir.
Switch on the intercom.
Robot.
Robot N71.
N71.
Identify this idea or goal and picture it clearly in your mind.
Don't forget to use your drift meter.
The music has gone and the mucus is up.
Oh, no.
We're really testing callers this morning. Good morning.
Good morning.
Are you man or woman enough to take the church?
Yes. As a matter of fact, we're planning the overthrow of the convention.
Ah, that's what we like to hear.
That's what we hear.
Yes, yes.
Kill Bob.
Meanwhile, there you are.
First to inspect in the privacy of your own home, shop, office, den for 20 years or express permission
already withdrawn by the Polk, McKinley, Harding, Dobbs, Coolidge men.
The only men authorized to stamp your application with its own seal.
Looks easy, doesn't it? But it won't come off.
Yeah, exactly. We were ripe the day we started this thing.
Yes, that's why they shut it down.
Yes.
How long are you guys going to be on?
We're going to be on until they throw us out.
Or kill me! Or kill me!
They wallow in our intellectual impotence.
Shorted the show out and spent the whole thing in one little three-second buzz.
Yeah, sorry. I didn't mean to use up all of our tangible effect.
Stay there until you fall asleep. When you fall asleep, that means we're off the air.
When you quit listening to us, we'll no longer be there.
You have to make the primordial matter of nature stand up and salute.
Hey, Bob, man.
Woo!
Yeah!
Give me some of that meat brownies.
Prop it up!
You!
Pass that prop, prop smoker.
Prop it up!
Prop, prop.
Give me some prop.
Give me that trouble smoker.
Put that prop on.
There's a big party for Bob, but he's in a trance.
There's a big party for Bob, but it's okay, he's in a trance.
He's dead!
Wild party!
But he's in a trance.
All the party guests are just sipping big mixed drinks.
And they're chanting voodoo chants.
Yada hey!
Yada hey hey!
This is the wall man, dear friend.
The wall man.
Get some props.
All I got, Bob, was a batu box.
It's okay, Bob's in a trance.
This chick came over.
This chick came over to get this prop from Indonesia.
See his green eyes?
It was just great.
It was marvelous, man.
Oh wow, Jerry Garcia's in a protest.
And the rest is a mess.
Yeah, man.
It's a real band.
That's Dolly Parton.
You're a good guy.
Hanging off the chandelier.
Wonderful party, Bob.
Wonderful.
Bob, you're a good guy.
Bob, I spelled something out.
You got a cloth to wipe it up with or something?
Dolly Parton and Paul Schaefer are making a spinach salad in the bathroom.
Wrap it up.
Hey!
Hey, Bob.
I spit on your floor, okay?
Hey!
Chop, chop.
productos materials products
our
lingen
X
etched, forged, and finished.
These authentic replications
not available in any store
even on this radio station
before their commission
literally without regard
for any quality.
They come with their own
adoption papers
and you can bring them
into their own home.
You're kind of crazy.
Ah, but now
by special arrangement
to the Postmaster General
of Guam
this 72-piece
commemorative plinth
honoring you
and the footprints
of the great jewel thieves
of the French Riviera
mentioned earlier
each encased in its own
watery silk caddy
that revolves 360 degrees
on genuine Swedish
ball bearings
has been cancelled.
Sorry.
Yes, indeed.
Oh, there it goes.
Oh, it hurts.
But we can carry it, caller.
Okay, hold on.
All right.
The resulting confusion
of all seismic signals
will cause
the simultaneous detonation
of American warheads
to arm and arm.
I'm not sure
if you've ever seen
the money
but who signed the check.
In the end,
the signature
is always the same.
It's merely a sport
to them
and they do it
for their own
lurid
misguided
husband.
And your own
against it
generating this
voice
to play
a song
that you can't
The unforgivable
pleasures
they derive
from
letting you
in on the truth
little by little.
The truth
will become
very clear
to you
in a moment
even now
when you're
deciding
in the mind
you've convinced
yourself
you possess
soon to be
replaced
at your request
to
the man
that set them free.
But surely
if they can
to spontaneously
abandon
the crew
who started
before
you
anner
that was
in your
truce,
there is
some
at the
fugitives from your consciousness arguing this very moment.
Arguing with the elder gods.
Arguing for your souls.
The parchment is signed by your willingness to participate.