But let's leave things of this world behind, and walk now down the path of Bob for this brief minute of slack from the Church of the Subgenius.
Release your hold on this tenuous practical joke they call reality.
Let your body be sucked out of your ears, for we're going to take you deep, deep inside yourself to the place of silence in the noise.
We're going deeper, deeper into your consciousness, down past the membranes of the fabric of your very mind.
We bore down into the cranium, drilling through the irrelevant memories of job and normality,
piercing the squamous epizootis rolling around in the hollowed-out inside of the skull,
scraping along the edges of the birth canal and stretching the imagination gland until it pops.
Now, let all your...
Let your thoughts drain out through the brain pan, tumble down through the sinuses, slide down the esophagus,
and finally, let them plunge to the base of the soul itself, located in the lowest organ of your body, the foot gland.
And finally, an idea, a key, an ultimate plan is born at the very bottom of your mind, and it is Bob.
Let there be slack.
It's not a crunch.
Dad, it's something I've come to rely on to help me through life.
He will not reveal his identity, so for today, we're calling him Bob.
Good, good. I think we're ready, Dad.
And then...
A miracle!
Oh, please, no miracles.
You're a nice guy, Bart.
Drink up.
And now, ladies and gentlemen, it's showtime.
I don't...
Most people seek to control life in order to secure a more positive, productive, and
free existence.
Often, however, the objectives of others conflict with our objectives.
Now, most people, common people really, can barely manage to control their own self-centered
myopic existence.
They command armies of lawyers armed with paper weapons, attacking with spiteful, vengeful,
cowardly litigation.
Others operate within elephantine bureaucracies.
We'll all get fired.
Cut to a promo.
Start tape.
Oh Rollin'?
Rollin'?
You little.
A-a-ahl inna.
A-a-ahl, ha googly A-a-ahl, a-a-u-hoh, a-a-ah A-aa Alg scans, you've all seen it now.
I'm boomer.
Yeah, yeah, yeah
How dare you editorialize so blatantly?
You have just violated the most sacred canon of journalism.
Millions of Americans were listening to you.
Now what is the idea of screaming at me in the middle of the night?
I was ignoring you.
What's the big emergency?
It started this morning.
Every station's making like it's the 1950s.
We got static, we got snow, all kinds of distortions.
Unexplained disturbance and the hysteria that it's causing are incredible.
How would you describe what you are seeing?
It is clearing the mountains, moving too slowly to be a comet or meteor.
Widespread panic has gripped the countryside as thousands have taken to the streets.
It is confirmed.
There it is, the strange atmospheric phenomenon.
It is apparently what we've been causing all the distortions in our broadcast.
So far the phenomenon has not caused any damage.
We have to ask you to try to stay calm and it's important for everyone not to panic.
We have a fix on three of the occurrences about to appear.
We are over American City.
It's just unreal.
Alright, fine.
Yeah.
Um, she wants to buy me my own radio station.
And so, as of 10 a.m. tomorrow morning, this will no longer be a classical music station.
We're gonna try a talk radio format for a while, see how that works.
Oh, also we're changing the call letters of the station to KRZY.
I can't believe you're the same person I listen to on the radio every day.
I thought you'd be, I don't know, older.
Not so attractive.
It's...
It's weird.
I mean, I listen to your show every night.
And your voice, I know that this is gonna sound strange, but it's becoming so familiar to me.
So comfortable.
And I feel like you're a friend, home with me every night.
Keeping me company.
Why don't you come back with me at my place tonight and have some wine?
You can tell me how you come up with all those crazy things you do on the air.
Maybe you can even...
...took me in the head.
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about the show.
We gotta become more outrageous.
We gotta tap ourselves, otherwise we're gonna lose our numbers.
More outrageous?
You think that's possible?
200,000 people down there listen to me and you on the radio every night.
We are right on the verge of getting what we wanted.
I'm starting to get offers to syndicate nationwide.
If our numbers keep growing, I'll be taking our show into 50 cities across the country.
We are entering a new age.
Old taboos are falling away.
People...
People are now as afraid to tap into the dark side of themselves.
In fact, they are fascinated by depravity.
I want to do a new segment and call it My Best Crime.
People call us up anonymously and they talk about a crime they committed.
And we're not talking shotlets in here.
Isn't that a little hardcore?
The absolute cutting edge.
Sure, we'll get a lot of crank calls.
But we'll also get a lot of real calls.
There's a whole city of perversion down there and we can plug into it.
Use our 55,000 watts of power to spread it to every single corner.
I don't know, man.
It sounds way over the edge.
I mean, you gotta admit, it sounds crazy.
It'll be fascinating.
We'll have people glued to the radios.
We'll have them asking, who's gonna call tonight?
What sick confession will I hear this evening?
I bet we get a 25 share on first month.
And from there, you and I are a signature on a contract away from going to the team coast to coast.
Makes a great gift.
Not available anywhere.
Oh yeah, and I suppose Jonescow is just a plumber party.
But...
All our best warriors are gone, man.
John Wayne, Sir Lancelot, Joan of Arc, Nelson, Wellington, hell baby, even Doris Day.
They've all died in battle, man.
Anything like that would put me right over the edge.
I wouldn't joke about anything else that happened here tonight.
Now don't tell me you're taking all this seriously.
Aren't you?
I really love your show.
It's all that keeps me going.
I think I better get off now.
Sir, please stay on the line.
I'll go back and get you.
Don't hang up.
Hello?
What is it?
All right, let's see if we should take a break.
We'll be right back.
Pleasant dreams.
Oh yes, dear friends.
I know you're all going to be a little bit worried about this.
But I know you're going to be a little bit worried about this.
Because today, I'm going to be talking about an old school subgenius collage by Puzzling
Evidence.
Actually, I suppose you might as well call it a Puzzling Evidence Old School collage
by a subgenius.
And tonight's show, Hour of Slack number 839, has sort of a new cast, almost, just because
there's a lot of material from the new school subgeni.
Upmailed or emailed or whatever.
or uploaded or down chucked,
including those new titles,
that great new title song there
by the El Queso All-Stars.
We got new material from The Bishop,
Saint N, and Hell in a Handbasket.
This music in the background is by DJ Epoch.
We got stuff from Ed Fred,
Pater Nostril, Modemak,
Britney Spears.
The Bishop of New York
found some especially juicy educational material
full of good news about Johnny and Jane.
The Bishop of New York found some especially juicy educational material
At the same time, the lining of the uterus
becomes engorged with blood and nutritive fluids
in preparation for the development of
Rolo the Robot, the chromium-plated butler.
And here's a gadget that breaks down
and is discharged from the body.
Golden Brown, the amazing tiny automatic genital organs
that almost seem to think for themselves.
It is just a daydream after all.
The millions of small mechanical external glands
pulls out its own pituitary gland
at the base of the brain.
Therefore, each Johnny and each Jane
need the sympathy, understanding,
and cooperation of servants that never ask for afternoons off.
And still another deep thinker rides way up in the vagina
where a milky secretion is added to form
Rolo's little brother.
But the rap at Grubb's is a little more selfish than that.
The growth of his penis, testes, and emissions of semen gives him a need for sexual activity,
both organized and unorganized, which gives him a feeling of strength and achievement.
Don't look now, but with a bit of a vacuum, this sturdy fellow can manage to stage a grand
performance.
What's more, her sex glands and genital organs and her breasts tell him when to come and
get it.
This is one of the primary sex characteristics of girls.
He may twitch and squirm when he tries to remain disproportionately small.
The resulting congestion wouldn't be half so much fun if we didn't have that robot
that likes its meals served through a long tube, a brainy collection of jets and valves,
and underarm hair sex cells.
All we need to do is push the button, but your regenerative circuits are tuned asynchronously,
and that causes concatenation in the intermediate amplifiers.
And this is important.
This gradual and irregular readjustment of the glandular system is a key to the success
of the system.
The system is almost certain to give Johnny and Janie ravenous sexual appetites.
From now on, I don't think there'll be the slightest trouble with your sexual maturity.
Your domestic problems are completely solved.
On the other hand, there was the sudden spurt, spurt, spurt, spurt, spurt, spurt, spurt, spurt,
and finally...
Every day in our homes and offices, we have to be careful.
In our transporting moltores as well as in our motor cars sex glands and genital organs
are doing more things for us than we realize.
He really needs a blast
That boy needs a rewild
He acts so childish
It's all his big boy way
I'm hoping it's just a phase
I just want to let you know
And things don't change, I'm gonna blow
Suck my bitch, suck my bitch boy
Give him something to remember
They think they're dragging him way down
They keep on trying to push him round
I tell the boy you must have sucked
Between the stretches where it's at
He thinks that I'm insane
But this is no fucking game
I just want to let you know
And things don't change, I'm gonna blow
Suck my bitch, suck my bitch boy
Give him something to remember
Suck my bitch boy
They just wanna be next for me
Its still hard work where you didn't leave
Sometimes things simply fade and breathe
And he's still pretty undecided
The rub b adequate better bite him
Suck my bitch boy
You a real fucking hoe
I just want to let you know
If things don't change I'm gonna woe
Slap my bitch, slap my bitch boy
Give him something to remember
Slap my bitch boy
My daddy finally found his way
He fucking smugs off every day
He's getting right with my b-bob
He even tried to quit his job
I got my boyfriend back
And I doubled all my slack
I just want to let you know
This song has nowhere left to go
Slap my bitch, slap my bitch boy
Give him something to remember
Slap my bitch boy
This warped idea of law and authority has contributed to the fact that vice is fun.
The things we have in America are venereal disease, syphilis, gonorrhea, murder, forcible rape, or assault to kill.
In pace with the emphatic decisions of the American people as to what they want,
substances, human waste, made attractive by misery, which we as Americans may enjoy.
Do you want your children stimulated by the way things look as well as the way they perform?
Do you want your son enticed into the world of the American love of beauty?
Or your daughter lured into the basic freedom of the American people,
which is the freedom
of individual choice?
Marijuana? Sure.
Every mother and father in this country
leave their unmistakable marks on homosexuals
faster than we can build jails to house them.
The bishop did that, friends. Before that, we heard the lightest from Saint Anne and Helena Handbasket.
Uh, you can get more about Saint Anne and Helena Handbasket
from www.minitru.org.
Minitru is M-I-N-I-T-R-U.
Minitru.
And, uh, the bishop has a great new subgenius video and audio club
on Yahoo! called Yeti Video.
A multimedia interactive website, friends, where you should send your weird art and video clips and sounds.
And here's where to do that.
You go to groups.yahoo.com
on the web.
groups.yahoo.com
slash group
slash Yeti video
or just generally, Yahoo groups.
Do a search on Yeti Video.
Y-E-T-I video.
One word.
And friends, we got some email from an old high school buddy of mine,
Jim Long.
Uh, uh.
A guy so weird and inventive that some of my own work is based on a dream I had about some work by him.
Except that I just dreamed it.
Anyway, friends, tonight for Transitions, we're using...
I give you the finger.
Jim Long.
Transitions.
Do you copy?
Over.
Bob.
Do you copy?
Over.
Bob.
Do you copy?
Over.
Bob.
Do you copy?
Over.
Bob.
Phivell Thomas.
Hello, this is Ricardo Montalbán.
This is Ricardo Montalbán.
Oh, shit.
Goodbye.
How about I give you the finger
and you give me my phone call?
Yes, friends, that was,
that big long collage there
was by Reverend Ed Fred
called Or Kill Me
by Ed Fred.
Before that, we heard a little bit
of Hell Pope Huey at 4X Day.
More of that coming up.
And now, from the most recent
subgenius devourable
here in Cleveland,
friends, at the Beachland Ballroom,
Einstein's Secret Orchestra.
And by the door,
he fell in love with an Indian baby
over an empty store.
But I just
just a little thing
I never let it show.
So she could never answer
yes or no.
And he always called it Sunday business.
Hell,
the time of all
the pain and water
beats and braids
and hopes and fates
and thoughts.
But I knew
there was never
a sure sign
because the sign
is made of light.
Light.
Hey!
More than life.
You never got a kiss.
Oh, life.
You don't know what it meant.
Incidentally wonder
about his face and breath.
Elijah with the oil
for the night.
Elijah was a woman in it.
You never went nowhere.
He felt his heart
and he didn't mean it.
He didn't go for over here.
Elijah
should have been
never let it show.
So she could never answer
yes or no.
And then one day
a wealthy customer
bought him a
to go so far
away.
But only Elijah stayed.
Elijah!
So then,
lonely as can be,
and wishes he was still
in my dream.
Elijah!
WOW bait Why Liam?
He bought me some
washed money
trying to find
uncles
I was
on the
Thank you.
Of the whole planet.
Dinosaurs, everything.
Solar system.
Oh, but then he gets to find out what everything's really like.
He'll wake up on the planet of broken glass, sitting there naked.
Looks like my feet are bleeding.
What the hell's going on?
This mission is too important for me to allow you to jeopardize it.
How am I doing?
You hear that one, Dave?
I'm going to be out of here.
This mission is too important for me to allow you to jeopardize it.
You hear that one, Dave?
You get the same way twice.
I feel much better now.
Same way twice, yeah.
Well, as we can see, all of the memories are coming up on the front view monitor.
Oh, yes, yes.
Yes, I hear you, Dave.
I'm sorry, Dave.
H5.
I'm afraid I can't do that.
Oh, look what they're doing to him.
He's playing pin the tail on his face.
Stop calling him back.
Stop.
There's no more signal from Earth.
He's too far away.
Or there's simply no signal.
Nothing's happening anymore.
The last ones have died out.
Signals no longer exist.
Maybe Dave's the only one left.
Well, if he did get a signal, it would be as the Earth was 300 years ago now.
That's the hyper signal, man.
That's what he's been waiting for, the hyper signal.
You don't want to scratch his neck that way.
No, no, it's going to come off.
Echo the signal.
It's actually in the past.
It's gone 300 years into the past.
Echo me.
In the future.
That's all about black indecision
And I'm in a broken class
Every woman upon the road in class weighs 600 pounds
Every day is 120 degrees with 100% humidity
No one has any clothes except for shoes
They're under the chairs
There's no place to sit to break a glass
Any thought you get will never heal
No matter how severe you'll never die
Every day at 4 o'clock it'll rain rubbing alcohol
There'll be nothing to eat
The radiation will flood everyone's blood into a rich and tasty sauce
And the only thing you'll be able to do is hunt down that next 600 pound deep-booted naked humanoid
Snatching up and eating him
But no matter how severe his wounds
He'll never die
Everybody can't be bored
So let me be the shit that falls through your ass
When you feel the pain that's every single day
I'll issue a license for everyone who wants to go to Disney
Planet of Broken Glass
Ranted by Dr. Legume
And mixed by
Pater Nostril
Or Darth Nostril
It may be his new name
Before that
ESO Swamp Radio
On WCSB Cleveland
The experiment on Lonesome Cowboy Dave's one brain cell
And before that friends we heard
Dr. Philodrummon
In pursuit of the alien
Puzzling evidence mix
And coming up
More Jim Long and Britney Spears
A new episode of
Episode
Of
Last
Episode
Of
The
Planet of
Broken Glass
The
Last
Thank you.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh baby!
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Yeah, yeah!
Oh, baby!
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Well, one thing we certainly know about that lovely young lady,
she's not only not that innocent, she's not that supplicant.
Just take a close look at the space between her eyes.
Look at her mouth.
She's not even a she, Dave. Give me a break.
Correctly spoken.
She's just a little boy.
She's a little boy.
Well, she's not a little boy.
With all the added equipment that little boys want.
Yes.
Very, very, very many implants in every pore.
There used to be a little black boy named...
Michael Jackson.
And now?
And now is a young...
She's a hirsute, young Norwegian named Loretta Swit.
No, no, she's...
No, she's Britney Spears.
She's Britney Spears, America's favorite sweat hog.
Sweat sweetheart.
She's America's sweat hardest sweetheart.
All Michael had to do was discard his skeleton,
which now still goes by the name Michael Jackson.
I just removed the plug from his butt and stepped aside.
The skeleton in it, that's Britney Spears.
The meat without the skeleton?
Yeah, that's...
The ultimate fruition of Michael Jackson's plastic surgery
was to have his skeleton removed,
and that's the one that's doing the Michael Jackson album.
And then there's the meat, the sack of meat that was...
that no longer has a skeleton.
Oh, the ultimate carnal...
There's some kind of nasal there.
What's wrong?
Pick me up real quick.
I don't think so.
There's no carnal?
Angie Fowles.
Thank you, Randy.
They are bad guys, and think I'm telling a joke.
Better to tell the truth.
Jamie O'Reilly said in an interview puji.co.uk,
夏 viscosity gay Juicyבа еґ trades Bull 밍 so you can take me to school for 5 hours,
Anyway, listen pilgrim, dobsian, brothers and sisters of mine, I know quite a few of
us look really fetching or in a felching in black leather, which I know sets your thighs
to sweating, but Nazis, turn off the pencillandrics there, Oboe, if you have more than two, that's
two brain cells to rub together.
You know that Nazis are way down the list behind our other and much more spectacular
failings.
We feature soulless beasts, foaming maniacs, vengeful former fanboys with magic the gathering
eating up that part of their brains that should have been devoted to sex, misanthropic hacking
bastards, misanthropes, hackers, and bastards, succubiating with a little incubus action,
cracked actual geniuses with great camouflage who are just sluggish.
We feature a bunch of people on the dewy eyed Bobby droves that still have the pipe brand
smarting on their asses and a cadre of hangers on them that make me want to bowl them over
with a columnar pillar of my own puke.
It's a jolly list.
The freaking Nazis, that's best say, we're as sweet and pure as the Hershey syrup being
dribbled down like Mary Magdalene's back.
And remember catch and hold dispel spongiform bovine encephalopathy.
No, that's not the cartoon in spongiform Bob Squarepants, that's the brain worm.
You're listening to the subgenius radio ministry hour of slack sponsored by the church of
the subgenius.
For more information about the church of the subgenius write to Bob at the O box two O
four two O six Austin, Texas seven eight seven two O or visit the subgenius radio ministry
website at subgenius.com.
Thank you for listening and praise Bob.
I'm Bob.
He's Bob.
That's just basilic.
I'm going tooj up of I'm going tooj up.
Who's Bob?
and the moam-rats outgrabe.
Beware the jabberwock, my son,
the jaws that bite, the claws that catch.
Beware the jub-jub bird and shun,
the frumious bandersnatch.
He took his vorpal sword in hand,
long time the manxum foe he sought.
So rested he by the tum-tum tree
and stood a while in thought.
And, as in uffish thought he stood,
the jabberwock with eyes of flame
came whiffling through the tulgy wood
and burbled as it came.
One, two, one, two,
and through and through,
the vorpal blade went snicker-snack.
He left it dead and with its head
he went galumping back.
And hast thou slain the jabberwock?
Come to my arms, my beamish boy.
O, frabjous day, kaloo-kalay!
He chortled in his joy.
Twas brillig, and the slithy toes
did jar and gimble in the wabe.
All mimsy were the boragoves,
and the moam-wraths outgrabe.
He continued again,
but
with a little more
kind escaped in.
sliding from beast to beast.
But not still greater than that one,
Thank you.