From PR News in Washington, I'm swollen from days of heavy conspiracy.
It's now at its highest level in 35 years.
The city of Chicago has released approximately 100 police officers.
It's really unusual for any city to release 100 of them all at once.
And local police union president Dean Angelo Sr. says he makes cops look bad.
And we'll see that over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over again.
The city fought the release of a video that showed the shooting death of a young PR News.
In Texas, searchers continue to look for heavily wooded helicopters and boats.
When it comes to requesting financial assistance from the federal PR News agency.
Economist Diane Swift, DS Economics.
Not only down to the Ziproff, Martin's vision reverted back.
We extender deep-based Broadmoor jumps is lost outside.
Wall Street 31, 1787, 28, 28, 49, 42, 6.
This is PR News.
The IOC says PR News.
The government says PR News slowed sharply in Washington.
And now, let's hear what a typical housewife thinks about.
Hi out there.
And speaking of hi, I'd like to show you the...
Oh, jeez.
You see? You see? You're stupid minds.
Stupid, stupid, stupid.
Well, I'm taking it from you.
You're stupid.
Stupid humans.
Nothing is more delicate or complex than the human brain.
Sorry, didn't mean to drop it.
Too late.
Let's see what happens.
Well, it's just a frozen death, so he can do that.
Then I can study the brain.
You are going to be all right, doctor.
Doctor, we'll put your brain back in. You'll be fine.
Everything is confused.
I must point out, doctor.
I tell you.
I know.
Well, is that I know dot com or something?
I know. I know. What you know, you never know.
That's right.
I've got to get back to work.
Okay.
We're going back to work now.
If I don't see you again, this will be a prosthesis.
Yeah, good luck. Good luck to you, too.
Take the Popeye spin.
You.
You want to work, don't you?
What?
Sedaptics.
Sedaptics!
I don't know what you're talking about.
I don't know.
What?
I haven't read a single word that's related to the world.
But I know that something is happening.
I'm sure I'll get the word out.
You're going to be all right.
I'm sure.
You heard the story.
It's true.
I'm sure.
I don't know how to do this.
I don't know.
first couple. And because that first couple embraced that enlightened redefinition, the course
of humanity was forever changed. And J.R., Bob Dobbs, and many others today in our society are
still asking you to embrace the idea that we really know is a better way. That we can define
good and evil based upon contemporary popular opinion. That you can define life and your
relationships to others in your own terms. In essence, that you will be like God.
This was the age of Jim Jones and all kinds of other vampires and psychic parasites out there
using religion to establish control of a segment of a confused and desperate population. And there's
no shortage of people like that.
For reasons good and bad, and real and imagined.
It's fascinating to me to look at religious experience, to look at cults, to look at us and them,
and all this stuff that I passionately disavowed. And then saying to me, which is what the subgenius
did, no, no, we know you don't believe in any of this stuff. We know that us and them
are not going to believe in anything. So, I think it's fascinating to me to look at religious
is wrong. But we're going to worship Bob Dobbs and we're all a congregation and there's the
pinks out there and there's us in here and we hate them and we love us. And won't that
be fun for a little while?
Slack is a gift to the God. The Baptist church did not save you. The Catholic church did
not save you. The unification church did not save you. The Jewish synagogue did not save
you. The church of the subgenius did not save you. But it was Bob, Bob who walked those
hot papers.
No, the church of the subgenius is not incorporated, registered, licensed, certified, approved
or anything by any creature of man's so-called state. It recognizes no head except the Dobbs
head, secular or sacred. Only that head of Dobbs. It recognizes the lordship of Bob as
the only sovereign, the king of kings, salesman and judge of all.
It is a missionary effort, you see, to educate both the masses and those in high places that
Bob lives, Bob sells and Bob has a law that should be kept obeyed and enforced as a society.
Oh yes, dear friends, this is Hour of Slack number 1813, recorded January 11th in the
alleged year of 2013.
We'll again be hearing both new doctrinal material and decades-old classics from the
golden showers years of the church, radio outreach, plus rare fireside theater. My old
beat-up back is back in much better shape thanks to the directed torture known as physical
therapy. But next we have to work on my pain in the neck.
Uh, speaking of torture, I'm going to talk about the church of the subgenius. I'm going to
suitable
for those looking for systematic ideas, help you from the start.
…
The wounds that curled up as I Łukåno just rolled on my cut. It seen like a
ечатue!?
Orange background.
wearing military and superhero cosplay outfits,
tricked a bunch of innocent conservatives into letting them into the Capitol,
where they proceeded to make poor, misunderstood Trump supporters
look like the stupidest idiots in the universe.
But we're not fooled, nor do we care,
because we have much bigger Megalodons to fry.
Yes, friends, a new subgenius book is out.
Eyelash by Reverend Nikolai Kingsley.
And if you don't believe me, just look at the front page of subgenius.com,
or for that matter, Amazon.
Yes, a subgenius science fiction novel.
As it says here on the back,
he swore he'd never deal with the aliens again.
But here he was.
Letting them beam him on board.
He promised that whatever they were planning,
he'd keep Ty out of it.
But here she was on the bridge.
What were the exes trying to hide
that was worse than soul harvesting and interstellar drug running?
And why were they being so nice to him at first?
What in the name of slack had J.R. Bob Dobbs gotten him into?
Who?
And friends, it says here,
oh, here's a quote from a great author about the book.
Nikolai Kingsley's writing easily equals that of the giants
on whose shoulders we crouch,
holding on for dear life with white knuckles
to the oversized weave of their immense dandruff-dusted sweaters
while they stride about their titanic world.
Oh, Reverend Ivan Stang said that.
Well, if I said that,
then you better pick up on it.
To quote Jimi Hendrix.
It's guaranteed doctrinally correct by the Subgenius Foundation.
Dobbs approved publisher since 1977.
That's actually true.
And it even has a little foreword by me.
But it is, in fact, a science fiction novel
set in the subgenius universe.
Reverend Kingsley obviously knew his,
his inside subgenius details,
especially about the aliens,
as revealed in Three-Fisted Tales of Bob
and Book of the Subgenius and all the other ones.
And I'm going to read a couple of excerpts from this.
There are two main characters,
Elif and Ty,
have been given a sort of instruction book.
About Ex Day and the Exists by Bob,
who is also a character in this.
And she was reading all the supporting data
on soul essence and its users.
For some beings even further up the scale
than the already advanced Exists,
soul essence was a drug.
How advanced are they if they have a drug problem?
It was all a lot more complex than it first appeared.
After sorting through the few bits of almost truth
brought back by actual abductees,
a depressing picture started to appear.
Out there were societies at every level of development,
hunter and gatherer cavemen and star travelers,
grubby medieval diggers in the dirt
and slick hyper urban data miners.
In fact, they were all in the same place.
Intelligent machines and non-sentient energy forms.
Every possible way of encoding life was represented somewhere.
Intelligent plants and non-intelligent animals that ate them.
Grazers grazing wherever there was cheap energy.
Hunters preying on the prey,
who were preyed upon by bigger hunters.
And parasites to fill the niches.
All arranged in order of who ate what,
wants and needs, and so on.
Needs made manifest.
Arrangements made to supply them.
Addictions indulged.
Little guys and big players.
Brutally repressive oligarchies
and ridiculously ornate hierarchies.
And dizzying chaotic anarchies.
Every manner of law and code and government and tradition
and the resulting confusion of jurisdictions and crimes.
Every element bumping up against the others
in a hopelessly tangled and
constantly shifting,
no-holds-barred death match fought between
mutually incomprehensible and rigidly,
grimly held world views.
The section on religion simply said,
Oh, just forget it.
Let's just say,
anything goes.
Every possible social problem would find expression somewhere,
and the ones that could be
profitably applied to other races,
higher or lower,
would spread in every direction.
Each variation on the old games.
Master and slaves,
farmer and cash crops,
citadel and barbarians,
dealer and addicts.
Every kind of scam,
confidence trick,
insider trading deal,
concealed toxic waste dump,
law enforcer bribed to look the other way,
rigged election,
and even the most dangerous of all.
Every market would be a gray market.
Everybody's ass would be up for grabs.
You could be the mayor of the planet one day,
and the next locked inside a cheap wooden crate
on your way to some alien creature's dinner table.
She tried to imagine a four-dimensional chart
that could show it all in real time,
and fell asleep to her own fantasy.
To dream of tentacled and subaqueous elder gods,
slime dripping,
their crusted carapaces wrinkled,
rigid, and nippled in dark ocean floor gray-green.
Deceptively friendly abominations of the abyss,
who watched through closed eyes,
and who burbled in a liquid language
just on the far edge of comprehension,
and who only wanted to buy some...
stuff, you know?
I got the necessary right here.
Name your price.
We're good for it.
That's a little section from page 13 and 14
of Eyelash by Reverend Nikolai Kingsley,
just published by us, the Subgenius Foundation.
For information, see subgenius.com.
And now this.
Oh, you guys are so crazy!
Ha ha ha!
I think that's as funny today as it first was
back in the sizzling 70s.
That's right, I'm Dexter Fong,
and nothing will make me forget the thrill we had
making funny records back then.
Yes, my late partner, Hideo Wallbanger and I
were the men of modern comedy.
And today, when the satellite and the radio
net is crammed with the stupid drivel
of the hot humorous 100,
where can a gone cat like yourself get the laughs
that we were making then just for you?
What thrilling moments.
Well, they're all yours now on a double fun, double deal,
Dope Humor of the 70s, volumes one and two.
Who can forget such modern comedy hits
as Cheech Chong's Rubin and the Jets,
or Kong, Wress and Wonders' Beat the Electrician?
Who did you have your arm up when you first
sighed to bootleg by the four or five crazy guys?
Or cut a rug to the antics of Hilario Gomez
and the Wanderers?
Yes, all million sellers, plus the fab fire sign,
together again on this bonus extra.
Yes, a rare collection of fill, fill, fill and fill
at their hilarious, inscrutable best,
if you order now.
Oh, God, wouldn't it be great to laugh again
and stop bumping into things?
Well, bozos, get on it and do it every day.
Now that 70s aren't gone, if you're still smiling,
order now.
Write Dope Humor Offer, Box 69, California.
That's write Dope Humor Offer, Box 69, California, now!
Let's hear about that radio show.
Amazing, isn't it? Listen.
I'm wondering about that voice we heard on the radio.
Uh, I think...
Hmm.
The color of these hot butter rum martinis.
I'd like to talk about...
You're the only person listening to the show tonight.
Yeah, I'm coming.
Okay, good.
Look at this surface, seething and bumping.
There's enormous bubbles popping.
See, the rest of our listeners are machines like this one.
They've made so much money in their regular day jobs
that they were able to fend off these legal problems for years.
Rely on your intelligence and on your memory.
And think about the case.
As it was.
As you blurted out...
You have to say the underlined word correctly.
But how many of you are really genuinely intelligent?
So there.
Bang.
Put a dual display on.
Uh, uh, over to you, uh, uh, puzzling.
Kill me!
Kill me.
I know what you're saying.
Kill me!
Okay!
Why not?
Oh, uh, no, in fact, I'm not ready at all.
Uh, um, uh, I am, uh, and I, uh, I, uh, oh, goodness me, uh, I have no idea how I, uh,
I came by this number.
I've, I'm at present having numbers, uh, uh, Dr. Howe's, I mean, uh, I mean, uh, uh,
I don't sound like him at all.
I know.
I'm presently having phone numbers dialed at random by this, uh, scumbag person who
I'm allowing to, uh, use my phone at the present time.
And he is, uh, taking over everything and dialing up people and appears to be dialing
up doctors of the air for some strange reason.
I guess him being his own person, he can do that.
Um, it's too bad I couldn't talk to you in a better context because I am, in fact, a
great fan of the subgenius.
And, um, but my friend, when I mentioned that, began dialing these numbers and putting me
on the phone and then running away.
And I am extremely annoyed by all this.
However, he is no friend of mine.
And I hope sincerely you will do your best to erase your memory of all this and can merely
continue to make the shows as bad as you can and abuse the callers and listen for Guy the
caller because he will be waiting to be abused more than the rest.
Woo!
Yes, here we go.
Some sort of universe somewhere, somewhere out there where there's...
...a show.
You are about to experience the awe and mystery which reaches from the inner mind to...
The subgenius.
Welcome the potential initiates and remain with us for the next thirty minutes.
Infinite numbers of...
Puzzling evidences.
phylos and huge studio here and the huge studio here we have to have a huge studio i have infinite
people with an infinite number of mouths and heads like shows all spooky and they never shut up
there he is okay now phylo's gone crazy in production studio one looks like they're
isolating the area pulling the doctors out of there well they don't have long to live here
on kpfa i can tell you that island or here on here
stan you remember the first time we raided the bob mansion the playboy mansion of bob oh man god you
could just smell the women he was roasting some over an open fire remember that well it wasn't a
real fire that's what i mean they smelled so crisp and crackly and
yeah those polyurethane vinyl fires they're not real but boy they look so good with those apples
in their minds mouth and just this is so many bob caught us he always does i hope i don't
i never have to do that again no you don't want to get caught in that web what did they call that
a job yeah it made us get a job god that was awful i hated that filing in the basement but
there were a lot of naked female clerks to help us there
remember remember lonnie and and jeanette jeanette the one with the bright red hair and the little
little teeny tiny sharp teeth yeah and what was it who's the one from the whale farm
oh betty bertha betty jean bad bertha big bad big bad birth of the do you remember the captain
you remember that oh yeah you know
he's bob this bob that's stupid i hate those bobby idiots you know 65 years old you know being some
place in florida or arizona but he's still you know in the wheelchairs given command but he's
just gotten turned onto bob so he was in that phase you know he was in that for year one
phase where everywhere he is actually is look there's hat今招跟bap another shop at a spare
bob
chinan
as well end in china
i'm a bad boy
you can purge it every now and then just every now and then until they were練
locked up with the fish, which was no mean feat.
The fish themselves were some 300 pounds.
Some of them weighed in excess of 700 pounds.
Each and every fish was equipped with a dynamic face of structure,
the kind that could tear apart pieces of rock with one grimace.
These were the fish that Bob had selected,
his mighty fighting sperm,
to spread like a mankind accordion throughout the depleted universe.
So you could just take it up to your room
and do whatever you want with it, you know what I mean?
Sit back in that old bungle-rungle roll-away bed
and watch the subway go by.
Take one last drink from that bottle of port.
Pick up the gun.
Look at it.
Put one bullet in.
Spin the chamber.
Put the gun down.
Pick it up again.
Spin the chamber again.
Put it down.
Look out the window.
You know, it's seven trains going by.
Ah, yes.
Life was beautiful.
A few more crackers, and I've got a little mustard left to put on them.
For a while.
Wasn't that something?
And guess what, dear friends?
The new Dobbs Docktown Mirror is out.
Volume 2, number 1, January 1st, 23 A.X.
Things to see, say.
Do, think, know, and buy.
And I'm going to read some sections from the Dobbs Docktown Mirror,
on and off, interspersed with things.
Such as,
from microbe to mutant.
If there is a god,
he is a machine that converts prayers into irony.
More.
Most forms.
Successful.
Eventually, you realize the conspiracy is cheating.
You realize that if you keep playing by the rules,
you lose the game.
But, if you cheat like them,
you lose your integrity.
The subgenius knows that the alternative
is to stop playing their games.
There are other games going on.
Give them a try.
Oh, yeah, you might still lose,
but it won't be because the deck was stacked against you.
Don't tell me about it.
Don't tell anybody.
Tell yourself how you're going to withdraw from the conspiracy's games.
Then, do it.
A little easier.
Resist oppression from outside forces.
J.R. Bob Dobbs can teach you how to oppress yourself.
Subtitles by the Amara.org community
And now, this.
This portion is brought to you by
Space Age Hardware,
where it's always technical.
Three square blocks of bargains.
Look over here.
Outdoor lawn stools.
Three for a dozen in concrete and brick.
Hatchet rests.
29 cents.
Single and dupal hose couplings.
Twice as much, and the price is bigger, too.
Free, free, free, free, free, red, white and blue paint sets
to every fifth customer.
Miners not included.
For a good screw, meet me at
Space Age Hardware.
Corner of Beaumont and Fletcher
in Downer.
So where's the next voyage?
When is the next voyage?
That's the one, the voyage that we're
going on to find the ancient...
To the little crinkly trees?
The ancient trees.
They look like little aluminum foil
up there where everything sounds like
only the city people
make. You hear conversations and pieces
of music while you're trying to sleep out there
because your mind starts
trying to filter out of all this
crazy sound out there in the middle of the night.
Yeah, in the ear. Because I've been lying there
in the ground and I'll hear people talking.
Think, and then think,
there's nobody out here. You'll hear them talking
and they'll be going...
...
You don't hear anything
distinct except once
in a while they say your name in a loud
enough way for you to know that
there's somebody talking out there. It's not a
suspicion anymore. It's an absolute
fact. The question now becomes
how long will it take for them to get to you
and how
fast will they kill you? Will they
kill you slowly or will they roast you
over some kind of a spit or will they just
take a bludgeon
and just hammer your head into
a bloody pulp? So
all they find is this stumpy thing
laying on a cot in the morning by the
camp. You know,
the
park ranger will come around
and say, oh my god,
the park creature
struck again. Okay, the truth. It wasn't
biohazard. It's a
warning sign.
And now some more reading from
the Dobbs.Town Mirror.
Brand new issue.
Immorality as a guide.
Why
in one's finite lifetime
would a person ever
pass by an opportunity
to complain?
Poets and plumbers agree.
Those who do not condemn the
past are remembered
to repeat it.
Those who repeat the past are
condemned to remember it.
Pay attention.
Some religions
are based on tradition.
Beliefs are
passed along in spoken form
or by example or out
of a book or an organization.
Some religions are based
on revelation.
Beliefs are revealed directly
to the believer, sometimes through meditation,
sometimes through divine
intervention.
The church of the subgenius
is based
on sending $35 to
the subgenius foundation.
Only one of these spiritual paths
guarantees eternal salvation
or triple your money back.
Thank you.
The Dobbs.Town Mirror.
And CyberChump for the music
in the background.
From PR News in Washington,
I'm Bart from Buying a Gun.
Scientists have announced
that for the second time ever
they have managed to detect
PR News. After the Fed
came out saying it wanted distortions
in the very fabric of space
and time. The team expects to see
many more PR News in the years
ahead. So that's kind of exciting.
This is really a new window on the universe.
What is radical?
What is not common sense?
Dow 56
17 733.
The National Rifle Association says this
is PR News.
PR News. PR News. Washington.
Washington. The purple dinosaur
who has been called everything from
refreshingly sweet to nauseatingly
nerdy. Well,
once again, rule
toddler TV. Menacing
the Teletubbies.
I believe that the Teletubbies are
their time is on this.
They're definitely never seen them.
Their days are numbered.
They may as well put a fork
in the Teletubbies once Barney hits the scene
again.
Hooded robe.
Subgenius hooded robe.
Clearly made to intimidate and impress.
And I'm guessing it dates
1980.
What's its origin?
The best item of its kind I've ever encountered.
Unfortunately, we have no information identifying
the subgenius. Robe is of excellent
quality and thin black wool, 58 inches
long from the neck. Nine button.
Front buttons are silver colored.
Permanently affixed to the neck
is a 14 inch tall hood which comes
to a point at the top rear and then goes 10 inches
forward to its front which falls the
face mask with one size
fits all.
For the men that want something extra
which would be at the top of the forehead. It's not available
in stores. Two and a half inch by two
and three quarter inch embroidered Dobbs
face. This is not amazingly
boring stuff. This is the real thing.
Amazing. Has wavy white
embroidered edge. Yeah, this thing is a
on the back is a 12 inch high
red inverted pipe. Does it have
the flap in the back? How much
does it cost? That's the important thing.
How much does it charge? It's $475.
Does it have the pyroflatulation
flap in the back? But it may
be so aged that it would fall apart.
It's actually real. Because if you didn't have that
flap and it cost $475
you could risk actually igniting
it if you weren't careful.
It's a mysterious subgenius robe.
Yeah, from some secret
society or order. Look at it.
It's a piece of hood. That's my sad subgenius.
With a skull and crossbow.
He thinks they like him but
when the UFOs come the ladies are gonna kill
everybody but me.
Well, you know, of course they'll spare
the righteous.
That's what all subgeniuses
think. I'm helping channel the thoughts of all
subgeniuses onto the show.
That means no one will be
spared. And no one will call.
They don't need to go to Brushwood.
The saucers will come and pick them up
wherever they are.
They'll be instantly
materialized.
It'll be like a rapture of subgenia.
Yes, thank you.
Right now we're looking at a picture
of all the subgenii sitting in their
pretend first class seats
on the space shuttles ready to leave.
Mysterious and threatening secret
clan or society hooded robe.
I was just telling you it's a subgenius robe
from the early 70s.
Well, it certainly looks like a
terrifying, intimidating robe.
It does, doesn't it?
It's quite wonderful.
Pledges and all that stuff.
Yeah, we used to make them run the gauntlet.
The famous
naked woman gauntlet we used to run
them through. They hated that.
Those bobbies. They always hate stuff
because they're nerds.
And they're so competitive among themselves.
That's what's so pathetic about it.
Just because the average weight of each of those
women was well beyond
300 pounds, that shouldn't have any
effect on it if they were,
you know.
Thinkers.
Thinkers. Thinkers from beyond the sun.
The competitive world.
On the backside of reality.
Conspiracy biz.
Forbidden fantasies that boil up in a
drenched sunburst of fun and relaxation.
Rest and relaxation at last.
I don't feel relaxed.
This show makes me all tense and itchy.
From rest and sleep.
Which?
Yeah, you can earn money even while you sleep,
with our custom
sensual cyber
brain
pan turnkey operation website.
And sooner are best men with thee to go.
You will be on the cutting edge
when you process
those credit cards with 60%
fulfillment.
Start up with only
ten dollars.
You must be two hundred and ten years,
twenty-one years old.
...wors and desperate men.
...and you'll be
Are you lonely?
J.R. Bob Dobbs is the Hobgoblin
of great minds.
He is the chicken,
the road,
the crossing, and the why.
Bob
is keeping a list.
And erasing that list.
He knows
where that thing is.
You can too!
When you join the church.
Of the subgenius.
Smile!
And send one dollar.
When you get to the
being proud of being proud range,
it's a self-feeding
infinite power.
And logically, being ashamed of being ashamed
turns into a kind of pride
and keeps you suspended.
Never entirely
without pride, but generally
feeling down.
There are many resources available to the
subgenius able to turn personality
quirks into sales.
Sales of products,
sales of souls,
sales of sales.
If you secretly
pretend to gloat about something that you
never did, and it makes you feel
a little better or gives you a silent laugh,
that's no vice.
Take my advice.
Because so-called
trouble and your
so-called permanent record
are not barriers for your
achievement of Slack.
Operators are standing
by.
As seen in
the Dobbs.town
mirror.
Available from
Dobbs.town.
And now this.
Dr. Synchronicity,
we can't blow the whole thing again.
Now last week we spent all of two hours
on the telly. And we're not going to get
on the telly until we thought maybe seven.
Prindle PR.
So that everybody can like, there were
a few people caught out in the cold without television
sets last week. And so we're giving you an hour's
notice at seven o'clock. It will
become really necessary for you to watch
Channel 11. Otherwise turn on
another radio show.
We'll even turn one on for you.
You can listen to something else. What's on at
seven o'clock on radio besides the
Fireside Theater radio hour?
They could go out to a movie.
You can see Gone with the Wind and
Gun of Heaven for 50 cents.
That's over on
Figueroa. You can now see Gone with the
Wind. That's because...
What happened? Yes, beautiful
Hawaii. Land
of violins. These
papayas grow six feet tall
and each of them plays the violin
from birth. That's beautiful.
Yes, they are enchanting, aren't they? Well, don't
worry. Those are great films,
Mr. Fosland.
Thank you. And
tell us a little bit about the people
of Hawaii. Well, here's our
sum now. These are your native
girls. They happen to be
yours. They couldn't be mine, of course.
That's a mustard plant,
Charlie. That's a
mustard plant. They grow over four feet high
and up.
You tell them about the little girl. It's amazing.
It's amazing. There they are, these little
children eat these mustard plants out there.
They work in the fields. Oh, must be hardy, but not hot.
Hardy, but not hot. They work in the
fields, these little children.
It's wonderful. It's orthogenic, too, you know.
Here comes a picture now
of...
That's Texas. That's Texas?
That's Texas. How did we get to... That's right.
I remember we flew back to Texas. The slide. Yes, it must have
been mixed up. Made a little mistake.
Oh, and there's Breaking Through
the Ice to Save Mr. Wilson
on the tour. That was on the
beautiful Tropical Sun tour that we took everyone
on last week.
Oh, and it rained. Yeah.
Yeah, it rained.
Before that, between
readings from the Dobbs.Town
Mirror, we heard news from
Leigh Murr, a clip from
Sandy Boone's movie about Bob
and the church, and by the way,
that was Nick Offerman,
not whatever I said
last time. Some
ESO Swamp Radio from WCSB
Cleveland with Chaz Smith and
Lonesome Cowboy Dave,
and some puzzling evidence show
from KPFA Berkeley with Dr.
Philodruman and Dr. Howell.
And puzzling evidence.
More of all of the above coming,
but now,
puzzling evidence from 2001.
Now, do you know where the hamburger
originated?
No.
It originated on the Russian steppes
where medieval tartars ate
raw meat scraped and
shredded with a dull knife and
seasoned with salt, pepper, and onion
juice. German sailors
picked up the delicacy at the
Baltic ports and took the recipe
back to their home base at Hamburg.
Finicky hamburgers, not
accustomed to eating their meat raw
like savages, took some of
the red out of the tartar steak by
broiling the outside.
Thus, the Hamburg steak
was born.
So even though the hamburgers
took credit for making it,
I guess technically since they applied
the heat process,
you know, I like to think about those
tartars out there scraping it with
a dull knife though.
Trying to figure out how to make steak
tartar but winding it up with a hamburger.
I just heard about steak tartar
like a few months ago.
Yeah? I had no idea that
people ate that. And did
you try some or? Oh no.
You would never, why, because of the sauce?
Because I wouldn't eat
raw meat. Yeah, that is a problem.
Me either. How about raw fish? Yes.
I don't even eat cooked
meat.
I will only eat raw fish
if they have
fins and scales.
I only eat nuts.
I'm a strict nutarian.
Like a breast-arian?
I eat seeds and nuts.
I'm kind of like a squirrel
in that sense.
I'm on a squirrel diet.
Does that work?
Yeah, it actually works
real well. It's sort of high in oil
but it keeps your weight down.
So you're not eating nuts?
No, otherwise. But you get lots
of energy?
Yeah, I'm a
bountiful
bastion of energy.
I'm a skyrocket of energy.
You can't push over.
You can tell right now.
Thank you, Doctors of the Air.
Coming up next is a song
by Reverend Morgan
Glutentag called
Hidden Track.
As he describes it,
quote,
I wrote a song for a hidden track
at the end of a CD,
but I didn't write the rest of the songs
and CDs seemingly aren't a thing anymore.
It ended up being
some sort of generic preaching
slash hobo warning.
That's
pretty subgeniously.
Hidden Track by
Morgan Glutentag.
They say you won't come back
if you take that hidden track.
Oh,
Hidden Track.
You'll pay a hefty fare.
Please, my friend,
take care. Oh,
Hidden Track.
Oh,
If you board that awful train,
you'll surely go insane.
Oh,
Hidden Track.
Dark things you must beware
when you ride those ghostly rails.
Oh,
Hidden Track.
There is no
dining car to speak of
even though
the passengers get fed.
If you
find it difficult
to slumber, you've made your
own bed.
Oh,
Hidden Track.
As we see as articulations within
three-dimensional means,
those things are bound by light
and by it. And so
such beings are bound by light's
limitations. And so
to occupy the space within
light would mean to operate without time.
The four-dimensional frame,
and so it operates solely in the now.
Unless these
beings can transcend their basic
frequencies and resonate in a
hyperspace plane.
Oh,
They say you won't come back
if you take that Hidden Track.
Oh,
Hidden Track.
You'll pay a hefty
fare. Please, my friend,
take care. Oh,
Hidden Track.
Oh,
Oh.
That laziness, I think, is very, very...
It's kind of provocative.
You know, slackers are attracted to that level of laziness.
Not that I'm a slacker.
What's that?
She's flossing just for you.
Well, I'm really just a slack abuser.
That's really nice.
I'm not a slacker per se.
It's just that when I find slack, I try to use it to its fullest extent.
I just want to tell her when she turns her suit toward the...
When you turn your suit toward the command center, the signal comes in better.
Yeah.
That's what it is.
You're lying on your back.
You should be on your side.
Then you can look out over the top of the cockpit and see the earth below us.
How do you guys know these things?
Because we're right up above you.
Yeah.
High above.
Berkeley.
Because we're on the internet, you know, and you can find anybody on the internet.
And folks, remember, we are going to find the end of the internet on this show.
To try to find the show?
She was looking for the end of the internet for four hours.
Imagine that.
She's up four hours of her life.
She'll never get back.
Oh, you were looking for the website that you can download the show from?
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
And now, friends, this.
This.
Onan's optimism rant.
The music in the background is by CyberChump from the CD called Their Moment of Perfect Happiness.
Dr. Onan Canterbite wrote this.
These are the end times.
One way or another, these are the end times.
For some, the end times mean...
It means an expiration of clean air, potable water, and a lack of food.
Or disease, decay, and death.
For some, the end times means the end of time.
A final triumph of time control as promised by J.R. Bob Dobbs.
The end times come to the pinks and the subgeniuses alike.
And sadly, in all forms.
But you're hearing my voice.
And therefore...
Well, these are...
Yay!
The end times!
Fate has not seen fit to end your time at this time.
No, you've got some suffering in you yet.
And that won't go to waste.
Jehovah One, alien space god, feeds on mortal suffering and seasons it with irony.
The same is true of all the elder gods and a few of the younger gods.
And there's no denying them their banquet.
The end times are the end times.
We pray they pray.
The conspiracy will tell you that there's no cause for optimism.
The conspiracy will tell you that optimism is expecting everything to turn out right.
Everything.
Every time.
And if everything doesn't turn out right every time, then optimism has failed.
Since optimism fails, one should stick with the success of failure.
Oh, the conspiracy is great at rewarding failure when it's your failure.
They don't like it so much when they fail.
They don't even like it when you notice that they can fail.
Gentle listener, you may be surprised to learn that the subgenius has a different perspective on the matter.
For one thing, optimism is not expecting everything to turn out right every time.
Optimism is when the subgenius is foolish and amoral enough to see all of life as one great sales opportunity.
Whatever happens, the market is opened to the sales representative willing to take it on the chin and come back with a grin.
Optimism is that infuriating, uncanny luck of Bob,
by which whatever happens is exactly what he wants.
He's not sure if he has what we would consider a memory or an understanding that future events will occur.
He just is.
Another thing is that even if we cannot quite ape the Dobbs nature,
we can frame optimism as the success of what we prefer to happen.
Not everything that happens, and for sure not what the conspiracy and frauds are,
is just a must happen.
When someone you don't like comes to a bad end,
or at least goes and bothers somebody else for a while,
that's hardly everything turning out right every time for them.
But for you, heck yeah!
Let those jerks get a taste of their own medicine for a change.
Not because it'll do them any good, but because it gives you slack.
So, you see, optimism is the evidence-based,
and the evidence-based response to these end times.
The whole planet is doomed.
If the ghost dinosaurs don't get you, the plastic in the placenta will.
If the oceans don't acidify you, the social media will sizzle your very soul.
This naturally and necessarily means that they who tamper your cause
will endure great agony and defeat.
Hooray!
Try to die last.
I'll say that again.
Try to die last, friend.
Or maybe just be glad for the simple pleasures when they come your way.
Keep a little spark lit to pass on to some other subgenius who's even more in the dark than you are.
Whether you believe all it takes is a little sprinkle,
or whether you believe it requires a full immersion,
you walk into that water and gain the gift of Bob-tism from your own hand.
By this sure means, ye shall know Bob-timism.
And thank you, Uncle Dr. Onan Canterbite,
for that optimistic, Bob-timistic, optimism.
Optimism.
Rant.
Be a gnat.
Oh.
And thank you for the music,
Zyberchunk.
They're all unsaved, you know, and unwashed.
The great unwashed are not so great.
Don't let those eyes roll back in the head of you.
And the unsaved are only great because we still haven't got their 30 bucks.
No frothing.
They're potentially great.
And no bleeding from the eyes.
But the pink can never be great.
The pink is like a blind, deaf snake crawling on the floor of a pitch black cave.
But old speedunker Bob, my friends, he's got a flashlight.
And he's got a bucket and a long, sharp gigging stick.
And soon enough, you will be searching for Dobbs on the scaly roof of your mouth, my friend.
It's not a scaly thing.
There's a man searching for Dobbs.
Does that stuff really work anymore?
Dobbs on the scaly roof face of another person's mouth.
All that fire and brimstone.
Does anyone believe anything anymore?
No, they believe more in soaps.
Except the midriff.
Soaps thrown on anthracite are the now common mediums for getting the message across.
I only honor the current marketing quirk.
What is the current marketing?
16-year-old midriff.
16-year-old midriff?
The halter top.
The teenage halter top.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's what's going on in all the test markets.
Yeah, it's fine with me.
Next it'll be the back of the knee.
That's fine too.
Yeah, but...
I'm telling you, from Columbus to Utah...
So you'll buy it as long as it's the body part.
I don't buy it.
No, he sells it.
You download it from the internet.
Like the great faucet of pornography.
Spewing and spewing.
He does not buy.
No, it's a cultural motivation.
Yeah, sure.
Well, my cultural icon would be perhaps to see...
I back him up.
To see, like...
Have you ever seen like a religious picture of the Virgin Mary?
Maybe hit me one more time.
Showing her midriff.
I wonder what kind of psychic image that would be.
I wonder what kind of impact that would have on people.
You're hitting him with two things at one time.
Your fist and your soft gloved foot.
You know what I mean?
You're kidding me.
Or the...
Yeah.
Well, no, I know what you mean.
I know what you mean.
You know what I mean.
I'm digging the...
Sneaking into the psyche, you know.
It's like being under the waterfall.
Yeah.
Only you're behind the waterfall.
Well, that's more zen.
You're not getting directly wet.
Yeah.
You're just sort of enjoying the spray coming from the...
Indirect wetness.
...flow.
Now, see, that should be the marketing ploy's...
Oh, yeah.
...name, indirect wetness.
I think people could understand that easily, especially what it has to do with zygotes,
killer sperms, perhaps that blue, blue mansion on the top of that green, green hill right
there where so many thousands of folks like you have gone before or walked through that
door, taken a nocturnal omission through the backyards, maybe smoked a little pie in the
oyster beds or...
Yeah.
...hung out by the farm waiting for dad to come back.
But no, he's never coming back.
But the dead must come back.
Sooner or later, heaven can't last forever.
Soon the dads will walk the earth again.
I'm sorry, son.
The dead will never walk the earth again unless, of course, someone with a very sharp little
brain like yours can figure out the proper sequence of the syllables.
It takes a lot of time.
We'll have to reanimate the flesh.
You can repeat after me, but it must be your reflection, not mine.
It must be your reflection, not mine.
Not that, no, no, no, no, no, the secret words.
Now, hold your hand over the top of your head so as not to let any omissions come out of
the top.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'll say it's a...
It's a rock and roll, baby.
...it was far sick.
Going to the rhythm.
Yeah, I swear.
Oh, he was about to say, oh, that's a great song.
I'm going to give the secret words and Chaz is sitting here looking at internet pornography.
Chaz, you've got a computer at home.
You can do this.
Can I sing a rock and roll?
You can make...
Oh, you can't listen to rock and roll and look at the internet pornography at the same
time.
Now, look what he's doing.
Look what came out of his ear.
His hairy, hairy ear.
Gross.
The bonobo sect will now come to order.
Oh, oh, before we forget, take a look at the secret words.
You're not supposed to get up on the console and do the same thing to the monitor.
Now I got this.
Bonobo, bonobo, bonobo, bonobo, bonobo, bonobo, bonobo.
See, he's saying it over and over again.
Bonobo, bonobo, bonobo.
Save it for the D Bible.
Save your spunk up for the D Bible at the Euclid Tavern on May 12th, my friend.
Save up that spunk.
Not that I practice what I...
You're a spunky punk.
All good listening moms and dads and childrens out there in listening land should be aware
of the sexual dangers of copycats.
I'm not going to do that.
Hey, speaking of sexual...
Stick to your own species.
Stay with your own species.
Nah, don't worry about it.
It's a good way of procreating the right species.
That's all I'm really doing it with monkeys.
Oh, better.
It's a metaphor, man.
Yeah, man.
I'm not going to do it to a monkey.
It's a metaphor, my man.
And now this from the Dobbs Ducktown Mirror.
Ideal preparation.
How can I play an instrument perfectly?
How can I write a popular book?
How can I meet my true love?
Two answers.
Luck or effort.
A, play more, write more, meet more people, including meeting people through those people.
If something doesn't work out, stop doing that and do something else that seems like
it might work or do anything else.
Just don't keep repeating what didn't work out.
Practice being more careful.
You're going to be more lucky too.
Say the words, I am lucky, aloud and often.
Or B, be instantly, completely lucky every time.
Praise Bob.
That's all from the Dobbs Ducktown Mirror.
The new issue, which is available from, well, actually we put it into every package we mail
out.
But you can write to.
Reverend Onan Kanabite.
Got your pencil ready?
Here's his P.O.
Box.
That's an easy one too.
P.O.
Box three.
That's right.
Onan.
P.O.
Box three.
Columbus, Indiana.
Not Columbus, Ohio.
47202.
And of course, you can always learn everything at.
Subgenius.com.
And for our prisoners who can't get on the internet and I don't know how they're hearing
this show at all except over broadcast radio, which happens in some cities.
You can just write to Subgenius Foundation and here's our address.
P.O.
Box 807.
Glen Rose, Texas.
That's it.
Subgenius.com.
76043.
Subgenius is spelled without an O. But P.O.
Box has an O. And 807 really means 807.
Box 807.
Glen Rose, Texas.
76043.
Subgenius.com.
Buy only Subgenius goods and services.
Such as the Hour of Slack.
The Puzzling Evidence Show.
Bob's Slack Time Fun House from Reverend Susie the Flusie.
Philo Drummond's Subgenius Network on OSI74.com on TV.
Dovestown.org for everything about the movie about the Church of the Subgenius.
Ask Dr. Howell at gonzotronics.com.
Slash ADH.
Freethink Radio.
National Cynical Network.com.
Time for the Show.com.
Subgenius.com.
Dobbs.town.
And on the internet, always be speaking of J.R. Bob Dobbs.
Praise Bob and thank you all.