Remember.
Alumni難 reiterate
We're sitting together
listening to this.
This is great.
Listening to them listening to them
Remember.
We're all sitting together.
We're sitting together.
Listening to this.
This is crazy.
Remember.
Remember
This is pleasing.
Remember.
Remember, we're sitting together listening to this.
This is pleasing to...
And this was pleasing to God.
To God.
What time is it, Tevis?
It's Bob time.
Time for the hour of slack.
Tevis, you know that you're not supposed to be watching the hour of slack
because it's too weird for you.
Uh-uh.
Oh, yeah, I'll prove it.
Right, Daddy.
Huh? What?
Right, she's not supposed to see the hour of slack.
Oh, Tevis is just as weird as the hour of slack, aren't you, Tev?
Yeah.
Hey.
Mr. Smith is a good white man.
A good white man.
Mr. Smith is our friend and father.
Mr. Smith.
The lid's off.
It's gonna be louder beyond Ontario than it's gonna be here.
Those sounds...
Sarah, beware.
Now, we are ready to begin the story,
Invasion of...
Gal Island.
Ben!
Get up off that chair!
Follow me!
Ready?
Go!
The subgenius hour of slack!
I have reordered time.
I have turned the world upside down,
and I have done it all for you.
It's a wildfire.
I see people all around me changing faces.
I'm doing things that haven't got a name yet.
Come with me now,
as together,
we relive a dangerous adventure in our planet's history.
Mark the tale well,
and take heed.
There is much to learn.
Our planets are alike in many ways.
What happened to us could happen to you.
Listen well, children of Earth.
And all Ç Blend with Single That.
Beyond breaking the law,
come on, let's build the absolute course come together.
of Confment Art thereof.
So bring the crimson professional from others and
Molineun title,
pueider,
rente...
Se광ARD.
Batha.
guitar solo
It's a wild, wild time
And I say it now all the time
I'm here for you any old time
Oh, lady, lady
Make a friend for yourself here
Bob is all around you
Bob is beneath your feet even now
Bob is ramping over your head even now
When you reach out your hand, it is Bob's hand that reaches
When you smoke that pipe, it is Bob that smokes through you
We are all a part of Bob, and we hate it
We can't wait to kill him for the last time
On the entrance ramp to the saucers
We shall slick it with his blood and grease it with his fat
And go sliding into paradise
Praise Bob
All around me are changes
It's a wild, wild time
The original words are still true
A useless object made useful
With end
The world ends this July
They die
There is one thing that puzzled me about this
When a spectator pushed the button
He electric bell did not ring
That makes it a work of art
And that makes my heart beat hard
What I always wanted to be accepted, not understood.
But there was one, but there was one thing that hustled me about it.
Smith is taking a swag.
We love you, dear friends.
Hey, that new church air is just great.
Hundreds of New Yorkers at a religious revival chanting the name of a modern-day prophet, Bob.
Bob's teachings are the foundation of a church that is so important to us.
It's a church that does little more than parody cults and American consumerism.
It's called the Church of the Subgenius.
Tom Vitale has this report.
You will pay to know what you really think.
But if you give us money, we will tell you what to think.
And not only have you paid to know what you really think,
but once you will get value for your dollar.
Americans will buy anything, and they're getting sold short.
That's the message.
That's the message of the Church of the Subgenius.
They have a very perverted view.
You know, we're just animals.
The Darwin theory, you know, we're just animals.
If you're involved in bestiality, that is okay.
It doesn't mean you're a monster.
Just don't tell anybody.
Or you're going to be ridiculed.
What's it seem to a dog?
Too hot, too hot.
To kill, to kill.
Star, star.
To wrap, to wrap.
This mission is too important.
I'm about to jeopardize it.
I don't know what you're talking about, Hal.
The marvelous show today, folks.
Our very special guest is loved and admired the world over
as a fine performer and a great humanitarian.
Please welcome one of America's oldest and most respected kids,
Ivan Stang.
Besides balancing with Mike.
Senator, do you care to cross-examine now?
Yes, I'd like to cross-examine him now.
Mr. Stang here.
When you sold these hydrogen devices,
I did my right.
The Malesians, were you aware that that was a taxpayers' property?
Listen, those Malesians are fighting against freedom
every bit as hard as the Church of the Subgenius.
And on top of that, these people can't be expected to protect
the Dobstown investment out there in the jungles
from the nearby hostile, fiendishly clever savages.
You must refer to the ucabalaponga.
Yes.
Okay, fiend.
they are. Very popular with this order.
They hate
the word mob.
Where's the missing money?
Well, you see, these freedom fighters, or
uka balapongas, ukas as we call them,
have used it all up.
They've fought freedom all over the world, and
that's not a cheap
prospect you're looking at there.
Now, I offer this document
in evidence, an
article from the Arizona Daily Star
entitled, You Could Lose Your Blues at
that Toddlin' Tucson Bar that's known as
Bob Dobbs.
It appears that this bar, which
has taken the name of Bob Dobbs, is
an utter warren of normals and
pinks of the worst stripe who talk about
sports and wear bill caps
and drink beer. What do you have to say about
this obvious betrayal of
the trust of your many followers?
Look, Bob gets a penny for every time his
face is Xeroxed, and he doesn't care
whether that Xerox ends up
on the wing of a Russian fighter
or if it's on a
nice old granny's
wheelchair.
That's right.
But. Or. And.
And it is a big but.
No ifs about it.
I mean, look,
you can't run a church
on air. This is
a world outreach. We're fighting poverty
and free thought everywhere
all over the world. So you feel justified
as a private citizen into
pushing your particular line?
Well, the, uh... Is that
what I'm...
You want him to understand?
As Bob said, the ends always
justif... more than justify the means
in every situation. And too much
is always better than not enough.
And if, uh, if you want to step on my...
I have... I've read the Constitution.
I know what the... what the rights
of religious subgeniuses are.
If we want to sell what you call
nuclear weapons, these are stage
props for us, uh,
to small, uh, countries.
And, uh, that is our prerogative.
Get left here and don't leave!
Nobody's gonna have a break!
Bob preaches that you have to believe
in everything, and especially,
um, you have to believe in
the... the God that tells you not to believe in him
because he doesn't want you to know
what he's been doing to you.
He wants me to take you to him.
Drink down the fluid now,
and even then you'll go to the next stage.
... phase two.
For the Honky and Jimmy show,
please return to the regular channel version
enclosed in the network box.
I'm gonna blow my head off.
You're not going to.
You're not the kind.
Uh, we better back off here
and, uh, think about Jim and you.
This would have been something
totally unpracticed.
Pretty much on the, uh,
on the cutting edge of, uh,
of a risky operation, to say the least.
Coming in on a wing and a prayer.
Oh, there's one more gone.
We can still carry on.
Coming in on a wing and a prayer.
I would love to believe that there was a God
who made us, who's looking out for us.
And loves us.
And takes care of us.
And...
And guides us.
And teaches us.
And because we're in such a mess,
we're doing things that are wrong.
Then we would be relieved of the responsibility
of taking care of ourselves.
And a voice would come from up above and say...
Build your own ships.
The cosmos.
Countless worlds upon worlds.
Worlds without end.
In these galaxies,
every possible reality exists.
And what is reality on any one world
is mere fantasy on all others.
Here, all is real
and all is illusion.
What is, what was,
and what will be,
start here with the words...
Bob?
The message is now part of and registered
in your subconscious mind.
Stop.
The blank of the healing earth.
So the healing earth will...
will heal now.
Well, I guess, Chaz,
you may have been right all along.
We may have to...
We...
I don't think we have to build our own ships.
We may have to build our own ships.
But we should go ahead and start.
Yeah.
Maybe draw a plan for our...
At least it'll give us a goal,
you know, something to do before we,
you know, hit.
I'll be working on my plan
for years.
Now, Nostradamus said that...
that X-Day would happen on July 5th
at 7 a.m., 1999.
I don't know if you were aware of that.
Yeah.
Edgar Cayce agreed with Dobbs
that it was 98,
but Nostradamus has been saying
it was that date on 1999
for a long time now.
So the Dos Equis next year...
Oh, give me one of them.
...may very well be...
Coldwell, please.
But if they do not arrive on Dobs,
then on Triple X Day.
The triple X Day.
The sex goddesses will be even sexier.
The year zero.
But what happens if they arrive
in the century?
What happens if they arrive
in Tecate or...
Oh, sweet Mary, child of confusion,
she runs the hills to cry.
Has the willows or an illusion?
Oh, tell me the reason why.
Tell me why, why's it all so hard?
Breathing in the air
Be one to him
Yeah!
Yes, dear friends.
Dear, dear.
Dear friends, where am I?
Where am I?
What?
In the background here, believe it or not,
Janice Joplin with Big Brother and the Holden Company.
Oh, sweet Mary.
From back in the day, friends.
That's what they used to mean by the day.
Just for some reason it seemed appropriate.
And, yeah.
And what have we been listening to, dear friends?
Wake up, Stan.
Oh, God.
Friends, I'm doing this one late.
Late at night, but I'm struggling on.
From the top, a little bit of Silica Joe, because we remember.
And I'm running some old tapes from Hour of Slack number 79 and 80.
The music you're hearing in the background is Einstein's Secret Orchestra live at the X-Day Space Jam.
You heard Bob is All Around You.
That was Friday Jones with Jefferson Airplane.
And Bleepo Abernathy's Subjection.
Genius Collage.
A lot of Media Barrage.
And then a little bit of NPR Radio, Ancient Subgenius Report.
Bits from the old Media Barrage 10.
Volume 6 and Volume 7 clips from Chaz Smith's Einstein's Secret Orchestra Slack Chats.
And KPFA, Berkeley, with Dr. Howell and Puzzling Evidence.
And in this case, Palmer Freedies in the Stang Scam Investigations on the Senate floor.
Old Media Barrage stuff.
And Galaxies and Galaxies.
G. Gordon Gordon.
And the Endlessness of the...
And friends!
Yes, dear friends, because you know something as next day draws ever closer.
I find myself not knowing sometimes whether I'm talking to you, listening by radio,
or typing to the internet subgenii on alt.slack,
or torturing the little fuzzy...
or the genius bunnies in the animal outreach where we communicate via animal testing,
or try to, friends.
About one out of every hundred bunnies manages to actually vocalize the phrase,
Praise Bob!
Or a scream that sounds very similar to that phrase.
Friends, this church is so multimedia, I sometimes get confused whether I'm shouting to rows of parishioners
in the pews of a nightclub,
stinking of beer,
or if I'm just ensconced on my...
throne of extra meditation,
and simply imagining that I'm at a devival.
A high-paying devival.
And there's one coming up, friends.
A devival!
At Euclid Cavern in Cleveland,
on Euclid Avenue in Cleveland,
November 8th, Sunday,
Sunday, Einstein's Secret Orchestra,
myself and who knows what all else,
and I just got back from a thing in Denver,
at the most oddball of cons,
the Death Equinox 98 convergence of weirdos,
uh,
it kind of reminded me of the Phenomicon in Atlanta,
because it was kind of like a science fiction convention,
except that instead of S-F, it was S and M,
and some of what they were talking about was real,
while seeming kind of like science fiction,
you know, conspiracies, mass murder, and sadomasochistic bondage and discipline.
I had never been friends to a party where people sat around poking fine needles into their flesh,
in neat little rows, and...
and designed for yucks and grins!
This is what they do for fun, friends.
And, uh, that was just the afternoon, after-hours parties.
You should have seen the seminars on that stuff.
I had a great time, met a whole new tribe of mutants I had not been aware of,
the Cyberpsychos of Colorado,
and this will benefit all mutantdom,
as it does whenever new, broken, and self-invented genes are added to the admixture in the VAT!
Friends, this convention was so cool,
they had a panel on prairie squid,
and a religion of jellyfish, and, uh,
friends, but of especial interest to the Hour of Slack listeners,
we discovered a great, simply fantabulbous musical combo,
called Little Theodore and Babushka,
this is the lightest bastard child of Devoe, you might say, friends,
in league with Negative Land, in fact, they toured with Negative Land,
or Duke of Uke, or the Swingin' Love Corpses,
or so many other great purveyors of spaz, spaz nerd jazz rock,
like all those bizarro bands that open up for us on our tours.
Um, spaz music of macho irony, dear friends, um, I suppose you could call it,
and what really struck me was that this little Theodore guy,
this singer, who I'll be playing very soon here,
dresses exactly like Jayner Hyperclete's Goodwill, uh, Loud style,
and kind of looks like,
lonesome cowboy Dave crossed with me,
crossed with Larry Fine of the Three Stooges,
and I, I just wish you could see the videotapes of this band,
these people spaz out better than any spaz dancers I've ever seen,
the lyrics are among the most simultaneously gut-wrenchingly funny and horrific,
that, um, and, uh, friends, they will be your instant heroes,
um, uh, and, uh, I've recorded portions of their live concert,
and I also got their CD, and I think you'll be able to tell which is which,
this is, um, friends, stay tuned here for,
Dropout ESO,
Little Theodore,
and Babushka.
.
I'm not ejingo
Get out of my head
Meow, meow, meow, meow
Sometimes you feel like 9
You can dance out in the ground
My, my
Get out of my head
Even swords they like
Drinking, drinking, drowsing, copulating, squabbling over nothing.
We may divert our attention from the inevitable for a little while,
but let's be so that right away to transcend this curse of being human,
which is highly, very unlikely, and clearly, painfully obvious
that we're all doomed! All doomed! All doomed!
All doomed! All doomed!
Who is that?
Who
Thanks, babe.
I make people like me then I turn away.
I make people hate me then I get in their way.
I'm always making jokes when there's business at hand.
Then I rope around at parties and a tennis I bet.
Thanks, babe.
Who needs me?
I never really care when people got nerves.
And I don't know what to say when they tell me their flares.
I'm only in the way when there's important stuff to say.
But people never ask me favors because I'm luckier than you.
Who needs me?
I don't have good advice on what movies you should see.
And I don't have favorite actors.
They're all millionaires to me.
I never dress correctly when it's time to go out.
So just leave me here at home.
Let me decide what life's about.
Who needs me?
I'm qualified!
You give me heart on
You make me grow
You make me imagine
All that I know
You make my blood run
You make me howl
You make my thoughts turn
A ringing sound
You make me chill
You make me die
You open me up
And you watch me die
You give me heart on
You make me cry
I watch the day out
Falling in cry
You make me go in
You make me fall
You make me started
That's a good call
That's a rhythm
To my pipe
Because I'm ready
You got a type
You sound flavour
That I need it
I know what you do
I think you try
You see the day
I hope it's true
When the sun goes down
All my exactly
Because this is true
Love
I don't know what to do.
I've been turned round in circles
7 sunny days before.
I lift my ten-toed steps in a row
I'm walking through the wall.
I don't know what to do.
I don't know what to do!
Little Theodore will be right back.
I just sit here watching squirrels.
They have much more fun than me.
Sometimes they run around all day in circles.
They fight and squabble then they lick their wounds.
At least they seem to have a purpose.
My mind's always clogged with leaves.
Like silly stupid advertising jingles.
And themes from TV shows I do not like.
I must not go out the front door.
I could get hit by a car.
Just like the squirrels when a dog is growling.
There's perfect safety high up in the tree.
I know I'm bad to just sit here.
I should not be so scared.
I'm so afraid.
But once outside I'd have to choose a direction.
It might be the wrong one so I'll stay here.
They tell me of self improvement.
And someday I could even have a job.
Then I would have become just like the squirrels.
I don't see how I could accomplish that.
First I'd have to choose a direction.
Like which tree I should start to climb.
They all seem to be up to the challenge.
I just take whatever's given me.
I'm not a crazy person.
So I'm OK here just watching squirrels.
Though the soundtrack could be much improved.
Those silly stupid advertising jingles.
And themes from TV shows I do not like.
Wa wa wa wa wa wa wa la.
Thank you.
And dear friends, we're speaking here from the Subgenius Foundation.
Post Office Box 1403-06, Dallas, Texas 75214.
Order today.
Imagine that.
Around that time period, around the Civil War in America,
the best that the military had to offer were cannons.
Now, cannons could kill a handful of people
if you hit them.
Hit it right in the crowd.
And that was the best of the technology
just a little over 100 years ago.
Then, then, we take the next step up.
What's that?
World War I, we had bigger bombs.
We had bombs that could kill people in a whole building.
And in World War II, we had blockbusters.
And blockbusters could destroy a whole city block, man.
And then after World War II, we developed the atom bomb, man.
During World War II, we killed people.
Hey, we could kill a whole city with one bomb.
And then we went to thermonuclear bombs
where you can wipe out the whole seaboard with one bomb.
And then we learned how to make individual bombs for individual people.
That's right.
Everyone will be born with a bomb attached to the brain stem.
Each fission fusion device is fully licensed and guaranteed
and may only be used once.
Once by the previous owner.
And there'll be no fighting in the battlefield.
You just go run out into the field
and the computer will decide if your head gets blown off or not.
Or if its head gets blown off.
It's all statistical.
That's the future.
That's the future of the war machine.
That's the future of the capitalist war machine.
Bomb, man. Bomb.
We must turn away people.
We must.
I feel like one little solitary teardrop
landed in my lap and now a whole river of tears
Let me wipe that teardrop away
with this baseball bat.
I'm drenched in sweat.
And as Alice swam.
Pazuzu's coming in the back door.
I can smell it.
Alice swam up behind her.
Hickling her.
That's what you said.
Nuzzling her underneath her pretty little frilly dress.
No, no, no, no.
With her little animal noses.
Making her giggle and shiver in the water.
Yes.
Alice enjoyed the feeling.
Oh, wait.
Now that was the other Alice in Wonderland.
I'm sorry.
What did you say?
Connie in Wonderland.
Connie and Bob.
Bob, not.
Bonnie in Wonderland.
Bob and Connie and Ted and Alice.
Yeah.
They were going.
I love that 60s porno, you know, Lewis Carroll thing.
And Peter.
Yeah, five people in a bed.
Yeah.
Each of like, you know, really strange looking people
with huge handlebar mustaches.
And like large, large ears.
Which was the most erotic part to me, baby.
I'll tell you.
Right, right.
And the men also had enormous breasts in those movies.
I mean, could you beat something like that, man,
if you wanted to with a stick or, you know?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, they don't make them like that anymore.
No, they don't make guys like that anymore.
You know what I mean?
They never made them like that.
Oh, come on, man.
Anymore.
Don't.
Tell me you've never tried a delicious young voluptuous.
They only make them like that in the future.
The future past.
You have to cast yourself up to it.
Oh, we have to the future past?
Yes, the future past.
It's kind of like Sunday page.
I got one.
It's fun streaming here.
I got him.
It's like fishing for squid, it is.
Oh, boy.
Hey, look at that.
I got a live one.
I've never heard of a live one.
Which future is this?
I can't identify it.
Quick, look in the future book.
It looks like it's the future.
Man, you're going too slow, man.
Watch it.
The wires are going to break.
You can't hit the future books.
You got to go.
Make sure you don't break the wiring there.
It's very tender stuff.
They don't use a lot of solder.
They don't use any of the pictures, though.
Oh, spin them around.
Oh, there.
There.
It looks kind of like that one there.
Yes.
Okay, now that looks like I can make that out almost.
It's yellow.
Why is it yellow?
Is it supposed to be yellow?
Yeah, in the picture, it's red.
That means it's infected.
Why is that?
You have to go get a shot.
Am I seeing the wrong thing or right or what?
But it's breathing normally.
I don't think it's infected.
I think it's just another species.
Mine's breathing real fast.
Are we seeing the same thing?
Mine's like yellow when it's breathing.
Well, your future is slightly different from my future because, you know, you're over there
and I'm over here.
So you're all red, but you're breathing normally.
I'm yellow, but I'm breathing fast.
Right.
So like over here, if a butterfly flaps its wings in Brazil, it affects us.
Over where you are, like a bird has to flap its wings in Brazil to affect you.
Oh, man.
Talk about your dimensional variances, boy.
We just, well, okay, now at least we've got something that has a color.
And it's vibrating and it's also breathing at a certain rate.
What mine right now, it looks like it's very frustrated.
It's trying to get out of the box I got it in.
I like the glimmery part.
Mm, yeah.
So you don't get that in the food that you get here.
Look at it glimmer.
Mm.
Oh, it's beautiful.
Oh, it is.
Oh, guys.
It's like a star within a star.
Oh, it's the prettiest thing I ever saw.
My leg's getting wet.
It's like, it's beautiful like wood, but it wants to make me cry.
It's lighting up from inside.
Oh.
A curious, green, glowing light.
It's the prettiest thing I've ever seen.
Go into it, man.
Okay.
Little, little, little.
Step in.
Sunglasses are going around my leg.
Let's go.
Come on, guys.
Wait a minute.
I don't, I'm not.
Oh, it's wonderful inside of here.
This is the best thing that's ever happened.
It's wonderful.
I'm like one of the president people.
I'm going through a crisis right now.
I don't ever want to go back.
Come on, Dave.
It's too late.
I missed it.
Let go of the negativity, baby.
Damn.
It was a groovy scene where it's at.
You can still see it?
Oh, yeah.
Oh, man.
I'm just getting glimmers.
Wait a minute.
Now it looks like a stupid silver ball.
It's shimmering and glimmering more better than ever.
It's coming back.
No, wait.
Oh, yes.
It's coming back.
And it is.
It's everyone's future.
Oh, wow.
It's everyone's past.
It's the whole future of the human race.
And they didn't tell us this was going to happen.
It's all the love and all the hate of the whole human race.
Hey, you guys.
Oh, and everybody's caught up with everyone else.
Look at that.
Yes, and love is reigning supreme.
People are walking around holding each other's hands.
And they're getting slapped.
Wait.
Oh, and they're sucking on each other's feet.
Look at that.
Oh, my God.
What's happening?
Oh, it's wonderful.
Oh, and it feels so good.
Look at that.
It's like we're going underwater.
We're going under the ocean.
Oh, man.
Wow, look at that.
They're all turning into the ocean.
Look at the dolphins.
Their brains are getting bigger.
Their heads are getting bigger.
They're all dolphins.
They don't have to breathe underwater.
Look at them.
Oh, my God.
They're so happy.
Their skin is golden.
Oh, sweet baby.
And it's silver.
And it's all the colors.
It's rose.
It's orange.
It's creamy, peachy pink.
I'm digging, man.
I'm digging it.
Oh, my other leg's wet now.
Oh.
Yummy Etruscan brown.
Oh, Etruscan brown.
Oh, I just want to stay here for a while.
We're time traveling.
We don't have to leave, do we?
I mean, it's only cool in the third century B.C.
I'm melting.
And they're putting Scythian hemperonis on my forehead.
I don't care if there's hair around it.
Come on.
Let's keep going in.
Uh-huh.
Let's go.
Hey, wait a minute.
It's not really hair, is it?
It's...
Come on.
Farther up and further in.
I think we're missing that spot.
We were going to stop.
Farther up and further in.
Don't be afraid.
I'm not afraid.
They're like candy sets.
That's just the naysayers trying to take away the candy that you deserve.
That's right.
I'm a zygote, and I'm proud.
I'm a circuit fish.
I'm a little baby elephant with wheels on it.
I'm going.
I'm coming.
I...
Go with it, Dave.
Come with it, Dave.
You're a circle of matches and sparklers, Dave.
Don't worry.
I'm coming with you.
You'll become anything you want.
All you have to do is think about it, Dave.
Think.
Just think.
If you want to be a little kitty cat playing with a ball of string, that's you, Dave.
I'm a little kitty cat playing with a thermonuclear device.
Yeah.
It's so small.
If that's what you want, yes.
Push the button, Dave.
Push the button.
And there's just a world of beautiful people and a voice telling me to push the button,
and I'm the only one who...
My brain's not getting big as fast as the others, and they're making fun of me, and
they go swimming without breathing every day, and their skin turns golden silver, and I...
My skin turns green sometimes, and sometimes...
Don't worry, Dave.
They're not making fun of you.
No.
They're making fun about you.
They're not laughing at me.
They're laughing near me.
Yes.
No.
I'm going to pull the trigger.
I don't like this dream.
They're laughing near me.
Go ahead, Dave.
Pull the trigger.
They're laughing about me.
Only something soft will happen to you if you pull that hard, hard trigger.
And you said it, Skyrope.
My thumb went right through the trigger, and now I don't want to blow it up anymore.
Exactly.
That was our point.
That's why we gave it to you.
We gave it to you.
It's perfect.
In its own little hermetically-sneeled tube.
It's...
It's wonderful.
Princess?
It's more than perfect, Dave.
Show Dave what's in the box.
It's the ecstasy of...
Here, Dave.
It's the ecstasy of the void.
Ecstasy of the void.
For you.
The void calling me back.
That's right.
Just for you.
When nobody's got heads, they can still talk to you somehow, and sometimes when they point
at you, it looks like blue lightning's coming out of their fingers.
But it's...
It's the same as the fairy light that was around the little blue fairy in Pinocchio.
Exactly.
Right.
Or the luminous beings.
It's exactly the same luminescence.
Yeah, the luminous beings.
A luminous blue leviathan really deep.
You remember the luminous beings out in Arizona when you were there, don't you?
Oh, yes.
Yes, indeed.
I remember the little triangles that were so dense.
They were eggs.
They would fly by in the air.
Eggs of luminosity with spirals of string coming off of them.
Glowing in a million colors.
In all direction.
And the egg was you.
I was a glowing egg.
Was a glowing egg?
I wanted to be something nice, a dream, maybe.
Maybe even a glazed doughnut, but an egg?
You wanted me to be an egg?
The egg with the glimmering light.
It's just a temporary assignment.
I'm sorry.
Take it.
Drink down the fluid now.
I need an advance.
Then you'll go to the next stage.
Phase two.
Start of phase two.
For the Hunky and Jimmy show, please return to the regular channel version enclosed in
the network box.
Let's glad that's over with.
I wish I hadn't shed it.
I don't think I did, though.
Wait a second, Hunky.
This music's the same as the other show.
Hey, hey, man.
Watch out.
I'm gonna watch one of them, you know, them nice British junkie monkey stories and get
you dated for little kids and stuff.
Woo!
Mosquito then sent a mental message to Toxid, since sector warriors can communicate
without words to their telebonded insectoid companions.
Toxid, you revolting genetic accident, take your smelly shell elsewhere.
See you, General Spybrax.
Ha ha ha.
See how well he obeys me.
He's loyal.
Stupid, but loyal.
A trait you will never share, mosquito.
But, little listeners, you may ask, is there hope?
Listen, you little listeners whistling in the glistening mists.
Listen to these inspirational words from the Book of Lies, Chapter 10, Bankruptcy, Verse
than Ever.
The passage runs, and I quote.
If you be tired or depressed, if you've got that rundown feeling, remember, you're not
just anybody.
You're special.
You are living proof that you are the best.
God does not exist.
Yes, you, little listener, if you are like most of the people who listen to this show,
are proof that no supreme being could ever exist.
Well, I guess I don't have to tell you everything you know about the revolution is wrong.
You know that now.
But did you know that Indians can be in two places at once?
That they can change into animals?
That they invented the wire recorder?
Well, I've seen it.
I've heard it.
Now listen to this.
The idea is not to be funny here.
Okay.
The idea is to give you some clues as to what's happening in general.
Thank you very much.
Okay, bye-bye.
Okay, bye.
This is actually the only way to escape this show.
He's listening to it.
I know.
Yeah.
Oh, wake up.
Something may happen, Harry.
Tell him to wake up.
This one's not very reliable because there are no definite rules.
Why are the subgenius...
That is the subgenius.
I'm going to get my mind together.
Does it hurt to listen to this show?
No, it doesn't.
Okay, here we go.
Should be watching all over this right now.
That's right.
The show should be laughing at your feet right now and just kind of licking at your
thighs.
Oh, it's so lovely.
Reverend Stang, I hate those bobbies just as much as you do.
You are listening to the testimony of the Reverend Ivan Stang of the Church of the Subgenius.
Reverend Stang stands accused of selling high-quality products to the poor.
I think it's the hydrogen weapons to the Malaysians.
I thought it was hydrogen peroxide, Senator.
Wasn't it hydrogen peroxide?
Hydrogen peroxide weapons.
That's right.
The giant foam bomb.
And it was found in the backseat of his Lincoln Continental, wasn't it?
That's right.
With the Malaysian...
Shredded body of the Malaysian secretary.
Yes.
Late...
And who was this?
The Malaysian secretary in disguise.
Well, you can see him down there sweating now.
I think it's...
Or...
It is the Malaysian secretary.
He's getting hot.
He looks a little nervous.
There it is.
He seems a little upset.
He's removed his tie.
He's standing on top of the table now and ranting.
Don't you want to be treated the way you are?
Twenty-five lawyers are trying to counsel him to get back down.
He's putting up a good fight, though, and there goes...
It's true.
Look at him.
The senator from Hawaii now is...
Throwing his books up at the council.
Yes.
He's mooting.
He's mooting the Reverend.
The Reverend from Hawaii.
Please don't judge me too harshly, Bob.
But...
I was getting hot.
Look at that...
I won't bother anybody for you.
It's all in good fun here at the Senate hearings.
We're going to have to scrub the skin off this boy.
Reverend Stang, can you remember back on last November 25th, your meeting with Dr. Drummond
and the president?
Could you please tell us what you were talking about?
Well, to begin with, the famous six subgenius girls that the press keeps...
I'm sorry.
...stepping on, that was...
They were secretaries.
And they were very valued members of the church.
I mean, they were helping us make decisions on these things.
They know more about it than we do in some cases.
So...
And the president, I mean, he wants advice, and we're all too happy to try to give it.
He can't...
Even someone in the position of Ronald Reagan can't just call up J.R. Bob Dobbs anytime
he wants to.
So...
Well, what exactly did you tell the president?
Well, look, I told him that I was going to call him.
I told him that the transcripts are available for $1 from P.O.
Box 14306, Allen, Texas, 75214, and anyone can read them.
We're not trying to hide anything.
So visit your local Junior Bob affiliate and do it now.
Thank you for that message, Reverend Howell.
Now I'm going to turn you to Washington, D.C., and the current hearings in Stangscan.
Now in progress.
Stangscan, it figures.
And poor, poor Tammy's left arm.
Left at home.
Also known as...
No one...
...sometimes...
...in the 32nd hour of the 127th...
This kind of love has its own rewards.
It does have considerable rewards.
Not that something I'd want to talk about on the radio with the new FCC rulings happening
the way they are.
I mean, now that we have to stretch an hour of slack out to an hour and a half, I don't
know.
It's such...
How can you expect us not to need money to keep this ministry going?
Satisfaction.
Self-worth.
There are little Malaysian children out there who could be supportive.
We could be giving them hot lunches in the home for slackless children, and yet you expect
me to spend it all on lawyers.
They're ready to go out to slaughterhouse 301.
Slack.
There.
Special classes.
Slack.
Look, I don't care what your reporters think.
I wasn't doing anything in that parked car with the...
Reverend Ann.
Except, uh, uh, discussing church.
Oh, do we need to do that again?
Okay.
But it would be wrong.
Uh, that's the, uh, clapper loader, uh, the best boy in the dolly grip who's just, uh,
there on strike.
I'm sorry to tell you that, Mr. Stang, but, uh, they say that this production can't move
on until their demands are satisfied.
Well, uh, let's go on with the press conference.
Uh, I...
We were just discussing church business, but obviously, uh...
What about monkey business, Mr. Stang?
What about that little blonde we've...
No, you're not going to do that.
You've been squiring routes.
Now, Reverend Ann is a, is a, is a devoted, uh, student of Bob and, and Connie.
Uh, she's a, she's a Connie-ite.
Where was Connie while all this was going on?
Just because she's not part of the Orthodox Stangian People's Covenant denomination of
Dobbs Yeti resurrected, uh, that doesn't mean I won't let her work for the church.
And that's all she was doing in the back seat of the car with me, uh, up by the barn.
No further questions.
Outside of the radio station.
And, uh, and, and it...
I'm sorry.
I don't know.
Nobody knows.
Go ahead.
Let, uh, let, let Jerry Falwell take over the church of the subgenius.
That's fine with me.
But you see, that would be rather difficult since they're now a mixture of Pentecostals
and Baptists, and we are, uh...
Are a hideous amalgam of, of cultish, gibbledy-gook nonsense, uh...
Here, here now.
Let's not backslide.
Uh, fight the good fight.
Oh, I, I quit.
I've had enough.
If I'm not...
I'm not allowed to, uh, to brag about my, uh, extramarital affairs...
...that I performed for the church...
Even though that wasn't actually...
What?
Uh, uh, six, six, six, six, six.
It's going.
Amen.
Recording.
Everything's going fine.
No...
So, we're at France.
Four.
Everything's fine.
He is, simply speaking, the world's greatest salesman.
And as far as I'm concerned, this is a trade-off between the two.
held that distinction every year for over a decade. He is the head of the
Subgenius Foundation Incorporated, an organization that markets its own unique
system of sales training aids. He has been nominated for the Horatio Alger
Award for his outstanding rise from poverty to the top in the business world.
And Simon & Schuster Publishers will publish his new book entitled The Book of
the Subgenius.
What I do with my spare time and off hours, I mean a preacher is a human being too.
I can't be expected to stand there at that pulpit 24 hours a day.
I'm sorry, you have to be expected to be in the public eye, constantly scrutinized.
That's fine, but I don't think I should be docked all that pay just because of one dream.
Now Mr. Stang...
Mr. Stang, could you please turn to page 27 in the, uh, in your budget here?
That's the revised standard version.
Now, this is all in code, is it not?
Self-esteem?
Well, uh, it depends on what you call code.
So when it refers here to He-Man, that's actually you, correct?
No, uh, He-Man is the senator from West Virginia, as a matter of fact.
Oh, I don't expect you to believe that.
Are you sure you're on the same page here?
Oh, okay, right, I've got it.
Okay.
27, go ahead.
There's some here of $60 million.
Where was that supposed to be delivered to?
Uh, well, uh, let me consult with, uh, my lawyer.
That, you know, I can't be expected to remember every tiny little detail.
Mr. Stang, are you familiar, are you familiar with the Drummond Amendment, sir?
Yes, sir.
Just a moment, yours.
Senator, my client wishes to read a statement into the record at this point.
Uh, very well.
I did not and will not ever, uh, admit the specific dream sequence that these Dream Monitor reporters have recorded of, uh, this, uh, alleged encounter, uh, uh, which I assure you is absolutely unsexual in nature between, uh, Reverend Mandy, Reverend Ann, and myself.
Uh, this is...
Just answer the question.
I'm answering the question.
Are you now or have you ever been a member of the human race?
No, I can, I can, uh, absolutely deny, uh, categorically deny.
Well, I've got some...
Well, my mother's got a, got a, got an extra tailbone back there and, and my brother has a supernumerary nipple.
I have proof that the nipple...
We have the nipple and the cockaxe on display and it's a good piece.
No, no one is, uh, completely informed of human...
I don't, I don't know.
Just...
...degenerate genes except perhaps our Yeti cousins in the Himalayas.
In the Himalayas, I mean, so...
And so you see, that's what Mr. Stang testified and that's what made him America's sweetheart.
We have a marvelous show today, folks.
Our very special guest is loved and admired the world over as a fine performer and a great humanitarian.
Please welcome one of America's oldest and most respected kids, Ivan Stang.
Besides balancing with Michael...
...is a man who many of you may have already seen on television shows,
such as the Lou Gordon Show,
Tom Snyder's Tomorrow Show,
To Tell the Truth,
and What's My Line?
He's been the subject of articles in Motor Trend, Newsweek, Automotive News, Penthouse Magazine,
and newspapers all over the world.
He is the only man in all of the sales fields to have a place in the Guinness Book of World Records.
If there is anybody who has created a more enviable reputation in person-to-person, one at a time, belly-to-belly selling than...
Reverend Ivan Stang.
...I defy you to name him.
What you are about to hear is truly an experience with Bob.
How are you?
I like you.
Here's a balloon for you. I give balloons away, too.
Thank you. Thanks for coming.
Thanks for coming, baby.
Remember...
Sitting together listening to this.
And this was prison.
Remember...