Hello?
You know, there's a lot of good things about this. There's no bad things.
Yeah.
And that's what this is. You know, it's...
But one of the more interesting things is it's not...
The Self Genius Power of Sparking!
Jesus.
It really is.
Much more valuable than diamonds.
Oh, insomigun, we are gonna be...
Okay.
Over tiered term cash tops during the fund liquidation index rebalancing.
And at the discount hog futures, the market was able to tighten with cash coming lower rather than relatively higher as it should in the future.
And I expected there wouldn't be a worry, but the price went down, and there was a big
drop.
Darkness subsides
Breakfast is served
The eggs seem less clammy today
Hallucinatory gelatinous bulbs
Encircle your glands before melting away
Tiny prepubescent porcupines glide
Down dark lonely streets
Inside of your eyes
The man who brings milk
Is not what he seems
Why don't you go home with your chicken?
Herb-encrusted meatloaf
Buttered heirloom
Potatoes garden
Cheese cooked in garlic butter
Apple cobbler
A sad penguin screams
Behind tinted glass
What is he saying
And why does he cry?
Does he understand?
It doesn't concern you
It's time to go home with your chicken
You can go home
You can go home with your chicken
You can go home You can go home with your chicken
Distant downloads
Stretched way out wide
Rappers to magical lies
Creosote stuck to your teeth and your hair
Your sandwich is ready, you no longer care
You didn't want mayonnaise, it doesn't seem fair
So why not go home with your chicken?
Bon duet, oh
It's time to go home with your chicken
Now you can go home with your chicken
Bon duet, oh
Now you can go home with a chicken
Clover bread to your side
C'est Recovery
Aww yes dear friends, that was the Rudy's Schwartz Project from its latest album
Postal of Ham
This is our Slack Number 1
1,686.
The short collages were done by Mr. Lemur.
And the upcoming long collages are by Cool Hand Chris.
From PR News in Washington,
I'm training people to interact with machines rather than human beings.
President Donald Trump is ordering new sanctions against Facebook.
Tolerance for this disgraceful must end now.
And food for animals, especially diapers.
On Wall Street, unsterile conditions and poor management.
53 today.
Brown University says this is hard to believe PR News.
Say, is anybody else hungry?
How about it, you two?
Couldn't we go someplace for something to eat?
You girls seem to think it's always the boy who starts things.
Oh, naturally.
Oh, no, Lucy.
I, well, sometimes we're partly to blame.
We invite a little attention.
Goes on, and then it's hard to stop.
There are times when it's up to the boy to say no.
Well, each of us has to set his own standards, I guess.
Jack, please don't do that.
Don't act like an iceberg all your life.
Look, we love each other, don't we?
Yes, but after all...
After all what?
Take me home.
I don't understand.
If you really love Keith, why you're not willing to love him all the way?
Completely.
Well, I may be old-fashioned,
but I've always been taught that sex relations should be saved for marriage.
If I did give in to Keith, I don't think he'd ever respect me again.
Not to mention my own self-respect.
Self-respect isn't important when you're in love.
Oh, I'm sorry, Dad, but I just want to...
How many times have I told you not to walk around the house like that?
But, Dad, it's only a...
You heard what I said.
Now go upstairs and...
Put something on!
But, Dad...
What happened?
I hit her.
I know, but why?
I don't know.
But was the moment that you had, the moment where you realized...
I was a young child, maybe eight or nine years old, and The Fly, the movie The Fly, was on TV.
And I didn't watch much of it, but I just saw that scene where...
Where Jeff Goldblum was like, I guess it's pre-transformation.
You haven't watched The Fly?
Not the whole thing.
It came out when I was a baby.
I never saw it.
I just saw this one part, but it was very important because he was naked.
And I just remember those long thighs and that beautiful face.
And I realized I was not gay in that moment.
I was like, I am so into this man-creature.
And I'm not even old...
Man-creature?
I'm not even old enough to know what that is.
As he's mutating into a fly.
Exactly.
I'm into people who have...
Shapeshifting powers, but also penises first.
And then shapeshifting powers second.
Maybe.
Maybe it's the other way around.
I don't know.
Of all the naked to see, to decide what you're going to try and bang...
It's going to be Jeff Goldblum turning into a fly.
I was so sexy.
I think other people agree.
Thank you, subgenius uber women of Austin.
Them being Reverend Annalise.
Anna Moll and Dr. Brew Ha Ha.
Soon, we will be rejoining Anna Moll, along with Dr. Philo Drummond, Dr. Hal, and Reverend Fanboy.
Inside the recordings from inside 21X Day, the one I had to miss.
But now, this.
And know what I have witnessed.
Now it is your turn.
Prepare yourself for a journey into a world where each new step may give you a better understanding of your old self.
And your own reality.
We're all living in America.
America is wunderbar.
It's amazing how anyone can actually stay sane once they've gone through this system.
There is a God.
I'm a man.
I know.
I'm a God.
I know how to make a difference.
I know I'm a God.
This is ingenious and it weighs like nothing.
You are on the air!
You hear sound out of things.
Good grief, there it is.
Beautiful.
Such amazing music.
Yes.
Who put this together?
What?
Yes, Reverend Stang put all this together.
Certainly not us.
This is why I paid my $35,
to not have to do any of the actual work.
Oops.
This is Anna Mall here.
At X Day 21.
Sitting near other people at X Day 21.
Yeah, like Reverend Fanboy.
Reverend Fanboy is to my other side of me.
The outside.
That's my funny church name.
Not on the inside of me.
We got other people that are here in my hearts and minds
that did not pay a registration fee.
No.
So, they can't camp.
But...
They are definitely here in my hearts and minds.
Yes.
Camping or no camping.
It's an egalitarian belief structure we have around here.
You're all beautiful people.
No, no.
In the eyes of God.
Wondrous mutants, maybe.
Beautiful people.
We don't hang out with them.
Beautiful in a mutated sort of way.
Have you seen our lives?
Wondrous.
Majestic.
Mutation is the thought that comes to mind, yes.
Absolutely unique.
Like nothing else I've ever seen before.
Beauty?
What is beauty?
Well...
Beauty?
It's...
Beauty is booty.
That's...
There we go.
We've found the exact match.
So, somebody's anaconda doesn't want none.
I'm just a bunch of beauty, baby bottle.
Unless it's got pirate treasure.
You mean like a sunken chest?
Like my sunken chest?
Like, booty.
Rrr.
Well, that's what it is.
Rrrrrr.
Is booty.
Well, that's what you're going for.
Beastie Boys.
Okay, because what's another word for pirate treasure?
Is that what you're saying?
Yes, that's something in not so many copyrighted words.
What I was saying.
Because the copyright police will be listening.
They're here.
Don't worry, they're here.
They paid their registration because they don't cheat.
Apparently.
Nope.
They're not.
They're...
John, you know, regular guys, you know, a Boilermaker, you know, shot in the blue.
The regular guys, those mutants.
Blue Collar, Salt of the Earth, that's, you know, those kind of mutants.
Salt of the Earth.
We were salting the Earth with them yesterday.
Salting the Earth with mutants as we came up down the highways to get to the landing site.
That's right.
We pulled the car over and we said, out, mutant!
And then we hoped it would form a breeding pair up in the mountains.
And he's like, ooh, you're so salty.
That's it, out, you salient being.
So when we were done throwing our friends out of the car.
Which made it, like, why didn't we bring more stuff?
Why did we bring them?
Exactly.
If we had started out without them.
Yes.
We could have just brought so much more stuff.
But it's okay because it'll all be waiting for us on the pleasure saucers.
If you two have paid your church dues.
That's right.
Do the dues.
It is cheaper than food.
Much cheaper than food.
Eternal salvation for $35.
If we have eternal salvation, we don't need food.
That's right.
I mean, we want it.
And we'll probably get angry if we don't have it.
We'll get grumpy.
So remember the Church of the Subgenius in your will.
We'll be saved.
Yes.
We'd like to talk with you about your estate.
Honestly, they could just send it to AMC.
N-A-M-A-U-L-H-O-U-S-E at PayPal.
No, not the...
Actually, the gmail.com is the PayPal of the animal here.
Once again, not a reverend, not a doctor.
I don't profess to have any of those titles.
I profess to have all of those titles.
I am an overlord.
That's right.
It's nice to see you lord it over us.
Yeah.
It's actually one of my favorite things is, you know,
not having to have my own possessions because I have all possessions.
That's right.
You know, because this is...
Is it mine?
No.
Why not?
You're borrowing it.
Am I?
Well, it's something apart from you that was acquired by another person.
Acquisitions.
Yeah.
Like pirates.
Some people don't want just stuff.
They want your stuff.
That's right.
That's the best stuff is somebody else's stuff.
It's most important that you liked it first and now they have it.
Yeah.
I find happiness is easier to achieve.
If somebody else...
If somebody else is sad near me, then I'm the happy one.
Oh, see.
Okay.
So it's a zero-sum game of slack.
I don't know.
I'm not good at math.
Well, it's just relative.
All things are relative.
Actually, maybe the zero-sum is why I'm so good at math because I haven't been working
with any other numbers.
It's like Gulliver's Travels, you know.
He just didn't actually change in size.
Gullible Travels.
No.
Gullible's Travels.
He just changed his scale.
That's the story of me.
So, change your scale.
Change your scale is the lesson here.
I mold my feathers.
I've got my summer coat coming in.
Well, I hope so because, by God, it's hot.
Who wears a coat during the summer?
It's another hot...
It's muggy.
It's not hot.
What are you talking about?
I came up from the Tejas region of the earth.
I hear it gets hot there.
It's a whole other country recently inundated with dust from another continent.
So, that continent became incontinent on our continent.
And...
Oh, dear.
I hear it's full of nutrients.
Sounds grave.
It's...
Is this some sort of...
Shallow.
It's very shallow.
From the Asian steppes, some sort of sandstorm that blew up.
It's a Saharan dust cloud.
Saharan?
It's from the savannah.
No.
How did it get to Bayou from...
Wind.
Oh.
Just wind.
The magic of wind.
Wait a minute.
Particles of wind.
Particles of dust.
You know they call them Wind Mariah?
They do.
I never did.
No.
You did.
They did.
We have our own special names.
We have our own special pet names for the wind.
But...
And the storms.
Well, the storms all get their own special names.
Yeah.
So, it's like 110 degrees right now.
It's warm.
Down where I'm from.
And I come up here and it's like 90.
Okay.
And everybody's complaining.
It's like 20 degrees less than the wind.
It's like 20 degrees less than where I...
When I was a kid it was like 120 degrees for 40 days straight.
You know?
Uphill.
We used to dive for fun.
Both directions.
That's right.
Well, you know, we also ran behind the mosquito trucks for safety.
Literally.
Puffing that stuff down.
Well, you know, the thing about it is I don't ever remember getting bitten by a mosquito
while doing that.
Right.
No.
Not a one.
Mission accomplished.
Thanks, Deet.
And I hope to see you guys there.
Honestly, if it weren't for Monsanto, we wouldn't have had the ocean on fire back...
You know?
The Texas City fire.
That was a wonderful explosion.
And something that should have been a lesson for all.
But people forget when you don't talk about it.
Nope.
Got to keep it in the mind's eye.
Thanks, Monsanto.
Yeah, thanks.
Really, honestly.
Like, a lot of boiled pork from the business.
fish that day. Didn't even have to
try. Okay.
Well.
The Texas City Explosion, if you're not
familiar, I suggest looking up
and learning up
on that before the books
become ash. Okay.
Yes, I will. Before the
YouTubes become ash. This is tingling
a memory I had of
reading up on all of the disasters
in
Ripley's Believe It, no, no,
Guinness Book of World Records. Yep.
So I actually have a dim awareness
of what you're talking about. You know, as a Ripley,
I take offense to that.
Shit. What, the fact that
we keep telling you to believe it or not?
No, the fact that you don't believe it
whenever I say something, but you believe it if you
read it and it's something that somebody I was
akin to wrote. Okay.
Gah!
Right? So
basically,
as a Ripley,
I can go
into any museum and say,
I'm getting a family discount. This is probably
going to ruin it from here on
out, but I'll go into those
Ripley's Believe It or Not museums and say, I'm a Ripley
and I'll show them my identification.
And they're like, oh.
They're like, well, do you have any ID?
And I show them and they're like, oh, oh, right this way
ma'am, and then open the doors and
all this stuff. And I get to see the back exhibits,
the really freaky stuff that they have
behind the scenes, or
the crap that they haven't glued together
yet, or whatever
it is at these Ripley's Believe It or Not
displays.
There's fish and monkey parts
hanging around everywhere. They're just trying to put
them together and get new exhibits.
We haven't figured out which, you know, like...
Just sew them together. Old Sal ran out of psychedelics
and can't figure out how to put the monkey bits
together on that goat. You know, we're going to
add some wings to it and
the next thing you know, oh, believe it
or not.
People will be like, afterwards, why did I...
I can't believe that I paid this much money to come into
this museum, is what they're saying.
That's the real mystery. How is that
still an industry? How is it?
Like, it's as if
a third of the world believe that the
Earth is flat.
Not a third. A third. Not a third.
No. Americans? Just Americans?
Not even a third of Americans. Aw, come on.
Okay, how much is it?
There's a couple of guys
that are really loud on the... Just because somebody
is making a lot of noise on the internet
does not make it a factual thing.
Okay. I'll accept that.
But there are some people in Denton that
have a display in the front yard of Denton's.
That is Denton, Texas.
Little D. It's just
there north of Dallas area.
And you can go and see the Flat Earth
exhibit while the
Earth lasts. In its final
days, you can go and see
how flat they believe it
really is. They have a pitcher
of water that pours down onto
a plate that has the pitcher of...
Different kind of pitcher. A pitch...
A jug of water
that pours onto an image
of the Earth.
A pitcher on a pitcher.
It's a meme waiting to happen.
Or a meme, as the kids
like to call it.
So, what you're saying is
that they're making it up.
They're fudging it all the way.
Well, see, that's the first part of
starting a religion is
make stuff up.
Everything I say is true and right.
You're going to need a lot of stuff because you've got a lot of competitors
out there that have worked overtime.
Yeah, right.
I mean, massive corporations.
How can you take a chunk out of that market?
I'm sure
someone's figuring it out right now.
We're probably just giving them ideas.
No, we've got to keep those to ourselves.
That's intellectual property right there.
No thinking allowed here, that's for sure.
We're at XDAY.
Our thinking is being done for us by somebody else.
Outsource that.
That's right.
Like the people who
code and hire somebody in Japan
or China, rather, to write all their code.
It could be...
Could be all kinds of places.
Then they forget how to write code.
Could be India, could be specific islanders.
All sorts of folks in the world are doing our code.
Yes.
The code that keeps me thinking I'm a real person?
Your code of many colors.
My code of many colors.
That's my hair. It's coded many colors right now.
Yeah.
Somebody glitched that.
If
if
if I was to be a robot,
I would like,
to think that I had, like,
extra powers.
Not mutant abilities, like
other people discuss sometimes on their radio shows,
but, like, actual skills as a robot.
I would like to be able to be programmed to do certain things, like,
um...
not be afraid of heights, or something.
I don't know. Useful things.
Okay.
You know, like, cause...
Cause, you know, there's a lot of stuff up there.
Ladder climbing robot.
Yeah, not afraid of heights.
Tower climbing robot.
Mm-hmm.
Skydiving robot.
Or what if it was a robot that was a scissors lift?
Drone.
And it would just...
Skydiving robots.
They have to be very tough.
Very tough, you know?
Yeah.
Yeah, I would also like to be not, you know, like, really durably coded.
Yeah, this human shell is so squishy.
It goes splat.
The insides are even squishier.
Yeah.
It's...
Gravity is not the body's friend.
And acceleration even less so.
The icing on the cupcake does not protect the cupcake when it's...
When it falls.
Nope.
You could scrape it off with a knife and tell yourself you're not gonna get botulism, but...
You know, might as well throw it all in the garbage.
Take the whole world, throw it in the garbage.
Actually, I save my botulism.
Cause every now and then, like, once a year, if I haven't gotten the flu, then I might need a good purge.
So I just look at the can...
You do not.
The open can of, when did I buy that kind of soup?
Do they still make it?
Botulism in the back of the fridge there.
And I'm like, eh, you know, maybe the nacho...
You know, the top of the...
The top layer of the nacho cheese.
Uh-huh.
That's liquid nacho cheese.
Right.
You peel that off.
The desiccated coating, yes.
The ones that are...
The fuzzy layer of cheese.
You peel that off.
Uh-huh.
And then you slop the...
Cause liquid cheese is supposed to be not solid.
So as long as it's not solid, it's still edible, right?
Is that in the definition of liquid that you're using?
That's edible.
That's the definition of edible.
As long as it's the same consistency as when I first purchased it.
Mm-hmm.
Cause if the bread goes hard, it's not gonna be as edible.
Unless you've made it toast.
Yeah.
I'm also old food tolerant.
I'll put up with old food.
Okay, so...
Three day old pizza.
When it literally is in a can, which should not ever be stored in a refrigerator.
An open can of something should not be put into a refrigerator.
And then you also, like, don't remember...
Oh, no, in the can.
Don't remember when you purchased it.
Yes.
Kind of thing.
The mystery of location of the food.
Like, you go in there and like, oh, I can just have nachos.
This is...
I could just rent nachos today.
And then, uh...
The botulism.
The purge.
Comes on.
I...
Good luck.
And it's a real, you know, you feel free after that.
Sure.
If you've survived.
It...
You know.
When you wake up in the hospital, yes.
They are so sweet.
They are so attentive.
They are.
Especially when you keep ringing that bell to get the nurse in.
They're so attentive.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
It's like, what's wrong?
Are you okay?
Why...
What...
What happened to you?
Why did you end up here as people come flocking into your room to visit you one every two
or three weeks?
No.
No visitors.
If you don't tell somebody, if you're not the squeaky wheel, they won't know to show
up.
Wow.
Okay.
And, uh, so, yeah.
I...
It's like, really, if you tell people that you ate something that probably had botulism
on purpose, you're probably not gonna have many visitors at the hospital.
You're gonna...
It limits the sympathy factor.
Not that hospital, anyway.
They might send you to a different hospital when you're done with that hospital.
Uh-huh.
Special hospital.
With padded walls and those extra long-sleeved jackets.
Mm-hmm.
And wrap around...
No, but that for real happens?
Just the hugging feeling.
What?
The...
The madness?
No, where they...
No, I had the madness before I had the botulism.
No, where they bind people up in, like, straitjackets.
Is that still occurring?
That's a thing.
Oh, no.
No, it's...
No, you...
You...
If you met somebody that needed to be in a straitjacket, you'd be like, well, that's
a good thing that's around.
You know...
That's...
I might be betraying some prejudices here.
Yes, you're right.
I would like to have that around in that case.
I mean, honestly, let's just suspend all expectations at this point and be delighted
with whatever happens, or fascinated by it.
Marvel at the wonder of the thing that you're not sure about yet because it hasn't been.
That's right.
You have to throw the caution to the wind.
I don't have to do anything...
No, I do insist...
That you throw...
If I have to do something, that's an expectation, sir.
No, to the wind.
I insist.
I'm not doing that.
What wind?
There's a slight breeze, but you know...
A slight breeze.
The wind called Mariah.
I thought we established this earlier.
Oh.
Call Mariah up.
Throw something at Mariah.
Got it.
I'm so sorry, Mariah.
Forgive me, I'm the F
I
Thank you.
Coming up is...
Well, it's hard to believe this is me
only a mere 19 years ago
because I sound so different.
But it's depressingly just as relevant today
as it was in 2001
when I whipped it out.
Think about it, though, friends.
I mean, really.
Reality.
And even its distant relative history
are actually a hell of a lot weirder
than any science fiction.
If something as far-fetched
as Nazis getting paid by the CIA
to train Middle Eastern fanatics
to fight the commies can be real,
and it is,
then why not the CIA and aliens conspiracy?
Huh?
I mean,
if the CIA conducted mass experiments on the citizenry
with LSD, and it did,
then why wouldn't it use some cover Christian organization
to turn earnest young weirdos into Manchurian candidates
and make them kill anti-establishment rock stars
or even presidents
just to make all earnest young weirdos
look more insane than the CIA?
It's infuriating.
You know, you can't just uncover a conspiracy
and leave it at that.
You always have to take into account
the deliberate disinformation possibilities.
For instance, maybe the feds pay Bob Lazar
to talk about crashed saucers on air bases
and soul-stealing gray aliens
in order to distract researchers from something far worse.
The murkiness level can become literally maddening.
And that just might be the whole idea.
No doubt about it,
you can go overboard, friends, way overboard.
There's those who believe the Holocaust was a hoax
and all the rest of us are crackpots.
You know, heck, if you're gonna go that far,
you might as well believe that World War II didn't happen.
You know, I'm not saying that.
I'm saying that the next logical step
is to believe that nothing the press ever reported
really happened.
And pretty soon, praise Bob,
you've got mountains of proof that you're always right
and everybody else is always wrong.
Then, of course, naturally, the conspiracies
that people tend to believe in
are the ones that make them look good
and absolve them of responsibility.
Over a hundred years ago,
some anonymous anti-Semitic Frenchman
penned a hoax called
The Protocols of the Elders of Zion.
And to this day, thanks to that hoax,
thousands of frustrated, nasty old rednecks
believe that the Jews control the world.
Now, believing that lets them off the hook.
The reason for their poverty and misery
isn't that they're a bunch of lazy, ignorant, alcoholic po-buckers.
It's the Jews' fault.
By the same token, bitter black people
who think that all white people must be out to get them
can find plenty of reinforcement
in the nation of Islam, called.
Inevitably, friends,
those who are the most paranoid
about a particular conspiracy
become a conspiracy themselves.
So where is the balance?
Which conspiracy theories should you believe?
For that matter, which conspiracy should you join?
Well, friends, we're here to tell you about
The Church of the Subgenius.
You know, we started a lot of those conspiracies ourselves.
You can always come to Bob
to find a conspiracy made just for you.
You can write to Bob.
I'm going to give you that free information
post office box.
Just say, Bob, send me that free information.
And Bob is at post office box 807
Glen Rose, Texas 76043.
That's box 807, Glen Rose, Texas 76043.
Short!
I remember a time when I thought all that babble
about multiple gunmen in Dealey Plaza
and the Oswald Doubles and so forth was silly.
And it is getting awfully crowded up there on the grassy knoll.
But you know, as I got more educated,
about the JFK puzzle,
I learned a terrible truth.
If you investigate deeply enough,
sometimes you become part of the conspiracy.
I'm now a participant in the JFK cover-up.
I know why the Kennedy family had to go along
with the Warren Commission.
But if I told
it would jeopardize lives.
Stop laughing.
I'll tell you, man,
you start out paranoid about them
and the next thing you know,
you're one of them.
And maybe it's an infinite regression.
Maybe there's no escape.
Maybe, maybe there's no one single truth
that everybody should believe in.
Not even Bob.
Maybe everything is a conspiracy.
You know, who knows?
Maybe one of these days we'll find out
even that's not so funny after all.
Good thing this is just a comedy show.
We'll leave that at home then.
We'll let the scourge of the population,
burning, explosions, the gases,
take that over.
We'll leave that all behind.
Okay.
We'll figure out some other solution to that problem.
It's not a problem though.
Just because it has a solution.
Every problem is an opportunity.
Just because it has a solution
doesn't mean it's a problem.
Sometimes people are just overworked and needy.
Oh, well, yeah, absolutely.
That's too big a problem.
Is it a problem?
Right now.
Is it?
Well, it's a problem for the people who are in trouble.
It's a situation, but it's a problem.
It's an opportunity for people who have control
over those people's lives, basically.
That's how I look at it.
Hmm.
I don't really think that hard as being an overlord, you know?
No.
You don't have to worry about taxation.
Just by whim.
Or elections.
Or administration.
You're just an overlord.
You're saying the people that I'm the overlord of have problems.
Of course they have problems.
Who doesn't have problems?
I don't know.
That's really not a concept I work with.
Is their life a string of perfect days strung together?
On the fabric of their life.
It's as perfect as it gets.
That's right.
I choose to have an imperfect day.
Actually, a very imperfect day is very perfect for me.
Mm-hmm.
If I had no, I don't know, variety?
Then what's the point?
Well, let's just start our existential crisis now at Home Kids.
What's the point of living?
Living if there's no change?
Well, of course there's change.
If every day you do the same thing.
If you wake up, you get dressed, or you don't.
You don't.
You might just lay there in bed.
You might play video games all day long.
You might have forgotten to feed that dog enough times where there's just a stuffed animal in the corner of the room.
In a pose permanently looking like it's hungry.
Then you're sitting there and he's like,
You don't have to worry about that dog anymore.
Problem solved.
All the solutions are around every, opportunities around every corner.
Solutions are everywhere.
But then, you know, you might eat food.
You might have food brought to you.
You might go get the food.
You might make the food.
You might have to go and cut the food out of its original source and turn it into nutrient-wielding goo blob.
You mean you cook it.
Cook it.
Yeah.
You know.
You could cook it.
Somebody else could cook it for you.
Like we have here.
And then, uh, of course, once that's all said and done, you know, you might go back to bed.
After the pooping and the peeing and whatever extra-meditary functions you gotta do each day.
But that doesn't sound like a day of problems.
It just sounds like a day of boredom.
After, after years of this, you might develop bed sores, which might be an annoyance.
Sure.
Or a medical issue.
But not necessarily a problem.
Now, I have the, I have really good bed sores.
The best.
Just the best.
Because that's the thing you put your money into.
It really has a return.
Yeah.
There you go.
Exactly.
Festering open wounds.
That's, uh, I would, I would, can I get an extra scoop of necrosis, please?
Yeah.
If you just give me one second, I'll get you the key.
Impotal westerns do wrong with those blows because their butt is exposed, and that's
I will be endlessly makeup shopping, so fuck remarkable existe long.
Luk, whatnwh thousand times I've gotten Kolbliker Bl Topareraa
and you're a Mooseimple Mermseianst I'm Blas.
Kaatikar quaisem.
Did you get one, ing at half an hour here.
You are delivery boxes and books and the usual big bang thougochis.
In English I think you just sort of, founder your ucci.
A.
Know what to do until this thing goes dark.
The way V sp RYAN's something well though I'm Forceful.
Tens of thousands of people are still living outside Berlin
because all have refused to party with them.
And the BBB BBC says...
The inside current of the Kravente has been fleeing a BBC crackdown.
The BBB BBC.
The United Nations High Commissioner for Refugees says
this is PR news in Washington.
You know who I've been exposed to a lot,
who just does it his own way, is Puzzling Evidence.
He really needs to keep his clothes on.
Where did you see him naked?
No, you just said he exposed it.
Oh, no. Ha, ha, ha.
Ha, ha, ha. No.
I listened to his stuff.
This is the trail of unconsciousness
that comes out of people's mouths, ladies and gentlemen.
No, I celebrate him and his work
because he just makes show, and it's always show.
Show is just always going on.
And it's this long stream of unconsciousness.
It's a long stream of unconsciousness.
That's what I'm hoping someday to learn how to do it
so that the show just happens.
This is part one where I learn how to blather.
Something...
I was going to say something has to happen,
but in truth, nothing has to happen.
Right.
And people have tried writing stuff
about how nothing is happening
with limited success.
And sometimes when nothing happens, it's funny.
Sometimes.
And sometimes when nothing happens,
it's just masochistic going over the same things
over and over again.
I was not a fan of Seinfeld.
I was saying you were pretty much describing that.
And then there's people who find...
Well, the Seinfeld show was Larry David,
and then Larry David's got the Larry David show,
and so it's the celebration of nothing,
the celebration of the quotidian and blah,
suddenly.
Yes.
Nothing happened.
But it happened suddenly.
Well, and it's also humor derived from shame,
humor derived from bad behavior.
I got a limited...
It's got a limited appeal for me.
That's not where I go for humor,
if I can help it.
And I'm not a prude either.
I just...
I get tired of it.
Find it boring.
It's boring.
Exactly.
Don't be...
Boring.
Yeah.
Boring is a sin.
If part of your day is watching Seinfeld on TBS
and you watch the commercials...
I'm sorry.
...then you have to stop.
You have...
Who is the person who's doing that,
that watches it, doesn't have a DVR?
It's like you could do literally anything
from robbing a bank to, you know,
driving your car into the ocean,
and it would be more productive...
Building custom pee videos.
That's...
Yes.
But we're still not talking about politics.
No, we're not.
No.
We're definitely not talking about
people who are
doing a handheld odyssey about
sex consultants...
Handheld.
Making...
Documenting the spoiling of bedware.
Of bedsheets.
No.
Definitely not talking about that.
You're triggering me,
but in a good way, by the way.
Well, pee and poop,
those are subgenius topics.
Pee dog and poop dog
are very important personalities in the church.
They are.
It's...
That don't come up as often as they have in the past.
And they don't come up as often as they should.
As they should.
I put this playlist together.
If one is listening to this
and it happens to get to your ears
and you want to find out,
a link to it is on the 21XDay page.
And I will probably find another place to put it.
But it's just subgenius stuff
that's on YouTube already.
They strung together.
And there's the most amazing rant by Philo,
who happens to be here at this X Day.
Yes, he is.
And it is just a torrent of swear words
and descriptions of disgusting bodily parts
and excretions.
Excreta.
Is that the lecture about eating fucks?
Yes.
Oh, yes.
I remember that.
I remember that when he gave it.
Were you there?
Yes, I was.
Oh, well...
In the front row.
You were blessed.
Definitely blessed.
You could hear him losing the audience.
It's so great.
And then you can hear people applauding
to indicate that he should stop now.
And then he gets to the end
and automatically everyone applauds
even though they've been dreaming about it ending
for the last...
Four minutes.
Well, they've been dreaming about it.
It finally happened.
And there was much rejoicing.
Mm-hmm.
Yes, I...
That was fun listening
on my way down here from...
Indeed.
From Metro Detroit.
Yes.
Fun, fun listening.
I can't...
See, you gotta take the time.
That's something I would ask everybody to do.
Take a little time as...
As Fightsitaj does.
To seek out the bulldada.
To seek out the weird media.
To seek out the stuff that's not on...
But if you're tuned into it...
The three...
Your channels.
If you're tuned into the bulldada,
you don't have to seek it out.
It seeks you.
Once you adjust your view...
You will find it everywhere you look.
Yeah.
Yep, there it is.
And you realize that as horrific the world is,
uh,
at any given day and age,
it can also be pretty fucking funny.
Yeah.
It's...
It's human beings
concentrating their energy on...
Well, making something...
Making something to be perceived.
You know,
talking about Ed Wood.
Just the obsession.
The people have got the obsession
to get the thing down.
And I...
Before there was electronic media or film,
it was the...
You know,
uh,
epic poet.
Traveling from town to town.
It's like,
hey, sit down for a couple hours.
I gotta tell you about Odysseus.
I gotta tell you about the Odyssey.
Well, they didn't, uh,
in some cases,
they didn't realize that,
um,
the rocks they were throwing at him
to make him shut up
were, um,
actually valuable, so...
Right.
He usually came away with a fortune.
We just never hear that part of him.
Nope.
Here's your bulldogger right here,
ladies and gentlemen.
So,
considering that,
even that is not a problem,
what would, uh,
what would a day with problems look like
for you?
A day with problems?
Yeah, I'm unaware of the concept.
All the stuff I need to have work
so I can get from one part of the day
to the next part of the day
fails to work.
That's a problem.
Okay, so,
whose idea,
of work,
this is the thing.
So, I've taken the idea of work
Yeah.
and realized that it's somebody else's idea
that's been pressed upon me.
Sure.
Right?
This is church secrets being revealed,
kids at home
that are playing along.
And I say,
hey, you know what?
That's somebody else's idea
of what I need to do with my life.
Mm-hmm.
But it's,
but I didn't give them any money.
They're just giving me this free
advice.
Sure.
I'm not an ad,
I'm not,
I don't like advertisers.
So, I'm just gonna cut that right out.
I'm gonna be,
I'm gonna pay to know what to think.
Yes.
Send my $35 into the Church of the Subgenius.
Well, they're gonna explain it to you.
And then they tell me
what to think.
And sometimes they don't tell me anything.
So, I don't have to do a darn thing.
It's really been working out well.
If you want to take thinking off the schedule,
join the Church of the Subgenius.
Absolutely not necessary.
Just let the,
no expectations there in the Church of the Subgenius.
No, there aren't, actually.
Which is exactly why I have no stress whatsoever.
So, we're never disappointed.
So, what you're saying,
Because there's no expectations.
I wouldn't even know what that was.
Aim for the bottom.
The choose to lose system works every time.
Yep.
So, what you're saying is,
other people want you to go to this place
to do a thing in order to earn a thing
so you can spend it on stuff
that other people said you need to have.
Mm-hmm.
So, you can
enjoy,
enjoy things?
Well,
it's not enjoy so much as survive, you see.
So, that's what you got to get past.
Ooh.
If you adopt,
if you do that,
you have to say,
I'm not going to let it get to me.
I'm just going to give,
render to Caesar what Caesar's can continue.
Sounds like a horrible idea.
Willful as,
as,
I can't say that word.
Huh?
Ignorance.
Willful as,
Oh, yeah.
Gosh darn it.
Willful ignorance.
That makes,
that turns the world.
Ignorance.
Yeah.
All those,
all those,
just so wonderful.
It's a gift.
It's just a little gift
that's given to you
by the corporation.
A little gift.
That's given to you,
like your little,
tiny semblance of,
of happiness
and brief moment of joy
in existence.
Man, if that's what you got going for,
what's the point?
What's the point of this daily grind
if it doesn't produce coffee,
which is delicious,
and I would be,
No.
happy if anybody brought me coffee.
Everywhere I do this stuff,
I get coffee.
So really,
it's just feeding my coffee addiction.
Oh, okay.
Well, as long as they have you
addicted to something,
so you have to return.
You thought it was all this
philosophy and stuff.
I just like coffee.
And they're always
pouring it down your throat.
So, you know.
They do that at a lot of places
that they want you to be.
Yeah.
Yes, they do.
Yep.
But,
but honestly,
if I don't have any kind of
expectations for myself
or for other people,
how can I be disappointed
and made sad?
But, yeah.
That, you know,
you can't.
Exactly.
I agree with that.
Okay.
That was,
okay, never make me do that much effort
in explaining why I don't have to
put out effort ever again.
Jeez.
Shall we step to the side?
So, wait, you're,
I'm ready to.
You're going to step aside.
Side, sir?
Yes.
You and your,
your predisposed predilections
to work the ethic
efforty.
I don't know.
Are there ethics involved?
Ethics involved in what?
Okay, then never mind.
Okay.
That simplifies it.
Thanks to Reverend Anna Mall
and Fanboy
and everyone at X Day.
I wish I could have been
there,
but I had to deal with
family matters
in the parched land
of Stang Ranch
in north central Texas
during a month of days
all over 100 degrees
and not a drop of rain.
We already made it
through one grass fire
and Princess Wee
and her mom
had to stay in Ohio
so it's just me
and the hound dog
and the new pit bull
clogger.
And Price Bob,
almost all the rest
of my family.
So it's not so bad
because my family is
so cool.
Even though the weather's
so incredibly hot
and threatening
and the national oppressiveness
is grotesquely palpable
on all levels.
Nonetheless,
we persevere
and we always have friends
such as
Bob Walsh,
Mark mchte
stan
A man is not visual
By the size of his feet
By the point of his choice
The grain of his voice
The strings of his jeep
The breadth of his vision
The cast of his hand
Like you would not believe
In a dry, dry land
Rain in the desert
Like you would not believe
Man from a hand
He shall grow
In a dry, dry land
Oh, I was a fool
I was counting my store
Yeah, I was counting my money
He spared my blessings
And I'll tell you what's more
Oh, I begrudged the poor
Yeah, I sacked me in the lake
As a man like you would not believe
In a dry, dry land
Like you would not believe
Rain in the desert
Man from a hand
He shall grow
In a dry, dry land
Like you would not believe
With
Well, all we can do is
Find a small sea
And hope that the miracle
Yes, will proceed
Rain from a earth answer, oiled by the air
Light it with renpah
We are being tested
We are being asked
To make good on our bets
And to help with the rest
Of the time's hard tests
And the rain will fall
And your face will stand
Yeah, you would not believe
In a tragic end
Like you would not believe
Rain and mist
Matter from the end
We shall prove
In a dry, dry land