I can't tell you how excited I am about our first guest this morning.
He will be joining us in just a couple of moments.
The Reverend Ivan Stang from the Church of the Subgenius.
Praise Bob!
We're having operating difficulties.
Hey, what's going on here?
The Subgenius Hour of Slack.
This Stang Back Saving Rerun is Hour of Slack number 128 from May 1st, 1988.
And it's a really good one.
Welcome to the end times, boys and girls.
We're going to shock shock the house with your brain and the world.
Bob is getting down with you here tonight.
Bob is getting down to help your plight.
Bob is coming here to ease your strife.
Come on, suckers, let Bob into your life.
And remind you of this.
He who laughs last laughs best, but also gets his teeth kicked in.
And if you can't laugh at yourself, make fun of everyone else.
Is it rolling?
Backwards masking, take one.
Satan is cool.
God is a jerk.
Wonder if we fooled anybody.
Yeah, I've heard about Satan trying to get people to sell their souls,
but he's not really too good at it.
Actually, he tried to get me to sell mine,
but all he offered me was crap like a Hugo and tennis shoes from Taiwan
and carob yogurt.
And he was like, I'm not going to sell you anything.
He was like, I'm not going to sell you anything.
I'm going to sell you this thing called a cheapskate.
And he got all huffy and red in the face and called me a spoilsport.
But I told him to go straight to hell because that just wasn't good enough.
I wasn't going to sell myself that cheap.
So there.
Oh, yes.
A dear, a friend's eye.
This is the subgenius radio ministry hour of slack at our new place on the dial.
Eighty nine point three.
Unusual.
I hope you're finding us.
And I hope those of you who never heard us before keep listening because I have specially designed this show.
This is a very unusual show for you strangers to it.
And what we what we're doing tonight is basically sort of a revised introduction to the church.
For new viewers.
Every three or four months, we do that just like a pledge drive just to catch you up on what the church of the subgenius is and why there must be and has always been a Bob.
Also tonight, though, we're going to preview the new album by the swinging area diets of Boston.
If you've never heard them, then hang in there.
By the way, while I'm still thinking about it, this is quark in the background.
Quark.
Mighty stereo background.
Friends listen on headphones.
You really should.
And start your tape decks up.
We'll also later be doing some reading from the new subgenius book.
Hi, weirdness by mail, which isn't out yet.
So therefore, you couldn't call this an ad.
Exactly.
You're getting a preview, friends of a major Simon and Schuster publication, and it's going to make some of you so mad.
So mad.
I hope if we're doing our job
So see if you can see if you can figure out what's going on here if you can't we don't need you
Understand that's the whole point of this
Okay, that's it now. You know what the Church of subgenius is about Bobby sex
Praise Bob dear friends. This is the radio ministry of the church
Let's start back at the beginning because a lot of people are not aware of
Exactly what J.R. Bob Dobbs and the church praise Bob are all about
Tell us all about it
Subgenius is the end times church for mutants
formed to spread the
Seed word of that great saint of sales J.R. Bob Dobbs
Bob formed the church in 1953 being the saint of sales
But he kind of kept it under wraps until around 1980 when he
recruited dr. Philodromo myself to begin
Releasing the secrets of his teachings to the public at large which of course
has had disastrous effects
Bob?
Bob Bob Bob
Bob is
Bob is sex
That's your key phrase
It will trigger the entire message without your being aware of it
We are controlling transmission
You've got to see this boy for what he is
He's a maniac out to rule the world
What can I do to make you understand him?
I love you
Bob Bob Bob
Bob loves you
The rewards are worth the effort
Oh yes dear friends the harvest
The Harvest
But you see if you do have some questions here you can still call
And speak to an actual human being who might answer your questions
And speak to an actual human being who might answer your questions in a linear way
Call the station
Or speak to the Will O Dobbs
And he'll give you information on where to get more information
And help you find out whether you can actually handle that information or not
Which is all another question altogether
You see
The keys to instant success
Mystic knowledge and miraculous adventures
Even contact with the Space Brothers
Within your grasp
Simply by tuning in
To this show
Every Sunday night at 9
Do you have different tastes?
Intrigued by the bizarre?
The kooky? The kinky?
As long as it keeps its distance
Do you enjoy getting unsolicited
But unspeakably weird
But unspeakably weird things in the mail
For free?
Love to snicker in superiority
Perhaps largely imagined
At the incredible gullibility
At the incredible gullibility of those around you
Enjoy reading the headlines
On sleazy tabloids
And ads for local psychic fortune tellers
Do you, my friend
Appreciate the unexpected
Glimpses of strange
Realities
Behind religions
Other than your own
Entranced by the
Thought processes of the mentally
Ill?
And bored to tears by any music
Video or literature that isn't almost
Shockingly original?
Are you painfully aware dear friend
That all great geniuses
And inventors of the past
Appeared totally insane
To everyone around them?
Then have we got a religion
For you, my friend
Actually that was the introduction
From the religion's second book
High Weirdness by Mail
No, let's not get technical
Superior mutants
Repent, quit your job
Slack off
The world ends tomorrow
And you may die
Well no, probably not
But whatever you do, just keep listening
The end times is here
At last the step by step process is revealed
This is it, the only thing that's left is to die
And that's the fate that promises
Action, thrill, success in sex
And business
Having all the guilt
But none of the sex
I did not put you here to suffer
No, I did not put you here to whine
I put you here to love one another
Yes, let me be that man
But for the time now, now, now
Let my people go, go, go
Yeah, you gotta let my people go, go, go
You gotta, oh, you gotta
Let my people go
Go, go, you gotta
Let my people go, go, go
Are they destroyed?
When you use insects to pass as Tyke-a-Bob
When you walk in through the woods
When you make out with the girls
When you feed up to the hounds
Tyke-a-Bob
That's right, it's by Onan
Onan Kennebite
Friends call it
When I roll from the seers
These two
Onan Kennebite
If you have any questions
Are we controlled by secret forces?
Yes!
You guys shall triumph!
I am completely agree
With all the obstacles
And with all the enemies
Who are between me
And what I want to do
I see that they cooperate
They are
They are in a providential mind
And they help me
To do exactly what
What I want
Because if I have not to fight
It is in the fighting
That I can see better
What I want to do
It is in the
In the friction
How do you say?
Friction
That thing become more clear
It become more clear
Just because
It runs the danger to be far
To go away from me
I want to see you in a better place than me
But we spread this mighty seed word
Of flak
And how to get it
How to fight the conspiracy
Through radio shows
In different cities
Through videotape
Two books now
Are excuse scrolls
Suitable for framing
And live shows
I do a lot of science fiction conventions
And then there is Buck Naked
Reverend Buck Naked
Here in Dallas
He occasionally plays with his band
More Drunk Cowboys
Here and there
He preaches
Although he is a
As a true subgenius
He is a schismatic
And has formed his own splinter group
Which of course does
Intense battle with my personal splinter group
It always happens
Drunk in Budweiser
Watching five-ball TV
It Bella
And Another
Battle
I can't resist
My passion
Will repeatedly
Embrace
People
We Christmas
Right Hoje
a truly well-rounded education,
you've got to study the extremists,
the obscure, and the so-called nutty.
You need the balance.
Your poor brain is being impregnated
with middle-of-the-road crap 24 hours a day,
no matter what.
Network, TV, newspapers, radio,
magazines at the supermarket.
Even if you never watch, read, listen, or leave your house,
even if you are deaf and blind,
the telepathic pressure alone
of the uncountable normals surrounding you
will ensure that you're automatically
well-grounded in consensus reality.
Screw consensus reality.
What we all need is more of that common-sense stuff.
Badly named, because it's not really
such a common commodity after all.
And our guru, the great mystic,
the saint of sales, J.R. Bob Dobbs,
often preached on this.
You know how dumb the average guy is,
he once asked his flock of apprentice sales ministers?
Well, by definition, half of them are even dumber than that.
Praise Bob.
Sad but true and getting worse each year, dear friends.
The kooks are our future.
So make no mistake,
it'll be a rich harvest for industrial skull farmers like us.
And those of every creed.
Because the brains of the all-too-willings are out there ripening,
ingesting a rich loam of made-for-TV UFO movies,
and absurd claims for holistic vitamins.
Radio preachers who converse with angels.
Millions of potential vegetables just waiting to be plucked,
shucked, and hauled off the market.
And if it ain't us that does it,
it's gonna be a lesser cult, or even worse,
some political group, dear friends.
So...
If you don't get it by now, you never will.
Like they say and say again.
I don't know what you're doing.
You wanna know what we're doing?
Sounds pink to me.
We've been talking about it for an hour and a half,
and if you haven't figured it out yet,
pal, you never will.
Well, I'm a Christian, and I think this is a sin.
I think this is a fake hate call.
Duh.
This is a fake hate call.
I wanna get some real hate calls.
This guy has a body.
We can't deal...
Listen, no friends out there.
We don't want fake hate calls.
We need the real thing.
I mean, it's just like in Dallas.
I mean, in the middle of the Bible Belt,
we've been doing this subgenius hour of Slack show
every Sunday night,
for almost a year,
and no one's killed us yet.
Well, did the Reverend ever explain to you
what subgenius meant?
Uh...
Was there a connotation to concern?
No, we didn't get into that today.
I was just wondering.
You know, I just kind of always took it on its face value.
Uh-huh.
Well, if you joined it, you would be subgenius, wouldn't you?
I believe so.
What is he going to be when he wakes up and starts breathing?
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
I'll tell you what.
I'm not going to turn my radio on Friday morning no more,
because I thought the little imbibing I'd done last night would pass,
but I ran it back into a nightmare when the radio came on.
Stuff happens.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha.
Thank you, Kelly.
Thanks very much for calling, Norman.
How are you, sir?
Yeah, I'm sorry I missed Reverend Stang a while ago.
Uh, he mentioned a Reverend Bucknaked.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
I think I knew him years back when he played in a band.
I believe that Reverend Naked does still play in a band.
Yeah.
Does he play the organ?
I don't know.
Yeah.
Well, this Bucknaked I knew could finger an organ better than anybody I ever saw.
That's about enough on that one, John.
Ha ha ha ha.
Hi, Kevin.
How are you doing?
Fine.
How are you?
Good, good.
I've never called before, but, uh...
Well, we're glad you could call today.
Well, thank you.
I do listen all the time.
I wanted to say something about that, uh, subgenius thing.
Mm-hmm.
I had seen a piece of paper, uh, that was printed by them about six or seven years ago.
And a friend of mine brought it over and said, look at this.
And we looked at it, and it was, it was the scariest thing I ever saw.
Um, I just wanted the, the listeners to, to, to hear this experience that I had gone through.
Anyway, I read it, and what it was was it looked like gibberish on the surface.
Uh, I don't know if you can hear it.
I don't know if you can hear it.
It was just, it was just a lot of weird lettering and, and words, you know, that didn't make
any real sense.
And, uh...
Until?
What?
Until I, I read through it, and it just, it was, it was like possessed or something.
It was scary.
It really scared me.
There was, uh, bad words in there and there was...
No.
...messy stuff.
I mean, not, not like full bad words, but like just, just really, really scary stuff.
Yeah.
And, uh, while you were reading it, did demons with fingernails begin clawing at your flesh?
Well, I, I know one thing.
I know they didn't claw at my flesh.
But, but it...
It's too bad.
...had me to the point to where, where I, you know, decided I better not read anymore.
And, and it was a question of, uh, I'm, I'm not a, you know, a religious fanatic or anything
by, by far, but I could tell that there, that there was definitely not wholesome stuff in
there.
And, and I just thought it was really, it, it made such an impression on me.
Uh, so, like I said, it was, it was, it was, it was, it was, it was, it was, it was, it
was, it was, it was like a seven, seven years ago I read this thing.
And it was just, it was done very professionally, you know, printed and everything.
It wasn't just, you know, scribbling.
But it wasn't wholesome?
No.
It was, uh...
My word.
I would say it was just really, really weird.
Weird and not wholesome.
Yeah.
Uh...
Boy, I'm suprised they allow that kind of stuff to be printed.
Well, no.
You see, it wasn't anything you could just, you know, say, oh there is, uh, there is bad,
you know, bad...
Bad words, yeah.
...words being written.
Yeah.
It wasn't anything, you know, you could just say, oh there is, uh, there is bad, you
It was more like, it was like speaking in tongues, except it was evil.
If you could imagine something like that.
Oh, I think I could.
And we thank you for alerting us to it, Jeff.
Well, you know, evil is as evil does or something like that, I suppose.
I wish that I could play the entirety of the tapes that these little interviews come off of.
They're usually very old interviews.
I'd love to play the whole thing, but they're from other stations.
Hey, let's do something new, you know?
Speaking of which, there are some new things here I need to cover.
See, the subgenius mentality does not have to call itself subgenius.
You'll be saved from damnation.
Damnation, if you do call yourself a subgenius.
And especially if you're carrying the right membership cards in your pocket.
You can write for information about that.
We'll give the number at the end of the broadcast at 10 o'clock.
But in the meantime, there are, like I say, other ways to do the same thing that a subgenius does,
which is to get slack.
And this weekend, the lead singer of the Swingin' Aeriodites,
who I've played many times before in their older incarnations on the show,
the lead singer Johnny Angel, a friend of Brother Cleve Duncan's, who you all know so well,
he sent me their album.
In fact, he sent me several copies of it.
And yes, the Swingin' Aeriodites have finally made it to vinyl, or whatever it is they record on nowadays.
Disc, film, you know.
Mm-hmm.
I think this is analog, not digital.
But I'm going to play just a few bits and pieces off of it.
This one right here is probably a good one to dedicate to the worried caller who called that normal talk show,
saying that the nonsensical subgenius stuff he had read seemed so evil.
You know, to others, to some.
It seems neither nonsensical nor exactly evil.
Everybody's heading west
Where they hear the serpent's best
We'll meet a former musketeer
And get the hell away from here
Oh
We must have fleeked the park this time once too often
Frankie and the Nugget, Pete, Jim and Terry
And the Reverend Jerry Falwell put the last nail in the coffin
We're going out west to the Golden Coast
I hear the preaching is peachy and the Lord is most
Now that we ain't got no home
It's praise the Lord and pass the copper tone
Go to where it never first came from
And wind it no crbanking
What?
What's stopping us?
We're going to the
earth
And burn our casa
survival
we got the
hoedads and
wahineys and
we had a big
revival
they claim a
rolling stone
shall gather
no moss
we'll build a
bitchin'
woody from
the holy
cross
surf and
sea and
waves and
sand
from the
shroud of
turret
and get a
groovy
town
Arthur
who art
in heaven
get me a
slurpee at
the 7-11
7-11
Frankie and
Annette
meet Jim
and Tammy
Frankie and
Annette
meet Jim
and Tammy
Frankie and
Annette
meet Jim
and Tammy
on your
knees
equipment
hang ten
we coulda
moved to
Kansas
we coulda
moved to
Texas
Frankie and
Annette
meet Jim
and Tammy
the Reverend
Jimmy don't
care cause he
likes both
sexes
Frankie and
I would have moved to New York City, but boy, oh boy, there's two Jews for every car.
Two Jews for every car.
I really wish to hell I was the Holy Father.
I wouldn't need a surfboard, I could walk on water.
Frankie and Annette meet Jim and Tammy.
David Lee Roth hears Hagar Sammy.
Oh.
And hang town.
Oh, yes, indeedy.
Well, we've certainly had some interesting calls tonight, since we've switched frequencies with KCBI, you see.
This used to be KNON, the station for open mic.
Blinded weirdos and rednecks and minorities of all kinds.
Anybody not totally into the mainstream and anybody into the mainstream.
Whereas KCBI was somewhat more narrow readership or listenership.
So half of the calls have been saying, hey, KNON, where are you on the dial?
And if you're hearing me, you already know.
And if not, then what's the point in trying to tell you?
We're a little bit to the left.
And the other half of the callers have called expecting to hear KCBI, which used to occupy this airspace.
And, well, for those of you wishing that you were hearing your good old KCBI Christian station that you're used to,
you are the lucky ones.
You are really lucky because you are now finally by accident being delivered from the false religion.
The biggest trick the devil ever pulled on you to the church of the subgenius.
The biggest trick ever pulled on the devil.
Let's see.
He and the devil thinks I'm kidding right now.
Don't you, Satan?
Oh, yes, yes.
It's a study in opposites, dear friends.
But at the same time, I mean, we're on the side of right.
And good.
The only difference between us and what you may have used to be listening to is that it doesn't really matter to us how much money you make.
See?
Or what religion you are, what color you are, what sex you are.
To us.
Now, I'm not speaking for Kano.
And it's not solid church of the subgenius.
We are.
We only do this one hour a week.
That's all.
The.
Slack you're going to get for a week in this form.
However, stay tuned for further slack of many different kinds.
This is a station that has it has gospel in the morning.
Hispanic music during a chunk of the day.
Soul and hip hop rap stuff.
Another chunk of the day.
Country redneck.
Good old Texas stuff.
And then the weird punk late on into the night.
Plus special days of talking.
Talk shows and.
And alternate news that you may not quite get the uncensored versions of another station.
So.
Yeah.
Why don't you use those of you who've never who have stumbled upon us upon our new frequency.
Please just keep listening.
Don't judge the whole station by this show.
How could any other show keep up with this?
They don't all have Bob.
Some of them just have records.
What you just heard a little while ago.
Was the swinging area.
Dice version of Frankie and Annette meet Jim and Tammy.
We're going to play some more swinging area.
Dice.
It's nice to reach out.
It's nice for a change not to be preaching to the saved.
That is the downfall of everybody from the early Christians to the new age fakers to the modern day Christian fakers.
Two.
In fact.
The subgenius fakers preaching to the saved.
I hope that you all you that you all who do who cannot figure out what's going on.
Keep listening and become ever more confused until the fear and puzzlement builds up in your mind to the point where you can't quit talking about it.
And those of you who work with you in your office and think you're a religious fanatic.
They'll think it sounds like a pretty interesting idea and probably ended up contributing money either to the station or.
Some.
Other agent there.
Oh you see.
You tried everything.
You ain't seen nothing yet.
Learn to think big.
Develop the tricks of length extension.
Bring your weirdest dreams to rampaging life.
Stand direct for your own abnormality.
Get some.
And for game.
Everything.
The student of Dobbs training is practically forced to bring his strangest desires into rampaging life.
I used to get embarrassed about my glass madness.
Now I get paid.
The pinks pay me fabulous sums of money for what they used to put me in jail for.
Thanks to Bob.
You've got the double.
Who does?
I'm hurting more and more.
On the toucher, dude.
It's a good deal.
We're behind even.
Wasn't lean at all about speed specialist?
I am basta there good with cash.
really wants to know.
Smell like pudding and it ain't on fire.
Same thing that you know you have to buy.
What that smell like fish?
Good if you really want to know.
I mean, good if you really want to know.
Yeah.
Dobbs has seen to it that he exercises this abnormality.
To do otherwise, he teaches, would be nothing short of spiritual suicide.
Man is a way of life to millions.
Yet half of them don't even know.
He's the one true living slack master with the spiritual know-how to help you bash through the locked doorway to financial heaven.
He is the one real shortcut to slack.
Now, see another dimension on your TV.
Yes, fear the stark fist of removal no longer.
Become physically attractive overnight.
Attain status, luck, prosperity by blowing them off.
All the way.
Even though that wasn't actually...
Talk about the amusement park.
Oh, well, yes.
If we give, we'll never be able to raise the money for that amusement park now.
Amusement park?
What amusement park?
Oh, the subgenius amusement park in Oklahoma.
On the highway, across from the Stucky.
Near that big cement dinosaur.
They got out there?
Yes, there's a giant crude cement bob now with a cafe inside.
Talk about the nail slide.
They must have had some of the hot chili.
The nail slide.
Cafe.
Yes, and...
Listen to that reaction.
You know, the shower of razors and a lot of fun in the funhouse.
Of course, my favorite.
Of course, you know what a funhouse is.
The distorto chamber.
It seems there are some people who have been locked in there since 1944.
A six million year cycle will end in 1944.
1998.
Bob sees the world entering a new aeon, which, in a few years, will bring more wondrous and
miraculous change and carnage, insanity, and destruction than all of mankind's history
and prehistory before it.
Bob brings a new destiny for America.
A time of cataclysmic economic change that will offer untold riches and power for those
in the know.
While billions of deserving people will be left to die.
Plagued with populism, consequences, or even deaths as it'sked.
On the surface, incredible gibtards.
Trn Cameron, star Jim Collins says that the recent
global disaster is yet another one.
...in his delusion.
Eternity will bebour Preparing for savauter Wack.
And ai-
We'r e gonna uhh Though, we're going to drop away from this...
from the dogma for a while.
That is an old classic
subgenius media barrage material,
by the way,
co-produced by myself,
Reverend Ivan Stang,
your host,
and Dr. Bleepo Abernathy,
and I believe Brother Cleve Duncan,
who was at one time
involved in the band.
We're going to continue playing
the Swinging Aeriodites.
This is the Paul McCartney Massacre.
You're going to love it.
This album is crammed with stuff.
A whole lot of it has,
each song has one or two words
that I, because of our dedication
to decency and morality,
and that this is a family show,
that we have to censor
some of those words.
This upcoming material,
I don't think I do,
this is from the Swinging Aeriodites,
and before I forget,
why don't I give you their address
so you can write for information
on procuring the amazing music
by these guys,
or tell your record store
to write them,
because they need,
all the support they can get
in this part of the country.
They're well known in New York,
L.A., Boston, and so forth,
but down here,
it takes a little longer,
and that's
Swinging Aeriodites
at P.O. Box
in Northampton, Massachusetts.
Yeah.
No.
And this is,
I mean,
you can't,
this,
I'm sorry,
I'm sorry for what we're doing to music
in the name of the Aeriodites,
but,
but I'm glad,
I'm glad if it hurts you.
I'm so glad,
and those of you who it most hurt
should listen closest to the lyrics here.
Thank y'all.
You think that people would have had it up
before McCartney?
I look around me and I see
that this is so
Oh no.
It's Yoko.
Some people wanna rid the world
of Paul McCartney.
What's wrong with that?
We'd like to know.
So here we go.
Oh girl.
Yeah
Oh.
Yesterday
All my troubles seemed so far away
Now I need a place to hide away
I believe in yesterday
Suddenly there's a hand overshadowing me
Pretty rubble standing next to me
I believe in yesterday
Why she had to go
I don't know
She wouldn't say
I said
Something
Wrong
Now I long
For yesterday
Yesterday
Yesterday all my troubles seemed so far away
Now I need a place just to hide away
I said something wrong
Now I look for yesterday
Oh yeah
Yesterday
We were in the studio
Someone said play
Yesterday
It wasn't yesterday
It was rock lobster
Oh yeah
There goes Ringo
Yesterday
Because he's got so many rings
And here comes Linda
She's a dog with wings
Down
I'm really down
Wow
Picture yourself killing time in the studio
Trying to pad this line
I'm gonna make this record
Two LP size
Suddenly someone says you're out of money
Did I mention Van Allwhite's thighs
Yesterday
All my troubles seemed so far away
Now I need a place to hide away
Oh I figured
That yesterday
Oh yeah
Say hoje
Oh God
Oh man
Great
religious broadcast and then sounded like the most blasphemous, heretical, evil, satanic thing.
And then suddenly it's rock and roll. And suddenly it's, it's, uh, I mean,
imagine what they think. And I will, I will lower myself to clarifying a couple of things.
Number one, the church of the subgenius is not satanic. Uh, we do occasionally make minor
financial arrangements with lesser demonic entities. Uh, only our guru, Bob Dobbs,
makes deals with Satan, but he's not friends. And the only reason he does that is because Satan
owes both Bob and his buddy, the fighting Jesus, quite a bit of, uh, what you might call money.
Uh, souls actually is the commodity used. Uh, J.R. Bob Dobbs is an old drinking buddy of the
fighting Jesus. Uh, Bob has instructed us that, uh,
that, uh, most everything Jesus said was really cool considering this. It's a, it's a bit dated.
I mean, you know, but relax friends in your own delusions, pull the wool over your own eyes.
Place to hide and reach your confusion.
Faith makes you whole.
We will save you from the evil of Satan.
We will save you from the clutches of the conspiracy.
We will save you from the chains of time.
We will save you from the men in black.
Because every subgenius must have Slap Prey, Bob.
Yes. Dear friends, we are praising Bob real hard tonight and praise the fighting Jesus too.
What the heck? It's just the fan clubs of the fight Jesus that make us mad sometimes.
And, uh, see,
See, we're just not as forgiving.
You know, Bob isn't as well-connected as Jesus or any of the other G's I.
There's so many of them running around nowadays.
But there's only one true Bob, friends.
Let me hear you say it.
Hey, Bob.
Oh, hey, Bob.
Uncontrolled thinking, controlled by Bob,
will usher in a spiritual rebrand
from a cascade of astounding mysteries,
supernatural bridges,
and a restoration of lost psychic abilities
that will transform the lives of those who dare to seek them and pay for them.
That's right.
You're lucky to live in the end time.
Here's my money, Bob.
The mile is 666.
Anybody knows that?
Oh, but actually it's 999, friends.
Bob's number is 999.
He's not the Antichrist.
He's not Christ either.
He's more like the Anti-Antichrist.
Whatever the heck that means, we just have to trust in Bob and have faith.
Faith is what it's all about, just like with your other religions.
Unquestioning faith.
We don't need to know why or wherefore or where the proof came from.
Bob said it.
I believe it.
That settles it.
Remember the motto.
Perform the salute.
Yeah.
I slack off and study the pamphlet.
And you can get those pamphlets, friends, by writing for information.
Free information from...
Got that pencil ready?
We'll try to give it again at the end.
Bob, there's a pipe in the sky, friends.
And you'll follow it anywhere, especially to P.O. Box.
807 Glen Rose, Texas.
76043.
Subgenius.com.
There is a pipe in the sky and it follows you everywhere, dear friend.
Are you gonna be ready to dive into Bob's pipe like a pinch of his frock and rise on
the smoke up to the escape saucers of the sex goddesses on X-Day 1998?
Or are you gonna be left behind?
Like the rest of the unbelievers, frying, frying in a hell of your own making.
...for the time in the end.
This randomness that finds all our colors in the air.
But before I go any further, I do have to give a, um, a little bit of a, uh, well, actually,
let's just, let's just, uh, calm down here for a second and put on some music.
Let's put on some more, oh, what kind of pleasant music here.
We Killed Elvis by the Epstein Brothers.
That ought to be good background for this little announcement here.
Ha.
You are a slack fan, so love this one.
It's doggy dip in garland time again.
Yes, it's time again to begin dipping your dog and my dog too.
Pesticide dips and baths for all dogs, uh, no cats please, to help get rid of a pesty,
fleas, and ticks.
Which can carry, uh, pretty serious, uh, diseases.
Some of them designed by our own defense department.
Uh, this happens, uh, these are like, uh, uh, special dip deals.
Uh, I believe it's a free, free dog dips.
And the reason why is, you know, you gotta get an early jump on those little, uh, arachnid-toid
fleas and ticks.
Ticks!
Shoot those ticks down, man.
They come in, let's, oh, oh, it's so fun to hear them pop.
When you put the match head on them.
But you understand.
You know, it's hard to, it's hard to know sometimes where to take the show.
It becomes so ugly and frightening, even for us.
The challenge of trying to, to save the unsavable, to find the unfindable cassettes, sometimes
drives us to use bits and pieces of actually, this whole show is composed of bits and pieces
of other subgenius shows.
Uh, however, the one I'm about to play is the probably most original of them all.
KPFA, Berkley, uh, excerpts here from more than an hour, less than a show.
Dr. Howell, Puzzling Evidence, Mobius Rex, Gary Grogfran, Lies, and Glass Madness sometimes.
And even more.
And even once in a while, me, me.
All right, all right, we'll be quiet.
Okay, everybody, keep it down.
The show wife hates the show.
There has to be a show wife hating the show.
Full voice effect can't be, uh, yeah.
Oh, there it goes.
I'm gonna show show wife my show thing.
Now who has unbuckled my buckling and unsnapped my shield?
He's doing that buckly buckling for the engine.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, he really likes that.
Yeah, well, I like to get out my bullwhip and, uh, just remove that buckle if it's got a badge attached to it.
Buck naked before Bob.
What? Naked before who?
I don't wanna be that. I don't wanna be that guy.
The buck passeth not.
Yes, it's possible someone was naked before Bob.
The buck is Bob.
Could be, you know, could have been.
As a philosophical thing, could have been, I guess.
Who is thing that you...
And why is he allowed to talk twice as fast as me?
I don't know.
Because you had too much show error, Gary.
And so did I.
It sure felt good.
How can you keep talking like that? I have noticed that you just...
It's beautiful. It's like poetry.
This? Yes. It's a constant.
It's like an isosceles triangle stacked onto...
Plank's number.
Wow, that's pretty good.
That's pretty scientific.
Well, how do you kill it?
Do you just, uh, like, plug it in?
Or do you reduce its potentiometer level to the minus 18th power?
Oh, it is still there. You just hand it over to Sid and he'll...
You gotta be able to pull yourself together pretty soon.
And now it's time for the show to be itself.
You wish, buddy.
How right he is.
Go on, show. Let your hair down.
Yeah, this show is self.
Take your pants off. Shake your shoes out. Take it easy.
Yeah, shake your booties.
Yeah, lean back and just, uh, ride with the slack.
Surf that bug plane.
Climb onto the slack wagon.
That magic surfboard of Bob.
Oh, God, it's messy in here.
God, my pants are getting all wet.
I guess I just get too excited around the show or something.
I don't know. Why are we doing this in an ice skating rink?
This is terrible. It's cold in here. It's cold, yeah.
These skates don't really fit.
But it's got the best snack bar for miles of water.
My feet hurt.
I don't know if I want to be here anymore.
Well, take those skates out of me. You've got them on upside down.
Oh, that's why they hurt.
When did we run up the show?
Is it like... last time...
What show? What?
We didn't get to run up the show until half an hour after we finished.
Oh, yeah.
By then, it had gotten kind of stale. It wasn't as good anymore.
I don't know how to explain that exactly.
Well, friends, I don't know if I really want to, uh,
to expose my audience as to what happens after the show is, uh,
and what is actually done with the souls of the listeners afterwards,
of which we collect here on the ends of the microphone in these special condensers.
Actually, it's not the microphone.
It's like a bounce back from your speakers that goes back to the transmitter
and then is mailed to the church.
Once again, at B.O. Box 14306, Dallas, Texas, 75214.
And you can also get information about, um...
Well, actually, actually,
friends, it's almost time for us to go.
I'm gonna play one more Swingin' Erudite song pretty quick here to get us out
and sort of, uh, transfer the Slack awareness over to, uh,
Robert Wisdom's show, American Music Party.
I had meant originally to start on this show this new little...
a department, a new department of the Hour of Slack,
which we will start next week, reading from the, uh, book,
High Weirdness by Mail, which tells you where to get the weirdest stuff,
from the weirdest groups, uh, under the categories of weird science,
UFO contactees, Jesus contactees,
even weirder religions than our own or yours,
uh, health and self-improvement scams,
new age saps, cosmic hippie stuff,
great catalogs, uh, and weird politics,
funny clubs, weird art, comics,
sleaze and rudeness,
and of course, the cassette revolution in independent music,
and so forth.
We'll read like one selection per chapter or per show
and tell you the addresses of where to write for free information
from these amazingly either brilliant or completely insane people.
Thank you so much for bearing with...
the truth...
and the fragments of it that hurt so bad.
On the Hour of Slack.
Thank you all.
And this is the swinging area that's coming right...
coming right...
I met him at the candy store
The first hit was free
Yeah, we get the picture
That's how I got hooked by the dealer of the crack
He lit the pipe and what did I do?
Do, do, do
I talked to Jesus and all of his crew
His motley crew
Little then did I suspect
In twenty minutes I'd be a wreck
Thanks for the craving
The dealer of the crack
I saw all those corny ads on TV
The blue tube
But what did they mean to a nice girl like me?
Not Jack
My parents said take care of yourself
But they're always wrong about everything else
That's how I got hooked by the dealer of the crack
They kept saying don't be pushed over and over, man
Till I pushed my TV set out the window
It just increases my paranoia, man
Lookin' in my mirror and seein' a police car
I mean, I'm gettin' better
Thank you, David Crosby
No charge, you...
I felt so helpless, what could I do?
Sell blood
I pawned mom's purse and her wedding rings, too
To the house of correction
I could run a three minute mile
Just to get my hands on that little brown vial
You made me a track star, the dealer of the crack
I saw all those corny ads on TV
But what did they mean to a nice girl like me?
Not Jack
My parents said take care of yourself
But they're always wrong about everything else
That's how I got hooked by the dealer of the crack
They kept saying don't be pushed over and over again
To the house of correction
To the dealer of the crack
Like, wow, like I met like the most awesome
Celebrities here at this hospital, you know
I'm a little campier
Like I met Dee Dee Nicks and Richard Pryor
And like Kimmy Baker, like she's really cool, you know
And like she had me some really neat makeup
And uh, Jerry Lee Lewis
And like Boyer Zero, a lot of chicken goin' on there
And uh, and Julie from the Love Boat
And uh, she's not a perky anymore
But like, other people are like really cool
And like, now I feel like one of them, you know
And like thanks to you, dealer of the crack
Like, I'm a celebrity too
And now the people of South Africa would like to thank Paul Simon for his efforts
Okay boys and girls
One, two, three, ah!
Ohhhh
Hello darkness, my old friend
I've come to talk with you again
Ohhhh
Because a vision's a black ribbon
Left in peace
Ohhhh