I've done far worse than kill you.
I've hurt you.
And I wish to go on hurting you.
What?
For earth's sake.
Yes, I know.
What time is it?
I wonder exactly in a temporary way.
Can we really understand time?
Of course you can, kids.
And here's the easiest way you can.
Just pull those gentle, gentle, tender flaps apart
and sit down quietly between your own knees
and just begin.
That's right.
Be brave and time to the music.
Go.
Well, we've asked everybody here
if they've got a special request
for each and every one of you here.
God have given
bad, bad hit.
The devil have gone far enough.
Prayer warrior.
Meet me on my knees.
On your knees, Friday night
at 7.30.
And listen now, my friends,
the prayer tower is open.
The prayer tower is open right now.
You that need prayer.
My God.
The prayer team
is here on the telephone.
Right now.
The prayer team.
What the hell is that?
Light your prop.
Light the fantastic bag.
Well, welcome to the hour of slack.
Praise Bob Gold and Connie Drag.
Yes, welcome to the hour of slack.
I have no time to make a show of loving kindness
before my fellow men.
Not in this life.
I've too much laughing to do.
Hurrah!
This goes to show.
What is with meaning?
You know what I mean?
Meaning is so relative.
What is reality?
What?
Yeah.
What is reality?
You know what you...
What?
I don't get it.
What is reality?
See, we can make people trip
right on the air
on various toxic substances
by bacterial agents.
And some of them only charge 15%.
Reality is what doesn't go away
when dot, dot, dot.
But let's leave things of this world behind
and walk now down the path of Bob
for this brief minute of slack
from the church of the subgenius.
This so-called civilization?
On the day when we finally realize
that things are all backwards
and we have slack without work
in the promised kingdom of Bob Dobbs,
then perhaps we'll find the true civilization
which needs not Xerox machines
nor fancy coats and ties.
It don't have to happen.
It can have them.
You can be civilized
and not live in a cave.
But you're probably going to be more civilized
being one of these characters
that sits in a cave
scratching his butt
than you are running around
on this treadmill of false slack.
Ah, yes.
And look at the humans
lined up for the slaughterhouse.
Ah, yes.
The harvest.
Praise Bob.
Let there be slack.
I'm just an American boy
Raised on MTV
And I seen all the kids
in the soda pop-ups
But none of them look like me
So I started looking around
For a light out of the dim
And the first thing I heard
that made sense
was the sound of a gun
Where the Muhammad
Peace be upon him
I shot and threw
La-yi-la-ha-yi-la-ha-la
There's no God but God
If my daddy could see me now
Chains around my feet
He don't understand
That sometimes a man's got to be
Maya, he's a fighter
He's a fighter
for what he believes
And I believe God is great
All praise due to him
And if I should die
I'd rise up to the sky
Just like Jesus
Peace be upon him
I shot and threw
La-yi-la-ha-yi-la-ha-la-a-ha
There's no God but God
guitar solo
We came to fight the jihad
And our hearts were pure and strong
And death befall
There we all offered the present
Prepared for our martyrdom
But I lost some of the plan
Some secret not revealed
Now they're dragging me back
With my head in the sand
To the land of the infidels
I shunned them
Now they're dragging me back
Layla, layla, la
As I do
I shunned them
Now they're dragging me back
To the land of the infidels
I shunned them
And death befall
There we all offered the present
And our hearts were pure and strong
We came to fight the jihad
Yeah they lined the road
And burned them down
and turned them against our guard
So that when you turn down
your mission
It will be long and long
Yeah they burned them down
yeah they burned them down
That's like a dream
Yeah they burned them down
And they burned them down
John Walker's Blues
by
Steve Earle from an album called Jerusalem.
Thanks to Dr. Legume for DCCing that to me.
Later in the show, friends, we'll hear Dr. Legume's stirring sermon at the Akron Devival.
Also, this show, number 857, is interwoven with collage cut-ups by Fernanda Nande-Lemur
and some clips posted by Reverend Tesla Coyle.
And, of course, ESO Swamp Radio from WCSB Cleveland with Lonesome Cowboy Dave
and host Charles Smith, as seen here.
What's going on in the world? I don't even know anymore.
Oh, drug dealer fight.
Would you know if this is a bad omen?
What happened in the last few days?
Well, they're bombing Iraq, but they're not supposed to let everybody know it.
I mean, in America, nobody's supposed to know about it. Everybody else knows about it.
They're already doing it?
Yeah, they're just doing it.
Just like go blow up somebody's swimming pool.
Just in time for the election.
Yeah, all that.
This just came out. The government, Washington, D.C., the government is preparing to invoke special powers
to help fight armed terrorist groups in the U.S., including measures that will require people
in parts of the U.S. to register, obtain permission to travel, and carry I.D. cards.
The so-called rehabilitation zones.
Debt cards.
Which will include parts of between 14 to 32 states are allowed.
Under a presidential decree issued September 10th that also permits security forces to conduct warranties.
Warrantless searches.
And hold suspects for months before consulting a judge.
And they can also hold the parts between their knees that are connected there.
In the zones, the government can require all residents to register with civilian authorities,
restrict travel, impose curfews, and issue special identification cards to local residents, the decree says.
Residents of areas where identification cards have been issued can be detained for up to 24 hours for not carrying the cards.
A military commander from the North American Command in each zone can collect information about where residents live,
what vehicles they use and jobs they work at, as well as who has permits to carry guns.
Do you remember the old days staying with the Wells Fargo guys and the other, what was the other one?
The dicks, you know, the private dicks.
There was Wells Fargo.
What was the other one with impunity?
They can't do that.
They could go around killing people for screwing up capitalism in the West.
Now get this.
Government officials could not be reached to comment on the plans,
but Attorney General John Ashcroft said that the powers granted to the state were soft.
When the decision is made to create a zone,
it is because we are facing the probability that something very serious is about to happen.
Right, fascism is going to take over.
To the civilian population.
Yeah, right.
There are new procedures which are being studied that we can use.
Not everyone.
Not everywhere, but specifically where we need them to protect civilians and attack terrorists.
Well, I think that's amazing that he was so psychic to know what's going to happen to us,
and yet he didn't know on 9-11-10th of September.
Now, I did get this off the internet on S-News by New Monet.
But that is a true thing, because I know I read it in the Payne-Dealer.
Yeah, I read it on the internet, and you're hearing it now on the radio.
So, I mean, it must be as true as anything else you hear on the radio or read on the news or the internet.
I'm more disturbed by what I...
I'm more disturbed by a science article I was reading.
What did it say, James?
Well, it was just talking about that we need to start opening our minds to the possible fact that the universe stinks.
And all the bubbles of universes that they...
That they think exist.
Are a fart bubble of God.
No, they're just because we think them.
Oh, man.
Yeah.
The eye in the pyramid's right in our own navel.
That works real well until you stub your toe.
Yeah, right.
And then all of a sudden you're not just thinking.
Until you don't wake up while somebody's stealing your van.
Your toe really, really hurts.
When you smell... you forget to smell the smoke.
Because we see them. Because we observe them.
Oh, yeah, so we're just...
They exist because we observe them.
We're just lackluster, dullardly observers.
Yeah.
Oh, well, if that's the case, Professor,
why don't you go into that briar patch and get my kid's ball?
Briar stang.
You're just imagining that briar patch.
No, you see the briar patch.
There is no spoon.
So it's there. It's there because you see it.
Or if anybody sees it, it's there.
You see the briar patch, but you don't see the thorns.
That makes sense.
If anybody sees it, it's there.
You're floating in a sea of briar patches.
You just can't feel the...
It's there.
You can't make the complex simple because it's complex.
And you can't make slack complex because it is simple.
And that's why we're trying to...
We're just trying to kind of cut through the bullshit, if we can, friends,
and try to figure out for ourselves what slack really is.
Yeah.
But it really, really...
And what we've been able to find...
I've been in this business for 20 years,
and you know what I've found out?
Not a goddamn thing.
I've learned how ignorant I am.
I've learned how stupid I am.
I've learned how I don't know.
And the best part is,
I don't have to know.
I don't have to know why the universe was created.
I don't have to know how it was created.
I don't have to know where I'm going to go when I die.
I don't have to know anything.
Because who said I was so fucking important
that I...
deserve to know. Maybe it's better if the Loch Ness Monster is never captured. Maybe
it's better if nobody ever shoots and stuffs a Bigfoot. Maybe it's better if the aliens
never land. Because friends, wouldn't it be kind of boring to find out? Wouldn't it be
terrible if all the mysteries were gone? Ah yes friends, the mysteries. The mysteries
are shit that can't be explained. That's what's important. The stuff inside, the music
that makes you feel good. I know people who were saved by Jesus when they went to see
the movie Jesus Christ Superstar. And then it was only years later that when they were
listening to the Rolling Stones that they realized that it wasn't Jesus inside them,
it was the rock and roll that they felt that would put that spirit in their hearts.
And it doesn't have to be Jesus. It doesn't even have to be Bob. It doesn't have to be
whatever your favorite drug is or your favorite personal savior. Because as we've learned
from Bob Dog time after time, we can't depend on invisible monsters up in the sky to answer
our prayers. And we can't trust aliens to come down from earth to save us. We can't
even believe in pipe smoking, get rich quick stuff.
We can't even believe in skiing smiling smiley faces of the 90's friends. I just believe
in me. Yoko and me. That's reality. And friend I suggest you take the same approach. Bob
is not the answer and neither is anything else. And in this church, in closing friends,
to bring this so that you can finally quit listening to somebody lecture you and start
getting back to the truth slide.
A very important message.
I'm not going to leave you with one thought. And it's the one rule, the one law of the
church of the subgenius. The only thing in the whole god damn book. All of these books.
The one valid statement that Bob said that you can live by. And here it is friends. Fuck
them if they can't take a joke. That's his voice. Fuck them if they can't take a joke.
That's his voice. Fuck them if they can't take a joke. That's his voice. Fuck them
if they're going to take a joke.
And you have to show it. God wants you to reveal your truth. You will not be far, you
will be far, just stay. Fuck them, fuck them if they can't take a joke. telling me if you
can't take a joke. In praise. We love you. God loves you. God wants you. All he wants
is to make sure you know him. God wants you. Doing evil for you. Those Christ people who
always would penelop, all shower in penetrate the Lord Jesus님,Lord Jesus you're born, living
here with him. All he wants is. Get out from here. check if all reason is to leave you out.
There's your money.
The Reverend Ivin Starrer!
Ladies and gentlemen, give him your money!
Come on up, give him your money!
He's gonna scream you!
Oh, damn!
B.O.B.
One, one dollar.
One dollar, one, one dollar.
B.O.B.
Remix number two by Dr. Onan's Wotan Band.
And before that, my sermon,
backed by Einstein's Secret Orchestra
at the Blind Lemon Club DeVival in Cleveland last year.
And speaking of last year, friends,
the world ends tomorrow!
We might all be killed.
There's a reason for that.
You see how those gears are slanted?
Right there.
Here.
There.
You can stylize snakes for breakfast.
And it was a very eerie experience.
Yes.
This is our crack.
Now it's on.
Running along the top of the muscles
and all of that was torn loose.
It's so wonderful.
You're considered benevolent in that part of the world.
The ice is right there.
Here.
There it is.
All right.
Look at that.
Just like that.
Just that.
Because it's plastic.
You've got the red dot in here
because it's so wonderful.
I'm going to get it for you.
And we were going around
and didn't even think we liked each other too much.
Well, you know what?
I don't have a clue.
$140.
The end times are near.
Hello, Mom.
Hello, monsters are born.
Did the end times come yet?
Are we incarcerated?
Are we dead?
Come here.
Or are we just thinking of a new way of living?
Look at this beautiful Bel Air mansion.
Made from stucco and cocoa and filled with your favorite 325 kids.
Some of them have their asses dangling from the cactus in the backyard.
But you're a cowboy dad and you're ready for this new century.
Let's go home.
Woo-hoo!
Oh, that's nasty.
Let's go and bomb with the president.
Woo-hoo!
Now that better do that again.
Bomb.
Let's go do some drugs.
Legal drugs, that is.
Woo-hoo!
Hey, let's put on a thing of those furry monkey pants and dance for the guy with the
grinding his organ over there against the telephone pole.
It's disgusting.
Of course it's disgusting.
We don't know why you do that.
You've got to know what you're getting into.
Uh-oh.
Come with me.
Walcott the
Seeker is going to get mad.
You just don't understand it.
Bye now.
What is the meaning of this?
You'll be reborn now, you hear?
What is the meaning of death in the cycle of rebirth?
What is the meaning of the tender, tiny thread
that extends from the flap below the reptile's eye
deep into the womb of nature itself?
Mama?
There's a seeker born every minute.
Well, as far as our scientists have been able to determine,
the purpose of life is, in fact, simply to squirt,
or in the case of some creatures, to ooze.
Ah, squirting and ooze.
An ooze squirt.
Yes, that's it.
There's no high, lofty meaning of life.
It is simply to...
Squirt and ooze.
Yes, and not for the procreation aspects,
just for the pleasure.
The mere ejaculation.
Yes, that's just the...
Vibration.
That's it.
Banging the nervous system ever so gently.
Yes, if you're looking for a meaning, there it is.
Doesn't matter whether it's by yourself or with somebody else.
It's just...
That's it.
You could just take a walk out into your neighborhood any day
and get on a bus and get that same sensation
as you ride over them old potholes.
You know, life ain't much more than a oozing and a squirting
and a kind of a dangerous feeling coming up the back of your neck.
Oh, I'm gonna rub my little round belly.
Things are growing up there now.
They're growing now.
They're like bad thoughts, you know.
They're just hanging to the top of your head
and they can't get out.
And they got to find a way out someday.
Oh, I can't wait to have Bob rub my little round belly
over at that rabbit supper tonight.
Oh, he's gonna rub you like the boot is belly.
He's gonna create more slack out of the top of your head
than you ever should.
Hey, old Bob, he's a boatie shot for.
He's a fully realized enlightened being.
He's gonna be at that squirrel supper tonight.
You gonna be there, Benny?
Hey, look, he's eating barbecued chicken.
And I never know, boatie shot for enjoyed meat that way.
I mean, you know, that way.
Oh, hell, you know, him and Bob go way back.
I threw up.
It's hard to pull it out of your moon pants.
Tease you just to let it go out in front.
Is that you going through?
There must be.
Now, why in the world would I be going there,
that the dog.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I kidnapped the future and ransomed it for the past.
I made time wait up for me to bleed my lizard.
My infernal breath wills the tree of life.
I left my sword on the rock of ages, who will tear flesh with me, who will spill their juice?
Who'll gout with me, whose candle will I fart out?
Good. I'm ready. So step aside, all you but loot, neurotic, insecure bespectacled slavs oh wink meat.
I'm a crime fighting master criminal, I am not insane. I'm a screamer and a laugher,
I make a spectacle of myself, I am a sight. My physical type cannot be classified by science,
my familiar is a pterodactyl, I feed it to feagles.
This is the one.
This is the two.
This is three.
This is four.
The Branflex, from TheBranflex.com
Before that, some Brag of the Subgenius Bobfoolery
by me and Philo.
and now, well, soon actually,
a classic live recording of a Jurassic song
by the Swingin' Love Corpses.
But first, heart ignition.
Heart, heart, heart, heart.
What's that noise?
Swag.
You've got to be fucking kidding me.
Name the killer.
Bulb.
Swag.
What's that noise?
And I'm testable.
Swag.
Well, it's been a while since time began
That struggle against nature, forcing nature against man
Tectonic play, movement of simple quicksand
Nature has the power, nature has the upper hand
Nature!
I hate it!
Well, the forces of nature come in many degrees
Maybe a forest fire, plague or killer bees
Maybe an earthquake or maybe typhoon
Tornadoes, volcanoes, rains will come soon
Nature!
I hate it!
Give a baby's dioxide
Blue go in
Wipe out a whole species
How does that make you feel?
Guard your hole in the earth
Fill that hole with plastic
The way we do it, we do it the way we do it
We treat our planet better than men
Oh!
guitar solo
solo
Well I wouldn't find nature
If I had my druthers
Wish I could control
the action of others
Solo
solo
We should love nature as one of our brothers.
Don't you know it's not nice to do your mother?
Nature!
I hate it!
Don't love it!
Nature!
Come on!
I don't want to get off the stage.
Who told me to get off the stage?
Am I just paranoid?
Nature!
I hate it!
The Swingin' Love Corps is live in St. Louis, 1991.
And now, from the Akron Devival this summer,
Dr. Katahdin Lagune,
who starts his sermon by reading a suicide note.
A suicide note? Is it mine?
Get it back!
Man, I found this suicide note.
It was from a young teenage girl.
At least from the content, I'm assuming it was a teenage girl.
It says here,
I'm tired of the pain in my heart.
You are all so unfair to me.
You don't love me and you don't understand me.
Everyone hates me because I'm fat and ugly.
The only thing I ever wanted was to be with Patrick.
But I found out he was at the mall with that slut Michelle.
And I hope they'll all feel bad when I'm gone.
But tough.
I tried to talk to you about it, Mom.
But you was more interested in your soap operas than my real problems.
So I'm not going to bother any of you anymore.
And I hope Patrick is real happy.
At the mall with his slut.
You're going so far, you!
I hope you're all happy now.
Goodbye.
What a stupid little bitch.
Fucking shit, yeah.
The very idea of offing yourself because of some stupid little problem like that
makes me think, well, what is a problem that's worthy of killing yourself?
And it reminded me.
It reminded me of when I was a child.
When I was a child, I grew up in a town called Mansfield, New Jersey.
And out on Route 206, which cuts right through Mansfield, New Jersey,
there's a farmer's market.
It's the biggest shop in town.
Everybody goes there.
It's the only reason anybody comes to Mansfield, is to shop at this farmer's market.
But across the street from this farmer's market, there was a junkyard.
Not just any junkyard.
It was an old military junkyard full of crashed World War II planes and trucks and tanks and such.
And it was owned by a man named John Mihaljec.
John Mihaljec had a lot to say.
He had so much to say, that out on Route 206,
down the entire length of his property,
he had these huge billboards with pictures of political figures on them.
They had a picture at the time, it was the 1970s,
there was a picture of President Richard Nixon with the bleeding body of a dead rat.
And there were these long, long ramps that he would put up on these billboards on his property.
And the town hated him.
But he does!
When he drove by, the ramps on the sides were so long and involved,
that the cars would have to slow down to five miles an hour just to read them.
Woo!
Oh yeah, they hated him bad.
So what did John Mihaljec do?
He ran for Senator.
Bloody hell!
That pissed off all the people who hated him even more.
All the townspeople hated him.
One day they said,
We're going to finally take care of this John Mihaljec problem.
So one night, some of the townspeople got together,
in the best tradition of the angry villagers in Frankenstein movies,
they all got their torches together,
and they went down to his property,
and they burned his house to the ground.
Yeah!
Oh, they burned his house to the ground,
but that's not all they did,
because his wife was in the house.
And they killed his wife.
They killed his wife,
and they burned down his house.
And they said,
Finally, we're going to see the end of John Mihaljec,
because no man is going to be able to stand up after something like this.
David Kuras.
John Mihaljec had other ideas.
John Mihaljec,
in the smoking ashes of the ruins of his home,
the smoking ashes of his now dead beloved wife,
built a giant teepee on that spot,
and let everybody know that we're not going to run him off his land.
The townspeople hated it even more.
So one night,
the townspeople,
in the best tradition of the angry villagers in Frankenstein movies,
once again got together,
and they went out to John Mihaljec's land,
and they burned down his teepee.
This, they said,
would run off John Mihaljec.
How much more could one man stand?
He would leave,
he would kill himself,
he would do something,
but he would be out of their hair forever.
John Mihaljec had other ideas.
And so,
on the smoking ruins of his teepee,
built on the smoking ruins of his home and his dead beloved wife,
John Mihaljec built another teepee,
an identical teepee to the first,
but with one small difference.
It was made of steel!
Yeah!
The villagers didn't know what to do about that.
They hated John Mihaljec.
They wanted to run John Mihaljec off his land.
But those stupid motherfuckers never could figure out how to burn down a steel teepee.
And John Mihaljec lived there until he died an old, old man.
Can I get a praise John Mihaljec?
John Mihaljec!
Oh, brothers and sisters,
John Mihaljec found the perfect solution to his problems.
Maybe you have problems too.
Maybe your problems could be solved by giving up or committing suicide.
Probably not.
Well, come to think of it, we probably solved all your problems.
But we're not the kind of a cult that's going to advocate suicide.
We are the first anti-suicide suicide cult.
One day we will all get together and after the point of time we will all drink Kool-Aid.
Then nothing will happen, we'll just drink some Kool-Aid.
You don't lie until we say so.
Yes.
So, I'm sure you have problems too, but I don't think that many of your problems are going to be solved by a big tin teepee.
However,
there is always a solution to your problems.
And only the perfect solution to your problems.
And brothers and sisters,
Bob.
Bob will give you a blueprint.
A blueprint for your perfect teepee of vengeance.
It will help you get over your problems without having to take a hundred Tylenol.
Yeah.
Tom Waits.
Are there any Tom Waits fans here?
Yeah!
Well, I remember there was a song by Tom Waits where he said something about a woman.
She was a crumbling beauty with a tattooed tear on her cheek.
For each year her man was away.
And then Tom Waits said,
Hell, there's nothing wrong with her that a hundred dollars won't fix.
Well, brothers and sisters,
it's even better for all of you.
Because there's nothing wrong with you that thirty dollars won't fix.
Yes, brothers and sisters, because that thirty dollars,
when put in the hands of Bob,
will help deliver unto you the blueprint for your own tin teepee.
That tin teepee will fill that tin teepee-shaped hole in your lives.
Oh yes, brothers and sisters, you may not even have very small problems.
You might have them tiny problems.
Oh yes, but Reverend Stang,
he's here to help you with those problems.
Maybe that hole in your life is shaped like a little bob pin.
Maybe that hole in your life is shaped like a bumper sticker or a t-shirt.
And brothers and sisters,
through Bob's love,
Reverend Stang is here tonight
to fill that t-shirt-shaped hole in your lives, brothers and sisters.
Oh yes, brothers and sisters.
Can I get a praise, Bob?
We're filling CD-shaped holes.
Oh yes, brothers and sisters.
And I saw a lot of you out there tonight
who have CD-shaped holes in your lives
that are just begging to be filled.
And Reverend Stang is here tonight
to help Bob fill your holes.
Can I get a praise, Bob?
Praise Bob!
Many of my victims have joined my unholy legion of the undead,
becoming creatures without souls,
living only for hideous,
torments.
And I think if we continue that way,
to, you know, do what they said to do with porcine beings,
what will happen next?
Well, did you write to your congressman about the pigs?
Of course I did. I did.
I said we would be liberated,
and he said he sent back a hand-memeographed, a Xerox letter.
He sent back a hand-signed letter, I mean,
that said,
Thank you very much, Citizen Dave, for your interest in the porcine.
We're preparing a place for you in the re-education camps.
We have your room number and your keys waiting for you.
And your special hot tub.
And then I wrote a letter back saying,
the pork problem is probably the most,
the biggest problem we have to deal with in these days of post-9-11 surgery.
Well, humanity is in danger of getting thrown out of the cosmic,
you know, tent party,
for crapping in the universal hot tub.
See, you said, yeah, that is true, though.
And not sending in their 30 bucks.
Yeah.
The United States Navy is going to build these things that create sounds,
sounds underwater around 80% of the surface of the oceans,
which will kill all the whales and seals and porpoises,
and nobody's going to stop them because they're the U.S. Navy.
What do you mean, Ghana?
Ghana.
They already,
It's a word we use.
I thought they already did that.
They get the most amazing recordings out of that.
Yeah, the wheels, the whales squealing in agony as the air drums explode.
Now, that is a song.
By the time they're gone, we'll have,
we'll have figured out their language.
Well, yeah, by the time they'll utter their last pained cry of, of, yeah.
Pained cry.
Oh, I'm sure they have vials of whale sperm hidden away somewhere.
Ah, yes.
Long DNA, then short DNA.
Any kind of whale, whale you want.
How about a Moby-Doby?
We've got a blue one.
We've got the oversized white ones.
Those whale incubators, though, are really big.
Yeah.
And whale, but there's a booming business in whale placenta.
Oh, and there's nothing better with a little bit of almond extract.
Whale placenta?
Yeah.
Shaved almonds.
You like to shave your nuts for the whales.
Well, you can get quite a bit from each birth.
Oh, yeah?
From those mighty mammals of the deep, yeah?
So, they're going to give, they're making like little quantsets full of whales.
That's what rich people in Japan are doing, man.
All the, all the really, the rich Japanese people.
Those are the cool, beautiful people.
They bathe in whale fresh, freshly caught whale placenta.
It is so lovely for my skin.
I just wave a little bit of whale oil on my arms, and look.
As smooth as a baby's foot.
And also, look what it's done for my hair.
So, that gets you away from the poo-poo stuff.
Hi.
And back into the menstrual placental.
The plasma part of the beginning.
My favorite place.
The primal mommy.
The original ooze from which it all sprang.
Friends, you and I, each and every one of us with the chromosomes dancing on the backs
of our spines.
Like little egg yolks.
Or like little egg yolks.
And can be no more than individual fried eggs.
And I'm sure you've all been there.
So, live it up as long as you can.
Send your $30 before you're completely cooked.
Do it.
Now.
Do it before your sex differentiates.
While you're still a yolk.
Before the zygote splinters.
Some of us may go in a different direction.
There are X chromosomes.
There are Y chromosomes.
There are now Z chromosomes.
Yes, that's right.
Have your genes outgrown you?
What about the anti-chromosomes?
I don't know.
What about them?
They're here with us.
Holding their hands and closing their eyes and saying the mantra.
Shoop.
The many moods of an alien.
I descended from monochromes.
I ascended from polychromes.
I descended from morochromes.
I am all chromatic activity.
Repeat this to yourself.
Sit down and close your eyes.
Close your eyes, ears, nose and throat.
For this is your good night's sleep.
What?
Insert transition here.
Yeah, right.
Well, I timed it.
I had the guy.
Yeah, I could tell that.
It was a 15 second segue.
Amazing timing.
I laughed so hard.
Sometimes I slow down when I read.
The timing really caught me was the timing.
It was a 15 second segue.
And Stang was supposed to say something kind of laconically funny.
And then you were supposed to say something really silly.
I'm going to sit over here and eat my cupcake.
I'll do all that later.
Okay.
So you'll make it sound like you said something laconically silly.
And then Chaz said something really silly.
And then, no, that's not going to be it.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, whatever.
It doesn't matter.
No.
These people are idiots anyway.
I mean, you put the...
It's not that it's a show farm.
You sew it together like a piece of stew.
You know, I mean, you just flap a shoe in there.
You put some of your own, I don't want to say the other words.
Some of your own...
Some of your own stuff in there.
You just, you know, you don't really care what goes in there because you have no respect
for your subgenia who listen each week.
What in the world are you talking about?
Oh, I'm just saying the way Stang so haphazardly throws his hours of slack together.
First, he takes all the drugs you can take.
Heroin, monochrome, femur, that weird poison from South America.
Well, no, that's how you organize a show.
You do heroin.
As a theme.
And then you pick certain material for the heroin based.
Show.
And then you do a bunch of crack and you pick all the material that goes with that kind
of a...
So you just pretty much live the life, aren't you, man?
You just like come out there and just live it.
You know, and so forth.
Down through...
You don't really care about your...
Nitrous oxide and...
Chromosomes and long jeans and shirt.
That...
God, see, I can't even remember what drugs this show was supposed to be.
You're a loser of your dollars.
Well, yeah.
Then later I got into work and you Эsset divorce for good and then back out to take
Like I said, that's my job.
Ah!
Free drugs in the next minutes.
Now, I'm going to have to go buy theseру
Hmm?
!
it's such a bizarre car," said Jordan Umber
headphone
We're all wired into a survival trip now.
No more of the speed that fueled the 60s.
That was the fatal flaw in Tim Leary's trip.
He crashed around America selling consciousness expansion
without ever giving a thought to the grim, meat-hook realities
that were lying in wait for all those people who took him seriously.
All those pathetically eager acid freaks
who thought they could buy peace and understanding for three bucks a hit.
But their loss and failure is ours too.
What Leary took down with him was the central illusion
of a whole lifestyle that he helped create.
A generation of permanent cripples
failed seekers
who never understood the essential old mystic fallacy of the acid culture.
The desperate assumption
that somebody
or at least some force
is tending the light at the end of the tunnel.
The End
of the World
Not when we think we've lost
So I'm running on my back
I'm gonna take me up with the spirit of the past
I'm gonna set me up with the spirit of the past
Cause when I'm gonna go away, I'm gonna die
And when I'm gone, I'm gonna live in darkness
I'm gonna go to a place that's so rare
Yeah.
I walked my way
But I pass everywhere
So I'm changing, with that
And I put my hands on my side
what they think of me
They close my eyes
I'm gonna go to the place right where I am
Let's go!
Hey, baby!
Adios!
Number, please.
One freeze. One freeze.
Thank you.
Hello?
This is Marlowe.
Why didn't you telephone?
I didn't have a nickel.
Oh. What did you find at the lake?
Shut up and get me my number.
Who's being cute now?
You are.
What?
Did you ever try to pull anybody out of the telephone booth?
Yeah. Muriel Chester and San Bernardino.
What's this, Crystal Kingsman?
I'm coming to that.
Oh. What man?
The guy I didn't know his name.
Oh.
Marlowe, where do you usually spend Christmas Eve?
To the gas station.
On the south road.
Oh.
Where do you?
In Little Fawn Lake.
It's a place in the mountains beyond Arrowhead.
Oh, brother.
Here we are.
How did I get here?
Thirty days in the water.
Luckily a sailor came along.
What's the matter?
There isn't much left of her.
Shut up.
This is Marlowe by Lemur and before that the Broken Circle Gospel Deluxe with Sister Sugar live at the Blind Lemon Divival. They're doing Spirit in the Sky.
Do you think it's alright to ring our land in a ring of iron?
I don't think so.
I'm trying to wind it up here. The road goes on forever.
They're exaggerating the harmfulness of uranium.
It's all been spent.
Or plutonium, whatever that is.
It's spent. I mean, Craig, what can it do if it's spent?
You just squirt it out of your... that tube of yours.
Like any common ejaculating orangutan, it's the used squirt thing, only it's plutonium and it's spent.
Talk about that.
I can see why they call him Lonesome Cowboy.
Cowboy Dave.
Don't get too close, man.
Not Popular Cowboy Dave.
No, don't, don't.
Now that was it. Now, I remember Popular Cowboy Dave.
I say do it.
He was tall. He was rich.
Imposable.
And intelligent.
Christlike.
Popular Cowboy Dave was.
But, well, we're going to have to have a...
That's a good name.
...we're going to have to have a...
Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
That's a good name.
Popular Christlike Dave.
Popular Christlike Stang.
And Popular Christlike Chaz.
And, of course, Popular Christlike Wee, even though she's a female.
Well, there was Popular Bull Girl Davina.
Oh, Popular Bull Girl Davina?
Yeah.
Was she Christlike in her appearance?
No, no.
No, she was just popular.
No, no, no.
Like a lonely traveler in the night.
Yeah.
Well, okay.
You know, that's what happens to some of them when they can't find that spot.
You know?
Yeah.
When they can't reach down there far enough.
That's me, man.
Yeah, me too.
We keep on looking for the itchy, slingy, ooze, squirt mechanism, and it doesn't ever shine.
Speak for yourself, Dave.
I am speaking for myself.
All right.
This is Provine Boy Dave.
Hey, look.
You say Yucca Teas, man.
And you're just deluding yourself.
And I say Yucca Teas?
We're all...
We're all lonesome, lonely stars in the night, lonely lights in the night.
We're just...
We come in alone.
We go out alone.
And you go out alone.
Ships passing in the night, baby.
That's right.
You're putting your hair off in the middle.
That's the bottom line.
You come in alone, you go out alone.
That's why you should spend the night with me, baby.
You squirt sometimes.
To make this loneliness end for just a little while, just you, me, and Bob.
Come on.
What do you say?
Baby, baby.
I'll be Christ-like just for a moment.
But you haven't seen the other cages.
Don't worry, Boris.
We'll get to all of the cages eventually.
But first, you must climb into and then escape the cage of B-B-Bob.
Check out www.subgenius.com or write to me, Reverend Ivan Stang, at P.O.
Box 807, Glen Rose, Texas 76043.
I'm Bob.
I'll see you next time.
Bye.
Study more.
It's a joke.
Not bad, juju.
Pretty fun.
Jonathan went into a manipulation. A man, a dummy, a wooden twilight zone.
Very little guy.
That's insider.
Tush.
The meat is actually not yet sold.
To a foolhardy head.
This program was made possible by the John Foundation.
Bye, everybody.