You are about to experience the awe and mystery which reaches from the inner mind to the subgenius hour of swag.
What were those noises?
Well, here's the recording studio.
Well, let's get out of the traffic.
No way, that's all it was.
The session's about to start.
Foreign matter that happened to wind up in your head.
As we enter, we can hear the last minute instructions.
We can hear the voices of artists, musicians, and engineers coming from the different parts of the room.
Now listen.
You walked in the crash, ran in a car, drove to L.A.
Why?
What a way to invade the earth.
How would you feel if tomorrow a flying saucer would drop a atomic bomb on every city in the United States?
This place is driving me nuts.
You and I are giving out a brain.
That's top secret information.
Nobody knows that.
What is that?
Top 40?
I don't know.
There's a lot of activity over there.
Let's do it.
Oh, sure.
Happy with a khaki sweatband, boat goat pot-bellied barnyard that only he noticed.
The old fart was smart.
The old gold cloth Madonna.
Dancing to the fiddling saw, he ran down behind the knoll and slipped on his wooden fish head.
The mouth worked and snapped all the bees back to the bungalow.
Mama was fattening lard with her red enamel rolling pin.
When the fish head fell, the fish head fell.
The fish head broke the window.
Rubber eye erect and precisely detailed.
Hair holes from which breath should come.
It was now closely fit with the chatter of the old fart inside.
An assortment of observations took place.
Mama licked her lips like a cat.
Packed the ground like a rooster.
Pivoted like a duck.
Her stockings down caught dust and dough balls.
She cracked her mouth.
Glaze caught one eyelash.
Rubbed her hands on her gorgeous gingham.
Her hands grasped.
Sticky hands like a duck.
Sticky metal intricate latchwork.
Opened to the room.
Ugh.
Smell cold mixed with bologna.
Rubber bands, crumpled wax paper bonnets, fat goose legs and special jellies.
Ignited by the warmth of the room, the old fart smelled this through his important breather holes.
Cleverly he dialed from within.
From the outside we observed that the nose of the wooden mask where the holes had been
just a moment ago was now smooth, amazingly blended.
Camouflaged in with a very intricate rainbow trout replica.
The old fart inside was now breathing freely from his perfume bottle atomizer air bulb invention.
His excited eyes from within the dark interior glazed.
Watered in appreciation of his thoughtful preparation.
Oh man, that's so heavy.
And he was just like a little baby.
There he comes.
And it's time for us to go.
Alright, we'll see you later.
See you next week.
Just the show.
Yeah, I know.
Unfortunately, there are many people at KPFA who have been here 5, 10, 15, 20 years.
From now on we'll stay on the air continuously until this crisis is over.
And no one leaves.
We now resume our regularly scheduled program.
Everybody say, hold on to each other and say, praise Bob!
Praise Bob!
I don't hear that! Say that again and say it like you've got a pair!
And all the children are in sin.
Watch out! Someone's coming!
Quick, hide behind the throne.
Hey, Mo, can you see anything?
Not yet. Wait a minute. There's a man coming.
He looks like a king.
A king? Oh, good. Kings are smart.
Maybe he can tell us how to get home.
Uh, sorry, Curly Joe, but I won't tell you how to get home
unless you're a king.
Unless you're willing to go home to Bob.
Yes, yes, yes.
Friends, a small taste there of the 10,000 great new tapes
that have come in since the last show we did.
Including, by the way, a Trout Mask replica live.
Yes, that was Captain Beefheart in a rare bootleg live recording
from 1978, I believe, live at my father's place.
You won't be hearing that one all the time on your local radio station.
And a wonderful little opening barrage there by Puzzling Evidence.
Oh, but friends, you know something?
I need more me's!
That's right.
I need one to do 500-hour of Slack radio ministries
and work on the subsequent CDs.
I need one to preach on all the preaching tours.
I need one to do the internet.
One to do the Stark Fiddlesticks.
One to do this church magazine.
One to work on the CD-ROM game
and about three to do business.
And one to be a secretary.
And one to be a good dad.
And one to service all of the church groupies.
But, you know, more me's isn't really the problem.
The problem is they all have to work for free.
And if they were me's, they'd all be fighting with each other.
In a way, they already are.
The radio me was the low man
on the totem pole lately.
But I had to take him out of mothballs for this show, friends.
Yes, yes, this one show is hour of Slack number 500.
Can you believe it?
500 hours of Slack.
Not devival, nor internet, nor jobs,
nor months of debilitating sickness
will stay our blabbering mouths.
Friends, even if all those debilitating diseases
affect our minds,
we'll still be able to keep our mouths.
So let's lean back and enjoy this lovely, lovely
hour of Slack number 500 commemorative hymn
by the great subgenius, radio subgenius up there
in Portland, Maine.
Dad and the Seventh Day Opportunists.
Oh, yes.
, I'm a radio subgenius.
Well, there's a great old show on the radio,
and it's called the hour of Slack.
It's been on the air since like 85,
man, you'd think the host would crack.
He goes by the name of Reverend Ivan Stank.
He's a rants-fueling creature for Bob.
And if it worked for the show on the radio,
he just might have a conspiracy job.
Well, I've got one hundred two,
three hundred, three hundred, four hundred,
five hundred hours of Slack.
And if it worked for the fact that I got them for free,
I'd probably ask for my money back.
If I played them all like back to back,
it'd probably take me about three weeks.
I'm talking 24 hours for 21 days without a sick break
or taking leaps.
I hear all about the word of Bob
and the church of the subgenius.
And Connie and Jinger and KPFA
and all kinds of really weird stuff.
Well, I've got one hundred two,
hundred three,
hundred four,
hundred five,
hundred hours of Slack.
And if it worked for the fact that I got them for free,
I'd probably ask for my money back.
Well, five hundred shows in ten or so years
is a whole lot of radio.
But on the fifth of July, 1998,
they say the whole thing's gonna blow.
And when they take me up on those play-ships
and they pass out the bags of the prop,
I sure hope they claim them old-hour Slack tapes
so we can listen to them all the time.
Now, what's the matter?
Oh, I'm sick and I need a check.
We all know that fire loves me
Get up the next day and get up the second orange Heppi
out of the voit,
and get up the next day and get up the second orange Heppi
2100, 2200, 2300, 2400, 2500 hours of the slide.
2600, 2700, 2800, 2900, 3000 hours of the slide.
3100, 3200, 3300, 3400, 3500 hours of the slide.
3600, 3700, 3800, 3900, 4000 hours of the slide.
4100, 4200, 4300, 4100, 4500 hours of the slide.
4600, 4700, 4800, 4900, 5000 hours of the slide.
The nerves are starting to crawl.
Therange EVERYWHERE
THOMAS MORTON
PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED STATES
CHRIS unfinished
Lами
You wouldn't believe me.
Your nerves are starting to crawl.
Look, I know you're awake.
I want to apologize.
Or at least I thought I did.
How do you like that?
You don't care?
You've got to believe me.
Pardon me while I cry.
I don't see nothing funny.
Maybe I better slap your face.
You know what I mean?
Now wait a minute.
There have been a lot of mistakes made.
And we're going to do something about it.
But I'm not going to go back without heads dropping in chickens.
I mean it.
I'm already in trouble.
A couple of hours here, a couple of hours there.
Feels good.
Thank you, Time Master.
Who said that?
Hey, Ray?
I've got to talk to you.
I get the feeling there's a message here.
I'll get back to you.
Cool it.
What do you got on your mind?
I'm sure you have a dandy reason for being here.
So look.
You're looking me straight in the eye again, and that means you're lying.
What are you trying to do to me?
Cool it.
Stop trying to help me and mind your own business, huh?
Look, I've got to have the money.
One for you and one for me.
It might take a whole day.
You don't know the half of it.
Pardon me while I cry.
Hey!
Oops.
Too much.
Well, do it again.
Wait a minute.
Something's not kosher here.
Oh, now I get it.
My feet hurt.
I think I'm seeing things, too.
What does that mean?
Everybody has weaknesses,
and that means you are going to have
weakness problems.
Me?
You've got to be kidding me.
Who's got problems?
Have you?
Okay, then. Maybe not.
A gag on Spanish rice?
Yeah, I'm loving every minute of it.
Let her rip!
How do you like that?
Is that good?
Hey, how do you keep from frying your tonsils?
I don't like to sound like I'm bragging,
but I'm not bragging.
I almost got killed.
I don't want to go through it again.
Your nerves are starting to crawl.
What?
I never give up.
Do you think this is art?
I thought it was a gag.
Well, you wouldn't believe me.
I'm not a gay.
You wouldn't believe me.
Your nerves are starting to crawl.
There's no sense in going on.
Thank you, Thighmaster.
Well, thank you.
As soon as I'm finished, I'm getting out of here.
Thank you, Thighmaster.
Oh, knock it off, will ya?
What are you trying to do to me?
Why don't you tell me the truth?
Your nerves are starting to crawl.
What do you think you're doing?
I'm not giving you the satisfaction of kicking me out.
I oughta break you in half.
You just want to admit there's another side.
My side.
This whole thing is ridiculous.
Better watch those.
Speak up, baby.
Are you telling me you don't love me?
No, what the hell are you talking about?
Huh?
That's a...
That'll be back.
I said my baby.
Yes, dear friends.
A marvelous little mix there
by
Ray Brunel.
Yes, Ray Brunel's tape number two.
The Elvis rap.
And this is Ray Brunel's
synthesizer
twiddlings in the background here as well.
And let me give you Ray Brunel's address.
He's a media junkie.
It says here, and you can write to
Ray Brunel, B-R-U-N-E-L-L-E
at
212 and a half
Miller
Avenue
Portsmouth
New Hampshire
Yes, dear friends.
Once again, that's
212 and a half
Miller Avenue Portsmouth
New Hampshire 03801
And you'll be...
There's a bunch more cool stuff on this tape.
Wait until you hear the Tom Vu rap.
We'll save that for next week.
There's next week's stack.
And
yes, friends, as I was saying earlier,
the devil, the devil,
the devil has been trying to
stop our tongues from a flapping,
friends. Well, him or Jesus
has been. And, you know, the
most important organ
in a subgenius's body
is that long, thick,
red,
bloated, stiff,
about nine and a half
inches organ,
the tongue and the flapping
lips. And that's just where the devil
or the angels struck.
At first it was
just the recurrence due to overwork
on the internet, I'll admit it,
of preacher's lip.
Believe me, you don't want preacher's lip,
especially if you're a preacher.
Which struck just in time
for a month's worth of
public ranting appearances on the part
of your dear friend and prayer partner
Reverend Ivan Stang, yours truly.
Then, when I finally got that licked,
so to speak, it was the superflu.
Tube neck, Captain Trips,
and then, after that, the ultimate
sore throat. But I'm a-healin', my friends!
I'm a-healin' up!
Because I did what
Bob said to do. I cut myself
some slack. I ignored
everything for two days. Two
whole days, friends! And now, praise
Bob, I can croak
again.
So, uh, oh, the conspiracy
tried to stop me. They threw
a car at me.
They tried to distract me.
The conspiracy sued me. Then they
overcharged me for all the cures. But by
gobs, we bounced back
to fight the conspiracy
again! Yes! Yes, somehow!
But you know, as, uh,
as they say
that Moses
parted the Red Sea,
that Oppenheimer
split the atom.
But as our friend here in Atlanta, Steve
Van Jack, once said,
Bob Dobbs cut the crap!
Oh, oh, before I get
going, speaking of cutting the crap,
I have to make up, we made a little
bit of money at the, uh, sacred sales
table today. And in order
to, uh, justify these things, we always
have to start off with a
sacred burning of the almighty dollar.
Yes. We burn
if we kill Bob, we burn our
God. This is a real dollar here. I'm about
to commit a misdemeanor, probably.
I don't think you're supposed
to do this, but friends!
My friends!
As long
as the smoke
from this dollar bill is going up
to heaven, those aliens from
Planet X know that there's still
one soul down here worth saving!
Ha!
And unfortunately, that's probably
not your soul, dear friends.
But, uh, that's the,
from the thin recording of the,
the, uh, Atlanta Devival Tape List.
We have been, uh, traveling and
doing things, um,
uh, you know, they tried
to silence me.
Uh, permanently. Yes,
they did. Uh, uh,
and to foil their plans,
I had to silence myself.
Uh, temporarily. See, tricked them.
Because Niki will forget
you if you clam up for a while.
See, you can beat them
if you're sneaky enough. That's what it
all amounts to. And we did
manage to fly in under the radar
anyway. I mean, sure, it made me
a, a sickly nervous wreck
and it took about a year, but my gobs!
I mastered the internet.
Yes. I'm a
regular internet god now. Since
the last time I talked to you live, dear friends,
I finished the official
subgenius worldwide
website. And get your pencils
ready, because I'm gonna hurl you that
URL, that URL, that web
address for all ten
of you who happen to be connected well enough
to see that stuff.
Now get this, um,
I hate to
put it this way, but, uh, we
have finished and published
a 5,000 page
stark fist of removal magazine
in full color.
That's right, I said
5,000 pages
in color. It includes
the updated high
weirdness by mail, uh,
in progress, um,
with the secrets of all our rival cults
and terrible sarcastic comments
about them. Um, it, it has
new rants, it's got secrets, tips,
a hundred pages of interviews, it's
got recipes. The only problem
is, it's on
the internet. You can't take it into
the bathroom with you unless you have
a portable computer and a phone
line. You can't hand it to your pals
unless you print it out, and that would take
days and ten reams of paper
and three toner cartridges.
But
if you have that
computer and
decent non-America online
type net access, well it's free.
5,000 pages of new subgenius
everything. Yo, you can even
download games like, uh,
Kill Bob and
the Dobbs Oracle. You can watch
little Dobbs head morphing
cartoons and listen to
weird Dobbs hymns, and I
know that at least one in ten of you
have web access.
So, that web address
of the sub-site. Now this is almost,
this, in the future, this will be as important
to you as the sacred P.O.
box or the call-in
letters of the station you're listening to.
That website is
as they all say,
http://
They all start with that.
Sunsite.
That's,
this is all in small letters, friends.
S-U-N-S-I-T-E
Sunsite.
That's the first word. Period.
U-N-C
Period.
E-D-U
Slash.
Subgenius. And it's all in
small letters without the giant S and the
giant G. And subgenius does
not have an O in it, my
friends. Okay. That's
sunsite.unk.edu
slash subgenius.
And that's all you need to know.
Check it out. If you possibly can't,
don't forget to click
Dobbs smack dab in the face
because if you don't do that, I don't
know if it'll work or not.
And that, by the way,
and that doesn't mean to point
your finger at the picture of
Bob on your computer's
screen and click your tongue.
That means you have to use the mouse
to move the cursor over
Bob's nose and
click the mouse button.
Okay. Um, anyway,
dear friends, uh,
we have been
in, in, ranting in Atlanta,
in Chicago, and in Cleveland, and
even in Dallas. Even in
Dallas, friends. And hung out with
the horrible rock band
GWAR. Um,
and hatched schemes
with them. Did tons of live
radio. Oh, oh, one thing else about
the internet I should mention.
Pretty soon people all over the whole
world will be able to hear the Hour of
Slack when WCSB
in Cleveland takes
the Hour of Slack and all its other
wonderful shows. Uh, Reverend
Cole's show and Lonesome Cowboy Dave
and Sadie's Pagan
Show and all that stuff
will be, um, on the internet for anybody
who's got real-time audio connection
can pick it up. And I understand that stuff.
It's working pretty good now.
Even on a 14.4 modem,
you know? Um, anyway, uh,
friends, um,
yeah, we, uh, we're, uh,
we made so many new friends
and new contacts, and
we glommed onto unheard of
new Jimi Hendrix bootlegs
and, and had record sales at
the sales tables and even made a buck or two.
So you can quit your saying,
oh, Reverend Stagg, that snob,
all he does is mess with the internet
like a geek. No, sir.
Since I got that website up to snuff
and made it public, I haven't hardly glanced at
alt.slack and have barely
skimmed my email. I've finally
gotten to the point that, for me,
the internet is only
another tool, like a
chainsaw or a
one-inch video editing suite
or a screwdriver.
I didn't go off the deep end. No!
Almost, sure. Made myself a physical
wreck, but I didn't let it get my soul, friends.
Instead, the
internet got Bob's soul.
In the genre.
Um, that, uh, no, that's,
that's computer music there in the background.
Where is this, kick-button
rock-and-roll stuff? This is for me.
What?
Yeah, that's
what we're doing here.
This is only the beginning.
Pardon me?
I was afraid of...
I was afraid... I was... I'm sorry.
This is only the... This is only... This is only... This is only... This is only... This is only... This is only... This is only... This is only... This is only... This is only... This is only...
Well, anyway, dear friends, we do have...
Man, I've got so many wonderful new bands in.
Tapes of strange, unheard-of bands.
This one here is the great Jimmy Ryan.
Just pounding away with this heavy metal stuff.
In the background.
Something called Gut-Wrench Stew.
Jimmy Ryan also from Dr. Bizarro's band.
And friends, we've got takes in from the likes of bands you've never heard of.
Like, we've got Red Snapper and the Catfish.
We've got Abdul the Mad Convenience Store Clerk.
We've got... Let's see.
The Acres of Shankers. That's a great band name.
Ad Nauseam.
The Adolph Jesus Experience will be coming up.
Uh...
After the Blast.
The Agent Cooper.
Aggressive Sheep.
Almost Drunk.
The Alternatives.
The Alzheimer's Parkinson Band.
The Amateur Professionals.
The Amazing Soda Bottles. Alright.
The And Then I Said.
The Android Gigolos.
The Angry Little Men.
They're kind of a strange punk band.
Uh...
Anna Otto and the Palindromes.
Anti Any and All Things.
Armhole and the Rusty Syringes.
Armchair Sadists.
Arnie Cooper.
Arsenic and Old Lays.
Art Deco and the Architects of Desire.
And Attack of the Five Foot Woman.
And those are just in the A's.
I had to... We got so darn many new types in,
we had to stack up the band names alphabetically just to keep up with them.
And that was just the A's.
Actually, that wasn't.
That was from the, uh...
That was a list of band names that you could buy for a buck.
If you're having trouble thinking of a band name for your band,
send a buck for one of those names to the Swingin' Love Corpses.
I took that off the Swingin' Love Corpses Internet website.
How about them apples?
Which you will connect to very quickly if you start poking around
in the Ears of Bob section of the Subgenius sub-site.
Uh...
Thank you.
Oh, for background noise here,
we have, uh...
The band tonight is called Limp Node.
I think they'll probably be called something else tomorrow night.
And we have no idea what is going to happen here.
That's the important thing.
Sometimes that works out for the worst, frankly.
Other times, it's the best thing in the world.
But we do have tonight some of the most powerful, hate-filled subgenius preachers.
We have Dr. Kitani LeGue, the most dangerous subgenius preacher.
We have Father Papa Joe Mama, the most, uh...
insulting subgenius preacher.
We have Sister Susie the Floozy, the sexiest subgenius preacher.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Whoo!
Praise Sister Susie the Floozy.
And we have the strangest subgenius preacher, Saint Janor Hypercles.
There will be a head-launching tonight.
We shouldn't...
We might even have...
Hell, maybe we ought to have the wedding ceremony right now.
Usually, we have the wedding ceremony at the end, but, you know, we might...
Maybe we need more...
We're going to get into some serious hating.
I wonder if maybe we shouldn't be sweet at first.
Oh, by the way, here's a suggestion someone sent in.
Um, you know, a lot of people like to have Bob Gobs' face tattooed upon their body,
which is, uh, wonderful.
I mean, you're going to be a very expensive lampshade in about three years.
But, uh, there's a cheaper way to do it.
Uh, you can have that actual face tattooed upon you.
Of course, the... your old royalties to the Subgenius Foundation.
The cheaper way to do it is just print the words...
I mean, the letters B-O-B.
Have those tattooed.
It's a lot easier for the artist.
And you can save money if you have it done on your butt.
You just put a B on either cheek, my friends.
Save you some money.
Never let it be said we were just money grubbers.
I don't know. What do you think? Should we have a wedding?
Should we have a...
Oh, no. Everybody's heard the wedding a million times.
Instead, I think we'll just pause for this word from your local amazing radio.
You're gonna pick it up and only watch TV?
When dad gets in a Raven's house on the T seetheyal.
Oh yes.
HARRIET'S CHILD
Use freedom and love for brotherly pleasure.
Theuffen
Alright, Cortes
Dear friends, it looks like I am now in control...
...finally. It's about time.
That old stupid show is over.
God, it was an old show.
And it's been so long.
At least it's not you talking anymore.
Now it's you talking.
Yeah, it drives me crazy to hear that.
But it's so good to be in control of a radio station again.
It's ours now.
They tried to keep me off the air in Dallas.
The fools.
They wouldn't let me finish my experiments.
Put this pre-recorded stuff on.
Yeah.
Like this.
You can tell that other stuff is old, but this stuff, this stuff's real old.
Yeah.
No, what do you mean old?
They just weren't cooking in the studio, so they put this tape on.
This was recorded before that last recording.
And it's only because we know that other recordings are going to be played in the future that we can make references to it.
The secrets of time control allow us this power.
The great power of the church of the subgenius.
We can even put music in the back of our voices.
Such is our strength.
Such is our power.
Such is our total in control of your control mechanism.
Oh, yes, that's right, dear friends.
It's a serious abuse of power here on the church of the subgenius.
Bob's lifetime fun house show.
Forget where the hotel room is.
Geniuses.
Subgenius geniuses.
Yes, we've been at the, uh...
I'll bring the free food if you'll bring the botulism.
Geniuses.
Subgenius geniuses.
I'll forget my lines if you'll forget where the ballroom is.
Geniuses.
Subgenius geniuses.
I'll bring the fans if you make sure they're all geeks.
Geniuses.
Subgenius geniuses.
Now, come on, you guys.
Let's not make fun of those nice science fiction fans over there at the, uh, Dragon Con Sci-Fi.
I mean, that's the reason we're all together here.
They thought that they were gonna get some sort of showbiz out of the whole thing.
Get some, some, uh, extra fanboys over there at their fan convention.
I'll bring the voluptuous vivid if you'll make sure they're talking to peni.
Geniuses.
Subgenius geniuses.
Now, let's not make fun of the geeks and the fans.
I'm...
No, we did that last year, actually.
I...
I kind of enjoy looking at those mutant girls on display showing a lot more skin than they would ever dare anywhere else.
They're not all girls, Stang.
Well, if I...
They are the third sex.
Highly illogical, Captain.
Well, if you can't tell the difference, what, what is the difference?
Uh, duh.
I mean, like, Romulan is no longer the official language in that sector.
I mean, come on.
Everybody knows that.
Uh...
Uh, duh.
All right, maybe I should explain what's going on here, dear friends.
That was, that was 1967 version.
This is your, your, uh, host for the night, Reverend Ivan Stang.
Uh, with, uh, special...
This is your host for the night, Reverend J.N. Hyperclay.
I'm gonna pull your volume down, J.N.
This is your host for the night, Reverend Joel...
I'm trying to keep some kind of control and make this a...
...a linea...
Down, J.N.
That's right. It's a radio station.
I've been up for five days.
Yeah, we know.
We've been talking about that for five days.
Look, um...
And I'll keep talking about it...
Now, wait a minute. On the fourth day, he was talking about how you've been up for four days.
I was over the last day in the dogma, you guys.
We're supposed to be doing a religious radio broadcast.
Doctor, like, you and Stang...
It doesn't matter. It doesn't matter.
He was talking about how you've been up for second days.
The first day, he was only talking about how you've been up all day long, and that wasn't unusual at all.
It doesn't work.
No, when I turn up your mic, I just get this cute music.
I know that's not you, Doctor.
That's me. My voice is too murky.
That's the music in his brain.
I talked to Dave Martin, and we started talking about a skull farmer, and we didn't kill her hard, and we ran over his face...
Don't let's not turn this into another one of those kind of radio shows.
...any other radio...
Martin?
Hm?
Now, friends, during our last lesson, we discussed the conspiracy and the fall of New Manta.
And I'm sure you remember, kids. I'm sure that someone here can get up here and recite that lesson.
Am I alone up here, or are there other subgenius preachers?
Father Joe Mama?
Psych Changer Hypercleans?
Dr. Katana Le'Vue?
Is anybody here?
There's hope. Not much.
A subgenius came up to the dealer's table today and said,
Reverend Stang, I'm starting a new schism.
You know, you can't really be a good subgenius unless you immediately split from the church,
or a heretical schism.
But the only heresy in this religion is orthodoxy.
This guy came up to me and said,
I'm the high priest, my name, his name was Jesus. That was his real name.
He kind of looked the part, too, and he said, I'm the high priest of the Church of the Anti-Bot.
And our slogan is,
Slack can only be sold, it cannot be bought.
And I thought, wow. I immediately went, wow!
That's a great slogan.
Let me write that down.
And I did. Here it is.
But then I realized,
Plight, man. That's a horrible concept if you think about it.
That totally contradicts the doctrine that we've always had,
that slack is the one thing that cannot be bottled and sold.
And because of that, because slack is individual to you,
conspiracy can't tell you what your slack is.
We're not going to tell you what your slack is.
The conspiracy will try to tell you that slack is,
you know, towing the line,
going playing by the rules,
going to work, coming home, getting drunk, watch TV,
party with the boys,
and have a good time as long as you're good looking and your team wins,
and you're drinking Miller Lite.
But think about it. The idea that slack can only be sold, it cannot be bought.
Why, that would put a religion in a damn good position.
In other words,
you can't buy it, but we can sell it.
Isn't that how they took early Christianity and slightly turned it the other direction?
You know, all of a sudden, the slack wasn't greed.
You had to pay for the slack.
I'm talking about Christianity-style slack,
which, you know, I mean, that's good for some people
if you like sitting around on a damn cloud playing a harp over eternity.
Shit.
But there's a man here,
well, we think he's a man,
if he was at one time,
someone who can give me relief,
who can give me slack, finally.
Friends, I want you to prepare yourselves
for the horror,
the sheer cantankerous horror of
Father Joe Obama!
Praise Father Joe Obama!
As the dark cloud of subgenius destiny
descends upon the shaking world,
beaks, normals, and mediocritons
must come to grips and confront the one thing they fear most,
the face of death.
Hello, friends, and welcome.
The sermon tonight is entitled
In Doubt of Darkness.
Because there is a place, dear friends,
in the house of Jehovah One,
where dogs and his overmen
peer down upon the earth for them and watch us at work.
They keep track of every sin and transgression.
They record every conspiracy crime
and document every peak offense.
These unforgettable acts
are carefully recorded in a 500-ton ledger,
the dreaded register of works.
Our next date, 1998,
this book will be towed through space
along with the exosauvada
emplaced in orbit around the planet.
The mile-wide hands of Jehovah,
the so-called left hand of removal
and right claw of retrieval,
will appear alongside the book,
one turning the pages, the awesome pages,
while the other running along each line
to point out every sin and sinner.
The third hand of Jehovah,
the feared star, this shall appear,
holding a giant magnifying glass
between the earth bomb and the orbiting book.
As the right claw of retrieval points to each day,
the thunderous voice of Moses
shall call forth the transgressor.
As that sinner cranes his or her head skyward,
the stark fist will focus the giant glass
so that every sin of that sinner
can be read as they burst into flame.
The longer the entry, dear friends,
the longer that sinner burns.
Those within a five-lock radius
will also read the charges
and witness the judgment.
The intense light shall blind them,
the excess heat will burn them,
but they shall live to bear witness
to both crime and punishment.
Their empty eye sockets and blistering bodies
shall serve as living testament
to the power of the God of light.
As our planet rotates beneath the giant lens,
Jehovah will direct its column of flame
across the burning surface.
Judgment day shall be the day
that the sun will last for months on end,
for the sun never sets on his empire.
Judgment day indeed.
Meanwhile, among the ruins of civilization,
the exes and subgenies will scurry about,
flushing out the surviving pinks and normals
from their hiding places beneath the rock.
Those holed up in bunkers
will receive special incentives.
Spaceship loads of Zyklon B
will gas the remaining vermin
from their rat holes.
Pink's and normals' hearing
now is truth or die.
There is no escape from the justice of Jehovah.
Thou shall embrace dogs,
pay homage to him,
or perish in his light.
Now, there are some normals out there
who think they can hedge their bets.
They think they can live the life of the subgenius
without joining the fight against the conspiracy.
They might even send in the thirty-dollar love offering
in Etebab's sacred P.O. box.
But alas, these people are ash.
Ash!
For they think they can buy off dogs
with a lousy thirty bucks!
Dogs resisted every temptation, dear friends,
every temptation the conspiracy could throw at him.
A model of every new car,
a model of every new bride,
and a mountain of every known currency.
Only a normal would be stupid enough
to think that they could outbid the conspiracy
with an insulting thirty-dollar bribe.
Dogs isn't interested in money, dear friends.
He only accepts the love offering
as a deposit on your soul.
It's supposed to be earnest money
to show you're committed in joining the fight
to liberate slack.
Laying neutral isn't good enough anymore.
You've got to go to war against the conspiracy.
Others may ask,
well, what about that poor soul
in some remote African village
born enraged without ever hearing about dogs
and his message of slack?
Will they be punished for not sending in thirty dollars
and not joining the religion they never even heard of?
Yes, dear friends, they will.
Only they won't be punished as severely as the others
who had the money and knew the address
but didn't send it.
Because on next day, dear friends, 1998,
all disbelievers will burn.
Only some will burn a little harder than others.
Then, of course, there's the bobbies.
I could reveal the faith that's in store for them,
but I wouldn't want to spoil the surprise.
That leaves only one category of people
who think they can avoid judgment but cannot.
That group is the subgenies with doubts.
The otherwise sage subgenius,
except for that lingering shadow of a doubt
in the back of their mind.
Oh, they believe in the conspiracy.
They believe in slack.
They've experienced both,
and they know they are real and of this world.
But dogs?
Well, they're still not sure whether or not
he's just some legend made up to explain
what being a subgenius is all about.
After all, there's no photos of him,
only a piece of clip art.
I mean, after all, if he really died,
there should be a grave.
If he really existed,
there should be government records.
Dear, dear friends,
these subgenies are in the gravest danger of all,
for they have no defense for refusing dogs into their hearts.
The other subgenie,
they had ignorance or stupidity to blame,
but a subgenius has neither.
They were given Dobbs' greatest gift,
the privilege of knowing him,
but turned and walked away instead.
Oh, they were provided every piece of evidence
one could possibly want,
but chose to interpret it in a way to disprove Dobbs
instead of substantiating him.
Of course there's no pictures of Bob.
Bob's a god.
You can't take pictures of God.
Everybody knows that.
Likewise, there's no grave,
because gods are immortal.
You can shoot them and you can bury them,
but you can't keep them dead.
They're immortal. They live forever.
Put them on a grave and they leave it every time.
Everybody knows that.
The government records of his existence
is a conspiracy.
Wake up!
It's a conspiracy!
I mean, they're never going to reveal the truth
because their business is lies.
That's why we call it a conspiracy.
Oh, dear friends,
we must return these Dobbsian doubters to the fold
before they self-destruct,
because doubts end Dobbs means death.
You have to serve somebody,
and if you're not a god,
you're not serving Dobbs,
you're serving the conspiracy.
Now, we're not the type of religion to use threats,
but imagine, if you will,
the sight of your own blistering flesh,
the smell of your own burning hair,
the sound of your very blood boiling,
and the feeling of your inner bones melting.
Oh, God!
The pain, the pain,
the pain you'll experience in those final hours
will make you beg for your body to burst,
just to end the agony.
But thanks to time control,
every second will be a year,
and every minute a millennium.
To believe in Dobbs means you will forever have slack.
A real subgenius can never be convinced otherwise.
If you worry about your fate,
even just a minute micron,
then you should worry a lot,
because if you are truly a true subgenius,
you know it, you feel it, you exude slack.
But if you have doubts in Dobbs,
you're toast.
You might as well just buy marshmallows
and stick them on the ends of your fingers,
because you're gonna burn, baby, you're gonna burn!
You're gonna fry, you're gonna stew in your own juices,
unless you change!
Now is the time
to get off the ground.
Join Bob Dobbs and bathe in his bliss,
or reject him and perish in pain.
It's your choice, and you alone must make it.
But time is running out.
Herein is the word of all three Bob!
Amen!
Oh, lordy, lordy, lordy.
It's, uh, Father Joe Mama.
Oh.
What?
Cheap, tanked, racked collections
are available at the dealer's table.
Oh, yes, that's right.
Dear friends, the great, the great Father Joe Mama,
and, uh,
oh, I don't even know what next.
There's so much tape I could pack into this.
We've got amazing Dr. Legume Rance,
but let's see what lovely sister Susie the Floozy
has going on over there at WREK
on the Bob Slacktime Funhouse.
1974.
Uh-oh.
The future.
Is the year that they are now planning
for sex on the streets
in every major city from coast to coast.
1974, did he say?
And get ready for a shock.
I can't wait.
The music that they're planning to use
to crumble the morals of America
is this rotten, filthy, dirty,
lewd, lascivious junk called rock and roll.
God help you compromising creatures
who allow this rock beat in your pulpit on Sunday morning
because they got Jesus saved.
And it's the same thing.
It's the same thing,
but the truth is
that it's got a lot of things tied to it.
It isn't just the lyrics.
It's the beat.
I preach into my conversion story,
which you can get,
how this beat gets them.
400 teenage girls in Detroit interviewed
as to why they had illegitimate babies.
It's not just the words,
the beat.
The fertility rates of the jungles
are the same beats
incorporated in this modern rock.
Just screw them up.
You're not hearing from a preacher now.
You're hearing from the leader of the White Panthers
planning a revolution, a sexual revolution by 74.
And all through rock music.
Don't you dare defend it.
I'll tell you, I'm brokenhearted.
In my citywide crusade, I can preach against immorality, sex.
I can preach against liquor.
I can preach against tobacco.
Name it!
They take it.
I've had two churches pull out of my crusades already
because I hit on rock and roll music.
Well, if it makes the devil that mad,
there has to be something wrong.
Our message is one, and that is freedom.
For the first time in America,
we have a generation of visionary maniacs,
white mother, country, dope, rock and roll freaks
who are ready to kick out the jams, all the jams.
Our program of rock and roll.
Not the waltz, not the polka, rock and roll.
And sex in the streets
is a program of total freedom for everyone.
We are totally committed to carrying out our program.
We breathe revolution.
We are LSD-driven maniacs in the universe.
We'll do anything we can to drive people crazy
out of their heads, into their bodies.
It's for grammar.
Rock and roll music.
It is a spearhead.
It's a spearhead of our path
because it's so effective and so much fun.
Nobody would stop and talk to me today.
How you doing?
I'm doing fine.
What's the meaning of life?
Inhale and exhale.
Life is living.
Life is all about love.
What are you hitting him for?
We just came back from the Cicada Theater.
You know, someone has suggested, you know,
that people do spend a lot of time making love
and they expend a lot of energy
and that if they could do something,
if couples could do something,
while they were having sex,
can you think of anything to do during sex
that would be productive?
Eat. That isn't productive.
How about making hamburger patties?
I couldn't do that.
Not while I'm there. Huh?
Really, if it was a pound of hamburger,
just to your left?
I couldn't concentrate.
Whenever I'm making love,
I have to concentrate on what I'm doing,
not the hamburger patties.
If I gave you two pounds of hamburger,
would you go home tonight and, if you do make love,
make some hamburger patties
and then I'll try and sell them, let's say, to McDonald's?
How much money would I get out of this?
What?
What would I get to profit?
Well, let's say if you could make 100 bucks a night
making hamburger...
I'd make the shit out of hamburger patties.
Well, I mean, I wouldn't be concentrating on my woman.
I'd be concentrating on making money.
What would be the best position?
The dog position.
Well, then where would the hamburger be?
I guess on her back.
So, obviously, the longer I last,
the more hamburger patties we get, right?
Have you made hamburger patties like this before?
No. No, hell no.
How about you?
No.
You know, you could put it like...
Can I ask you a question? Yeah.
What's the purpose of this?
I'm trying to find out the meaning of life.
Have anybody ever flicked your bitch?
Wouldn't this turn you on as you were making love
to know that he was making hamburgers on your back?
Yeah.
What's wrong? You're looking at her in a straightaway...
I was thinking, you know, I was trying to figure all this out, you know?
We're gonna make this a real situation, right?
And what I'd like to do, because if this works out,
we're gonna try and make some commercials.
We'd like to just film you.
Yeah. Why not?
I mean, it's slick to me, guys.
Now, would you be at all nervous if there also was a dog involved?
Yeah.
Oh.
Oh, howdy-do, Seekers.
Oh, welcome to Bob's Slacktime Funhouse.
I'm the rapidly rotating, righteously irreverent Reverend Susie the Floozy.
And, hey, you look like you need to unwind.
Here, let me loosen your collar.
There. Doesn't that feel better?
Now, get out of that bulky race.
I'm gonna get you a new suit.
Oh, what a week, Seekers.
In this climate of hysteria,
don't think the full story about the Branch Bob Dobson involvement
in that Oklahoma thing will ever come out.
It was just a couple of goofuses who were going into the Federal Building
to slip a Bob virus into the IRS computer mainframes.
And the one in the GM truck rear-ended the guy in the Ford Pinto.
What a sap foo.
Oh, this colloquial thing.
The colossal monkey ranch has made things really unpredictable.
But one thing will definitely come out of this.
The Republicrat repression machine is going to gather more steam
than ever from this little incident.
Oh, what a stroke of luck for them.
I bet they can't believe it.
It's goosed their plans for domination ahead beyond their wildest dreams.
Now, nothing stands in the way to stop their police state juggernaut.
And the most draconian measures will seem reasonable
to the paranoid media fear-imprinted American electorate.
They'll love them for it.
Oh, I was thinking that until X-Day I could weather this storm,
but now I'm not so sure.
A couple times a conspiracy's veil has slipped,
and I've seen the writing on the wall.
And the words belong to them.
Oh, we went to see Faster Pussycat Kill Kill again the other day.
We stopped at a bookstore across the street first.
And while Reverend Rex hit the magazines,
I went trolling for a copy of Revelation X with Brother Marcus.
And we couldn't find one.
It wasn't filed under psychology, the arts, self-help.
If that wasn't it, what isn't what it is, I don't know what it is.
It wasn't under sexuality, literature, poetry.
We gave it a chance. We looked everywhere.
It wasn't even in the religion section, nor mythology.
Our rich traditions were not represented on the shelves.
Not the stories of Niki and the first pipe maker.
You know, there probably was a copy of Revelation X there in that alleged bookstore.
Back in the humor section.
I don't know. I didn't look.
To tell you the truth, I didn't have the stomach for it.
I had to leave before I vomited down my cleavage.
It physically sickened me to see my faith denigrated, dismissed as a lame-ass joke.
And openly mocked by this hive of pleasantly bookish pinks.
But then the fnords hit me head on.
And I saw those pathetic pinks anew.
Sickly or with the pale light of Bob.
I saw those poor idiots for what they are.
Smug little sacks of meat.
Thinking that there they are, nestled in the repository of all wisdom.
With all the knowledge of the world laid out before them.
But the conspiracy has the cards all marked.
And they're dealing from the bottom of the deck too.
The conspiracy controls which books are available.
Which ideas will be disseminated.
They control not only what you read.
They control how you interpret it.
They control the use of the very words with which we communicate.
Oh, and dear friends, the only way to break that insidious control is to write for free information from the Church of the Subgenius.
And I'm going to give you that post office box address as soon as I find suitable music here.
God, I'll just grab anything.
Here.
I don't even know what this...
No, that's going to be too pink.
What?
No, that's really too pink.
That's so pink, it's funny.
But I don't want something...
Friends, okay, you love Bob.
You have to love Bob.
You will love Bob or he will kill you.
And you...
And...
Now where...
Oh, it's on pause.
And you must write for free information.
Just the postcard is enough.
Who knows?
You might throw a little bit more in there.
Send us a free self-addressed stamped envelope.
And you would really get something.
And you would really get some action.
From, just addressed at two, Bob at post office box 140306.
That's Bob at box 140306 in mighty Dallas, Texas.
And that's Dallas.
There's two A's and two L's.
Dallas, Texas.
Taxis.
75214.
The sacred zip code of the church of the subgenius.
And we had to interrupt Sister Susie the floozy in the midst of her insanity there.
Actually, it's the only true sanity there is.
Is the sanity of the subgenius preachers.
Like yours truly, Reverend Ivan Stang.
And like Father Joe Mama, who's the wonderful...
What was the name of it?
In doubt of Dobbs.
Yes, friends.
Are you in doubt of Dobbs?
Are you on the edge, just on the, in the middle of the fence, just wondering?
Well, I think I know what these people are trying to say, but I just don't want to take the plunge.
Well, it's probably wise of you to, uh, uh, pull the wool over your own eyes and relax in the safety of your own delusions.
But sooner or later, you will have to find yourself awash in the delusions of Dobbs.
Uh...
Okay.
Um...
Uh, yes, friends.
And, uh, other, uh, addresses I can give you.
Let's see.
The, uh, uh, well, subgenius email.
You can email to old Reverend Stang.
Just don't make it, you know, have mercy.
Don't make it long.
If you've got a legitimate question, let's not be frivolous.
That's, um, i.stang at metronet.com.
And if you weren't able to catch that, then you ain't got to be frivolous.
You got no business of messing with it, now do you?
That's the thing.
Some of these people that, just the very ones who have the most to fear from the Church of the Subgenius, are often become attracted to, uh, the light of Dobbs like moths to a flame.
And the same thing happens.
They get burned.
They're brushed.
They're biting off a bit more than they can chew.
They're trying to, they're trying to get Bob's attention.
They want to get Bob.
They want, they're thinking, oh, Bob, uh, you're the, you're the best.
You're the endless font of slack.
Why don't you grant me some?
Well, my friends, he's the endless font of slack.
That's right.
And his slack has to come from somewhere, now don't it?
So, uh, you go ahead, kids.
Go seeking Bob.
Bob Dobbs in the flesh, in person.
I, uh, I wish you luck.
Uh, you're gonna need all the luck you've got dealing with the luckiest salesman in the world.
Oh, yes.
. . .
And, uh, anyway, uh, I, I guess that's the, the, the end of the show.
And, um, is it?
Yeah, yeah, them tapes, they're just running out.
I'll let, uh, Jimmy Ryan here carry this out.
Just some fairly regular guitar playing.
Huh.
Well, the bass, the drums.
Yeah, we're coming in right now,ümü.
But, uh, I'd like to hear you at least a couple hundred parVEL ofNothing.
. . .
. . . .
Is there
any more?
I got a monег.
. . .