Thank you for joining us tonight. Now, I just heard in the report that
The subgenius power of swatting!
That is correct.
To engage in this attack?
That's correct.
Jeez.
Why, what, why, what, why?
It's the anointing that will break the yoke of Satan's bondage.
And I want you to know that I had just been experiencing an attack on all sides.
It seemed like on every front where we tried to advance,
the devil would just unleash literally hordes of demonic forces to stop us.
And after a few weeks of this, I just began to feel a deep hurting in my belly,
way deep down in my spirit.
And some people say, Brother Popov, what, you mean you experience pain too?
Yes, I do. I hurt just like you do.
I feel the pain of a satanic attack.
Just like you do.
And that's why I'm concerned about you.
That's why I feel for you.
I feel in the spirit your pain and your suffering and the sickness that Satan throws at you
to try to overcome you.
But bless God, Satan is a defeated foe.
But while I felt this pain, it seemed almost as if a spontaneous thing happened.
As I finally, I, no longer, but I really didn't even know how to pray
because I didn't know exactly what the devil, what was coming at me.
Satan was bombarded.
He was firing me from so many sides.
Actually, I felt kind of numb.
Ba-ba-ba-ba-boom.
Hello, Bob.
This is Jesus.
Give me Elvis.
All mine.
Hello, Jesus.
This is Bob.
I'll connect you all in time.
Hello, Bob.
This is Elvis.
Tell that Jesus
to stop.
Stop his crying.
Hold on, boys.
Now, this is Bob.
I think you'll hear each other fine.
Okay.
Now, hello, Jesus.
This is Elvis.
I wish to talk to you so long.
Hello, Elvis.
This is Jesus.
It's great to hear you.
It's a song.
Oh, listen, boys.
I won't fool you.
Yeah.
The meter's running
on this call.
Wait now, Bob.
You shouldn't charge me
because I am
more than all.
Hey, now, Jesus.
Since I'm Elvis,
I'll put this call
on my bill.
Sorry, Elvis.
Your card's expired,
which makes me
feel quite ill.
Oh,
Bob.
You tell me
what you hope
for your time.
Sorry, Jesus.
I guess no one.
So I'll disco
next to the line.
Hey, man, it's best
13 spirit
people
Build a fire and dare stand near it
In the distance, thunder hear it
While we're waiting on a 13th spirit
This is the tale of the boy with the bucket
Bringing fuel to the fire
I hear the fox preaching to the chickens
A lion, lion to the choir
We're waiting on a 13th spirit
We're in a fog, I wish the wind would clear it
I want to welcome you, return not fairy
But we're waiting on a 13th spirit
A 13th spirit
I am James, the long lost brother
Left flat footed on the temple floor
It's so easy to make the big promise
When you're not around to tell the poor
We're waiting on a 13th spirit
Build a fire and come stand near it
I want to hear the truth, I do revere it
While we're waiting on a 13th spirit
к Pour it on up to three
Let it fly hard like the sound of the baby
AC residus
Just sky in down
A city on did I
América
Just sky in down
A city on did I
There's just too much to remember
I can't keep my story straight
I'll be going down to Egypt
Or lover in the desert
Waiting on the 13th spirit
Just waiting on the 13th spirit
Everything you know is wrong
Every note of every song
Every truth you've ever known
Are lies
Everything you know is wrong
People know what they believe
But nothing's really up their sleeve
They try to hide their victims
They try
JFK and grassy nose
Dinosaurs and holes on holes
Desert storms and somebody's brain
Brains on drugs
Everything you know is wrong
Smash a little egg with a frying pan
Fry it up
Cook it up
Serve it on a sandwich
василки
Order from cártel
These are just in youruke
I like being to be aіл
Michael iron man
Ppl might be a part of this
I just didn't understiiiiiii
of it
I need to eat
my money
Thank you.
Yes, dear friends.
Ah, yes, yes, yes.
This episode of our Slack is going to be a lot like the last two because we're,
this month we've been using a lot of the same source material.
Let's see.
What we just heard was a really ancient recording, probably 1980.
That was Glass Madness, one of the many cassette tapes that he mailed to us.
And I guess I overdubbed.
Before that, the kind of Zappa sounding thing called Everything You Know Is Wrong.
That was Dr. Bizarro and the Disgustos.
The guitar player was our old friend from the Flyin' Ryan Brothers.
And the, yeah, that was from the 80s too.
I think that stuff was done originally on cassette.
I used to play Dr. Bizarro and the Disgustos on cassette back in the day.
And he's just, after 35 years or so, put it on CD.
And they sound really good.
There's probably more of that coming up in our second hour.
Because we're going to have a second hour tonight.
How about that?
At least here we will.
Maybe not where you are.
Oh, The 13th Spirit was the Rainmakers from the album Monster Movie.
It's a great movie.
Kind of a spooky song.
Calling Bob, Elvis, and Jesus.
That was our good old buddy, Reverend Bleepo Abernathy.
One of many songs he did, Bob's songs.
I've been unearthing stuff from the original Bob's Songs 3 album.
That was assembled in 1981, I think.
And Lee Murr did our titles.
And friends, now I'm going to play another one off Bob's Songs 3.
Midnight Rainbows.
Rambler by D.K. Jones.
You midnight ramblers.
When I say midnight ramblers, I don't mean just black knights.
I mean you black-hearted men and women.
I'm midnight ramblers.
I am.
All midnight ramblers' faces are not black.
So what's our harm?
It's as black as midnight.
I'm talking to you.
Hold up, men.
And women.
You bank robbers.
You say so.
Uh-huh.
Sure.
Yeah.
And you bank robbers.
Right.
And kidnap.
Yeah.
You old bloody men.
All right.
I'm talking to you.
Yeah.
And we got some people in the church.
Yes, sir.
Stay down just as late as a midnight rambler.
All right.
I don't know what time Brother D.C. got in last night.
Yeah, Brother.
We about to have dinner tonight.
I'm gonna take everybody out of their head, if you don't mind.
Mm-Hmm.
Yeah.
We're gonna raise them up here tonight
for at restaurants in all l penetrations.
Mm-Hmm.
Okay, it's a little secret, we can hear back fortune.
rebirth of this little pig.
Yeah.
Hey, I wanna...
Mm-hmm.
It's a little blue screen
A little guy who sure gets tough, you know
When it's dark, shit ain't green
I was watching Dick Mad Dog Girl
Sorry, sorry, I forgot to call
When I'm watching the TV, yeah, you know
I don't care at all
I'm watching the TV
And it makes a fool out of me
Watching the TV
And I don't have to worry about me
When I'm watching the TV
Turning on as soon as I get home, you know
I grab myself a beer
The signal's always right on now, you know
I put your picture up in clear
I was watching Dick Mad Dog Girl
Sorry, sorry, I forgot to call
When I'm watching the TV, yeah, you know
I don't care at all
I'm watching the TV
And it makes a fool out of me
Watching the TV
Yeah
And I don't have to worry about me
When I'm watching the TV
Yeah
It's a little blue screen
A little guy who sure gets tough, you know
I'm watching the TV
And it makes a fool out of me
Watching the TV
And I don't have to worry about me
When I'm watching the TV
Yeah
And I don't have to worry about me
Watching the TV
Gonna get on a cable, on a cable
Ten channels up, get it over left
A dollar a day in a house
Well, look at the gentleman, please suggest
Hello, Larry, I'm watching chips here
It's all in our family, yeah
Sorry, honey, I can't call out, you know
I gotta watch the Dick movie
It's on the TV
And it makes a fool out of me
Watching the TV
Yeah
It's a little blue screen
And I don't have to worry about me when I'm watching the TV
And it makes a fool out of me watching the TV
Watching the TV
What am I gonna do when the X is gone?
I don't mind if all my things are melted at the same time
As long as I get to witness it
Yeah
Well I'll just be getting on
I'll just be getting on
Gotta finish another project
I got so much to do
And I'm hardly getting paid enough
I'm busy
To get by
How come I'm not making lots of money?
Not money for money
But money for time
To get some art projects done
Maybe make up some more songs
Cause right now
I'm making up this song
I'm losing money
Cause I should be working on an art project
If I can still and make some
Real kind of rent-paying coins
Or food-buying dollars
And I need some food to buy them all
Food buying dollars, just a few food buying dollars. I need to buy a few more art tools. I need to buy some more materials. I need some time to do some sketches. I gotta work out some concepts that might make me a famous guy someday.
Well, if I really worked out, maybe I could be able to pay my bills and be a pretty happy guy. Still go on vacation once in a while.
Get the supplies I need to do my art projects, to get things done that I visualize. I think about so much that I think would be neat.
I want to do some art projects that take so much money. They take so much time. It takes time to buy money. And I ain't got neither. I ain't got neither. I ain't got neither.
But I got both.
I got Bob.
This crazy man, he makes a lot of promises to me.
This guy with a pipe in his face and little half-tone dots all over his face.
He got...
He got them Bob Dobbs looking, Bob Dobbs face, and Bob Dobbs hair, and Bob Dobbs eyes, and Bob Dobbs nose, Bob Dobbs lips, Bob Dobbs chin, Bob Dobbs cheek.
Subtitles by the Amara.org community
Plenty of meat, plenty of cake, man saved some for me.
Plenty of folks needing a break, man saved one for me.
There was a time that I believed this was a good country.
For taking a risk, making a mark.
Taking a shot at a dream.
But I think that those days are over.
Opportunities are few.
Rich get richer, poor get poorer.
New world order's coming true.
Plenty of cheeses, plenty of guns, man saved some.
Oh no, this is what we need, saving from, man saved me.
Shaking the nuts out of the trees, strange foot indeed.
Stirring the fear, doubting the guns.
Turning your gun on me.
You don't serve no God of forgiveness.
You don't serve no loving God.
If we could get him in a courtroom, we would sue his ass for fraud.
Apocalypse a bit heavy handed.
Eternity a long, long time.
If there's a hell, I think they'll demand an encore from you.
One more time!
Plenty of attempts, plenty of tries, plenty of chance to choose.
Plenty of truths.
Trumping the lines.
I'll save one for you.
The frown of the boss, the back of the line.
All things must reverse.
Take it to court.
Telling the judge, I'll see you in the hearse.
Universe is arcing to justice.
It's a long and blinding curve.
Suddenly it's there in front of us.
Who's your master?
Who do you serve?
There's plenty of love, spread it around.
You saved some for me.
There's plenty of love.
Man saved some for me.
Plenty of love.
Oh, saved some for me.
There's plenty of love.
The Rainmakers.
Save some for me.
Also from that album Monster Movie.
Before that, a little bit of Glass Madness.
Watching the TV was the Pink Boys, probably recorded in 1979 or 80.
The Pink Boys singer and songwriter was Dr. X, the late Dr. X, my old high school best buddy.
He and Dr. Philo Drummond and I were the original three wise guys that, uh,
initially got Bob's project going there.
And of course the midnight rambler at the beginning of that mess was D.K. Jones.
Uh, as it says here though in our last, uh, well, the third testament, the Bobliographon,
One handy thing about God is that you can blame everything on him, even Bob.
No matter how badly you screw up, you can always say,
God isn't finished with me yet.
Well, sir ma'am, J.R. Bob Dobbs hasn't even started in on you yet.
As the great Ninslow said, any idiot can fail.
The idiot who can stub his toe or step on that nail or wreck his car and not start thinking the world is conspiring against him
is the idiot who succeeds.
Every time I see some moron on TV telling me how his ranch is going to be,
I say, I'm going to take him and his car into a concrete bridge abutment.
But he didn't die because the Lord was looking out after him.
I say, you idiot, it was the Lord that drove you into the abutment in the first place.
The only safety is in killing that vicious deity and every other deity that comes along to ruin your life.
Says Ninslow.
And what I say is, the problem is that religionists are always trying to tell God how to run his business.
How to run his life along with their own and yours.
Ever had one of those people threaten to pray for you?
They're so busy blabbering at God, as if he hadn't heard it all ten billion times before,
that even if he were inclined to respond, he wouldn't be able to get the word in edgewise.
The popular mainstream God is so weak and pathetic
that illiterate human po-buckers the world over
feel compelled to do his dirty work for him.
Evidently, he can't do much himself.
Were we to concern ourselves with an omnipotent universe maker,
we'd probably give it credit for being able to take care of itself.
But few of the faithful think nearly so highly of old everything man.
Again, as Ninslow said,
my life at worst is better than God's life at the peak of it.
I'm not sure I'd be so happy if I didn't have to go through all this worship that we all give to him,
that's supposed to do him so much good.
Did you ever wonder what it is that he gets out of that?
How does God benefit from people worshipping him?
What happens if we don't?
Does he get sickly?
Is he like Tinkerbell when she doesn't get enough claps?
She actually does die and the play ends right there?
I don't know, maybe if everybody stopped worshipping God, maybe he'd just die.
And that was Orton Ninslow in a talk tape to the Subgenius Foundation in the year of 1992.
Princess We is here.
I was reading from our out of print book, The Bobliographon.
That's always good for something.
We're going to try to get this right.
We're going to try to get it back into print.
I could put it out there illegally, because it was produced as a PDF.
But technically it's actually still owned by an out of business publisher.
And we still don't have Neighbor World, the novel by Lonesome Cowboy Dave,
completely online and ready to sell yet, because two shows ago,
if you recall, you called me,
the five-dress
case would even be able to be in that shop later.
No, his answers are only easily twenty- assume it's not an out of special collection.
It is an out of piles.
kaduria will give you a copy,
but I can understand him a little.
Maybe what you can do now,
or maybe you haven't melted as much as he's put out there,
it. But I think we'll go back to the music for right now. In this case, that will be
Exposed Foreheads, a song called Right Sized.
Right Sized
full implications.
And the understanding that once you...
Dave is neither
a joker nor an ace,
but a deuce. So his super
power, well, his power
is he can make himself
smell like any kind of cookie.
Oh.
Unusual,
not very...
Especially useful power.
It means paleophysicists
will culminate
in monstrously biting you in the
forehead and eating you like a cookie.
Well, a lot of us subgeniuses have
a super power,
but it's not really that
super. Like, mine
is I can type faster than
anybody else with only one finger.
And...
Or two fingers if I'm cheating.
My daughter could
receive
and send faxes
with her voice.
Yeah, with her voice. She could send them with her voice.
She couldn't, obviously,
she couldn't print out a fax, but she could
listen to it real closely and say,
it's an advertisement for
cruise ships
for your employees.
You know, you could ignore that.
And then she'd
get back on him and insult him. She'd be going
like that.
They'd get this crudely
spelled out,
assault.
She couldn't or she didn't. She just didn't
want to because she was so angry.
She could and she did.
I'd be careful. She might be listening
right now, although it's very unlikely.
She's always
said that the hour of slack instantly
gives her a headache.
Ever since she was a little kid.
I understand, yeah.
She first was on this show
at the age of three or
four.
Yeah, the frozen
smile syndrome. What do you think
of the old man show?
What do you think of what the old, and then
you get the frozen smile.
What the hell does it
mean? It doesn't give me that bad of a
headache, Dad. You hate it.
I can listen
for five minutes. No, I didn't
expect my kids to
understand or be
interested in my job any more
than I was in my dad's job.
He was a lawyer.
What a brilliant officer.
I didn't know what the hell
a lawyer did.
He never explained it to
us. All I knew is that there was
some kind of monster that he fought
called Teamsters, and
they often won.
Well, that's
kind of silly, really,
because why
would an individual lawyer fight
Teamsters? Because he was
the representation for the
trucking companies and
bottling companies all over this
great nation.
That's just like
what's the name of that
man from the 1970s,
Gell Parts and the Bravehearts and the
Stewhearts? They're all
in it together, especially the
company of devils, of sly
foxes and other outwooded
personnel that live not
even close by. Are you talking about
lawyers again? Yeah,
of course. You know, squareheads, golfers,
you know what they call them.
I suppose your pappy never played golf,
or did it play him?
More like it played him.
He had, I vaguely remember,
a set of golf clubs, but he
was
not really
that kind of a sports
fellow.
Yeah, and he used to like to dress like a woman
sometimes, once in a while, right?
In a very small community. That's not funny.
He liked to
dress like a cowboy, too.
Did you see that picture? He must have
seen that picture. What picture?
No, I don't know what you're talking about.
The picture we don't want to see ever again.
Actually,
remember he was in some little
play in the
Lions Club, and he played
a large
woman.
He wore high heels and stockings
and a dress and a wig.
Yeah, we saw that picture.
It was not PC
either.
No.
But who is?
Who is PC?
I mean, everybody
has somebody else's idea of not
PC.
For instance, it's not PC for me
to say, oh, you mean fake news
like the Bible? For some reason,
that's not PC enough
for some people. Go figure.
You played Lenny
Bruce Wonderbrow
earlier.
Earlier, didn't you?
No, I'm going to play that
in our second hour that no one
else can hear tonight.
You're warming up like your testicles are on
fire or something, you know?
Oh, thanks for telling me.
Oh, my God, Dave, you are such a good friend.
That is a good friend.
That was a quick call.
Man, I had to pat him out fast.
Thanks, Dave.
That was important.
Smoking, but not
for the right reason.
Well,
I'm not going to do that.
Well, you know, it's a token argument
for a token planet.
It's not a real substantial
place that anybody would want to spend longer
than three or four thousand aeons.
Where are you talking about?
A planet, this
begotten, this shot, and
you know, all this other stuff.
This planet?
This planet.
Would you and your like
and your ilk plan
on evacuating on certain days?
It never, ever happens.
I know how to make that happen.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, I do.
I've been reading a sci-fi novel that
they have a pretty plausible way of kind of destroying the Earth
and causing everyone to have to.
Well, anyone who can leave has to leave.
Of course, only about with the combined efforts of all nations,
they're only able to get about 2000 people living in outer space
when the Earth is destroyed.
And of those 2000 people,
a year later, there are only seven left
and they're all women.
Now, hasn't this already been turned into a movie?
No, it's a well, no.
Nobody should be.
There's something like it.
It's a novel called Seven Eves,
or one word, Seven Eves
by Neal Stephenson.
That bastard.
I'm so jealous of him.
I'm going to cut his fingers off so he can't write with a goose quill pen anymore.
That's why we can't get a terrible game over.
He's too good.
I've read all of his novels three times each.
That's how much I hate him.
And most of his novels are over a thousand pages long.
Oh, my goodness.
Oh, that's amazing.
Yeah.
But anyway, here's the important thing.
What I was going to get to was here's how you destroy the Earth.
It's easy.
You just blow up the moon first.
Lesson one.
Now, we don't have anything that we can blow up the moon with yet.
But.
We're going to have to.
I heard you.
A projectile thrown fast enough.
Yeah, baseball.
A heavy enough thing thrown fast enough from somewhere hitting the moon just the right way
could cause it to explode into maybe a dozen pieces.
But the thing is, then those pieces start banging into each other.
And eventually they turn into space boulders and gravel.
That eventually starts finding its way to Earth.
And we get the most wonderful shooting stars and meteors in the sky for 25 years.
And they heat up the atmosphere so much that it boils everything on the surface, including
almost all the water off.
It's like Baron Von Munchausen when you see the moon is crying and something comes out
of its eye.
Well.
Like a big droplet of snow.
If you could hit it with a big enough rocket right in the eye, it would blow up.
And maybe you could break it into chunks that would then eventually they'd form a beautiful
ring around the planet like Saturn has.
But first, the refuse would burn off the atmosphere.
Yeah.
So, yeah.
The Earth's atmosphere.
Again, if you could get 2000 people into habitats in space, all attached to the International
Space Station somehow.
By within a year or two, just by sheer human nature.
There'd only be seven of them.
There'd be 16 of them left and then there'd be one more big fight and there'd be only
seven people left.
Do you understand, though, that you're basically talking Dr. Strangelove talk right there?
You want to evacuate the planet like only 2000 people, which is some prescribed number.
That's about how many people we're all evolved from.
Of the rock.
Oh, yeah.
So we're taking one variety of every genetic sampling or something.
Here's what's worse.
They lose their samplings.
They're sampling sample genetics.
It's all gone.
The genetics of all the rest of the world are destroyed.
And luckily, one of the surviving Eve's is a geneticist and is able to, by parthenogenesis,
is able to get all of the other Eve's pregnant.
But she's also able to doctor the genes a bit so that they the the new seven human races
can be tailored to be somewhat like their original Eve.
Oh, good, good.
You get these tough-
The mitochondrial mama.
You get these military type ones.
One of them is unfortunately descended from the president of the United States who snuck
into the space habitat, and she is as bad as Trump and Hitler all put together.
She's the reason why it gets whittled down from 2,007 people.
And so her descendants are all smooth-talking, tricky liars.
The descendants of the science person are more science-ly and so forth.
They even end up-
Well, they're all like a damned alcoholic, Stan.
Well, the crazy old Eve, or the youngest one actually, decides that she doesn't want
her genes tailored at all.
In fact, she wants her worst traits, like bipolar condition.
Yeah.
To be accentuated in her children.
So she was actually conditional to be a polar bear until her last excrement, whenever
Tuesday that was, that they were trying to impromptu the-
Well, you end up with an interesting variation on the human race, rices, where it's no longer
rices divided by anything like skin color or looks, although they still look different
from each other, but in new ways.
The main thing is their personalities.
Each race has a completely different overall personality and culture.
And that's what we have to look forward to if we can just destroy the moon, Dave.
Well, I can hardly wait.
I think we need to start like- Jerry Lewis had a great telephone idea of, you know, let's
destroy the moon now and save all the handicapped-
He hasn't listened to the last 10 shows.
Who?
What do you think the beacon is all about?
Legumes, beacon products.
Oh, yeah.
And the
The moon was replaced by a gigantic spherical mothership.
It's just still not talking.
It looks about like a- Well, I see.
the man.
Let's hope that when it does start talking
it says the right thing.
He probably thinks
World War II actually happened.
He probably thinks there was a real
World War II, yeah. It was a hoax,
dude. It was a hoax
just so they could take your planet away.
It was just to make you paranoid
so they could switch planets with Mars.
I just, the other day
while I was masturbating softly to myself
and arguing with the policeman
and stuff like that, I started thinking
how many times I've been led down the
primrose path, and thinking,
thinking, thinking, and
thematically disagreeing with the same
old participle every single time.
It just comes back
to you like it's a thematic argument
about, you know, what we were
talking about before I started talking.
I think that's what's on everybody's
minds today. Yes, I think
so too. Yes, yes.
Rolling around in their heads like
old ball bearings in a coffee
can. Yeah,
that's annoying and rattling.
Metaphorically speaking, I've ever heard in a long
time, buddy.
Meatballs in a sidekick.
What is it again? Meatballs in a
sidekick?
Yeah, something like that. I've
already forgotten. A suitcase.
Meatballs in a suitcase, and that's
why I forgot all about it. Metallic meatballs
in a suitcase. Metallic
meatballs. These metallic meatballs.
Metallic meatballs.
Meatballs.
Well, at least we're not all a bunch of
gorillas living in the belt
of the savannah somewhere like, although
many of the people... What do you mean
we're not?
It's just a metal and
concrete savannah. We're
still the gorillas. Actually, we're
a lot worse than gorillas.
Gorillas are peaceful
vegetable chomping
hermits. Yeah.
We're more like chimpanzees shrieking
white Muppet arm
waving, shrieking, big
tooth, biting,
face eating.
Violence soaked.
Yeah, violence soaked
fiends. Yeah, then think about
Bonobos, so sexed up they can hardly
do anything all day except for going around
servicing each other's needs.
Well, you know, their rep is
a little bit exaggerated. They've been
known to bite a face off themselves.
They're not as inclined
to do it as a regular chimp.
But they'll still
they'll still...
Okay, look, if you're an animal and you
could pull a human's arms off,
why wouldn't you?
Yeah, that's...
You're right. Well, especially if the human
is annoying. Right.
Like keeping you in a prison.
Right.
Or trying to give you a zigzag stripe or
keep you from getting a massage if you're
in line, you know.
Hey, if those Planet of the Apes movies
ever come true, we're history.
We're history, baby.
Why?
Because they'll...
The monkey flu
will kill us if the chimpanzee
arrows and slingshots
don't. Right.
Is that what happened? I missed the premise of the movie
of the third, fourth, and fifth
one.
Well, you know, they remade
all five of them.
I gotta admit, the makeup is a lot
better.
A lot better.
Yeah. I saw one little clip,
I think, and I did
marvel at that, that they look so
advanced now.
Especially for, you know,
giving the dog a pair of pig ears
to wear and then making fun like it's a birthday
cake or something on somebody's hat,
you know. Well, you know how they do
those special effects is they have this helmet
that a very imaginative artist
wears, and he concentrates on
the scene
hard enough it'll come to
life on a
screen. It's like a mind
reading visualization
computer. It costs
a hundred million dollars
a second, though.
But that's how they do it. That's why those movies are so
expensive. Yeah.
That is a pretty, you know, it's a big deep pocket
book. You can only afford to have that done.
Yeah.
Think how many bad takes they have, too.
You know, the guy imagines
he gets a little distracted and suddenly
what's supposed to look like a scary
ugly monster has
lovely, great big breasts
jiggling around, you know, so it's
okay, take three.
Try to concentrate,
Fred.
And they've got you in the
M.I.R. box and they're saying
if you make one little move,
it will show and we'll have to kill you all
over again.
You don't want to get spasmodic
or disagreeable when anybody's
doing stuff like that because, oh,
it's my lunch hour right now, and I
want to go home crying in
a cup, of course.
Where's your cup, Dave?
It's right in front of me,
lad. I need it
at all times now. Not like
in the days past when I could conceal
myself. How often do you
have to empty the cup of tears
you hold under your face?
Oh, I would say the average human
being despised
as a despicable type
of animal. No, no, no. I was going to ask
you how
long does it take for the
cup of tears under your chin?
to fill up?
Usually two to four
months. Oh, you're
not crying at all, man. I thought you were going to say
five or ten minutes.
No, it's just if ever it's very quickly
you can say. He has a great life.
He only has to empty
his tear. You only have
to empty your cup of tears
once every three or four months?
Well, if you are very, very
argumentative, that's a very long time
to have many tears in there.
That means it's
decomposing well.
It's not anything like the Spanish food
I'm going to quit feeling sorry for Dave.
My cup of tears
fills up in about a day and a half.
Well, I wouldn't
go that far because I don't know
what that means. Well, you may not
stub your toe as often as I do,
but every time I do, I cry.
Not because it hurts that much, because I was
stupid enough to stub my toe.
And he's mad at himself
for stubbing his toe.
I'm so mad at myself.
I'm going to hold my breath until I turn blue.
That'll show me.
Oh, man.
I commiserate with you just like
a small package woman.
I can see it coming down the freeway
right in the middle of the road.
Paying no attention to anybody else
who's driving except for
Belinda or whatever her name is.
Oh, man.
Are you playing the Russian music
or is it playing you?
I'm not playing any Russian
music. I'm playing
music by
Cyber Chump.
The construction of things is the
side we're listening to.
It sounds all gentle and magical.
Yeah, it's not distracting is the main
point. I could put on, I could
always put on something
else. It's very
futuristic without sounding
complacently futuristic as if we had
the same, you know, we all had
the same appendices or
variations. Dave,
on this show,
everybody hears a different
piece of music.
I mean, I put on this
sort of all-purpose background
tone and the individual
listener may hear it as synthesizer
music or banjo music
or as tubas,
you know, it depends on what you're oriented
towards. Their own personal filter.
Yeah, your own personal filter.
That is a beautiful, thank you
for letting us get out of that
excretory valve. It just,
it doesn't know how to play the sawbones or
the trombone or anything like that
anymore. Just because.
And we stand by them because
we could, we salute their services
even if it's only
like maybe four or five of them.
I'm not
a sawbones, but I play one
on TV and in a band.
My dog is my sawbones.
I think the dog and the docs
are in league with each other because
the doctors told me I had to walk two
miles every day or I'd die.
And I went, yeah, sure.
I wasn't going to. But now
the dog basically sits next to my
desk and barks in my face
and puts his nose under
my elbow where
it's near my keyboard
to make me take him
for two mile
long walks every day.
So it's like I just can't escape.
I can't escape
this planet. And by the
way,
as a result of this, I
weighed myself the other day. I only weigh
150 ounces now.
Yes, he's just disappearing
into thin air.
He took his toenails off.
I mean, he gave us his toenail
clippings and put them in a little valve
as they used to do in the
ancient imperial days.
He put them toenails
in there and he weighed them up
and it came to exactly
150 OZs
or grams.
Whatever you said.
No, his whole body weighed 150.
No, no, no.
That's his toenails again. His body had
no witness weight because it was all full of
sweat and beaver.
I used to look like Raymond Burr
as Ironsides, but now I
look like Sheriff Rick
Grimes on Walking Dead.
Well, at least you didn't have
the same sexual appetites as William
Burr and Francisco Hernandez
and Franco. He was a bad one.
Did you ever read about him?
Francisco Franco? No.
The general who took over
Spain? Yeah, no, no.
I didn't, I don't, but that's not my favorite
kind of pornography.
Old
fascist porn? No.
I'm not into old fascist porn.
Oh, man, you can't.
I'll leave that to the Trump
voters. I'll leave all
the old fascist, wrinkly
old fat fascist man porn
to the Trumpies, Trumpanzas
as they call it.
Everything old is new.
You can't blame them.
No kidding. The dumb people won.
I'll be that blunt.
Yes, I will, because the show's
almost over. I have to get off the air.
The dumb people won.
Well, but just for a minute.
But like a puppet
or maybe a clavichord
or one of those ancient...
Pay attention, Dave.
First, we're going to...
This is a part that...
Only you're going to hear.
I feel...
It's a...
There, that part's done.
And now we do the end of the show.
Friends, you've been listening to Hour of Slack
number 1,639.
Goodness gracious.
In the middle of September of the year,
the conspiracy likes to call
2017...
Meh.
We know it's not that.
We're not sure what it is.
We'll find out this May 7th.
Or July 5th.
And Dave, I suggest
that you call in
on the next show
in about 15 or 20 minutes.
Okay.
Call in on the next show in about 15...
Because this show's over.
That's it, man.
That's it.
Here, dear.
Take your medicine.
Come on.
Let me have some more pills
before you go.
There you are.
Now take care of yourself.
Yeah, take care of yourself.