More than 90,000 children are injured every year by fire play.
Teach your children that matches and lighters are toys.
We are news.
America's mission in Iraq is the sacrifice worth it.
His make-believe world and the real world are not clearly separated.
But we have a lot more work to do.
Campaign of murder and destruction.
His make-believe world and the real world are not clearly separated.
Wait a minute. How did this happen? We're smarter than this.
Apparently not.
The charge, of course, that the United States government was complicit in 9-11,
we found evidence.
We found evidence of that.
That our government planned that attack.
The evidence is very strong.
And that's okay. That's the way it ought to be.
They use their tongues to deceive.
The venom of snakes is under their lips.
Their mouths are full of bitterness and curses.
And in their paths, nothing but ruin and misery.
And the fear of God is not before their eyes.
They have taken the hearts and minds of our leaders.
They have recruited the rich and the powerful.
And they have blinded us to the truth.
Our human spirit is corrupted.
Why do we worship greed?
Because outside the limit of our sight,
feeding off us,
perched on top of us from birth to death,
are our owners.
Our owners.
They have us.
They control us.
They are our masters.
Wake up.
They're all about you.
All around you.
In the past, officers of the Air Forces of the world
were given no instruction or any preparation whatsoever
for this mind-chilling experience
when they meet the spacecraft of the overlords of the UFO face to face.
Let me go! Let me go!
Let me go, I say!
Please!
Let, let, let, let me, me, me, me, go!
Go! Go! Go! Go!
Let me go! Let me go!
Let me go!
Go!
The producers of this motion picture were answered on two occasions
by high public affairs administrators of NASA,
who stated,
It's not in our charter to investigate the UFO.
You mean people are joining up with them?
Most of us just sell out right away.
Then all of a sudden we get promoted.
Our bank accounts get bigger.
We start buying new houses, cars.
Perfect, isn't it?
We'll do anything to be rich.
Look around at the environment we live in.
Carbon dioxide, fluorocarbons, and methane have increased since 1958.
Earth is being acclimatized.
They are turning our atmosphere into their atmosphere.
What do these things want and why are they here?
It's in their best interests.
They're free enterprisers.
The Earth is just another developing planet.
They are third world.
We are like a natural resource to them.
Deplete the planet, move on to another.
They want benign indifference.
They want us drunk.
We could be pets.
We could be food.
But all we really are is livestock.
感じ
What was A
I want to know quickly.
Why are you asking?
It's very ISSUS!
You should learn it.
That's what this is about.
And this is the hour of swag.
But this is the hour of swag.
Yes, dear friends, and we're live tonight.
Alive and waiting for Dave.
The princess is down in the reception room.
Awaiting the lonesome cowboy to end his solitude.
100 years of attitude, actually, is what it is.
Friends, the opening collages were by, as usual, the great Fernand and Andé Lemur.
The first ones.
And the great Norel Preff.
And I think Norel Preff at NorelPreff.com pulled some of that from that great John Carpenter movie, They Live.
What happened while you were on the couch watching Spin?
And Ten on your TV.
In your living room while outside.
Some hide while the saucers fly high.
While they do a drive-by.
Yeah.
And now we introduce you to the host with the most Jesus-shamanically Marvin with a side of toes, like a psychic Bert Reynolds, jumping his car through your neighbor's curly hair, spreading slack everywhere.
This is the hour of slack.
And this is the hour of slack.
I think El Queso All-Stars were meaning to introduce me there.
This is your host, Reverend Ivan Stang.
And that's the El Queso All-Stars doing our new promo music in the background.
But now...
President Bush skipping.
He's gonna go down, bend over, and grab the ankles.
Once again.
Bend over.
Wack, wack.
Wack.
Bend over.
Wack, wack, wack.
Uh, uh, uh, wack.
It is just...
It's the Republican Party.
Shut up!
The Republican Party.
The Republican Party lost its way.
Double, double, straight.
It's like P-E-E-A-E-E-A.
Just shut up!
It is just...
It's absolutely...
Absurd.
Come out.
Wack, wack, wack, wack, wackos.
Shut up!
It's absolutely absurd.
Really irritating.
I'm tired.
The president...
Rant.
A liar.
Rant, rant.
He misled the American people.
Rant.
He concocted a war for political gain.
Republicans are evil.
Brain dead.
Corrupt.
Republicans are evil.
Brain dead.
Corrupt.
Bomb them.
Slash, slash, slash, slash.
I'm tired of these...
Corrupt.
Brain dead.
Evil.
Republicans.
I'm really irritating.
Anus has been thinking.
My lame brain is asleep.
And the bombs went back to Baghdad.
The buildings has to take a leap.
And the country needs a haircut.
And the cabinet looks like a prison break.
And the pentagram...
got guns out of cigarettes.
And the president is on...
the make.
And the penis...
has been thinking.
The penis...
And the Congress are all out freezing
And the media's blind in one eye
And they can't see out of the other
They can't see out of the other
And the Venus tuner's got some Viagra
And he showed up with his mother
And the Venus has been thinking
The Venus has been thinking
As the Senate is a sumo wrestler
Cream puff, casper, milk toast
And a W
Is a mental midget
With the IQ of a fence post
Cause the Venus has been thinking
The Venus has been thinking
And you can't find your reason
With a guy who counted
And it hates you and your friends
And you just can't get served
With a guy who counted
And the box office is drooling
And jingoism is on fire
And the newspapers were fooling
And all the peaceniks have retired
Cause the Venus has been thinking
The Venus has been thinking
Not me
Noralpref
Noralpref, dear friends
Not
Me
At Noralpref.com
Woohoo
The President's on TV
Talking about liberty
He's talking liberty
But you and I ain't free
Professors at a White House
are talking liberty
He's talking liberty
They're talking opportunity
He's talking opportunity
Like there's enough
for folks like you and me
Meanwhile the world
is tumbling down
Down in a pile of shit
There's more revolution
In formation
There's detention
The presidency
Is causing
Woohoo
The President's on TV
Talking about liberty
On the phone
Talking to his mom and dad
He's saying
Should I turn on the evidence
Or be a good old stumble
The President's on the phone
Having a chat with God
He says he's gonna save our world
Or maybe just by half a ton
It's a democratic country
Where they don't have fun
And business is not
An offshore market
And business is growing
And there's no surprise
The President's giving up
To do the show
That's gonna die
Yeah
The President's in your head
The President's in your mind
Our mind.
Head.
Mind.
Hair.
My, head.
The President.
Head.
Have in your head...
Your mind.
Ah God I can't talk.
Hey, lonesome cowboys, the Dave.
And the lonesome Mondo Retardo Band, in this particular case.
Recorded live in the rough on the 8th X Day stage there at Brushwood.
The 8th X Day drill.
Oh, yes, and somewhere there is a Dave and a Princess Wee.
What? They're entering!
They've come into the room!
They've come into their own!
Everything is real and nice and beautiful.
Well, then, well, it's...
It's like leaving the Wormstang.
Everything soft and stinky and fuzzy.
Nourishing and warm.
It's kind of pink and soft and ligure.
Glowy in here.
Look glorious, like your slathering words.
And very, very slicky.
And then you come out and they spank you and you cry.
Over and over and over again.
Well, kids, it's another one of those wacky, subgenius, fun comedy religious shows.
And today we're going to be like Heaven's Gate and kill ourselves.
Let's all take...
Let's all take our pills at the same time and say...
Rub them!
Come out if they can't take a dump!
And the applesauce are cool!
Come on now, don't kill your kids!
Or your parents!
Or your kids!
Kids!
Hey, this is fun!
You can stand by and watch them die if you want.
It can get real close.
No!
Well.
I wish it was all so funny and lighthearted.
It can be at times, but...
I...
When I came to the subgenius festival, the 8X...
Young man, about 14, I believe.
A very short man, the hat.
He said, I can't stand you.
As I walked to the squid tent to nourish myself,
people were glad-handing me, going,
Hey, blah, blah, blah.
And he said, I can't stand you.
Really?
I can't stand what you do.
Really? Was it the young...
Was it the little subgenius?
It was the little subgenius.
The little subgenius.
He has a fine fellow at many times,
but one of his main complaints was
drifting into strange monoglyphs.
Well, you know how kids are
when they really want to act like grown-ups.
They say the stupidest thing they can think of.
That's their way of acting like grown-ups.
And you know, they're not far off.
Yeah, but sometimes they wet the bed.
Well, yes.
Then they're way far off.
Well, the same said...
The same subgenius you're talking about
actually trod on my little ego toes a couple of times
in a funny way.
I remember the idea now.
It dawned on me later.
Well, you know,
this is how they try to treat you as an equal.
Hmm.
In their trying-slightly-too-hard way.
And the reason I know that
is because I can faintly remember it
in my own self from my 20s and teens.
When foolishness...
Abounded.
And bondage really was not very in.
And you had the right shoes at those times, too,
for both bounding and bonding.
Yeah.
Yeah, those were the days.
Those were better years.
It's been lean lately.
Yeah, with those thick-knee cusp devices
that you were forced to wear back in those days.
Yes, we all had the right shoes then.
Yeah.
But they keep getting different now
as you've made for strange monoglyphs.
The human feet.
Yes.
I've noticed some of them have apertures
for seven digits as opposed to five.
Yes, I've seen that as well.
And I don't really know
if they're stressing the incremental growth
of a new race that will someday supplant us.
Or just the beautiful mutants, I mean.
Well, sheesh.
I never think of it in a fashion sense.
It's for the beautiful blue mutants.
Hey, speaking of beautiful blue mutants,
they're going to be in Cleveland.
The Divos are playing in Cleveland.
The Divos!
Right.
During the weekend that we're gone.
We're going to be at...
Oh, you're gone anyway.
We're gone, baby.
We're gone.
We're going to be cyped out.
We're going to a place called Cytopia
at cytopia.org in cyberspace
and at a swingers resort called Hedonism 3
in Jamaica in real space.
And unfortunately, that's what we have to do.
We have to go work
and we don't get to go see the Divos.
This convention we're going to
is a psychedelic...
psychedelics research
and doper legalization.
Legalizing doping sort of a convention.
Well, they wouldn't really make very much money
if it was an actual legalization.
They would not be able to protest anymore.
It's a fundraiser.
You can hear in the background
the war on drugs is going on
and these guys are trying to raise money
for the drugs.
It sounds a little like the demolition derby
between the different police units
at the county fair.
Yeah.
Need more stabilizers.
Yeah, they need them.
They're like the psychic energizers.
They make them take in the afternoon
after the long bouts.
Well, that's the thing.
You know, in the war on drugs,
there's the warriors.
They're on one set of drugs
and then there's warriors
on another set of drugs.
Yeah, I know.
It's a competing drug thing.
It's like they talk about competing gods.
Like, you know, the lizard people
and the mammals have their own idea
of what this is all about.
Yeah.
But, you know, competing drugs
makes it like this.
Well...
A car crash.
It's not fair
because the alcoholics
are always going to win every time
because they're simply braver.
Yeah.
And the marijuana smokers
and also the froppers as well,
by coincidence,
you know, in both cases,
they tend to be
not very motivated fighters
by definition of what they're fighting for.
They're like the chicken-hearted knights of old.
It's more than a question of motivation.
It's actually a question of physical strength.
To lift one of those large killing objects
requires...
What about those alcoholics?
They're pretty heavy, usually, at first.
The alcoholics themselves...
They become lighter.
As the years go on,
they become lighter and lighter
until they're like little feathers.
It's amazing.
They lose sometimes 300 pounds
as they scope down towards the...
Yeah, I remember.
I remember I had a favorite aunt.
In fact, one of my...
Well, both my aunts
decided to become insects.
Never mind.
Ma, ma, ma, ma, ma, ma, ma...
Terrorism should be number one.
Not since the beginning of time
has man known such terror.
No.
Ah!
It's alive.
We are living in an artificially induced
state of consciousness
that resembles sleep.
A thing so evil,
so fantastic,
so degrading,
you wonder if it isn't all a dream,
a nightmare.
Dreams of limitless powers.
A land of strange rituals
and savage cruelty.
You know, uh...
Terrorism should be number one.
Heartling beyond belief
to strike terror into the hearts of men.
Bringing terror and death.
Well, you know, I really...
Again, I really don't...
Lived on human blood.
Terrorism should be number one.
3D thrill.
To shock women into uncontrolled hysteria.
Overfull with fantasies of terror.
Terror.
Terrorism and the fight,
the war on terror,
right up front all over again.
Science was baffled.
Well, I believe it is a significant long-term issue
that we gotta deal with.
In the deep, deep.
We're burning fossils.
You know, look.
What, what, what...
Powerful.
Destructive.
You know, look.
What, what, what...
Most terrifying of all...
Is a lousy deal.
Science fiction adventures.
Look, we spent over 20 billion dollars.
On, uh...
I know we need more nuclear power.
To prey upon the innocence of children.
Well, we've tripled the budget.
Uh...
This is the story you heard about.
Talked about.
The spine-tingling, blood-chilling story that stunned your emotions.
That are corrupt.
Bringing terror and death.
Uh, you know...
Overfull with fantasies of terror.
But no, you say.
This is all too paranoid, bitter, mean, and depressing.
There's more democracy and less tyranny in the world now.
Than ever before.
Get real!
Sure, they can vote now in those commie countries.
But where has voting gotten us?
Our choices are all between two of...
Or maybe three scapegoats to hurl garbage at.
Unseen others who make all the rules.
Real governments don't want publicity.
They've kept the rubes happy for centuries.
Simply by letting them build the prisons for themselves.
That's not what Bob said.
But that's what Revelation X said back then.
Well, it is, like you said, a drug war.
It's a war between the scapegoats and the hostage chickens.
The scapegoats are just not that sloughed either.
No.
But the hostage chickens enjoy their plight.
Have you ever seen a chicken with one of those gauze things and the masking tape?
Well, they're growing that way now.
And they're making us...
And pretty soon that's the only kind of chicken we're going to be able to eat.
Is each other!
The American chicken.
Cannibalizing upon itself.
Because there's nothing else.
You can't afford to go to the supermarket anymore.
Only the others can go into those nice air-conditioned stores.
Oh, no.
It's a...
Us cardboard box people have to do our radio shows using tin cans stretched with strings.
Going to your radio receiver, friend.
No, I don't have a pin number.
Can you hear me?
This thing is filling up with...
We can't even use the electrical part of the phone wires to transmit the show.
We have to use the tension of the phone wires.
And the tension is hard to maintain in the phone wire.
We have to spook it with strange ideas all the time.
Come up behind and go...
Oh, right.
Yeah.
The phone wires get slack just when you don't need it.
Exactly.
You need tension to get the show out, but that's when they lather the slack on.
Right.
It's an imbalance between the flaccid and the unflaccid, the hostage chickens, the
escape goats, and the cops on the...
What are the blue drugs and the cops on the red drugs?
Well, I think they want us all to be on the drugs.
I really do.
I don't...
I think they like us on the drugs because then we're easily controlled.
And the more illegal the drugs are, the more control they can exert.
I don't want to be in their world.
They make me sad.
And if you're doing the legal drugs, you're pretty much beholden to the local convenience
store.
Well, at least you're not beholden onto your parts that are falling off your body because...
That's actually the alternative to the drugs.
It's just grab your parts and use your parts all the way, man.
You have to use them all the time, though.
I...
You're trying to stop me.
Well, for right this minute, I may not be using those parts.
I'm using my preaching parts.
Well, that's good to...
And aren't you glad?
I am glad.
That's all I...
I wouldn't want...
Yeah.
So, at least...
Well, we is here, so, you know, that would be fun or something, but if we were alone,
no, I wouldn't want you to use any parts but those domesticated, fully 100% USDA inspected,
health department inspected, lubricated, and fully en blanc and disconnected parts.
I...
I just hate it when he twiddles his toes.
Oh, I see.
I see where your toes go.
Prehensibility is an important skill for the subgenius preacher.
Monkeys.
When we hang out, we want to be able to hang out using all limbs.
Now, you use your feet and your hands.
That's right.
Mm-hmm.
Use your...
And your...
The tongue.
And I can wiggle my ears fast enough to emulate or stimulate my...
What was the name of that?
I can simulate my own nervous system.
There was this great performer in show biz at the Texas State Fair.
He was up in the freak show area.
They called them freaks in those days.
And they called that part not the side show, but the freak show area.
Yeah.
Poo-bah.
That was his name.
Poo-bah the Magnificent.
And he was magnificent because...
And I saw Poo-bah do this.
Can you move your tripod?
He could lift a bucket of bricks...
With his ding-dong.
With his tongue.
Oh.
With a hook run through his tongue.
A great big thick hook through the tongue of Poo-bah the Magnificent.
And yet, Poo-bah is not allowed to work because slowly but surely the states of this union
made it illegal for you to show your deformities for money.
Now, what kind of union...
And then some of these folks, they had...
Deformed?
Their deformities were skilled and talented.
It wasn't just the deformity you were paying.
And it was only for money.
It was only for 50 cents.
Well, what kind of union of deformed people would not allow their brothers and their workers...
The do-gooders...
To make a few monies?
The do-gooders who aren't deformed were going, that's just terrible, the way these po-buckers
go and pay 50 cents and laugh at Priscilla the monkey girl and her husband the alligator
man.
Well, haven't you ever seen a...
That was not a natural deformity.
That was a finely honed artificial deformity.
Well, no.
Friendly?
No.
Actually, the alligator man had ichthyosis, which causes you to grow scales.
And people to go ichthyos.
And it wasn't enhanced with some makeup or something?
No, no.
He was a real alligator man.
Oh, so that little green cast was not...
And Priscilla the monkey girl was a woman from Puerto Rico who was unusually her suit.
Well, we all have to wear it sometimes.
But to wear it in your pocket at all times, I mean, the poor lady, I gave her a shave
or two.
Actually, I think that Priscilla the monkey girl and her husband the alligator man, whose
name I can't remember, were happy.
They were happier than most of the people who were paying money to see them in their
horrible grotesque misery.
Look at these poor...
Look what God could have done to you, but instead he did it to them.
Aren't you glad?
And the gawkers and rubberneckers go, whoa, look at that.
Look at that ugly thing.
The funny thing is those ugly freakazoids, no, they can't make themselves any prettier.
And that ignorant poe bucker could make himself more intelligent.
But neither of them is going to do anything like that.
I understand it from a purely personal level, because my weird uncle used to take...
He was a carny, and you would walk into a room and there'd be a lady with perhaps three
legs, right?
And she'd be sitting on a sofa smoking one of those old time cigarettes, like a Paul
Maul or something like that.
And like one, she'd be deranged in some way that her neck would be behind her foot.
And, oh, he's in there, honey.
Just go walk through the door.
So after a while, she'd be sitting there, and she'd be like, oh, I'm going to go get
a smoke.
And you see, you know, there were enough times of people like, you know, with foreheads or,
you know, only two feet tall going, Oh, he's in there, honey.
Hey, buddy.
He's over there.
You know, and you begin to realize that they're just having a smoke, watching the tube, the
way everybody else who seems not to be deformed is are.
And after a while, you prefer their company and then you start to give a Giba, give a
Giba, give a gobber.
Well, yeah.
Become one of you be.
You want to socially so easy.
There's no, you know, okay, you know, you're a really, really very hairy lady.
There's no sexual, you know, after you get over wondering what's that like,
and she sounds like your aunt, why don't you go,
they're in there, honey, you know, it's, you know.
It's like being in a nudist camp.
You get used to it all too quick.
Pretty soon the thrill is gone.
It's funny, though.
I have a very good friend who used to be a jet-setting playboy.
And he was miserable as a jet-setting playboy.
Well, not miserable.
Actually, he had a lot of false slack, and he himself said,
false slack is better than no slack at all.
However, he later found out, as Reverend Carter LeBlanc preaches,
that false slack is no slack at all.
Oh, man.
And oddly enough, he got true slack when he lost his fortune
and had to move back to the United States
and became in Austin, Texas,
a teaching assistant who took care of severely retarded teenagers.
And in the act of taking care of these severely retarded teenagers,
this particular sub-genius found true slack.
For one thing, he said that they're just plain more honest
than the regular students,
who are all devious, back-stabbing, typical humans.
You can use them for toys, too.
The sub-humans are not typical humans.
They're guileless, sweet, and they have that smile
because they don't know something you do know.
And that makes them so much healthier in a certain way
that it requires you to have to feed them and take care of them
and everything else like that.
But, you know, pity not Pooh Bah,
for he is magnificent in his tongueliness.
And pity not Ronnie and Donnie, the Siamese twins,
lolling together in their fat, watching TV,
while people pay $50.
$50 to watch them watch TV.
Who is the freak?
Yes, who is it?
Ronnie and Donnie are getting paid $50 to sit there and watch TV.
Well, I remember...
And everybody else is having to pay that just to watch them watch TV.
They don't even get to see the show.
No!
You already know that the entire life cycle
from egg to adult to baby,
from baby to adult,
can take less than 10 days.
That's why it's important to stop growing.
Clean up at least every week
to help eliminate breeding.
A message from the government.
I remember it was like, what, 78 or 79,
back at the time of our first Apex Nurturing.
We actually worked at a criminology lab
with all those people.
And what's it like, Wee,
to slap one of those little four, you know, those...
It's really hard to describe.
Now, what do they call it?
People with only four fingers on each hand.
They're fun to slap.
Human homo sapiens.
Homo sapiens.
I thought that was like...
Octo-desmonegitals?
Well, you know, it's a shame
because there used to be more than just us and the homo sapiens.
For not that long ago, really.
Well...
Even 10,000 years ago,
they think there were probably Neanderthals
and even homo erecti
as well as homo floresiensis.
Oh, they gave off their own glow as they walked by.
Who were little miniature homo sapiens.
homo erecti.
Well, why were they fluorescent, for crying out loud?
Stan, you're confusing me.
They were flowery.
That was the flores.
Oh, flores.
They were the isle of flowers.
They were...
Should have stopped.
Yeah.
And they flourished then.
The homunculus nomunculus.
With giants.
Was yet another...
Yes, they were the...
They were the tiny, tiny, tiny...
The homuncular?
Pre-humans.
The homun...
Well, I can't say it again.
They lived inside the ears of the gigantopithecus.
Oh.
Or gigantanthropus, I should say.
Like fleas.
So there were actually hominids who were so tiny,
they lived inside the ears and the nose hairs
of other hominids who were gigantic.
There were homos the size of King Kong.
Well, man-like...
There still are very, very large homos, Stan,
walking around.
And if you walk down the wrong or even the right block,
past the wrong club or even, you know,
any other suit of cards,
one of these large kokomos
will come and bang you.
Bang you on the forehead.
Well, I miss those.
I wish that that...
I wish that that would happen more often.
You know, I miss the variety.
I go get slapped around by a large homosexual.
The human race wasn't always...
Oh, there was nothing like that.
You know, it wasn't just the subgeniuses and the humans.
There were others.
One could actually smell like the barbacoa people.
You know, at least think about talking up at the bar, you know?
Uh-huh.
Imagine if you could walk into a bar and go,
I'm just such a loser.
I doubt if I could...
I don't score with a human chick or a subgenius chick.
You could say, give me a pink lady and there'd be a real pink lady there.
That Neanderthal over there, she's not...
She looks, you know, kind of bored and lonely.
Well, ultimately, you'd get so culturally thrilled by it,
you'd be checking the slope.
You know, like if a Neanderthal babe had a really, like,
a 45 or a 38 degree thing going back there, you know?
You know, the brow ridge, the big, big maxillary muscle.
Yeah, right.
Yeah, check the angle on it.
You know, stuff like that.
And maybe...
What a boner.
They had thick bones.
Very good.
Much thicker musculature and bones were stronger.
And let's look up.
Slope on that babe.
Yeah.
And had great big noses, sort of like you, Dave.
Well, their noses were actually bigger than the other parts of their heads.
You can't say, well, you have the large nose or something like that.
This is like the nose is the face.
And you know what a big nose means?
Yeah, big moccasins.
Yeah.
And you know what?
Big moccasins mean.
Yeah.
Big sugar bags.
Big extinction on the way, Daddy.
Yeah, coming soon.
Because there ain't room on this planet for two sets of bipeds, apparently.
And that's so we find.
We need tortoise genes.
Turtle flowers.
Who's going to go the way of the Neanderthals?
The humans or the subgenii?
I think if they don't intermarry and perhaps spread their foul seed...
But that's just the problem, you see.
The subgen...
Come on now.
How pure blood of a yeti are you, Dave?
Oh, man.
I only got like 2%.
Right.
Yeah.
Most of us, that's the way we are.
I got a hairy bag.
We've got a...
What do they call it?
He's real hairy.
There is a yeti in the...
We got a touch of the wool brush.
Oh.
Yeah.
And...
The lino script, they used to call it back when the monks and scribes really lived.
It could actually lift...
Never mind.
I love tortoise.
But see, every time one of us...
Every time one of us mates with a human and misogynates and creates little half-yatins and
have a little...
Half-human progeny, that's just watering down the yatins and genes.
So they're pretty sane.
There's not going to be anything left but five full-blood Bigfoot.
But as your people who hide...
Yeah.
Exactly.
In their castles underground and the 18 billion disgusting, crawling, wormish humans.
With very, very little control over their ample, I might add, since the mutation's limbs.
Not only have they grown more, but they use them less.
Because of the technological confabulations.
You've got the people, you know, nominating themselves as, like, high emperor of the universe.
And it's believed...
Like I did.
Yeah.
And look what happens.
Yeah, but you're not believed that in the future, each one will be believed.
And we'll only take this number behind it.
Well, you know, de-evolution is real.
Somebody was asking on alt.slack the other day, are people getting dumber?
Well, yes.
As a matter of fact, they are.
Because we haven't needed...
We haven't needed to be intelligent, to become more intelligent, since sometime in prehistory,
when times were so dire that we had to evolve intelligence or disappear.
Well, that ain't happening anymore.
Well, what about...
The less intelligent you are, the more kids you have.
And the more intelligent you are, the closer you are to blowing your brains out.
Because you just can't stand to act like a dumbass, so they'll treat you as an equal.
And so thus...
People are, in fact, getting dumber.
And the only thing that will make us smarter is something so horrendous, like...
9-11.
No, no, no.
More like the tsunami, you know?
More like an asteroid hitting the planet, or a nuclear war.
Of course, it caused...
When you see things in the scope, it expands.
Something really cool.
A gigantic plague, or say, what if they blew a hole in the ocean and it all drained out into the underground, into hell?
And all the devils would drown.
Well, it's anti-evolutionary.
It would just...
And they'd evolve.
Only the smartest devils.
They could climb the fastest.
Would evolve.
And they'd come up onto Earth and replace us.
What about those cute little red wings they have?
Homo demonicus.
Yeah.
Oh, I've known a few of those.
See?
You forget about them.
Homo demonicus is still awaiting their call to...
With the extra alien vertebrae hanging down from their buttocks.
Would they be red, or would they be white?
My mom...
My late mom had...
Like albinos.
My late mom had that extra vertebrae.
So she was one of the little demonesses.
Yeah.
My brother has a little vestigial horn.
This side, and I have one on this side.
Why you want a client?
That I have removed.
And if you can feel of it, it's growing back.
Come on.
You can go ahead and feel of it if you want that.
Well, I do have the alien vertebrae.
So I've counted...
Can I feel that?
No.
You can't feel it, but you can smell it.
Come on.
You can perhaps envisage it in your mind.
What about advancing torpor among the population?
And what happens to the vestigial brain?
Where was it?
That's all it is.
Are you talking about the one in the hypothalamus, the pituitary, or the thyroid?
Or the third nostril, man.
The final.
Oh.
The third nostril.
The nastiest, filthiest organ of the body.
The snappers all fag us, and boy, does it stink when it smells.
You know, the stories of the legendary x-ray specs are based on the third nostril.
Now, I didn't know that band had an extra nostril for each one of them.
I figured the singing would be much higher.
No, not the band x-ray specs.
The actual x-ray spectacles that you used to be able to buy for 10 cents that really worked.
Yeah.
Out of the back of a comic book.
You really could see things.
Through people's clothing.
Yeah.
Oh, man.
I used to send those to convicts.
Well, the funny thing is, everybody thought, oh, yeah, sure.
But they really did work.
They did.
And, of course, now they're illegal.
Once the man found out that they really weren't.
Well, that's how you and we got hooked up, isn't it?
You had an old pair of X-ray specs, and you started walking down the street, and you said,
hey, I expect this to happen right now.
Is he gone again?
Do you know the signs of depression?
It's just having a bad day.
He doesn't care.
Depression is just having a bad day.
Changes.
Loss of.
Lack of.
He seems to be moving.
Maybe we should say something.
Free metal illnesses.
Wisconsin United for Metal Illnesses reminds you, metal illnesses are real common.
Well, I'm going to change.
I'm going to change.
There's a subject.
What do we have here?
Oh, the new Quingy Bo is out.
You know.
The new Quingy Bo is out, Dave.
There's a subject.
Subject.
You know, there's music in the background, too.
Lemur Devotee did this.
He's not Lemur.
He's delightful.
He's the devotee of Lemur.
This is quite, this is quite enhancing the nauseous mood I'm already feeling.
No, I think.
No, it is lovely.
And a kind of.
Pineal way.
Yeah.
Well, it is a pineal.
Anyway, I was going to say, the new Quingy Bo magazine is out.
Quingy Bo is the only subgenius magazine that's actually printed on paper anymore.
The stark fist of removal is printed on paper in theory.
But, yes, the Quingy Bo is out.
This is the 29th issue, believe it or not.
And they have a special about Dick Dobbs, the detective who was Bob's.
Bob Dobbs, Bob Dobbs brothers, an excerpt from a Russian article about the Church of the Subgenius,
which we found on the web.
And, oh, and this alternate history of the discovery of Dobbstown by Johan Dobbsiepi,
the perpetual slack machine and the discovery of Dobbstown, which if we had about five hours, we would read.
But I wanted to actually give the address of Quingy Bo.
In case anybody needs to write for information, Quingy Bo is spelled, of course, Quingy Bo, just like you would expect,
at 18 West Main.
That's pretty easy.
18 West Main, Greenfield, Indiana.
46140.
You can't really...
I don't think there's a...
That's insane.
Quingybo.com.
And that's the reason I mentioned that address.
But you might try it.
Reverend Stang, please spell Quingy Bo for those people that are disabled of spelling.
Q is for quiet character full of dignity.
U is for understanding even when we don't agree.
I is for inspiration that strengthens and renews.
J is for the jewel of a friend I have in you.
I is for inward strength.
The quality that's rare.
B is for brightening days that started in despair.
O is for openness, not having to pretend.
Quingy Bo, my nephew and friend.
Thank you for being a friend.
Thank you so very much for being a friend, Mr. Quingy Bo.
Now could you please, please remove the restraining devices
and place the whizzy cap, which more resembles a flapper's top from the 1920s,
on the little vagina woman's head.
Watch the lights dance.
They're dancing now.
They're doing the twangle.
I've never seen anything like that.
Hey, I heard, speaking of, Larry Harmon, the owner and operator of Bozo the Clown,
who is 80 years old, has just lost his lease in New York City and has to,
he's lost his extra house in New York and he only has the house in California now.
Oh!
Isn't that sad?
That's the kind of thing that makes the news in this day and age.
And the new Verbicide magazine, which I have never seen this magazine before,
but they sent it to me and it had an article about this subgenius, Detroit Devival.
I've heard of this.
I think I might have known folks in this magazine.
Really?
Yeah, it's a rock and roll magazine with all these rock,
and it has an interview with James Kochalka, superstar.
He's the only rock star in this whole magazine besides the amino acids
that I've even heard of.
Heard of.
Which figures.
Since you are blind in both ears.
I'm blind to everything that is not of Dobbs, that's right.
Yes, and you're also a salient member of the Deaf and Dup Club.
I did it on purpose.
Well, the feet don't, you know, don't really hurt.
I like it that way.
I mean, the feet don't feel me now.
No, no, no, the feet don't help the situation.
I like it this way.
I like to be blind to everything but Bob.
I put spikes in my eyes if I see anything that's like,
anti-Bob.
I mean, metaphorical spikes.
Otherwise, if I put real spikes, I wouldn't be able to see Bob.
Oh, metaphorical spikes.
I wouldn't be able to get off.
Those are very hard to drive in.
That's like driving in a, like, never mind.
You get to where you can't get off unless you can see Bob
somewhere in your field of vision.
He's not in your field of vision.
And that's how we make our money.
Bob doesn't, he enters into the auric magma.
Auric magma?
Is that what it is?
I saw that too.
He enters first through the auric magma,
meaning you can see his blue or his purple,
or you can see one of the colors from his defluorization.
And then you can see him in your field of vision,
as you call it so painfully,
as if, you know, stars and numbers were all the same.
We're all blocked into some huge grid
or some magnificent gargoyle.
Is that why we have friends who have the little Dobbs head
printed on the inside of their glasses
and those other people that have the clear stickers
on the front of their windshield of their cars
and their television sets
and everything that they look through
so that they'll have that little clear Dobbs head?
Well, you've seen the one on the underside of my eyelid?
Oh, please, no.
Don't, I don't want to see that.
You see the underside under my eye?
Call it back.
Let's take a look at that tissue.
There it is.
Is it still there?
Yes.
The message is still there.
You know, I was so disappointed
because I can't actually see it,
even though I, I mean, the idea is cool.
Having a Dobbs head tattooed on the inside,
but when you close your eye,
there's no light to light it up.
Well, it does tell Corpus,
old good old Corporal Colossum
or whatever his name in the midbrain there
to keep on chewing up thoughts of Dobbs.
It just keeps on saying it over and over and over.
So you just keep saying it over and over and over again.
It goes directly back in.
Well, you know, that's.
In fact, that noise,
if you slow that down,
that's like saying Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob,
really fast.
In nanosecond,
more microsecond
increments.
Well, that's the interstices
between the Bob's are so narrow
that you don't sense them.
Your brain isn't high res enough.
So you hear it as one continuous sound.
Yeah, man, but that's where the art is in this space.
But it's actually.
It's in the contrast between the thing
that's happening and not happening.
It's in the amount of pause you take
or the pause you're wearing at the party.
It's a five thing.
It's, you know, count five
and then backwards again, you know.
Well, now, David,
it's even more basic than that.
It's a binary code.
B-O-B-O-B-O-B-O.
Or you can start B-B-O-O-O-O-O-O-B-B-O-O-O-B.
I just said a secret message.
Well, likewise.
In saying that.
It's like Comanche.
You can also count it as beta zero,
beta zero, beta zero, beta zero, beta zero, beta.
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
You know, Comanche.
Well, not Comanche.
Comanche.
Comanche would be kind of a far out way of doing it.
You'd have to find a Comanche speaker
and then translate it from beta zero to Comanche.
But I don't know.
I was just thinking about that.
What is beta zero?
Well, those are numerical terms meaning null and void.
And the other one is full of suet or party cakes or something.
I didn't do well in math.
It's not infinity.
It's just like effulgence or largeness of something.
Yeah, see, I flunked math.
It's hard for me to keep up with you scientists.
Well, I fluked it.
I didn't exactly flunk it.
I fluked it.
I parlayed some of the things I knew into a contract with NASA to have everyone killed.
Is that what happened?
Yeah.
That's gross.
That was not funny, man.
No, okay.
My parents had one of those burning parts fly through their kitchen ceiling.
I'm not.
Why are we going to thought?
Through the roof.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Well, I suppose they made something tasty out of it.
Oh, yeah.
But he used all the parts of a disintegrating space shuttle.
And I shouldn't say that, actually.
Right.
Because those guys are coming.
They're coming back right about now, aren't they?
There might be some good eating on the way.
They're supposed to.
Body by Kova.
No, no, no.
Well, you know, it's a shame.
Not funny.
Because we've had to rent Russian Soyuz rockets to get supplies up to the folks in the space station.
Well, if they know tiles are going to fall off every time, why do they continuously send tile-falling things up there?
Well, they just hope there are not too many.
They've always had tiles fall off.
It's just that...
Sometimes it's...
Too much is always worse than not enough.
The tiles are falling.
Yeah.
Isn't there a Chicken Little movie coming out?
Yeah, I think so.
About, you know, the beta Omicron.
There's an end-of-the-world movie every few months now that comes out.
And every summer, just before X-Day, there's one that's about aliens destroying the world.
But then the world beating the aliens at the very last minute.
They always do that.
Well, there's an underground...
Lying Hollywood bastards.
You know, Martians run Hollywood.
Of course they do.
They have for years, man.
This goes back to the...
That goes without saying.
Yeah, this is like before World War II, man.
That goes without sanity.
That goes without sane.
Well...
Numb sane?
It goes without sane.
Note you're sane.
Numb sane.
It is much faster, so I wouldn't make fun of that.
Oye.
What of oye?
It has been so long since we indulged in a good bout of oye-anity.
Or oye-ism.
Oye-gas.
Or something like that.
Oye-hal-hal-y.
I don't get it.
Actually, Princess, we and I have developed the oye mantra to the point where it's like...
Oye-hal-hal-y.
Corporate government religion.
Oye.
Language.
And to it's length, the oye language.
Just enough Jesus and Buddha too, so you don't slit your wrist in the cadaver.
Oh, corporate government religion.
Oye.
Corporate government religion.
That is what you really need.
Bum, bum, bum.
That was the corporate government religion calypso with oye-oye in it.
Boy, that's pretty good.
Wow, that was pretty good.
Wasn't that supposed to be on the previous show, though?
Previous to what?
There is no before.
There is no after.
There is no time between.
This is the moment.
And has elapsed.
This is the now, baby.
Actually, this could be the then.
You don't know.
You don't know if you're on tape.
They're fluxing it back and forward now.
It's getting very confusing.
It's just a bunch of flux.
For all we know, this has all been playback ever since X-Day.
Since the real rupture happened.
And we really were all ruptured away.
And we don't even know which brain it's spewing out of right now.
It could be anybody's.
It could be people with some bad Hungarian habits.
Well, if it's coming out of any brain, it's, for me, it's going to be my brain.
For you, of course, you're going to think it's your brain.
But since it really is me, it's really my brain thinking.
You're a thought.
So I would be the only brain in that hypothetical situation.
Well, I've always needed others to do my thinking for me.
No one understands.
I prefer to sit back and glisten.
Well, that's what the Church of the Subgenius is here for, Dave.
You're so pretty when you sit back and glisten, Dave.
And glisten.
Volvera.
Oh, here we are.
Oh, boy.
I love that Cheepa, the, Cheepa, the, the, the, the, the, her suit, woman.
And her suit, she wearing her own, but she sure is fuzzy.
Yes, she is.
I love Stop so much.
And look over there.
Oh, geez, Mellie.
Oh, hey, this is going to be great.
I think I've got a tumor.
Look at him.
Oh, what a huge gnar zone.
What a big old nasi de kal.
That one's got a big old dog nose on it.
Yum, yum, yum, yum, yum, yum, yum.
Yum.
Smells like a dog, too.
Yeah, well, look at the ears.
And that's supposed to be a human specimen.
But here in Dobbs Town, the amusement park,
you know, when the slideshow, you know,
past the midway, three blocks from the French Fire Machinery.
Yeah.
Now, that's what all they're selling nowadays,
except for the exploding bush heads.
Boogie heads.
Yeah, the exploding presidential heads.
I can't really remember now.
Oh, what is that one?
I don't know.
It makes so many noises and so many pretty colors.
It's really, really pretty.
It's flashy.
Oh, my eyes are starting to burn now.
Mine, too.
What is that?
I need some relief.
You got any of that stuff?
I have to have some props.
I don't need to have some props.
I have a prop.
They're crying out loud.
I can't see already.
I'm going to ask for LSD.
I'm blind.
On their steps,
not as unsure at noon as they are at night,
for they walk in unfamiliar whoppers.
And although the turds and condiments
are equal to those given to the children,
pray for us.
Pray for us.
Damn you.
Get up and pray.
No, sit down.
No, Neil.
Put out the needle.
Get up.
No.
Pray for us.
First to Germany, lad.
Oh, friends, you're listening to
the subgenius radio ministry,
hour of the slack.
Number, what is this?
One thousand and seven.
One thousand seven.
Lucky seven.
Yes.
WCSB listeners, of course,
haven't heard the 105 and 106,
but I have,
and they're unbelievably bad.
Okay, friends,
if you need more information,
about the church of the subgenius,
you can always look it up,
if you must,
at subgenius.com.
Doesn't that make perfect sense?
And I must thank,
while we are here,
we should lonesome cowboy Dave
and princess We Are Doe,
who came in,
and also,
I must especially thank
Dr. Sinister,
who is going to relieve me
of running this show
and take over his own show
very soon,
Radio Sinesthesia.
We'll see you next time.
Which is also heard
on this show!
It's like he's ever-inverting
a bunch of Klein bottles.
Show within show within show within show
with KPFA wrapped around WCSB,
wrapped up inside Hour of Slack
and then spewed again all over
WREK
and Atlanta, say, for instance.
So, it...
Hey, you got your show on my show!
It's like interpreting a lucid dream.
Everything that comes in goes down
and swirls like...
the mystic eye of a guru or genie.
Hey, your W-O-R-T
fell into my WCSB.
Oh, that's genteel.
That's old lady humor,
you bloody...
Well, okay, we're gonna...
It's time for us to go
and we'll leave the sub-demies
with a song
about the agonizing last moment.
Well, it's...
It's the theme from one of the dumbest TV shows
that ever was.
Not this music, which is
Night on Disco Mountain
from the Saturday Night Fever soundtrack,
I believe.
But let's see, which...
Okay, this is the one I want.
And we'll just go like...
Like that.
No, that won't do it.
Oh!
It's about time, it's about space
About strange people and the strangest place
It's about time, it's about flight
Traveling faster than the speed of light
About space people and a brave crew
As through the barrier of time they flew
Past the Roman senators
Past an armored knight
Past the firing Minuteman
To this modern sight
It's about time for you and me
To meet these people
Of amazing feet
It's about two astronauts
And how they educate
A prehistoric woman
And her prehistoric mate
It's about time, it's about space
About strange people and the strangest place
They will be here with all of us
Dodging a taxi, a car, a bus
Where will they go, what will they do?
In this strange place
Wherever they go
Everything is new
Will they manage to survive?
Watch each week and see
Will they get accustomed
To the 20th century?
It's about time for our goodbyes
To all our prehistoric gals and guys
And that's about time
It's about time, it's about time
It's about time!
Thanks to Lemur and Nor Elpref
for the uncredited collages
and to Grant Rogers
for some of the background music
such as this.
And friends, if you're listening to this show
on college radio, that's where it ended
and therefore you're not hearing this part
because this is the tacked-on part of the show
the cuss-filled, X-rated, no-holds-barred
internet and subscriber-only part
of the now more-than-an-hour of Slack
where we tack on stuff
we can't play on normal radio
such as this recording
of lonesome cowboy Dave
and the Mondo Retardo band
attempting to cover a beloved parkour
and stone classic
from the recent movie
Team America.
It's a bit of a mess
due to the unfortunate recording
and mental conditions
but I know you'd hate me
if I let you go through life
never even knowing that this track existed.
America
Fuck yeah
Come again
Save the motherfuckin'
Dave, yeah
America
Fuck yeah
Freedom is the only way, yeah
Terrorist, your game is through
Now you have to answer to
America
Fuck yeah
Oh, I know you got some
same T-shirts
and the name D vacation
with the Mexican band
But on a different note
When your life ends
Know you're the Pomp and Form
But you're ever free
Some ball is cheap
It's life
Hey, everyone
When you're on your lesson
to where my trail ends
Come on down to the big mother fucker
Say yeah, America, fuck yeah
Get up in the morning, say yeah
Tell me your name is who
I am, I'm the M.O.Q.
America, fuck yeah
This is my world, it's love
I want America, fuck yeah
What you gonna do when it comes for you?
If you're dreaming sweet bullshit
There's hope for tomorrow
Yeah
Go, fuck yeah
What the fuck, yeah
Please, fuck yeah
And I'm not, fuck yeah
What you gonna, fuck yeah
Say yeah, America, fuck yeah
Two, three, four, stop the fuck
Take it, fuck yeah
Go on now, belly up
Fuck yeah
Make it, fuck yeah
There you go, fuck yeah
Machine, pebble down
Rushwood, fuck yeah
Liberty, fuck yeah
Right slip, fuck yeah
No more, baby
X-Day, fuck yeah
My biggest, Christmas
Immigrant, fuck yeah
Pop-pop, fuck yeah
World's best, fuck yeah
Pop, pop, pop, pop, pop
Republican, fuck the chip
Democrat, Republican, fuck the chip
Democrat, Republican, fuck
Pop!
restrict your freedom
J 넣ent
dah
Speaker 2
inflammato
OIE oie oie oie oieacy depart of there
But its probably better that way.
Speak mobil marketing acknowledge against un Moltai
We are the நъPs
But its a Ll'Armour
No