Ladies and gentlemen, this is what is commonly known as money.
It comes in all sizes, colors, and denominations, like people.
We'll be using quite a bit of it in the next hour.
Luckily, I have enough for all of us.
The Self Genius.
Our self.
You've got a macabre sense of humor.
Neither do I.
My dear listener and friends, this hour of Slack number 1180 is not in fact that,
but is truly Bob's Slack Time Funhouse number 740.
Yes, it's a Suzy the Fluzy show, an incredible show,
which she did a few weeks ago when the Econo Cataclysm hit.
This is a collage episode.
It's an episode that she calls not the Stock Market Show,
but the Stark Mock It Show,
a depression comedy.
First broadcast on Bob's Slack Time Funhouse at WREK in Atlanta,
one of the greatest college stations of this or any other planet, friends.
And so without further ado, we go directly into the Econo Cataclysm,
of Suzy the Fluzy.
Apples.
Get your apples.
Come on, you financial whiz kids.
You've got to keep your strength up while your whole house of paper crap is collapsing around your ears.
Apples.
Come on, you failures.
Get your apples.
Lord, I'm so hungry.
But I don't have enough to buy an apple.
Oh, please, dear God.
Can I trade you my blackberry for it?
Ah, what the hell.
Sure, lady.
It's just such a kick to see the mighty fallen.
Sure, I'll trade your blackberry for an apple.
Fruits, fruit.
Here you go.
Oh, bless you, bless you.
And here you go.
Sweet.
Soccer.
Ah!
Hey, lady, this isn't a blackberry.
This is a wallet.
And it's stuffed with...
Fifty-five thousand dollars?
Come back here, you thief.
You ripped me off.
This won't even buy a freaking paperclip.
Oh, damn it.
Stiffed again.
Ah, hell.
I guess I really shouldn't laugh at them.
I know their pain.
Oh, yeah.
I was rich once.
I put half my money in toilet paper.
And the other half in revolving doors.
And I was wiped out before I could turn around.
And it wasn't hard to do at all.
You know, you can't help but find the poor house.
It's the last address on Easy Street.
So now we're all in the same sad sinking ship, aren't we?
Yep.
Looks like the worm has turned.
The chickens have come home to roost.
Our hash has definitely been settled.
And now everybody's in the same sad-ass situation that I've been in for years.
Oh, yeah.
Welcome to the exciting new world of dumpster diving and do-it-yourself dentistry.
And, hey, if you can scavenge enough ketchup, dog tastes good.
Oh, and all of the seekers.
All I can do is find more reason to believe the word of Dobbs.
Because if you remember what he prophetically spouted in a fight with his neighbors back in the mid-50s,
it's all come horribly, horribly true.
You'll all be eating roach crap by the turn of the century.
Get your toilet green here.
Try new.
New toilet green.
Why?
Hey!
Toilet green.
Toilet green is people!
And people taste good.
Yes?
Don't open the show.
Thought you might want to celebrate.
Fresh off the boat.
Well, you heard wrong.
Pull up a coffin and lie down with the rest of us.
Gee, business is so tough that nobody wants to owe me anymore.
You can go.
Gather round, people gonna tell you what they're on.
About the time that the clock's all quit.
And the robber will fail.
Every day of the week, a fortune given away.
Yay!
The music quickly changes as we move into the Wall Street area.
The financial district.
The cash register of the world.
Whatever you want to call it.
Money means security.
No money means terror.
Oh, oh.
This is Angel.
We are the Android Sisters.
Today's topic is money.
Money is important.
Everyone needs money.
Have you been deprived of money?
Do you suffer from money withdrawal?
Do you need a money fix?
Is your money fix not big enough?
What if you lost your job?
The job you can't stand.
The job a machine could do.
Do it.
Do it better.
What if you lost that?
Then what?
Uh oh.
No money means terror.
Oh.
Are you happy?
Do you wonder why you are not happy?
Do you live in a constant state of fear?
Have they made you into a money junkie?
Do you hate your job?
Do you have a job to hate?
Are you looking for a job?
Are you looking for a job you will hate?
A job that could be done by a robot.
A job to save the world.
Is this not a stupid way to live your life?
You need money.
Money means security.
No money means terror.
Are you happy?
Do you wonder why you're not happy?
Do you live in a constant state of fear?
Do you know how easy it is to control someone in that state of mind?
Do you know how many hours a day you think about money?
Do you ever think about how much you think about money?
Aren't you sick of thinking about money?
Money.
Uh.
Eh.
Pooey.
But money means security.
No money means terror.
Oh.
Welcome, ladies and gentlemen, to this guided tour of your New York Stock Exchange.
The shares we trade here are owned by millions and millions of ordinary Americans,
just like you and Howard Hughes and J. Paul Getty.
The market is a ticker, a slender piece of tape,
which notifies the...
The public of its economic shape,
which, if it weren't legal, would be statutory rape,
that's perpetrated daily from ten to half past three.
A simple little business.
It's A, B, C.
A is for analysts.
These are highly skilled professionals
who spend their entire lives studying the market.
Sir, do you think the market is going up or down?
We have every confidence that if there is no decline,
the market will go higher.
We passed the New York Stock Exchange,
the nerve center of the U.S. stock market,
where transactions reaching into the billions are undertaken every day
in the closely packed office buildings and banks.
Today, a seat on the exchange costs over $500,000.
Gold.
Real gold.
Ha, ha, ha.
More. Give more.
You've got it bad.
Yeah, take it to the security bank.
I'll fix you up.
Thank you.
There you are.
You can count on Acorn immediately.
Thanks.
Good luck.
Acorn, we're going to become bankers. Rich bankers.
What for?
Make money, get rich, live high.
How much more high you want to live than we've been living?
Well, you're going to go to work,
and you're going to like it.
I'm going to work, but I ain't going to like it.
Don't forget, being a banker in a small town's a big job.
You know, you're so close to the folks you deal with.
Why, your word has got to be twice as good as their bond.
There. I'm through preaching.
From now on, you're the chief.
I'm just a depositor.
Well, you know, sometimes it's not enough.
Merely to teach, one has to punish as well.
A little bit of the old pause.
Pause for pause.
Here.
Here I am, Daddy.
Mine, what a big cigar.
Yes, and a big man that smoked it too, honey.
Mm-hmm.
Honey, I does everything in a big way.
It must have cost you a lot of money to keep that car in show for while you were born.
Chicken feet, honey. Just chicken feet.
You must be powerful rich.
Oh, I got a little. I got a little.
More, more, more.
Lay more eggs. More.
Gold. Real gold.
More. Give more.
Some more.
More, more, more.
Ouch, said the hooker.
You see, mark that person of irritable mirth.
He's made a million out of man's inhumanity to man.
Salt of the earth.
Yes. Salt of the earth.
Perhaps together we can restore his faith in the mystery of life.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Oh, where is the money?
Look up, the skies are sunny.
Oh, magic action, you are through.
You've done us wrong.
Sure is a pretty thing.
Hey, what's all this?
Oh, I'm just getting ready for the new
vegetable present, that's all.
What's all this about a new present?
Ha, ha.
Let me resuscitate you.
Grrr, grrr, grrr.
Say, Mom,
by the way, why don't you let me take a shot
at reinvesting those government 3.5%
of yours? I can get you 6 or 7%
easy. You must never touch those bonds.
They're here for the protection
of depositors. Oh, don't be nervous.
It'll all be over before you know it.
Ha, ha, ha.
Money, money, money. Money, money, money.
Money makes the world
go round the world, go round the world.
Go round. Money makes the world
go round. Of that we can
be sure.
Stop on being poor.
Money, money, money. Money, money, money.
Hi there, investors. This is the friendly voice
of Dow Jones reporting on the state of the
bustling American economy.
At 12 noon, the Dow Jones averages
are down 7.43.
Next report
on the state of the bustling American economy.
will be at 1 p.m.
The bigger deals to come.
Oh, my goodness. Champagne.
You lived in the poorhouse.
Oh, well, on a day like this,
we ought to get fuzz, I mean fizzed up.
Oh, I suppose you should. There we are.
The first
in this country on the brink of a financial
absentee. Oh, things would be
all right if people take their money out of their stock
and stick their foot in it.
Drowned by the promise of the women
and the lace
and the gold and the cotton
and pearl.
It's a place where they keep
all the darkness you need.
You sail away from the light
of the world on this trip, baby.
You will pay tomorrow.
You're gonna pay tomorrow.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
That comes along with the territory.
Right?
If you're one of the high rollers.
Lots of status.
If you will, I'm gonna strip you naked.
So let me give you some ammunition
about the people out there who think
that they're doing okay.
Now, one of the things you never want to come up to me
and say is I'm doing okay.
Okay.
It's all I'm taking from you.
Get back!
Ow!
Stop pummeling me!
It's really painful!
That's what I thought.
Ow!
Punk ass.
That is true.
I can't stand that because I know how okay
most people are doing.
You've heard me say that most people
in this country are broke.
Most of the people in this country are broke.
Why do I say that?
Why?
Have you been part of the 5% cutback?
You're not doing right.
Has your rent just gone up this month?
Yeah.
Has the inflation escalator just hit you?
Holy mackerel, what a lie.
Shut up.
What do you really mean by that?
If you answer yes to any of those things,
you're broke.
Don't feel bad.
You're in the majority.
The first thing I write on the board
is a large circle,
and I put a dollar sign in it.
And what I want you to do for the moment
is envision that as your income.
The most profound thing you need to know is this.
Whatever it is,
it is.
This could be a problem.
If that's all you have to work with,
you can't keep living on the if-come.
Ah, that's what means
that you've prepared for an emergency.
Where are those keys to my safe deposit box?
I'm going to take those $100,000
with the government's bombs
and I'm going to pack them right up
the head of the seller
so everybody can see them.
I'll stop the gold rush.
They'll never catch a banker
with his pants down.
Put on your pants, Captain.
Please.
Once again, attack dogs were used
to put down an attack dog.
Another food riot.
Now here's Jay with another gloomy market report.
Lovely day, isn't it?
Lovely.
Papers say nice day tomorrow, too.
I haven't seen the papers.
Yes, well, there's not much in them.
Not much.
From what had gone before,
it was clear that this was to be
no picnic.
Say,
did you ever hear of a thing called
amnesia or aphasia?
That means when your whole past
has been wiped out,
when you can't remember,
anything that's ever happened before.
Well, believe me,
I'm saving my money for a rainy day.
Goodbye, moderation!
If a person goes out
and hangs on a binge,
they can't come home and say,
I'm going to pray and have this not happen.
They're still going to have their hangover.
God's going to punish them.
They're going to lay in it
until that part of it is gone.
My God!
In other words,
once you create a problem
through a sin in one form or the other,
you're going to live with it,
the built-in punishment thereof.
Hello, Bob?
Say, listen, Bob.
Yes, give it the words.
We'll hear everything right away.
All right.
The most glamorous street of America,
Millionaire's Row,
is where the homes and estates,
of many of New York's
wealthiest psychiatric and alcoholic citizens, stand.
I awoke this morning in my push-button
Neiman Marcus said,
La, la, la, la.
I caressed the sables that had died
to provide me with a spread.
La, la, la, la, la, la.
And I don't know if I ever thought
of it quite this way before.
But I woke this morning
with a loud, clear conclusion in my head,
which said,
rich is better.
Um.
Rich is better.
Shut the hell up.
We never see a headline
without a red line today.
And when we see the land floor,
we can look that guy right in the eye.
We're in for money.
Come on, honey.
Let's spend, let's spend, let's spend
all we've got.
Prosperity will get them into hot water.
But it takes money.
We haven't got it.
Suppose I knew a way to get a hold of some money.
How?
We can't afford to do anything crooked.
You understand?
Hey, listen, I know it's crooked.
But I got into this jam through helping you fellas.
It's a shame to leave all that money down there.
Yeah.
That town owes us plenty.
It sure does.
It sounds good, but what about Bob's orders?
We won't even know about it
until we give him his share.
Just remember that this thing
isn't as black as it appears.
Anybody for me?
Stop it!
This, this is just...
I am just...
But I'll take all the responsibility.
Well, I don't like it.
Oh, yeah?
After all, now,
the fine hell I'd be
if I didn't take a chance for it.
What's a friend good for
if he don't stand by a man
when he's in trouble?
Oh, thanks, Harvey.
Just give us a line
relieving us of all responsibility.
You're right.
Well...
I know I'm right.
And someday you'll thank me for this.
Say, I'm thanking you right now.
Someday he'll thank you, eh?
Only when he does,
I won't be here.
And a chill of the heart
and his Austrian son,
left to hide out in Rio
to fly out and relive the past.
Sammy showed them around
when they got into town,
but he warned them the rules
they'd be changed
since they played the game last.
Oh, the chill of just grinning
and wanking his friend.
I forget what went down.
After that, it all happened so fast.
God bless America!
Ah!
Come on!
Let's get out of here!
Looks as if you were expecting a childbirth.
And how.
Stores bankrupt,
factories closing,
banks failing.
One never knows when they're gonna be wiped out.
Oh, you're getting yourself all a-twitter over nothing.
Your money's safe in our bank.
Well, how do I know where it is?
I'm not losing any sleep over it.
Everybody over in Hillsdale had confidence in their bank,
and it blew up this morning.
Oh, crap! It's on fire!
It is, ah!
It was full of frozen assets.
Well, nobody's gonna freeze mine.
Come on!
Bob generally knows what he's doing.
He does everything for the-
Sit down. Shut up.
Our government is fully aware of its difficulties.
It can pull itself out of its economic rut
without the assistance of any other crackpot.
Its attempted action must therefore be attributed
to a diseased mind,
afflicted with hallucinations of grandeur,
and obsessed with an insane desire
to become a public benefactor.
One has to be smart when observing the effects of money on the arts.
Another fine mess.
No, we have but slept.
Slept?
Yes, through the economic recession, you see.
What?
Well, five million years ago, the galactic economy collapsed.
And seeing that custom-built planets are something of a luxury commodity...
You know we built planets, do you?
Oh, well, yes. I'd sort of gathered.
Fascinating trade.
But like the good book says,
there are bigger deals to come.
And that's bad.
There was something funny about the whole business.
The market has a logic!
Whose wonders never cease!
It's basically predictable and free of all caprice!
It hits the floor in time of war and lore when there's peace!
And all the smart investors rely on LSD!
A simple little business.
It's A-B-C!
Oh, my God!
Do you realize if you don't open that bank and pay me back what you owe me,
your grandchildren will be on the street?
The bank will open.
You'll get every cent.
I'll believe that when I see it.
But there'll be a warrant on for it.
A warrant? For whom? What's his description?
George wondered if his name was on that list the cops had found in the cabinet.
You know, Bob, I don't know.
I told you long ago that that mongoloid George was our nemesis.
Now he has struck his final blow.
George! Look what you've done!
Uh... uh... uh... uh...
Warrant, you're... you're an idiot.
Now that jailer, he saw all the smoke in the air
And he wished he was there
Instead of inside watching ourselves
But, Harland, if I don't get those bonds today, the bank will have to close.
So we said, go do your share
We ain't going nowhere
He agreed, grabbed his gun with a smile
And he wished us all well
What kind of a bitch are you, fish-face?
Before he had got to his car
We had cut through the bar
Snuck outside and just sat back to watch
Till the bank fell
The shock and terror had made him wet his pants.
A few or three days ago, he ordered a sign,
This bank open for business.
And I ain't seen him since.
Shall I cart it over and put it up?
Sure. Put it up.
Yeah.
The bank's gonna open.
Oh, well, I'm awful glad for all of our sake.
Yeah. Goodbye.
Goodbye.
What a bad joke.
As we move deeper into the heart of Wall Street,
We pass Trinity Church on your right.
Why did God let this happen?
Jesus, you're a thief.
And John the Baptist and Uncle Sam
They was carrying the plans for some new kind of object for peace.
John the Baptist and Uncle Sam
When all of a sudden this river-gate band
With their guns in their hands
Stopped the boat that demanded
That look in the top-secret case.
Oh, but just in the nick of time
They were stricken blind by a low-blind plane
With no name and no number to trace.
Oh, but just the same
John lost his head and they said he was gone.
He tried to run but someone held him down
And Sam tied up his hands.
He cried out to his boss but he couldn't get across
Cause the knives were all down and the crowd
Cheered him on from the stands.
But he finally did get away.
You can find him today.
It's a silver place and still waits for the boss to call back.
Prosperity will return in a moment.
A tablet bears these famous words.
Give me your tired, your poor, your huddled masses yearning to be free.
All your peace are belong to us.
Music
And if there are warning signs on the horizon,
We need to pay attention to them.
How do you know that?
How do we know that?
Um, and we need to act in a positive way
To make sure that our economy continues to grow
So people will be able to find high-paying, high-quality jobs.
I, I, I, I, I, uh...
Don't look now, but there's something funny going on over there at the bank, George.
Gosh, okay.
I've never really seen one, but that's got all the earmarks to be in a rug.
Ugh!
Let me out.
Get off, buster.
I'll give you $500 for your place.
I'll make it a thousand.
Money.
That's not good anymore, eh?
Here comes another.
Pull that guy off there!
I'll be back in time.
Time for what?
I said, take my money out.
Take your money out?
Yeah.
I was only fooling you.
Yeah, there's a run on the bank.
What did you say?
I said, there's a run on the bank.
There's a run on the bank?
Certainly.
Oh!
My money!
Oh, my money! Oh, my money!
Oh, oh!
What's going on in the bank?
He's throwing all of the money out.
Really?
Yes, I'm going to tell my husband.
I'm going to tell my husband.
The boss was asleep when he heard such a clatter.
Sprang from his bed just to see what was the matter.
Looked down on the street and that scene filled his eyes.
But you know he wasn't even surprised.
Well, he got on the phone and he ordered some thunder,
some rain and some disc blades to plow it all under.
Someone asked why with a sigh.
He explained that the fools was up doing it again.
Wait a minute! Wait a minute!
Wait!
You can't close this door in my face!
Open it up! Open it up!
I've been thinking, Bob.
Maybe if I went out there and talked to those people,
I could make them understand about you.
Oh, you'd just be wasting your breath, Ben.
Only thing that mob will understand is a bullet.
Yeah, maybe they'll get one.
Say, Bob, I had an idea.
You promised me no one would get hurt.
Anyway, the recession came.
So we decided to sleep through it.
We just programmed the computers to revive us when it was all over.
They were indexed, linked to the galactic stock market prices, you see,
so that we'd be revived,
but everybody else had rebuilt the economy enough
to be able to afford our rather expensive services again.
Good God, that's a pretty unpleasant way to behave, isn't it?
Is it?
I'm sorry, I'm a bit out of touch.
And until further notice, this station will continue its around-the-clock coverage
of this national television program.
What is that?
Oh, horrific.
And now we switch you to the state capital.
Now what?
Where His Excellency the Governor
Oh, Jesus.
is speaking from the executive mansion.
Holy mackerel!
And then I got scared to death and closed the doors.
I...
You must come with me.
Great things are afoot.
You must come now or you will be late.
Late? What for?
I don't know.
Now the first thing I noticed when we hit the street
was the seventh fleet.
They was cruising the center of town.
Spook mills very strange.
And nobody seemed real clear who had sent them now.
But they sure looked grand with the band of balloons and the pound.
I love a parade.
And they played cankers away for the rest of the day.
Except for times that they'd lower their guns and shoot some renegade down.
And now back to prosperity.
What?
You almost had me.
You mean you're growing your own power?
Every cent.
But I don't want any eyes.
But I want my money.
Well, if you'll just wait a moment, I'll...
You mean to tell me I can't take my money out when I please?
You see, I have to get an okay from the president.
Well, it's none of his business.
I put my money in here and I've always to take it out.
Wall Street is still the banking and financial center of the world.
Today, a seat on the exchange cost around $500.
Five hundred bucks!
Now come on, give me my money.
Do I have to stand here all day and yell for you?
For my money?
My money?
This is Angel.
We are the Android Sisters.
What is your question?
All of reality exists in our minds.
Is that true?
What is your intelligence rating?
I'm classified as a 5.5555.
You understand we only speak to you on the level that you can comprehend.
I appreciate that.
For those of you watching out there, adjust your I.T. ratings.
I'm 5.5555.
What is your question?
I already asked it.
I said I already asked it.
What is your question?
All right, I want to know if reality is in my mind or is it out there.
I mean, what if it's all in my mind?
I mean, change my mind, I could change reality.
Right.
Wrong.
What?
What's wrong with you?
Dear confused, briefly, reality is merely what everyone agrees is real.
What everyone agrees is not real, does not exist.
Who programmed you?
How should I know?
Everyone, I don't know.
I'm still confused.
Dear still confused, you are confusing the symbol for reality.
Reality.
Money is a good example.
Money.
What about money?
I like money.
Money.
I will use two pieces of paper as an example.
Can you see this?
I see one piece of paper, the other's money.
Two pieces of paper.
What?
Here are two pieces of paper, both the same size, both just paper.
Paper.
Humans are obsessed with money.
Money.
Not all humans, just some of us.
Most of us.
One piece of paper is worth 500 solar credits.
The other is worthless, not even worth a solar centavo.
Do you know why?
Sure, one is a piece of money and the other is a piece of paper.
They are both paper.
Yeah, right.
One has been blessed by the treasury wizards.
The other has not.
That's it.
The symbol is controlling your mind.
Hmm, I see.
Oh, our time is up.
This is Angel.
Looking for the right loan can sometimes leave you in the fog.
But when I ask for credit on the equity in my home, I got it.
When I ask for my loan to come through in a hurry, I got it.
Got it.
When I talk, bankers listen.
Right, boys?
Right.
Now who is it?
My money!
God, I'm not leaving until I find out what's going on.
Okay, okay.
I want it to wait outside as promised.
I'm not waiting outside.
For the love of...
My money! My money!
I'm asking you, do I get it or don't I?
No.
What?
Now, let's have no more curiosity about this bizarre cover-up.
I've been wrecked before, but never in such a unnatural and brutal way.
Good grief!
That woman must be lashed until she drops.
She is undermining our civilization.
Hundreds of people are being demoralized.
You stop heckling me, I'll beat you a lot sooner.
Anything for a buck.
The fabulous J.P. Morgan Financial Empire was reconstructed with money donated by schoolchildren
from all over the United States.
Yeah!
Oh!
Come on, I've got some work to do.
Oh, you are you!
Oh, you're all killed, Jerry!
There you go.
I just wanted to see if you had your price.
Most of us do.
Oh, yeah!
The market is a hot tip your neighbor will supply.
In which you keep investing till its price has hit the sky.
So when you go to sell it, there is no one left to buy.
It's plunge ahead with Edsel and sell AT&T.
And you'll be a rich man.
A simple little business.
It's A-B-C.
At 1 p.m., the Dow Jones averages are down 777.43.
That's our stock market, ladies and gentlemen.
Great.
Now what?
The impact was so great that a song was written about it.
When you haven't any coal in the stove and you freeze in the winter and you burst to the wind after a break.
When you haven't any shoes on your feet and your coat's in a paper and you look 30 pounds underweight.
When you go to get a word of a day.
When you get a word of advice from a famous.
But hunger comes around.
At your window, see, a love flies out the door.
For money makes the world go around, the world go around, the world go around.
Money makes the world go around.
That clinking, clanking sound of money, money, money, money, money, money, money, money.
You get a little, get a little money, money, money, money.
Mark again, about four pounds.
The clinking, clanking, clunking sound is all that makes the world go round.
The box has the food
Now, to come to make a touch, the bank has food.
For the last time, I'm asking you for my money!
My money!
Well, you don't have to holler.
What do you want?
I told you, I came here to take my money out.
If I can get it...
You know, this bank has been open for 60 years,
and no one has ever lost a dollar.
Uh-oh.
Oh, help! I'm ruined!
Oh, cut it out now.
Why, I thank you for 20 years.
Yes.
And the minute people start crying about hard times, you get panicky.
You come yawning in here for your money like a wounded wildcat.
No, we don't need...
We need customers like you.
It won't limit your business.
What am I going to do with it?
Oh, stick it in your shirt.
That's the thing for it.
Not getting it ready for you!
Not yet ready for you!
Won't be long, though!
When a bank goes fresh, I don't lose my cash.
I find great enjoyment in unemployment.
I'm the only man the world can overcome.
In other words, gentlemen, hallelujah, I'm a bum.
The workers will rule the world someday,
and all of your kind will be wiped away.
Your socks and pants may have holes,
but your booter packs down your soles.
This ain't right, Bob.
Nothing's right anymore.
Go on.
Now, get it ready for you.
Lyons! Cossacks! Hoovers! Cossacks!
Ah, what do I see?
You shiver and tremble, and you call yourselves free.
You're slaves, and what's right to the powers of cash?
I'm proud as can be that they can't frighten me.
You'll die as you live, a useless slut.
Parasites living off parasites.
And what have you got?
Ah, let's go to them.
Oh, shit!
I'm for sucking them!
Oh, scum.
You're bum.
Welcome to your king.
Does your majesty bring news of the plutocrats down south?
Those rich idle shirkers who live on us workers.
Yeah, you work hard with your mouth.
Yeah.
That's just about enough.
Love that radical stuff?
If a man doesn't work, he ought to be dead.
Ha ha ha.
Pardon me, egghead.
You talk like a rat.
You're a parasite, Saul.
You're brothers in crime.
When the revolution comes, you won't sit pretty.
Egghead, I demand an explanation.
Well, it's up to you to prove I'm wrong.
Any time now.
Ha ha ha.
Why the hesitation?
Not long now for free money.
What?
Free money.
Where is it?
Here, very soon.
And it's free.
Free money.
Arriving soon.
Now.
Is this your order then?
One hundred gallons of blood, two hundred gallons of urine, five hundred cubic feet of
animal manure.
Yeah.
Where do you want it put?
Put it in the vat.
Put it in the vat, Fred.
Don't brush the stairway.
The prolongation of such a weird, fantastic, and impractical plan has concentrated by the
defense in these times with the country incapacitated by economic ailments, and indeed, the country
is in danger of an undercurrent of social unrest, is capable of fomenting a disturbance from which
the country may not soon recover.
It is our duty to stop it.
Prosperity will be turned in a moment.
My money, my money, my money.
Tell her that we'll have the bank open before noon tomorrow.
You will?
Oh, I always said you'd put it over.
I am so screwed.
Nonsense.
Yeah, nothing that, uh, does a rat poison wouldn't cure.
Now, now, John, that's no way to stop married nights for the new president.
I give it to the little guy.
I'm going to give it to the little guy.
Yes.
My money.
To keep the respect for the people in this town.
What I did was for them, too.
I took a risk for them, and I lost.
You've struggled and worked and slaved for them, and what's it got us?
I'll wind up in jail and you'll wind up at the poorhouse.
We can't think of ourselves now.
Why not?
Haven't we sacrificed enough?
What have we got left?
Responsibility for the people of this town.
Responsibility?
Oh, I've heard all my life, it's the war on honesty, the war on this and the war on
that, the war on them can rot, for all I care.
Good evening, everybody.
I am John.
My God, it's almost dark.
They'll be waking up soon.
Dammit!
Millionaire's Row is where the homes and estates of many of New York's once wealthiest citizens once stood.
Once the most glamorous street of America, Millionaire's Row.
It's pretty much Skid Row today.
Who do we eat?
This is military orders. All civilians are subject to summary execution.
Stay in your homes. Repeat Conrad Channel.
This is a class one emergency. All civilian traffic is barred from...
They're down on steel and carbon and high on UFOs.
Up here I.G. Farman, that's how the money goes.
Do you realize the truth, Bill?
Yes, I do.
Your country has no future now.
You see?
There's nothing you can do about it.
You're stupid minds. Stupid.
Our job here was a success.
Stupid.
And soon we'll be back in the 23rd century.
You see? You see?
We dream of wealth.
No. No.
Good morning.
Things can't go on like this.
I've tried and tried and I can't stand it another day.
I don't care if we starve.
Oh, Lizzie.
Shh.
We has to trade in Lizzie,
cause we is needin' food.
Oh!
Oh, I'm stripped of everything I've got!
Get out of here.
I was with
dress two
split
and fall
I thought the
doves
had my
back
Now, I'm in
I think I'm going to be sick.
Your nose will tell you we're approaching the financial district.
Like a bitter, sour ass.
Today, a seat on the exchange costs around five cents.
And it's pretty much falling.
Don't throw your garbage down here.
But worst of all was the disgrace.
Wait a minute.
Listen.
Don't you hear that wailing?
Wailing?
Men marching, marching.
Marching in the rain.
Jobs. Jobs.
Gee, don't it get you?
Okay.
Is anyone here not a downer?
Anyone?
No.
What would Jesus do?
Like the good book says.
On the way!
We've been going through a tough time together.
This town, this grand country of ours.
But the worst is over and we've learned a big lesson.
Yeah, but the biggest thing of all we've learned is this.
There are bigger deals to come.
Don't be mad at me.
You know when the Dow Jones is up, it's good.
When it's down, it's not so good.
Indeed.
I'm going to put the money back in the bank.
In what bank?
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
Go.
Wall Street was falling apart.
I'm sorry, old man.
I know this spot you're in.
I'd give my right arm if I could help you.
Make it two pounds on your left foot.
Stay on second row.
Better keep your foot for when we're ready to run.
I forget what went down after that.
It all happened so fast.
Yes, it was looking real bad.
And it looked like we had it.
It lost it.
I don't know what happened.
It's like we were in the park at the dock when the army arrived.
Big trouble, you know, because they was sweeping the town, chasing renegades down.
There was no friends to be found.
There was no place at all left to hide.
And the Austrian's son, he was having so much fun.
He'd been put in command of the camps and his prisoners all died.
Meanwhile, way across town in the penthouse suite of the tallest building, New York.
And we're here to see the arrival and departure of the elite of international society.
The men and women who shape the destinies of nations.
We are here to sacrifice them to our gods.
Right along.
Narrow winding staircase to the top of the tallest building in lower Manhattan is worth the climb.
The view at the top is breathtaking.
Always has been.
Any reason for a change?
We don't want money.
Money is a curse.
It's risky business and worse.
I know a fellow who found some dough.
He put it in a bank.
The bank gave him his dough, began to grow.
He got rich in a hurry.
Then he started into worry.
Worried because he was in dough.
And.
Jumped right out of the window.
1046 feet up.
And 1046 feet down, down into the street of shadows.
The street of forgotten.
Maybe you just forget the whole thing.
If you're smart.
The impact was so great that a song was written about it.
After you jump.
Up.
The sky strayed above.
After you jump.
And we read about it in the paper before you go.
Oh.
Can I have your stereo?
Ding-a-dum.
Da-da-da-da-da.
After you jump.
And they read your final statement.
And they scrape you off the pavement.
Before you go.
Oh.
Can I have your stereo?
Ding-a-dum.
Da-da-da-da.
After you jump, and they take you to the morgue
And after you jump, and they ask me why, what for
But I don't know why, but can I come along for delight?
After you jump, they'll say that you had everything
After you jump, they'll say that you could really swing
Before you go, oh, oh, can I hear the stereo?
After you jump
After you jump, oh, oh, can I hear the stereo?
Oh, oh, can I hear the stereo?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, can I hear the stereo?
Coming down now are the first of New York's once wealthiest citizens.
It's estimated so many people quite sensibly plunge magnificently from this point
that if they all pried the sidewalks in one time
there wouldn't be enough room on Wall Street to take care of them.
Funny, funny smells.
Oh, boy.
Eek!
Meanwhile back on the street
This clown in a gown and a hat with tattoos on his shoulder
Comes over and whispers, it's gonna be alright
It says he's in!
Personal friend of the boss
And then asked if we got any sheep
He can sacrifice later that night
We said no, said oh, and then wanted all
Chantin' some strange sound of language
And wait for his world in the sky
Most unusual individual confused me in all that
Sam and Attila, their skin-dead field of action and danger
They burned every manger in town
And old John's eyes were hazy
Must have gone crazy
Goin' around trying to drown everybody he found
And the Austrian son was still having his fun
No, should be too sad to death
They know that all we're making is sound
And then they move it all, making this sound
And it's a warning without any warning
The sky opened up and the boss stuck his head through the clouds
Something they'd never seen before
And the army and navy, they opened a fire
But it grabbed them, that lightning
That laid them all under the ground
Sam jumped up to salute
The boss said that's real cute
But it's a little bit lame
Cause I've seen what's been goin' down
Sam said, you've done it all wrong
It's them that you're wrong, not me
Can't you see that's Attila and the Austrian kid?
The boss says, yes that's true
But I also want you
Do you think that I'm blind?
Did you think you could keep yourself hid?
And just then the clown in the gown hits the ground
And starts kissing his feet
But his steps on his feet are all the same
And his tongue says, who is this kid?
Alright, look everyone
He hasn't been gone that long
Look!
That's him, that's the guy
Gotcha
I swear to God
It's all a big mistake
You gotta believe me
I'm so sorry
You stand here convicted, very late
Of sneak thievery
Low hydrogen
Greed in
I'm sorry
Sodomy
I don't know what happened
And enthusiastic corruption of the public good
You've got the wrong man
How many times have I heard that before?
Wall Street is a 500 billion dollar graveyard
Free electricity! Free electricity! Free electricity! Free electricity! Free electricity!
Wall Street, Skid Row, whatever you want to call it
Is the worst slum in Lower Manhattan
Oh gee, don't cry
It ain't so bad
You go to sleep like a good little kid
And tomorrow morning everything will be alright
As if on cue
Snap it up, will ya? On stage, forgotten man number
Forgotten man number, everybody on stage
Come on girls, make it snappy, forgotten man number
On stage, alright girls, on stage
Forgotten man number, on stage
Forgotten man number, alright Miss Carol
Forgotten man number
Now, I'll be loud and clear
Remember my forgotten man?
You put a rifle in his hand
You sent him far away
You shouted, hip hooray
But look at him today
Remember my forgotten man?
You had him cultivate the land
He walked behind a plow
The sweat fell from his brow
But look at him right now
Forgetting him, you see
Means you're forgetting me
Like my
My
My forgotten man
Remember my forgotten man
You put a rifle in his hand
You sent him far away
You shouted here for air
But look at him today
Remember my forgotten man
You had him cultivate the land
He walked behind the plow
The sweat fell from his brow
But look at him right now
Forgetting him, you see
Means you're forgetting me
Like my forgotten man
What do you think we are?
Animals?
What are we?
Almost shaking?
You're right.
We're men.
We are men.
Run!
Now let me see those eyes.
I don't think I feel so good about this all of a sudden.
I wouldn't do this!
It's nowhere near the wake.
No about that.
What I'm saying is no such thing as
Does it make me happy to see him fcry like this?
I don't even know why subscribe to this channel
Bye bye
Stay there for a while
And live in this right way
Oh don't doing well
This is dangerous
Understand more
What benefits?
Stay, well not GREAT
Estoy...
Hey!
You
The people
Don't do it
We're loose
Never
Not right now
Jesus
Oh, hear this.
Go to your cabin and wait there.
Maybe the ship's going down with all hands down.
This is the United States Army.
You're surrounded.
You have 30 seconds to move.
You have 56 minutes.
Your head is full.
You're a defender.
We are the real forgotten men.
Yes, we're forgotten.
We're not to break the track again.
For we are forgotten.
We're not to fall back by.
Oh, glory was our pride.
But soon our glory died.
Now the young are memory.
Oh, we're forgotten.
Remember your forgotten men.
We're forgotten.
We're not to let us live again.
We may be marched away.
To fight for you, I say.
But we're forgotten.
We're forgotten.
Please just forget about it.
Leaving the sprawling financial tenement district behind,
we find ourselves suddenly out in the open
in a beautiful park
at the very tip of the mountain.
The top of the island looks quiet now.
Oh!
Yeah, very funny.
We have learned that the stock market may go down,
but the sun will always come up.
The sun will come out tomorrow.
Bet you bought a dollar that you'll borrow.
Ah!
Sir, listen.
If we could, for a moment, move on to the subject of fiscal policy.
Fiscal policy?
Yes.
How can you have money?
It doesn't grow on trees, you know.
Well, if you would allow me to continue.
Yes, since we decided a few weeks ago
to adopt leaves as legal tender,
we have, of course, all become immensely rich.
Yes, I really wonder if that's the case.
But we have also run into a small inflation problem
on account of the high level of leaf availability,
which means that I gather the current going rate
has something like three major deciduous forests
buying one peanut.
So in order to obviate this problem
and effectively revalue the leaf,
we are about to embark on an extensive defoiling process.
So the idea is to do what we do best.
and start a new irrigation campaign
and, um, burn down all the forests.
I think that's a sensible move, don't you?
That makes economic progress.
You're absolutely...
Farming!
You're a bunch of raving nutters.
Well, is it, huh?
I have got news for you.
It doesn't matter,
a pair of fetid dingoes' kidneys,
what you all choose to do from now on.
Burn down the forest anything.
It will make a scrap of difference.
And that's it.
Your race will be dead, gone,
and good riddance to you.
Remember that.
But there must be something we can do.
No, nothing, really, nothing,
because it's all been done.
I mean, listen, that doesn't change the future
because we've seen it.
I mean, wise up, kid.
The human race is currently sitting round that rock over there
making documentaries about themselves.
There's nothing you can do to change it
because it's already happened.
It's all been a bit of a waste of time for you, hasn't it?
It's sad, though.
Just at the moment, it's a very beautiful planet.
It is. It is indeed.
The rich primal greens,
the river snaking off into the distance,
the burning trees.
And that's the way it was.
And that's the way it is.
And that's the way it's probably gonna be.
Much money.
Give us your money.
Ow! Ow! Ow!
Prosperity will return tomorrow.
Shit!
That was Suzy the Floozy's incredible show,
Bob Slacktime Funhouse number 740,
first broadcast on WREK Atlanta.
Rerun here on the Hour of Slack
because we're getting ready for Existlessness.
And so many other things.
And for more information about the Church of the Subgenius,
I want you to do whatever you want.
But you can, if you wish,
look at subgenius.com on the internet.
subgenius.com on the internet.