That's what I want
They are not complete
They cannot be
They don't even start to know
I want to hold you
I want to show you
Everything that love can be
I want you next to
Plus two
I want you to be
With me
bass solo
© BF-WATCH TV 2021
on KNON in Dallas, Texas.
Remember, Bob is the comrade of all people.
Here in China, just like in America,
the people need slack.
In Chinese, we call slack 了天牌.
But it must be true slack,
not the bad slack of the conspiracy.
Please, Bob, help me somebody.
Bob!
Eternal salvation
or triple your money back.
The Church of the Subgenius
Mis amigos,
queridos,
¿Qué quiere en su vida?
¿Riqueza grande?
¿Una mujer bonita o un hombre guapo?
¿Un coche rápido?
¿Fuerza tremendo?
¿O simplemente una filosofía perfecto?
¿Por qué trabaja como perro
para estas cosas?
Puede tener todo con la Iglesia del Subgenius
por un dólar solamente.
¿Conoce usted Bob Dobbs?
Bob Dobbs y su Iglesia son la troca a salvación
en este mundo desconcertado.
Traen suerte sin termina
y satisfacción última en su vida.
En todas maneras.
Sí, el mundo es a punto de terminar.
Pero puede escapar los desastros
con el suerte grande del Bob Dobbs.
Bob es el amigo de todos humanos real.
Le haré borracho con felicidad y slack.
Por solamente un dolor,
puede obtener su suerte
increíble y saberduría.
No es una broma.
Por favor, escribe Bob a
P.O. Box 140306
Dallas, Texas 75214.
Tendrá una experiencia
la más grande de su vida.
Pongo suyos ojos verdes.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
Condensed.
Heraglic function.
That's it, friends.
Ah, yes, praise Bob.
And this is the last hour
of the pledge drive.
And this is your announcer,
your mere host,
Reverend Ivan Stang,
with our good prayer partner.
Well, we got, I'm Pastor Buck Naked,
and over here is Dr. Chaos.
Hello.
Whew, help me somebody.
And as a special guest tonight,
we have the great author,
Jay Condom, author and musician
and artiste, one who all of you
probably know as the author
of the great comic book, P-Dawg.
There's nothing wrong with saying it.
It's like saying Pee-wee Herman.
Where is that?
Where is Mr. Condom?
Ah, here he comes.
Let me give the number, Stang.
Yes.
Let's do that.
Okay, we are still in pledge drive land.
The number to call is 828-9500.
We're going to be soliciting your pledges
for the Hour of Slack,
your fist against Criswell.
828-9500.
And 823-7490.
Call that line only if you want to talk to us.
On or off the air.
It doesn't have to be on the air,
but we'll pick up that line separate.
828-9500.
There are plenty of volunteers here
to take the pledges.
And like I said,
if you want to call 823-7490
to talk to us, that's fine.
Other than that,
call those other lines
to make a pledge for the Hour of Slack
radio ministry
to keep K&ON's challenge going.
And if you want to tell Criswell
what you think of him,
then tell us.
Oh, yes, dear friends,
because you see,
you see,
we can't keep saving the world for nothing.
There is no more money.
We've got to get some money.
That's it.
our money is which?
America's ultimate freedom.
I know,
Ken,
was the most spent
Criswell saying
that he super cared
about American spirituality
when he knew
he was going to die.
The8
Our às
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
Oh, yes, it's true.
It's all true.
Everything you ever heard.
Everything you know is true, friends.
And I tell you what.
We just, now, Buck, what were you saying?
Do we have a call from someone who dares to support this blasphemous show?
Yeah, we're getting a couple calls of support, and we're only 6.5% to our goal, and time is closing in.
So please call us and make your place to the Our Slack Radio Ministry at 828-9500.
By the way, I'm telling all our volunteers tonight not to pick up line one, which is 823-7490.
That's to talk to us.
I think we just lost a caller that we were going to talk to, give him a healing.
He's pink.
He needs a healing.
But 828-9500 is your number to pledge.
That's right, and friends, tonight we've got an action-packed show.
We've got an exorcism coming up.
That's Cecilia, you listening.
We've got your ritual coming.
And we're looking for the hate caller, the wonderful, hateful old lady who called last week that we were never able to get on the air.
Yeah, let me say a few words about that, Rev.
Yeah, we had a...
Yeah.
Call her.
I think she was from Old Women for Criswell or something.
And she called in, and she was giving me a real taste of heck over the phone.
And I told her to read her Bible, and that really got her excited.
Yeah.
So we would like that woman to call us back, and we do like hate calls.
I know that sounds crazy, but we're not afraid of controversy.
Oh, we have to have it.
We have to have it, friends.
You know, dear friends, we can't keep on saving the world with Bob for nothing.
What do you think this church and this radio station runs on, friends?
Does it run on money?
Say no!
No!
No.
Does it run on air?
Say no, my friend!
No!
No.
Does it run on honey?
Say no!
No!
No.
This church and this radio station both run on money.
Money.
And you must take it upon yourself, my friends, to entrust to Bob that which is Bob's.
Give the Bob his due, they say.
And look what your pledge gets you, friends.
Another few minutes of slack in this life, but even more important, it buys you time
in subgenius hell.
Now, there's many levels to the before or afterlife.
at the lowest rung you know you find the christian hell that's at the very bottom but only christians
go there then a step up from that you have the christian heaven that's usually reserved only
for christians also and that one is uh it's like a total absence of pain and pleasure but then
but then friends for the really good people you take a step up to the subgenius hell
and as it says in janer clothesians 151849 but by the time you get to the christian heaven
my friends you'll be wishing to god you'd made it to subgenius hell
because subgenius hell consists of total pleasure for subgenius's friends and
which
we've
Total torture and misery for the unsaved and the pink ones.
But up there at the very top, the very pinnacle of the afterlife, you get to the subgenius heaven.
And no, you won't be, quote, sitting on damp clouds harping and trumpeting all 24 hours of bloody day.
Nay, nay, for it's a squirting universe, my friend.
And in the subgenius heaven, you actually become the squirt.
For eternity, or the ooze, as the case may be for 50% of the population.
Praise Bob.
But only, friends, this only happens.
You can only gain admittance to Asgard or Valhalla, home of slain heroes for Bob,
by pledging that which is most important to you to K-N-O-N,
the only station that dares bring you more than one minute of slack.
A whole hour of slack, friends.
I know that ain't much.
It's more than most people ever even dream exists.
So we do want you to call that number, that sacred number, 828-9500.
You numerologists out there know what that really means.
And you kids, by the way, the children's subgeniuses, I know it's kind of late.
You should be asleep.
But get your decoder pins out because the special subgenius code will be coming out.
And you'll get that.
Nasty joke you can tell tomorrow at school.
That traveling salesman joke, friends.
And that traveling salesman, you know who it is.
It's Bob.
He's the traveling salesman of mythology.
Yes.
Oh, yes.
Oh, and we will be, by the way, playing that wonderful tape that the famous Mr. P.P. sent us.
So, Mr. P.P., please don't call in begging us to play your tape.
We will get it.
We will get around to it this week.
Oh, yes.
And we've got an exorcism to perform.
And, well, we might as well get to that now.
By the way, to pledge, once again, that number is 828-9500.
And I must say that, friends, you subgenius believers out there have shown a poor, poor record for tithing this time around.
It's embarrassing to walk into this station and see the big thermometer.
With our thermometers down there at around $10,000.
We need to pick it up, friends.
Just one or two hundred dollar donations to this station.
Not to the church, nay.
Bob doesn't need your money.
All he wants is your soul and a little link from your spinal cord down along about the 14th vertebrae.
Oh, we love you, friends.
And we love the souls that we store in those canisters.
Isn't that great?
True, friends.
Praise Bob.
It's a lovely love.
Oh, and thanks to Reverend Chris Gross for that beautiful music that just ended and signals me to go to another something or other.
We ought to queue up.
Huh?
Another canister.
Yeah, let's get out another one of them canisters, boy.
Those souls, boy.
Inhaling souls.
There's nothing like it.
That's not my headphones doing that, is it?
Oh.
Yeah, we're going to be needing the soul sucker tonight.
There's a lot of filthy souls out there that need to be cleansed, I'm sure.
Cleansed of that filth that fills their wallets.
That pathetic, useless garbage the Federal Reserve puts out.
You can't do that much with it, but this station can.
It can save the earth with the church.
But, uh, well, uh...
We need to queue up that record.
We've got a famous musician and, as I said, the author of P-Dawg Comics.
Let's hang loose on that for a minute.
We need to give the numbers again.
We aren't getting much of a response at all.
The number is 828-9500.
We do...
Well, you're not kidding.
We do need your support for the, uh...
Our Slack radio ministry.
And we're not getting it.
And, uh...
That's 828-9500.
828-9500.
And the reason...
Oh, there's a little support.
Well, let's listen to these callers and see what they have to say
and come right back after we play this record.
We'll be right back.
The mule nose could taste makes a big difference.
Oh, friends, if you only knew what went into that.
Let's fire that puppy up.
If you only knew what went into that mule nose on mule nose records.
And this is by.
Check the mystery fluid.
The mystery.
Yeah, check the level of that mystery fluid before we empty that mule nose.
Let me say once again, the number is 828-9500.
That's 828.
828-9500 to make a real pledge to the hour slack radio ministry and then send it in.
We've got some bonuses we'll tell you about just in a minute.
After this.
Start that record over again.
Yeah, start that record over.
Lee Harvey was a friend of mine.
Homer Henderson and the Dow Worthington Garden Boys.
Oh, yes.
Lee Harvey was a friend of mine.
Oh, yeah.
I was born in Dallas in 1952.
The Harvey moved across the street on Beckley Avenue.
He used to throw the ball to me when I was just a kid.
They say he shot the president.
Yeah.
I don't think he did.
And Lee Harvey was a friend of mine.
He used to take me fishing all the time.
He used to throw the ball to me when I was just a kid.
They say he shot the president.
Oh, yeah.
I don't think he did.
I don't think he was president.
I've seen that picture of him with pamphlets and a gun.
The shadows are pointing every which way.
But there's only just one son.
Someone played the photo and snuck away.
And here and there.
They say he shot the president
I don't think he did
And Lee Harvey was a friend of mine
He used to take me fishing all the time
He used to throw the ball to me
When I was just a kid
They say he shot the president
I don't think he did
I've seen it all on TV
Lee Harvey got gunned down
Murdered
Murdered by Jack Ruby
The biggest sleaze in town
He stuck that gun into his ribs
And said, here's looking at you, kid
Ruby killed Lee Harvey
TV proved he did
And Lee Harvey was a friend of mine
A very good friend
Yeah
He used to take me fishing all the time
That's right, he did
He used to throw the ball to me
When I was just a kid
They say he shot the president
I don't think he did
Oh, yes, dear friends
That was Lee Harvey was a friend of mine
By Homer Henderson and the Dow Worthington Garden Boys
Oh, yes, and we've got
We've got Homer Condom here
Right now
Oh, friends, and that
That song has so much meaning for so many of us
I think we ought to dedicate the next five minutes
To puzzling evidence, by the way
I mean, how many of you really
You know Lee Harvey
He was just set up
He was an okay guy
He was, as a matter of fact
Oh
This is a little-known fact that I should mention
I know a guy who was a very good
Another person who was a good friend of Lee Harvey Oswald's
His name is Kerry Thornley
Lives in Atlanta right now
He is actually the co-founder of the Discordian cult
And about 2% of our listeners are actually
Probably members of that cult
Yeah
Yes
Murray, who goes by other names in the Discordian world, was buddies with Lee Harvey and the Marines.
And his name is in the Warren Commission.
He got checked out, too, in the great, that beautiful, orchestrated cover-up that they did.
You ought to talk to some Dallas police about what they think about it.
Well, I know someone else they could talk to, and that's Bobby Sox.
His father fired Lee Harvey Oswald from the Childs Stovall map-making company.
That's a shame.
You know, if they hadn't have fired him, he wouldn't have become a dude.
That's right.
He wouldn't have had to go to Russia and all that other stuff.
He thought he was a spy.
Well, there's some evidence that we turned up here at Mule Nose Records to further indict this conspiracy.
What was that?
Don't worry about it. It was a conspiracy.
But anyway...
They like to do that to let us know they're listening.
Here's this burned letter, this memorandum we found.
Listen to this.
They say his nagging Russian wife made him fall for Marilyn Monroe.
When Marilyn came to Dallas to O.H. Lee's should go.
JFK stole her away.
Lee Harvey flipped his lid.
They'll say he shot the president.
We'll agree he did.
This is an inter-office memorandum framing Lee Harvey Oswald.
And I think Spector is responsible.
If not...
If not smirsh.
No, not smirsh.
At the bottom, it says P.S.
You are no longer a smirsh operative.
Well, my mom and dad were once kicked out of Jack Ruby's club.
Wow.
Yeah, how about that?
That's an honor.
Yeah.
And I personally know Larry Buchanan who made the film The Trial of Lee Harvey Oswald.
Bucky Buchanan.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, in fact, a couple of Texas Monthly issues ago, you could read my article about...
That great filmmaker in Dallas, Larry Buchanan, who tried to defend Lee Harvey and other great patriots like...
Other great Dallas patriots like John Hinckley and...
Which magazine was that?
Oh, that TM magazine.
Oh, TM.
So it says TM by Ivan Stang.
That's...
No, no.
It uses my fake name.
Oh.
But we're going to...
Friends, the number to call...
Listen, this is serious.
We can't keep...
If you little pledge partners out there would call...
And cough up those bucks, we wouldn't be listening to this through crummy headphones.
That's right.
We'd be...
Friends, we'd be doing this show from a spaceship.
And Lee Harvey is a K-N-O-N exclusive.
No other radio station will play it.
The number to call is 828-9500.
Give him that number again, Doug.
That number...
Who's Doug?
That number is 828-9500.
Sorry, that's your fake Christian name.
Now, we've got a comment...
A comment...
From the...
Our listening audience to this next bit of news here.
So we're going to put this...
Patch this dude in here.
Okay, let's see if we can do that.
Let's see that.
Hello.
Hello, friends.
Okay, what do you have to tell us on the AeroSlack radio ministry tonight?
I have something to tell you about our not-so-good friend, Mr. Criswell.
Oh, the evil Criswell.
Oh, heck.
Yes.
Yes, Mr. Criswell.
Mr. Criswell is the anti-Bob.
I have definite proof of this.
That's a stiff accusation.
Yeah, because there's been so many anti-Bobs brought up.
He wishes he was the anti-Bob.
He is the anti-Bob.
He ain't man enough to be the anti-Bob.
No, we're not talking...
We're not talking Neeky here.
This is not Neeky.
This is worse than Neeky.
He's not Neeky.
Even the amazing Criswell wasn't the anti-Bob, and if he couldn't do it, no one can.
Now, come on.
This even beats the Oklahoma 900-foot Jesus.
Oh, my friends.
This is serious.
This is serious stuff he's talking here.
This is top-flight dogma here.
The closure here is no better yet.
Leave the room.
Criswell brainwashes, but the problem is his brainwashing is not complete.
It leaves his subjects in a dazed state.
I don't want my brainwashed.
It's incomplete.
They still have this longing for something else.
You know what they're longing for?
Friends?
They're longing for Bob.
Praise Bob.
Bob.
They want Bob.
That is why Bob is greater than Criswell.
Bob completely brainwashes his subjects.
They no longer have wants or needs.
Their brains are so clean and so pure and slack.
They just...
They howl and...
A new slate.
Okay.
A new life.
Okay, well, thanks for sharing that with us.
Praise Bob.
Oh, that feels good.
Fuck it.
Oh.
Oh, that was a nice...
That was a great call.
That was an excellent call.
Well, friends, while we're on the...
While we're on the...
No, he didn't.
Signing off.
I heard him say the F word.
No, he didn't.
He said...
Fuck it.
As in suck my soul.
That's not...
That's not a customer.
Oh.
He said it that way.
Oh, sorry.
See, this is the soul sucker here, friends.
My mistake.
Now, go ahead now.
The Dr. Chaos now has a pledge drive announcement.
The number to call is 828-9500.
This, by the way, this is not one of those annoying type pledge drive announcements.
This is a real from the gland pledge drive announcement.
We're not playing games with you.
We really do need the financial attention at the station to continue to fight the fight.
And, by the way, now we have a pleasure.
Our best pledger tonight, Martha Thompson, wants to know when the next D-Vival is going to be.
And we're going to announce that for you, Martha, in just a little bit.
There is a D-Vival coming up where you can meet a real subgenius.
Or something.
Although, you seem like you're a real subgenius.
By the way, Martha, I don't think it's too much to say that she did pledge $30 to fight the fight.
And she gets a bonus.
She gets a bonus.
She gets a boner.
A bonus.
No.
Oh, that's two of them.
Well, actually, she gets two bonuses.
Oh.
She not only gets a pamphlet, a subgenius pamphlet, which all pledgers,
get, but for me, she gets two buttons.
A J.R. Bob Dobbs button and a Barbara button.
That's Bob whenever he's a woman.
And L. Ron Hubbard says people can push your stress buttons.
And we don't have any callers at 828-9500.
That's 828-9500.
I hope you can remember that number.
And we need real pledges.
Oh, there's a few.
And I thank you both for that.
There's a few more.
I really thank you.
Norton, come on down, pal.
I've got something to show you.
With chaos now.
Doc?
Yes.
Well, hello and good evening, my friends.
I am the Reverend Dr. Sardonicus Chaos.
And I have an important message for each and every one of you out there.
You know, there is an old saying that the best thing,
the best things in life are free.
Well, my friends, that is an untrue statement.
A conspiracy lie.
A demonic pink lie.
Slack is one of the best things in life.
And around here, slack does not come cheaply.
There is no free ride, my friends.
Picture yourself driving through the desert
when all of a sudden your car's radiator overheats.
You pull over to the side of the road and open up the hood
and the radiator starts sparting like a geyser.
Sparting and oozing.
Spewing steam everywhere.
You're stuck out in the desert in the middle of nowhere
and it's five miles to the nearest Stucky's.
You figure, well, I'll have to hitch a ride to the nearest service station
and get my car towed in and fixed.
But every car that passes you is being driven by Criswell
or one of his followers.
The evil Criswell.
Do you think they're going to...
Are they going to stop and give you a ride?
Well, you'd better think again, friend.
You're probably not pink enough for them.
Anyway, if the Hour of Slack radio ministry
is your vehicle to get you to the land of slack,
then you, my friend, must buy the next tank of gas.
Why?
And you want to know why?
Why must you buy that next tank of gas?
I want to know why.
Why?
Because we are under so much pressure
from those followers
and those churches.
But you can help us change that.
Send in those pledges.
Send it in.
I'm sorry I asked.
All of them in.
Now...
Friends, with that pledge to this show, you get...
You get the subgenius pamphlet number two,
the amazing new pamphlet,
and those fantastic Bob Dobbs buttons.
That's right.
If you will specify that you pledge to the Hour...
For the Hour of Slack show,
you get that pamphlet and those buttons.
Ah, yes.
And it's magic.
Friends, Bob will lock into your soul,
and you'll never escape.
And you'll be so glad to have given up your free will
to that great master
who has no mind of his own,
but merely acts by chance,
for he is the Bob.
Ah, yes.
Now, we know that some of you out there are Slack vampires.
You listen to the Hour of Slack every week
and figure this is great.
No commercials, no salesmen,
no unwatchable,
no wanted blah blah being forced on me by the conspiracy.
True Slack.
But, you see, without your pledge,
we won't be able to continue.
Pretty soon, you're going to be listening to the same old, same old
that everybody else's tone-deaf grandma is listening to.
Is that what you really want?
I didn't think so.
Well, you know what to do.
Send in those pledges.
Now, unlike other ministries,
we do not use guilt as a weapon.
We let you use your own guilt against yourself.
All right.
And when you start feeling guilty enough,
you will know what to do.
Dig down deep.
Way down deep.
No, further than that even.
And give until it hurts.
Send in those pledges.
At 828-9500.
We've got lines open now.
828-9500.
Send it in.
Call it in right now at 828-9500.
Send in those pledges, friends.
Thank you.
Praise Bob.
Fight the fight against the Criswell demons
by calling 828-9500.
Yeah, we've got something on line one.
Oh, friends.
And you know, I think it's time to do that exorcism that we had promised.
This is KNON 90.9 FM in Dallas, Texas.
Hold on.
As you well know, 90.9 FM.
Oh, yes.
Okay, hold on.
Hold on.
Are we trying to get a call?
Yeah, we've got a call.
Oh, here we go.
In Dallas, Texas.
This is the subtenor of radio ministry.
Power of Slack on KNON 90.9 in the left excess.
Oh, hold on.
I think I've messed up one more time.
Okay, hold on again.
Oh, we're friends.
We're striving.
Did I do it?
Is he on?
No.
Hello?
Sweet hour of Slack.
Caller.
Hello?
I'm holding it.
Is the caller there?
I think I killed our caller somehow.
I think we need to follow up here with a song by Reverend Seth Deitch and Dr. Ahmed Fishmonger
of the Church of Mr. Science of the Subgenius.
But first, we need to announce that our phone lines have dried up again.
It's 828-9500.
We're only 7% towards our goal.
7%, friends.
Can you stand it?
We're only 7%.
7% of our goal of assuring K&N and Wynn's existence versus the onslaught of the Criswell
barbarians.
Now, this is no joke, friends.
We are not kidding.
We are actually under constant attack and threat by the Cris demons.
And I can't get a skin mask.
Hello?
K&N and Wynn?
Yeah.
You're on the hour of Slack.
Are you a brother in Slack?
A minister of Slack?
I need help.
My car is trying to achieve Slack.
And I want to make sure it gets a blessing from Bob so it'll achieve true Slack and go
to Subgenius.
You need a healer of appliances, friend.
That's a very specialty trade within the church.
A healer of appliances should be seen through the church.
And we can't tell you exactly how to get that ministry over the free airwaves of K&N.
Oh, please.
This is a free station, son.
I'm willing to support the hour of Slack.
I'm willing to support it.
I'm willing to make a pledge.
Thank you.
And just call 828-9500 and make that pledge and keep it going because remember, the Cris
monster is out there and he's going to get us.
And your car is healed.
Go home, jump in it, ride off.
Well, I wouldn't say his car is healed just yet, but also, we were going to tell Martha
about the DeViva, weren't we, Stan?
Oh, yeah.
Why don't you quickly tell Martha about that?
Okay.
Well, you know, I don't know where it is.
It's actually at the next big science fiction convention, the Fantasy Fair that you will
read about in the papers on July 5th, about 1130, wherever that is.
We'll be telling you.
And Martha will already have her buttons, won't she?
Yes, she will.
Martha certainly will.
I hope so.
Martha will be well prepared.
She won't die.
She won't have to be sacrificed.
You know, what it's going to take to bring Bob back from the dead is probably the sacrifice
of thousands of lives of pink boys.
So to speak.
But, friends...
Hello.
Hello, my friend.
How are you?
If you hadn't called, we would have played your tape.
If I wouldn't have what?
I'm going to make a pledge.
Well, then call the other line.
That's 828-9500.
Okay.
Please call and make a pledge at 828-9500.
Let me tell you the story of J.R.
Bob Dolls.
Friend of man and yeti, he walked with the gods.
He wore a silly grin and he smoked a stupid pipe.
He fought the conspiracy every day of his life.
He whipped the stench of many a man.
He bothered many children.
With his money...
He blessed.
Counted the religion in which we all believe.
Brought us all the slack that everybody needs.
Was the greatest salesman the world had ever seen.
He could sell the parts after he ate all the beans.
He could sell a pile of shit to a common fly.
All...
All of us who knew him.
He would never die.
Bob Dolls.
He was a real man and brave.
He's lying dead in his grave.
Without Bob, what are we?
What are we gonna do?
When the men from Planet X go marching through?
Our whole race is stuck in jail with only Bob to raise the bail.
But now he's dead, so we'll do what we do.
He founded the city known as Dobbs Town.
He's in Malaysia.
It was rarely found.
There is study for hidden science.
Until that fatal day.
When he came up to his block in the city by the bay.
If you had ever seen him.
If you had ever dared.
Most had no occasion.
Others just made scared.
So others said,
Bob came to San Francisco for the even of the eighth.
When the Holy Smiling One would step out on the stage.
Bob looked to the left.
Then he looked to the right.
Then he strode out with confidence into the bright spotlight.
He waved at all the cheering fans as he stepped up to the mic.
When a praise was heard.
Cassie Bullitt sent him to eternal night.
Bob Dobbs, Bob Dobbs.
Proud to their savior had come.
Retreated by the flash of a gun.
Without Bob we have flown.
He would be the beard.
As we swiftly approached that fatal year.
For in 1998 he would have set the record straight.
But now he's dead.
So we're doomed over here.
Oh friends.
Please save Kane Owen from the false churches.
Call us at 828-9500. This isn't a joke or a rehearsal. This is real. This is K&ON
asking you for your help in a real crisis. Please stop the false churches
and call K&ON at 828-9500. Now dear friends, we got a letter in the mail.
Actually, we've gotten several things in the mail. I'd like to... There's apparently a
computer network, a subgenius computer network centered in Dallas and we got a
letter about it and then I lost the letter here at the station when I was
about to read it at some point. It dematerialized. So I think that was Frank
Kennedy. Please send that information in again if I don't find it again. But
friends, we have here a letter from... an informal request it says from Cecilia
and she says, Bob rules. Dear Bob,
Bob rules. Dear Bob,
I need some help. Two weeks ago, my fella whose name we can't mention who works at
Bluebonnet and I were listening to the show when he who must not be named and I
think you know who I mean jumped out of the radio and bit my guy. He bit my guy
and he's been an utter beep hole ever since. Could you possibly heal him on one
of the shows in absentia? He listens faithfully.
It's really a problem and I would certainly appreciate your hitting him
with the soul sucker or whatever is appropriate. He refuses to give me a hard
time because of this. I'm miserable. Thanks so much.
Praise Bob, Cecilia. Now Cecilia, I'm afraid what it's gonna take here is a
full-fledged exorcism... subgenius exorcism rant. All right. All right.
All right. All right. Get ready now, my friend. You're out there. I know you're listening.
I know you're listening to what's going on. It was Bob who banished you to the pit. It
was he who flung you from the depths of heaven to the pit of hell. It was he who cast you
out, unclean spirit. He has dominion over you. I order you in the name of Bob to come
out of this poor servant of Bob.
Thanks.
I command you to put your hands on the radio.
Good. Good. All right. So we take you out. It's nice to see you. Yes, it's nice to see
The power of Bob compels you.
And I demand you to come out.
Come out!
Come out of that innocent person.
Come out of that innocent person, unclean spirit.
Oh, yes, friends.
Oh, yes, I feel the power.
I'm in the spirit, dear friends.
I'm getting a sign.
I can see someone in my mind's eye.
No, wait.
It's someone out there he's afraid to call.
It's a young man.
His name is...
I can't quite get it.
Frank, I think.
I'm getting Frank.
But he's deeply troubled, friends.
He's burdened.
He's bound by demons.
He's bound by binding spirits of...
Sea demons?
It's conspiracy false street drugs, friends.
He's bound by...
He's bound by drugs.
He's got terrible financial problems
because he can't afford the drugs.
He wants to be free, but the demons won't let him be.
He needs slack.
He needs slack to set him free.
Oh, yeah!
Bob, are you listening?
I want you to come down.
I want to cast out all the cancers, tuberculosis, tumors, arthritis,
and bad checks from this man.
I want you to cast him out from the crown of his head
to the sole glands of his feet.
Cast out that demon.
Beat off the devil.
And set him free.
I command this now in the name of Bob Dobbs,
High Epopt of the Church of the Subgenius.
Help me, somebody.
Praise Bob!
She ain't got no legs.
My legs are on fire.
Pull the lever.
Down you go.
Niggy be gone.
Face you, Niggy.
Well, that opens up a line at...
9,500.
Niggy is gone, and now we need you to pledge your funds
to keep K-N-O-N doing this kind of real healing.
Where else can you hear?
But K-N-O-N, 90.9, the voice of the Yetis.
Where else can you hear a healing like that?
Nowhere else.
It's the truth.
It's nowhere else.
And, you know, where else can you listen to a crazed maniacal caller like this?
He's on the air with us now.
Hello, caller?
Yes.
Well, what do you got?
I'm pink.
You're pink, too.
But your money is green, Frank.
But your money is green.
Now, have you pledged to...
Have you pledged to...
Or, it's like, be honest, truthful.
I've pledged to audio abuse.
You pledged to audio abuse, okay.
Well, that's cool, and, you know, really, you know, if you help audio abuse, well, by
gosh, you're fighting the fight.
How much did you pledge?
Twenty.
Did you send it in?
Yes.
Not yet.
I got it right over here.
But it's in the bag, right?
Right.
Well, great.
Well, thanks.
What would you like from us?
I need to be saved.
You need to be saved.
Well, you know, actually, you know, we're the church, we're sort of a self-help church,
and we try to help you to save yourself, but, you know, there's only so much slack in the
world, and you may not get that much of it in your time, but yet you have to keep the
struggle up and fight the fight to get that slack.
Or send money to the station or...
Call that number, 828-9500.
Now, if you...
It's...
I guess what we're trying to tell you, friend, is how much do you listen to our Slack radio
ministry?
Do what?
How much do you listen to us here?
Oh, every week.
Every week.
So, do you know about what we're talking about, about Slack?
Yes, Slack.
Right, Slack.
Well, what's Slack mean to you, then?
Utopia.
Remember, we're trying to get you to use your own brain, so what's Slack mean to you?
That's all?
Yeah, really.
That's a good answer, Ron.
Is it?
Yeah.
What is Utopia, though?
Yeah, but what would Utopia be?
I mean, would it be a place where you wouldn't have to what?
Or you would have to what?
Or what?
Never wind.
I mean, what's your idea of heaven?
I mean, do you want to go to a heaven where nothing ever happens?
No way.
Where you're just having to listen and mind your manners the way you did on Earth?
No.
Is that what you're looking for?
Why is that so exciting?
I mean, is that what you're looking for?
Well, Christian heaven is a joke.
It's boring.
Yeah?
But, I mean, I want something besides that when I die.
Right.
You don't want to keep your pants on no longer.
That's for damn sure.
Okay.
Go to hell.
So, you say you want subgenius hell?
Yes.
Okay.
Now, did you know that, by the way, talking about Christian theologies, did you know that
heaven is hotter than hell?
Really?
Right, because there's, if you look in your Bible, there's seven suns that eat heaven,
okay?
And now, if you took an earth, okay, put seven suns, that would be hotter than the molten
gaseous threshold of brimstone.
Oh, that's all the time we have.
I'm sorry.
But anyway, here's a soul sucker, okay?
Oh, yeah.
That's it.
Well, that opened up a line at our private line here at 823-749-0.
You can call us and enjoy the experience of being on our Slack with a real subgenius minister.
That's 823-749-0.
But the main number to call is 828-9500.
That's 828-9500 to help us fight the fight, to bring the power of Bob into the lives of
all of us.
Remember, KNON, Voice of the Yetis, 90.9 in Dallas, Fort Worth, Arlington.
Yeah.
Coppell.
The Metroplex.
The Metro-Mess.
And we've only got one light shining.
A traveling Bob.
Just one little light to keep KNON open.
Only one light, friends.
A traveling Bob went up to a farmhouse, knocked on the door.
The farmer opened the door and said, yes.
The traveling salesman said, my car's broken down.
May I stay the night at your place?
The farmer said, yes, but you'll have to sleep with my son.
The traveling salesman said, oops, sorry, wrong joke.
Ha.
And that, friends, was from Victims of AIDS.
And now, Dr. Chaos.
Dr. Chaos?
Yes.
I'd like to speak about the, I'd like to speak to you about the religious hypocrites,
the false churches, the people that are, shall we say, giving us a rough time.
828-9500.
Operating and degenerating within the conspiracy, religious hypocrites are sub-hypocrites.
They're human.
Their hideous purpose in life is to hatefully, hatefully attack and destroy all that is truly slackful and good.
Quoting mechanically from their religious books, they proudly ask others if they are as saved as their sick minds say they are.
Self-tormented.
The false churches slyly torment and confuse those that they pretend to help.
You can't shame them, for they have no shame.
Only monstrous arrogance.
And that is why we need your help.
Awaiting navigational input interface for base computer.
Check.
Prepare for interlocking.
Oh, yes, friends.
We've been waiting for a sign.
For a sign from you, from out in the audience, to 828-9500.
Please call the Hour of Slack radio ministry.
Don't let us die.
No!
Don't let us be destroyed by the false churches.
It, it, it's...
It's pulverized by the masses and...
And ruined by the, by the humans, by the human beings that are ruining us.
And, and taking away all your slack.
Hey, it's not mine that I'm worried about.
I've been slacking off for years, but I'm worried about your slack.
And you're the one.
Don't you see?
You're ruining your own life by not pledging to King of the Wind.
It ain't the money, friends, it's the power.
It's the power to, to keep this station on the air.
Just to talk to you freely about what we really believe.
I'm the, I don't, there's no, not enough money in the world to make me sustain.
I'm the only one standing here and saying, oh my, my God, my God, what has Dallas come
to?
When only, no, no lights at all on the board and only me, only me out here screaming and
telling you, please, please, please get it away.
Because I can't do it all myself.
I don't have the money.
I don't have the funds.
I don't have the slack to keep this station on the air by myself.
My, my, my, my, the leads in my forehead's stood out.
And I can't make it work.
I can't make it work.
Only you, only you can give this station the ability to survive.
And there it sits.
There it sits.
Dead.
There's no, there's no, ain't no more slack in the world.
We thank all our, our pledgers that called us.
All our pledgers that called us would, but it's all over now.
I don't think we're going to make it.
We only made seven and a half percent, seven and a half percent of our goal for the play
show.
And I can tell you who made some of the most of the quo for the generation, and this was
theivers.
And I don't think anybody, nobody could ever make, make city life sound like this again.
It was anything but the heavens.
Others stopped the ship and the sea, the Venus, the lleva, and the tartaram of the river.
I'm in Tibet.
us on the air it's 828-9500 828-9500 keeps us on the air reverend buck can i make a comment please
yeah please because we don't have any lines lightning it's it's hard i'd uh i'd just like
to say if i may that uh all you people out there that that are not pledging and and you know that
you're feeling that guilt and we're not making you feel that guilt you know that guilt is coming
from inside you you're making yourself feel guilty but let me say this if you don't pledge
don't come crying to us when niggy takes control of your life hello it smites you hello hello
well say it say it or spread it this is uh
bohemians against bill cosby great
oh my god you wrote in didn't you yes i did
okay well that was a good letter uh did you get a packet of information
uh well stang takes the mail not me oh really yeah i addressed the pastor buck oh then i'm
waiting to get us i have three letters for buck in my bag here that i have not looked at
well there's some important information taped about uh bill cosby okay we'll look into that
we'll look into that why didn't he go to bed with more women
White women.
We'll get with you later, okay, Dean?
Oh, yes, dear friends.
We're running down towards the end of this Hour of Slack radio ministry.
828-9500 is the number to call.
That's 828-9500.
Make your pledge to the Hour of Slack radio ministry and put us over that magic 8%.
And, friends, you have to remember that this is a church.
This church does everything that any other church does.
We put out books.
We put out pamphlets.
We put out incredible audio tape lessons that you can hear.
And, friends, that number to write to for information for the church of the subgenius is
P.O. Box 140306, Dallas, Texas, 75214.
Get your pencil or get your mind together.
It's P.O. Box 140306.
P.O. Box 140306, Dallas, Texas, 75214.
That's 140306, 75214.
140306, 75214.
And, dear friends, it's a blessed message that we're bringing you now.
Call our station.
828-9500.
Pledge to the Hour of Slack, please.
Please.
And, oh, yeah.
Bye-bye.