Sire, there is no more money.
We gotta get some money.
That dirty purgish harker, that black whore.
You people think we just improvise this stuff.
From the keyboard and stuff.
But no, we have to rehearse this stuff all week long.
And we have to ride this bicycle treadmill that runs the electric generators that make the power spew out over the airwaves.
Out into the invisible air where your ears pick up the rare material and strange music that this station plays.
Such as the Hour of Slash.
Stuck in an availability room somewhere deep beneath the surface of the earth.
The Reverend Ivan Stang, made of pure cream cheese and three pieces of toilet paper,
has rebuilt his entire personality from a foam-like mug distributed by the Church of the Subgenius through
the
WCSB.
Welcome to the Hour of Nothing.
Slash.
We had such a good cue there, I thought maybe you could use that.
No, I don't care about, I don't care about creative cues.
That's all you need to buy.
For this station!
There's only one thing that matters between birth and death, and that's donating to this station to keep it on.
This station will be hauled off dead in a casket tomorrow if they can't pay their electrical bills.
And clones of Cowboy Dave will have to quit writing those scripts because no one will be able to pay them $75,000 a year to do this show.
It costs money to do these kinds of elaborate productions, friends.
But friends, it's not real money.
It's the kind of money that you...
You need to make your life twirl around like a little Twinkie stick.
It's the kind of money they give you in outer space.
The kind of money from deep, deep in the cosmos.
It's not paper money.
Nothing as flaccid and tricky.
Nothing as...
A milky, clinky silver dollars.
No, we're talking...
Psychotronic, subphonic money.
The kind that'll bring you a long-sleeved shirt.
This is Reverend Stang on November 10th.
So-called 2016.
And I feel like I've been being groped by an evil fat man for two days straight.
I'll get over the trauma easier than most people, but we don't feel real funny quite yet.
Oh, I have a funny feeling, all right, but it's not fun.
Anyway, this happened to be pledge drive week at WCSB in Cleveland.
And yet the studio phone was disabled.
So I had to send him this...
Generic pledge drive CD that I usually take to pledge drives, but don't play most of.
It's actually a pretty good collage of old rants with a cast of dozens
spending 35 years of pledge drives at two different stations.
But anyway, whenever it says to call the station,
instead go to subgenius.com and push the donate button.
Or do the right thing and buy the $35 membership.
Uh, kit.
Become a proper minister, finally.
And get into the secret good part of the internet.
Both links are right at the top of subgenius.com.
And you even get to see our classic TV commercial for free.
Sire, there is no more money.
We gotta get some money.
That dirty British architect, Black Morton.
They're here.
A minute.
It's showtime.
Time for the subgenius hour and a half.
The show that dare not even exist.
Join us now as we rocket away out of normal time into showtime.
It's mysterious, evil, spooky, eerie, creepy, wacky, kooky, fun.
It's the subgenius hour of swag.
And here we got brains the whole operation.
Faster signal goes up.
We're in the satellite.
We're bumping out all over the world.
Pretty fancy, huh?
Not too familiar with it, the satellite.
You're buying time.
Time, friends.
Because Mr. Moneybags, he's paying a salary.
A salary?
He throws in a hundred bucks a week and consequently I can't preach against drinking because his
icebox is full of beer.
I hope he's talking about you, my friend.
Pay us not to preach about beer.
I can't preach against sugar.
That's because I'm a man.
Because they all smoke.
For me.
I have to let them out for 15 minutes between Sunday school and worship service so they
can go out and light up a Chesterfield or something or the end of it.
And what kind did Jesus smoke, friends?
It's time to open your heart, close your mind, unzip your lips, and bend over because you're
about to receive the word of Bob.
And pull out that wallet, friends, because it is pledge drive time.
Praise Bob.
It's either the last pledge drive for a while.
Or the last hour of slack.
This could be your last chance, folks.
I thought you boys understood.
It's business.
That's all it is.
You still don't get it, do you, boys?
There ain't no countries anymore.
No more good guys.
They're running the whole show.
They own everything.
The whole damn planet.
They can do whatever they want.
What's wrong with having a good for a change?
And they're going to let us have a good if we just help them.
They're going to leave us alone.
Let's make some money.
You can have a little bit of fun.
You can taste that good life, too.
Now, I know you want it.
Hell, everybody does.
You're going to make a million dollars.
Ah, yes, dear friends.
It is, in fact, pledge drive time.
And that number for you and everyone else you know to call
is...
In Cleveland?
Yes, it's 6900.
And you can remember that because it has a 69 in it.
That's a secret number.
It means that's like when two little rabbits get into each other's rabbit holes.
And friends, this station, referred to herein, hereafter as this station,
can, in fact, and must be reached at this station.
And I know you want to...
Make us look good.
I know you want to help us look good in the eyes of this station.
You know, it's a student station.
I'm not exactly a student.
Friends, it's so you know what you must do.
You must help.
Friends, if you are listening from Sweden, if you are listening from China,
if you are listening from Japan, if you are listening from Iraq,
send that money in to this station.
And put it to the name of...
Al.
Of...
Slack.
Because if...
You know, friends, if we don't start getting some of those calls coming in,
I'm going to be forced to go back to my old pledge drive tapes.
And, in fact, I'm going to do that right this very moment.
You're going to make a million dollars.
Dear friends, this is your dear pastor, Reverend Ivan Stang,
calling out to you from the...
Depths of my heart.
And I can see so many of you sitting there hovering by your phones, waiting.
Now, the phones are ringing here.
We're doing great.
This time, we've got all the beautiful girls, the mighty, studliest of genius ministers,
sitting here waiting to catch your calls.
They're all busy.
But if you get a busy signal, just call back again.
Because we sure ain't going to turn down a bit of your money, dear friends.
You know that.
That's one thing you can always trust a Bob.
Listen to those things going off in the background.
And, uh...
So, for all I know, maybe these...
Ah, yes.
Oh, we got...
This is one of the callers that wanted to meet Reverend Stang at a cheap motel.
That comes with a $200 pledge.
Yeah.
Ah, baby.
Sire, there is no more money.
We gotta get some money.
That dirty, purgish, hard-to-back, black, rotten...
Gorton, blackin', backin', hackin', mackin'...
Ha.
Wow.
Wild, wild Dave is here.
That...
Where can you get an argument like that, especially when your head is square,
you're...
You're...
Um, pocketbook is elongated, and yet your listening pleasure is far from orgyastic.
If you were, like, into physics or geometry and stuff, just for the pure radiation sickness of it,
you know what I mean?
Just the slamming and banging of the, um, animals as they pledge themselves to oblivion.
Friends, you're animals, too, just like us.
And you need sustenance, just like this station does.
This station is an animal.
It's a shuffling beast.
Uh, shuffling towards Bethlehem.
This monkey doesn't survive on peanuts.
Uh, Pennsylvania.
Yeah.
Huh?
Towards Bethlehem, PA.
No, this station doesn't...
Is not a monkey and does not survive on peanuts.
It will not be your big, bad bitch.
It must.
If it is to, uh...
What is it?
Survive.
That's right.
It's mu...
Like the...
For prevail.
Prevail.
To even prosper.
Because you could just survive like a la Island of Dr. Moreau, but you want to prosper.
Yeah.
I mean, you want to live it up, baby.
You want to be able to dial ear...
Any time, night or day, and go...
Okay, that's my...
That's my soul.
You know, that's my thing.
Well, you know, it could be that someday they could dial ear...
Oh, no.
And there'd still be a station here, but it wouldn't be what they were expecting.
It'd be Rush Limbaugh, the 18th version of his daily show.
Followed by Hannity discussing what Rush said.
Followed by, uh...
What's his name?
Pegwed...
Peg...
Pegleg Wooden...
Never mind.
Followed by dead silence as an EMP shuts off all electronic machines in the North American...
American continent.
As the emergency medical system transpires across all the way from the Canadian Arctic all the way down to Hexico...
As the whole planet shuts down, you can hear the doors slamming.
Are you going to let that happen, or are you going to call...
The door's open!
...the station, baby?
Bathby?
Baby?
For 15 minutes.
Well, I guess they're not.
Okay, I'm just going to go right back to, uh...
Oh, they...
I mean, when this show ends, if you haven't helped the station, what you know as reality...
Is going to come to a crashing halt!
You see what I mean?
We were playing that cheery music because we wanted to be positive.
But you know, frankly, friends, positive thinking can kill you.
Uh, look where positive thinking has gotten most of the world so far.
People say, Reverend Stang, he's a pessimistic booger.
But frankly, I'm worried that my most pessimistic predictions might turn out to have been, in the long run...
Idiot!
Idiotically optimistic.
And our fear tonight is that you out there taping this show will think...
Will think, oh, well, uh...
Well, they'll stay on the air, or not.
Whether I give, or not.
But folks, if you don't pledge, the world will literally, will literally come to an end at the end of this hour.
If you, and I don't mean just some of you, I mean you, the one listening right now.
Oh, you're laughing.
You're laughing.
It's going to collapse around your...
Pathetic ears.
But you nihilistic teenagers out there.
Oh, no future, man.
No future.
You know, that's why if the rival cult that wants these airwaves had this hour, they'd raise 10,000 bucks by now.
And you know what they'd do with it?
They'd build concentration camps for the likes of you.
You abnormal.
You, you punk.
You old hippie.
You, you humanist.
You subgenius.
You, you, you fy fixing drug.
You walking around the fire.
You fucking addict.
And your new LucaStagh that we're gonna start off with.
My son is payin', my konkretb trainings, I Yoo, go to the notca day.
Show him that fat, I saw you on social media.
I gotta pin it straight, right?
I hope it's not too late to be Ora
But's all for our holistic middle school life.
I just can't hold so much back on mobile hockey if you give me a paycheck that doesn't allow Tortax to figure out how to play with Sh mi say.
So friends, you know, the money isn't just for the hour of slack.
And the type of slack you're going to be getting is guilt.
Guilt.
Tonight we're going to whip us up some guilt.
And some of you are saying, oh, it's pledge time.
Reverend Stang's going to rant all night about money.
And you'd better be afraid that that's true, little Bobby, little gimme Bob out there.
At this level, our salesman can see the top of the ladder and is well on his way there.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Hey, praise Dr. Dark, who pledged $19.98.
$19.98?
No, $1,998.
That's a new unreasonable record.
How can we top that from one collared green?
Here's how we can top it when we get one from Australia.
That's who just topped it.
The Reverend Chang.
The Reverend Chang smoker listening by internet called all the way in from that distant climb, that wombat-ridden land.
That wombat.
You could hear kangaroos in the background.
The sheilas and the roos are all humping together and rutting on the barbie of the shrimp and all of that.
And, friend, how come it is that we're getting calls from as so far away as Australia and Cleveland?
And yet we haven't heard from them.
We haven't heard from you.
We haven't heard from you, my friend.
You're our only friend that we haven't heard from.
Is it a moonless night, friend?
Is the wildebeest crying in your left ear, making you want to go things to your mucilaginous passages you've never done?
Forget about that stance.
That stay-at-home, hate-the-ether way of thinking.
Get out there and pledge your numbers.
You've got to do something, and those numbers are.
No, that's...
Yes, yes, yes, no...
$6,900.
That's $6,900.
I hope you understand the significance of that pronunciation.
If you spell it the nuclear way.
Dave here has a pronounced speech impediment.
It's not an impediment.
Well, some not very well pronounced.
It's a high-spirited way of expressing myself.
Hey.
And you could be on the radio, too, just like us, if you could just bribe us with those pledges, friends.
Yes.
That's true.
We might even let the numbers of the, what, the evacuation numbers?
Have you noticed that we read your number out on the air?
We give your home address?
Well, no, not that, but your social security number.
Yeah, your entire church name.
And don't you want to talk to Princess Wee in person?
That's not a recording.
I mean, if you talk to Dave or me, we're just recordings.
She's real.
And that's...
And when you call her, you not only get to pledge your monies, your hard-earned scrids,
to a baseball cap for $25.
I mean, you know, people talk about local, alternative, and college radio stations
as if we had some hidden treasure here in Smallburg, Peppytown, USA.
You know?
But isn't it true?
You're it, Dave.
You're it.
Oh, no.
They're it.
Are we it?
No.
They're it.
The vast listeners, some of them are a little bit too heavy and need to cut down on the food a little bit, but...
That means you're it until you call in to this station.
The Radiothon 2005 begins on noon Sunday, November the 6th, and ends on noon Sunday, November 13th.
On Friday, there'll be a special opening.
An opening?
You like openings, don't you?
Yes, orifices everywhere.
Creases?
Dents, grooves.
Like the convolutions in your...
The dents.
How often do we recognize the importance of dents as sexual appurtenances or a sexual...
There is an aspect, a sexual aspect to the dent, just as there is an opposing one to the bump.
And you can learn more if you call and talk to the actual queen of all the UFOs at...
This station.
That's the only way for us to get your address so that we can send you the postcard that reminds you to send the check to this station.
Because you can do that, friend.
You can do that if you're listening to this show by internet three weeks from this pledge drive.
If you're listening to this show on one of our beloved other stations, such as WREK in Atlanta or beloved...
Any of them.
You can still support your...
Your local hour of slack station.
You say to yourself, oh, I listen on the internet.
I live out in Wyoming.
Play that post office box back in...
However...
Send it.
You could...
You've got that stamp.
You've got that pencil.
You've got that MP3 of this show.
Write that address down.
This station.
There's only one Clevelandite who cares or knows anything.
All of our fans are from somewhere else.
That's why you, far away, have to send those trickles of surprise checks.
And you can always put some weird little extra clipping or statement in there.
A kissing mark on it.
Some random surrealism to confuse the nice volunteers here at the station.
Some that open your mail.
We've received some absurd objects that, you know, have no explanation.
So please, you know, it's better off with the stained toilet paper going,
than looking at something for three days and having to call in a nuclear, well...
Just do it.
Nuclear.
And remember, friends, these pledge-a-thon...
Friends are like radio wars.
They seep down into the consciousness of the average citizen and make him not want to pledge.
But if you want to fight back against constipation, radio broadcasting,
flaccid, placid, overweight, understyled, incorrect...
Overly easily understood.
Overly easily, easily, overly, overly easily understood radio.
Unlike this show.
Connect in now with...
Say, I'll do virtually anything.
And especially to piddle your exogenous zones.
If you'd like to taunt to the lovely princess we are...
Can't you taunt to her?
You're going to get more than an exogenous experience.
You're going to get an...
You're going to get an awakening that's going to thrill your sphincter and your family's collective sphincters
for thousands and thousands of years.
And I'm not exaggerating either, am I?
I'm...
No, Dave, what are you...
I'm probably exaggerating a little bit.
You can't exaggerate.
No.
There's no way of exaggerating the importance.
Look, if you pledge now $50,000, we'll send you a hoodie.
Now, we all know that that means it's like a really cool sweatshirt.
But in your sick imagination, you could probably make it seem like some hoodlum was going to come to your house,
bark down your cattle, cause cerebral damage to your grandparents, and blame it on somebody else.
Or kill me.
Or you could kill me.
Or kill Bob.
Yeah, you could.
You could just do that.
Instead of calling this station, then just at least...
Look, even if you're lying, even if you're one of those hypocrites, you just want to talk to Princess Wee
and have her take your number down, go to a bunch of work, and have some other volunteer send you the postcard reminding you.
And even though you have no intention of ever actually paying, go ahead and call anyway.
Okay, I...
Because who knows?
You may decide that some...
Maybe suddenly you'll get a conscience.
Okay, Officer Sting, could you please step aside?
We have enough of the hard call.
Bob, you want to come over here and tell them what they'll get?
I'm afraid nobody wants to do Bob.
And Bob doesn't want to come over here.
He's just looking at us now with a weird glare, so I'm going to shut up.
There are people who want to do Bob, and those are the people you should really avoid.
I don't want to imitate him in his presence, and if he doesn't want to talk, then...
Okay.
Never he hardly ever does.
And when he does, it usually is some message about Mars needs women.
He's stuck on that Mars and women thing.
And he'll go back there.
Venus doesn't need women.
It's got all the women it needs.
Venus is practically nothing but women.
It is a woman.
So wise up, man.
What are you going to be?
Mars, a Martian, a Venusian, or an Earthman?
Or a blister who calls in with that pledge right now.
It's just a pledge.
It's just a promise.
That's all.
What are you going to do?
What are you going to do when it starts raining, and you want to be the hippest encumbrance on your whole gulf?
And you're just dry.
You're just a dried up old raisin of a person.
You're going to need an umbrella to keep out the sunshine once the sun goes over.
What more could we...
I mean, it all adds up.
It comes to that great fruition, that conclusion.
Everything points to that number.
And your pledge to that self-same number at...
This station.
The synchronicity is so vast, it endures you right as it's dropped in front of your nose.
Ha ha ha.
Six, eight, seven.
A million, it is.
A hundred.
Okay, I'm going to give them no more chance, and we'll just play this.
I'm going to call the same policeman that I was trying to get in, and go out and arrest some of these slackers.
And I say with a small L in the background.
Right, that's it.
The small S for slacker.
These aren't real slackers.
And have them brought down here and give me $40.
And I promised to pledge $20 for a white or black logo shirt, and then use the rest of it to buy a beer.
I mean, it's like you get...
And it's tax exempt.
You're tax unripe-able.
Just think about it.
You can currently...
Let's not get into any...
You can crunt.
You can crunt, man.
Don't you see, man?
You can crunt now.
These big girls, you had them those.
I'm going to go.
You can crunt.
Big girls there.
They knit and weave stories you can't understand.
Unfortunately, if you don't have the imagination to supply that part, at least you will have supported this station.
Don't be a nitwit, friends.
Go for it.
This station is where to send that check if you're not hearing this live, but on some insane playback later on.
Yeah.
Be a superhero, friends.
Be your own hero.
Be a hero for once.
Can you imagine yourself careening down the slopes in one of those knit winter hats?
You're cruising down those...
You're slaloming.
You're shushing.
Yeah, that's right.
And suddenly you realize...
Realize...
Excuse me.
Suddenly you realize you're shushing down the cliffs of Garfield Heights.
You're not in New York State.
You're in Gotham City itself.
You're in Goth...
Yeah, right.
No, no, no.
You're Batman.
You pledged.
You paid.
You sent the money in and now you feel good.
You're good.
You're Batman.
I feel bad.
You're Batman, all right.
You're built for this job.
That's right.
You can see thousands of miles in the future and in the pasture.
You can see things others cannot see and you see in your future...
A $30 large...
In the year 1998, the men from Planet X shall descend on this earth.
In power and glory to lift up those dues-paying subgeniuses who went to subgenius.com and did
the right thing.
Yes, the right thing.
What will they be wearing?
Yes.
They reached down into that deep, deep, deep pit in their body, that dent in which they
found, yes, the most secret, intimate organ of their body, the wallet, and they extracted
it, and they pulled from it...
Gently.
...those dollars that they then rubbed upon themselves.
Yes, just gently first.
And then they blessed it against a picture of Bob, and then they put it against a picture
of their mom and their dad, and then they put it in the mail and sent it to the station.
That subgenius tongues might air wag and near want for extra pizza at the station staff
meetings.
Friends, when you donate to this station, you're not just helping us improve our equipment,
stay on the air, and make a better signal.
You're helping to pay for the pizza that makes the station staff meetings bearable.
Some of these people actually stay alive on the stale pizza that they eat after the
station meetings.
Don't you understand how shoestring these thumbs are and these little, these budgets
are that takes to bring you this great entertainment here on...
This station.
And now, this.
All right, I'm on it.
All the good ol' boys are here tonight.
We'd like to welcome you down to the television mission.
Don't forget, if all you can do is sit at home, then try to keep yourselves awake and
dial the phone.
Call in for pledges.
Call in for pledges, yes.
Yes.
Answering the phones this evening.
Beautiful Dr. Saifah.
And the best thing you can do is dial this number that you see on your screen as quickly
as you can with a contribution to the television mission.
Oh.
You revolting genetic accident.
Take your smelly shell elsewhere.
Yes, Dave.
You disgusting creature.
Think of it, Sting.
Even Fireside Theater endorses your church.
Sorry I had to use that word.
But little listeners, you may ask, is there hope?
Listen, you little listeners whistling in the glistening mists.
Listen to these inspirational words from the Book of Lies,
Chapter 10, Bankruptcy, Verse 10.
The passage runs, and I quote,
If you be tired or depressed, if you've got that run-down feeling,
remember, you're not just anybody.
You're special.
You are living proof that God does not exist.
Yes, you, little listener, if you're like most of the people who listen to this show,
are proof that no supreme being could ever exist.
It's a duck hunt.
Uh, Hanson, please, don't, don't, don't start.
Please, please.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
I've got to start anyway.
I don't want to start.
Believe me.
Dear friends, I'm, I've got to admit, I'm just too depressed to do a, a good show.
Come on!
Get up off that chair!
Follow me!
Now you can have something to sell.
We all know we're in the art of selling.
We create a mental and an emotional climate of unconscious selling.
Right in your own home.
And you could call in and you can talk to the, there's some sexy ministers on the, on the lines tonight.
Your prayer partners are here, uh, ready to receive your promise.
Your covenant with Bob, friends.
Why, the, uh, the evil, uh, Dr. Zaphod here picked up, he got one from Joseph Prowl for 200 bucks.
And I, I happen to know that that one's not a joke.
Now, I know that, you know, not everybody can, can...
uh, can give that much.
You know, Dr. Drummond and I once talked about, you know, who means the most to Bob?
Is it the little old lady who can, who, you know, doesn't have anything at all to her name,
but, but she donates a quarter, her last quarter?
Or does, or is Bob more impressed with the rich man who could give a million dollars,
but only gives 10,000?
We prayed on that, friends, and we realized that in Bob's eyes,
that rich man is the only one that's going to get to heaven,
because he paid more money.
So I want you to call.
We gotta sell you, friends.
We're not just gonna sit here and talk.
Bob said we had to party.
Didn't he?
He said we had to party.
Didn't say we could.
He said we had to.
And so, we must also sell.
Praise Bob and thank you.
Or they're destroyed.
When everybody sells...
We're all selling.
...for we all have something to sell.
Yes, everyone selling together, mighty symphony of prosperity.
For we all...
...have something to sell.
A candy-colored clown they call the Sandman
Tiptoes to my room every night
Every night.
Just to sprinkle stardust and to whisper
To whisper, dear friends.
Everything is just fine.
It's just fine.
When we were born
After this life
We were destined
To make it right
To be determined
And this is our fate
We're singing this song
Singing this song
So you can relate
We are going to save the universe
This time
Friends, it looks like we might actually save the universe this time.
And only it's not really us saving it,
But these fine subgeniuses
Wonderful, wonderful callers who have pledged
These pledgers who have pledged in
And callers such as
Reverend Steve Sinek
The faithful, faithful subgenius
The one that we always depend on
When we miss the recordings of the show
He is the one who has them
Thank you Steve.
From far away in Chagrin Falls
From the bottom.
Chicken Falls.
Much to our chagrin that he's so far away
And yet he can hear the show.
Down in the valley there.
And Chris Sazekas or Sazekas
Sazekas.
Or whatever. Even here in Lakewood, Ohio.
So there are people locally who do care.
But the great Rex Ouroboros
Rex, thank you.
Is, has called in
To help us
From our bridge
To the brotherly sister station
In Champaign, Illinois.
Oh, praise brother Ravoporous.
I can hear the corks popping now.
He has reserved the
Destroy All Monsters video I'd noticed.
There is no blame.
Oh, the great David Bochner.
Thank you David.
He is the David Bochner in Toronto, Canada.
Isn't that nice?
Listeners in Toronto calling in.
David Bochner did not just pledge.
David Bochner put us on the internet
You might say. And kept us there
For a long, long time.
And we still can't leave.
Scott Points in Athens, Georgia.
Now what kind of a show is this?
Did we get calls from so far, far away?
It may be Athens, Ohio, no?
No, no, it's Athens, Georgia.
Oh, I wish I were in the Lamb and Cotton.
And he's getting the Slovenian glasses.
And the hour of slack triple X.
That's a good choice.
And another one.
Here comes the lovely Miss Wee.
Princess Wee brings another one.
Chris Turner, the Reverend Ant...
Oh, that's anti-chri...
Reverend Antichrist.
A turnip cannot pledge.
That's not quite the same as Reverend Antichr...
No, it's Antichrikes.
Antichr...
But Antichrist to Mobile, Alabama.
A survivor.
Oh, I wish I were in the Lamb and Cotton again.
A survivor of the...
Terror.
Of Hurricane Ivan.
Oh.
And Her Highness Hellnoe.
A lovely Lakewood, Ohio.
Another Lechner.
Her Highness Hellnoe, the creator of the Bobby Awards almost every year.
Did I mention John Visnavkas?
No, you did thank you, John.
Or Vinaukas.
But we love you, John.
Yes, Bob is a...
This is a religion of love.
So just imagine he has read them and pronounced them anonymously.
Too late for the anonymous ones.
Anyway, thank you, anonymous, again and again.
Thank you, all of you who were and shall ever be...
Mon-ton-imus.
Mon-ton-imus Bay.
You don't have to be monogamous or a baseball cap wearing,
winter knit hat wearing,
No, it helps.
aficionado of music,
and diverse talk in spunky rhythms
of strange ideas and beautiful searches into the past.
Like when we go tripping down Mam-mammary Lane.
Oh, yes.
There are lots of jugs.
I talked to a listener. There's a listener in Detroit
who thinks you're real smart.
Remember that? We met that guy.
We met this guy that said that he thought
you were real smart and he gave us all those
Firesign Theatre albums.
And that man was himself extremely big.
Brain damaged.
He gave us each copies of all
the Firesign Theatre albums
on CB.
And only 72% of mine actually worked.
Oh, really?
Yes.
Well, I hadn't even tried to play 72% of mine.
Oh, I played as many as I could.
Oh, yes.
Oh, we're all bojo's around this.
Well, you know, the CD
technology is crude.
Mine is, yes.
And yours, of course, is even cruder.
And then there's your ears, and then there's the stuff
in between your two ears.
And there's what comes out of my mouth, which is also crude.
But not as crude
as the sweet crude
we're pushing, ladies and Germans.
We're bubbling crude.
If Eichmann were a vastly
vaster man,
if Adolf Hitler did all he can,
we still wouldn't hate
you as much as we hate ourselves.
For you not pledging...
What the hell?
As puzzling evidence once said...
Let's get the flop.
Let's frop up so we can get back to hating
the conspiracy instead of ourselves.
Yeah. Puzzling evidence.
I thought you said that. About frop.
Oh, I thought about 40 times.
Hapsifropipulus?
Well, what's...
They can't get any hapsopsifrop...
...fropsepulus if they
pledge to this or any other...
No, I wish, but
that's an
imported herb
that's pretty expensive
from Tibet. Now, Buddhist llamas
or is it just the alpacas?
Any of these different animals,
how do they ingest it? With their teeth?
No, that's not the way it works.
The llamas...
holy men
Tibetan llamas...
Well, you claim to be holy, you know...
The frop only grows
on the graves or droppings
of those holy men or
on the graves or droppings of the
Himalayan Yeti.
That's what I thought.
In America, that would be the
Sasquatch or Bigfoot or
the... what is it?
Homo Hoaxis.
Oh,
wacky, hacking man.
That would make no sense, dang.
Anyway, so if you were a Yeti and you
were just to randomly go out and poop in the
backyard, would there a Dalai Lama
emerge from a hapsopropsepulus bush?
No, but if you... that would be the only
place in your yard where you could grow
the things, the plants.
I know they only blossom
during a full moon.
So... It's like wolfbane.
Yeah. It is
wolfbane. It's exactly the same
thing. As wolf... as
the... the... well, not the...
the wolf... there are different
plants that are called wolf's
bane. So one is like... One of them is a
slightly poisonous thing that grows
in the Balkans or someplace. But that's
anti-lycanthropic, right? And that helps
psychological
lycanthropy.
But then physical lycanthropy can
only be
combated by Haba-frop-zipulops,
which is why when you run out of frop,
you turn into such a bastard.
I just thought you were going to
say, you know, if you had the original wolfbane,
you'd still turn into a wolf after you
smoked it, but you just would think that you hadn't.
But if you smoke real
Haba-frop-zipulops, you not
only will think you haven't turned into a wolf,
you won't. And...
Or you will, but you won't care.
Which is even really
the best, I guess. Well, we're at the deep
end of the pool now, and I don't know if I can
swim that well. I don't understand it.
Actually... I dived right in, and this
is where I'm at. I'm kind of like over my...
head. Or...
Anyway, so, none of
these people have pledged for Haba-frop-zol...
Well, never mind.
I'm sorry. I'm not... Oh, they might not know where to pledge.
Of course, they need to pledge to...
this station.
And are you too mad, Bob?
Someday you'll be the Bishop of
Tinkleberry. Yes.
Someday we shall bring Bob back to
life. We will find his
old pipe shanks and stems.
We'll scrape them out and get bits of saliva.
We'll retrieve the
DNA of the original Bob
before he was killed. Any of
those times. As part of our master
plan, Bob will not only live again... And Bob shall walk again!
...and walk the green earth. He will sell
again! He will sell again!
And you will be one of his
victimless crimes. You shall
own what he does not. You
shall become a part of a vast
invisible fortune, which grows
more invisible with each second.
Yes. Please.
Give us some...
money! Money!
Money! Money!
All right. Arms for the poor.
Penny for the old
guy. Penny for the old guy.
Can you spare a quarter for an old
altar boy, Father?
Can you spare a quarter
for an old altar boy, Father?
That's it. That's it. That's it.
Yes, friends, you too can be
exorcised. You can have the
demons of money exorcised from your
wallet. You can do it yourself by calling
this station and pledging
your hard-earned dollars.
I think at least they should pledge
just based on the fact that we haven't
conducted this pledge-a-thon like
this. We only do this once a year!
Yeah, we only do it once a year.
You know what it really costs to run a
station like WCSB? You know,
in fact, we're not going to play any music.
We're going to boy you to death.
We could talk with
NPR-type accents, public
television, volunteer accents. Dr. Tom Winkle
is here from the faculty accent
department. And, uh,
Tom, how long have you
been working here and why do you continue
to work here? Uh, continue?
Never mind. Oh, I've been at the Tweed
for 25 years now.
That's a nice suit
you're wearing. I was wearing the Tweed.
And I noticed the back
of your suit is all shiny.
Oh, no, that's where I peed.
There's all the back-slapping
you've been involved in at those faculty
luncheons. Want to get
something published? Publish this!
Oh! We need
money! Let's see what was on in
the old days when we had something to
think about. I've got
one hour to convince you how badly
we in the station need your support.
Uh, we have a
special, special form of slack
in store tonight.
Instead of us giving you slack
for once, you're going to finally
give some back to us.
Of course, some of you have been doing so all
along. Praise Bob.
But for the rest of you,
oh, this could be the moment of truth.
The moment at hand.
You have to love Bob.
He loves you, but
you love Bob.
You have to.
Or else what happens
if you don't love Bob?
He'll kill you.
He'll Bob you out.
He'll Bob you out, folks.
You heard it here first.
If you don't love Bob,
he'll Bob you out.
Oh, baby, it's sad.
Only if, you know,
if you love Bob,
you don't pledge.
Bob, lay away
your reverend stans.
Too many reverend stans
can really make you...
Dear friends, we need that money.
Oh, my gosh.
Let that old goat look at those phones
light up.
Oh, yeah.
We need to do a shake it off.
Shake it off.
Can you imagine a world without slack?
A world without the hour of slack?
And even almost as bad,
without this station.
Because if you don't send some money
by midnight tonight,
you're gonna be wishing to God
you had, or Bob,
or somebody else.
The money's no good.
Just get a grip on yourself.
The money will be no good
following the Great Collapse,
which is imminent.
Yes, the time to donate is now
because your money will be no good tomorrow.
It's true.
Just look at your money
sitting there in your wallet.
It wants to be used.
It wants to be useful.
And yet, it's just like so many pieces of paper.
But if you send now,
if you pledge now,
the money will be good.
That's right, because we have
a secret plan
to ride out the coming collapse.
Well, it's not a secret anymore,
but we have ways of making the money worth something
tomorrow in ways that you will not be able to do.
We have ways of making the money work.
For it is written in the scriptures,
do not store up treasure on earth,
for thieves may get to it.
But store up treasure
at this station,
for no thief can touch
your money there.
And where your money is, so shall your heart be.
And if your heart isn't in this radio station,
why are you even listening?
This is what I ask you.
Hmm?
It is easier for a camel to get through
the needle's eye than for a rich man
to make it into heaven without having
divested himself of some of those riches
on this station.
The Saint Stymie
de Bergerac
Stymie de Bergerac has called in with a pledge.
We praise Saint Stymie,
the greatest
peonman in all of
the Coventry area.
Consider your donation
a little bit of lube, as it were.
This will help you squeeze through that eye
of the needle. We're not asking you
for an erectile lubrication.
We're not asking you for that kind of donation.
You could donate your sperm any time
you want, and you know what? They might
give you 25 bucks if it works.
And you're better off taking that 25 bucks
and sending it to this station.
And...
I forgot
what the hell I was talking about.
Who cares? As long as we
get the money and stay on the air.
We're talking pennies a day.
Yeah. Like the levy guys
say, how much will this cost? 100,000
dollar homeowner. Well, none of you own a 100,000
dollar home. You own a 45 dollar car.
But, if you
send 15 dollars now, you may
quit smoking! And we
may continue to buy CDs
and other... and citizens
rights and other things. Call it the
never say quit or
never say
continue. I don't know. Yeah, you could play with the idea.
Never say quit package. Yeah, think of... Is that
worth some money to you folks? Not only
will you be listening to this station,
you'll be smoking its ashtray, and
shooting its clashes.
This is radio you can smoke. Yeah, man.
Think of it. But don't let the authorities know you're smoking this radio station.
We know you've been doing that. Yeah.
We got our eyes open.
Heck, we used to before they sealed that window shut.
Back in the day, yeah. You know, when Bob
Dobbs runs out of frop for his pipe,
what do you think he puts in his pipe? He puts in
this station. And your
soul! And you don't have to be as wealthy as
Bob to support us.
Oh.
No, friends, as a matter of fact,
a tiny little... we've been
bandying about huge
figures like $15, $20.
Hey, $5.
A $5 check or
money order thrown into an envelope would make a huge
difference. You'd get a thank you note. $10
would make twice as much difference.
Yeah. And $100,
well, then... What do they
get for $100? Lonesome Cowboy... For $100, Lonesome
Cowboy Dave will come to your house... I will not smooch
buttocks. And place upon your... No.
Fundament the bestowal of his
kiss. No. I am not a fundamentalist.
Nor will I smooch a fundament.
I may have one
as a schnack, perhaps. If you want to kiss
the fundament... He's not a fundy boy!
Now, there was a $200
cheap meetin' to Reverend Stang at a cheap
motel pledge, but nobody's
really taken us up on that since a long time
ago in Dallas. Do you think it's the economy, or do you
just think it's your disheveled appearance and
the fact that you've been in the tabloids so much lately?
A little bit of everything, of course. Yeah.
I've done a little bit of everything. When the collab starts,
everything starts working against
the protean... Peak slack, man.
Yeah. Was it Sata who wheeled the
cliff up the hill, or was it Prometheus
who liked to eat his own liver, you know?
Not here! Or Wotan
who kept picking his eye hole.
His little scabby hole where his eye
used to be. Right after Burt Lancaster
or somebody shoved a
big hot stick in there. Friends, it's not
easy being a god. It isn't.
It's a bit like juggling, actually. Some of the time.
But it is easy to
be the god of this station
by being the
friendliest, nicest pleasure to call
it. The last minute,
and get in your call,
your donation to the Hour of Slack. Now,
if you're really cool,
you'll do it again
for the next show.
Think of it, comrades.
As we... Where they actually let you call in if you
have the nerve, or if you're...
And... If you've had enough
coffee. You know, a $30
donation can actually get you
a date with Bob.
That's right. Absolutely. Not Bob Dobbs,
but Bob Dolchin. No touching, no feeling, and no
Tostitos at the bar. This is...
strictly a pre-functional
date, as they used to call it back in the days of
Bob's a hooker, like you.
Fondling Bibles. Bob's just
another hooker, like all of us.
He'll do it for...
This may say something about him, the fact that it says
quantity available unlimited.
So he's willing to go out with as many of you
ladies as are willing to pony up. Use your
imagination, girls.
Why do you think
they call it...
Well...
Well, actually, now
it's the time to say that you are in fact
listening to a pledge drive on...
this station.
You know, you think in profusion
about how little there is of this
activist sort of
voice in the radio nowadays.
Too many people talk about their titties, their twangers,
they look at their history or geology books
as they get ready for
the next adolescent
tune. But here on...
this station... You hear a plethora...
Is it a plethora? A plethora.
A plethora of adult entertainment,
and you don't have to use your imagination
to watch those boobies flounce,
or those ideas come out and
pink on you. You don't need a placenta.
No, you don't need that savage placenta.
What do you think you are, David Lynch back in the early days?
F-f-f-f-f-fallin'
around, checkin' things out?
Nah, man. You're born again.
Into the new flesh.
A flesh of
listeners.
A carnal union of
millions of listeners.
You can't get out.
You must give back.
Okay!
Action!
I'll give you your hand on this.
I plead you should have this. I plead you should have this.
Now you can have...
This amazing new symphony...
...of prosperity.
...generates in the mind of the salesman
before it does in the prospect's mind.
You all
sell something to sell. Everyone selling
together.
You can call in tonight, set it up,
you'll never have to think
again. And of course, a check
or money order is always
so much fun!
Come, a big gib's
a golly goshin', better puke your
peat on full-throttle potentate,
elsewise your wants'll be
waggin' down on mammy's hind
nannies. Why can't your
peas are poppin' squeezin' when the gushers
are goin' all normal like?
Got your no geisha sense
in your sneezin' chamber, boy?
Heistin' a empty
platter in your bean bag?
Where's your rollerballs, eh?
I can't gropp me no
love-grow on this
loo-joo-loo-joo band.
You gon' have to spreech
English, Jake.
Get right with your muscle snake,
snunk monkey. Quit spritzin'
your plizzerer lessen it's
snowin' white lute juice, baby.
Elsewise your pleatin' bleeds
like a cheater's blowin' hot water.
You go blind, or please
your neither tryin' not to.
Either way, you're gettin' up on
the wrong orbit for this kinda
free-needin' bleedin' side
trade, eh? Well,
won't you go stand there like a damn
nickel slug, or you gonna plus
your plimper and righteous hargin' it,
P-boy? Got
weeny rivers and fluter tubes,
don't you?
Join gumption's with the true and
the sea brave, and pee for
your job, man, and send your jeans.
Buy out the gland
owners with what you earned
with your skinny peelin'
face of pain.
This has been your enunciator.
Thank me.
Amen.
Today,
today,
buh buh buh.
Buh buh buh.
I must not fear. Fear is the mind killer.
Fear is the little death which brings me...
Mis amigos queridos, que quiere
en su vida? Ripesa grande?
Buh buh buh. Buh buh buh.
Buh buh buh.
It's a buh
world after all.
world after all. It's a buh
This station.
This is the subgenius
radio ministry
hour of slack.
We are full grown.
We are grown up
men.
We are all past
the age of reasoning.
It is our
mission.
It is our task.
It's obvious.
Yet you still
ask.
We are going to save the universe.
We are going
to save the universe.
This time?
Oh yes dear friends.
That's right.
We'll be saving the universe
on this, this, like I say it's one chance.
The swinging love corpses
want you to save the universe.
Robert Anton Wilson our special celebrity
guest star wants us to save the universe.
And the zombies for Bob here answering the phone want, they desire,
they desire for you to save
this universe.
So you know how, you know that number.
You've memorized it by now. It's been hammered into your head enough.
Hello listener.
I'm your guardian angel Sergio.
I just stopped by to ask if you were donating
to Radiothon this year.
What? You're not?
But don't you understand how important
Radiothon is? Let me show you how things
would be if no one donated to Radiothon.
See that over there?
That's this station.
But wait. Those aren't the same DJs you know and love.
Because no one donated to Radiothon
this station ran out of funds.
When that happened, everyone had to leave.
And now the evil preppy kids have come in
to turn this station into a farm club
for commercial radio.
And now they're doing a five hour Dave Matthews marathon.
Stop polluting my station
with those unholy sounds!
And look over there.
That's little Johnny Indie Rocker.
But he's not an indie rocker now.
Without this station he was unable to get turned
on to underground rock music like
The Shins or the Brian Jonestown Massacre.
Instead he's been listening to Creed
and Limp Bizkit because the corporate music
machine has fooled him into thinking
that sort of music is alternative rock.
This station was never around to show him
the real alternative and now he's
screaming nonsense about the Nookie and
listening to that ironic cover of
George Michael over and over again.
And look at all the blues fans.
They've got the blues alright because they
don't have any blues to listen to on the radio!
And I could show you all the downtrodden
punk metal, jazz, folk, reggae, and ethnic
music fans but I think you get the point.
All of radio has become a swirling vortex
of tripe, drivel, and crap because there was
no this station to redeem it.
The corporate music machine got its way
so now all there is to listen to on the radio
is country, top 40, and Dave Matthews.
But it doesn't have to be this way.
You can still donate to Radiothon.
All you have to do is call this station
and a friendly operator will be ready
to take your pledge.
Remember, every donation is like a
silver bullet in the heart of the corporate
radio beast. It's your donation that will
support us and keep us afloat.
What's that? You'll donate?
Woohoo! Go ahead and call this
station right now.
I don't like
status, luck, prosperity
by blowing them
off. But don't blow off that pledge
drive, friends. Bob's promises
to all of you show the nature of
abnormal behavior. I'm not
gonna, we ain't gonna be taking no guff.
This time, this time,
this time you are going to pay up.
You are going to call because
that sweet name of Bob,
and the sweet name of Bob, my friends,
what, what, what,
what else can you do? What else you gonna
do with that money?
Well, I can probably think of all kinds of things you can do with that money.
I mean...
Oh, yes, friends.
See, if you don't call in, that's all
you're gonna hear all across this
nation forever.
And it won't even be Elvis, probably. That's the
shame of it all.
It'd be the bald-headed Elvis
from Michigan, I guess. But you're laughing.
Oh, yeah, you're laughing, saying,
oh, I don't care. I don't care if radioactive
rain destroys all the
fish and fauna and pollutes the water
from me not supporting
the station. Oh, I don't care if
our, if firestorms
kill all dormant
seeds on Earth, making
regeneration of plant life
possible. Oh, I don't, I'd
just as soon get... This state
is a nation. For free,
I don't have a spare $10
because I'm gonna spend it on cigarettes
and liquor and
and false slack.
Oh, yeah, I don't care
if vast quantities of nitrogen
oxide dramatically increase
ultraviolet radiation to the point
where humans and animals are blind
and we can't even hear an hour
of slack with our eyes.
Oh, just compromise
your immune system
by not sending
not pledging a penny or even
worse, by pretending
to be a subgenius and
pledging but never even actually
sending the check. Huh?
Sick.
Sick creatures out there.
They don't even care.
I mean, it is so ironic because
some of these false preachers
can raise millions and millions
of dollars. No problem there. Well, I tell
you what, I challenge you,
Jim Swaggart. I challenge
you, Jim Baker. I challenge you, Jim
Swaggart. I challenge you, Oral Roberts.
You see this hand here? You see this
hand in front of me, Mr. Jim
Baker? This is called the claw
and it's got the power of dogs
in it and the power above. And I challenge
you to show your ugly face
here at this radio station and come forward.
Go ahead. Come forward with
all your millions.
I'm ready to have a match without
rules. No rules at all.
One will survive. One only.
One minister will leave the match
still breathing if one of you
goody-goody preachers
has the guts to show up.
Yes. I'm sitting here drinking
some Texas Select beer,
friends. Beer! You hear that,
Jim Swaggart? You don't drink beer, oh no,
or smoke on froth because
you don't know the power of these herbs.
I challenge any minister do-gooder
out there to show up. All of you
with all your TV shows
and all your bought-off politicians,
your paid-off judges. Do any
trick you want, but I got the claw, I got the
power of Bob and the power of
Texas Select and you, my friend
listener, has the power to call this
station.
Do it. Do it. Do it.
The times, the end
times get closer and closer every
minute. Imagine some guy
or some gal driving around out
there. They're tired of listening to the
same old music on their conspiracy
radio show, so they try
switching channels and they come upon
this. They hear these voices.
Talking and they think, now what
is this? A talk show? A church
show? A comedy? I mean, oh my
God, are these people serious? It's
too developed to be a joke. Should I
kill them or should I?
Or should I? Or should I?
Which will it be, friend?
Which will it be?
Kill us or pay us. Either
way, call this station.
It's, there's some, some have-nots
out there. I know by definition many
subgeniuses are have-nots in money,
but they do have slack and at least, they're
know what they're missing. So,
you've done okay by not having money,
haven't you? And so therefore, it won't
hurt you a bit. Uh, it won't hurt
you to have a bit less. And the
money doesn't go to me, it doesn't even go to the
Will of Dobbs, it doesn't even go to someone else.
Your membership money does though.
It goes to keep this station on
the air without this station.
You won't get the hour of slack free, you'll be
like everybody else out there.
Give to us
something to live for.
Anything.
We need hope now, love.
Put a rope on the son of a
bitch!
Okay friends on the internet, where I can
flog our swag legally, if
you want to help yourself and the
Church of the Subgenius and get a
pretty cool package with like 25
different nifty things in it, like
pins and bumper stickers, and
a real preacher card, you need
to go to subgenius.com
and click to become a
subgenius minister.
You'll see photos and a list of all the
stuff you get, and you really do get to
go to the scrub genius forum,
which is members only, and we talk
in ways that people don't talk on
Facebook. Much, much
smarter ways, ironically enough.
Isn't that funny? We also have
things like t-shirts and damn near
everything you can think of with Bob's face on it.
That and a huge selection of
other subgenius graphics
on coffee mugs and so forth.
And we sell several very
weird DVDs
and CDs of the Bob songs
and old mp3
stashes of this show.
And best of all, from our main
online store, you can
buy the book of the
subgenius, which is by far the greatest thing
we have ever done.
It's an actual Simon & Schuster book,
22 bucks, in print for over
30 years, and every
copy that we send out is
signed by yours truly.
For that matter, your address on the
puffy envelope is handwritten by me
also, so it keeps
my fingers nimble. That's
subgenius.com.
And remember, it's only
money.