Well, right now, this minute, I'm going to do something that may overthrow the entire radio business.
But I'm not going to say a word about laboratory tests or quote you statistics or make medical claims.
All I'm going to say simply and honestly is this.
Ladies and gentlemen, try, just try...
The Sogenius Power of Swag.
Praise Bob!
What the hell do I think you're doing?
Did you know Bob is coming?
Pop is coming!
Praise him!
The end is nigh.
Yay, yay, yay, yay, yay!
To life is...
1998.
Praise Bob!
Bob is coming!
X-Day is coming!
For day five dollars.
Your wit would not threaten us.
Shrew's brain for occupation.
The Sogenius Power of Swag.
Oh, sleek and bastard, you make me writhe.
Fear is the root of all courage and profit.
Come on, Shane.
Don't tell me you believe all this.
I traffic in the inexplicable.
Take off that white hat.
Boy, he's a skunk!
Go take it off.
Ever since I was a young boy,
Lulu has been back in service
He brings you even more trouble.
Bob!
And he's trapped.
You've broken we time'srados!
Do me this favor,
Because the rules are the only thing we got.
Promise to the rules.
None of you ever give the slightest consideration to a word I say!
That's because you're very boring!
Some kind of an avant-garde hoax has been perpetrated.
I'm not going to listen to it.
Let's go to the beach.
It's night and it's raining.
I see you're determined to start an argument.
Go to bed, please.
Hug?
There's nothing less attractive than a psychiatrist
who pouts.
Cut short.
What do I have to do just to get in a word with you?
Offer sacrifice?
Then here.
I brought you a mud pie.
Now can I talk to you?
Will you talk about the moon?
Listen, everyone knows the moon is Roquefort.
I've come here to talk about Colonel Fell.
What about him?
Major Nanick approached him this morning.
Complaining of a strange and wondrous illness.
And do you know what that heartless butcher prescribed?
He said, here, take this.
It's a suicide pill with a mild laxative side effect.
What kind of bedside manner is that?
I frigged the arrow of peace.
Why'd you wear that arm there?
I was in the morning.
For God.
If God exists then he's a thinker.
More likely a foot.
A giant, all-knowing, all-powerful foot.
I don't belong to the goddess alive and hiding in Argentina.
But I believe in the devil all right.
You know why?
Because the prick keeps doing commercials.
The best value involved that keeps getting better.
And what is it that the youth of today wants, Alan?
Oh, well, you know, it's that this gore type of blood and bullets and, you know, death and being crushed.
And your brain's coming out the ear and that skull with that dagger through and that, you know, that.
You know what I'm saying.
I mean, it's that death, gore, dismemberment, whole type of go for it type of thing.
What's up?
There's a bunch of assholes fucking around in the harbor area, attracting the cops' attention to my investments and screwing up all of my business.
I am the Big Mac.
I am the Big Cheese.
You might say that I am the Big Mac with cheese.
Now, this record that I'm speaking to you on now, I made myself.
It's absolutely true.
I did.
I made it myself.
Nights and nights of hard, diligent work.
I got the machine from a supermarket in Quique.
It formally cost me 39 and sixpence.
And apart from one or two small faults, which the average person wouldn't really notice, it really is an excellent machine.
Frequency response is mild.
And anything you record on it, it comes out absolutely lifelike.
So why pay out in 20 guineas for a machine that you can get for 36 pence?
Why, indeed.
Anyway, I'm not going to keep this great secret to myself.
So what I'm going to do is, I'm going to tell you what you need to make this marvelous recorder.
And tell you all about it.
You need 200 screws, a whacking great few miscellaneous wheels, and a couple of reels.
A furlong of wire, a bit of old tire, 400 volts, and 240 volts.
Consisters, condensers, transformers, and knobs.
A smooth-running motor, centrifugal rotor, capstan, and roller.
A bracket to mount a revolutionary counter.
And just for a jade, you'll need some good tape.
Right. Now you've got all the bits, all the pieces, everything you need.
All you've got to do now is put it together.
You screw down the motor and gurgle the rod to combine the condensers with vertical sensors.
Transistors are gutted and bolted and nutted, all covered in wire and bits of old tire.
A couple of wheels, transformers, and reels, and amps are best parted to bring out the flutter.
Soldering blobs that smack on the knobs, compulate base on the lateral face.
Frugalate wire on the fast-arbor biocid playback response to pedicle sconce.
Add sugar to taste and a bit of fish paste, a few drops of oil, and bink to the boil.
Put in the fuse.
And turn on the juice.
And you're ready to go.
Uh, chat, uh, uh, chat, chat.
Hello, faithful listeners.
This is the Colonel, the overseer of the slaves known as Four Letter Words, also known as a manager.
This album is laden with subliminal messages, here to teach you about the subgenius, the cult of the subgenius, and J.R. Bob Dobbs.
And, by the way, can I get a house?
Jalapena.
I also want to tell you, by the way, this is protected by the B, the O, and the B with the D pinkies.
He's the master of slack.
Bob Dobbs.
He's the man to stab you in the back.
He's got a soup pipe.
Bob Dobbs.
Never listen to the hype.
And stand on his way.
Bob Dobbs.
His pride's gonna sting.
He can tell anything.
Bob Dobbs.
Family knows no chain octopus.
All the chicks dig.
Bob Dobbs.
He can even fuck a pig.
He's got briefcase.
Bob Dobbs.
He can divide our stage.
And stand on his way, all you pigs stay away.
Oh my Bob?
No ?
No.
My Christina won the vino.
He's a master of slack
Bop-Dop
He can stab you in the back
He's got a zoom pipe
Bop-Dop
He has a license to the hack
He can sail anything
Bop-Dop
He can jump into some onion rings
He can stand on his way
Bop-Dop
He's power's gonna stay
All the chicks dig
Bop-Dop
He ain't even fucked a pig
He's got a briefcase
Bop-Dop
He's kickin' the değer spree
Ex-ale-de
He's a master of slack
Pigs will stab you in the back
He's got a suit pipe
Never listens to the hype
Pops stands on his way
His time's gonna stay
He can tell anything
Puppet is an underage
All the chicks dig
He ain't even fucking big
He's got a briefcase
He can't be better than
X-Men, Tom's way
All you pigs stay away
But let's leave things of this world behind
and walk now down the path of Bob
for this brief minute of slack
from the church of the subgenius.
And so once again we find this deep-rooted contradiction
within the word of God
who he himself has said
I am everything but yet
everything
everything is me
and by this very self-same contradiction
we know that we do have some measure
of free will
yes, free choice
and it's up to us
to decide whether we're gonna sin
in the ways that God wants us to
or if we're gonna sin against God
but yet since he is everything
and everything is him
or her or it or everything
one could say well
everything is everything
so a sin might as well be a good deed
helping a little old lady across the street
might be a sin if everything is everything
now this is an acid head sort of motive
to think in
and I don't think anybody wants to go along
with such a vague
and to say the least fluid philosophy
because we have to have some sort of standard reference
for goodness or evilness.
We gotta zero our meter on something.
So why not let that something be Bob, friend?
Let there be slack.
www.subgenius.com
Try that at home.
Wycliffe Notes
www.subgenius.com
ENG
Oh god how do I fall?
I'm so fucking noticed
I was like here's the Eminem thing
Wow
Yeah.
I'm like, oh my god.
I fucking heard that chorus before, and I know it, and here it is, and I'm rocking out to it.
You know, I know a couple words.
And then they fucking come in with the real chorus, all right?
Like, they've been fucking with you.
Like, the thing they played earlier, oh, that was just like a little teaser to the chorus, all right?
And they didn't even play the chorus, all right?
You didn't realize this shit, because they went back in the verse, and they go back, and they play the teaser,
and then they play the super chorus, all right?
I mean, that's what I'm saying.
There's the chorus, and then there's the super chorus.
And I thought, fuck it, man, I can go super uber chorus.
This song is called Madness Is.
See if you can spot the super uber chorus.
Have you heard it?
I did it.
I went and gone quite crazy.
You'd be absurd.
Admit it.
For you to try to save me.
This is me.
Take it or leave it.
What else can I do?
Can you see?
Can't you believe it?
My way might work for you, too.
A conscious choice to quit the search for meaning.
A tiny voice inside your head is screaming.
This is me.
Take it or leave it.
What else can I do?
Can't you see? Can't you believe it?
My way might work for you too
So just let go, lose it
Give into insanity, there's hell refusing
No one else can set you free
Come on, choose it
Madness is as madness does
Let go, lose it
Lose it just because
So fire, shrink
Dump your medication
Down the sink
I mean it
Prepare for true elation
This is it
Take a seat, can't you believe it?
My way might work for you too
So just let go, lose it
Give into insanity, there's hell refusing
No one else can set you free
Come on, choose it
Madness is as madness does
Let go, lose it
Lose it just because
They wanna control you
Put a chip in your mind
Don't tell nobody I told you
If you do, you'll know that I wrapped out mine
They wanna control you
Put a chip in your mind
Don't tell nobody I told you
If you do, you'll know that I wrapped out mine
They wanna control you
Put a chip in your mind
Don't tell nobody I told you
If you do, you'll know that I wrapped out mine
Wrapped it right out
Wrapped it right out my head
Out of the head, indeed, of Reverend Andrew the Impaled
live at X-Day 2012.
Before that, a minute of slack from 1985.
Before that,
the Bob Dobbs punk song was by
The Four Letter Words
on the Bob Songs 5 album.
The long media barrage with British cuts
was from slackmaster Sarcastro.
And the child voice was Young Jack,
thanks to Dr. Legume
and more so to Reverend Pockets,
who did the hard part.
Before that, title by Lemur.
This episode of Hour of Slack
was assembled on the road.
In fact, I'm recording this
at my dad's house
in San Diego,
Stanksville, Texas.
And he's asleep,
which is why I'm whispering
and there's no band behind me.
But now, Dr. G. Gordon Gordon.
The problem with electronic media is,
particularly television and others,
that everything is turned into entertainment.
And the entertainment is
not to educate you in an entertaining way
or to inform you in an educated way.
But rather to disturb you,
to titillate you,
to anger you,
to worry you,
you the viewer,
the consumer,
the user,
that they think of as
someone who is comfortable in their environment,
don't require a lot,
or somewhat passive,
and they're looking in for a little entertainment.
And all of these emotions,
that they are designed to bring out in you,
are not emotions that we have a lot of control over.
They're tugging down in the lower level of your brain,
so to speak,
getting into those instinctive areas.
Sex, fear, procreation, you know, food.
Oh yeah, a lot of food ads on TV, isn't there?
Well, think about it.
Folks, everything they're doing to entertain you
is trying to sell you a bomb, a cure.
A grail.
Yes sir.
Eat this, you'll feel better.
Oh yeah.
Take this, your tummy won't hurt.
Take this and you won't have green demons
from the energy dimensions running through your bedroom at night.
Oh yeah, they got the bomb for you.
And in this country, the bomb is bi.
That's right, you're upset, you're confused,
you're a little eh, edgy,
because, you know, all you do is watch television.
And you have this feeling of unease.
And then something pops up there and you go,
man, I have got to have that 1472
Hyde-related double-drive disc clutch, baby.
I'm going down putting on my credit card right now.
And you do.
You get that sum gun.
And it's yours.
But, you know, it doesn't make the unease go away
for more than just about the time
you start watching television again.
Yep, the biggest evil on the face of this planet
is commercial television.
Military threat.
Flaming debris.
Fatal heart attack.
Stress engines.
Prison disaster.
Economic collapse.
Dangerous radiation.
A tide of violence and human misery.
A liar and an unlawful killer.
Time is international smuggling pipeline.
Starving victims.
And now they die.
Chemical weapons.
Carpet bombing.
Deaths.
FBI.
Kill and injure children.
Police conspiracy.
Negative attacks.
Discipline.
Sex.
Died of a heart attack.
Dying of breast cancer.
Dying of a Japanese nuclear bomb.
Mountains of credit card debt.
The mountain of cocaine.
Tons of cocaine.
Atomic bomb radiation experiments.
Unwitting test subjects.
Dangerous radiation.
Marijuana abuse.
Hooked on drugs.
Time for us to bug out.
Rock.
Rock by rape.
Sex.
Drugs.
Rock by rape.
Nazi war criminals.
Cancer.
Darkness.
Murder.
Caution.
Terrorists.
Castigation.
Police conspiracy.
Dramatic urban torture.
Drunk driving.
Hostage siege.
Government shutdown.
Collapses.
Desperation.
Despair.
Deep into death.
Criminal.
Persecuted.
Semi-automatic handgun.
Explosive gunman killed a tourist.
Human victims.
Racist.
A massive lawsuit.
Hostage.
Ethnic war.
Cancer death rate clean for their lives.
CIA narcotics operations.
Hungry.
Homeless.
Frustrated.
Terrorists.
Spoiled.
Unsanitary.
Hard-hitting.
Losers.
Brutal.
Bizarre.
Critical bombing.
The gang droop.
Criminal.
Anti-government.
Deeper and deeper into damage.
Even death.
Anti-drug.
PEA.
Worldwide ban.
Time for us to bug out.
Rock.
Rock by rape.
Sex.
Drugs.
And rock by rape.
Disgruntled conspirator.
But not a drug.
Attack.
Killed.
U.S. war plane went down in flames.
Crashed.
Gunned down.
Shooting death.
Blood drops.
Murderer.
Desperate tragedy.
Isn't he dead?
Death penalty.
Ransom note.
Forbidding.
Notorious.
Overwhelming.
Communist.
Urban punishment.
Low ethics.
Extortion and murder.
A plane crash set an entire neighborhood on fire.
International smuggling pipeline.
Make it faster, better, and cheaper.
Health risks.
Criminals.
Murdering a man.
Tough.
Diplomatic.
Hell on earth.
The American people.
Magnetic radiation.
Fraudulent assassin.
Mysterious murderer.
Chemical terrorism.
Military targets.
Photo crisis.
Danger.
A freak accident.
No known survivors.
Wild and woolly semi-automatic truck bomb.
Emergency anti-vacuum shooting rampage.
Notorious negative police brutality.
Fear.
The hidden Nazis next door.
Marxist rebels.
Serious murderer.
Accidents.
Problems.
Punitive damages.
Like that negative, heart-wrenching controversy.
Time for us.
To be continued.
Stuck.
Struggles.
Drug out.
Rock.
Rock by rape.
Sex.
Drugs.
And rock.
By rape.
Drug out.
And that's part of our world tonight.
For the CBS TV News, Dan Rappaport reporting.
Good night.
And have a great weekend.
Thank you.
Give it up for Evolution Control Committee!
Now I lay me down to sling you
I pray, I pray
MNO acid ancestors
Now I die
Before I wake in silent void
Galactic space
Shimmering
Molecular designs
Are you trying to bum out the people that are tripping or something, Chaz?
Hey man, you trying to put a dodecahedron in the back of their
Trying to get them too serious?
Sexual shadow space now?
Hey man, life is a joke, it's a lie!
You-you-and friends
Someday you're gonna shut up like hell
So you better make, you better shout and make a lot of noise
Because someday your vocal cords are going to be frozen
Just like that is snow right to the left of your
They're on demand at all
So I'd like to give thanks to the universe for every single extra second that I get to live
Praise Bob and Hail Connie
Thank you, Spectrum
God, there's at least seven minutes left of this life
This little life
Captured forever on the spinning disks and reels
So much more permanent than you or I
We are but mayflies
Bugs
Perhaps just as we examine and pity and laugh at the little mayfly in its brief span
Perhaps some larger creature
Like the man
Is gazing upon us
Perhaps all of us
Our little world is but an aquarium
And you are nailed to the door of perception
Endlessly watching it swing open and shut
Jesus came knocking
But no one answered
It's more like Prometheus on the dock
Waiting for the persecutor to let him be
Buddha came knocking
And they hit him on the head with a stick
Bob came a-knockin'
But you didn't have your thirty dollars
And he was too filthy
And so Bob was wroth and wrath in his anger
And he yanked upon the rug and spread the banana peels
And so many fell and the bigger they fell
The harder Bob came
And his laugh rang out
For political corruptigation
From holiday to holiday
And a very, very drastic disease in the body politic
We thank our Lord Jesus
The fight-meister Lord
And his big shiny fangs
For God has made us in his own image
And he's tired of looking in the mirror
Bob, make up your mind for the American people, why don't you?
And just step in and take over, won't you Bob?
Hey!
I want some cheesy poops, mother-
Not that Bob!
Not Bob...
...Grodds
Bob Dobbs!
J.R. Bob Dobbs!
The living avatar of Slack!
He'll groom we thanks
For our frop
Our...
Frankness
Our frang
And our pang-eye
And other things
That the listener does not know
It is time
For all of you to know that Bob is a fang-eye!
And to decrease
Let go
The many, many foods you have ingested today
Float downstream, dude
Black is the color and none is the number
Turn off your mind, relax
Void, void, void
Anything that makes it harder to pee
Is anti-Slack
J.R. Bob Dobbs, 1959
I believe that prunes are God's answer to man's every dilemma
Anything that makes it harder to learn
Is also anti-Slack
Reverend Ivan Stang, 2000
We can only offer our Sinjurish thanks for that
So turn off that TV!
And turn up your radio!
And read a book every now and then!
FOO!
We had two bags of grass
75 pellets of mescaline
9 sheets of high-powered water acid
A salt-free lipoid cocaine
And a whole galaxy of black and blue
So after this order of rum
Take the buzz-bottom and light them all you fang
And put them to sleep
So watch your rock to the serious drug collection
And let's see if the pressure is right again
On us, roying forungs
Walter Bond
adding shit to a 집
We need dice
And 내려wn'
We darned
little bit fuzzy. I can see the air moving.
You can see the light vibrating.
I am so high.
Oh God.
Bob, I am so high.
High.
So high.
Oh Bob.
Bob, I am so high.
I may never come down again.
I am so high.
Hey Larry, look at the sounds, they're dancing with those pigeons.
And Suds has turned into a bear.
When did Scotty grow a tail?
And who put Satan in front of the computer?
Gotta tell you Larry, I'm really high.
I'm really high.
High and so high.
I may never come down again.
But I am so high.
And look guys, there's a mermaid.
A beautiful mermaid coming.
Oh my goodness.
What a beautiful mermaid.
I am so high.
I may never come down again.
I am so blind
Yeah
I may never come down again
I may never
come down again
I am so high
I am so
high
I am so high
Actually, I'm not.
Alright, now we're going to stop here.
I'm going to slow things down a little bit.
Okay, that was fun.
Now back to the music.
I can't get high enough
To make this shit alright
I can't get fed enough
No, I can't get fed enough
No, to make me feel as though
Whoa, I've got something inside
Get up, brush my teeth and hair
I'll get out, I'll end up anywhere I've found
A place that opens up at ten
I'll sit through the afternoon
And drink and drink
And pretty soon I'll think
Everyone is my good friend
But I know
They all just hang around me
here hoping to see
that train wreck
we call me
I can't get high enough
to make this shit
alright I can't
get fed enough no I can't
get fed enough no oh oh
to make me feel as though
I got something inside
I don't
have to try real hard to find
something to blow apart my mind
distractions
all around
just one two three
four at a time I might
just leave more satisfied I fly
yet my knees still scrape
the ground
just give me
one more then I'm sure I'll be
good
I really wish you would
though I can't get high enough
I can't get high enough
to make this shit
alright I can't
get paid enough no I can't
get laid enough no I
can't sleep late enough
to make me feel like I'm
refreshed can't you hear me
I'm screaming right
in front of you I know the
words aren't getting through and that's
cause my lips barely
can't you feel me
I've fallen down around your
feet in a heap and
incomplete drooling on the
ground and broken down
yeah
alright
thank you
do drugs
lots of them
can I have some
can I get you a cup of coffee
or some water
no
this is good coffee
tastes awfully good
in the world of me that's torture
yeah
this is totally unbelievable
life altering sex and then you just
disappear I mean
you suck to be coffee
there's a new movie
about Napoleon
I thought that was my
old movie
this new movie about Napoleon
and he's played by Ian
Johnny Potts
for Meeks Napoleon
wow cool
oh didn't they already do this in Bill and Ted's
excellent adventure
you know in that
Terry Gilliam movie
why Johnny can't smoke pot
why Johnny Cash smokes pot
I knew Johnny Cash
smoked pot
he doesn't know how to
he's so bad
um okay uh
let's go to the next one
let's backtrack a little bit
and make sure that we're on the same page
I wouldn't want to be at cross purposes
you haven't heard of that
no
we're gonna have to kill Johnny Potts
I want each and every one of you
Johnny Potts smokers there
Johnny on the spot
but to what
or Johnny on the pot
he comes out
and we'll smoke some more
sailing away on the briefest of fogs
I'm not going to do that
Harrison
yes
its our new day
only like. Stop adopted these
omый
way
yeah
head
bread
Their minds dead, sent them to bed.
Wouldn't it be nice if we had ten and barbie crutches
so no one ever had to take a shit or tangle.
Grandma, bless what I kind of puffed up on the screen.
Desecrating family sanctity.
Never dip your pool, can't you just say no?
Condoms are satanic, Jimmy Swagger told me so.
Ah, swing it on out there for me.
Ah, I think you've stepped in something.
Hello, condom.
Hiya, fellas.
Condoms breathe their shit, covered with slime.
Wrapped in sanitary sleeves.
Help breathe in age when you get laid.
Roll it on and shake your butt.
Breathe it in, soon you'll feel it up.
Never leave a wet one on your neighbor's doorknob.
Grandma, bless what I kind of puffed up on the screen.
Desecrating family sanctity.
Never dip your pool, can't you just say no?
Condoms are satanic.
Ah, ah, ah.
Leave it.
I'll bet you don't explode your...
Condoms are satanic, Jimmy Swagger told me.
Don't come in, Jimmy.
The Rudy Schwartz Project did that.
Condoms.
From Don't Get Charred, Get Puffy, the re-release.
We heard some very old 1980s puzzling evidence from KPFA.
The song, I Can't Get High Enough, was by Reverend Andrew the Impaled,
from 15XX.
16XX will be July 1st through 7th, 2013.
On January 30th, there's a devival in Detroit at Smalls.
January 30th is 13013.
Just saying.
Act accordingly on that date.
The blues jam, I'm So High, was several-fisted Tales of Connie,
the X-Day Jam Band, with Priestess Pisces making up the lyrics,
Fat Man D, also warbling, and music by Reverend Angry Larry,
Reverend Suds Bashaw, Bishop Stick, Senator Speck,
and Trademark Gunderson of Evolution Control Committee,
who also did Rock by Rape, also live at X-Day.
The radio ranting about life and death was with Lonesome Cowboy Dave
and Professor Chaz Smith from ESO Radio, WCSB Cleveland, around 2000,
where we also discussed how Texans do things.
It's like a monkey humping a football.
When they have an inbreeding too much.
A Texan likes to just crawl on top of something and wreck it for everybody else
and cost everybody a whole lot of money and just be loud, loud, loud.
The basis of the church of the subgenius,
the product of a perverted or a few perverted Texans' minds.
Read, if you will, this exciting chapter from Humping the Football.
Bob actually is not a Texan.
Well, I'm not supposed to be that specific,
as to what he is or isn't.
But he is a Midwesterner.
He would, to a Yankee, I suppose, somebody might mistake Bob for a Texan.
Well, what about perhaps a Skanky or a Nor'easter
or one of those other platelets that you find?
Oh, they probably think he's a Russian communist.
Well, he is, isn't he, in some strange way we've yet to discern.
Bob only believes that everyone should be equally rich, not equally poor.
But without working, there lies the rub,
and he'd like to rub your lips.
You're a little round belly.
He can rub the Buddha's belly any time he wants,
but he better stay away from my front.
Rubbed by Bob.
You've been screwed by George and ticked off by Tipper.
Ain't it about time to just bend over and pull out that wallet for J.R. Bob Dobbs,
the one true savior, messiah, and holy man.
You know, when the pinks interview me on TV about Bob,
I always say, oh, no, he's not the messiah.
Oh, he's not that well-known.
You know, I joke about it.
But the truth is, J.R. Bob Dobbs, a living man whose business is in Texas,
is the God walking on earth now.
He is not just the son of God.
He is God.
Bob Dobbs.
Not some silly Internet character named Bob,
but J.R. Bob Dobbs himself, that man Bob,
whose first certificate I've seen,
who I saw shot and killed.
He's at stage.
He is God.
And this Christmas, we celebrate the birth of his business manager, Jesus.
Praise Jesus.
Jesus is almost as great as Bob, friends.
Jesus Christ.
In my religion, that's the way we believe he is a prophet and the son of God.
I remember the first time that I danced with Bob.
But Bob himself changed God's diapers.
Voice andQC
Bed or something?
Yeah, you lived in the very beginning
It's sadness,
loneliness.
Better to get bone causal thinking than j常
Let God kill you.
For God's sake.
フ shrimp, quake.
Are you ever compelled to say it?
What?
See, that's what I mean.
It?
What?
See, that's what I mean.
It?
What?
See, that's what I mean.
It?
Barbecue, average, entropy, reversion.
All your life your priorities and your forgeries get no sympathy.
Hey, I just pet you, cause you're so cuddly.
Your name is Bowser's, my fuzzy buddy, and all the other cats try to be cute.
I like to feed you, and you're so cute.
You're crunchy cat food.
Unable.
Threatening.
Objective.
Mutated.
Praise Bob, that was the Psychoskeletons, found as such on SoundClick.com.
From Lemur, it's PR News.
And next up, Jonathan Coulton from his new album Artificial Heart.
From PR News in Washington, I'm a folk hero for trying to thwart PR News on Monday.
A federal appeals court claiming responsibility for an attack that left two U.S. Marines not
harmed.
As Daniel Carson reports, economists say there's PR News.
Economists say there's been another so-called PR News from Washington.
They gave me a test to make me the best that I could be.
They knew all along that there was something wrong with me.
We picked out a spot and made a hole.
Wire and glass and stainless steel.
Now I can imagine how I feel.
I got a new heart.
Artificial heart.
It's not a real heart.
It is a real artificial heart.
There's blood on the bed, but here in my head I'm feeling fine.
It's easy to sleep when I'm not buzzing all the time.
So funny the way I was before.
Once I was blind, but now I see.
Once I was him, but now he's me.
Got a new heart.
I got a new heart.
I got a new artificial heart.
It's not a real heart.
It is a real artificial heart
You're at me again, I nod and pretend to think it through
I don't need to think at all if I don't care for you
It's not an emergency for me
I look at the walls and they go clear
Cover my eyes and disappear
I got a new heart, I got a new heart
I got a new heart, I got a new artificial heart
It's not a real heart, it's not a real heart
It's not a real heart, it is a real artificial heart
Don't pour your love out on me, baby
If you do, then I think that maybe
I'll just lay me down and cry for a hundred years
Don't pour your love out on me, honey
Take my heart, my soul, my money
But don't leave me here drowning in my tears
You say you're gonna leave
Gonna take that big wide turn
Gonna fly right out of here
Without a single word
But you know you'll break my heart
When I watch you close that door
Cause I know I won't see you anymore
Don't pour your love out on me, baby
If you do, then I think that maybe
I'll just lay me down and cry for a hundred years
Don't pour your love out on me, honey
Take my heart, my soul, my money
But don't leave me here drowning in my tears
Haven't I been good to you?
What about that brand new ring?
Doesn't that mean love to you?
Doesn't that mean anything?
If I threw away my pride
And I got down on my knees
Would you make me beg you worthy please?
You're my only one
If you know you need me
So tell me, just tell me
You're my only one
There's so much I wanna do
I've got love enough for two
But I'll never choose a girl if I don't have you
You've been listening to the subgenius radio ministry
at the subgenius.org channel.
hour of slack. For free information, write to P.O. Box 181417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118
or see www.subgenius.com. Praise Bob!
Thank you, Reverend Baby Bear. Don't Pull Your Love was, of course, by the Rudy Schwartz Project.
Before that, Jonathan Colton. We personally gave Jonathan Colton a subgenius ministership
after his concert in North Carolina recently, and he was very polite about it.
Now, we'll let the show run over its edges with some amazing guitar work embedded in a live
performance at Last X Day Festival by the great weirdo singer Tommy Amita.
And the band, Amiba Knievel. Praise Bob!
This is called Cowboy Ed and His Caterpillar.
Cowboy Ed and his caterpillar
Riding out across the plains
Watching from the westward
Grounding up all the aphids
Cowboy Ed can't complain
It's all in a day's work
Cowboy Ed is glad to be of service
Don't squish him, it only makes him nervous
Once upon a time in the west
Ed was a normal-sized boy
Who wanted to be a cowboy
Something happened to shrink him
To this size and size again
He didn't let that stop him
Cowboy Ed is glad to be of service
Don't squish him, it only makes him nervous
Of course, four and seven years ago
Our fathers brought forth on this
Common animation
The first ever song to be sung by a cowboy
Conceived in liberty and data
Cated to the proposition
All men are created equal
Those old words and honest they once said
Still ring true even for cowboy Ed
Cowboy Ed
lime
New Zelotnik
Mais le prix
guitar solo
Tune in next week, Cowboy Ed will fly
When his steed becomes a butterfly
Ha!