For the next hour, sit quietly and we will control all that you see and hear.
Turn on the machine.
This is Radio Yerevan.
Wake up, puppet boy!
We are conscious of our responsibility and obligation to provide programs
which will be enjoyable, entertaining, and tasteful.
There is absolutely no other possibility.
We subjected it to careful editing to eliminate elements which we might consider in questionable taste for late-night viewing.
As it will be shown, it is well within the restrictions of the television code,
which is even more restrictive and stringent.
In many cases, it is not.
We are sensitive to the concerns which prompted your letter
and assure you that this network will continue to adhere to the high standards we have maintained throughout the years.
Thank you.
You are about to participate in a great adventure.
You are about to experience the awe and mystery
which reaches from the inner mind to...
The Self-Genius Hour of Swag.
What?
You can relax and enjoy this quality product,
secure in the knowledge that it has been specially created for the lover of fine things and the man of good taste.
Oh, sorry. You can edit that out, can't you?
I can't.
Just simply.
othes
Over all, we want you to be satisfied with the queen,
the cierto esperar sacrificio
is as difficult and as complex as anything...
If you need anything,
you are wrong.
Are you?
I'm not talking to you.
on a friendly basis.
Now we're heading into the sexual or gonadial area of the Doug Smith brain.
As you can see it has some similarity to the previous portions of the brain and the typewriter area.
But the enormous stamina of this human.
Saying hey, hey.
Yes, that's all the trigger the Smith brain needs to get an enormous rise.
I say something.
Can I say something?
This show is our only method of communicating with you earth people.
In hopes that in the storm of Babel you will understand the basic reality of our planet.
And apprehend that we are not simply a comedy group or a humorous exercise.
But actually the emissaries of a distant civilization which only wishes to confer its own understanding.
Upon the citizens of your rather distant planet.
We thank you for listening.
How do they do it?
Well, like this.
Put that on like this.
Oh no, not like that.
And like this.
Ouch, that hurts. No, cut it out.
Oh, hey, hey.
Yes, you'll see us.
Enthroned in glory.
Trailing clouds of glory.
Emitting the sacrosanct.
The call of heavenly flame.
Like the gods we are.
Yes, that's our aura.
What, radio?
What?
Radio gods.
Yes, I think so.
You can watch it.
See the lightning.
Do you wanna party?
Yes, dear friends.
Hell yes, friends.
We're back.
That wonderful hour.
Friends, that bad hour.
That one time hour, friends.
That mysterious hour.
That poltergeist infested hour, yes.
Friends, the poltergeist is working tonight.
Yes, he's working double time.
Because one of these day decks won't turn off.
Get your finger out of the hole there, Dr. Stang.
You're liable to hurt your...
There you go.
There we go.
Well, let's turn on the dampers and see if we can get the nuclear power plant started
here, doctor.
I'm anxious to take off.
Take off.
Hold on.
Hold on, personnel.
Clear most area at this time.
Will you get all those guys out of the other side there, please?
What'd you do, doctor?
Central control processing on.
Their central control is on.
Dr. Stang, you're on, doctor.
Good, good.
Okay, you want to close the watertight doors here?
Yeah.
Oh, watch out for that squid, man.
There's a prairie squid right by the door.
Speaking of which...
And inject some of those caller souls, would you, into the retribution chamber?
Primary and secondary circuit tests commencing now.
Well, we really...
Yes, line two has a prayer request.
Is that so, friends?
Well, tell them to pray.
I have to run away from anything because I don't believe in anything.
What direction is the zoo in?
Back the other way.
That where you escaped from.
I'm not going to go into that because this is a continuation of last week's show about
censorship, both of the subgenius church and also by us.
The First Amendment gives you the right to choose what you hear, what you say, and what
you think.
We've got to get out of here.
Chris Cole, hang on.
If you're going to shut all up, do
it right.
No shall we ride five o'clock?
Get out of here?
Done.
We're ready...
Go oppress or risk.
. . Zhi.
So what?
Why shouldn't they be offended?
What have they done that they shouldn't be offended?
What was that?
Shh.
Who gives a...
Could you state that as a question, please?
Where are you?
Who gives a...
Money, talk, and book...
Walk.
How do you feel about that?
I don't give a...
Censorship is never going to accomplish anything.
As long as there are a few formatted words in the album,
it will always sell an extra million copies.
We want people to make up their own...
The First Amendment gives you the right to choose what you hear, what you say, and what you think.
The money, talk, and book...
...they offended me by trying to offend themselves.
School.
I don't give a...
I don't give a what?
O-B-E from their nickname,
album doing I Don't Give a Bleep. They're kings of feedback series. And you can reach
out. These are available as LPs and EPs and tapes and everything else. You can call Out
Band Experience, Reverend Bill Miller at area code 617-LICK-OBE. That's right. Lick-OBE.
617-LICK-OBE. Or write them at post office box 221. That's 221 Boston, Massachusetts.
02123. What an easy address. Box 221 at 02123 there for kings of feedback. But speaking of
censorship, the other kind of censorship.
The kind that's not excusable. The Nickelodeon TV network offers a pretty insidious yet kind
of beautifully ironic and telling example. Last night we were settling down to watch
our favorite show, Ren and Stimpy, and Nickelodeon showed the powdered toast man episode of Ren
and Stimpy, but it was censored. In the original broadcast of it, this was a rerun.
The powdered toast man becomes president of the United States and when the oval office
gets a little chilly, he burns the bill of rights in the fireplace. And as we understand
it, after they showed that the first time, Nickelodeon got three, count them, three letters
from patriots, patriots complaining that it was bad, bad to show the bill of rights being
burned by a cartoon character.
So, Nickelodeon censored it. Which is typical of these would-be patriots who are so very
attached to the symbols like the bill of rights or the flag, they'll kill to protect the symbol,
but they'll also kill to prevent the practice of what those symbols stand for. They like
the name of the bill of rights, but their mind can't quite make the connection between
the name and what it actually means, what it stands for. And in fact, they hate and
fear, dear friends, what it actually means. And it's these corporate chicken gut soup
boys that are so quick to kowtow to three kook letters, it makes me sick.
Make up scarcity, defy reward.
And I'm seen as it relates to community standards.
Community standards.
We don't all agree.
We're losing our minds.
Virtual reality.
Community standards.
Oh, hypocrisy.
Insanity.
This is art.
CIT.
Obscenity.
This is art.
If you did it.
Obscenity.
Because we want you to be just like us.
Normal.
My lyrics were put on trial.
Rob.
As in Robert.
Well Bob, what makes you think you and your artistic whore community stand in the same community?
Normal art for normal people?
A closed mind is your destiny.
We know there's no reason to live if you have your mind closed.
You must open up to all things that come before you.
Open your mind.
This is art.
This is not a fantasy.
This is the reality of life.
There are people who don't live like you.
There are people who are not like you.
There are people who don't want to be you.
He said come over here and stand in.
Now this is not FCC approved.
This is not for your children.
This is not for your mother.
Everybody stand up.
People should make up their own minds.
FCC approved.
Art.
Obscenity.
Reality.
I don't care.
I...
I don't listen.
I don't buy it.
We live in precisely a quindi'
Art.
I'm over the edge.
Where are you?
ã‚ŒãŸ
That was Community Standards by Kings of Feedback.
Also known as Out-of-Band Experience.
Coming up, 10 Inches of Slack.
This is an album by, well, not by the Subgenius Foundation,
but it's got a lot of subgeniuses on it.
It certainly has material that relates to this mighty church.
This particular cut done by Skull and Bones called Who Killed Africa?
It's there ready to be hatched.
It's in 1969.
Okay.
After the AIDS virus was appropriated for, as we see in Hospital 1509,
when they got their $10 to $25 million for this.
In 1969.
Okay.
They took the virus after having completed it in the laboratory,
infecting the smallpox vaccine.
100 million Africans were injected or infected from at least 1976 until 1979.
Wait, wait, wait.
You're saying from 1976 to 1979?
From 1979, 100 million Africans were infected with or given a smallpox vaccination
that was deliberately infected with the HIV virus?
According to the London Times, May 11th of 1987.
We're just talking about the AIDS conspiracy.
We're trying to get rid of Black.
We're trying to get rid of Gator.
If somebody was playing with this virus in a laboratory and it got loose, I don't know.
It's a conspiracy.
We're looking at some of the literature that Dr. Strecker points out
is that we'll never be able to do anything with it.
I mean, we're trying to get rid of Blacks.
We're trying to get rid of Gays.
We're trying to get rid of Gays of 200.
Who else are we trying to get rid of?
Okay.
Very legal.
It seems as though the credibility of the experts involving who's responsible for AIDS
is still in question.
But the masses of people are doing research
and living and searching as we are.
And then we come and, as Dr. Silverman said,
they found places in 1955 and 1968 that predates the information that the masses of people seem to come up with.
But we just don't believe that that's really legitimate.
It has been really terrifying for these administrations.
This is not softball games they play.
And when the director of CDC sits up here,
he's got a shotgun sitting next to him.
Especially in the early years, this was extremely repressive government.
Don't kid yourself on this.
I mean, I've worked for lots of governments around the world.
This one was some of the most repressive I've ever been involved in,
in what we as scientists could say to the public.
I was writing memos that we were caught between a rock and a hard place.
It was a huge epidemic.
And no resources.
And the secretary of HHS was saying,
I've just checked with all the public health service folks,
and everything that needs to be done is being done.
That was a direct lie to the American public.
And then, and then,
the folks at CDC are caught in the middle of that when you ask,
what is the truth?
Probably the silliest debate that's gone on with AIDS is this abstinence condom issue.
It has been absolutely crazy.
Because the truth,
and when the director of CDC sits up here,
he's got a shotgun sitting next to him.
And it's only behind the scenes as the truth comes out.
That's not good for the American public when you've got such an epidemic like this.
What it provokes is an,
I want to throw every gay person in jail.
There is a problem with homophobia in this country,
as we've been told by the AIDS community for years and years and years.
There is a problem.
There's a problem with racism in this country.
And one of the things that we find, unfortunately, still,
as we take materials out into the country,
and we do test these throughout the country,
that these unfortunate, uh,
aspects of our human societies do bubble up.
Tell me about it, pal.
That was, uh, from the EP,
vinyl EP called 10 Inches of Slack,
a cut called Who Killed Africa by Skull and Bones,
which I believe is actually the same as Reverend Richard Longenecker of Shout Out,
who produced that EP.
The EP also has songs by three other bands,
including that old piece by D.K. Jones,
Huge Voodoo and Me,
well, not an old piece,
Jim Bob Joyce Speaks,
the one that, uh,
well, you've heard it.
You can write us, friends,
for free information.
That album will be available from the Subgenius Foundation in Dallas, Texas.
And, uh, you can write us for free information on just about anything involving the church.
Give us up, genius.
Just write to Bob at Post Office Box 140306,
Dallas, Texas 75214.
We will be giving that number again before the end of the broadcast.
Ah, yes, dear friends.
The devil owes you money, friend.
But Bob, you're the best.
Bob Dobbs is the bank where you can cash it in.
We gotta burn out the banks of the devil!
We gotta root him out!
Burn out the hate!
Burn out the radiation!
Burn out the fire!
Standin' around actin' like you got wires of blood and anybody else,
but you ain't, cause I'm the one that has it, not you, me.
What are you talkin' about?
About I know things I ain't never learned.
How I can see signs.
It's somethin' that just happens,
and I got to do some things sometimes.
I got to do some things sometimes I don't even wanna do.
And sometimes inside me I can feel it.
I can feel it pullin' and tuggin' at me and pushin',
and I can feel my blood beatin',
and I got to do this thing right now.
It's wires of blood.
Ain't everybody has it.
See, it's a gift.
It's a gift, like a gift for the prophets.
Now, I ain't sayin' I'm a prophet.
No, it ain't like that, but it's like that.
You're crazy, boy.
You get away from me and you stay away.
I'm goin' where I'm goin'.
I got a woman. I got a woman, see?
And that's where I'm goin', to visit her.
He thinks if he keeps on insulting you that you'll go away.
Whoa.
Scary and neat.
Oh, we wish. They wish.
More cars going in and out of little car doors.
We can do those clicks, too.
Oh, there he is.
Fire! Fire! Fire!
Fire! Get the car doors, okay?
Okay, good. We've cut rid of them. They're dead.
For once.
And we can continue with...
Ah, yes, your subgenius...
Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
Uh...
Back, back on the airwaves again.
To exploit women and men.
Because, you know, Bob Dobbs can free you from the petty constraints
of so-called
civilization.
He'll show you how to beat the system
without effort.
Because ever since the very
first day of Bob's life,
from his very conception,
which we call the day of the Burst Trojan,
the church has strived to negate,
to negate the smarmy, mealy-mouthed,
coke-bottle-up-the-butt puritanism
that has helped make human beings
the violent, vengeful, uptight killer apes.
And of course, they are today.
Well, we aren't trying to make a big deal
out of unrestrained sexual, mental, and spiritual freedom.
It's Thame that have gone out of their way
to twist natural impulses
into narrowly defined
Dobbs disapproved artificial behavior patterns.
We're not trying to pry open your skull
to eat your brain
like those other religions.
We just want to air your brain out.
We know that if you'll just let your skull breathe,
it will inhale the truth
of what Bob is saying.
And we aren't trying to envelop the globe
with the church because we want to.
It's because we have to.
Because it's fated.
The church must sweep over America
or time itself will stop.
There are many ends of the world preached by many religions,
but none of them are as permanent as that.
Bob has a better end of the world in mind.
For us.
We like to call it the practical joke
that we don't stick around for.
Of course, the normals think this is all just a funny, funny joke.
And you can indeed look at it that way.
Bob is the stand-up comic.
Earth is the straight man.
And the end of all normal human reality
is the punchline.
Can you turn up the bass a little bit?
Turn up the bass, mate.
Pass that bowl of frop over here, man.
Can you turn up that bass?
Get that frop out of that place, kid.
Give it up for that bowl of frop, man.
Frop man!
More feedback.
I am the frop man.
Google, Google.
Oh, Mitch.
More pills, Bob.
We've got fucking, fucking, fucking...
We're gonna...
This is the most illegal, most illegal thing you'll ever make.
Ain't you gonna eat us, too?
Yeah, yeah, we're gonna eat you, man.
You've never seen this.
This is illegal.
You're gonna get a bucket of pills.
Doctors are Bob.
He's gonna save us home,
pills are the best,
and we'll leave a 35 state spot.
These wonderful, wonderful doctors are all bucking the pills.
You won't believe.
Ask your waitress for a codeine injection after the show.
Bucking the pills.
Not responsible for loss of brain cells, loss of psychic abilities,
astral projections, other psychic phenomena, ESP, dream phenomena,
loss of limbs, self-mutilation, suicide, all these things.
Rolling.
Type is rolling.
Beyond our earthly veil of illusion are vast, bodiless powers,
great intentions of dark and light,
locked in a constant, aeon-spanning struggle.
And we are their weapons against one another
in the coming apocalyptic storms of the near future.
It's no cosmic coincidence that the Earth and its solar system
just happen to be lined up in their present configuration
at this particular intergalactic crossroads
and that it just happens to be now.
No, these events were all set in place one day 80 million years ago
in fabled Mutantis.
It was decreed then by the yetis of old
that on Jupiter...
July 5th, 1998 at 7 a.m.,
their true descendants, the chosen ones,
the high unpredictables of the subgenius church
under the last bob,
would be rewarded in that great rupture.
X-Day, when the men from Planet X will come
and we faithful shall be lifted up in power and glory
to the escaped vessels.
Oh.
Of the sex goddesses.
Fleeing while enjoying on TV
the cataclysms on Earth
while being transfigured into over-men and uber-women.
Superior mutants who will lead a new race,
the master race because it comes in all colors,
to the promised land of Dimension X,
the pleasure dimension of eternal slack
and cytor-spanning.
And the best part about it,
We have to get rid of the phantasmagous squirt.
Sounds good, huh?
And believe it or not,
it's not really very expensive.
But it is a little risky.
Most subgeniuses thrive on danger, though.
They get off doing just what the conspiracy
doesn't want them to do.
In fact, it's many subgeniuses' only reason for living.
But rest assured,
the conspiracy sleeps lightly
when the strong awaken.
It is watching us with its vast, cold, impersonal eye.
Subgeniuses don't use all those fake names just to be cute.
They do it to help clog the thought-crime computers.
The dream police and the anti-sex leagues
toil deep into the night trying to analyze
and sort out all our contradictory clues.
They know, they know that somewhere out there,
maybe in the alley next door,
there lies a purebred subgenius who got away.
And as long as the subgenius gene lives,
they are in danger.
For there was a legend.
A legend that someday,
there would come a man with a pipe.
One who could outsell the conspiracy.
That man came,
and he keeps coming.
But he's got some new clients now,
and they'll be arriving soon
to inspect the property.
The stars shall descend upon the earth.
The heavens shall open up and rain fire.
The earth shall rise up and swallow the conspiracy dupes.
Those remaining masters unlucky enough to survive the Holocaust
shall perish at the hands of their slaves.
It will be a bloody day.
A day of vengeance.
A day of purging.
But until that day,
we must feed and gather strength.
We must build and perfect that special vehicle
for exploring the frontiers of Dimension X and outer space.
The brain.
We must purge that brain of all the banal social interactions
that are turning it to sludge.
We must move, hone it, tighten it, update it.
Use it to build guns and flyers.
We must throw him out until GrangstanceArepa.
We must purge him,
and get him into the dark.
We must purge it
until Dimension X theirs is no longer known.
You know what?
See,
the truth is,
we,
partying mothers,
four or five different records and tapes and things from people that had some relation
to the Church of the Subgenius. They were all very friendly to us. You know, they said,
well, if we make any money, we'll give you some. And is this okay? And it is, usually.
Here's one from France. We got a CD in the mail from France from a group called Come
Together Productions. It's actually a collection of about 20 different bands, and they're all
kind of psychedelic sounding bands. It's kind of, it's like an Iron Butterfly Zeppelin airplane
or something. However, one of the groups on there is our old friend John Bartels, and
this is a piece that wasn't on any of his cassette tapes that he sends us. So stay tuned
here for John Bartels singing about
Neil Young.
Ah, yes.
And sometimes when I get bored, I go nuts and I play a second chord. Oh, yeah!
I'm Neil Young and I'm getting kind of old. All I gotta do is play one chord. Just like this. Yeah!
.
John Bartels from, John Bartels of New York off of a French CD covered with pictures of
J.R. Bob Dobbs. Man, it's a small, wide CD.
.
The bitch, the weirdness, the twisted psychosis, the gut-splitting owls and screaming senseless
chuckles.
But you must regain them in full forced impact if you want to survive the scabrous abominations
that slither from your TV set, or slip from your newspaper, or burrow into your belly
to tunnel up your spine and devour your brain.
That is the space they're fighting for, and their goal?
Neutralize the Deviant.
But through Bob, dear friends, through Bob, through Bob, you can transcend mundane existence
and become logic-free.
With these
secrets known only to the ancient yetis until now, Bob Dobbs can explain anything without
logic.
And with practice, so can you.
Select individuals receive private lessons.
But don't worry, anyone can pay for it.
So why wait?
Ask Bob into your life today.
No reasons will be given.
Count on it.
And don't let the sacred babble of Bob be drowned out by the pathetic
peep, peep, peep of pinkness, dear friends.
Join the warrior elite and fight the castrating cosmovogues.
Because it's what you don't see that sells you.
It is a laughing matter.
Be like the man who almost thought for himself.
Because, dear friends, you can't be a warrior without a laughing matter.
I invite you to take the time to take a look at this fish to the biting of the finden,
stunned forgetto, deepening quality hell live Taxi to a
theutes help love hasn't lived for centuries nope
put you on your back, you can become extremely
the 47ãƒ«
Lucy obedient brother
let it ride
you can expect special
pops
usual
tricks
hit your
kind of
Sweeter English into your heart.
But Hal is talking over there more than when I'm talking.
I don't like that.
I need some more over here.
Hey, is that?
Yeah, okay, I see.
Just switch it down.
Oh, it's the both doing it.
Okay, but the one that really gets me is that one that's like an oscilloscope.
If you could be here, folks, I think you would really appreciate the wonders of modern radio communication.
They've got needles, switches, buttons, slide bars.
Like a mad scientist's laboratory.
I don't know.
I'm just going to do this.
Whatever it's doing, I don't know, but it's doing it.
Stop it.
Quit it.
I don't know.
Cut it out.
But they're crying in pain, so this must be the pain button.
Hey, it hurts.
Turn it off.
But I'm supposed to hold these records up here so you can all hear them.
You can hear the covers of these.
These are the records we use on the show.
No, you can't.
The ones you've heard a thousand times, but they're just like new music every additional time.
Well, I wouldn't know about that.
And now I've started something else over here.
A machine just started waking up, and now...
Sid, calm down.
The machines in this studio make the weirdest noises I've never understood.
No other radio show has...
What is the deal over there?
I think that's the calcinator ray.
It's like this radio show.
It runs itself.
I can't even...
You know, as hard as I try...
It's a steaming power sport.
I've got what I think is control, but maybe it's nothing more than just a mere compression control.
Maybe I'm just fooling myself.
If I only could get a collar, I don't even know if I'm recorded.
I may be previously recorded, and they're fooling all of you.
That's probably what it is.
These guys are the kind of guys that will...
They'll record something and act like it's happening now, and really it happened...
three or four years ago.
A month ago.
Maybe last week.
And that's really...
That may be the case here.
You wouldn't know it unless you call.
That's the only way you can prove it to yourself.
You have to have that real-time connection between reality, which is out there, and then in here.
Hello?
Callers?
You know, one reason why...
it's easy for us to stay in Dallas...
is because we have so much hate.
You know, it's good for the artistic aspects of the Church of the Subgenius,
because we have plenty to hate.
This is a city full of normals.
A bunch of...
And what's worse, what's even worse than a normal...
is a token weirdo.
One of these passive weirdos.
Oh, I appreciate all the cool things.
I watch Ren and Stimpy.
I listen to the Hour of Slack.
I'm like, so cool.
I know all the right bands.
I know all the cool books.
I read William Burroughs.
Yes, I've read all his books.
And, uh...
But, uh...
Oh, but I can't.
I mean, I don't have enough money to...
You know, I mean, that station's gonna be on the air anyway.
I don't need to send in my...
any kind of money to help support KNON.
Oh, no, I'll just, uh...
Somebody else will do it.
I'm a real mutant.
I'm like a rebel.
I hate everybody.
Ha ha ha!
All the sins and all the inequities
of mankind throughout history
will be placed on the shoulders of Charlie Manson.
That leaves Charlie a hero!
He is a super guy!
He is above good and evil!
He is the second!
The coming of Christ!
And begged forth by the masses for centuries!
The same, sir!
The little, decrepit souls
wiring aimlessly into an infinite nothing!
Kneel, you leader!
And who's that man?
Who's the one
who has taken the sins
upon his shoulders of all mankind
and has gone beyond
the simple morality structures?
The one who has been
transformed into a new value!
I say again!
Charlie Manson!
You can't live forever!
Is he more willing to die
at this very moment?
Just accept Charlie Manson
into the very deepest essence of your soul!
You'll be redeemed, brother!
Sorry, you fucking city!
I said that you didn't know
what we were talking about and have guerrillas!
That's about right!
The final justice!
easy- etc.
Follow the answers!
There's production between the two!
He's a tie-dye with a heart on.
The revolution is waiting for a spark.
Everybody's ready.
Are you weak little questions?
Don't say it!
Are you little, mmm, little loving
sacramental squishy little questions?
Don't say the true
cry that is needed!
We will
talk about the
smut peddlers
selling their bodies
mindlessly on the streets
for ten dollars
so they can get a dime of crack.
And these pornographers
they have people masturbating
inside their theaters.
And these evil heathens
killing their babies.
These huge markets that sell
to death and destruction.
Abortion was ordained
by God to
wipe out all the children
of godless parents.
And God has
sent down a decree
that these children
will be aborted.
Blood on the ground!
Jesus getting stung!
Just the power
the demons need!
Thousands of cops on the streets!
We want to see
the real voice
that is
intimidating
the high priest!
These gay
God-had-lust
mobbers,
soldiers of Satan,
bodies in the streets!
We want to see
the eyes of
the people
who look
and die!
We told you
this would happen!
But you will have pity on them
instead of hospitals
where they can die!
You know the beauty of a way
to destroy a famous
synagogues building!
That is after
the sun comes back again
and rules us for one thousand years
and many people are judged
and executed!
And be weary
of the
death of the
deceased!
Be weary of your
unsafe neighbor!
For they are wretched,
wretched flock!
They must die!
They must kill!
They must be against us
for years!
For years we have tried to be lined up
guns and executed!
They will say,
good works God!
But that is when they see the destruction
that they will encounter!
They will die a very gruesome death!
All who do not believe must die!
All who do not believe!
How many will die!
Millions will die in the battle against Satan!
Millions speak the truth!
And the truth hurts so bad
it is still the truth!
The temple of death!
The hate!
Storm!
Kill!
Die!
They know who killed them!
The ancestors of the American Indians!
The letter space!
The UFOs!
The spheals!
The human slaves!
They are wrecking rape camps!
But they don't care!
They would rather die than a thousand
screaming,
anarchy for the masses,
a tent revival of body parts,
death,
destruction, mayhem,
and black flags!
We could have made your limbs regrow
and healed your sick and unwanted children!
Endless masses looking for a reason to die
and not finding it!
They have declared war on the people!
Drop your crack pipe,
your bong,
your guns at our feet,
and we will save you from your miserable self!
If you could just call and help us out
to prove that somebody listened to us,
give us a sono,
push đhed s rapporti à la nous-fait!
ÑĞ´'hank oto on,
eccériques des Siènes !
Prï¿½ï¿½humÄs Harmer combina
psīt kés
isodxa
brakes muscilam
That means a politically incorrect statement has been made within the last 24 hours on this station.
Approved by Federal Communications Commission regulations, of course.
What happened to the sound? I had a... Ah, here it is.
Let's all sing I Love Ronald Reagan.
Oh, so this is the mix.
I mean, this is what I sound like?
This is what I sound like?
Oh, my God.
He's the best man president we've got.
Wow.
Oh, I love Ronald Reagan.
Well, the caller's calling in.
Come on in, callers.
Come on, callers.
Caller, you there?
Let's hear you.
Meese. Meese.
Are you there, caller?
Mr. Meese.
Ronald Reagan, walk me down the stairs.
Mr. Meese, time to get up, sir.
Do you hear the caller?
We hand the Meese's to pieces.
Mr. Meese, time to get up, sir.
Are you there, Mr. Caller?
Sounds like he's overdriving the climate change.
Sounds like some kind of a war call.
Sounded like some kind of a show to me.
A horrible sounding show.
Yeah, well, dear friends.
Boy, is this...
This is like way past my bedtime.
Sitting here filling in for lost show makers.
But we'll be able to use these recordings
when we do pledge drives
and yet have to send copies of show out.
That's why I'm being so careful with these recordings.
Because you never know when you might suddenly need
a pre-recorded hour of slack show
thrown together unexpectedly
in the dead of night
by the things of Bob.
Are you fed up with boring radio?
Iron of Turgeon Antidia's Top 40.
Prepare to puke over pretty pop.
Well, it's time to...
Tune in to...
The Soap Genius.
Hour of Slack.
That's what that is.
Oh, kill the airlock.
Yeah, well...
Okay.
Friends, let me tell you something.
First off, number one...
Let's get serious about this, Doctor.
First of all...
Cassette deck two...
Is not working.
And the ports on the starboard side are completely...
That's okay.
We're losing air fast,
and we're gonna have to try to keep up with it.
Well, I'll open up this big blue cylinder of church.
Oh, yes.
Heaven.
Now I feel considerably better.
Oh, yes.
Now, baby, this church air...
Praise Bob.
I feel that church air now.
Do you feel it?
Friends, can you feel it out there in the radio audience?
I bet you can.
Yeah.
Reach out and feel it, friend.
And if you can't reach down and feel it,
then you're gonna...
And then...
You probably don't even...
You probably don't even know what a prairie squid is.
You probably don't even care what one tastes like.
So, dear friends, once again, as we saw it,
we come to the end of this side of the show.
Once again, you'll have to...
Turn your show over.
Turn your radio over, flip it,
so that you can hear the rest of it.
The subgenius radio ministry,
Hour of Slack.
I'm sorry.
The next move is Hall's.
We've got to break this conspiracy of silence and secret orders.
You've got to right this man now.
Now, you listen to me.
I'll only say it once.
We are not sick men.
God.
Who's God?
A lovely little tape edit here from Joe Riley.
Praise St. John.
What you are about to see, you may find hard to believe.
It is a tale of the supernatural, an experience of the occult beyond all imagination.
It is a story of frightening monsters of human origin
who could only be repulsed by monsters more wicked,
like the underworld demons who avenge spilt family blood.
That's right, dear friends.
It's the subgenius radio ministry hour of...
Slack relentlessly pounding on and on into the night.
Chopping and digging our way through the airwaves to reach your ear,
to punch our way past it and get into your brain.
Ah, yes.
It's a shame.
I'm going to get us off on a nice note.
This is...
Saint.
Feresht vape,
by Dee Fredit.
Feresht by VapeHouse.
That's how they say it.
Oh, and if you're any a fuki fan,
God damn, Yumi,
I'm gonna love this.
That was a lovely album the hots irrigation over Ubuntu made me re-edit.
vape.
Vape.
Every step you take, I'll be watching you.
I'll be watching you.
Every single day.
Every word you say.
Every game you play.
Every night you stay.
I'll be watching you.
Oh, can't you see?
You belong to me.
And my poor heart aches.
With every step you take.
Every move you make.
And every vow you break.
Every smile you fake.
Every claim you stake.
I'll be watching you.
Every day you think of me.
Every day you sing me many songs.
Every single week I stop to think of you.
Every day you say that you love me.
Every day you say that you're CrimePopuff.
Oh, can't you see
That you belong to me
And how my poor heart, it aches
Every step you take
Every move you make
Every bow you break
Every smile you fake
Every claim you stake
I'll be watching you
Yeah, that's right, I'll be watching
Follow your ass home
I'll be watching you
Look in the window of your trailer home
I'll be watching your ass, bitch
I'll be watching you
That's right, I'm watching you
I'm gonna stay slick
I wear a bow on oneã¨æ€ Harland
I will say to you
I'm the only one who feels she's dead
But camera is the last thing that I can do
I'm the only one who feels she isn'tså
Thank you.