Listen.
All right, on one.
Going up in five, four, three, two, one.
The Soggy Power of Swag.
We'll meet again at midnight.
And let's have another disclaimer.
The program you are about to hear, Bob's Slack Time Funhouse,
is actually a special edition of the Hour of Slack tonight.
Any reference to Bob, the Church of the Jub Genius.
The Church of the Jenkum Genius.
Religion, politics, or any other touchy subject is intended only as humor
and should cast no reflection on the high standards of WREK Atlanta,
its staff, nor that of Georgia Tech.
Ah.
We're going to have to change it to Church of the Jub Seniors after this.
Yeah, man.
I have two brain cells left.
They're on opposite sides of my head and they're not touching.
You can't have them.
I've only got a half of them.
No, you're not getting one of them.
Why do you think I only have two left?
You've caged all my brain cells.
I did.
It was like a pack of cigarettes.
I wish I knew what happened to them.
I must have smoked them.
Hey, do you need to flip CDs?
Or anything?
Yeah.
Because one CD only lasts 80 minutes, right?
Well, no.
I'm making a huge file and then I'll split it in half.
Oh.
Yeah, I'm doing things on Soundforge.
Huge.
She grabbed her bosom while she said that.
She got excited.
She wants that huge file.
Or what she could grab of it.
It takes more than two hands.
She wants your huge file.
I can kind of grab part of it and shove it around.
See?
She wants your huge file.
Mm-hmm.
It's a huge file.
Oh, there's going to be a huge file.
Oh, man.
I'm about ready to upload.
Yeah, there's a huge file on you somewhere, don't you know, Stank?
Yes.
Oh, I've tried to add to it.
Uh-huh.
Have you applied for your FOIA?
No.
I don't want to know.
No, I actually had to contact the FBI at one point and go,
look, you guys probably have a file, but let me pad it for you.
Here's some other.
Uh, thank you, my love.
Just so you don't get surprised.
A secret service showed up at my house.
Again?
No, no.
Back in the olden days.
In 1981.
Did you know that when I came to the door, they asked me, they asked if I was, I, um,
they didn't know my last name.
This is the secret service.
All they had was my first name and my middle name.
And this is my street human name.
So I was, you know, is this Doug St. Clair?
And I, at that point, that was my cue to say no.
Technically, technically you were right.
They just wanted to see if I was a turban wearing type of cult leader or just a regular joke kind of cult leader.
Or like, you know, wind turban or.
And when I saw the swing set in the backyard and so forth.
You were swingers?
Yeah.
Back then.
Wow.
Nobody would have this now.
Nobody except others.
What was it?
Jubb seniors.
Yeah.
That's easy for me to say.
Church of the gum seniors.
Look, when you, when you get the dentures, I'm not keeping track of the jar.
Adventures in dentures, baby.
My, my granny ran over hers.
That was hilarious.
They were in her mouth at the time.
My dad's, this is not a joke.
My dad's dog ate his dentures.
Now wrap your head around that for just a second.
The dog just sat on my foot.
He bit me.
Ah.
The dog ate my dad's false teeth.
Which was a complete set.
The kind like the three stooges would, you know, run around chattering or something.
You had, you had denture hound.
He's rare.
What a smile that dog had.
Man, he had these weirdest canines.
They were just sort of not pointed the right way.
But hey, it worked.
He thought he ever wanted after that was mashed potatoes.
That, that helps those dogs that are so ugly and shave them and make them walk backwards.
Yeah.
The teeth would help.
That dog died of a rattlesnake bite.
Sad.
He tried not to bite anyone.
Dogs has always been my friend.
Uh huh.
I feel bad about laughing now that your dog is dead.
Well, that was my dad's dog.
Right.
Absolutely.
That is okay.
Actually, you know, um, they could have been a dog.
They come and go and animals don't last forever out on out in the countryside.
They's good eatin' huh?
Yeah, they're well, there's coyote traps everywhere.
You know, it's amazing how varmints have adapted to humanity.
Certain, certain varmints have actually spread that used to only live in certain areas are now spreading into new areas of the country like coyotes and so forth.
Right.
And they are showing up where they never used to be because they fit in quite well with, uh, humanity and their pets.
Mm-hmm.
Because they eat our pets.
That's what most coyotes.
They eat your mammals.
Yeah, they, they, right.
You people who own mammals, that's sick.
Hey, I don't own a mammal.
They have teats, they have fur, they have sweat glands.
Ah!
But I happen to own an amphibian.
Ooh.
How's that?
Miss reptile lady.
Excuse me.
Snake woman.
I, I suddenly have professional courtesy.
Listen, we're going to have a little bit of a discussion.
I have a little bit of respect for you.
You vertebrate lovers.
Oh, uh, uh, we, I was thinking how we, of, um, how my poor newt, Fig, hasn't been fed
his, uh, sea monkeys.
Oh.
Wow.
And we had a sea, there was a sea monkey at, in the audience at our, at the panel.
She was gorgeous.
Did you tell her that you fed her kind to your amphibian?
Oh, yeah, yeah, I did.
I made a real big deal out of it.
Sea monkey, do monkey.
Yeah.
She was, she was pink, but she looked just like the sea monkeys.
In the air.
On the package.
Yeah.
She was, and she was like the teenage daughter sea monkey.
Uh.
She had really nice scales on her chest.
Judy.
Yes.
She was, yeah, she was, she was really.
And a tail.
And she had the three little antennas on top.
Yeah.
And, and when they took, somebody took her picture with me, I held up two, three fingers
behind her head.
Oh.
See.
I'm, I'm a real humorist and jokester.
That's, that's pretty smart.
But yeah, that was one of my favorite, uh, costumes was the, the sea monkey, or, or.
When you, uh.
Uh, no, apologies to Reverend Artemia Salina.
I was gonna ask.
Who's probably not listening.
No.
Mm.
Out of spite.
Not, not if he knows his deal.
Right.
No, no, no.
Cause you're, you're making fun of him.
Uh, no.
No.
I, I, I've, I've genocided his people.
Well.
The sea monkeys.
That's a, that's a version of making fun of people.
Sea monkeys, my left butt.
That's Brian Shrimp.
When the ex-
Genocide has always been considered comedy.
Don't you know that?
When the exes come down and wipe out the human race, they're gonna say, oh, we were just
playing around.
What's up?
I'd be laughing.
I think that's pretty funny.
It's just the way it is.
Not every.
If we're lucky.
Well, you know, most religions in, I think in most religions, people kind of want everybody
else to die.
Yeah.
That's nothing.
I mean, that's kind of what a religion's all about.
Religions are nothing but telling you who to hate.
Basically.
But what's gonna happen to them for, for not having faith?
It's not that we love Bob so much.
It's that we love the idea of everybody else going to hell.
Yeah.
Damn straight.
Damn straight to hell.
The envisioning of, of the, of the various ways to.
The burnings.
Yeah.
The screams and agony.
The nerve endings held in fire.
You mean all I gotta do is pay $30 and that'll help everyone else go to hell?
Right.
Sounds like a bargain.
Yeah.
What a deal.
Wow.
Well, you know, burning.
What were we, what was back on burning?
Can we go back to burning?
And every time you make a deal, Bob gets a deal-do.
That's a new one on me.
That makes him so happy, I'm sure.
I hope he's got some lubricant with that.
I'm surprised I can still sit down.
Yes, yes, yes.
Long ago, I had said.
Goat Seed by Bob.
That every subgenius.
Oh, ouch.
Every single subgenius.
The boat.
No, that pipe is big, man.
Is a part of Bob.
Every subgenius is a body part of Bob.
And I figured out stangs.
Adenoids.
Why does everybody pick on me?
You're the scribe, man, you know?
I think Charlie Brown said that, didn't he?
So, so which part would I be?
Well, it's the part where all the crap comes out.
You don't want to know.
The mouth.
Kind of in a back ways way of looking at it, unless it's a William Burroughs story,
and then it could be the mouth.
Yeah.
You know, we're all pipes in a way, because we're basically donut shaped.
There's a hole at one end and a hole at the other.
And you can actually run a string all the way.
And it's like a crazy straw.
You could run a string all the way through.
Yeah.
And the same.
Matt's crumb effect.
I've been tired of Knight's Monster Tri-Z.
Almost every single.
And I think I saw an S. Clay Wilson drawing where the smoke was actually.
Yeah.
Actually filtered through the whole person there as a filtration device.
Oh, wow.
Wow.
Yeah.
Well, topologically, we are pipe shaped or donut shaped.
Right.
A pipe is just a very weird shaped donut.
You could say.
A torus.
A toroid form.
Yeah.
Maybe we're all Klein bottles.
Uh-uh.
That would explain a lot.
I tell you, it freaks me out to think about that.
When my son was little, he.
I was a Mobius child.
I was a stripper.
The term, the word infinity really bothered my son.
I can see that.
The concept of it irritated him and scared him.
And just hearing the word made him think of it.
He was more into infinity.
Which it hurt his head, you know.
He was sort of precocious.
He also, like me, seems to feel the cold breath of the Grim Reaper breathing down his neck
every second of his life.
I feel that down my pants.
Does it?
It doesn't like to waste time because of that.
Which means, you know, not wasting time could mean you should sit around doing lazy, pointless
things that you sort of like to do because you should.
Some wise man said you should live as if this was your last day or as if you were going
to live forever.
One or the other.
Anything else is a cheat.
From PR News in Washington.
I'm Sarah.
I'm Sarah McGuire.
won't let students see former Attorney General John Ashcroft.
Ashcroft was arrested yesterday for murdering his own family last weekend
at a mobile home park near Brunswick.
Seven of the eight people killed were repugnant.
Space shuttle Discovery astronauts are reporting humans started the space station today.
This is PR.
American lawmakers are now 42% contained.
They're expecting an uptick in unfair PR news in Washington.
Wow.
I feel like I'm in a restaurant somewhere off of Route 29 in North Carolina.
And the guys in the band are wearing sparkly jackets.
Right.
Bright colored handkerchiefs on the pockets.
I'm trying to order a fettuccine Alfredo, but a man with a pipe comes up to me.
Try the veal.
He says, look, Pisces, don't order the Alfredo.
And I say, but Bob, I like Alfredo.
Look, Pisces, don't.
Order the Alfredo.
I said, well, then I don't want to eat here.
He goes, fine.
And I leave.
And the place blows up.
Wow.
See, there's a moral to the story.
Do what Bob says.
Exactly.
I'm Alfredo to dark.
The band Devo did what Bob said.
Bob said, Devo, Warner Brothers isn't any good.
You need to end your contract with Warner Brothers and go with some little label.
And then do music that's going to appeal to the mainstream.
And they did.
And that was the end of Devo for about 10, 15 years.
Now they're back doing all their old stuff.
Having a good time?
Oh, yeah.
Having a great time.
So as far as I know, I've actually seen most of the Devo's fairly recently.
They're, you know, I think Jerry's 61.
Yeah.
Now, but he's just as filthy minded as ever.
Oh, that's a relief.
Yeah.
He's he has his own band called Jihad Jerry.
Have you ever heard any Jihad Jerry?
Oh, it's great.
He's a he wears a turban and it looks like a jihadist, basically.
But it's kind of a cocktail lounge turban terrorist outfit, you might say.
Wow.
Nairobi trio.
Space age.
Bachelor terrorists.
By way of Somalia.
Right.
Snapping and...
Yeah.
You can...
Or devotees, if you didn't know about Jihad Jerry, just Google or Goggle or whatever that
is, Twitter it or tweet it or whatever you kids do nowadays.
Not necessarily beautiful, but mutated.
It's come out what?
Number eight?
Yes.
Volume eight.
Now?
Yes.
I have not mentioned that yet on my show.
And St. Byron Werner, who's spinning the discs here.
He was a part of the show.
I'm a potato.
Yeah.
The rural war room cover of...
I'm a potato.
It has to be heard to be believed.
Then you will be heard on our Slack number 1,221.
It's fantastic.
Yeah, that's it.
I also like Devo Dan's version of hey homo.
That's wonderful.
This sounds like the launching sequence for the...
The launching sequence.
The lady who turned me on to hey homo, I have a recording of her doing a gorgeous gospel
Bob song.
She's also in the Mutant Mountain Boys, which is a bluegrass group out of Appalachia that
covers Devo.
So that'll be coming up on our Slack.
That was a little subgenius gospel tune.
And we've got one more for you tonight.
I know you're sick of us already.
And we need you all to tell us what you think.
So we're going to play a little bit of the song.
So if you get to know the tune to this, sing it along with us.
Help us praise Bob.
Thank you.
May your records be unbroken by and by, by and by.
I'm a potato.
There's a vine of heaven waitin' in the sky Bob, in the sky.
Well I've played the beast that beat me.
One bright and sunny day
When I've been listening too fast
I put on some Q&A
My turntable started jumping
What it did I know not how
Won't live by the looks of how I cried
When it scratched my duty now
Sing it with me
May your records be unbroken
By and by, by and by
There's a vinyl
Every way they turn in the sky
By and by, by and by
There's a vinyl
Every way they turn in the sky
But I bought a second copy
Listened through red-eye express
When my girlfriend
She came on to me
Started taking on her dress
So when I could've, could've
I should call me
My turntable started jumping
With a sweeping, silky voice
I just told her
You gotta wait now
Girl, I'm listening to the freedom of choice
May your records be unbroken
By and by, by and by
There's a vinyl
Every way they turn in the sky
By and by, by and by
But I know I've been a sinner
In my life, that evil twist
Gotta say I ain't no Christian child
Cause I'm a new traditionalist
But I know I'm a new traditionalist
And I hear that truth evolving
Oh no, I never stop
But my heart is never glad of it
When I shout that name above
May your records be unbroken
By and by, by and by
Oh no, I never stop
There's a vinyl
Every way they turn in the sky
By and by, by and by
There's a vinyl
Now I know I
Ain't no youngin'
One day I gonna be old
I got that
Turntable
And I got that devil feelin'
And now it can't be told
But I got my high five
I got my jukebox
I got my album and my ladder
Should I ever lose my way
Now I'm a sinner in my life
Like I spoke no lie
May your records be unbroken
By and by, by and by
There's a vinyl
Heaven waves it in the sky
Oh I'll bear the sky one more time
May your records be unbroken
By and by, by and by
There's a vinyl
Heaven waves it in the sky
In the sky
By and by, by and by
Baby there's a diamond sketch
Oh-oh, oh-oh, one day I gotta get old
This game is in the way
of your life
Mind is all about knowing
group out of Detroit that covers
Negative Land
called the 180Gs
and listeners
who are familiar with Negative Land
will be
how shall I put this, excremeditating
their britches when they hear
this stuff.
It's kind of rare because the only way to get
it is you have to buy Negative Land's new
DVD
My Favorite Things
or some of our favorite things
which is absolutely
mind-raping
DVD.
Does it tie you down first?
Huh? Does it tie you down first?
It doesn't have to.
Only if you ask it not to.
Your brain bends over and takes it.
Recording.
Everything's going fine.
No trouble.
Just get set and get going.
Amen.
Recording.
Everything's going fine.
No trouble.
Just get set and get going.
Amen.
Recording.
Everything's going fine.
No trouble.
Just get set and get going.
Amen.
Recording.
Everything's going fine.
No trouble.
Just get set and get going.
Amen.
Recording.
Everything's going fine.
No trouble.
get set, get going.
Amen.
Recording.
Everything's going fine.
No trouble.
Get set, get going.
Amen.
Recording.
Everything's going fine.
No trouble.
Get set, get going.
Amen.
Recording.
Everything's going fine.
No trouble.
No trouble, no trouble, no trouble
Get set, get going, do it
Do it, do it, do it, do it, do it
Everything's going fine
No trouble, do it
Get set, get going, do it
I wanna see you one day
Everything's going fine
No trouble
Just get set and get going
Do it, do it, do it, do it
To the S, to the E
To the X, to the D
To the I, to the R, to the T
To the Y, to the Z
To the 180 G
Coming at y'all from the studio
In full live stereo
Some songs are old
Some of them be new to y'all
Ain't no trouble
Making new music out of mass media rubble
Everything's going fine
Hanging round the microphone
With a bottle of cold duck wine
We got fruit and crackers
And three kinds of cheese
Please allow me to introduce to you
The 180 G
To the S, to the E
Everything's going fine
We know y'all gonna listen
And try to understand
We're taking a positive journey
Through a negative land
Duh, duh, duh, duh
Calling the number is 180
Everything's going fine
And the letter is G
No trouble, no trouble
Get going up, up, up
Calling the number is 180
Everything's going fine
And the letter is G
No trouble, no trouble
Get going up, up, up
You know, I'm going to have to call my ride in about 10 minutes or so, I think.
Oh, that's what they call it now.
Yeah, that's what the cast...
I got to pick that up from my kids.
Who's the one being ridden?
Are you the rider or are you the driver?
I'm always the catcher.
Or the flak catcher.
I thought the job was slack catcher, but it turned out to be flak catcher.
Is it more like crack snacker?
Don't they wear lobsters on their legs?
I noticed here at the WREK studio,
there was kind of a mailbox set up with different shows.
With Dymo labels.
Yeah, the one for my show seemed to say the hour of lack.
Yes, I like that.
There was some problem.
They had problems with their S.
I like that.
I have problems with my S's sometimes.
Yeah, mine gives me no end of grief.
No end.
Yeah.
What a wise S.
What a wise S you are.
Yeah, she is pretty wise.
Yeah, I was cracking up.
Yeah, they offered to make me another label when I said the hour of lack.
They're like, no, I love it.
It says everything I think about your show stinks.
Thanks so much, Susie.
Yes.
Can you feel the love in this room?
It's sort of thick and heavy and smothering.
Oh, I can feel the love all right.
It smells like a mean spirit.
It's not dead.
Which also smells like a fish.
It smells like fish.
Mm-hmm.
What doesn't?
Give it enough time.
Everything smells like fish.
After three days, right?
Yeah.
Okay, that's what I thought.
I think Ben Franklin said that.
Mm-hmm.
In a way, maybe.
Something about dead bodies, fish.
Yeah.
Ben Franklin also said lighthouses are more useful than churches.
Good old Ben.
Yeah.
The only president who was never president.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I heard a woman homeschooling her kids when I worked in the library, and she was saying
something about Ben Franklin and I'm shelving books, and I almost fell out, she said.
She was telling him about things he discovered, and then she held up the book, and she said,
children, here's a picture of President Franklin.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I heard a lady at our library said, Ben Franklin, you're the only president in the world.
I heard a lady showing kids this statue out in the garden of Icarus, and she's saying,
well, this happened a long time ago, and no one was sure if it happened or not, but there
were a lot of eyewitnesses.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Yeah.
Arkansas.
Ladies and gentlemen, and this is why everything is screwed up.
Diva was right about everything.
About everything.
About her.
Gosh, that's a great song.
Yeah.
She's...
Pisces is referring to a song by a British group called The Attery Squash, and Reverend
Diva Schematic is the lead singer in that.
She is incredible.
She's incredible.
I love her.
around Nobody recognises substance in its sound
Remember?
We danced in groups, that was the fashion of the time
To songs we moved every night We built our lives on fire, that neon dream
pop And now, and then, it was our time
Now every generation needs its own identity So they just borrow one from two decades back
Then they get bored with it and pass a glowstick to a younger band
Who haven't yet become all jaded and pratt
Now we don't mind our future listeners of the song
You don't remember who we are or where we're from
And that's okay, cause when they reassure us
You've been stressed We can't pretend that we were here
Way back in the day
We danced in groups, that was the fashion of the time
To songs we moved every night We built our lives on fire, that neon dream
pop And now, and then, it was our time
We danced in groups, that was the fashion of the time
To songs we moved every night We built our lives on fire, that neon dream
Part of me I'm a dream pop
And now, and then, it was our time
Now life's too short to wait
For the enemy to tell you
What guilty pleasures are
And what's too cool for school
Though lucky us, this song
Coincides with some revival
Don't wait for anyone to tell you
What to like
Oh wow, a black and white
That shows we've got the common touch
Kids make themselves unhappy
Just to fit in
And if you need this song to realize
That quite simplistic point
Don't worry, here comes another big old
Sing along
We dance in groups
As was the fashion of the time
To songs we move every night
We built our lives
Off of our own me on dream pop
And now, and then, it was our time
We dance in groups
As was the fashion of the time
She is incredible.
You know, I don't know what she looks like
I do.
I have a Facebook recognition problem
Right.
Isn't there another song?
I think Caldivo was right on
Not Necessarily Beautiful But Mutated
Number 7
With some guy doing it
I don't know
I thought you might have gotten that one
You're thinking Byron was wrong about everything
Yes
That wasn't on volume 7 though
Who did that? Pivo?
Or is it Wevo?
Pivo, I think
Oh man
Man, non-stop Pivo
The new Pivo record is out of sight
I just gotta say
Well, you're one of those Japanophiles, right?
I like some of the stuff from Japan
The stuff that's really lively and Devo-inspired
Like Poly6 or P-Model
Or groups like that
Pivo
I wish I wasn't completely and utterly deaf
What?
I could still hear music
I can read your lips
Quit making that joke
But you can't read
You know, everybody says that
Well then try it like this, Stang
There are some lips you cannot read
I can make fun of you because I'm almost deaf too
It's the price we pay, friends
So you should donate the next pledge drive to this station
Whichever station you happen to be hearing this on
We don't need pledge drives, we're rich
And, uh, really?
Yeah, WREK doesn't do pledge drives
We're rolling in money, what do you think you're sitting on?
That's bales of money, Stang
Oh, what?
Wow
Yeah, look at this
Look at this place, it's so posh
The station I leech off of is at a state university
Well, this is a state university, isn't it?
No, it's Georgia Tech, that means they're God
Oh, so it's Rich Kid College, right?
Yeah
Yeah, see, ours is for the poor farm kids
And look, we're not fighting over microphones
We've got extra microphones here
And you've got turntables
That's where Bob is sitting on mic number two
Because these microphones
Bob is full of number two
And they don't interfere with my boobs
Yeah
That's true, they're not causing feedback
No feedback
Pisces is, uh, built like a house
A ceramic defecatorium
Yeah, and, um, and we, at Ex Day with our Tarzan's radio station
We discovered that you were kind of a feedback machine
Right
In certain positions
Wow, just like Sherman and Mr. Peabody
We should have set you up in front of a theremin
You get a kind of a liquidy sound
I've played the theremin with my boobs before
Yeah
I did not know my boobs had any musical talent
Right
One for volume, one for pitch
Right, yeah
See, I can even try
Yes, well, but see, we're not, we don't have speakers
There's no, there's no big speakers
That's what that, so you can't
I was hoping we were getting feedback
Maybe we don't have enough ums
Ums?
Ums
Listen, I wish you listeners could see what I'm seeing
This doesn't have a camera in it, does it?
No, every, everywhere has cameras
It's a good thing no one has a camera in this studio right now
The camera's probably under there
Yeah
We're in a public building, and they've got cameras
Oh, okay, so
No, I meant, you know, like the streaming kind
Some, some, uh
Oh, it's streaming somewhere
Somewhere
Some unparanoid stations have
That's not a sprinkler nozzle
Have a little, have a little camera so that
He's just glad to see you
The internet listeners can watch a person sitting there
Pushing a button every now and then
That's a camera, and it also releases a sleeping gas
Oh
They're very thorough here, I mean, they study a lot of things
That's pretty professional, yeah, I guess
Yeah
Quest for Knowledge covers up a lot
I saw that, it had Ron Perlman in it, right?
What?
Oh, Quest for Knowledge, yeah
Yeah, he played the caveman
Yeah, yeah, and, uh
I played the caveman
And my, my daughter was in it
Tommy Chong's little, little girl's in that
She teaches Amadou, well, dance
Down here, they called it the Quest for Far
Right, a dance
Yeah, she teaches Amadou dance face-to-face
Yeah
Rather than a kind of a rumba or something, I guess that was
Far
You know, there's a town in North Carolina, and it's spelled K-I-N-G, but it's called
K-I-N-G
There's a place called Fuquay Varina
Yes
North Carolina
And as, and as you can imagine, I want you to, listeners, say that
Fuquay Varina
I had to drive there in the middle of the night
And all I wanted to ask the guy, where did this place get a name like that?
Here's what you should all do
There's a town in Ohio by the name of Chardon, C-H-A-R-D-O-N
Where the kids are always knocking off the C's on the street
Fuquay Varina, North Carolina
That's a suburb of Cleveland
I call it Chardon
Sure, sure
Chardonnay
There's also a street called Ivanhoe
Which I like
They got that right
It intersects with St. Clair
That's one of the most deadly
Neighborhoods on the planet
I promise you
I go to work once a week
I do the ghost tour up at
Marietta Square
And I have to report to work on the corner
Of Dobbs and Church
Streets
Wow, that's pretty good
Show us a JPEG
It's right by
It's about just a few feet
From JonBenet Ramsey
Show us your JPEGs
Show us your GIFs
Oh, that's a thing nowadays
Never look a GIF horse in the mouth
Or up the other
And are we gonna go see
JonBenet while you're in town?
You know she asks about you all the time
She remembers how you
Desecrated her grave when it was fresh
The last time you were in town
In 1997
Do you remember that little trip?
Yes, I remember
I've still got the letters
You blamed Jesus for it
You robbed a murdered little girl's grave
Yeah, we did
And not only that, but we read the letters
Over the air
She stole the letters over the air
And the letters that were left there
They were just amazing psychological
Windows on really hideous lives
Okay
Okay, quick
Live with me if you wanna come
I know why you're here
Oh yes, I understand
The needs which drive you
The desire, the lust
That libidinous twist
Inside you
Because you want to get a little slack
I'm right, aren't I?
I'm crazy, but I'm right
Oh yes
Oh
Oh yes, I can smell your need
On you
Through my bob-given third nostril
Oh, that third nostril
That he's gonna open up for you
And I can whip-read
The psychic stench
Of a mere handful
Of precious, unsaved subgenius souls
Out there
I know you're out there
And you know, I know
That you wanna give it up
For Bob
Yeah
Oh, that is always good
Because, seekers, this is
A feel-good religion
And the Church of the Subgenius
Says not only that
We're a feel-good and after-you-go-good religion
You get your rocks off
You walk away and leave the mess
Yes!
In a nutshell
That's the promise of X-Day
Because we want to leave this stinking, smoking, charred world behind us
Oh, we shall commune with the sex goddesses of Planet X
Thanks to Bob
Oh, sure, it hasn't happened yet
Oh, but we are going to get our slack
By any means necessary
We take our slack where we can get it
We can abuse an inch of slack
Into a parsec
Absolutely
Oh, but also within this hideous, compelling course
Is concealed the face of death
Death is ever lurking
A clear and present enemy
Sucking at your heels
But even worse is a conspiracy
About the death of a subgenius soul
Because you might look
Like you're alive
Oh, but you're smothered in false slack
It might feel like the real thing
If you drink enough of this beer
Or if you wear these shoes
Or if you drive this car
You are going to be just as happy
As the idiots you see in the commercials
That's not possible
Because friends, that is a base illusion
You might think you're surfing the lux lane with Bob
When in reality you can't see it
But baby, you're tailgating the honey wagon
Dance Trace
And you don't even smell the shit looming
In your immediate future
You've been brainwashed to ignore the shit
You're swimming through now
How can you accept the existence of more shit
If you're blind to that?
Oh, because you're suffocated
Under layers of expectations
And responsibilities
And vapid media
Entertainment
And all of the snores you can't even see
The conspiracy's rigid template
Is constantly pressing down on you
And you have to cut off parts of yourself
Just to fit in
Well
As much as I hate to quote Dr. Phil
How's that been working for you so far?
Sounds like you need a little bit of a change
Because you know, Seekers
If you're not happy
That's not your fault
In your helpless pursuit of happiness
The conspiracy of the normals ensures
That your miserable existence
Is more of a curse than a joy
When you know that you are the superior species
Aren't you?
Dance Trace
Oh yes
Because
Uh
You've been called so many names
You who have been called weirdo
Geek
Mutant
Oddball
Psycho
Throwback
Dildo
Dipshit
Doofus
Have been spectacle-y
Don't slab a wimpy
You are boss me
Listen to my horse croak
Oh you're gonna be doing that little girl voice stang
Hi dear friends I'm my friend Susie the Flussy
And yeah I'll have to put some cheaters in there
And give you a nice stuffed balcony
Some cutlets
Yep
We'll get real chicken cutlets
That'll work
Well our nice devival will be the most merciful devival
Because we're limited to only 40 minutes
We're in between two giant Tesla coils
You're right
And they have to cool down
Yeah we will be performing between gigantic
Testicle coils
Yeah
Teslacles
Is the jargon term
Oh okay
Yeah
They play music with them
It's that that Nicholas Tellsa
Yeah
Have you said
He's from Venus
He's on the Czechoslovakian money
Nikola Tesla is
And uh
No I think he's on the nickel
No we were shown the bill and it also had Bob
What
Well it could have been a printing error somewhere after it left the treasury
Well there's a
Czechoslovakia
Maybe they launched a nickel on the Telstar satellite
You know the communications
Marijuana is the fuse
But LSD is the Bob
I would take a bunch of Bobs
And blow up
All the planets
Man yes the most evil of the super villains is only six years old
Wait until he's ten
My God
He'll take on whole galaxies
Maybe he'll blow up the planet Bob that we heard about in Titan Asia
Oh God yeah
Fortunately he was too short to hit the destruct button
On the thing you must be at least this tall to destroy the earth so
Yeah they actually had an earth destruction machine in that super villain
That's kind of a risky place to bring a machine like that
That sounds like a Warner Brothers thing that Marvin the Martian would have
It had a big shiny candy like button
Candy red button
And when you pushed it smoke started coming out of it
Yeah and weird lights and bad noises
It was a good history eraser machine
And smells but I think that might have been from the audience
Oh you mean it wasn't just like wire grown
I think they pooped themselves in fear because that thing looked lethal
Yeah yeah
Well we've fallen in with the scientists now
We're no longer relegated to the comics track
They never know what to do with the church
We defy categorization
Scientists are weirder than hippies
Yeah oh man we're in with the freaks now
Well we could sort of be in the skeptic track except that we're religious for now
I don't believe in that stuff
Skeptics are going to have to prove it to me before I believe their point of view
I think we'll be in the filking track next year
Oh God
I want to be in the mime track
You're a Dallas street mime weren't you?
Yes I was
Well not exactly but I was in the mime track
I was a person who delivered balloons to sick people
You were a Dallas street mime don't try to candy coat
And then one day the car broke down
Yes that's right
And you had to go into some place and make a phone call
And it turned out to be a rough sort of leather biker bar
Where they were only too happy to see you and greeted you in a royal style
That well was more like Catherine the Great
Actually it was the Salvation Army
Oh
And I had to walk into the downtown Dallas Salvation Army
With white face on and a tuxedo
And all these homeless dudes sitting around going
And I had to get
I had the balloons for me
The balloons for me
The lightest man they've ever seen
I had the balloons for me
You didn't forget my birthday after all
No he's going away
God them was lean years
You know I'm still
To the left or to the right?
I'm still
Lanyards I think it's pronounced
You can hang yourself with it either way
Ha ha ha
And I thought my jokes were bad
What?
It's five times a day now
Jokes?
Yeah
Do you know some jokes?
I got to say that to one guy dressed as the Joker
It's a Joker line
It's the first line Joker says in the Batman movie I think
What?
And I thought my jokes were bad
Oh
When he walks in on some gangsters just before he
You said that kind of like
Just before he does the magic trick where he makes them go
And he makes the pencil disappear
You said that as if Charles Nelson Riley and Paul Lynde had a baby
Ha ha ha ha
Ha ha ha
I think they did
Which one's going to carry it though?
You know I saw
They'll fight over it
I saw people dressed as the Watchmen in all sizes
There were silk specters that were tiny and skinny
And they were great big large silk specters
Ha ha ha
They're just
All of the Rorschachs were little guys though
That was good
I saw a 350 pound middle aged Batman
Who had a 250 pound middle aged Robin with him
Right
They were walking on the street and it was just
It was the spectacle
That's beautiful
That was
That's so beautiful
Normals are cruising by to take this in
And I have no idea what they think of some of this
Are you sure that wasn't actually Adam Webb?
Adam West
Trust me
But he had the nipples
Like on the gay Batman movie
But they were on big man boobs
Adam West he used to go by the name Bill Anderson
When he advertised for the Piggly Wiggly markets in Hawaii
Ha ha ha
Adam West was once
Bill Anderson
Once given a professional massage by Sister Decadence
With Happy Ending?
He asked
He asked about that
And she doesn't actually do that
Everyone asks about that
Yeah she
But
Except for Charles Nelson Riley
She was
She was honored
But she had to pull out
He was a gentleman about it
He was
He wondered
Do the Batusi
He was pretty suave about the way he asked
What else he could get besides just the regular massage
I don't doubt that
I read Burt Ward's tell all book
Boy Wonder My Life in Tights
Oh my God
It was nothing but a huge sex romp with him and Adam West
He wears the tights when he's not working
They were up to their eyeballs in trim
Constantly exploiting it
Well there were TV stars
I mean
Boy those are tall women
Just saying
Ha ha ha
I saw a perfect Julie Newmar Catwoman today
I mean she
Was she being a bitch?
Well I've heard that that goes with the territory
But
She looked right
That was unfortunate
She did look right
To find that out
Julie Newmar moved to Dallas for some reason I think
I saw her from a distance hobbling around somewhere
That upper lip was so full of collagen now it's gonna cut off all of the edges of the nose
I'm just saying
Just saying?
Yeah
You don't have to hold back
We got a history I don't want to bring it up
Okay fair enough
Fair enough
Mm-hmm
My fellow citizens
I stand here today
Yet
For us
The time has come
To seek the pleasures of riches and fame
In places like Concord
For us
Because we have chosen conflict and discord
Petty grievances and false promises
And worn out dogmas
Now
Every so often
A watchful eye
Can spin out of control
And so
Recall that earlier generations who seek to advance their aims by inducing terror and slaughtering innocents
We are a nation of Jews
Who seek to sow conflict
These things
Are true
Thank you
God bless you
And God bless the United States of America
Thank you
You know it's only about what ten minutes before we press the big button
Five minutes
If that
Seven
Six
Oh wait maybe five
What the heck
These are so
You guys have some sort of read out here in the station
I see
One, two, three, four
We've got six minutes
Shau pha san twai waj mahal ya
Don't say that
It'll open up the dimension
And the elder ones
Will cross over
Dammit
You didn't say that out loud
Did you
It's all those technical things.
Whatever you kids do now, don't knock on that trap door there and say,
Y'all saw Toph three times.
Would you stop?
Okay, Mom, we won't.
Really? Really?
I can now have on my tentacle sex outfit.
Eh, what?
That brought a halt to everything.
Tentacle sex outfit or something.
Molioka. Molioka.
When I have tentacle sex, I take my outfit off because that slime gets all over everything.
That's why I said I have to have on the right outfit to start.
And then it does turn into pulpo.
It always does.
It's always about pulpo.
Polka?
Pulpo.
That's Californian for octopus.
That sounds a lot like pup torb.
Is there pulpo in pup torb?
Is there pup torb in pulpo?
You got your pup torb in my pulpo.
You got your...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's slimy.
This tastes awful.
It smells like dead fish.
We've seen it all.
Maybe we'll get high.
It's not a fish.
It's an invertebrate.
Boy, that sounds really intolerant of them.
I said they smell like fish.
It's a mollusk.
No.
I dig my own grave.
It's a cephalopod or whatever.
Yes, a cephalopod.
Encephalitis pod.
It's an encephalopod.
But then it's a...
Yeah, it's both.
But you know...
It's a mollusk and it's a cephalopod.
It's too late for me to be up.
If you get in a really, really, really bad pickle for some squid...
A really, really bad pickle.
I've had a few of those.
Cuddlefish will do.
No, no, no.
If you get in a bad pickle for some squid sex,
an octopus will do.
Right, yeah.
Sure.
If you can't find a prairie squid and you can't...
Or you found a prairie squid and you're stupid
and didn't get your debeaking tool when you picked it up,
an octopus will do.
Dummy.
That was advice.
Well, now, I thought I was coupling with a prairie squid
in the 1996...
Oh, that was a real...
No, no, that was a Mississippi Delta squid.
I found out later I'd been raped.
Well, well...
That was like I didn't know I'd been raped
until the check bounced.
It was a lot like that.
Hey, be glad it wasn't an Amazonian tree...
Well, arboreal squid.
Candiru squid.
Yeah, they're really bad.
Someone told me that the cuddle bones,
the little parakeets,
like so much, actually comes from the cuddle fish.
Yes, yes, they do.
That you don't want to cuddle with either of them.
But if you want to know how to get squid,
there's only one address you need to know to write to
for free information
about where to get these fabulous, squishy sex partners.
And got that squid ink ready, friends?
Yes.
That's right to Bob.
That's right, Bob.
That post office box.
1-8-1-4-1-7
Cleveland Heights, Ohio
44-1-1-8
Wow, I'm impressed.
I have trouble doing that sometimes.
I do it so much, it's imprinted.
And every time you change that P.O. box,
I'm going to rip out more chunks of my brain.
But if you're not handwriting friendly,
you can always visit the website.
Yes, that's right.
Which is?
Subgenius.com and Subgenius doesn't have an O in it.
But dot does and com does.
But you don't have to write out the dot part.
Yes.
I just thought I'd confuse him real good there.
For a while, we owned the domain subgenius.com
because it would forward,
bump them on over to the correct one
because so many people,
they didn't want to leave the O out and look ignorant.
Well, I...
They're not geniuses.
By definition.
Well, yeah.
We know that.
Everyone down to amoeba.
Well, this has been a wonderful show.
It hasn't been Bob's Slack Time Funhouse.
It hasn't been the hour of slack.
Yeah.
It's been both, yet neither.
It's been no slack at all.
It's been neither fish nor fowl,
but it smells.
It smells like fish,
and it's been very foul.
And the rash.
I'd like to thank Reverend Ivan Stang
for being our special guest tonight.
St. Byron Werner for mixing the sounds.
Priestess Pisces for providing what she does the best.
And yes, even Fat Joe himself showed up to help out tonight.
Who are you?
I'm Reverend Susie the Floozy
of the Church of the Seaside.
Subgenius and of WREK Atlanta.
Good night, Seekers.
Wee, wee, wee, wee, wee, wee, wee, wee, wee, wee, wee, wee, wee, wee.
Oh.
And that, kiddies, is our fairy story for tonight.