At the moment, I'm thinking about my reputation.
You're going to marry me, Bob.
Listen, I've told you how it's going to be, and you might as well get used to the idea.
Because if I have to, I'll smear you, Bob.
I'll ruin you for the hour of slack.
From PR News in Washington, I'm suffering two years of declines.
President Obama is appealing for an anti-Islam video,
but said the video justifies an attack or any other violence.
President Obama said he understands why crude and disgusting people took offense.
At a time when anyone with a cell phone is obsolete.
PR News.
The latest snapshot shows an increase in major percent.
A 16.6% increase in 5.4%.
Analysts say they order a suspected drunk driver
to call for the return of unionized NFTs.
For PR News, the political one.
Official North Korean media also said that teachers would be given PR News in Seoul.
UN Secretary General Ban Ki-moon is again sounding the alarm about PR News,
saying the international community cannot afford PR's reports.
He says PR News is spiraling out of control.
Ban said Russia and China have blocked PR News.
He says this is PR.
Tattoo.
Variety.
Nikto.
Tattoo.
Variety.
Nikto.
Tattoo.
Variety.
Nikto.
Tattoo.
Quiet numbskulls, I'm broadcasting.
Lay your hands on the radio.
Lay your hands on the radio band at home,
and we're gonna look to God.
I'll take that as two.
Here we go.
Everybody get in line.
Everybody from the new freak nation.
Open up your tired eyes.
Oh, get up now from your hibernation.
Our research shows a shocking rise in evil bullshit.
And how they bullshit, it's sick.
You'd be surprised to know just how deep it's got.
Or maybe not.
So everybody, now's the time.
Snag a weapon and fight a lot.
Right.
Behind me
The freaky time is coming soon
Our non-believers leave the room
Listen, won't be said again
This is your life to defend
We won't stand and leave by
As it devolves into madness
Resolves in a sad mess
A broken pipe dream of the day
When freaks take control
Oh yes, that's the goal
Now who's still with me?
Hurry up this little time
I'm burning up with anticipation
You've heard enough of leaders' lies
Lies
You've learned enough to know the true frustration
Burning in the hearts of every woman, man and child
A fire wild style
Sad truth is most folks are trained to just ignore it
And that's why I'm here
To get some shit
To turn the other cheek is fine
If you don't care, but if you do
We're counting on you
We'll raise your hand and take a vibe
Afraid your species needs you now
You came in thinking life was play
But hey man, that was yesterday
Look around and you'll see
This is just the beginning
And if your head's spinning
Take that as your cue
Up the band, they'll be first to arrive!
And if they don't survive
We'll call upon you!
And the few who understand what's right
And the few who hunger for some confrontation
Will get to undertake the fight
Get set to usher in the new freak nation
No one knows why
All the freaky kids are in the dark
That's out of screaming
Or that they're dreaming, scheming
Once it flows, this river ain't never gonna stop!
Even if we drown
For you, step one is just sit tight
And imagine all the things you'd change in this world
And some of you are gonna die
Some of you are gonna fail
Others will end up in jail
Danger lurks, so please take care
Try not to get killed out there
Most will say that we're mad
And implore us to give in
But the way that we're living
Just makes my hair curl up your fist
And focus your power
For you soon know the hour
Will take back the world!
Everybody get in line
Everybody from the new freak nation
Everybody now's the time
Snag a weapon and file out right behind me
Thank you freaks, that's for all you freaky people.
A Letter to Bob
By Reverend Baby Bear
Dear Bob Dong
I'm writing to you
Things have been so hard
What should I do?
This slacklessness is getting to me
I am a slave
I long to be free
He wrote me back
To my surprise
And here's what he said
To open my eyes
He said put it in your pipe
Put it in your pipe
And smoke it
I wrote him back
What do you mean?
If you're telling the truth
There's no proof I've seen
Your advice doesn't help
With my job or my bills
Or those pink boys and girls
Who make me feel ill
He wrote back again
With the same canned reply
The same paper and pen
And the same pen
And the same damned advice
Put it in your pipe
Put it in your pipe and smoke it
I was so pissed
At this salesman's dimwit
And his thousand yard stare
And his shit eating grin
I wrote Bob you're no help
You're as dumb as they come
Never mind the advice
I'll just face it alone
I don't find a better job
Some way to pay these bills
And I don't have a job
And I'll freak out the pinks
I'll give them the chills
Then Bob appeared to me
But I still didn't give a shit
He smiled and said
My dear you've got it
Just put it in your pipe
Put it in your pipe and smoke it
So that's how I learned
This lesson in life
No one needs anyone
To smoke their own pipe
The
End
And I was just picking the wedding music
This is the same one we used
At Nicky and Bob's ex-day wedding
Very good
You DJ'd
Actually Dr. Howell
Shall I do it again
Would you like me to do it another time
No you can do that this time too
Very well I shall
Because you know the material
The Abominable Snowman
Beast from 20,000 Fathoms
Bride of Frankenstein
The classic
Oh and what's the other one
Also I was going to play that song
From A Funny Thing Happened
On the Way to the Forum
Isn't there a show on
Bring me my bride
Do you have it
Yes
My bride my bride
I've come to claim my bride
My lust for her no longer
Can be denied
Yeah there's actually
You have that one that's Here's to Your Illusions
From Fla Huli
Fla Huli
I don't care about no Fla Huli
There's no Fla Huli fans out here
Me no savvy Fla Huli talk
No speaking of Fla Huli old man
Stangor from Fla Huli
Stangor eats Fla Huli
You're like from the planet Fla Huli
Like the planet Koloth
You know I have to keep up with these things
These theological developments
Yes Dr. Howell
We made it
We must keep up
We're still at the 50 next day drill friends
Actually the 17th such drill
If you want to get technical
That was Dr. Howell with G. Gordon Gordon
Dr. Philo Drummond and yours truly
Reverend Stang and we have
Several of the bands from our little
Summer camp out coming up
The Slot Rods
The Evolution Control Committee
Amoeba
Amoeba Knievel
Heard in the background
And now to get us started the musical styling
Of Andrew the Impaled
They deserve it
On this special day
This special day
Approaching the nuptial hour
Yeah I just queued up
Bring Me My Bride
Although I'm not going to play it
Right this second
Why are you telling us about it if you're not going to play it
I'm just talking to myself
Well don't talk to yourself
Stang
Go out and have a smoke
Of what?
I quit smoking in 1997
You say
On November 17th
The old Stang the irritable Stang
You gave him a cigarette
And he just calmed right down
100 million seconds ago
The confessions of Ivan Stang
Since I had my last cigarette
This man when he quit smoking
Had such a terrible addiction
That he had to use nicotine patches
And there were days in his early
Period of quitting where he looked like the mummy
Because he had so many
Nicotine patches all over his body
And I was smoking
I was secretly smoking too
Man that is a buzz
Like five of those big patches
Five
And a pack of Marlboros
And smoking at the same time
Yeah that will keep you awake
Well it was work related
Reverend Stang you've always been a drug abuser
You're just an abusive personality Stang
You do these things to yourself
Look what about the time
We had to wean you off all those white powders
I mean you know come on
What about that time you ate nine aspirins
And drank a coke real fast
I needed those white powders
My crotch was sweaty
Yeah but you could leave them lying around
I would think they were the other kind of white powder
What bothered me was the
Bobbies that would try to snort it off
Of my damp crotch
It's horrible the things people will do
For religion and drugs
And I just work here
I mean really honestly I'm just a clerk
Did it get them high
I can't hear you
Did they get high
He asks did they get high
I was being facetious
I don't know
Did they get high
You can't tell the difference with some people
Anybody's dumb enough to snort
White powder off of my lap
What difference does it make
Well if you were
If you were a kitten at Tibby Dodd
I might snort white powder off of my lap
I wouldn't do it off your lap
But I certainly wouldn't do it off your lap
That's Reverend Kitten on Tibby Dodd
Oh my gosh more ice creams
Oh we're very good friends staying
We don't go on formalities
Did you know that
Jay Condom
Reverend Jay Condom dated Kitten
On Tibby Dodd
No I didn't
She dated Bouncing Boy
Yes she dated the guy who drew P-Dog
The original P-Dog comics
Who's a
Stumpy little fella
With a beer gut
He became Kitten on Tibby
The famous porno star
Kitten on Tibby Dodd's boyfriend
But
She broke up with him
When he referred to her
She had
She actually had breast cancer
And then had reconstructive surgery
And he referred to it as
A bolt on
Her bolt ons and she was offended
And broke up with him
And she was referring to her
Brand new fake breast as bolt ons
You have to be careful in situations like that
This next song is called
I Missed the Boat
Like the unicorn
Ha ha ha ha Bob
Praise
Praise Bob our drummer
Got it?
Is it okay now?
Okay okay
Okay everybody
Oh ladies and gentlemen
Playing
Bass for the first time
Andrew the Impaled
For the first time
In our band actually
Not for the first time ever
And actually
The rest of the band Red Bob
Junkins
Everybody say happy birthday
To Red Bob
Thank you very much
Thank you
And the great Bill Sperry
On guitar
And
I'm Tommy
Amoeba and this next song
As I said before
I Missed the Boat
And this is
Sitting on the dock of the harbor
Staring at the oil in the water
Forming pretty colors and patterns
Worming pretty colors and patterns
Like there is a rock
Neptune and Saturn
Saw this great big passenger freighter
Pulling out to see a bit later
Then I saw her face in the porthole
And it made me feel like an asshole
Because I missed the boat like a unicorn
I missed the boat on the Dallas phone
I missed the boat but it's not so scary
I missed the boat but I caught the fairy
I missed the boat like a unicorn
I missed the boat on the Dallas phone
I missed the boat but it's not so scary
I missed the boat but I caught the fairy
Caught the fairy, caught the fairy
Read the news today in the paper
Bought some capsized passenger freight
Saw this great big passenger freighter
Tied a ways and turned it upside down
Like the famous SS Poseidon
Forty portals broke in the motion
How they caught them all in the ocean
Then I read the list of who made it
And it made me sad and elated
Because I missed the boat like a unicorn
I missed the boat on the Dallas phone
I missed the boat like a unicorn
I missed the boat but it's not so scary
I missed the boat but I caught the fairy
I missed the boat like a unicorn
Caught the fairy, caught the fair....ry
Caught the fair...nnin- конечно o.o
aaa...raaa....ry
guitar solo
I Missed the Boat by Amoeba Knievel.
That is Tommy Amoeba and band.
You can find them and all the other bands we play tonight on Facebook
if you can spell Amoeba.
Look it up.
And now, from Detroit by way of out of space,
the Amoeba, I mean the Slot Rods.
Play that one with the notes.
Huh?
Play that one that rocks.
That one that rocks.
Oh, coming up.
I Missed the Boat by Amoeba Knievel.
That is Tommy Amoeba and band.
You can find them and all the other bands we play tonight on Facebook
if you can spell Amoeba Knievel.
That is Tommy Amoeba and band.
You can find them and all the other bands we play tonight on Facebook
if you can spell Amoeba Knievel.
That is Tommy Amoeba and band.
Well, let's get the party saucer serving, shall we?
I'd say it's just about time for lunch with evaluation control committee
and another great video done by Trans Fatdy.
It's girls with meat, ladies and gentlemen!
Slow polo
Ambergers!
Amber..
MARKENDEIS
Markendeeis
Hamburgers!
Potato salad!
Watermelon!
Hamburgers!
Potato salad!
Watermelon!
Thank you.
Here's sensational news.
A terrific offer.
Listen.
One, 89 cents.
Two, 89 cents.
And three, 89 cents.
Right.
Man, here's your chance to get 89 cents.
Imagine.
In one combination package, you get only 89 cents.
Yes, sir.
89 slick sweet cents.
Retail value, 49 cents.
Okay.
I ask a lot of people this question.
Some people don't know the answer.
They think they know the answer.
But anyway, who knows who the bad was in the good and the bad and the ugly?
Me.
Okay.
You want a shirt?
This one's called Lee Van Cleef.
Okay.
Thank you.
This, what you're hearing now, is the Slot Rods live at 50 Next Day.
Before that, we heard,
You can find them, by the way, at
Also on Facebook.
For that matter, everybody here is on Facebook, except me.
I keep a relatively low profile there.
Coming up, more Evolution Control Committee, plus a wedding.
A real, legal, subgenius wedding, live from 50 Next Day.
Oh, and thanks to Reverend Baby Bear for the poem at the beginning and the end.
And to Lee Murr for the titles.
PSA and PR.
Some of the subtitles may not be as clear as very natural, so I won't go through all the talk.
world ofnde화
well restaurants
around.
Are going south,
episode one.
Thank you.
Yes okay well let's begin.
You can ease that music up a little bit I think.
And let the lovely couple come forward friends.
Reverend Gorgon Millar.
and the inaptly named Princess Squirrel Face.
She does look like a princess.
But to be a squirrel face, you need much bigger teeth.
I was honestly looking forward to giant teeth.
Don't stop me if you've heard this before,
because we did just do it two days ago.
But I'm going to try to do some extra stuff for you guys.
Friends, these two are preparing to launch themselves into the future,
not unlike the bleeding head of Arnold Palmer,
which usually has to be launched by somebody else,
but you guys are doing the launching yourselves.
I'm just helping.
As most wedding ceremonies have,
the preacher gives this corny advice on helpful hints for a marriage.
But I bet you guys have been shacked up for a little while.
But I'm sure that as good subgeniuses,
you haven't, you know, until you're married,
you wouldn't have sex or anything like that.
Of course not.
This is the part that I neglected to explain to Reverend Suds and Priestess Pisces,
and that's why they haven't given birth yet.
I know you guys haven't done this routine yet.
Oh, he's got two daughters.
Yeah, but that was with a human.
Subgenius, when subgeniuses mate, the gestation period is very swift.
There'd suddenly be ten little bat-like creatures flying around.
This is a brief explanation of the Yeti bat-squid symbiont.
Uh, birds.
And the bees, basically.
The facts of life.
And I'm going to go ahead.
Oh, there's no kids here, so I can use the full vocabulary.
When a face-fucking bat attacks a male Yeti subgenius
and ejaculates its poisoned sperm down his throat,
and the Yeti is not promptly treated with face-fucking bat-sperm antidote pudding,
it must find a prairie squid to fuck or it will die.
When a bat-sperm-infected Yeti,
fucks a prairie squid,
it empties him out like a man-shaped condom,
leaving only the undamaged skin lying in a heap upon the ground.
The prairie squid stores and mutates the Yeti sperm
and ejaculates it into the female Yeti on not infrequent occasions.
That means they do it a lot.
Uh, the prairie squid mutated Yeti sperm,
swims up the tubes and impregnates the female's entire lifetime supply of eggs all at once,
transforming her, that would be you,
into a vast egg bag with a little tiny human torso on one end.
Sort of like that female alien in Aliens.
Uh, some guys are really turned on by that.
Uh, the thousands of prairie squid mutated Yeti sperm,
impregnated Yeti eggs,
hatch out into thousands of face-fucking bats
who seek Yetis to face-rape, etc.
So, those are the facts of life.
I know it may sound complicated and disgusting,
but, you know, once you get started, you'll see what I mean.
It's actually, especially the part where you swallow the face-fucking bat sperm antidote pudding,
that's really the main reason most of us do it at all.
Okay, so let's get to the point now that we've covered the scientific details.
Uh, these two are true Yeti mates, you can tell just by looking at them,
and must be together, because there are basic primate needs
that are true from monkeys to humans to subgeniuses.
All three types of primates need, um, grooming,
is what the scientists call it,
uh, making out, and backing out,
and back rubs and stuff, is, uh, what we call it, I guess.
I think it's where true love comes from, myself.
You have to have physical touch from another person,
or you go kind of crazy.
Every now and then, one of us is lucky enough
to finally find another one who, for whatever reason,
rubs just right,
co-groomer, picks your fleas just right,
you know, that whole thing.
Uh, don't do that with ticks.
That's different.
Um, who smells just right,
who looks at you just right,
and, best of all, who laughs at your jokes.
Thank you very much, Princess Wee.
She laughs at all my jokes.
She's so polite.
Without all that, you go half crazy,
but with that, you can go completely crazy,
fully crazy.
That's the, the, the great part about le-
being legally marriage.
They can't stop you.
You, you have this excuse.
In fact, we'll soon sign the paper that
even the government gives you the excuse.
Even your religion.
Which, you already have that excuse here,
but we're formalizing it.
Uh, I am qualified to do this because
I have a, um,
a Universal Life Minister's card in my pocket.
That's not it, but it's close enough.
It's my FCC license, actually.
Good enough.
But I do have it.
And I also have a piece of paper that says
my mind is normal.
Sorry.
I really do have one of those.
Um, and also, the other thing that makes me qualified
is Princess Wee and I have the happiest marriage
in the whole world.
And I said, I mean, we don't fight.
You oughta hear our fights, man.
They, they're, it's like, uh,
who's afraid of Virginia Woolf?
I'm the asshole, of course.
And as Nenslow, the great Nenslow said,
in every relationship,
there has to be a mean one and a nice one.
I'm not sure why that is, but apparently it's true.
I'm usually, you're the mean one?
Good, good.
It's, it's best,
it's, I think it's best if the girl is the mean one.
I'm usually the mean one,
unless she's tricking me that completely.
Uh, weddings always feature, uh, quotes,
usually from some, uh, wonderful, nice poetry.
We prefer quoting monster movies,
which always seem more entertaining to me.
And the, the, I'm gonna quote
The Bride of Frankenstein.
Friend.
Good.
I could also throw in food, good.
Smoke, good.
Wine, good.
But really, the friend is the, the most important part.
And the way that you can tell that you are true Yeti mates
is that your worst quarrels will be a thousand times better
than everybody else's honeymoons.
Everything will seem perfect
when you have a true Yeti mate.
You'll be total blithering idiots.
And not that you're blind to each other's faults.
You notice the faults, you just don't care about them.
That's not the important part.
And any stupid mistakes that your partner makes,
I'm afraid you may have to deal with a lot of these,
um, will, will just seem to you
to be part of his or her very existences,
his or her very existences eternal flirtation
with the entire universe.
You'll both continue to make thousands of stupid mistakes,
uh, because for one thing you're subgeniuses,
but because you're psychotically preoccupied with each other
all the time.
So your ability to deal with the others,
which is all of the rest of us, may be severely impaired.
Uh, but that doesn't matter.
And the normals around you will still screw up a lot worse.
As, as, as distracted and screwy as you may be,
remember, they're even worse.
Um, that's always been easy for me to, uh, remind myself
over and over again.
Your friends will probably decide that you've lost your minds,
and they will be right, because you are soul partners,
only partially in this world,
uh, maintaining the least possible toehold on reality,
good for very little else than laying around
experiencing your joint nervous system,
which is probably about as close to real slack
as any of us will ever get.
Best of all, you have an excuse.
You literally can't help it, right?
I mean, if we tried to keep you guys apart, would it work?
No. Duh. You can just tell.
And in order to do that,
in order to get a little bit of God in here,
I'm gonna quote Einstein,
who was not a subgenius
and would not have been qualified for our august religion.
But he said,
My religion consists of a humble admiration
of the illimitable superior spirit
who reveals himself in the slightest details
we are able to perceive
with our frail
and feeble mind.
I notice he refers to God as him.
But he was old.
That was in the old days.
And it was Einstein.
He could get away with a lot.
The masculine was thought to embrace the feminine.
Um, an old Chinese proverb,
more to the point, says,
I hear and I forget,
I see and I remember,
I do and I understand.
And, uh,
Reverend Gorgon and Princess Spurlface
are about to truly understand.
And no.
Of course, that means you have to do it.
But we're not gonna make you do that right here.
All you have to do here is make out pretty good.
Um, they don't seem very alike.
You really, guys, really don't look very alike.
Um, but your true soul is, um,
soulmate and yeti mate is supposed to be very different from you,
had better be very different from you,
because if you're the same,
you get more cow-like.
You amplify each other's faults.
You just make everything
dumb easier.
As different people,
your holy differences trick you
into learning from each other
and seeing new ways
and learning new tricks.
When you get to my age,
you don't imitate the guys,
what you see guys in porno movies doing.
You work on that now.
But you don't want to go through the conversation
I had to have with my doctor.
She wanted to know exactly what I did.
I wouldn't tell her.
But the main thing is, friends,
uh, you hone the skills of marital compromise
to the point where you get better at working and playing with others.
And you can use those skills on the job
or in real life.
Either one.
Even both.
Two heads are better than one.
Especially if both heads are not completely filled with brain cells.
As I've said many times,
Princess Wee and I only have half a brain cell each.
But it's the other half.
So, as long as we're together,
we have one fully functioning brain cell.
Now, some people change when they get married.
Oh, how terrible.
You might become something new.
Although, you probably won't.
You guys, obviously you've been together for a while.
When you were on your own,
you didn't need to grow in quite the same ways
because who would complain if you didn't?
But when you share your whole life with somebody,
they're going to complain.
And you have to grow.
There's certain parts grow faster than others,
I've noticed at certain times.
I like that part.
Uh,
when you share your whole life with somebody,
you have to grow.
That means compromises, loyalty, devotion,
which sometimes can be a pain in the ass.
But it's worth it.
Absolutely worth it,
because the payback is,
you get to soak in pure love.
The real thing.
Which is very rare,
and congratulations to both of you.
I mean that.
If there's anything eternal in life,
that's probably the best way to find it.
And so friends,
those of us gathered here today,
by the way,
if there's anybody who objects to this ceremony,
I don't care.
Keep your mouth shut.
Don't speak.
You just forever hold your peace.
Um,
these two,
Princess Squirrelface and Gorgon Miller,
Mylar,
oh is it Mylar?
Okay.
Sorry about that.
Who were apart,
come together now in our presence
to declare their love and be united in marriage.
You know, there's all this stuff about,
but you must be able to stand alone and dance alone
and not be too dependent and co-dependent
and needy on each other.
Screw that.
Go ahead and be co-dependent.
Go ahead and be needy.
That's what it's all about.
You know,
you gotta scratch each other.
You can't scratch your own back.
Or pop zits.
That's one of my favorites.
So, yeah,
go ahead and intertwine to your heart's content.
Need and co-depend all you want.
If they can't take a joke,
you know what they can do.
And we've just explained what you guys can do
in, you know, great scientific detail.
In coming before us all here today,
you're performing an act of faith in each other.
A faith that will continue to grow and mature
and endure.
And if you have your love set on that faith
for all the days ahead,
then cherish the hopes that you hold right now
and resolve that love will not be blotted out
by the commonplace
or blurred by the mundane in life
and screw the boss.
Uh, you know,
if you need to stay home and make out all day,
bye gobs.
Bye.
Well, actually, maybe,
you might need to hang on to your job, so,
whatever.
What you guys have is a lot more important
than any of that other stuff.
You know, the rituals of daily life
eventually make some things seem, uh,
almost mundane,
but I'm sure that you'll come up with something
to keep it lively.
Having fights often is a real good way to make up.
The making up part kicks ass.
So, believing in yourselves and each other
will strengthen not only the both of you,
but it'll strengthen all your friends.
The rest of us who know you
will also be given hope.
Those who haven't found true Yeti mates,
even if it takes until you're 60 years old,
don't give up.
Even if you only have that true Yeti mate
for five minutes
before an asteroid comes down
and crushes your true Yeti mate,
that five minutes is worth the 60-year wait.
I speak from experience.
I'm, well, 58 years.
Okay, this is the good part.
In our presence, you're now ready to pledge your love.
Do you, Princess Squirrel Face,
take this man,
Reverend Mylar,
to be your husband,
to have and to hold from this day forward,
for better or worse,
for richer or poorer,
in sickness and health and kinkiness,
to love and to cherish?
Say, I do.
I do.
Do you, Reverend Gorgon Mylar,
take this woman, Princess Squirrel Face,
to be your wife,
to have and to hold,
holding, pardon, and having.
Having is good, too.
From this day forward,
for better or worse,
richer or poorer,
in sickness and health and to love and to cherish?
Say, I do.
I do.
With their whole hearts
and all of their organs
and their complete devotion,
they pledge their love today.
Now, do you have a ring?
They've got a ring!
You now perform the sacred symbolic temple of Devoe.
This is symbolic of a pole going into a hole.
I'm not sure what that has to do with weddings,
but it's very traditional and romantic.
Princess, we and I, by the way,
tried to get our, when we got married,
we tried to get the rings on the wrong hand.
They didn't fit.
It was a subgenius wedding.
All right.
Oh, do you have any vows to say to each other?
I figure you probably handled that last night.
In that case,
you must now seal your vows with a kiss.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Now we're talking.
This is what it's all about.
Now shake on it and say it's a deal.
It is now a deal.
I now pronounce you man and wife.
Friends, I am pleased and very proud
to present the newly married couple,
Princess Squirrelface and Reverend Gorgon Mylar.
I am pleased and very proud
to present the newly married couple,
They are now hitched.
You've just done the easy part
and let the party begin.
Huh?
Did I learn anything?
Where's my unscrewing fork?
You said there are no excellentitudinals.
I said,
yours and mine
are not necessarily odpowied.
So I said it all.
you've been listening to the subgenius radio ministry hour of slack
for free information write to p.o box 181 417 cleveland heights ohio 44118 or see
www.subgenius.com praise bob
here's my love religion
love my religion
Friends, we're glad you listened to this show,
and we're even more glad that some listeners have donated enough to help us keep on going for another couple of months.
Not just this show, but subgenius.com and all the other archive sites.
But if you truly love Bob and want some of that slack back to rebound to you,
you should go to subgenius.com front page, or especially the radio page, or the catalog store pages,
and help out financially as best you can.
Now, we know what it's like to be on the brink of total poverty,
and we don't want any subgeniuses to make their own situations worse.
But some of you still have jobs.
Even five bucks makes a big difference, even if it's only once a month from enough of you.
Fifty bucks makes an even bigger difference.
All we're saying is that blowjobs could go the way of Steve jobs if you don't pay dogs.
We also take checks and money orders to subgeniusfoundation.
P.O. Box 181417.
Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
Thanks for anything you can do to help let there be slack.