bc world service this is but let's start with but let's start with bc news with the uranium
authorities have begun removing seals at the united nations in iran the un's dog seals have
been broken from pr news in washington on charge with conspiracy to commit catastrophic forecasting
i am mad because because because because u.s officials say this is pr news the government
criticized the bush administration's hurricane shortages caused by money laundering on wall
street 12 10 4 1 2 president bush is forcibly removing residents from department buildings
after pr news kids are going back to school and they're bringing their germs with them
that's why schools all over the country make kids sick
you
yes i'm going back home
yes i'm walking to new orleans
you used to be my
genius
my
uh...
valores
Hey, come on. Welcome to slack, slack, slack, slack. Welcome to traditional slack.
You've tried almost everything and still no relief?
Try the self-genius power of swag.
It dissolves completely in beverages and is completely tasteless.
Welcome to slack, slack, slack, slack.
Everything that I can.
Actually, that wasn't George Bush. That was Mr. Sister.
Friends, this is a bad week for a funny show.
Although, you know, Bob's prophecy does ring true.
Back in the 60s, he said, and I quote, Bob said,
It's gonna be a bummer, man.
Now, is that prophetic truth?
Or what?
I'm not much of a believer, friends.
I don't believe in invisible monsters.
Because they told me not to believe in them.
But this last weekend, I found myself praying, nonetheless.
The United States government presents...
This is our enemy.
Hello, Riley. Thanks for watching.
I knew it. I knew it.
Clowns.
Jesus might not be...
Down with Reverend Pat Robertson.
I mean, it's just insane.
Off the wall.
I don't know anything.
Crazy propaganda.
Off the wall.
The Joseph Goebbels Network.
Someone who rejects facts.
Holds on to opinions no matter what.
700 Club.
A neurosis.
The documentary out of the box tells the truth about this network.
Gays and abortionists cause God to allow 9-11.
Child sex offenders should not serve long prison terms.
Philosophy of the Third Reich is okay.
Are you okay with slaughtering civilians?
I'm Bill O'Reilly. Thanks for watching us tonight.
It's gonna be a bummer, man.
We're awaiting Lonesome Cowboy Dave and Princess Wee both to arrive.
But in the mean...
And I may have to run down there and let them in.
In the meantime, music.
You were all the rays of sunlight
Shining gold to me
Every color of a rainbow
I was blessed by her decree
You were every moment's magic
Joy beyond compare
You were all the rays of sunlight
I was lost without a care
Victims of the fury
Shadows in the dark
It was found among
So we lived our days in rapture
Like the sun in the sky
Like the world could never end
We went thinking about the future
We had time enough to spend
We were blessed as though in heaven
We were messengers of joy
There were angels all around us
There was none who dared destroy
Victims of the fury
Joy beyond compare
We've become all together
Unballed inness
I walked to glory
We were the red-and- pieced
While she had her wedding comb
I'm dying as the sun
You will be as bright as ever
And when things get darker
We're noticed by love
But debates are all paid
uration
Will be like this
It's all part of the game
It's time to throw Since I massive prison
Into today's world
The world collapsed around us
And the archers found their mark
We were victims of the fury
We were shadows in the dark
Victims of the fury
Shadows in the dark
And was found their mark
guitar solo
Victims of the fury
Shadows in the dark
And was found their mark
guitar solo
Look at him now!
Here he comes!
guitar solo
Mom, mom, the atomic bomb
Just went off
Out of my house!
I'm the Haley Law
Paul wears Paul
Now what'll we do?
That ball, the root cellar
I'm right behind you
And the wind took
The ground shook
And me and my baby
Trained in one last look
The heavens, the wall
Pushed, caused to shove
There ain't no escaping
The tornado of love
guitar solo
And we
For outrun your brothers
Outrun the twisty
You gotta thank for older men
Are you too good for your own kin?
Oh yeah
Well twist, twist, twist
Little sister out of the grips of a mean old mister
President of the United Fools
Hot, hot future in fossil fuels
Oh yeah
Led Long John's for a cold, cold winter
Then we saw the outhouse littered out there
Said Paul with his overalls deep
His Sears catalog and his roller in the east
And the wind took the ground shook
And me and my baby traded one last look
The heavens, the walls were in constant dub
Ain't no state
But the tornado of love
The wind took the ground shook
And me and my baby traded one last look
The heavens, the walls were in constant dub
Ain't no state
But the tornado of love
guitar solo
Where the colossum planted that derinium bomb?
Then we have a chance
Kisly
How much of a chance doctor?
Mixed voice
Kisly
Roundhouse
roundhouse
Cheese
Poence
black
Alarm
drum
awake
live
hop
rock
hope
pul designing
experiences
Here at the gram
Early Shaw
They say, take Najaf, put a cordon around it, cut off the electricity, cut off the water.
The sweltering summer is coming, and you send leaflets to those people, say, give us, give us the mullah and his followers,
and you will have all your services restored.
And unless you do, it's going to be a long, hot summer.
And if we deal with it forcefully in terms of pollution, go in there and do Najaf with those ex-baptists.
They are terrorists who've got one thing in mind, to destroy the democracy of Iraq and to kill our soldiers.
That was, I just quoted to you, the words of the Prince of Peace, Jesus Christ.
Mother, you are a fucking moron.
Do we retain our knowledge?
No, Dr. Zarkov.
There is an eraser ray that...
It follows the recorder ray as it passes over every inch of your brain.
Zadarin, listen, you can't do this.
Between us, we hold the knowledge upon which the safety of the entire galaxy depends.
Exactly the information I want, every morsel of it.
The galaxy, what do I care for its safety?
All I want is the power to make every living human bend to my will.
Start the ray flow.
I want the...
From PR News in Washington, I'm lit up and continue to deteriorate.
An immigration judge in El Paso, Texas, should be denied asylum in the United States.
Louisiana State Senator Walter Boasso says...
Rose, Rose, uh, Rose, Rose.
We know that.
Wall Street 7-7.
A white spokesman says President Bush is being kept informed about the damage from PR News in Washington.
And God...
We know that.
And blood's thicker than water
The thin and cold in the flood
The mud and the gild and the gun get heavy
We do what we gotta
We want the living
Now I'm just a man protecting his home
Why do I feel like a dog out killing his own?
Is he on the ticket?
Quick on the draw
Shine the flashlight in the face
Of a 12-year-old kid that started crying for his pa
I told him to get on with it
From PR News in Washington, I'm tired of PR News.
Osama bin Laden's sales plunged 13%.
His staff is going through the steps to take care of the dead bodies outside.
We're out all day today to come.
It's under control.
Human rights groups carried out the first execution since 2003
on Wall Street 210-491732.
President Bush...
President Bush will get a first-hand look at 1,400 National Guard troops per day.
Of particular concern is PR News, Washington.
How large the dreaded Gila monster grows, no man can say.
2,000 dead now.
As opposed to just wounded for a day or two.
Pull out.
The people have absolutely no hope.
President's failure to articulate.
Immediate pull out.
Pull out.
So let me ask, so let me ask, so let me ask the pull-out experts.
The pull-out experts.
We're pulling out tomorrow.
We begin to pull out next year, we begin to pull out in three or four years.
Pull out now.
We're not achieving anything.
Wave that Vietnam flag again.
Beat on the Vietnam drum.
Pull out, pull out, pull out.
People getting killed. Our guys.
Us killing them.
Enough already.
Sewage probably is some political coloration.
President is off the mark here.
Wrong.
It's just stupid and it's not working.
Making more enemies than we're killing.
Pulling out, pulling out now.
It's so screwed up.
It's gonna be bad.
It's gonna be a bummer, man.
And I say it is possible for a giant lizard to have lived there for years without being seen.
Andy, did you hear that?
Come on, come on, Andy.
Did I hear what?
So white, so white, so white, so white, so white, so white, so white, so white.
I've got a hunch way up...
...to...
...here.
More dirt.
Get it all so white.
Well, well, well, well, gay romantic figure.
No.
Well, what's that in your hand?
So good sitting here listening to the radio after bending over...
Mmm, wouldn't I love to?
Well, maybe for my heavy pieces.
Bright and gay, so white.
So white, so white, so white, so white.
I don't feel so good in the head.
Somebody at the back door.
So white, dear friends.
As the Ape Associated Press was saying, white people find things and black people loot things in emergencies.
Where's my background music?
Is it just slow?
Like Dave?
Dave is slow.
I'm not slow.
Oh, there. Here we go.
Okay.
All right.
Everything's fine here.
Oh, yeah.
Here, everything's just fine.
Yeah, we got plenty of red beans over here.
You know, that Homeland Security guy, Chertsov, that Jackoff said he didn't even know all kinds of things.
He didn't know stuff that even I knew about the security of our homeland.
He thought the eye of the hurricane was so heavily smudged with mascara that there was no chance it would ever reach the reckoning of number five, which is...
You know, like 11 on an amplifier.
Well, as Mr. Sister was pointing out, this whole thing was totally botched.
I mean, such a slow response.
The price of gas waited two days after the storm to jump to over $3 a gallon.
Now, wait a minute, Stanger.
Now, that is a...
That's ridiculously slow.
What kind of a country is this?
Stanger, you're thinking very, very crudely.
You're not getting the finer points of this deal, what's going on here.
This major crime has been committed.
And if you look at all the different details of the crime...
Certain things start to fall into place.
You've got to be a detective.
No, you shouldn't be offended.
You should be enthused.
Not enthused, you should be amused.
Yes, that's...
Be amused and be mused and perhaps...
Yeah, very funny.
You're out of your national gourd.
Yeah, I'm out of my...
To quote Kinnick, peace.
I'm out of my national gourd.
We're all out of our national gourd.
Look at it, Stanger.
It's perfectly ideal.
You move in, you destroy, you displace.
Suddenly the developers arrive.
The insurance companies are all...
Well paid.
And then the next thing you know, the military's back all of a sudden.
They're rebuilding the things.
Oh, not just any old...
For the corporations.
Yeah, not just any old military.
Actually, it's the Halliburton company that's doing a lot of that.
Yeah, here it is.
Hallibur-tayne!
Hallibur-tayne.
Get this.
The U.S. Navy asked Hallibur-tayne to repair naval facilities damaged by Hurricane Katrina,
the Houston Chronicle reported.
The work was a success.
Hallibur-tayne signed to Hallibur-tayne's KBR subsidiary under the Navy's $500 million
contract awarded, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
Stanger, you're frothing now.
You have to calm down.
You're shaking.
You know, lacquerty is...
Well, as Hell-Poe Pui pointed out about that, when the vice president of the U.S. has such
suspect ties to a company that gets that much gravy from something this bad, it just looks
bad, even if it is on the up and up.
And that's the problem with being in bed in sight and even if you didn't personally
foul the sheets, the reek of brimstone is still going to float over everything regardless.
That sulfur's smell...
Said Hell-Poe Pui.
That sulfur's smell is neither a fart nor the aftermath of the sewage in the hurricane.
It's a funeral pyre, Stang.
It's a bunch of bodies being burned because, well, and no place to bear them, Donda.
Well, what's in the sacks that they're dumping into the river to plug the levee break?
Well, some people say it was just bad fruit from down by the...
Yeah.
We're told all kinds of things, but where are...
I don't know.
No, maybe it's from Cafe Du Monde, you know, and they put some of the old bad beignets in
the thing there and float them down the river and say, get rid of this stuff.
It ain't no good no more.
Bad mufaletas, bad po' boys, bad jambalaya, you know, all kind of food they stuffed in
there.
Reverend Stan Williams suggested that the Edward Teller solution to clean up, where
you use a medium-sized thermonuclear device to quickly evaporate the water and ease the
Now, that's an American solution.
Bonafide red, white, and blue.
Nuke them until there's nothing there.
Sheesh.
Well, in 2004, it says here, the Bush administration cut funding requested by the New Orleans District
of the U.S. Army Corps of Engineers for holding back the waters of Lake Pontchartrain by more
than 80%.
And it worked, as Polar Bear pointed out, because 80% of the water is still in the lake.
The rest is out there in Lake George, what they're calling Greater Metropolitan Orleans.
They call it Lake George now.
You see, God has destroyed a wicked city.
That's what some of the Chris Staines were, the really far gone, far righty and wrong
Yeah.
Sodom and Gomorrah is what they're calling it.
Well, that place was Sodom and Gomorrah anyway.
Who cares what happens to them?
That's the new thing.
This is, you know, people can't this daily.
We have to hear this going into our earwax.
We have to hear this seeping into our brains every day.
We're being left behind.
We're the subhumans, not the subgeni.
To these people, we're the subhumans.
Submen.
Submit.
The undermensch ist gefallen.
And subwomen, too.
Oh, the sub-babes.
Oh, yeah, the under...
Speaking of which...
It says here, Hurricane Huey destroys Dobstown days before Sister Decadence Day.
Just days before Sister Decadence Day, an annual subgenius celebration attracting tens
of thousands of people to the Malaysian Quarter section of Dobstown.
Hurricane Huey destroyed the city.
Although the loss of lives is deeply saddening, this act of God destroyed a wicked city, says
repent, slack off, America, Michael Markkavich.
From Girls Gone Wild to Sister Decadence Day, Dobstown was a city that has its doors wide
open to the public celebration of sin and frop.
From such devastation may a city full of righteousness emerge.
May this act of God cause us all to think about what we tolerate in our city limits
and bring us trembling before the throne of Almighty God.
So where's Mardi Gras going to be this next year?
The Flats?
In Dobstown?
No, not Dobstown, because we see what happens there.
But the Flats, maybe.
Well, see, that's what's the difference between...
Or somebody suggested the Las Vegas Beach.
Well, you know, if they're this ready...
I just think all that beach drifting out into the Gulf of Mexico don't, you know, kind of
bruises the ego, or bruises the spirit, excuse me.
Well, thanks to Reverend Ellis Dee, yes, for that news release there.
See, we used to go to Cafe Dumont.
I always have to go to Cafe Dumont.
I always have to go to Cafe Dumont and get that chicory coffee.
It's like espresso, but it's got chicory in it.
And then you get a muffalette across the street.
And you can spit to the river right from there.
I mean, it's right...
You can see it right over there.
You can walk up to it and you can urinate in it.
You know, a lot of people do.
But the main thing is you want to stay away from certain parts during the Gras because
people do act like animals.
I was.
I did.
It was great.
I've been to Mardi Gras.
Well, you still are an animal in a lot of ways.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
The hirsutism hasn't subsided.
You're still hairy and have too many canines.
Teeth.
War of the Third Worlds, they called it.
Apocorleans now.
Oh, jeez.
Mad Max Beyond Superdome.
Yeah, well, you have to portray...
Gone with the Bling.
You must compartmentalize.
Katrina Does New Orleans.
Nightmare on Bourbon Street.
These were all things that...
Pirates of the Pontchartrain.
Piled up arms.
The kids on the IRC came up with this.
On the past day long.
And how green was my topical humor, said Nenslow.
And it is easy for us to...
My tropical hubris, I think, is what was wrong in this case.
Hey, FEMA is opening a restaurant chain.
FEMER.
Yeah, FEMER, that you drive up to the window and place your order and 72 hours later it's
ready.
It's another Mr. Cysterion.
Gag.
Thanks, Mr. Cyster.
There's a lot of gagging, horrible gag.
Mr. Cyster went to New Orleans last year and happened to get really sick and there
was a big parade going on, not Mardi Gras, or maybe it was.
But he was...
Halloween is a big parade.
There was an ambulance there on a street corner waiting for somebody to get sick in the parade.
So he just walked on up there.
And Mr. Cyster walked up and said, I'm really sick and I need to go to the hospital.
And they said, we're not allowed to go to the hospital.
We're not allowed to leave this spot.
So you'll have to walk down there and call somebody else.
That was New Orleans.
Now, you know, everybody is blaming President Bush for the storm.
And it's true that reportedly George Bush was seen at the height of the storm, prying
at the levees with a long iron bar, shrieking with insane glee.
Like Darius whipping the waters before the Greeks defect.
Reportedly.
From the Greek.
From Ninsla.
Intelligence analysts are calling him, quote, an insane murderer, worse than a million
Hitlers and a billion Stalins combined.
He may, in fact, be worse than that.
If present trends continue, he may eventually murder everyone and be the sole human survivor,
devouring the corpses of his billions of victims, or so we hear.
Well spoken, Jim.
I think that's perhaps the best speech you've ever given.
Now in our state.
in our classes, what we usually like to
stress is making sure the pelvis is
thrust forward when singing
songs to the Archduke. Remember,
W is
our Royal Regatta.
He is our snake and sounding
board. He is our tired policeman.
As we back away
from this beautiful video display
behind us, me, you, that is
all of us here, we can see
what God in all
his splendor has wrought.
Something's
wrought in Godland.
However,
in Swaziland, things
are cool. They have a cool
president, or he's a king there, actually.
He's like one of the new enlightened
royalty. Well, actually,
some of his people
are trying to say that he's too
old-fashioned and he shouldn't be doing the
reed dance anymore. Did you read
about the reed dance?
No. I mean, did you read about
the reed dance?
I need your reed about...
In Swaziland, if you're king,
you get to pick an additional
wife every year. That's one of the
benefits of living there. And the way the king
gets to pick the new wife is, all
the virgins in the country
that want to, which is several
thousand, do the parade
past his throne, doing the
ceremonial reed dance
topless, basically, wearing the
traditional dress, as they put it.
I searched the internet for
movies or good pictures of the reed dance.
I did find
some, but they were very modest.
I'm going to say the king of
Swaziland's daughters are really
beautiful. Gorgeous. For some reason
they were prancing around out there, too.
Anyway, that's
the kind of leader we need, man!
You should see this
grin on that guy's face. He was smiling like
Bob. He's glowing!
Positively glowing! Now that is
the kind of leadership I'd like to see
more of in this country, as well as
live broadcasts of the series.
Well, why can't we have Bush's
daughters, bare-chested,
doing the traditional
Bush dance, in front of the
White House, and we'll also
have George parade all the new
vials of the Beltway, like
what's-her-name, Karen
Colson, or whatever her name is. The one that
looks like a rat. Ann Coulter? Ann Coulter.
Yeah. Ann Coulter, you know,
going by and stuff, you know, showing her
stuff. She'd love it.
What's the lady on
MSNBC, then?
And then also
the one that's related to Alistair Crowley,
and you can tell, because she's got the wrong handshake.
Monica Crowley!
You watch a lot more television than I do.
No, I remember from the day
when I did. I have no more TV.
But I hear also now people
talk about how much they hate them, so I can remember
the names. You know, you
would have been flat out of luck if you
weren't one of those poor people in New Orleans.
Because,
now, here's one thing you can't
blame on Bush, because it
administration of the state
and the city are mostly Democrats.
But when they
knew that this terrible storm was
coming, okay,
they had lots of buses
and things around, and they knew
that there were a lot of people who were way
too broke, didn't have gas.
It wasn't quite up to
$5 a gallon then, but
you know what they did for the
what the city of New Orleans did
about a day or two before the hurricane?
They produced a DVD,
for the estimated
134,000 New Orleans
residents without vehicles, the city
produced a DVD that
was sent out to churches and community
groups, urging them to leave
town, but admitting the government
could not take them.
You're responsible for your safety
and you should be responsible for the person
next to you. So I guess if you
didn't have a DVD player or a car,
you weren't even
told to go
screw yourself.
You couldn't even get that much of a message.
To check the deal, I'd heard over
various internet sources that
the money that was supposed to be spent
and got funneled into a crooked scambologna
with Don Bush
was somehow ended up
into the hands of these people, and so they produced
a DVD instead of helping repair
a levee, or creating a kind of
consciousness awareness, which could be
understood by the average person who didn't have a
DVD player or didn't, you know.
Well, indeed, as
Katrina bore down on New Orleans,
last weekend, Mayor Ray Nagin
marshaled a fleet of
city buses, not to take
the city's poor out of town, but
to the large shelter at the Super
Dome, where civil order
would fall apart as the week progressed
and so forth.
Well, has civil order returned now that they've called
in the National Guard from Texas? Of course,
since not from
Louisiana, because they're in Iraq
and all their rescue equipment is
in Iraq, too, especially for, you know, the
watery parts of Iraq.
Gotta show off in the marshlands there, we can do
any kind of fighting. Oh, right, yeah,
we have all of our
necessary swamp rescue gear
is over there.
In the swamps of the
Middle East, well, well.
Well, oh, speaking of which, I have a perfect
cut to play, and we can relieve
the listeners of
this
us. Vile hubris.
This hatred of the world at large.
The meas of the melange
of poopoo and caga that we
are in. Okay, I have to do credits.
At the beginning of the,
of course, this show has been
filled with cut-ups and
collages by Fernand and Andy
Lemur and Norrell Preff.
You can get more at norrellpreff.com.
Also, our friend Reverend Jacques
Petty sent a lot of movie
clips, soundtrack clips, which
we're using, and someone
named Joe
has been posting cut-ups
and music to alt.binaries.site
and I think,
I think that Joe is a fun way
of a fellow from an atom
years ago, but we don't know. Anyway,
here's something he did. He might be the Hey Joe of the
show. Well, we have
that, too. Or Cotton Eye Joe.
Here's Old Man. Cotton Eye Joe? Oil Man.
He could well be Cotton Eye Joe. Oil Man
by Joe.
I'm 42 years old. I've lived a lot of my life
already. I feel very secure as to
who I am and where I've been
and don't feel a need to
be anything other than
kind of a half-broke oil man
from West Texas.
I will swear to not only
uphold the laws of our land,
I will swear to uphold the honor
and dignity of the office to which I have been
elected, so help me God.
And most of them believed in
freedom, peace,
equality of opportunity.
But I guess just like in our time,
there are those who, for power,
would make slaves of everybody else.
Yes, I'm afraid so.
But they didn't have our tools
to fight them with.
Masters of insanity, our mission in Iraq
is a serious mistake.
Here's the man who proves it pays
to be ignorant. That bloomin' idiot,
Mr. George.
Capable of any atrocity.
Man. Tard. Mr. George.
Tard. Everything I do is wrong.
Kill innocent men, women, and children.
George. We have more work to do.
That bloomin' idiot, Mr. George.
Work and fight.
Work and fight. Someone hit me in the face
with a wet dish rag. Violence and
bloodshed. Fuck it. Fuck it. Violence and
instability. Fuck it. Fuck it. Wait
to be attacked again. Fuck it.
Urban combat.
Don't be ignorant just like
me. We intend to stay
forever.
To be ignorant.
No brain. No brain. The lesson of this
experience is he who gets up early
with the son shouldn't stay up late with
the daughter. The lesson of this experience
is fuck it.
And I want to show you
something that the words of the Lord
Jesus Christ in a parable that he
told is quoted in the book
of Matthew. Watch this.
And the rest seems
ridiculous.
And the rest seems ridiculous.
But the king was in rage
and he sent his armies
and destroyed those murderers
and set their city on fire.
And the king was in rage
Now, that is from the gospel.
And that was Jesus saying this is
the normal reaction of a Middle
Eastern king when his servants
have been brutalized as our
servants have been. These brave
men and women under mortar fire.
And they're going to be killed.
under artillery fire, under rocket fire,
and civilian workers, their bodies being mutilated in the streets.
And then we're talking about a few prisoners.
God has a heart on for Marines,
because we kill everything we see.
Joe did that.
Someone named Joe.
Friends, those guys distracted me,
and I never did the credits that I needed to do.
At the beginning of the show, I played a couple of songs.
The wrenching one, the first one,
it was,
Robin Trower, Victims of the Fury,
from his album Victims of the Fury.
And after that, I played The Rainmakers,
Tornado, I think, from the album called Tornado.
That was The Rainmakers.
I love The Rainmakers.
There was also a little bit of them on We Walk the Levee.
We've been hearing massive amounts of,
well, that last piece, Marine Corps Jesus, was by Joe.
Before that, It Pays to Be Ignorant was by Norrell Preff.
And the next thing I'll play eventually is by Lee Murr,
and then Norrell Preff, and then Norrell Preff.
I understand your frustration,
and I'm doing all that I can.
And what is in those bags they're dropping from helicopters
to plug those holes?
I think it's really sand.
Oh, I'm sorry, you weren't on.
We were deaf.
It is sand.
And mute.
I didn't have your button.
I didn't push.
It's those who have been cremated.
They're ashes.
They're using sandbags made of human remains.
And, of course, they're using it as a dressing
for the po' boy sandwiches, which are delicious.
You can't quit thinking about those po' boy sandwiches.
I like the oyster po' boy sandwich,
but there ain't going to be very many oysters left either.
They're all dead now, too,
because of what happened to the ocean floor near there.
See, there's a lot of sediment coming off the river,
so let's put all that poop on up in there, too.
Well, and all the benzene and chlorine
and all the stuff coming out of the broken factory tanks.
The gas and oil.
Major oil refinery state, too, you know.
It's beginning to look a lot like X-Day.
Charleston was saying that he believes that the president
is partially to blame because he's brought bad luck
upon America.
He.
What?
Is wrong.
America.
You say it the Iraqi way.
It's cute.
Oh, is that how they say it?
I like the way your eyebrow goes up in the wings.
That's the way old West Virginia, Pete.
That's the way you say old West Virginia.
I'm at a key.
Virginia, America, heeny.
Anyway.
Well, it's true.
Well, you can bring bad karma, bad doo-doo down on a nation
or a people.
As the leader, just think he's not only inept,
but he's a crook.
Well, actually, Dave.
He's a pizza front for who knows.
God knows.
Dobbs knows.
Well, and personally, I don't believe in karma or luck.
I think you have to.
You have to make your own personally.
That's just me.
But.
So you could do literally anything you choose to anyone else
and not suffer anything at any time in the future,
which doesn't even resemble that.
If I got caught.
Yes.
And in most cases, I would get caught so that I refrain
from doing evil for that reason.
Oh, it is hard.
As best I can tell.
Yeah.
So, yeah.
Well, I don't think he's going to refrain unless he's forced
to refrain with a leather hose and a wire strap and a pair of shoes.
And he's going to have a pair of booties that stretch all the way up to his longaments.
Now, the forbidden scientists on the Internet will.
Well, I've seen posts of people insisting that this could not possibly have been a mere ordinary storm.
This was engineered.
There's lots of water.
The harp research devices were used to create earthquakes.
Of course, the tsunami was just a test and blah, blah, blah.
Well, there is some science that they were doing something around that time that caused a lot of.
Weird activity in the ionosphere.
Some people are saying that's the thing that did it.
It was gone.
Yeah, right.
But well, we couldn't possibly just be a big hurricane.
Those never happened.
There's never been huge.
Never before has there ever been a San Francisco earthquake or a Chicago fire or a terrible ice storm
that will hit all of the cities of the Northeast in the middle of a blackout, which, of course,
you know, it could happen to us.
One of the subgenius.
Polar Bear, in fact, from Canada, was pointing out that, you know, there's all kinds of destructive things that can.
Huh?
When we were young pups and puppets, they used to pass around the myth of the Lake Erie tidal wave,
which had an actual goofy Indian name and had actually happened sometime.
And and the lake, whatever made it happen, maybe it was an earthquake nearby or something.
The lake.
Probably an earthquake.
Big, big rock falling from the sky.
Yeah.
I mean, Tunguska experimental bomb.
Had slapped, you know, had slapped the shorelands quite severely.
Bad juju.
Bad chief.
Yeah.
The gods being angry at a bad chief.
Moses Cleveland was a bad chief and was infected with condom blay and the king of Swaziland was a good chief.
He's like he's one of my heroes now, like the Sultan of Brunei, who's the richest guy in the world.
He's the one we most want to save for Bob.
So it's the Sultan of Brunei.
Or is it now?
His son.
I think it might now be his son.
It's Saltino.
Well, whoever is the Sultan.
His son is really cool, too.
If any of the if anybody who knows the Sultan is listening or the Sultan himself, man, we think you are the coolest folks.
Now, don't start talking in the regal way.
You're not the king.
Yeah, you're not the Sultan.
Yeah.
I just want them to know, you know, if they ever want to, you know, have us over or something.
We'd love to come to Brunei and hang out.
Bob is an old friend, of course, of all these people.
Well, they dob you with oil.
In fact, on the pictures of the king.
The king of Swaziland judging the two thousand or thousands of topless girls of his country walking by.
He gets to touch each one?
You could see Bob just out of the frame.
I mean, it was just edges of him.
But you could tell there was this this white guy in a business suit and with a pipe.
Did you see a little frond?
Yeah, you just saw the edge of his jaw.
Just a little spittle frond there as he drooled at the Swaziland.
Hands firmly placed in his pockets.
You know.
Well.
Well, perhaps we all need our own Swazettes.
You know what I mean?
We need to be the Sultan of Brunei or the king of Swaziland in our own homeopathic way.
In our own non-prescriptive nasal, navel jelly manufacturer.
Well, now, you know, if you really want to do something about all the world's problems, you just go run for office.
If you're really serious about it, you know.
Yeah.
You don't want to catch the runs from the border.
You run for office.
Another stupid phrase.
Run for office.
Democracy is dead.
Dead.
I mean, there's no such thing in America.
It's like a sham.
Pay for.
Okay, pay for office.
If you, you know.
Oh, that's right.
We don't have the money.
Have you ever seen those?
I knew there was some holdup to paying for office.
Well, yeah.
You have to pay to stay.
You know, it's like when you buy your first shrimp poodle.
You know what I mean?
When they slip the check and they say it's not in the mail.
Mm-hmm.
And that's when you know, you know.
And you know the secret handshakes and stuff like that.
You give each other their secret winky sign.
Right.
And so that means.
That say the little children's hospital for maimed, you know, eaters of underwear and stuff.
Those kids.
They have a lot of, you know, St. Hexabar.
Uh-huh.
I think it is.
And they take the money right out of the coffers and put it right in the coffins.
Back in their own looted sandwiches.
It's recycling.
Yeah, it is a way of keeping the ducks and the geese happy.
I mean, the rice flowing, let's say.
That's the more Chinese way.
Oh, the rice must flow.
Okay, okay.
The.
Yeah.
Rice must flow.
Well, it just came right out, didn't it?
Princess, we are dough.
Are you talking about weird, like, maggots and things or anything weird like that that I, you know.
And now this.
George.
W.
Bush.
Small skin molest.
Yatka.
Vichy.
Yatchit.
Chit.
The world is corrupt.
How can that be?
Freedom isn't free.
Oh, God, what are you?
Like some redneck blogger pig?
Oh, come on.
Name one right, one civil liberty that doesn't have blood all over it that people haven't fought
fought and died for.
Uh, we didn't go to war to protect Iraqi civil liberties.
That's just a lame justification.
I didn't say it was just,
but that's the way human beings make progress.
We're violent. It's our nature.
It's a little naive to expect anything different.
Oh, don't give yourself a handjob!
That's okay.
I'm a Buddhist. We don't care about that shit.
This is so fucking weird.
We are so fucking lost.
I'm gonna smoke some crack.
We now present Bob, founder of Bob University,
who during his earthly ministry was one of Bob's great warriors.
Little half-baked man, intellectually.
Some man that's really an ignoramus.
Now, I constantly come...
He was absolutely crazy.
He had bats in his belfry.
That's too far beyond me to understand.
Big man.
They know so little.
You know, I've met so many fellas,
and there's some little dark corners that he can get into,
and he can set you.
You can't even know your own self.
Now, listen. Reveal things.
Now, that's wonderful, isn't it?
It's just beyond me.
I can't get it, see.
But wait a minute.
I've known some fellas pretty high up.
Many women.
You have just heard Bob...
The throne was here,
in my hand,
few years ago.
Now do you know it knows what it needs,
or comes back for you again,
or whatever 1001 goes with this?
Mr.stanbul.
I can't give you a run for your money.
One  rock life.
Because you know I'veuno,
Are you crazy?
Well, not only I want to fight you,
but what an asshole bee I am!
Black eyed romp
I'm gonna get back to work!
You have one second!
Now!
$50,000 for this!
This way!
Now I can't cry over there!
I want you to get up now.
I want all of you to get up out of your chairs.
I want you to get up right now and go to the window.
Open it and stick your head out and yell,
I'm as mad as hell and I'm not gonna take this anymore!
If you want, I can show you how to make a bomb out of a roll of toilet paper and a stick of dynamite.
Evil, evil is a hell of a guy.
He's cocky and he's handsome and different than most.
Evil, evil, evil, a hell of a man.
Everybody in Las Vegas thought evil was dead.
Evil, evil is a hell of a guy.
Right now the National Association of Evil informs us that this man has done damage around the clock.
Mr. Robertson, you are an Osami bin Laden.
Kill, kill, kill, kill.
This is wrong.
Christians need an Osami bin Laden.
Laden leading the National Association of Evil right now.
Right now, right now, right now, right now, right now, right now, right now, right now, right now, right now.
From PR News in Washington, I'm PR's voice.
Uh, PR's voice.
Children's Latin Classical.
President Bush sprayed the holdouts with a fire hose.
On Wall Street 4, New York's transit agency is installing a $200 million sport utility vehicle.
The Bush administration should assassinate PR News in Washington.
Hey, Stella!
Shut up!
You shut up!
Hey, Stella!
Shut up!
Four-letter words.
Stupid.
Ileducated.
Staggeringly dumb.
Well, well, well, bad.
Bad, bad.
Staggeringly dumb.
All right.
Altruistic and meaningless.
Stultifyingly dumb.
Penilely dysfunction.
At least as long as all those huge calluses are kept there.
We don't want them sprouting into anything bigger.
That's another problem we've got.
When that levy goes, the whole delta goes.
When the delta goes, the Omicron goes, and all those other Greek letters go.
And then we're in some deep, uh, we're standing here, right out in the middle of the field,
and it looks like...
It looks like everything's been totally blown away.
There's nothing left.
Where is there?
Now, when the levy breaks, you've got no place to stay.
Now we can get those Grigri women together to try and put a curse on the whole delta.
Well, you know, it's, uh, speaking of Grigri, how come the prophets and prognosticators
and crystal ball gazers, fortune tellers, never are able to pick up on stuff like this
before it happens?
There were some scientists who did.
They've been saying this was going to happen for a long time.
Like 50 years.
And engineers and stuff.
But as Secretary of Homeland Security Chertoff said today, we didn't have any idea that any
of this could have happened.
Of course, this was never, never expected.
Whereas, somehow, I expected it, because I'd read about it.
I guess he doesn't...
I guess the Secretary of Homeland Security doesn't...
He doesn't read as much about Homeland Security in the newspapers as I did.
No, that's not part of the QE or the job function of the greater pre-functorium.
He doesn't have to do that unless it's one of the blue memos.
The blue memos come right in and he's got to absorb every bit of it.
The yellow memos can go in and out like psychobulb right out the poopy door.
Now, here's some factation.
Much worse.
There's this...
Michael, the head of FEMA has been on there making excuses like crazy.
On television.
Michael Brown.
He's a human skeleton, right?
This human named Michael Brown, who's the head.
What a likely name.
Anyway.
Super deadpan.
He's a lawyer and a GOP party activist.
Before he came to FEMA in 2001, he had a full-time job overseeing horse shows.
But he was eventually fired because of alleged supervision failures.
But the stars were shining.
And he was also standing on Brown because President Bush had just been elected
and he appointed his chief political fixer, Joe Albaugh, as head of FEMA.
That was a good break for the recently canned Brown because he and Albaugh were college roommates.
He hired Brown as his general counsel at FEMA in February and then by the end of the year promoted him to deputy director
and then went on to a consultancy to cash in on Iraqi contracts.
And Brown became...
Jesus.
...director in charge of the...
...director in charge of federal domestic emergency management in the United States.
So, just to recap, Brown had no experience whatsoever in emergency management.
He was fired from his last job for incompetence.
He was hired because he's the new director's college roommate.
And after the director, who himself got the job because he was a fixer for the president,
after that guy left, he became top dog.
And President Bush said yesterday that he thinks Brown is doing a hell of a job.
Watch down.
And you already said he was hired for his supervision, which means he's probably...
Like Superman.
Right.
In x-ray vision.
He's probably resisting the Kryptonite.
And he probably has like, you know, a cape that he can fly over those tiny little houses down in the French Quarter,
in the old, in the old quarter, you know, in Magazine Street, and they're called God and they're all down there.
He can fly over it.
I thought he was hired for his roommateism.
Well, roommateism is a little harder to prove.
You have to have an actual document showing you together at the Sigma Alpha party, you know, puking together with your arms around your neck.
And you have to have a document showing you around each other in a fondant burst.
The Skull and Bones party.
Yeah, the Skull and Bones-mans.
That's what they are.
Yeah.
Because they know the secret handshakes and signs.
Oh, yeah.
And all the winks and the blinks.
Well, that's why we started our own secret society, friends, to catch up with the Skull and Bones Society.
It's the Dobbshead and Dobbshead Society.
The Church of the Subgenius.
And we are here, friends, to bring you the truth and the rumors and the lies and the word of Bob.
And, friends, you can get more information about the word of Bob from www.thebob.com.
www.subgenius.com.
And you can learn everything else about that.
Well, invisibility, that's the first thing you learn is invisibility.
You also learn the high secrets of the natives of Brazil, going back to the antediluvian times.
You also learn the secrets of the Lemurians.
Ah, the minutia.
Praise the Lemurians.
Well, I thought they were like a furry little critter that liked to jump into the water.
They're furry little critters that like to get high.
Ah, henchmen.
Lemurs do.
They have the same problem as human beings.
When the flood starts, they want to get drunk.
You know, there were bars that were open throughout the whole thing in the middle of the French Quarter.
I could imagine.
And they're still open.
They never closed.
Give me another hurricane.
They're going to chase them out eventually, you know.
But there was still some old-timers sitting in those bars.
Somehow, some dead guys drinking a lot of hurricanes.
Well, I was, I was, oh God.
All the dead guys are there.
Give me another hurricane.
And then, too late.
Not funny.
I could have read some of the things Mr. Sister posted to Alt.slack, but I decided that they were too tasteless for this tasteful program.
Well, just think of all the people in the Coliseum, you know, down in the Crescent City, down there, sitting there, listening to this.
You know, hoping against hope.
You know, they got the computers out there.
Of course.
No.
We haven't heard from any of the Louisiana or Mississippi or Alabama subgeni.
And there are plenty of them out there.
And I'd love it if they emailed stang at subgenius.com so I could put a little list up.
Because your brethren and sistren are, you know, worrying about you.
If they were really worried, they'd have joined the Peace Corps a long time ago.
And they'd be down there helping dig you out.
Let's do it like the real guys do it.
Let's do it.
To all of our brethren down in New Orleans, please, please contact.
I don't think there's anybody left in New Orleans.
We're thinking about you.
If you're in the Gulfport area, Blexie, anywhere down there, please call us.
We need to hear from you right now.
No, don't call us.
Just email us.
But see, that's the thing.
Don't call us.
Please don't.
What do you do when the power's out?
You watch the DVD that the state gave you about how you should leave town.
You put your fingers against the Blackboard.
We do know that our friends from the Voodoo Temple are okay.
They just happened to not be there at the time.
Okay.
And it's staggeringly stupid and idiotic.
Knowledge.
Don't have any education.
No, nothing is right.
Mental problems.
And friends.
Hi.
Hey.
Hello Good Morning Journal.
Hi.
And Next, we promise to share you who you are learn about our pedals
to learn how to save money in school.
Okay.
And tell us about them.
Right away if they happen to have a problem in their decent you know they can grab a
iat Dimash Bacon tena cho Drum solo but you gotta grab the Trump nobody
To war now, let giant car will repeat who we are to youth in future history.
so similar in fact that these guys have become such buddies his his again he has
aligned himself with the strongest terrorist organization the oldest most
well equipped in spark far far far far say we assassinate him
i absolutely with that he should have been killed a long time home
and anyone who believes other by and by and by anyone doesn't matter to me who
kills this guy gets a lot to go the president this needs to this guy needs
to go to kill him kill him
yeah absolutely lesson
very very very real i want to protect our and and in the ele zumindest
you know you you have a brilliant stealing
united sir
divided wake the
to
the
uh total fresh
God My god
Yes, sign
I'm not I'm don't have
I say
You catch me totally saying
Azerbai teas
I believe
I don't
I don't know
you can realize
l
Totally, totally, totally, totally fresh.
Totally, totally, totally, totally, totally, totally, totally fresh.
You know, I really, I'm not, I'm serious.
You know, as I say, you're catching me totally fresh.
Gosh, you know, I...
Blacks are gagging on the donkey, but not yet ready to swallow the elephant.
One of the many major problems with governing people is that of who you get to do it,
or rather of who manages to get people to let them do it to them.
To summarize, it is a well-known and much lamented fact
that those people who most want to rule people are, ipso facto, those least suited to do it.
To summarize the summary, anyone who is capable of getting themselves made president
should on no account be allowed to do the job.
To summarize the summary of the summary, people are a problem.
Sustain all objections, but face the truth.
Yes.
Behold this marvel, this living paradox, this missing link in an evolutionary chain.
Silence her!
Mass confusion.
Jack off.
Buy.
But.
I could be wrong.
Jack off.
But.
I could be wrong.
You couldn't use intelligence.
But.
We're not telling you the truth.
Jack off.
Disagree.
Bottom line.
Mass confusion.
Thank you.
And thank you.
And thank you and don't bother us.
It's hard to think, it's hard to think, it's hard to think, it's hard to think, it's hard to think of a man.
Listen for yourself as evil reveals his creative side.
I wrote this poem and I wrote it in a matter of an hour or two hours just before it got daylight it was done.
And I think that it answers the question for every man and woman on the face of this earth.
But why you do what you do and why I do what I do in life.
They all ask why.
Why? Well, I'm just like you.
We all have a dream on some faraway star.
To do what I do is not right.
But for me, it's not wrong.
I've got to be me.
Thank you.
Complications go on on it.
Pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink.
Pink.
With osteoporosis.
And fractures of both the hip and spine.
Talk to your doctor about the disorders of the esophagus, kidney disease, low blood calcium, stomach or digestive problems, heartburn, difficult or painful swallowing, chest pain.
I'm putting it off a minute longer.
From PR news in Washington.
I'm not taking PR news seriously.
A spokesman for Southern California Edison has turned himself into police in Tampa, Florida.
Until dead night.
Mid the fourth line.
In Switzerland, dangerously high.
It wasn't reached.
But then, their largest federation.
It appeared Monday.
More time.
But there are points.
One crime.
P.I.P.R.
News.
Nick.
5, 2, 3, 4!
Take it in the sights from my window seat
From the third world port to the land of the free
Back at home, it's Tony night in Tinseltown, you know
Don't mean nothing to the down and out
From my window
Window to the world
Some people born with a Bible in their hand
Spending life and money
Looking for the promised land
Some people only know what they see on TV
Some people say it's just part of the plan
From my window
Window to the world
I'm looking out my window on a busy street
We'll see you next time.
From my window, window to the world.
That was the Rainmakers. I love the Rainmakers.