For men on the go, it's not what's in the pipe.
It's the pipe itself.
The Bob Dobbs Classic Meerschaum, hand-carved by the finest craftsmen in Malaysia.
This and other fine Bob Dobbs smoking accessories
cast a spell of their own for the discriminating smoker.
Bob Dobbs pipes never go out.
Of style.
Available at Kmart, Walmart, Target and Hypermart.
Too much church air.
I'm expanding my air.
It's... it's...
Praise...
And welcome to the Sergius Radio Ministry.
Order of Church.
Christa!
Yeah. Now, before we really get going with the sermon here,
I'd like you all to share something.
That's something we've done in Texas and Arkansas for many years.
It's just to kind of make people understand the solution.
The solemnity, the profundity of the whole thing.
Lower your heads and we'll share a sacred moment of noise!
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Can't go, can't go, can't go!
All right!
Ah, there we go!
Now I see some people are into it!
These people have slack!
The sound itself, it... it has a stink to it.
It's bad!
Ah...
Who's gonna job that greyhound, children?
Greyhound!
Greyhound gone!
Son of God, cut your middle to the middle!
Move as an every-born-a-savior!
Greyhound gone!
Always drive 55!
Ah!
Almighty Father cries first command!
Greyhound gone!
Horned cops in a lucky track!
Mary and Joseph wade at the station!
Greyhound gone!
They're hitching a ride to the Holy Nation!
Ah!
There's no smoking or chewing on the bus to Jerusalem!
There's a virgin Mary!
Prayin' on the old dentist boy!
We snagged the old breakin' hole!
He did burn us, she did!
We're talking to fires!
And I'm coming down for the man!
He's gone!
Hat-coil plan is headed for the border!
And they're running like hills from a federal court order!
Full ahead!
Exact change for the law!
And the police!
Three Hail Marys and on your knees!
Take it to the bridge now!
Ah!
He's gone!
W're going to spelling all her name on the register!
Ah ah!
Ah ha!
Brother Dollar and the boy on the White Horse!
Did you so ya anyway?
I have a little small thing to tell you!
A jive 꺼
It's thick
It hardened and lips weren't soft
I'm hanging on your desk for weeks, tell me you don't break it for me.
The influence is with our best advice, and I'm calling God for a thing.
He's gone.
And there's a subgenius down here with a bomb strapped to his chest, so you goddamn
well better enjoy it or he'll kill all of us.
He is Bob, ready for fun.
He wears a smile.
Everybody run!
Yep.
The damn bomb.
The decks are all running, dear friends.
That wonderful song that started the show out was Greyhounded Jordan by my brother Cleve
Donut Duncan.
I think his best song yet, making it perhaps the greatest song ever recorded.
Praise Cleve.
A lot more Cleve coming up tonight, so hang in there.
And from now on the first words I want to hear out of your filthy sewers is praise Bob.
Let me hear it.
Praise Bob!
Sound off like you got a pair.
Dear Bob, my life has changed completely.
because of your ministry.
Dear Bob,
my life has changed completely
because of your ministry.
Dear Bob,
my life has changed completely
because of your ministry.
Here's another one.
Dear Bob,
my life has changed completely
because of your ministry.
Bob needs an order to pursue his plan
for world domination.
I say, Bob
guides my hand in all things
and pays me off in pure slack.
Here's another one.
Dear Bob,
my life has changed completely
because of your ministry.
I dare you to kill me!
This is the mark.
You can always tell it's going to be
a Bob Righteous revival
when there's technical problems
and headaches
and when there's always a need
forivel pilgrims working together
in values.
hacia el This is the mark
that is going to be
礼 Поз twitter.com
and I 거 drilling
weight of hisだ
law
l sh Sicht
Well, I can't just stand like this in the dark.
Bob is the only drug. That's the only drug. You can't come down from Bob.
Just say no.
Just say no-ow.
That's it old man.
Oh yes dear friend.
Hey Bob. Hey Bob. Hey Bob.
Alright I can see we got the spirit.
The spirit is moving tonight.
This is the subgenius radio ministry hour of slack.
Spreading the seed word of J.R. Bob Dobbs.
High E-bopt of the church of the subgenius.
We'll have the air of my ears.
The way you love my ears.
It feels like my mother said.
My ears.
Oh God my ears.
The pain I can't get anywhere.
Thank you Bob.
Oh God my ears.
I can't stand it.
Thank you Bob.
I'm playing loud and proud.
Ah my ears.
I can't stand it.
I'm playing loud and proud.
Ah my ears.
It feels like my mother said.
I'm playing loud and proud.
Thank you Bob.
Alright.
Hare Krishna. Hare Rama.
There's a flower right in my mouth.
Well here we are at Columbia University's Halloween Spook House.
Recognize your voice man.
Hello.
You are.
He's a radio guy.
Yeah, yeah.
Dude, he's a radio guy.
I heard about it.
That would be you.
I've read that book.
I'm kind of one of the...
You gotta explain something to me.
Has Bob seen your $20, my friend?
Then you're still king in the eyes of Bob.
A king boy.
You got your year, $20.
You would earn you a seat.
Well, anyway, as I was saying,
some people think the church is like
some sign of the end times,
the mockers that will come at the end times,
and those people should be damn glad
we're helping to fulfill biblical prophecy.
To us, who've been with the church a long time,
it's a mystery.
We don't know what the hell this thing's gonna turn into.
If we did, it'd be boring to us.
It founded...
The church actually was founded in 1953
by that man, J.R. Bob Dogg.
Hey, Bob!
Bob founded his church
when he discovered that there was a conspiracy,
a conspiracy of normals
robbing away the slack
of the true subgeniuses
as opposed to human beings,
mere humes, as we call them.
It's sort of a do-it-yourself religion.
Bob founded his church
not on a rock,
but rather on sort of a shifty,
shifting sandy beach
of rock.
And it's a church of hypocrisy.
Every church must have its fair measure of hypocrisy.
And certainly we've got more,
we dole out more of it than anybody else.
Like I said, it's a non-organization
for non-joiners,
which makes it a little bit difficult
to raise funds at times.
But the point of it is that all subgeniuses,
people say,
well, what the hell is a subgenius?
There's no definition. They're all different.
That's what it means.
There is no typical subgenius.
If any two are alike,
one must die.
The only thing
that the subgeniuses have in common
is that they have nothing in common
with the conspiracy.
What we're trying to do
is tempt sinners
away from the devil.
Because Bob is a better tempter
than the devil.
However, where they go after that,
it's up to them.
The subgeniuses believe
in the God that doesn't want you
to believe in it.
And one of our missions,
the headquarters is in Dallas, Texas,
what they often call
the buckle on the Bible belt.
What we try to do is
unbuckle the Bible belt
so that its pants may drop
and it may gaze unflinching
upon its own private desire.
It's a war, dear friends!
It's a war against the normal!
And we aren't just the regular
kind of mutants we're talking about here.
These are more like the monsters.
The monster type of mutants.
It's the humans versus
the subgeniuses.
And the ironic thing is,
in the early days of the church,
80 million years ago in fabled Atlantis,
we helped to design the humans.
Probably our biggest mistake!
So, friends,
as I said, you know,
the fact that Jesus smoked
Chesterfields even though they didn't exist
2000 years ago,
is an example of our faith.
You don't use your mind
to think about your religion!
You just feel it! You feel it in your heart!
Bob sold it! I smoked it!
That settles it!
It's a question of faith!
This is like the sorrow
of world religions
putting those two C's
on both cheeks!
The bloody marks on the beefy seat
of the conspiracy!
It's like the Robin Hood of world religions
robbing from the lost,
who were mostly thieves to begin with,
and giving to the saved!
And if you, my friend, can make it,
can buy this book of the subgenius,
that videotape
on sale for only $30 today,
if you can make it
to the jungle encampment in Dobstown, Malaysia,
if you can survive
the acubating, the excrementation,
the pyroflatulation,
and the head-launchings, my friend,
you will be a weapon for Bob!
A weapon for J.R. Bob Dobbs!
A minister of Bob, praying for slack!
You and your subgenius fools
shall never defeat me, Bob Dobbs!
Oh, no?
Then have a taste of my
stark fist of removal,
Dr. Conspiracy!
Neegie's henchmen won't get any slack
when they face Bobco's new
Bob Dobbs action figure
with flying rocket fist,
flamethrower pipe,
and magic briefcase!
Too much is always better than
not enough when you collect
the subgenius universe!
Bobmobile not included, batteries
and some assembly required, action figure
sold separately from Bobco!
I am
a subgenius!
And
by that threat you will touch
what falls to this grade of man!
My power wasn't given to me
in exchange for prayer
or meditation,
I paid for it
in cold, hard American dollars!
Salvation you get for free
is worth just that,
doesn't you, queer?
Of course, your money
ain't worth jack anyway!
The conspiracy says to that
but a very important element
of your soul adheres
to those otherwise worthless,
unborn and unborn
The conspiracy says that
Bob needs in order to pursue
his plan for world domination.
I say, Bob
guides my hand in all things
and pays me off
in pure slack!
So I say to you
whips, you fools,
you dupes, you pigs,
give me your money!
You won't need it in the future!
The future offers you
naught but destruction!
You know what I mean?
I mean, I!
I dare you
to kill me!
I need to be, I mean,
I'm one of the good guys!
My cards shall prevail!
Let out the crazy
man inside you, he knows
what's what!
Smile when you call me a fanatic!
Or you say, me,
primate! Me,
overman!
You think I'm dumb, but you are blind
to the conspiracy that runs your life!
And you have your geniuses
running things for you
and you think they're gonna make things safe and simple!
And I'm gonna make things
safe and simple and easy for me!
And the entire
sub-genius race!
Even if it means wiping out
your sick society in total
with no more sentiment
involved in swatting the blind!
All this that we might survive
the end times!
You know why?
Because I am, I am,
I am, I am
a sot-tee!
I say, all you blow-dried,
white-wired, sipping designer
jean-clad, French film watcher,
walkman, toting hip-wimps,
a few house-coated inquirers,
a caravan-reading, trailer-in-camp,
bar-shopping, hair-curl, motorheads,
cock-holsters, all
you dupes! The corporate
big-money, oil-exploder,
tree-killing, land-raping, food-freezing,
desk-warmer, tri-laterally
establishmentarian
foe-hunting, back-stabbing,
poverty-spreading, farm-wielding,
meringue-heading, pencil-necked,
eraser-headed, politicals!
Kill the conspiracy!
Kill them and eat them!
And f*** their wives!
Who do you think you are?
What do you think you're doing?
Do you think you got it good?
Well dispose of those illusions!
Dispose of them all right now!
Because on July 5th, 1998,
at 7.30 in the morning,
you shall be judged!
You shall be judged!
Calculating alien races!
From your own!
If you don't want to
f***, you won't escape
their scrutiny!
You will fry!
Well we will party!
Bottle of Thunderbird, I'm gonna
get down and do it right in
Nazian Dirty!
You know why daddy?
You know why?
I'll f***!
Now some of you Christians out here
may be getting a little upset at what I'm saying
but I'd like to remind you that the founder of your religion
was not quite so
squeamish as some of you!
Yeah!
Let's go!
Ah yes dear
friends, this is
your host and
good prayer partner
Reverend Ivan Stank.
And uh
the amazing
rant that you heard
just a little while ago
was a
heavily censored version
of uh
of Brother Cleve
Duncan's testimonial
with background
sampled music by
Huge Voodoo
uh
more on that in a minute
I'm really sorry
about having to put cuts
in that rant
where the taboo verbal expressions
were excised
you may or may not have noticed
but you know
until the
prudish word fearing
conspiracy is defeated
well you know we're not allowed
to play certain words
because of the
assumption in some quarters
that some words
can actually
harm you
more than the images of
rape and violence
shown pretty much all the time
on television
uh
someday these things
will change under Bob
now
almost all of the rest of this
show
was uh recorded
uh this weekend
it's almost all material
recorded this last weekend
last weekend in New York
and New Jersey by myself
Reverend Ivan Stang and uh
especially the Reverend
Dr. D.K. Jones
as well as his
friend Reverend Bruce Grant
before
during and after a
subgenius revival at Columbia
University
uh
D.K. Jones uh
is uh
a subgenius musician you'll be
most familiar with
uh I guess from his score
for the subgenius video Arise
and in fact uh
the music that'll be coming up
and that you've heard some of already
uh the stuff with
preachers sampled bits of
preachers over it is by Bruce Grant
and D.K. Jones going under the name of
Huge Voodoo
the more linear instrumental
background music such as
the stuff behind us right now
is by D.K. Jones
and myself believe it
or not but mostly D.K. Jones
I would like
to thank all of those who
helped support the station
with their pledges
uh last
couple of weeks and especially to those who
helped with the pledge drive such as
Reverend Willa Dobbs
and the good
Pope as Cecilia and the bad
Reverend Trickster
Shaman
praise Bob
dear friends
stay tuned and uh
you'll eventually hear the
post office box number to write to
for information regarding
this mighty
church of the subgenius
whose uh radio
voice program your name is
now hearing the subgenius radio ministry
hour of slack
ha ha
praise
old Bobby
,
so that's that's our background track
yeah what I need
at 16
what I need to do is
I don't know what I'm
this is soundtrack for cleave walking home
lighted
yeah let's put this
the lonely cleave walking home
lighted night
he's had
one too many
and suddenly
he ran into the brick wall
oh my head
what happened
where am I
the last thing I remember
I was trying my first
hit of
frop
oh what has it done to me
and
I'm
I never should have joined that
church
it was
it was Bob
Bob
there's only one thing
left to do
I must
kill
Bob yes yes
that's the answer
it is
my duty
to kill
Bob
I must
kill
the
devil
come
kill
me
I
will
kill
me
Harvest what you can and what remains because tomorrow you'll be empty and alone.
I feel like I'm doing just the nothing.
Don't have a house, can't pay the rent.
We live like we believe it.
I feel like I'm doing just the nothing.
It somehow sends, I don't know what it is, but it just works so well for Sylvia.
But what happens when that loose, easy, so-called tramp is your own sister?
I wouldn't want to lie now.
How did Bob strike his first million?
When a man like you paid a dollar for one of these bumpers,
or ten dollars for this amazing poster,
it's true.
It's true. Bob's church was built on a ten dollar bill.
And it's ridiculous to think we're going to give it away
just because a bunch of lazy mutants think they own the planet.
Bob?
There are a lot of different ways.
How about getting a copy of the Economicon?
Is that spells?
Oh, we can't know.
If every Hobart or Pink Boy had one of those,
there'd be so damn many old ones and guardian demons coming up out of it.
So are there any rituals?
You'd be like ghostbusters over here.
Yeah, he's a warrior.
I'm a dragon.
I can't roll.
Uh, I'm casting out a false prophet.
Bob?
Yeah?
Doug Quaid is here to see you.
Yeah, I'll be right out.
Okay.
Now, help me out here, Doug.
You were interested in a memory of, uh...
Buy and be saved!
Give unto Bob that which is Bob's.
Render unto him that which...
before he renders you like a...
pink boy in a slaughterhouse.
I swear.
What are you?
Uh...
To be perfectly honest with you, Doug,
if outer space is your thing,
I think you would be much happier with one of our Saturn cruises.
No, I'm telling you, Doug, your brain will not know the difference.
And you're gonna love this, Doug.
We offer you a choice of alternate identities during your trip.
So, what's your choice?
Is it your first trip?
Mm-hmm.
Good evening, Doug.
Hey, Paul, what do you want for Christmas?
Benny, what were you doing launching that bleeding hat on a Thursday?
Why was you wearing them big green straps?
You know you should not do that, Benny.
Take it easy, Doug.
Okay.
Doug?
Doug, I'm gonna call a doctor.
Doug.
Doug, there's something I want you to know.
You were the best assignment I ever had.
You wouldn't shoot me, would you, Doug?
After all we've been through?
If things have gone wrong, I'm talking to myself,
and you've got a wet towel wrapped around your head.
No, no, we're sorry, Bob.
We didn't mean it.
We didn't mean it to...
We won't call you anymore, Bob.
Please don't drop that bomb on us.
No, Bob, don't do it, please.
When's that bomb gonna get here, Bob?
I already filled up my will.
Oh!
Oh, it was just a little one, Bob.
Me, gee, Bob.
Fuck Bob.
Where in the world can me, gee, be?
Niggy?
Where is to, Niggy?
Where is to?
I know you are there, Niggy.
You're not going to get me this time, Niggy,
because I have the gun, and the diamonds,
and the map, and the documents,
and I have the device.
Yes, I have the device.
And you are foiled finally, Niggy.
Niggy?
Where did you go?
Where did you go, Niggy?
You can't fool me this time, Niggy.
I signed the papers already.
You can...
What?
No!
What is this?
The... the tapes.
The blank.
The documents, they've fallen to dust.
The negatives.
What about the negatives?
They're... they're gone.
They're gone.
I had the negatives.
I had the device.
I had the girl, the gun, the map.
But... but...
But, Niggy has them now.
I should have listened in the temples of the old ones
when they told me.
They told me that for every Bob particle
there must always be a...
a Niggy particle.
Why didn't I listen?
Oh... oh, the... the pain.
Kid's sake, I could have had it all.
I could have had everything, but...
but Niggy has it now.
Ah.
Finger down.
I'm not going to get the formal training for coming over, man.
I skirted him.
As many as I can.
Sure.
I skirted the... the formal training.
I sort of came in at a level.
Oh, man, I... I laid the first cornerstone.
It was a human skull.
A human skull, not a subgenius skull.
A big difference.
Have you ever seen,
Have a Nice Day spelled out in skull of normal people?
It's a... it's sweet.
It's kind of neat.
Or Save the Earth spelled out in the chopped off arms
of... of, uh, Peruvian peasants.
It's a joyful sight.
It's key, man.
Yeah.
It's... it's so neat.
It's like the new age.
Don't be afraid.
Don't want to...
Don't want to hurt you.
Shh.
It's all right.
It's okay.
Come on out.
I got her.
Ow!
Here.
Watch her.
Don't let her go.
She's coming to kill you.
What?
She laid out here.
Where'd she go?
She's coming down the bottom.
Down the what?
Down here.
Here.
Here, here.
That's the issue.
Keep back.
Don't scare her.
Grab her, man.
We're gonna lose her.
Damn it.
Don't be afraid.
Okay, un storied.
There we go.
The
I don't know if this situation has ever happened.
I would kill an animal.
I would, I would, I would kill an animal.
Wait. No you don't.
It's okay.
You're gonna be alright now.
Shh.
Easy. Easy.
It's gonna be okay.
It's alright. You're gonna be okay.
You know there was this woman in line ahead of me at the post office this morning.
She was wearing that new Connie Dobbs perfume, you know?
And, yeah.
And, there were a lot of new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new, new.
And, I don't...
I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't know.
It's too late now, baby.
The time...
Has already begun.
I...
I don't think I can...
Where is our lucky groom and poor pathetic bride?
The poor martyred bride.
Let's see, I guess if y'all would see Brandy and Glenn.
If y'all could stand.
Yeah, right there.
Woo!
I'm more used to preaching in tents.
Ah, yes.
Hey, if Reverend Sun Young Moon can marry
thousands of people,
thousands of people who've never even met,
then a Church of the Subgenius short-duration marriage
could be the answer.
Yeah, as a matter of fact,
this is one thing you can do as a subgenius minister.
You can do legal weddings.
You can also do the short-duration marriages.
This certificate here,
produced by Reverend Buck Naked in Dallas,
can come in very handy.
Because the short-duration marriage can last for an hour,
a night, a week, a year, whatever.
And the divorce,
divorces are cheap.
They come with the certificate.
All right.
Anybody else want to get married tonight?
Step right up.
Get your holy short-duration marriage certificate here.
Test your mettle and win the little lady
a rubber Snoopy doll.
Guaranteed, friends,
to absolve and sanctify
all otherwise illicit couplings.
Free short-duration divorce
if you're not completely satisfied.
All right, now you two stand together
and face me.
I like that.
All right.
Let's be solemn now here.
Do you, Glenn,
take, swear to tell the truth,
the whole truth and nothing but the truth,
and tell, so help you Bob?
I do.
Do you, Brandy,
swear to tell the truth, the whole truth,
and nothing but the truth, so help you Bob?
Yeah.
All right, good. Okay.
Now, how long do you wish for this period of sanctified couplings to last?
One year.
One year?
Oh, yeah, that's right.
You told me that.
One year.
Me.
You sure?
All right.
Oh, yes.
Dearly beloved,
we are gathered here today in the presence of J.R. Bob Dobbs
and insert other deity names here,
any other deities,
to join this man, Glenn,
and this woman, Brandy,
in the bondage.
Of holy, of matrimony,
for better or for worse, but not for law.
Do you feel the spirit?
Yes!
Then put your hands on each other.
If there are any here who feel this man and this woman
should not be joined temporarily,
just hold your peace,
because we don't want to hear about it.
No, we don't!
All right, now, put, hold tight, hold tight now.
Oh, lovely, lovely couple.
Do you, Glenn, take this woman, Brandy,
to be your lawful wedded wife
in short-duration subgenius matrimony
to have and to hold for richer or poorer
in sickness and kinkiness
for the next year?
Say, say, I do.
I do!
Do you, Brandy, take this man, Glenn,
to be your lawful wedded husband
in short-duration subgenius matrimony
to have and to hold for richer or poorer
in sickness and kinkiness
for the next year?
Say, I do.
I do.
All right.
Now, shake on it,
and say, it's a deal.
Woo!
Right now!
Now, get out,
oh, he's not,
oh, yeah, we're not over,
we're not finished yet.
We got a really important part,
the symbolic part's coming up.
Get out the ring.
You do have a ring, don't you?
Oh, the best man,
the best man here,
let's give a hand for the best man.
Yeah!
All right, um,
we take this ring,
give that to, uh, to Glenn,
and Glenn, you, uh,
and she inserts, uh,
her finger into the hole.
We take this,
we take this ring as a holy symbol
of the estate of marriage
as well as of the pole going deep
into the hole repeatedly, obviously.
By the authority invested in me,
by J.R. Bob Dobbs,
in defiance of the laws of the state
and of nature,
I pronounce you man and wife
for the next one year.
You must,
you must now kiss each other,
right in front of all these people.
Praise Bob!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
This is so romantic.
Ooh, ooh, yeah!
Take it off.
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Praise Bob!
You are now duly authorized
and excused for sexual couplings
of any perverse and unspeakable kind
for a period of one year.
Ashes to ashes, dust to dust,
it is done, amen, and a women.
Praise Bob!
The felicity of all marriages,
and of all the rock and roll music,
is obviously a meaning
by which the white man
is purely driven
I'm in love with a nigga.
If you talk to the average teenager of today...
If you talk to the average teenager of today and you ask them what it is...
The obscenity of...
If you talk to the average teenager of today and you ask them what it is about rock and roll music that they like...
The first thing they'll say is the beat, the beat, the beat.
Why I believe that is because I know how it feels when you sing it.
I know what it does to you.
The evil feeling that you feel when you sing it.
Why I believe that is because I know how it feels.
I know the...
The last position.
The end.
The beat.
Well, if you talk to the average teenager of today and you ask them what it is about rock and roll music that they like...
The evil feeling that you feel when you sing it.
If you talk to the average teenager of today...
The savage teenager of today.
The beat, the beat, the beat.
The evil feeling that you feel when you sing.
Why I believe that is because I know how it feels when you sing.
The spirit of the living can't be the...
Come out! I said come out of this body!
Come out of those muscles!
Come out of those bones!
Come out of that heart!
I said come out!
I said come out Satan!
In the name of Jesus!
Go!
The same I will!
The devils of hell!
Why I believe that is because I know how it feels when you sing.
I know what it does to you.
I know the evil feeling that you feel when you sing.
I know the lost position that you get into when you feel it.
I know the future and the record that you bring the faith back along.
Even someone who has a
The voice in your head¢
With a texture in Your heart.
Now, one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Come out, Arthur. Come out of this boat. Come out of this boat. Come out of this boat.
Come out of that horse. Arthur, come out. Arthur, come out.
In the name of Jesus.
Come out of this boat.
That's a cold, cold kind of hell.
Cold in here.
Wish I could light this here pipe.
They gave me all the frappy in the world.
And it's too cold to light this pipe.
Oh, Bob, where are you now?
Why'd you leave me in the hands of me?
However, Bob will offer you eternal salvation or triple your money back.
Which unfortunately gives some the image in their minds of Bob standing in the gates of hell handing out $60 checks.
Well, that's real funny.
I hope you boys are having a good time.
I bet you thought I was a good guy.
I bet this old church thing of yours is gonna be big, big fun.
Big barrel of laughs.
Oh, yeah.
I bet you thought you were gonna be some kind of high school lawyer with that Bob fellow of yours.
Well, you're looking at a pretty damn long eternity.
Oh, by the way, here's that triple your money back.
Uh...
It's, uh, what, $60?
One for you, Smith, one for you, Jones.
And, uh, don't let this deter you from doing business with us again.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
You're listening to the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
For free information on Bob Dobbs and the Church of the Subgenius,
send a self-addressed stamped envelope to
Got your pencil ready?
Bob, Post Office Box 140306, Dallas, Texas 75214.
That's Bob, P.O. Box 140306, Dallas, Texas 75214.
Stay tuned and praise Bob.
Ah!
Woof!
Ah...
Wellman...
Dennis locked me in this little box.
I can't feel anything.
I can't see anything.
It's totally black.
I have no sensation in my hands.
I don't know if I'm moving or what.
I'm just in this little box.
He said I could talk to you.
He said you know what to do if you wanted to help me.
Oh, God, help me, Peter Wellman.
I promise I'll...
I'll pay you all the royalties.
royalties that I didn't tell you about. And whatever you want. I mean, anything. Tevis,
you can have Tevis. Just get me out of this box, Wellman. Please, no, no. Don't believe what Paul
told you. It's all a lie. It's all a lie. Whatever I did, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Let me out of the
box, Wellman. I can't. This is a bad show, Wellman. This is a real bad show.
No. She says she'd almost rather see me in Tevis than in nothing at all. Bright, perky,
almost psychedelic. The Tevis line of fine men's undergarments. Underwear you'll never change.
Sweet talk me all you want, but you'll never get me out of my Tevis.
The Tevis line of fine men's undergarments. Underwear you'll never get me out of my Tevis.
I am a 🎵
Thank you.