I'm afraid.
Be quiet.
There he is.
Look at his face now, David.
Yes.
I see it.
It's composed.
It looks human again.
Perhaps we're not meant to tamper with the natural.
Self-genius.
Powerful.
Quiet.
He's looking this way.
It's me, though!
No!
The god damn it!
He's still coming!
The story of Bob goes back in time to the very beginning of time.
And it's a tale that keeps repeating itself throughout the centuries.
Dr. Darkstriven.
Awesome things happen at Dr. Darkstriven.
I got engaged at Dr. Darkstriven.
Wow.
Really?
Yep.
Did you really?
Yeah.
I lost my virginity at Dr. Darkstriven.
Aww.
I think it was 11X day.
Yeah.
That was wild.
Embarrassing.
Messy.
It can be.
I think that was what happened.
Wait, wait, wait.
That's what he told me it was.
That's what Bob said.
Was it the...
Congratulations, Daggy.
You just lost your virginity.
The other virginity.
Is that what it was?
Oh.
And he left me 50 cents, too.
50 centavos.
Christ, Bob.
Well, that just shows you got something for nothing.
Yeah.
And he took away my virginity for only 50 cents.
How about that, ladies and gents?
Oh.
Really now, are you guys in this cult business just for the bucks?
Yeah.
guitar solo
Hello? Hello?
Can you get that up a little?
Hey, Bob.
Are you alive?
Let's all jump on Bob's back and talk to him.
Yes!
Hey, Bob.
Turn it up, baby.
Come on, turn it up, Bob.
Oh
Search for the self
psyche the soul the head and alter ego
God loves sheep and nudists there this obscure and obscure use
Oh
The best TV Western
Pardon me say so
Oh
Love the people you represent to go on a cell right down
While it going was good
You watch them suffer while you sold your crime
You're a bad excuse for the worst idea you're gonna buy yourself
Never going back
What just disappear
Nην
Oh
Well, what's that all about?
It's time for a call to call
I don't wanna be, I don't wanna be part of this
One thousand billion
Seven one billion pounds
Well, what's that all about?
I think I'm caught in love
I don't wanna be, I don't wanna be part of this
I've got the boys of steel
If you'd wake up and feel good
You have to keep it surreal, likes
What if I make your leg next to it?
Then I can mess with my barbarians
Take care of my life
I'll call this time you're shoving
I'll put your own bread back up in your oven
Et cetera
In the scheme of things
It doesn't matter
Watch your thing, I don't give a ton
To show the way
To buy the way
Depending on your leaning
To reverse it in their meaning
But your liberty
Is my incarceration
How you doing? What's going on?
It's f*****g
Rock Creek Park
Broccoli
Self-leveling concrete
F*****g
With 5-2-1 penalties
RoboNet Twitter
Our f*****g
Only nature
F*****g up in the c**k
Earth, take it off
F*****g, it's by the water
F*****g, it's by the sea
It's like a treasury socket
But on your own it's Wetter
On your own it's Wetter
I'm on my own with my own name
On my own it's Wetter
We're coming after you, dude.
We're coming and we're bringing hell with us.
One thousand billionaires
and one billion miles of feet.
Well, what's that all about?
I think I'm copping out.
I don't want to be, I don't want to be part of this.
You guys think I'm crazy.
You think I'm crazy.
I could be bütün schw teefe's
Dürer
Juncker
Toilet
Florian
tö скор
St. Louis
ceviche
The best TV westerns.
Diane, Diane, Diane, Diane.
Watch him, Joe.
You know, that's real pretty.
It's real pretty, for sure.
Yeah.
Nope.
Aren't you gonna smile?
Oh, come on.
Please.
Nope.
Well, sit down, sir.
What's that supposed to mean?
Oh, I think I have time to do just a little bit of credits here.
What's in the background is the Rudy Schwartz project.
A ditty called Send In Shutwell.
Lemur did the collages that we're hearing tonight.
Except for the one that had music with it.
Obscurum per obscurus.
That was Slackmaster Sarcastra with all the funny bouncy sounds.
The guitar instrumental.
The guitar instrumental at the beginning was the amino acids.
And the roll neck sweater song, which is partly in what sounds like Scottish or Irish brogue or something,
is from Pilgrim Speakeasy, a project of Reverend Roger Rogge in the UK somewhere.
Anyway, on with the Rudy Schwartz project.
We'll be back soon.
slash.
madre.
Thank you.
It's sort of touching and then after that we'll be funny again.
Okay?
See you on the saucers.
Yep.
guitar solo
Do you see what I see?
Is the group all annihilation?
Will we hell today?
Maybe red horizon
Wonder of blackened day
Love of murderer
tvnew beauty
let begin
highlight
Who am I insurance,
Uh, yesterday?
And keep sufferin'
Outwards the Milky Way
Outwards the direction
We are on our way
On the moon we escape vessels
Sex, fantasies and very squid for everyone
Subgenie journey to that distant shore
You've got your money
For a little ride
This is taking us away
To the new bit funny
Say the car's been tied
To the night at the end
Of the old night
To the new bit funny
To the night at the end
To the old night
To the new bit funny
Thank you.
Yes.
With the President riding in a tank with his head just sticking out above the turret, wearing a helmet, a very distinctive appearance for a future Commander-in-Chief to assume the elective office, the highest in his country.
And it's a beautiful spring day. We have wonderful weather. And here is Dr. Philo Drummond.
Yes, there he is riding his, his, what is this? He's in a tank?
No, it's some kind of military vehicle.
Military vehicle.
Is this what we want?
This may be the brand new Milton Bradley vehicle, which cost taxpayers over $70 trillion.
It's a very small vehicle.
It scares small children and young girls.
His helmet is too small for him.
Yes, I think he sort of grew into it.
He never took it off since his electoral defeat, the first time he ran for President.
I don't know if I can follow him into a war zone.
Well, you may not have to.
Or a war.
Zone.
Or not.
Now that we are fighting a five-front war, it's necessary to get even more tanks in production.
It's a war of ideas. It's beyond the front.
So, along with President Dukakis, I and many of the palpitating Americans say, tanks for the memory.
Yes, tanks are a rough side in any man's war, but when they're on your side, well, that's the way to fight it.
We fight a war every day of our lives. A war of me over I.
We've always been at war with East Asia. What's the matter with you?
I'm going to defeat that one so that I can prevail.
East Asia.
Is our enemy...
Well, me gives away the secrets.
And we have to sacrifice them.
When it's over, we can build some better buildings and have better food.
Use more water the way we used to in the old days.
I'm really thirsty. I'm going to get a drink of water.
Sorry.
Where's the clean water around here? Somebody left that dog bowl in the street.
That werewolf piddled.
How are we going to get a drink of water?
Well, you can't.
And that wolf piddled.
I think it just flew out there. I don't think an alien actually came along and pushed it over.
Use this desalination purification tablet.
First of all, it's been identified.
Which show is this, you guys?
The Denning Puddle of Puddle.
Which show? I'm confused.
I can't tell.
Which show is this? Is this the show with...
Is this that Lonesome Cowboy Dave show?
Is it Deuteronomy 69712-5233?
Is it not in...
Is this the winning lotto number?
No, that was the cage number back at old Reformatory 6 where I spent my early days.
Well, it was actually the ward number.
The Halcyon.
I don't want to talk about that. I'm sorry.
I don't want to talk about anything.
We can change the subject then.
Oh yeah, you had something to talk about.
Oh yeah.
The...
We heard that...
Don't tell Mikey Alcandor about all of our women because he's going to steal them all away from us.
I guess...
Well, from you guys because I am one of those women so...
So, you know...
You're talking about Michael Alcandor, the crazy guy?
Yeah.
Invades the subgenius IRS channel?
Yeah, he's going to steal all the women...
He said.
Yeah.
But he found out that there's really attractive women and I don't...
You're going to steal the male monkeys.
I don't even think he knows about the new girl yet either.
I don't even think that he knows about Reverend Cinnamon.
She's really new.
She's really nude, too.
I saw some pictures of her.
She is jaw-dropping.
Yeah.
I don't know.
Maybe we shouldn't put her on the sub-site.
She's like Susie's friend, Julie Newmar.
Yeah.
She might be too pretty to break the sub-site.
Julie Newmar is an antiquated reference to a movie star, isn't it?
Yeah.
Too Wong Fu.
Yeah, sure.
She's Susie the Flusie's best friend.
For real?
No, not at all.
Just the opposite, in fact.
But that's why I said that.
It's okay, though, Dave.
I think it's okay.
Well, it's not bosom buddies anyway, because Susie the Flusie has a pair of tarantulas on her, like a little...
She's been posting pictures of herself.
Yeah, with the bosom and everything.
I remember.
It's the big, brilliant freeze of 2012.
I remember her face.
Remember those sub-genius girl calendars?
And we even had beefcake calendars.
That was before your time, baby.
It was before my time.
There were like five years' worth of them.
I want to see the beefcake calendars.
I'm in the beefcake calendar, believe it or not.
Wait, never mind.
I don't want to see it then.
I was a lot skinnier then.
And I'm in disguise.
Yes.
Sorry.
As a male human being.
Were you in it, Dave?
No.
No, Dave.
I was in the reptile section a few months afterwards.
And they thought it was going to go with the big G, you know.
I'm trying to find background music to play, but it looks like my themes from SF fantasy and horror is missing.
He's frantically searching through CDs.
Yeah, real professional here.
I'll put on this one labeled Monsters.
We've used that a lot.
Also, he left his hat sitting over here.
Right next to me.
And I'm pretty sure if I put the hat on, I will get some sort of magic powers.
Or I'll start seeing Bob everywhere.
And I don't know if I'm ready for that.
No, most likely you'd start seeing little white snowflakes all over your shoulders whenever you wear black clothes.
That is weird.
Okay, now I really don't want to put it on.
I had a dream that Bob was like a pizza delivery guy.
And the pizzas were like plastic and stuff like that.
They weren't real pizzas.
But he delivered them and collected money anyway and stuff.
And it was snowing like this radioactive snow.
It's synchronistic, isn't it?
Was it the iodine?
1-3-1.
1-3-1 snow?
Oh, yeah.
That's my favorite pizza topping.
You guys get a lot of that in Ashtabula, right?
Well, I think you're getting a lot of it where you are since the tides have been corrected by the Ubermensch.
Oh, okay.
That would explain the why.
I think you're getting the right spots all over me, I guess.
Hey, we had the big WCSB Halloween masquerade ball last night.
I know.
You all got naked.
I wasn't invited.
And there was a picture of a chicken on the roof.
You were invited.
Dave, you're always invited.
You have a perma-invitation.
Just like the perma-wave in my brain.
Yeah.
Like the perma-later in your brain.
Perma-wave.
The perma-later.
Perma-later.
How come that's funny?
I forgot what a perma-later was.
You know what a perambulist is, don't you?
No.
Yeah, sure, sure.
Perambula.
Does anybody know what a perambula is?
No, Mr. Dave.
It's a baby buggy from the 1800s.
They call them perambula ears.
Oh, right.
Okay.
Well, to perambulate was sort of like to drive around.
When cars were first invented, they would say, let us go out and perambulate.
Is that going to be on the test, Professor Dave?
Unfortunately, there will be no test this year.
There will be an in-class function in which all will be forced to participate.
There will be no...
I have something to brag about, and I can't wait.
For my 61st birthday, I moshed.
I moshed at the WCSB party last night when the last band was playing.
I put on my gladiator monster hunting outfit, which is real and has a real hard metal shield on it with a big dob's head in the center.
And I went down there, and Princess Wee and I were dancing around near the mosh pit.
And the moshing youths were eyeballing that big dob's head shield I was carrying.
And we all kind of realized...
I realized all at once that I would be the perfect thing to smash into at high speed.
And they were very polite, violent moshers, and they would make eye contact with me and make sure I was ready for them.
And then they'd come slamming into the shield.
And in fact, knock me down once or twice.
Uh-huh.
Wow.
But I was real proud of myself and had to brag because I had moshed with the youth.
And see, moshing wasn't even invented when I was of concert going.
Oh, you foolish liar.
That's not true.
Well, they didn't know about it...
You couldn't even dance if you wanted to.
They didn't know of it in Dallas until after people in the Northeast had been doing it for five or six years.
Yeah, I've been wearing these big Dr. Martin's boots and clobbering each other in front of stages.
That's all it is.
Well, I've seen it a lot more violent than at this one.
They were really well behaved.
It's the late 70s resurrection.
It's the early 80s resurrection.
It seems like a defeats purpose to be so well behaved.
And you performed there just as you would have when you were 30, 50, 20 years late.
No, I was a dad in the 80s.
I couldn't go moshing around.
Well, you had no thyroid gland.
Children your age should never go out without the right clothing.
I was a baby in the 80s, so I didn't mosh at all.
And you're still a babe now.
She's my Reverend Baby.
Yes.
I asked my mother if she knew what moshing was.
And she said, yeah, that's when they swan dive off the stage.
And the people in the audience carry them all around.
And I said, well, it's kind of like that.
That's a related thing.
And it also means eating, right?
Mosh.
No, that's not moshing.
I get confused between the mosh and the mosh.
I meant to nosh last night.
And found myself being tossed around by youths.
Yeah.
That's what you should be doing on your 60th birthday is noshing.
You were noshing later.
Speaking of the stage dive thing, there was, oh, God, what show?
It's the band Ace of Spades.
You guys know the band?
No, I know nothing.
Yes, you do.
Oh, my God.
My brain just went blank.
I know Ace of Spades.
I just can't think of the name of the band.
The Ace of Spades.
I've only heard the Duke of Uke ever.
Ace of Spades.
Yeah, I know.
The Duke of Uke performs that at X Days.
Oh, my gosh.
That's the only version I've ever heard.
How am I not remembering?
Anyway, they were playing.
That one band.
And somebody climbed up the monitors and stage dove, and they immediately put their
instruments down and stopped playing and just walked off the stage.
Wow.
That is good.
So they don't like it so much anymore.
Wow.
I guess.
I had a similar experience where, an actual experience where I got later fired from a
band for stuff like these.
I used to drink a lot when I was playing and stuff.
And so I did an Iggy dive off the stage.
And there was a table right below me pretty far.
And they had amassed all their beer bottles in the middle of the table with some sort
of anal little punk rock deal or something.
And I could see myself as I fell off and was like,
Motorhead.
It was Motorhead.
I don't know what it is about being on the radio that makes me forget every band name
that I've ever heard.
Oh, it was Motorhead.
Motorhead.
Yeah.
Also, speaking of which, you should-
I think I've heard bands just in time to save my life from being impaled on the beer bottles.
That was really her-
Heathen's the Hawkwind thing.
Beer bottles are hard to fall on.
Oh, right.
Now that we're talking about bands-
We have to talk about an election.
And it's not the scary one that's even scarier than Halloween.
It's a-
It's scary enough.
It's more of a petition.
Our friend Reverend Heathen-
Yes.
Had pointed out, had noticed that the band Hawkwind was not mentioned in the Rock and
Roll Hall of Fame.
And he thought it was high time that they get mentioned.
And I do too.
I've never-
We agree.
I don't actually have any of their albums.
Just agree.
But-
I agree.
Thank you, Dave.
He started a petition at moveon.org.
And I'm going to give you the tinyearl.com code for anyone who wants to get the band
Hawkwind on the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame.
Got that pencil ready?
Got that pencil ready, friends.
That tinyearl is tinyearl.com.
That's T-I-N-Y-U-R-L.com.
Slash, and then here's the hard part.
McKay-Fackle.
Which is spelled M-K-8-F-A-Q-L.
No, maybe it's a one instead of an L. I'm not sure.
M-K-8-F-A-Q-L.
It sounds like a mind controller.
It's got M-K there.
And either L or one.
It's a mind controller.
M-K-L for experiment.
I like M-K-9.
That was a really good Mortal Kombat game.
Is the link found on subgenius.com?
That was also a CIA mind control experiment.
M-K-9?
No, I played so many hours of that game, though.
Anything with M-K in front of it.
I know, but that's why you're mind controlled.
Anything with M-K in front of it will have a digital future and minimal prosperity.
Darn it.
And an expanded forehead.
Daggum it.
Really, really, really, really big, like, donkey ears.
Consorn it?
Nonsense!
Stuff and nonsense.
Tarnation.
Who called the greatest librettist of the 20th century, Pinocchio, a hoax in the doddler?
Or, um, what did you say?
I don't know.
I don't know what you said.
What?
She's making fun of Pinocchio, man.
I wouldn't do that.
I'm a hardcore Disney fan.
Monstro is my favorite.
I stand by it.
Pinocchio is a really scary movie.
I don't know.
It wasn't the one that traumatized me.
That was Snow White.
But Pinocchio has that.
Yeah, that traumatized me.
The kids start smoking cigars and cough themselves into donkeys.
Yes.
And that's like a, don't go to that movie on acid kids.
Oh, no.
What's way worse than that is the pink elephants in Dumbo are, it's horrifying.
Even to a sober person.
Yeah, you feel trapped.
Yeah, it's pretty actually unbelievable how, I forgot how intense it was, but I think it
scared me as a child because I had no idea why it was happening.
You didn't know what the DTs were or hallucinations or anything?
Well, like I vaguely understood the drinking, but I just didn't understand why they were
spending like seven minutes of the movie on a really weird tripped out thing like that.
Okay.
Yeah.
All these things are variables.
I mean, they make sense, but they are.
No, you are.
No.
You are.
No, you are.
No, you're kids be quiet back there.
I'm going to dump you out.
I don't like something that I need.
Turn around, go home.
You want to go to Disneyland or you want to keep fighting?
I want to go to, you don't promise those things idly.
I'm not going to play.
You're going to play.
I'm sorry.
Well, Dr. Sinister just wandered in, too.
It was a malignant odor.
I could smell it.
I want to hear it.
Because my show is called Sinesthesia, my voice has a very particular smell.
It has kind of a synthetic, a lacritude built on three common elements.
Nice color, too.
Pink oil?
Definitely, definitely part of it.
Not stink oil, snake oil.
He said pink oil.
Is that what they're selling these days?
Yeah, we should be pink oil salesmen.
We should sell pink oil to the pinks.
It's think oil.
Or press the oil from the pinks.
Yeah.
Some listeners may not understand that pink, the term pink is a derogatory term for normal people used by subgeniuses who like to think they're abnormal.
How do we get ambergris from them, though?
From the pinks?
Yeah.
You have to go to that one particular part of the ocean where they swim the most, and then it'll actually just wash up on shore after.
No, that's diapers.
Yeah, that weird brown foam.
Yep.
That's what the diapers created, that weird brown foam.
No.
I'm sorry.
That was a joke.
There it is.
Fully placed, just like that rocket ship through your nostrils.
Rocket away.
We can't rocket away until we get home.
No.
And then we'll probably blow up on the launch pad.
Most of them do.
For those of you who don't know what the reference in Spanish is meaning, he's saying that he's in a secret laboratory where he's living right now in his home.
He has a number of the very sterile monkeys that he plays with and conducts experiments.
So he's going to have a lot.
He's going to have a lot of fun when he rockets away.
You like ponies?
You like monkeys?
Maybe I use too many monkeys.
Oh, well.
I've just been thinking about being one for a long time.
One monkey don't stop no show.
You've kind of had monkeys on the mind this evening, Dave.
You've mentioned monkeys several times.
Yeah, I've been wanting to be one.
I thought, like, what a beautiful life, you know.
They just come around and grab fruits and berries and coconuts and things like that and have sex all over the place.
Did you know this?
They found.
Monkeys have little factories where they make where they sharp.
They'll get together and find a sharpening place and sharpen sticks.
And after a while, the little utensils they make, it starts to look like a factory because, you know.
There are those monkeys that actually cook.
You're talking about the U.S. House of Representatives.
The monkeys that cook.
I mean, it's very primitive cooking, obviously, but they get like the they get like the big whatever they eat.
And they peel like the skins off of it and they leave it sitting in the sun for about a week.
And then they have these little holes that are bore into rocks and they put these big things or some kind of nut into into the little hole in the rock.
And then they sit there and smash it with a bigger rock or a rock that they can hold.
And that's how that's how they eat.
That's what they do.
This is like a whole cooking process to this whole thing.
And the kids watch them do it and sit there and like try to practice and learn.
It's, you know.
Are you talking about monkeys of a specific?
Kind.
I think they're actually chimps.
I was pretty sure they were monkeys.
I didn't think they were apes.
The question is, do they let it ferment and then get drunk on it?
That's that's the mark of intelligence.
That's what apes do.
That's why bees were attacking us in October, because it seems like even bees have discovered fermenting fruit at harvest time in these climes.
You find bees get real aggressive and bite and sting you and so forth.
You know what?
I'm referring to.
At Autumn Fires, we found out what happens to a bee if you give it church air.
Really?
Yeah.
Nitrous oxide?
Laughing gas?
I don't know what that is, but I know church air.
Church air.
Right.
You inflicted that on a poor bee.
Did it laugh?
Did it fall over and laugh?
Did it go, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah?
It got really slow and its little antlers just drooped down.
Oh.
And it got.
It's antennae.
It was having a bad.
It was having a bad trip.
A bad church air trip.
No more church air please.
Don't stone the bees unless they ask you.
Unfair.
Remember those giant bees.
No, more church air.
We need only enough oxygen to provide ignition for the.
To fill the pews.
If you know what they mean, pee you.
We had passion flowers at the last place that we lived and there were these giant bees as big as your thumb.
They were huge.
And they would get so drunk on the passion flower.
What Ev?
That they would kind of fall asleep.
Do you remember that?
They would be.
They would be like sitting on the passion flower and they'd be just like.
Princess, we the cool kids now don't say what Ev.
They just say Ev.
I invented that.
That's how I know how cool it is.
No, we're already down to the.
Ev.
The.
We're just.
I don't know.
The, the.
It's already been supplanted but.
Yeah.
That's the internet age for you.
Just like a retarded Canadian.
Hey, that's not very nice.
I mean, you know what I'm saying?
They try.
Whatever.
Sorry to attack Canadians again as usual.
I love Canada.
It's a wonderful place.
Why don't you marry it?
I want to marry it.
I do.
You should.
I want to dress up like a rugged Mountie and storm my way over the bridge.
And the church is subgenius.
Make my way to the nearest bar and say,
Milton Snod, you're under arrest in the name of the Queen.
You hear a dog bark, and I pull out an AK-47 and shoot myself.
Oh, don't do that.
Well, you know, the Mounties are just like everybody else.
They need affection, eyebrow medicine sometimes.
I got it.
You got to pet their little heads for at least like 15 minutes a day.
You tell them they look pretty.
Eyebrow medicine?
Okay, they're called the Mounties.
Who is mounting them?
If they're the Mounties, there's someone who is the Mounteur.
Who is doing the mounting?
Actually, you see, you got that mixed up.
Okay, they're called Mounties in English because they're mounted, but in French, they're called
the Moontaires because they're the ones doing the mounting.
Ah.
If they were French, they would be Mountie.
If they were French.
They're mounted.
Call Les Moontaires.
Maybe I'm spelling Mountie wrong.
I mean Quebec.
There's no I in Mountie.
Actually, if you're my Mountie.
Yes, watch your poetic license, too.
That's the reason why we can't break this loop right now.
So you might as well just start singing the freaking song and get it over with.
Hey, I've got...
I have to bring up a really hard...
I've got a horrible subject.
Uh-oh.
Oh, okay.
And not everyone will agree with me, but I have to tell the subgeniuses not to vote in
the election that's coming at this time.
It won't be coming for those who listen to it on the internet, but in two days is November
4th, big midterm elections.
And I'm telling the subgeniuses not to go out and vote because being subgeniuses, they'll
disobey me and actually vote.
Because I'll say that.
I only say this every couple of years.
I only say this every couple of years, friends.
But when you don't vote, you're voting twice for someone who would like to lynch you real
slowly and then see you accidentally die.
Do you want me to read that disclaimer behind you before you continue any further?
No, I'm not going to tell them.
Portions of the following broadcast may be found objectable to members of the listening
audience.
Therefore, WCSB advises listener discretion.
There we go.
You're safe.
Go.
We won't tell you who to vote for as long as it's not Republicans.
No, no.
We really won't tell you who to vote for.
But I sure won't vote for any Republicans.
Jesus.
I'm terrified.
It's scarier than Halloween.
But I've got to be ready to bend over and take it.
The lynch mobs will be on their way because I already...
Princess, we and I did some bad things.
We read Yahoo comments posted by right-wingers in doofus voices.
They're going to get you.
That really...
That really upset some of the...
Oh, what's the polite term?
Right-tards who didn't think that subgenius libtards should do things like that.
But we were just reading their own words, albeit in a somewhat doofus series.
The hard part was coming up with enough variety on the doofus voices.
I mean, how many different southern accents, Texas accents, can I do, for instance?
Only about ten.
And there's ten billion doofuses out there.
Ten billion.
It's kind of like dark matter, you know, something like whatever percentage of the matter in the universe we can't detect at all.
It's, you know, talking about the dark doofuses.
Like, we can't...
Ten billion of them, you know, even though we can only count about seven billion people.
That means we can detect less than half the human population.
Yeah.
That's terrifying.
It makes it perfectly...
It is.
It's scientifically valid.
And it's stone-sure enough, too.
It's not.
Well, some people think that voting just validates this crooked...
...system.
But what it was, I think it was Palmer Vreede said something recently on his Facebook world,
along the lines of, yeah, six million Jews were going,
what difference does it make who you vote for?
Both sides are exactly the same.
That was a rather horrifying way of putting it.
But, you know, there were a lot of people in Nazi Germany going,
well, this will pass.
This is going to blow over.
Nobody's that crazy.
Including the Jews.
Yeah, especially.
There were many who did not take him seriously and thought it was all rhetoric.
Right.
But rhetoric is going to kill us all because that's all it is, is a bunch of crap rhetoric.
They just tell us a bunch of stuff.
Yeah, but it gets the emotional people really more emotional.
I get really tired of both sides calling the other side the Nazis.
Everyone wants...
Well, the sleeper are the ones that are putting me to sleep.
Well, what is your fascist state, darling?
I must say, there's no way...
There's no way around that politically, scientifically speaking,
because you have the emergence of the corporate state and socialism for the rich,
and that's called fascism.
Now, you know what's fascism?
I know someone, and I'm not going to name them,
I'm not going to say by name,
that lives in San Francisco who gave out carrots on Halloween,
and that's fascist.
No kidding, man.
If I was a kid, I'd be going, what a fascist.
But they're orange, like a pumpkin.
Yeah, but they're not candy.
That's the point.
I want candy corn.
I want the wax.
Mom gives you damn carrots.
I want the candle wax.
Give me the candle wax and sugar.
They're sweet, though, like candy.
Carrots are sweet.
Like candy.
No.
It sounded like mommy.
You're talking about that good-looking woman spy in San Francisco, right?
No, that wasn't good-looking.
That spy woman.
I know who it is.
No, it's Reverend Cinnamon.
She's the one that gave out the carrots.
I know it is.
I know.
Oh, well, if she does it, that's okay, because she's so good-looking.
I wish she'd bring some white, though.
Oh, is that for Dave Everton saying, that's a very shallow way to view reality?
It just completely and totally turns me off to hear such insipidity and such shallow,
shallow, shallowness.
Well, then it shouldn't bother you that we're soon going to have to turn this radio station off.
Well, no, no, just this show.
Actually, just this show.
That wouldn't even bother me at this point.
But, yes, I understand.
Man, Dave should tell you, Stan.
Oh, yeah, The Hour of Slack from the Church of the Subgenius.
That's it.
And subgenius.com has everything on it that you would need to know, although you might
have trouble finding it.
Some people seem to find it hard to navigate.
It seems rather automatic to me.
My hint is look at the words at the top of the page, and if you don't see the one you're
looking for, try scrolling down the page.
A lot of subgeniuses, by definition, don't go to that much effort.
You know, the scrolling down, or even lowering the eyes a few inches.
They wear funny 60s suits.
I'm sorry.
Well, anyway, we do have to sort of go or something pretty soon here.
And then what comes up?
Oh, the next show.
Time to deliver plastic pizzas in the radioactive snow.
Get out and vote.
Vote.
That's Bob's job.
You told us that earlier tonight, Dave.
Yeah, he said he was going to vote for all of us, too, and he didn't, because I checked
the absentee ballots for a certain friend of mine.
Vote for Bob!
He always lies, and he's always right.
Oh, man.
If you could start a religion or something based on that idea, I mean, just think of
it.
If only.
Because of the religious power you would have.
It's not a religion.
It's a difficult.
Okay, okay.
If you could start a cult like that, think of the Rick you would have been saving that
one.
It's the Diffie cult that puts the duh in fundamentalism.
Right.
How about a Tardo club based on what was it you said?
That one thing.
But it's the end.
And if you could even start a, like, make a Bible out of that or a cram or something,
that would be really smooth.
Oh, it's downloadable on Wikipedia or the internet or someplace already.
Okay, Dave, we have to cut to the news now.
Thank you, Baby Bear, for being here.
By the way, Baby Bear wants to come have lunch with you and Ashtabula on her travels.
Yeah, can I do that, Dave?
It might be possible.
We'll give you a call soon.
Maybe in five minutes.
Maybe in tomorrow.
But something will happen.
Anyway, friends, thank you.
Praise Bob.
And now this.
From NPR News in Washington, I'm now in effect.
298 people gathered to collect chickens more than two weeks ago.
For now, they're working on recovering 80 chickens in an ambush near the PR site.
Critics say that's a social network such as FaceNerf and TwitBook.
209,000.2% who addressed the recent surge of 6.1%.
Including many illegal percents.
U.S. cell officers made a travesty in great stock due in part to X down in windmills.
The Fed invested in Zeddy Cup victims from things during core weak measures.
Dow was 16469.12.
This is PR News.
I've been to an election night party before.
I got to go to the Sherrod Brown victory rally this fall at Public Hall.
It was pretty fun.
At my age, it's hard to get an election.
What's that?
You said at my age it's hard to get an election.
Oh yeah.
At this age, I flee elections.
Free elections.
Never mind.
Uh huh.
Oh yeah, you can get in a lot of trouble for walking around with your election freely.
If your election lasts longer than four hours, see a doctor.
Even worse, wearing it on your sleeve.