Oh, my Lord!
Now, I want to make absolutely clear that I'm in no way interested in the contents of your tights.
You might be, my Lord, if you knew what I kept in them.
Uh, I've learned it myself, Bob, that I know what a gentleman keeps in his tights. Thank you very much.
But, my Lord, I have a great secret.
What?
Prepare to be amazed.
Oh, no, you haven't got one of those birthmarks shaped like a banana, have you?
No.
Or a tattoo saying, get it here?
Oh, God, you've got one of those belly buttons that sticks outwards, haven't you?
No, my Lord.
Well, what can it possibly be?
The Self Genius Hour of Swag.
Ah, good Lord.
I find you curiously pleasant.
I'm in company, Bob.
Yes, friends, like last time, as X Day gets closer, I have less and less time to put into the kind of dense hours of slack we're known for, if you're knowing about it at all.
And our options in such cramped times are reruns or uncut live shows at WCSB, which means actually going to the station.
Or, well, like we're doing this time, uncut other subgenius shows recorded elsewhere.
In this case, it's Dr. Philodrummond and I appearing with other guests on Dr. Hal's two-hour show, the Ask Dr. Hal Show on Radio Valencia in San Francisco.
Best of all, with only a few edits, it was hour of slack ready, and that saves us a lot of time.
You will not believe the creature known as Zero Boy, who is another guest.
The music in the background right now is Boron Nozzle recorded live.
And now, back to the Ask Dr. Hal Show.
Don't toss and turn all night with spiders in your hair.
Thank you very much, Dr. Hal, for coming all the way to our country to be interviewed for this radio show.
Gosh, it's so wonderful to be here.
I'm determined to represent my country.
My religion and my radio station.
All right.
First thing, I want to say that as an American, do you think that you'll ever be able to understand the plight of most of the people of the planet, which number America almost 13 to 1?
Probably not.
Okay, thank you.
That's all we need for that question.
Their problems are not mine.
I really can't cure the problems of some foreigners on the planet.
I'm just going to try to get them to understand the plight of some of the people on the other side of the world.
Next question, please.
The next question I have has to deal with the fact that America is the largest polluter of the free world.
And we would like to know what you think about that.
Well, you know, in order to keep the financial intestines producing energy, we have to generate waste products.
And that's why we're advancing to higher grade plutonium this year.
My next question is about the sexuality of dinosaurs.
What do you think dinosaurs were thinking when they were reproducing?
Was there a pleasure aspect to this?
They were thinking most amorous thoughts, of course.
Yes, they were enjoying themselves as one can hardly imagine if one only weighs several stone.
But if you weigh 82 pounds, you can imagine how much you weigh.
If you weigh 80 tons, your orgasm will be proportionately increased.
Now, I have another question.
It's about the thorough recesses of the mind.
Let's go back deeply for a moment and think about that perhaps people who are reproducing at this point in the planet,
are they being selfish or do you think it is part of the natural progress of what is happening?
Do you know whatmoi mean?
craftsmanship ofgiois mind are the foundational 00.
And aviation mechanics can beocaphoria,
are children's luck.
and humans with people with bsad ibis requirements their happy lives in the firm.
The mission that I progress is to build the standing wreck to whiskey.
And Sweden is giving me the real signs that there's good
This is great.
Yes, of course. It's wonderful to be here.
Don't blow it, you know.
The courtiers are all watching us,
and we've got to make a good impression at court here.
No problem. I'm the king. No problem.
Lord Squanderfield.
I am founding you.
And Bishop Westchester.
Hello.
I'm diddling a chicken with a chicken feather.
For the waters, my lord.
I said, do you come here for the waters, my lord?
I say, where?
No, certainly.
Lord Squanderfield.
This way, gentlemen.
We are having parquet in the margarine room.
Yes, parquet in the margarine room.
My favorite margarine.
I remember this from my childhood.
Well, we're all going to meet the king.
And, you know, as great and as glorious
as his majesty is, and the sunlight,
it's shining over the benevolence of his reign in this realm.
There is one problem, which is that he can't eat his meat
while it's hot, because he's got so many courtiers
to carry it to him.
I cannot eat my meat while it's hot.
By the time it gets to his majesty, it is cold,
and so the scurviest cook in his kitchen gets his meat hot,
but his majesty does not.
Oh!
You have a bit of snuff.
Just a bit of the old snuff.
The snuff, I say.
That snuff is enough.
Not strictly speaking, up to snuff.
Oh, there you go, sir.
Oh, yes.
No.
Oh, no.
Try a bit of this metaphysical tobacco.
Stop that.
Fetched from far Morocco.
Thy rich perfume exhales the room,
oh, metaphysical tobacco.
Oh.
You, obviously.
You are the ambassador of England, Dr. Halbert.
I was sent here by my sovereign,
and I will attempt to represent him to the best of my ability.
I was wondering what you are hiding
under that very big pair of pants of yours.
Why, nothing.
C'est la mode.
No fashion dictates that I wear such exaggerated pantaloons.
What is this I've found?
It is merely a fashion of the time, I assure you.
A fashion of the time?
No.
I'll have a long time checking out
your fashion.
My dear sir, I do not dictate these things.
Dictate?
Oh.
You are making so much out of whole clothes.
It's a dick.
Listen, I was just wondering, what is this hiding in your pants now?
This happens to be my own personal doubloon changer.
I can't do it on my own.
I was in humanities at college.
Humanities.
That is true.
My instructor was Dr. Langley, and he taught me to sing a song.
All right.
Hal, you'll have to sing a song now.
And here it is.
I need you to sing this song, and it goes something like this.
No, not that one.
No, no, no, no.
Well, I had a dream.
A dream of yesterday.
You know, if you break my heart, I'll go.
And tomorrow.
But somehow.
But I'll be back again.
I got lost again in my dream.
In the deep of today.
That was sweet.
That really was.
The way you sent him off that way.
Well, I did what I could.
After all, am I not only one man?
I think so.
I think you're not only one man, but maybe two men.
No, don't confuse me.
You could be three men.
I could be a free man if I chose.
You could be yourself and someone else.
But who would that be?
You can be what you won't.
In the army?
As Bob said.
All that I can be.
You can be what you will not be.
Yes, but you will not.
That's what religion is all about.
You can be what you will not be.
Yes, well, you can in the sweet by and by where there's pie in the sky, but...
No, I mean now.
Right now.
Yes, you're offering what no one ever has been able to...
I've become a grinning fool who thinks he can do no wrong.
I already am.
Because his every move is guided by the hand of some superior great wise force.
Sure, everything I do is on the QT because I do it, see?
Do you have green lipstick on?
Yes.
And I admit.
Yes, I got this at Walgreens.
What is the deal with that green lipstick?
It's just, you know, kids like it.
They think I'm cool.
I'm trying to look young.
That's why I shaved all my hair off and got the tattoos and the nose ring and everything.
The tattoos, eh?
Well, I...
Yeah, see?
I'm not...
I'm just trying to look cool.
I guess that's not for everyone.
I think there's actually beer in this doctor now.
You know, if you're 57 years old and you do all the fads that young people do, that makes you look young.
I think this really, really, really contains real beer.
Reverend Stanger leaning on my leg very closely.
Tom Savini.
It's very, very...
Well done.
Yeah, he's well done.
That leaning you're doing is just really getting to me.
I was digging my elbow into Philo's leg because of the tight quarters here, and it was hurting him.
Now, now.
Gentlemen.
That's humorous.
Gentlemen, please.
Please.
That's humorous.
Hurting a man.
That's a humorous...
He's hurting my tight pants.
That's funny.
Radius and an ulna.
The pain of others.
That's funny.
It was hurting my pants.
I'm completely impervious to physical pain except my own.
Oh, somebody's calling.
Somebody's calling.
That's inside your head, Hal.
Don't, don't, don't.
Someone's calling.
No, they're calling.
You're just imagining it.
There's somebody calling.
You're right.
There is no...
But, no.
Well, what do you call that?
Come on.
I ain't hallucinating here.
You probably aren't on the air.
I call it a cruel, cruel hoax.
Hello.
Speak.
Speak, speak, ye fearful guest, who, if by...
Take him out!
Hello?
...hallow breasts still in rude armor...
There he is.
...come to don't you.
Hello.
Hi.
I hear you.
Hello.
You're not on the air.
Yes, I am.
I can hear you.
I hear my voice on the air.
It's a cute little girl.
I hear his voice.
How are you?
On the air.
Her voice.
You do not.
Yes, I am.
Yes, I do.
I hear you.
What's your name?
These are the demons of the sand dunes...
No, no, no.
Dr. Howell, I can hear the calling.
...calling you out into the endless desert.
They want you to become some sort of mummy out there.
I hear the calling, Dr. Howell.
Do not pay attention to those voices.
How long have you been out here, Howell?
Far too long, but thank heaven...
Is that a hawk flying above us or some sort of vulture?
A refreshing draft.
Oh, well, good for that draft.
For those who never drank a dram.
How many more miles do we have to go before we get to this damn treasure?
Well, that depends on...
He lost the map!
He lost the map again.
And the compass.
And the water purification.
And the water purification, but he has a beer.
It ain't even a beer.
And miles to go before we see it.
It's super sugary cider that's going to haunt me all the way to the Isles of Langerhans.
Wait, is that what I see?
A spy ahead of us?
An arched way in the sand?
Actually, it's not that bad.
It's only got 16 grams of carbohydrates.
Still...
The Isles of Langerhans.
Yes, I advise you all steer clear of those accursed isles.
Remember our camping trip years ago?
When we and Michael Pepe were out there and I was throwing down that lemonade.
The very stuff that you're talking about now.
Yeah, that was a great camping trip.
It made me...
We just had that giant tarp and we all sort of slept on the giant tarp and rolled around on it all night.
You may have rolled on the tarp like some...
You rolled out of...
I remember that night you sort of rolled out of your sleeping bag and were...
Slept?
Well, that's how I rolled, man.
Half on the tarp.
That's just how I rolled.
That's the way you rolled.
Yeah, he rolled down the hill and into that ditch.
Dr. Hill, Dr. Howell.
Then the brand came and washed him down to the sea.
He rolled down to the sea.
That ditch was a big...
He woke up on an island far away.
He's got a big roll.
Thank God I was on Monster Island.
He was on a roll that night.
By the way, that new movie I think has dinosaurs or monsters in it.
What about the Mysterious Island?
It's out now.
Right now.
I don't have high hopes for that one.
Did you see that?
Starring Train.
Train.
The rock Johnson.
The Nazi.
The new Nazi.
Same people.
A new Nazi?
The Nazis from behind the moon.
Nazis from the moon invade the earth.
Now the Nazis are mooning us?
When are those guys going to go away?
When are we going to be through with the damn Nazis?
I mean, it definitely looked totally over the top.
Being mooned by Nazis.
That's also happening in our national electoral politics.
It turns out that on the dark side of the moon, Nazis have been there since the 40s.
And they've built like a supersonic Nazi.
Like supersonic.
Nazi hell creatures.
That news has finally been released?
Only they're not.
I thought only Bob was allowed to speak.
Yes, I thought they came from the center of the earth.
They're going to make contact with their brothers in the center of the earth.
It's like that Cowboys and Aliens thing.
Why are they behind the moon now?
They're supposed to come from the hollow earth.
Well, they're going to make contact with their Nazi brothers in the hollow earth.
Actually, this is the time to interject.
They're trivializing fact is what they're doing.
The moon is hollow.
And we're exploring that with a special probe that NASA is sending there,
which is specifically to figure out just how hollow our satellite, the moon, is.
The moon, Dr. Howell, as you know, is in fact the skull of an ancient monster.
And at its center, there is still viable moisture at the so-called central sea.
Yes, the treasure, the DNA of that thing.
Journey to the center of the moon.
Um...
Uh-oh.
The huge god.
Occasionally visits solar systems in our neighborhood.
And it would be bad luck if it came to visit us because it's...
I mean, just think of like a centipede crawling around on an apple.
Pay no attention to the man.
It's a big stupid thing and it messes up the whole planet before it leaps off.
Well, they show up and immediately spray for tool users.
Uh, they can bury whole lands and countries in giant walls of earth and rock
as the brainless thing goes.
Goes by.
It's, uh, regrettable.
That's why you better be on Bob's team.
It's just a piece of space trash.
Bob's space...
It's a piece of galactic debris.
Bob made friends with them creatures and that's how you can be safe.
If you're Bob's friend, then you're a friend of those creatures.
The amusing thing is...
They won't kill you.
They'll take you off in their escape vessels.
Science...
You can have anything you want forever and ever.
...does not remove the terror of the gods.
If you only knew the malevolent blackness that is out there behind the stars, you would
laugh at the terror of the gods.
The idea that here on our planet of green trees and flowing water there was any recourse
to be had from the most malevolent and destructive principles in the universe, as epitomized in
my twelve-module course in Success in Sex and Real Estate.
Oh, yeah, sure, sure.
They, they, they talk all about the Whore of Babylon, but they never talk about how
good-looking she is, now, do they?
She's kinda good-looking unless you look really closely, and then she's a penitent.
Oh, yeah.
I mean, that's the way, uh, they, she's pictured in the Jehovah's Witnesses...
...pouring into those rather skillfully produced...
They seem to suck me in.
...regular intelligence...
It was just the opposite of what I had in mind when I started out.
Now, now, don't worry.
Everything's going to be all right.
And then the next thing I woke up and I was married to her and she was making me run
a vacuum cleaner up...
...just fine.
...the living room floor.
It's okay.
...she made a mistake.
She made a mistake.
We need the dishes.
Okay, okay.
What do you mean?
You've never done the dishes.
Wait a minute, uh, where the hell am I?
What have you done to me, Doctor?
This is a place I often come to meditate.
You will come to know it well.
Well, why have you strapped me into this wall like this?
What are you gonna do with that thing?
The denizens of the deep must feed Mr. Blumzack.
No.
No, please, no.
They must eat...
No.
...to live.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
Even...
...as...
...you and I...
No.
No, no.
Nooooo!
Nooooooooo!
Oh, this is terrible.
Terrible.
Nooooo!
It's...
It's terrible.
Really, truly terrible.
I do regret it.
I'm so sorry these measures...
These...
These measures were necessary.
I...
I may have some slight...
...twin...
...skills...
...at...
...having performed...
Oh, my...
...god...
...I...
...to think of the indignities that a...
...a human body could suffer.
Well, I thought I had seen the light.
And now it's actually swelling up like some sort of insane pufferfish.
Good lord, look at the size of...
I'm getting out of here.
Come this way, Hal, quickly!
I'm...
I can't get up.
Help!
I'm...
...guessing...
...the world...
Are you alright?
Oh, I'm asleep.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
I think you might...
Oh, dear me.
I think you might be in for a tough time.
Hark!
We have ne facial and a slow mutuality.
Aside, due to the dinner at 1985...
And they're now dropped without burning towards the dried ice!
Seems to be alive.
Sus lamp pieces and something like that?
Hustlers this year don't need mày-
plane over there. You do, thank
God, but do we have enough petrol to fly
her out? Uh, yes.
I was able to find a small
55-gallon drum
worth of petrol. It will get
us to the farthest edges of this
deadly valley. Relax, settle back, and enjoy
our feature presentation.
Yes, ladies and gentlemen,
nothing can harm us.
We do what we can do
and what we must do.
To bring you award-winning radio.
Harry, Harry.
Daddy.
What is it, my dear? Mother, mother.
Why, when you knew perhaps this would
end up going the way it is going.
Send that child to bed.
You, sir, back in your bed or you'll have me to deal with.
Mother. Foolishness is bound
in the heart of a child, but the rod
of correction shall drive it from him.
Don't hit him, Harry, please, don't hit him.
The little swine. Where's my
father? I'll teach him
to usurp his place.
The linch of the wound
cleanses away the evil.
Now, my boy, have you been studying
your Euclid? Let me
hear your recitation.
Come, come, do not
stammer.
Have you played the poppin' jay
instead of attending
to your studies? You'll notice
ever since we put him in the
lock-up when he was found guilty
of abusing the child, he's just been talking
to the wall all day long as
if he's speaking to the child. I'll have my revenge on the
pack of you, I will.
For four years he's been in there.
Let's see if we can get him.
Sometimes he comes back into sanity.
Sometimes a thousand
twangling instruments about my ears.
And sometimes voices.
Halbert, can you hear me,
Halbert? You do not exist, sir.
You are a phantom. I'll open the
door, Halbert, and I'll let you out
into the corridor. Oh, you will? Okay, I take it all back.
If you'll be nice.
What do you want me to do?
All right.
Oh, hey!
This is, uh, Dr. Stang,
and this is Dr. Ha-Ha.
This is some vile hallucination. I refuse to believe
in the reality of these experiences.
As devilishly and real
as they look and feel.
Nurse, do you
think that, uh, he's
safe enough to allow
into the hallway? I'll never get
into that hallway. Probably not, from the looks
of the room. The dream is
that you're always trying to get there.
You'll never get there because that's not
what the dream is about. The dream is about the search.
Halbert. I'm never gonna get there, and you're
never gonna get there. You searched for a supersonic Nazi hellbreacher.
We're stuck here forever. Don't you understand?
Well, I'm not gonna do it. Tell me about your wife,
Halbert. I'm busting out of this.
Remember your poor wife?
What do you know about my wife?
How dare you mention my
wife? That's the weakest excuse
I've heard all day. Take it back, I tell you.
I think you'd best go back into
your cell, Halbert. Never!
Get back in there. Get back in there.
You swine! I'll be
revenged. Hey,
where'd you get that, Halbert?
That's a revolver. What are you doing with that?
Get against the wall.
You can't get away. Give me those keys,
please.
Alright.
I believe I'll take these.
Well, not before you take them
over my dead body!
I'm sorry. I had to
do it.
Yes, those shots are particularly painful.
Oh, look. There's a dead body there.
Yeah, look at that. And it says,
stinking up the place. Well, I gotta take
a powder, so, um,
let me tell you one and all.
You're a swell bunch of guys and gals.
I appreciate you coming by tonight.
I've got a gorgeous popsicle stand.
It reminds me
of my adventures with
Zero Boy in the Congo. Don't forget, leave no trace.
So long ago. You know, there are vast
stretches of unexplored
equatorial Africa, although we hardly
think so. Pack your trash there, fella.
Snooping eyes in the sky.
Take your junk with you. But much of...
of the Congo is simply uninhabitable
by man. Why you'd be devoured
by clouds of stinging
insects if you tried to go 25 feet.
And the heat often
gets up above 125.
Well, when you wrote the book,
um, Mr. Robinson,
you were in the Congo, and, uh...
I was searching for the lost
Apatosaurus.
Oh, there it goes.
I guess I don't have to search for it.
There it is.
Okay, well, look at it go.
Well, that, uh, that just
took care of that. Um, uh, what he said
was is, uh, it's gonna cost, uh,
45 bucks, a case of beer,
and, uh, a color TV.
Do they think I am made of money?
Um, either that or they're gonna cut your head off
and shrink you down to a size of a fist.
Oh, I don't want that. No, no, no. I, I, I gotta
shrink back at home. Okay, I'll tell you
what I'm gonna do. They're planning on doing some shrinking
of their own, I believe. And it gave me a
shrinking feeling to see the glare
in their eyes as they stared
toward me and our well-fleshed
companions.
Yum, yum, eat him up.
Calm the old boy down. What's the word for friend?
Bala. Uh, no.
Kimo Sabe. Uh, Bala
Reri. Pasco!
Excuse me, sir, but, uh, I don't think
you understand. Uh, for some reason in your
head, it's a very typical colonial
white, uh, Caucasian
way of looking at it. It's a common mistake.
You somehow seem to think that we don't understand
English when, however, we've been a trading
society for thousands
of years. Well, dog, my cat.
I actually went to Harvard University, and
my brother over here, uh, you know,
graduated from Cambridge at 14.
People don't know that. It happens.
Well, is my
countenance crimson?
It just, uh, shows to go, yeah.
All right, uh...
Dr. Hell, it's...
It's the phone. This is ecumenical
radio. It's the police this time. Are you kidding?
It's the phone police. Another
phony, phony, baloney phone? They've heard that you're not
taking calls, and they're... It is.
It's the phone, all right. I'm not taking
calls, but I'm gonna see who it is
unless it's that argumentative
Pete Goldie fellow. Hey, get that Pete Goldie
guy. If only this
would go over the radio the way it's supposed
to. Why do you suppose it does not?
Bad telepathy.
It's your show. Hello, are you there on the phone? Because it's your show,
Dr. Hell. When you call us,
yes, I'm right here, and I
am afraid you're not on the air.
Connie Dobbs?
Oh, no, this is terrible. I
wish I could put you on the air, but we are
having a malfunction. That's Connie Dobbs.
Hold the phone up close
to the mic and turn the volume
up real high. But you should whisper.
I think we've all, and everyone
in this room has had sex with her.
Give me a blessed moment.
It's Connie Dobbs.
I put you on the phone by holding
your phone.
To the microphone, and here we go.
Think about it, man.
I'm sorry.
The next voice you hear will be that of
Connie Dobbs, concert
of the E-pop, J.R.
Bob Dobbs.
Connie, are you with us?
You know what?
I think she rung off. I think she
hung up. There's no more
Connie Dobbs. No how.
I would like to take a moment to
remember what Connie meant to me.
Before that historic moment
when she was torn apart
from us on that show,
that fateful day. It was.
Yes, of what's the day's date again?
That's a good one. I wish I could
tell you. It's the
10th of February. I'll never
forget that day. Or was.
I'll never forget. It's what happened when
I cried for at least 20 minutes
after she was ripped off the line.
In just a few minutes,
it's going to be to the next day when
the whole Ask Doctor,
Hal, so Miguel, has to
fall into place. All the ducks
have to be in a row. So are you going to go home and
go to sleep, Dr. Hal?
I haven't been able to do that all week, but
maybe I'm going to get some hours
of slumbering and snoozing.
Behold,
he that keepeth Israel shall
neither slumber nor sleep.
Let's all hear our snores, eh?
Snores?
Here in beautiful Snorewood,
California, where
saw through logs
all the night long.
You're going to lounge in the bosom of Morpheus.
A sleep apnea-induced cloud.
When you're laying there in Morpheus' bosom,
don't you be
fiddling with those nipples now?
Let me hear your snore, Hal.
Morpheus, you don't want to get
Morpheus sexually excited.
No, there's much complaining about my snoring.
People are incredibly intolerant
of my snoring. I don't know what's the matter with them.
Let me hear another snoring.
I slept in the same...
I slept...
God! Good God, Ben!
That creature is...
That was amazing.
Alright, alright, alright.
I was dreaming of the nightingale.
The beautiful song of Philomel.
With lullaby, sweet lullaby.
Hal, have you ever had a loved one
record your snore and play back the recording?
That would be the ultimate betrayal.
You, man.
Be ready for a real shock.
Oh, I don't want to hear it.
The one good thing about it is
that you're asleep when it happens
and you don't have to listen to it
and now even that will be taken from you.
Right. You'll know what you've been doing
to everyone else and you won't believe it.
I couldn't believe it was me.
I'd never heard anything like it
short of a machine shop.
Well, I...
It was horrible.
And I feel terrible about
everyone I've kept awake forever.
This trip, we bought my wife
a white noise headphone set.
And it's worked.
It's worked for her.
Yeah, for her.
It didn't make you snore any less.
Well, at least you don't have to wear
that damn thing that they put on you
with a thing like an elephant's trunk
that sticks out.
You know what I'm talking about?
Oh, yeah, the CPAP machine.
The CPAP machine?
Every X day, another person
is on the phone.
On a CPAP machine.
It reminds me of my...
Oh, God.
The X's are taking...
What a bunch of...
They're rupturing us up
one piece at a time.
What a bunch of sissies.
Like...
Sissies?
They'll take part of your lung power.
They'll take part of your memory.
They'll take part of your morals.
Reverend Stang, quit fiddling with my knee.
They'll take one of your teeth.
Reverend Stang has to do something.
They took his hair.
Idle hands are the devil's playground.
And those brain cells.
Look at them hanging out there
where they should be.
The axons and dendrites.
The Hatfields and the McCoys.
It's ongoing.
Every second,
they're lifting another part of you
up to the saucers.
Do you have as much money
as you used to?
You are lifted off piece by piece,
particle by particle.
You know what?
I can't wait, Reverend Stang.
When I get up there
into the saucers
and we head over to Planet X
and we finally get there,
the sex goddess is working us over
all the way there.
We finally get to Planet X
and I'm going to have
the best comic book collection
just waiting for me there.
But in the Congo,
they'll run...
They'll rot.
You see, if Planet X is tropical...
You won't have to because
you'll have an identical one.
Yeah, that's true.
We'll all have, like,
identical comic book collections.
Have I mentioned that I have dibs
on the Rijksmuseum in Amsterdam?
Yes, you have many times.
You mentioned that a lot.
Many, many times.
You can have those drabby old...
those Rembrandts,
those old dark...
Did I mention the Grand Canyon?
Yeah, you mentioned the Grand Canyon.
And grand it is.
You know, there's a nifty canyon
right above the Grand Canyon,
which few people know about.
You've got dibs on a whole bunch of stuff.
But, you know...
Which side?
You can only hold them
and you can only hold
so much in your hands.
Is it on the Flintstones Village side
or the north side?
You're like that monkey
reaching into that jar
and grabbing those...
It's a special, hidden, forbidden...
Oh, you're great.
Dr. Howell, I was at a place
called Hidden Valley.
Hidden Valley.
Hidden Valley Ranch.
A campground in Joshua Tree National Park.
But get this.
If you got a hiking map,
it showed Hidden Valley Campground.
But then, behind some topographical stuff,
there was...
the name,
The Real Hidden Valley.
Oh, it's all enough
to make one's head spin.
So, needless to say,
Lisa and I
and Princess We
went to that place
as fast as we could.
Yeah.
We got into the Hidden Valley.
It was, in fact,
very much like
entering the Valley of Gwangi.
It was, in fact,
the guy who discovered it
had to dynamite it open.
And it was used by rustlers
for hiding their stolen cattle in.
And then it was owned by a rancher
who said,
why, now that the cattle
have eaten all the grass
and stripped this place,
I believe I'll open it to the public.
And it is a beautiful, hidden valley.
But these hidden valleys
can regenerate themselves.
Full of dinosaurs.
I know.
But few will believe it.
Only I could see them.
The actual Valley of Gwangi
must be in Mexico's
Sierra Madre Oriental.
You think?
Surrounded by mountains.
Oh, there's the phone again.
The beast.
Apollo Mountain.
Yes.
Greatest animated film ever made.
That's interesting that we can hear it ring.
Oh, you're on the air.
But we can't hear it.
Oh, no, I'm sorry.
You're not on the air.
You kind of are.
We can't get the phone to work.
It's Connie Dobbs.
Oh, come on now, honey.
Are you having some technical difficulties?
I'm here.
Can you hear?
She's at the bottom of the sound well.
Yeah, at the very bottom.
This is outrageous.
Try it now, Connie.
I'm down, Pete.
I'm down.
She's done something terrible.
It does sound like Connie Dobbs.
Turn that music off.
Good Lord, man.
Stinking music off.
This is Connie Dobbs, man.
Help me.
Help.
She's yelling for help.
She's yelling for help?
You'll be stuck at the bottom of the well.
Oh, she's stuck at the bottom of the well.
Well, well.
Like, this is a job for...
We need you for a...
You are Bob Dobbs.
A photo shoot.
Well, yeah, we do the photo shoot first,
and then we'll call Bob,
and he'll come and get you.
Can you hear me?
Just barely.
I'm not a liar or anything.
Just barely can we hear you
because the radio setup is so unworkable.
We need to get you both some money.
Yes, that's right.
I hope everyone heard what she said.
Can you bring us some of that good home cooking?
I want some of that good home cooked money.
Now try it, Connie.
Hello?
I hear you now.
What's going on?
I think I managed to fix the technical problem.
You did something.
It's her.
Get out of here, my dear.
Listen, I'm so happy.
I feel much better.
I came out of that well.
You're happy.
I'm in ecstasy.
The fucking thing is finally functioning,
and I think I figured out how to do it.
Well, let's hear your ruminations.
Turn your mic down, Hal.
You're running over money.
I'm sorry.
You're over how much now?
Is that all right?
I had it turned up.
Oh, it is.
It is.
Connie loves y'all so much.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
I had you turned up loud.
You've got Reverend Stang masturbating on the air.
Stang is overwhelmed by listening to Connie's voice.
Oh, well, bye, kids.
Take those special pills, do you?
He doesn't take Reverend Stang much.
He gets set off by the nearest...
Please excuse this unfortunate display.
A little breeze blowing by his pants will set Reverend Stang off.
That was not amusing or entertaining.
But anyway, Connie...
I'd like to know.
I'd like to know a little something.
How come there's all kinds of pictures of Pete Goldie on your show?
Yeah, what's the deal with Pete Goldie on your show?
Yeah, and the socks.
What's with the socks?
You're saying there are pictures of Pete Goldie?
Yeah, look right over there on your website, Dr. Hal.
On your website.
On that website.
There's Pete Goldie on your website.
Well, you know, without Pete Goldie, there wouldn't be much of a website, would there?
This is the Ask Dr. Hal show.
Well, how come there's pictures of Pete Goldie?
I'm very confused.
Connie is very confused.
Well, I guess we consider Pete Goldie a natural phenomenon,
worthy of celebrating in the decorative element of our website.
I wish you were puzzling Evidence Showwife, because she's a really good cook.
And so cute.
She is a good cook.
Connie's not so much of a good cook, because she has people cooking for her.
Yeah, that's right.
Connie can't cook for shit.
They're cooking all the time.
They're cooking for Connie, if you know what I mean.
Connie can't cook worth a crap.
Only Bob's best friend could get away with it.
She's saying something like that.
Yeah, Connie's not a good cook.
She's like...
Dr. Drummond, please.
She's like, knows how to...
We know you have unusual privileges here, but...
Connie's idea of cooking is to order reservations at the...
That's like saying Tammy Faye Baker was a crappy lay.
Come on, let's keep things in perspective.
Well, you would know that.
You would know that, Reverend Stang.
First hand.
I used to be a good cook when I was younger, and I was, you know...
Of course.
I used to have Connie's recipe book.
Now that Bob is gone...
It's not around.
Now, I just don't cook as much, and I have people who take care of that for me.
As they should.
I understand you got in trouble in your presentation up there in Point Arena recently.
Is that true?
No, no.
I don't know any kind of cooking you're talking about.
Who would have said such a thing?
Just because you showed a film which was slightly racy in its contents,
there seems to be some palaver, which you should completely ignore.
People seemed to feel the fest when some kind was pulled.
Mm-hmm.
Connie, dare I ask a question?
Naturally.
The trouble follows you, but it never catches up, is what I heard.
Where danger threatens, trouble follows.
Some of us who work for Bob do have trouble.
Connie, do you know if Bob ever got that message about the money that he owes us?
I need special pills to function.
I hope...
You gave Bob that message about the money, you know.
The money?
That he said...
Money?
He said we'd get.
I'll tell you...
I mean...
What message would that mean, now, Dan?
Bob wouldn't lie.
He wouldn't, would he?
Bob did not lie.
I lied sometimes, but you know, that was a long time ago.
I don't lie anymore.
What was the time I lied?
I remember when we laid together, Connie.
Yes.
Oh, now, stop.
Everyone thinks they have sex with me, and some people I did have sex with.
Some people I didn't have sex with.
Because, you know, I don't have sex with everybody.
But a woman has that need.
It's impossible to have sex with everybody.
Just don't even try it.
Just a couple.
Just a couple people.
A couple hundred here and there.
A couple hundred here, a couple hundred there.
Yeah.
What people don't realize is that women have that need, too.
Well, I've always defended you whenever somebody called you a slut.
I always, like, really stood up for you.
You just called her a slut to me a minute ago.
But I was just relating a story I'd heard.
You betrayed her.
You said she was a bad cook.
Well, that's true.
I can't change that.
That's true.
That's just a basic fact.
Yeah, that's not true.
I'm not a bad cook.
She won't even deny that.
She's just said she's not a bad cook.
She just doesn't cook anymore.
All right.
That all depends on what your definition is.
I know I'm not supposed to say this, but I love you, Connie.
I love you.
Don't go away.
That's Reverend Stang.
You recognize his voice.
That's Reverend Stang, ladies and gentlemen.
I know his voice would be more recognizable if it was covered with a pillow.
I can't stop thinking about you.
All right.
I will do that, Connie.
I will keep thinking.
Keep thinking.
But only of you.
Yes, a lot of good may that do you.
And yet, life is composed of hopes that never bear fruit.
And that money.
That money, Bob, owes me.
I'm sorry, Connie.
That's a different matter.
That makes sense.
You know, you don't have to.
You don't have to have people thinking about you.
Bob always said, you've got to have thousands of people thinking.
Thousands of people thinking.
The thousand and one monkey.
That one monk was enough to turn the tide.
That little simmon was a treasure to all life.
He was the first one to think of using a frog to master back with.
Exactly.
The most brilliant monkey since Cheetah.
There we go.
For Lou.
Fred.
Now, let's not get carried away here, ladies and gentlemen.
You know, I want to point out something that may be getting lost in all the fray and foo-for-aw.
This is simply a show.
This is not anything anyone should be excited about.
Worry, see, no problem.
Everything's okay.
There's nothing at all to worry about.
Have you got any evidence with you?
No, I fear not.
He flaked off and, uh, finked out.
Pinked out, we call it.
And what about Mr. Pete Goldie?
Is Pete Goldie there?
Pete Goldie didn't make it either.
Who's going to fight the next war?
He's not there either.
Pete Goldie did not make it.
No, sir.
No, ma'am.
Well, how come there's all kinds of pictures of him on your website?
Because he operates the website.
I tried to get pictures of you up there, Connie.
I swear to God.
I tried.
Wow, pictures of you would be great up there.
Yeah, send me some and we'll use that to decorate the website.
Yes.
We need some more decorations.
Better decoration on that website.
We do.
I don't know who is in charge.
I wish I could personally dedicate, I mean, decorate your website.
All right, gentlemen.
Well, I did take my pills.
There she goes.
Goodbye, Connie.
Goodbye.
I love y'all.
I love you guys.
Come back again, please.
Connie, I love you.
Connie.
I love you.
Go, go, Connie.
No, Connie.
I love her so much.
Connie.
She's gone.
I would do that forever.
Just for now.
It wasn't time for us to meet.
If only she knew how much I love her.
She might change.
All right.
She is gorgeous, too.
I've got to tell you.
Oh, Connie.
Be still, my palpitating heart.
Now, see, if that website switches over to pictures of Connie,
we'll know that Pete was listening.
All right.
Let's check him out.
Ooh.
Came waiting.
Hey, how about this?
That's still pictures of Pete Goldie.
These are pictures of Pete Goldie.
I always wondered what he looked like.
Hey, so you learned how to get the phone in the mix, Dr. Howe.
Yes, it finally occurred to me that there was one more button I hadn't tried pushing all this time.
It's always the last one.
The big red one that said panic on it.
It kept you from pushing it.
Exactly.
That is the one.
It said on.
But I thought, why not?
What the hell?
I mean, you know, you only go around once in life.
It might mean, of course, it also switched off the internet connections.
We switched it back and forth.
But finally, we got something we can work with, live with, exist with.
And so I tell you, I'm tired of all this tension.
I simply want to relax, settle back.
And by the way, we are, as I can tell you know, over the Terminator of Midnight by 10 minutes.
So we can go on as long as you.
Okay.
The connection comple-
Come back, my dear.
My God, he's listening. There's Connie.
There she is on the RadioValencia.org website.
He's put her up on the site.
Look at what Pete Goldie has done.
Praise Pete Goldie. Truly.
He is all that legend says him to be.
I told you.
A holy man who walked alongside Bob.
And by the way, tomorrow, if you manage to make it to the show,
K-Rob has created a new intro for Pete Goldie,
which makes him seem like the second coming of Christ.
It goes on and on with stars, landscapes, planets, spaceships,
and it builds and builds and builds and builds for about three minutes.
Well, folks, I hope this is interesting to you.
It certainly is to some people.
Others may wonder what sort of booby hatch you've stumbled upon.
All I can tell you is this is the Ask Dr. Hal Show live on radio.
The Ask Dr. Hal Show.
No toils not, nor does it spin.
It has no particular use of any kind.
It is anti-utilitarian and in its own way Lutheran
as it interposes no interlocutor,
but is simply a simple-ass agreement between you, the listener, and me, the broadcaster.
An agreement to keep listening because you never know what might happen next.
You might even see a dragon.
A dragon in the bathtub bathing up.
Or a flying saucer that is looking for its cup.
So keep listening, and eventually we're going to do our outro and get off the air.
We have presumed upon your patience long enough.
Yes, we will go our separate ways and remember this night for all it was and might have been.
For all it was and might have been.
This night.
It only now starts to begin.
Aye, shipmate.
Thou hast said it.
So we sailed away for a year and a day to the land where the bone tree grows.
A tree that climbs into the stars and where our souls be showed.
And there atop that glimmering tree,
a glittering lizard sits.
Its gills and puff.
And all across, it feels as it does sit.
And then it hurls its sinuous self down from the tree above.
And only then will it find love.
Because upon the ground impaled it is upon a branch.
A branch.
It's demised.
It did see when it did sail.
And now its guts are wrenched.
I got that one.
This, uh, sorry tale is for all ears.
For nature gives it free.
But when you're hearing dust but beget a new story we have for thee.
That's right, ladies and gentlemen.
Keep tuned and we'll tell you all about it.
We'll tell you another of our terrifying fairy tales.
Terrifying fairy tales.
Just when you thought it was safe to do whatever it was you were about to do.
A small sample from our quartet of death.
Ain't that nice?
Well, you know, the Carnegie Company does make a popular version of that.
A nice little model about five inches long.
I have it too, yes.
Dunkleosteus.
The...
Huge prehistoric giant fish they used to call Dionyctheus.
Excuse me, but who left this Dunkleosteus in my bathroom?
Discovered by a Dr. Dunkle of the Cleveland family.
He wouldn't fit in most bathrooms.
He wouldn't cause he's the size of a railroad boxcar.
Yep, that's right.
He's enormous in size and he's got great big ugly teeth that's all fused into one supertooth.
He's so ugly he's got a skeleton around his eyeballs.
And his mama's so ugly.
Instead of eyelids he's got skeleton lids.
Like the irons of a camera.
The eyelids of God.
His eyes...
Behold, his eyelids try the children of men.
His beak is the size of a Volkswagen.
His face is the one big assembly of dots that shine in the dark.
But yes, it is true, the Dunkleosteus.
Now nobody really knows what the other end of the animal looks like.
All depictions of its tail are pure speculation.
No! No!
But we know it must have had one.
So did it have a hetero-circle tail like most living fish of today?
Or did it have a primitive eel-like flipper system terminating in a point?
Or did it have some other weird, primitive, atavistic character of the primordial ooze?
Alright, so let's just click back one to time transfer.
We're gonna...
Take this Dunkleoptimus.
I'm glad this is only a dream and could never actually occur.
We're gonna go to some sort of lake from...
Let's see, what do we give?
That's 8...
180 million years.
Lake Ukabalapanga-Wadapadawalakala.
That's a...
And that's 180 million years ago.
It was formed here when an enormous meteor petulantly smacked into the earth.
Now, alright, so...
We've got that time, we've got the Dunkleoptimus.
Is that... how do you say it again?
He started as an optimist, but soon, in Darwinian conditions,
defiled into a pessimistic condition.
Alright, let's put a...
The Dunkleosteus.
Dunkleosteus.
But, you know, I have no idea what a Dunkleosteus might be,
but its previous name...
It sounds like something that came out of the bathroom.
Its previous name was Dynichtheus.
Dyn as in terrible, as in dinosaur, as terrible lizards.
And then ichtheus, fish, so his name is Terrible Fish.
This is serious, looking fish.
So isn't that a beautiful name?
Why do they have to...
God almighty is here.
Why do they have to turn it to goddamn Dunkleosteus?
Alright, so let's say we...
And it's Dr. Dunkle discovered it.
Well, that is true.
You should name it after the discoverer.
That's it.
If that's what he wants.
Dr. Dunkle's discovery.
It's the biggest thing in the Cleveland natural history.
It's pretty damn big, although there was another fish...
Next to the Yeti jawbone, Dr. Howe.
...that almost, even uglier, and twice as big, called Xiphactinus.
A giant, hideous, buck-toothed, prehistoric fish.
A fish that begins with an X.
Xiphactinus.
So a Chinese one?
No, but he's got an undershot jaw and big, snaggly, spike-like teeth, and he's huge and
predatory.
And how long is he?
Oh, about 35 to 40 feet.
Oh, that's nothing.
Philo's daughter's tongue goes from here to Alpha Centauri.
Sure, and everyone knew that already, but there's no harm in repeating it again here
on the air.
It's a rare among friends.
For Dunkleosteus existed in the Lower Devonian Period, long before there were any critters
like us anywhere, even in the mind of God.
But if we go through time, and we were allowed to bring one device, what would it be?
Well, I wouldn't want to go paddling in the ocean with Dunkleosteus swimming around.
You would need an oxygen tank.
What if you had a three-masted frigate or something?
Would you need an oxygen tank, or would you instead be hallucinating because of the vastly
greater amount of oxygen in the atmosphere, if you were breathing Earth's atmosphere at
that time?
Now, that's why they had giant spiders in the age of giant insects, because there was
more oxygen in the atmosphere at this time.
So their spicules could absorb more.
How big were these spiders?
Horribly large.
Like horribly in the sense of like a monster?
Like a meter or half a meter?
You wouldn't want a meter.
Oh, really?
It's that kind of like, how big would their web be?
Sort of like that Gillian's Island episode?
Nobody knows if they made a web, although I suppose they do since they appear to have
spinnerets at the end of the abdomen.
But really, now there's some different theory that they were aquatic or something like that.
And how big are they?
About the size of a bushel basket.
But there were larger ones with a greater leg spread.
There were large giant spiders.
There were giant arthropods.
And where did you see these arthropods?
Like those of human beings.
No living man has seen them.
So you're telling the court right now that no living man has seen this creature?
Fossiliferous evidence from the Carboniferous period, eon upon eon before any vertebrated
animal was assured upon the land.
But actually, that's not true either.
They had good cartilage, though.
Actually, there were vertebrates living.
They were living side by side with these giant insects.
And they may remember some way how bad it is to live with bugs bigger than you are and
carry a resentment forward even to today where we view the insect kingdom with suspicion
and alarm.
That's me.
Say the truth.
I also don't feel a bit guilty about devouring chickens because of the age of birds.
Yes.
And that one TV special I saw.
I thought, okay.
We're just getting back at them for the day.
That's all it is.
Yes.
There were the days when we were trod underfoot by their close relatives.
But now they furnish our table.
A well-rounded capon.
Yes.
Nothing would be more tasty when you add the spices.
We need to go.
Is it time to depart?
Is there time for me to do the outro?
Let's keep going, man.
Time to do the outro?
Shall we begin the end?
The end of our hopes and dreams?
It has to end sometime.
So here we go.
I'm going to pull the switch.
Pull the plug.
We have to get Philo back to the nursing home.
I know.
The old boy gets a little frisky, if you know what I mean.
Okay.
We're going to do it.
We are.
I swear we are.
He thinks he's Johnny Wise-mo.
I had so many plans.
So many wonderful plans.
Hold on there, rookies.
Yes, Dr. Hal Showman.
The show is getting ready to go out in style, which we usually do.
And thanks for listening to our broadcast.
Yes, we essay to be here every week, although sometimes we find it impractical.
There are certain personal demands on one's time for which one might, under some system
of justice, be excused from the practice of justice.
from adhering to petty regularities of duty.
I will tell you that as long as there is breath in my body...
What the hell are you handing me here?
What is that? That's awful. It's icky.
I found it on the floor.
He found some ghastly thing on the floor.
Well, there it is, you know.
Horrible in the extreme.
I thought it was a bug at first.
It looked like a bug when you handed it to me.
It looks like a bug that's been covered with hippie hair.
A hippie hair bug?
And I happen to know exactly how a bug of that kind would look.
Yes, of course.
I had hippie hair.
It's long still, but it's thin.
I could hide it all behind my ear.
That's how I travel.
In your salad days,
in your greener times.
They tell me about those.
They tell me I had those.
I'm glad to know that I had such good times.
I'm glad too, because what else do we have?
Even such is time which takes in trust our youth,
our joys,
our all we have,
and pays us with but earth.
And dust.
Our potency.
Who in the dark and silent grave,
our continents,
when we have wandered all our ways,
our eyesight,
shuts up the story of our days.
Sense of smell.
But from this grave, this earth, this dust,
Bob Dobbs shall boing up in triumph, I trust.
Hwuh? Hwuh? Hwuh?
Sure.
Why not?
Isn't that the racket we're in, gentlemen?
Oh, is this on?
Yes, Bob shall be back, and bring comfort to all.
Ah, hwuh?
And now, ladies and gentlemen,
the Ask Dr. Howell Show live on radio
ends its broadcast day at RadioValencia.fm.
Here you see file footage of ducks bobbing in the water,
and now a shot of light breaking through the trees,
all in scratchy old Technicolor film.
The Ask Dr. Howell Show is a product of its time,
and allowed by the management and staff,
for the time being, of RadioValencia.fm.
Despite its name, RadioValencia.fm is hardly ever an FM station.
But in times to come, according to the doctrine of the faithful,
at one time in the near future even,
it will be heard as an actual radio station,
as, according to some tradition,
it recently was, until held back by the demons of darkness.
On behalf of the staff and management of RadioValencia.fm,
the Ask Dr. Howell Show wishes you a profound good night,
and good morning.
Pull somber the horses,
they will not fall asleep,
but rather have a few hours aue after the morning show.
Triple the tears on the abacus,
when in a spell about a welsh jester,
Top the
that fly at the stars in the depth.
Good night, Broadway.
¶ drinr
© BF-WATCH TV 2021