I'll start with you. I'm getting leery of these offshore funds. I suggest we sell 10,000 shares of OUS. What's your opinion?
Give me a moment, Bob. There is something I want to check on that.
The entire San Francisco stock has been stolen. John Bishop has been liquidated.
Yes, my information seems to indicate a sell. I agree.
Now to regular matters. Do you have the joint venture agreement with Yugoslavia handy?
Strange, strange. That looks just like Bob.
No, stop!
We gotta warn Bob that the mask he's delivering is really a Bob Megabyte.
And I didn't want to tell you those from him because you never let me input anything exciting.
But I didn't know it was gonna get Bob in trouble and I was wondering if Megabytes are gonna blow up any nanosecond if we don't.
You are about to participate in a great adventure.
You are about to experience the awe and mystery which reaches from the inner mind to the subgenius.
The new Prime Minister.
You're a swat.
The aims as published in the manifesto are total domination of the world by 1958.
That's what we're planning to do. We've had to revise it. We're hoping to bring a new manifesto out with a more realistic target.
How we aim to go about it is as follows.
We shall move about into people's rooms and say,
Excuse me, we are the World Domination League. May we dominate you?
Dude, Bob's in major trouble, and it's all my fault!
Howdy!
The end.
Howdy.
Well, that was it.
So much for all the...
I got caught dead in my tracks.
Here I am, standing here, three feet away from the microphone.
Trying to work them...
I don't even have the other headphones.
Am I on the air?
No.
No?
We don't...
We're not starting yet, don't worry about it.
Hello.
Go ahead and use the bathroom if you need to, right now.
Here, listen to this for a while.
We're not on the air yet.
Oh, baby, here we go.
We'll be right there.
My lithium, baby, can't you see?
Oh!
Oh, yeah!
My TV is watching me.
You know, if a solar flex ain't nothing but a very expensive hat rack, baby!
Oh, and my goal in life is to be picking my nose on TV
because my TV is watching me.
I can't find my remote.
I don't know where it goes.
My TV is watching me.
I see Michael Jackson and Lisa Marie.
Malcolm X is a hat, but Luther King is a street.
My TV is watching me.
I was in Branson, Missouri, and I was hooked on phonics.
My name's Carbuncle Jones, and I'm supersonic.
I see the one, two, three faces of Bob.
Bob in the replacements.
Bob the self-genius.
Bob.
Bob on three, two, three.
Yeah, everybody!
My TV is watching me.
I got Latter-day Saints messing with me.
And knocking on my door won't let me be.
My TV is watching me.
Well, the outcasts will be heard.
You gotta speak the truth.
Make the weak and the greedy.
I'm reeking the credo.
So what's your name?
Break me my lithium.
Watch him now.
So what's your name?
of me man take your eyes off of me oh yes dear friends yes yes oh uh take your eyes off him
how can you dare to gaze upon that living freak a living monster my friends a mistake of nature
and science mojo nixon uh uh the great mojo nixon and he's got a fantabulastical new album out
uh let me get these little zapalian levels straight here and uh yes uh uh this this uh
new mojo nixon album album whereabouts unknown uh on ripe and ready records we'll be playing more of
this album in the future uh but for now you ought to get your pencil and write down right for the
ripe and ready catalog dear friends and here's that catalog number coming up
uh
p.o box 339 montclair new jersey 07042 once again friends mojo nixon's new album uh ripe and ready
catalog p.o box 339 montclair new jersey 07042 uh yes and uh we heard a little bit of media barrage
there from
uh well we had pieces sent uh by nick nolan up in canada praise reverend nick nolan and uh
puzzling evidence of course uh opening there the kpfa show we'll have lots more of that
at some point this show or next show uh with special guest star sphinx drummond
and uh oh and little bits and pieces from a cartoon show called reboot which is uh something
to check out it it's
looks pretty weird and uh yes dear friends i just got back from the pittsburgh show uh a devival there
and winter star there were some great ranting friends at the pittsburgh show absolutely great
uh father joe mama and uh dr legume uh did their their finest yet legume scared the heck out of
everybody there was a side show called a circus apocalypse there which involved uh no less than
uh bug eating uh bug eating uh bug eating uh bug eating uh bug eating uh bug eating uh bug eating
uh bug eating uh bug eating uh bug eating uh bug eating unique mushrooms and uh orange
sportswear and other tastes there was-, an armada video game with the resistance-based
med았어요ffian
all of a sudden uh a onttype backdoor love story has started oh my god i'm running out
of time guys time is up well let's keep going
And at that point I should probably take out Frank because it's going to get into a lovely
and what can I, I'll just stick this ESO in the background because we've got some more
lonesome cowboy Dave and Chaz recordings from ESO radio there in Cleveland.
So the WCSB listeners, praise WCSB, will have to listen twice to this horrible, horrible thing.
It's more scariness and mystery radio there also with Pee Wee Ardo and some new OBE is coming up.
Friends, it's horrible. Yes, yes, we must help Bob. He has the mask and the frappy.
He's about to sell off Yugoslavia.
Yugoslavia. We must stop him.
And Bob has no idea. I see what you mean. We've got to warn Bob.
Well, there's still a Bob to warn.
We must assume we have been penetrated.
We are sending all Darfur personnel out of the country on trumped up errands.
We want five thoroughly reliable men sent here at once.
Usual covers.
Now, production simply must be increased at the Turin plant.
We believe Giovanni should be replaced.
I'd like everybody's opinion on that.
All existing heroin from Marseille refinery and increased purchases of raw opium in Turkey, regardless of price.
Zach and I agree on Melatesta.
What do you think?
We agree, Bob.
Okay.
Same time, day after tomorrow.
Jesus.
If we've been penetrated.
If I know Bob, God help the smart bastards who did it.
Oh, no. Is that possible?
Is that possible?
Possibly.
Possibly a show has gone through.
Oh, no. Not now.
Oh, no.
Bob.
Bob's racing against the clock.
And the clock's gonna win.
You know what this means, Enzo.
Oh, boy, do I.
Time has come.
Turn on.
To the live view.
Tune in.
And drop out.
Are you ready?
Experiencing an arctic gas gas.
Your colors become electric.
Sounds reverberate.
It's all part of a cosmic.
Unconscious.
Turn on.
Tune in.
And drop out.
Are you ready?
Man, you're talking about a war crime.
I got one.
We got one for you now, friends.
Oh, that was OBE.
Out of band experience.
You should call them up for their catalog.
One six one seven lick OBE.
Can't say that number enough for you.
It's actually a really fun answer machine thing that you get to hear.
And now I don't want to have to deal with these guys again.
But we're going to have to go back in there.
Friends back in that ugly, ugly, ugly place.
The studio at WCSB.
For Einstein's Secret Orchestra.
History.
Man.
Right!
Gaze deep into your radio speaker.
And you can visit heaven anytime you want.
It's a big, big lie.
Journey to the center, to the very center of the web of your mind.
Man was not meant to fly.
Hundreds of people reported seeing and sense in the belt of their human.
The good, the slack, and the Dave.
Woman was not meant to kiss the bird.
Yep.
Dave was riding across the prairie,
toting his drum,
toting his guitar,
shooting fairies.
Shooting fairies out there.
They were extinct by the time he made it across the range.
By the time the range wizards made it there,
there were only five people left.
Yee-haw!
Lonesome cowboy Dave all alone there on the prairie.
Talk about heliocentric world.
The lava pools was melting.
Him and those angels that he could hear whispering in his head.
The angels that told him,
Dave,
who to kill.
Dave.
You know who.
You know who, Dave.
They told him who to kill.
He was a gunslinger.
Yeah.
Gunslinger and a pooter pop.
He was a holy gunslinger.
He was a preacher.
A preacher on the range, on the wild, wild west.
A gun guru with a fast hand and a quick conversation.
The gun.
The gun because it has no sex.
The gun is the perfect teacher.
The gun has no name.
The gun has no identity.
The gun has no sex.
Oh, no, not the gun.
Not the gun.
The revolution come from the gun.
The revolution is a thief.
He was the mal-quoting.
Cowboy that rode the range.
Lowbrow spouting.
Carrying that little red book and the big black book.
And also.
There was no contradiction in him to Dave.
My cage and his cage.
And he won.
He was going to bring communism and Christianity to the west at the same time.
Get down on your knees.
Get down on your hands and knees.
Do you see who this is before you?
This is not the picture of J.R. Bob Dobbs.
This is Vladimir Indy.
He's Lenin.
And I want you to know what he did.
Did you ever hear the story of Lenin's raincoat?
No, no, I mean Lenin's overcoat.
Oh, hold down there, cowboy.
I want to make a few introductions here before they go and scramble your brains completely.
Welcome to this batch of recordings by Olo T. Schickelgrover and the Happy Philanthropist Orchestra.
Our first tune is a little number that goes something like this.
I don't even know what you always say about me.
This is so.
Uh-oh.
I am a jelly pill donut
Ich bin ein Berliner
This is ESO Radio
and my guest in the studio
is not the normal Einstein secret orchestra.
No.
No, the baboon is not here tonight.
The violin is not here.
Well, she might be later.
In the studio
for your listening pleasures
this evening
this evening only
and only on WCSB.
Visit heaven anytime you want.
Anytime?
Anytime.
Day or night.
Simply gaze skyward
and point that third nostril
directly above the emerald wings.
The princes we are Doe,
lonesome cowboy Dave,
and the reverend Ivan Stang.
My name is Chaz
and I'll be mixing this whole mess.
So sit back and do your job.
He's the mess mixer.
Don't relax.
And we're gonna play a game.
Ha!
My friends.
Game time.
We're going to play a fun game called
The Subgenius Reality Reboot.
La la la la la la la la.
Pornological de-mentertainment.
With your mind in mind.
As I used to say back in the old days,
but seriously now friends,
this is a game that works from your radio,
out.
You plugged a little disk into your radio.
Go ahead.
The one that came in the mail.
That slipped out from between the pages of that magazine.
You know.
It's so repugnant I can't stop at it.
You're gonna love this game, man.
It's better than life.
I hate life.
You'll find it a handy replacement for your life.
I need a handy wipe for my replacing life.
What there was of your life.
I hate life.
It is the bomb.
Guaranteed, friends,
to utterly and totally change your life forever
and get you to think like Dobbs.
And what an awful mistake that would be
for each and every one of you.
So put your hands on the screen.
Go ahead.
Reach up there.
Touch.
Caress the screen.
Screeeen.
And put your ear up against the speaker.
Because what you want to do is get the image injected directly into your eye's retina.
And if you can take those little wires out,
unclip them from the speaker,
and take a little alligator clip and put the same wires from the speaker
right against your eardrum.
You have to use really tiny alligator clips that go down inside your ear
and clip it right to the eardrum
because we don't want any,
anything,
you know,
this doesn't need to be filtered through the air.
It picks up a lot of pollution and conspiracy taint that way.
Now,
lean in.
If you want the quick 10 second,
quick implant brainwash,
just lean in real close.
And when you see Bob come up on the screen,
give him a great big kiss.
Go ahead.
Don't be embarrassed.
Even if you're a guy,
you know,
he's a deity.
It's not like just some guy.
It's Bob.
Go ahead, Dave.
Can you kiss?
Oh, come on.
Go ahead.
You can kiss Bob.
Kiss the hem of his garment.
Oh, God.
Hey.
No, that's not it.
That's kind of gross, man.
Oh, God.
Everybody's grossed out, Dave.
OK, wipe up the Dave slobber off of the Bob hem.
I mean,
remember to use these special handy wipes.
They can retain a disinfectant and not leave you
when the time comes.
And that's right.
Just let the disinfectant roll over you.
It's going to clean out all your hair.
all those other viruses.
It will replace your previous viruses
with a new one.
A special new telepathic brain-eater type virus.
It actually...
What it does is it creates tool-pick hallucinations.
In other words, if you concentrate closely enough...
Focus.
Focus on the music...
...that Chaz is playing there.
Bring everything...
Focus on the music.
Now, concentrate.
Think of Bob dancing to the music like a little puppet.
Focus on that.
Let the wet wear of your very synapses be rewritten.
Just follow the bouncing ball, the bouncing pipe,
and concentrate.
Concentrate, friends.
Help Bob to slant the head...
Half-worlds, just so.
Okay, if Bob can slant the two half-worlds
at just the right metaphysical angles,
it will open up the axis, the astral axis.
You'll be able to cruise the Akashic Records at 78 RPM.
As a symbolic, this is the occlusion of both hemispheres
wherein prismized beauty, Akashic Records,
which did that all, which is happening,
well, will happen, perhaps.
Just look at this show as a dream stimulation device.
Just close your eyes and let the dreams wash over you.
It's what they call an organic virtual reality game.
Yes, yes.
It's a game, only a game.
Let the oracle of the sex goddesses
come to the forefront of your third night.
Nostril.
Drink, drink, deep draft.
Drink steeply of that draft.
What? You have to go to the bathroom now?
All right, you may go to the bathroom.
We all may go to the bathroom before resuming.
Resume.
All right, now reboot the deity.
The deity.
He just lit up.
The deity just lit up.
He's rebooted.
Okay.
Now, what was it we were going to talk about?
We were recreating a human form
of a combination of a new form of recombinant DNA
you had developed,
and also a polyphone which you had developed,
and we were going to go deep, deep, deep into the oracle.
Deep into the oracle.
Just lean into the foam.
Just sink into the foam.
You're floating in a sea of pills, friends.
You're just too blind, deaf, and dumb to taste them, see them, hear them.
Yeah, go ahead, kids.
Oh, yeah.
Make that pact with the devil.
Yeah, listen to that crazy, weird show on the radio.
Go ahead and drink them liquid false slack drugs.
Yeah, go get it.
You're going to sign up.
Sign up with the devil.
I tell you, man, sometimes I can't stop crying, man.
Yeah, play it.
Sometimes I just can't stop crying, man.
Play your music backwards.
Sign up with Satan.
Pay your taxes.
Go ahead.
I tell you, listen to my voice.
I speak at a time.
It's your soul.
I talk to you and I die.
I die on my knees.
I, I, I.
Well, it's your soul for now.
Where is owned?
Which cannot be owned?
What sees?
What cannot see?
What hears?
What cannot hear?
Yeah.
What looks at its own eyes?
What can't look at its own eyes?
Shut up, little man.
Nobody asked you to say anything.
I've had some wonderful ideas for getting the dominating going.
I've got some extremely subtle advertising slogans that should get the public behind us.
You know, Bob isn't one of these namby-pamby,
uh, messiahs that thinks that you have to be forgiven for something.
He, he's not here to forgive your sins.
He doesn't care what your sins are.
He probably never even noticed them.
But he does bring not forgiveness, nay, but an excuse, Bill.
A, a rationalization, a great justification for your sins.
And he sells a $3 certificate that will, uh, guarantee that everyone knows that you have
that all-inclusive divine excuse.
You know, cause what do you really need?
Do you need forgiveness?
Have you done anything that you really need?
Well, I shouldn't ask you that.
But don't you really need an excuse more than you need the forgiveness?
You know, let's be practical about it.
Yeah, yeah.
I saw an advertisement the other day for the Secret of Life.
It said the Secret of Life can be yours for 25 shillings.
Send to Secret of Life Institute, Wilsdon.
Uh, so I wrote away, seemed a good bargain, Secret of Life, 25 shillings.
And, uh, I wrote it down.
And I got a letter back saying, if you think you can get the Secret of Life for 25 shillings,
you don't deserve to have it.
I don't know.
It's some kind of a mystery.
It doesn't make sense.
I mean, you listen to the show and you wonder just what it is they're talking about.
Fine, just go.
We're Bob's only hope.
You haven't lost me yet.
I'm not going to.
Bob!
Dude, go away.
Warning, game corruption.
Yes, Bob, you're okay.
Not good.
This is not good.
Bob!
I am a jelly-billed donut.
Open up my side.
Look in the middle.
You will see a little bit of jelly right there.
I am a jelly-billed donut.
Get a little bit of powder sprinkled on my top.
Leave it on there.
Oh, man.
It's enough to drive you completely out of your mind, isn't it?
Yes, this is Olo T. Schicklgruber there with the happy philanthropist orchestra.
Frightening.
No, it's on the air.
Why can't I...
I'm all scared.
I'm all confused.
I thought I could hear and see and be TV, but...
But is that the one I'm thinking of?
No, no, that's not...
I'm all wrong here.
That's...
Well, see and see, and I don't see.
See never will.
Gosh darn it.
What's wrong with Channel 2?
Channel Toodaloo.
It just doesn't...
It has a real hard, hard bad thing.
Oh, no point in complaining about it.
Okay, you better get it.
Boy, it's dancing all over the place.
That effervescent...
Oh.
Phantom spirit.
Swirling and twisting.
Look at it go.
Around and around and around.
There we go.
We're backing up the spirit.
And let's see here.
See if you can...
It seems to be a VH problem.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, UVH, I think it is.
Oh, I do not.
Just see if there's a special control.
You know, they often have a little teensy knob on the back or the side for the V.
Let's see here.
Whoa, whoa.
See these newer...
Oh, you had it for a moment.
Oh, yeah?
Okay, all right.
Do you have the VH knoblet?
There.
Oh.
Yes, in Gobbler's Knob, Nantucket,
this strange stone was found.
A new system narrowing and broadcasting your brain.
So if you're watching Channel 2, that's what's happening.
We're joining a little bit late the scary, spooky story.
In fact, we don't even know what the scary, spooky story is.
It's the story of the lost jewelry of Atlantis.
Not that again.
Well, there it is.
In all its impotent splendor.
Shut up, little man.
I got a decent dinner ready.
Nothing happened with the dinner.
Because you crucified it.
You ruined it.
Shut up, little man.
But Dr. Legume demonstrated last week with a couple of spoons in a restaurant
that you can, in fact, gaze upon your own eyes.
He did.
He was.
He used a spoon on either eye inserted.
Now, kids, don't try this at home.
This was done by a professionally trained subgenius psychic surgeon,
Dr. Katahdin Legume, in a Chinese restaurant.
And he would insert the spoon underneath the eyelid,
the bottom of one eye, and underneath the other eye,
and slowly, carefully...
Slowly.
try the eyeballs out of his socket without disturbing he would stretch the
optic nerve and the muscles but he wouldn't tear them and he'd pull his
eyes out pop them out just enough and then turn them inwards so that he could
actually be looking from one eye into the other eye.
or then he would fork over his eyes and they look just like
Gordy on Star Trek it was amazing it was it was funny dinner tricks and it's a
shame that we couldn't bring the opening act from the Pittsburgh subgenius'
diVivals to Cleveland because there was a wonderful opening act called circus
apocalypse do you remember them princess we are the
Yes I do. It would be very hard for me to forget about that.
I'll never forget the things that I saw them do that night.
It was a return to the good old days of vaudeville.
You know, kids are bored with MTV and the public executions
and the broomsticks up the wazoo on TV nowadays.
So they like to see live shows where people bleed for their art.
I mean, this is real art, friends.
You call them people?
This guy, this young practicing artist stood in front of this
dues-paying subgenius crowd and hammered a nail,
a six-inch nail, into his nose, straight into his human nose.
Seen here on screen six.
You really did it.
You call it a human nose?
He then extracted the nail and replaced it with a long screwdriver.
Deep into his sinuses, his third nostril,
opened up all the way.
And he said that it...
We said, does it hurt?
And he said, not enough to...
get off.
And then this young man at this subgenius revival,
and this is the kind of religion we're in, friends,
he stood up there and he ate handfuls of live mealworms,
live crickets, and one screaming Madagascar cockroach
to demonstrate that,
to demonstrate his agreement with vegetarians
that people shouldn't eat dead meat,
but should only eat living meat.
Or light bulbs.
He also ate a light bulb.
And then to top off the show,
this great, greatest of all subgenius creatures
had his lips sewn shut...
With piano wire.
With piano wire and a needle.
Live on stage,
to demonstrate the futility of subgenius preaching,
which we may also be demonstrating tonight.
We sometimes locate stuff for Christ.
The Church of the Subgenius is, of course,
a completely unique organization among covert
and information-sharing groups,
since its public facade of excessive and ludicrous fantasy
has made it possible to be absolutely and publicly truthful
about its aims and goals.
Its continuous cries of wolf
deliberately destroy its credibility,
making secrecy unnecessary.
You don't know all you want to know, man.
You can't know all you want.
The facts of Dobbs' origins, nature, structure, and intent
appear to be another set of fantastic fictions.
The Church's hide-in-plain-sight approach
to sensitive and dangerous information
makes it possible for anyone to penetrate the organization
and retrieve and disseminate any information.
It's like hermetically sealed, man.
Nobody can get in there. Nobody can get in there, man.
It's like a spider. It's like...
It's like a web of...
Yeah.
You know what I mean. It's just...
It's an interesting web.
You can get into the web.
In fact, you know,
the mouth of the great spider
of the Dobbs Palace
is the only way to get all the way to the very center
of the web.
Man, this stuff's all covert, man.
This stuff's all covert. It's all hush-hush, man.
You don't want to get into this stuff, man.
You don't want to go in there, man.
Oh, anybody can get in.
Nobody wants to go in there, man.
You want to know about it, but you just want to know enough, man.
You don't want to know all about it, man.
Oh, it looks like a lovely fairytale.
It's a fairytale palace from outside.
Oh, yeah, when you first dial it up,
you're looking at the prettiest, like, Cinderella's palace
there on the screen.
And you say the magic words,
and the great gate opens up,
and the stone rolls aside,
and suddenly you're looking right into the mouth of the spider.
The eyes of the spider.
The eyes of the spider have created
cool animation in them,
so that you just want to stare at it.
It's like computer animation.
Dobbs head mandalas.
And the ears of the spider are what you're listening to right now.
And they look so pretty, and it all sounds so pretty,
that you just want to just stroll.
That spider's jaw opens up,
and that red carpet-like tongue rolls out.
Oh, you just want to stroll right in.
And you want to just, you know,
you're looking back into the web site of Bob.
You'll find out everything you need to know in there, friends.
It's the link that leads to the center.
Yes, the very center of the web itself.
Of course, you don't get to the very center at first.
You gotta pass over the tonsils of the great spider.
Slide down that long, slimy chute.
And you find yourself landing on your butt right in the middle of the great vault.
The cathedral, we call it.
It's actually the thorax of the spider.
You're kind of in the center of his chest.
And that's where we worship.
We have an altar set up there with a big TV on it.
That's where the naked zombies for Bob go dancing around that great altar.
The arachnid dancers.
And you can, when you're standing there in the middle of the great vault,
the cathedral of slack,
you can see eight hallways leading off out of that huge chamber.
Eight hallways.
You can pick your way.
You can wind your way down those hallways.
There's the hall of sex hurt.
That's the one everybody usually tries first.
It's got the word sex in glowing neon.
Oh, baby.
At the entranceway.
You go in there thinking, oh, boy, I'm going to see some of that subgenius,
pornological, demontertainment.
Oh, yeah, I'm going to see some of that.
I'm going to see them naked stripper preacheresses like I've heard about.
Or maybe there'll be pictures of Reverend Susie the floozy in there.
Oh, yeah.
It's a madness of gold, baby.
Such a pleasure.
But, friends, it's even better than that.
At the end of the hall of sex hurt,
you get to have sex with the great spider.
And she'll lay her eggs in you.
And she'll spew you right back out onto the web.
Only now you're one of her agents.
One of her pipe smokers.
But let's not get ahead of ourselves.
You can pick any of the other halls.
After you've got the eggs laid in your bowels,
you could go down and visit the hall of bulldada.
I am full now, man.
I am full bulldada now, man.
I am ready. I am full.
That's the tunnel that leads to the greatest bad movies
and silliest radio preachers in the universe.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
Go down the hall of evils.
Into the house of hate.
Into the cavern of conspiracies.
And when you get out of the hall of evils,
then you get into the hall of goods.
And that's when we sell you some of those goods.
And all it costs is just little tiny chump change.
Bits and pieces of your useless soul.
Yes.
I mean, this is a religion.
This isn't just a, you know, this isn't the home shopping network.
Sure, you can buy the stigmata.
You know what you can do with that stigmata?
Do you know what you can do with a big enough shop?
A hole in the palm of your hand?
Well, I'm not allowed to talk about it on radio, friends,
but if you'll step into the hall of answers, you'll find out.
What would I like to know?
Name, name.
Oh, you're looking for the hall of questions.
Oh, I forgot I asked you a question.
We don't know what's in the hall of questions yet.
It is a question.
That's what we don't know.
But what we do know is in the hall of science.
That's where, friends, in the hall of science,
there's the dead man's secret drawers.
Prepare the laboratories.
It's a novel experience.
Let's notice the...
Where you can learn your future, yes?
The oracle.
...the future in this man's liposuction.
The fat makes a configuration.
It is an anomaly.
Yes, we're able to read your future
in the patterns of the liposucted fat
removed from your thighs, your hips, buttocks...
And 250-pound rapists.
...during psych... psychic surgery.
Oh, you need to know this.
Answer the game.
Come on in.
Yeah, this is the only computer video game
that will actually perform psychic...
...psychic surgery on you.
The game itself will push its fists
so deeply into your belly,
your tummy muscles,
that the skin will part without excess bleeding,
and the shaman will be able to remove
the chicken gizzard tumor or...
...foul, disgusting cyst
composed of everything bad you ever ate,
all the preservatives.
And he will extract that foulness,
that evil humour from within you.
And then, why, covered with some chocolate sauce
and, uh...
Yes?
...set afire with a little cognac on top,
why, you'll have...
...the finest dessert.
Oh, fleshy lantern, that's what you want to put in there.
Fleshy lantern?
So, come on in, folks.
Bob's Diner.
At the sign of the spider.
Queel on in.
Come get caught in the web.
Come after...
It's bouncy.
It's like a great big net,
like at the surface that the acrobats fall into.
You can just jump into the web and bounce up and down.
It's important.
It's a little sticky, sure,
but...and you'll get a little on you.
But it feels good.
Yeah.
And those cuddly, furry spiders
that crawl in and out of your mouth
while you lay there all hypnotized.
Oh, they tickle, don't they?
They are so tickly.
Those little tarantulas.
They're just agents of the big tarantula.
Antimony.
And when they've laid their eggs inside your glands...
Oh, they're so sweet.
...you'll be able to go out and lay eggs yourself.
Now, what I want to know is,
can you perform mystic surgery with a spider egg on your belly?
You'll go out and lure your friends into the web
where you can impress them by performing psychic surgery on them,
inserting, yet again, more eggs.
And every time you bring in a new customer,
you move a little bit higher up on the pyramid.
That's right.
If you can...once you've signed up,
if you bring in five more friends...
Don't be afraid to climb the ladder.
...you'll climb the ladder,
the ladder of the web,
until you're sitting right under the abdomen
of the great spider herself,
catching those warm eggs as they poot out down your throat.
Oh.
Mmm.
Better than an all-you-can-eat breakfast at Shoney's.
I want to change it.
I want to change it. I want to go...
Scrambled spider eggs.
They're...
And they're made of information, friends.
It's not like we're adding poisons or evil preservatives or anything.
No, no, we're just filling you up with knowledge.
That's all.
Did you ever see that movie Videodrome?
It's like that, but it's not like that.
Pearls of wisdom.
Have you seen the pearl?
Have you had the dream of the pearl?
Does this viscous liquid contain...
Are you capable of storing more information than the average?
It's okay.
You...
Yes, yes, you just sort of slurp it up.
You just place yourself right under the abdomen of the great mother spider
and let her...
start excretin' that web fluid right in.
You'll...
You'll have spidey powers yourself, Dave.
Psychic-a-bin war boys.
Rolling around and around.
Oh, boy.
Time.
Mother spider-built time.
But it's not like occult or anything.
This isn't like one of those Egyptian occultists,
uh,
you know,
like,
this isn't one of those satanic deals.
Uh,
when we worship the great spider at the center of the web,
it's not like we're,
uh,
you know,
just, uh,
trying to condone evil or human sacrifice or anything like that.
Oh, but she's a spinning woman.
No, no, no.
Or, or, uh...
She's his grandma.
No, no.
We just want you to have fun.
We want you to join with us in,
in the brotherhood,
in the sisterhood
under the web of the great spider.
Who protects us.
Yes, she protects us.
She nurses us.
We may nurse at the teat,
at the information teat of the great spider,
of the sticky, sticky web.
All the victim shares a blood,
and the blood expands.
Look at Chaz fiendishly playing that gigantic organ of his.
With that wax mask on his face.
Look, Princess Wee is sneaking up behind him.
She's, she's tiptoeing up behind Chaz.
She's, she's reaching out as if to lift the mask from his face.
She's going to do it.
She's grabbed the mask.
He turned around.
His hideous, hideous face.
You're listening to the Subgenius Radio Ministry
Hour of Slack.
For free information on Bob Dobbs
and the Church of the Subgenius,
send a self-addressed stamped envelope to,
got your pencil ready?
Bob, Post Office Box 140306,
Dallas, Texas 75214.
That's Bob.
Shut up little man.
Nobody asked you to say anything.
Trying to get machines in to do everything that we're doing.
He's very fond of machines.
He wants machines to be doing everything.
And this will give everybody else a lot of leisure, you see.
And if everybody has a lot of leisure,
they'll be forced to read his ghastly old book.
That's Bob, P.O. Box 140306,
Dallas, Texas 75214.
He'd like to see machines all over the place, you see,
spying on what we're doing.
But very soon, you see,
all the machines will be wandering around
on spindly legs, great metal spindly legs.
And we'll all be living in little metal boxes.
And the machines will pass by,
an awful antennae will come in through the window.
And they'll check up.
They'll all start breeding amongst themselves, the machines,
and going out to the cinemas with each other
and sitting and whispering in the dark.
And holding their metallic tentacles together
and reproducing.
It's a horrible idea.
I can't bear the ideas of machines.
I can't bear the ideas of machines doing everything.
Hey, Chaz, remember those interesting recordings
that we brought in?
There's the Charlie Manson karaoke.
Which crept out on two legs.
And the ultimate heavy metal song,
the song that pretty much tells the truth about heavy metal.
The song that every kid should be forced to listen to
on glue.
That's number...
Did you flip your tape?
Yes.
Mine is gonna be coming out soon.
By the way, you are listening to WCSB Cleveland,
the radio voice of Cleveland State University.
This is ESO Radio.
What was the cut on that?
Number 666.
Anything you want to say about this?
Well, this band, Kings of Feedback,
out of Boston, Massachusetts,
I think these guys have maybe taken heavy metal
to its final logical extreme.
I think that any child, teenager, young person
who's been considering a career in satanic devil worship,
backmasked heavy metal music,
should take a good, close, hard listen
to this sorry, sad situation.
Oh, my God.
It's pretty serious.
Kids...
Listen to it backwards.
Well, they're gonna listen to it backwards
at the same time.
Oh, I got it all messed up now.
Did you erase that CD?
Man, it was the only one I had.
He pushed record instead of play.
I have something called C-index on here.
Oh, wrong one.
Here you go, kiddies.
Chew on this for a while.
Yeah, kids.
Rock music is leading our young people
to drug addiction and promiscuity.
to the power of the cosmos
and all the powers in command.
And virtue in the form
and all else that has that power.
Ah!
Oh, .
Oh, my God!
Ah!
You seem a little nervous.
My friend.
When the strength of my soul
You're telling me from beyond
You'd better be ready
To speak your piece
You call me from beyond
You disturb my rest of sleep
With your childish games
You don't know what you're playing with
This is not a game
But it's a voice in you
This is your life
You're not alone
You're not just another stupid heavy metal band
Listen to your music backwards in reverse.
If the troops they were foot
You know you can't get in
Heavy metal, heavy metal, heavy metal
I'm a singer, you know
Where are these metal cuts?
The bottom is dry and sweet
This is heavy, get it?
Oh!
You wait for me
I used to be a nice guy just like you
And then I found
The truth is in the taking
You know I'm slow
And I will need a line
But you have a spit in your face
I'll tell you how I got here
You're ready for me
You ready for me
Can it be ready to face the consequences?
It's never too late to redeem yourself
One last chance
That's all you have
It's up to you
You ran from me
No escaping my eyes
You will see them in every dream
You ran from me
You never escape the eyes
The sun will never shine with these eyes
Would you like a drink?
You ran from me
You'd better be ready to face the truth my friend
I'm here for you
Slo-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o
Edward? Edward? Edward?
The number you have reached
1-800-OUTBEND
Has been changed
The new number is
617-LICK-OBE
Please make a note of it
At the tone, record your message
J.R. Bob Dobbs told me to call and here's my really weird message
Bob Dobbs
Still distorted
No one could have anticipated this thoroughly modern telephone could wreak such havoc
Hello?
Edward?
800-NOB-O-O-B-E
I love you every time I call, I love it
You guys are sick but I think I love you very very much
Call me to get me free information by mail, now
Oh my God, all that noise is gonna drive me into orgasm
617-LICK-OBE
If people would just listen to our music they'd see we have a humanistic message for the kids
You know, social and environmental concerns
You're gonna slay us all!
Are you a voyeur? Do you like to watch?
What's your name?
Bob
Hi Bob
What are you gonna do with it Bob?
Tell me, tell me how you like it if I came in your room right now
Uh huh
What would you do to me?
Baby if you came in my room right now I'd want you to put your feet
Oh boy
Oh yeah Bob
Oh yeah
Uh huh, do you think you can find
Uh huh, do you think you can find my sub G spot Bob?
I think so
Come up baby, find it for me
Yeah
Oh Bob, oh yeah
4, 3, 2, 1, fire!
This is all Bob ya know
Ah ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
Augh