I'm sorry, I'm caught in traffic. It may be a while before anybody can get into the station.
Don't you have an emergency DJ? Somebody with a deep voice hidden in a drawer?
Just follow the format. You've only got a few more hours.
Well, for a start, I'm going to sit here and get smashed out of my mind.
And I also have it on very good authority that the world is coming to an end.
So I thought I'd go home and watch it on television.
Typical.
Yes, typical.
Come on out, willing slaves. Welcome to radio school.
Don't fight.
Move it.
Say, where's the student union? Where's the co-ed you promised us?
Shut up and get inside.
We're not criminals. We just want to learn to talk good on the radio and make big bucks.
You'll all be radio heroes soon. Just climb up, mush mouths, and listen to the boss in the chair.
What boss? Where?
Oh, you can't see me, can you?
Well, that's the magic of radio, baby.
Hey, hello, students. I'm the Lightning Bug.
And welcome to the Lightning Bug School of Pirate Broadcasting.
Not affiliated with those pirates at the Buggery School of Flycasting.
You whippy noodles will be given new voices and personalities through EST, Electronic Sensuality Transformation.
I'm going to turn you brown-shoed squares into disc jockeys working for my secret broadcast cave.
And now, the subgenius, our boss, what?
Watch me.
They'll dance out of their pants to the sounds you send them.
And you'll all get French jeans, out-of-sight salaries, and all the coffee and cigarettes you can drink.
You'll be stars, and they won't even know who you are.
J.R. Dobbs, Bob Dobbs, J.R. Bob Dobbs was on the number one list of frauds and phonies for Time Magazine, and I didn't know who he was.
Exactly.
And J.R. Bob Dobbs is the creator of the Church of the Subgenius.
This guy, the Reverend Ivan Stang, is one of their...
Disciples.
Yeah.
All right.
You know, it's funny.
I don't think Jesus had a disciple named Dopey.
Poor Bob.
You, dipsticks, stars, it makes me laugh.
Take them to the secret broadcast cave and train them all to talk like me.
Real sexy.
Come on.
To help carry on our important work, I want you to join the secret squadron.
I want your blood.
And I want your souls.
And I want them both right now.
I want you to get up now.
I want all of you to get up out of your chairs.
I want you to get up right now and go to the window, open it, and stick your head out and yell,
I'm as mad as hell, and I'm not going to take this anymore!
I'm not going to take this anymore!
I'm going to take this anymore!
And I do, too.
Good.
This is Ren Hoak.
And this is Stimpson J. Catt.
Of the Ren and Stimpy Show.
And you're listening to the Hour of Slack.
Keep listening, you idiots!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Else I shall kill you!
Nostradamus forecast that Armageddon would come in the 20th century, the days in which we live.
Born in hell, you little green bastard!
Hey, hey look up in the sky!
So what Ozzy, it's just a rainbow.
It's a magic rainbow.
Hey, what'll it be guys?
I'll have a coffee please.
Coffee for me too Joey.
Yeah.
Thank you, coffee's great.
I got that war anxiety, my nerves, I'm a bundle of nerves,
it's like it's coming at you from all sides, you try to forget it,
and you turn on the TV, there's a story, all the scuds,
Yeah, it's everywhere and stuff.
and Tel Aviv and the blood, and it's gonna get bad.
You look like a bundle of nerves, maybe you could use something to eat.
Look, they got nice Danish over there.
Yeah, I wouldn't touch those Danishes, they're as hard as a rock.
Maybe.
A rock, a rock, a rock, ah there it is, again, a rock.
Hey, wait, wait, wait, it's getting a little late, but a nice, just, just, maybe a nice bowl of cereal, settle your nerves.
A bowl of cereal, well it's a little late in the day for cereal, cereal,
Syria, that's the country that borders the north of Israel,
Hey, hey, hey, calm down, you're going crazy here.
they're gonna get sucked into this war as soon as the Arab coalition goes under, ba-dum!
Change the subject, change the subject, okay?
Alright, alright, alright, I'm sorry.
You know, your birthday's coming up, right?
My birthday.
That's a happy thing, you know.
That's a happy thing, no more war talking about me.
Maybe you want a nice watch like the one I got here, look at this nice Rolex my wife gave me here.
Hey, yeah, it is a nice watch, is that a fake Rolex or is that real?
No, it's real, real.
It's real, it's real, Israel, Israel again with the Israel,
and Tel Aviv, those poor people, they got the scuds dropped on them,
they don't know, they're gonna snap those people and I'm not gonna blame them when they do.
Dave, Dave, Dave, Dave, let's just talk about our families, okay?
Alright, I'm sorry, I'm all, I'm all, I'm not obsessing on it, it just happens to be that we're in a crisis.
You know, life goes on.
Alright, alright.
How's your kid?
Oh, my big guy, he's great, I get, well, you know, he gets into trouble sometimes,
I had to have a talk with him, you know, I sat him down last night, I sat him down,
Gotta do that sometimes.
And I sat him, sat him, sat him, Hussein, the bloodthirsty butcher of Baghdad.
No, no, no, stop it, stop it.
He's like another hitman.
Somebody's gotta stop him, but I don't know how we got, it's over, it's not about making aggression.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, you know, I know what you like, football.
Football, let's talk football.
Now, who's gonna do it, the Giants or the Bills?
Oh, the Giants, you can bet the Giants, I'd put money on that.
Nah, I bet it's gonna be the Bills, cause, you know, it'll be over quick, man, the Bills,
Half hour, I bet, the whole thing.
Half hour, you bet, half hour, half hour, Albertine, half hour, Albertine.
What are you talking about?
Half hour, Albertine, don't you read the papers?
Half hour, Albertine is a base where they keep missiles there, those Tomahawk cruise missiles,
they're launched from command centers and they're gonna go up against the Scuds, everything reminds me of that.
He's gonna take the order, we can have something nice to eat.
Alright, alright.
You guys ready to order?
Yeah, what are your specials today?
Specials today is barbecued sparabs.
Sparabs, that sounds pretty good, I'll try the sparabs.
Sparabs I like, sparabs, sparabs, Arabs, Arabs, and there we go in the war again, I can't stop this.
No, no, don't do this to yourselves, don't do this to yourself like this.
You can't let this take over your life.
No, no, not the end of the world, it's just this little guy out there.
I mean, Scud, see I'm doing it now, I'm doing it, look at my plate, it rhymes with Kuwait, Kuwait, Kuwait.
Why were you Mrs. Grey? I'd get out of here while you still got time.
Few days will put you in Fort Dobbs.
You'll be safe there.
Oh, don't grit.
Okay, grit, don't grit.
Ahhhhhhh!
Apparently, Bob came and did something with all of us.
You've got to see this guy for what he is.
He's a maniac out to rule the world.
What can I do to make you understand?
I love you.
Annihilate, kill, kill.
Sure hate to shoot you in the back like this, but it's the law of the west.
You ain't gonna hit me again, are you?
Now let's see you just drop them pants.
Watch that buzzard, mister.
CUT IT OUT!
My equilibrium, destabilized.
Now that's a little rough, and that doesn't sound too good to the polished ears of the liberals and the modernists, so they soften it down, you see.
And of course they would read that verse, let God be true in every man.
Uh, be an untruth in a measure to a degree by chance in my opinion, they'd say.
Ha ha.
Yeah, let's soften that because somebody might get offended.
Mm-hmm, yeah.
But the Bible says let God be true and let every man be a liar.
But God could blame him if he almost took up the trouble he had, of course.
Annihilate, kill.
Oh!
Talagallus!
Go, go, go, go.
An airplane flight shouldn't be completely safe.
You need a little danger in your life.
Take a fucking chance once in a while, will you?
What are you going to do?
Play with your prick for another 30 years?
What, are you going to read People magazine
and eat at Wendy's till the end of time?
Take a fucking chance.
What do they can decide?
No, we already know
That we are here to go.
We are here to go.
We are here to-
Go, go, go, go, go.
What is real in mind?
What's at the top of the pile?
Where does he draw the line?
Let them figure it out.
Go on and step across.
Just remind yourself that we all need to go.
The odds of you being killed by a terrorist are practically zero.
So I say relax and enjoy the show.
You have to be a realist.
You have to be realistic about terrorism.
Certain groups of people, certain groups, Muslim fundamentalists, Christian fundamentalists, Jewish fundamentalists, and just plain guys from Montana.
Are going to continue to make life in this country very interesting for a long, long time.
That's the reality.
Angry men in combat fatigues talking to God on a two-way radio.
And muttering incoherent slogans about freedom are eventually going to provide us with a great deal of entertainment.
Especially after your stupid fucking economy collapses all around you and the terrorists come out of the woodwork.
You'll have anthrax in the water supply and sarin gas in your air conditioners.
There'll be chemical and biological superpowers.
Case bombs in every city.
And I say enjoy it.
Relax.
Enjoy the show.
Take a fucking chance.
Put a little fun in your life.
I'm not close to love.
Go.
What is really in mind?
Who's at the top of the pipe?
Where does he draw the line?
Let them figure it out.
Go on and step across.
Just remind yourself that we all need to go.
Go.
To me, terrorism is exciting.
It's exciting.
I think the very idea that you can set off a bomb in a marketplace
and kill several hundred people is exciting and stimulating,
and I see it as a form of entertainment.
Entertainment, that's all it is.
Yeah.
Shit.
Take a fucking chance, bunch of goddamn pussies.
Oh, friends.
The times are grim,
but we try not to be.
The ranting there was by George Carlin,
I wonder how he feels about that particular rant now,
but that was mixed in with the Devo song
by Reverend Phineas Narco of Midnight Voice Jail,
which is part of the National Cynical Network.
You can find Midnight Voice Jail on the World Wide Web.
That's the only place you can find it.
Before that, friends,
um,
a collage by me of clips and collages sent in
by champion Jack Codini,
New Monet,
and Artemia Salina,
or Salina,
or whatever,
from Alt Binary Slack,
and the war anxiety comedy piece about the Gulf War
was by Reverend Bleepo Abernathy and Billy West.
The radio school thing came off of a puzzling evidence show,
from a couple of months ago.
There's a lot more puzzling evidence,
old puzzling evidence KPFA show,
very pertinent, however,
with special guest Papa Joe Mama,
and of course, Dr. Howell.
And now, Frank Zappa.
Some take the Bible for what it's worth
When it says that the meat shall inherit me
Well, I heard that some sheik
Has bought New Jersey last week
And you suckers ain't getting nothing
Is Harirama really wrong?
If you wander around with a napkin on
With a bell on a stick
And a pen on a stick
And your hair is all gone
The geek shall inherit nothing
You say your life's a fun deal
And you're up against the wall
Well, people, you ain't even got no kind of deal at all
Cause what they do
In Washington
They just take care of number one
And number one ain't you
You ain't even number two
Well, Jesus freaks
Well, they're friendly, but
The dish they believe
Has got their minds all shut
And they don't even care
When the church takes a cut
Ain't it bleak when you got so much nothing?
So what do you do?
Hey!
Eat that pork
Eat that ham
Laugh till you choke on Billy Graham
Moses, Aaron, and Abraham
They're all a waste of time
And it's your ass that's on the line
It's your ass that's on the line
Do what you wanna
Do what you will
Just don't mess up your neighbor's bill
And when you pay the bill
Kindly leave a little tip
And help the next poor sucker
On his one-way trip
Some take the pie
Whoa, whoa
Whoa
Oh, give me half a dozen for the hotel room
And so it came to pass
That outer space convened a high tribunal
To see whether mankind was worth saving
Chosen to speak in his behalf
Was a wanderer through time
Who was a combination of all men
Of the pious and the fallen
The bold and the meek
The dreamers and the builders
The chaste and the guilty
The great and the poor
The rich and the small
Men of all times
All represented by one
Who came to speak for all
Before the high tribunal
Bob?
What?
Bob, save some for me
Don't worry about it
Pathetic
You don't feel so cocky now, do you?
Whatever he's paying you
I'll double it right now
You know what the tragedy is here, Bob?
We could have been friends
But you wouldn't go through proper channels
You went over my head
That hurt
But life goes on
It's an old story
The fight for love and glory, huh, Bob?
It helps if you think of it as a game, Bob
Every game has a winner
And a loser
I'm cashing you out, Bob
Bob?
People are calling in trying to escape the show
They've given up all hope
That Bob will straighten out and fly right
We're just mopping up
It's almost all over down here
The operation's almost done
35 minutes left until the next news update
Turns out they've bombed Dobbs town again and we heard that Dobbs has sent his family
back to Malaysia.
But cut those potatoes in exactly one inch cubes.
That's our military subgenius specification on those potatoes is one inch cubes only.
Anything bigger or smaller are going to have to be set back for retrofit.
So you may go back to sleep for approximately 20 minutes but then I expect to find you at
your post.
Bye now.
The poor EO Hippas is not used to the war yet.
The war visits her.
As it will visit all of us.
The blocky boots fall down to the ground.
The farmer screams.
off the mountains
my sockets looked down on the chest bone
meadows and the sun dropped down
and the moon ran off
his heels and elbows
and he was chalked
in all the comets to lighten the dust
for
fear they'd be seen
in the sky turned white in the middle of the night
and the big floppy boots
started down into the ground
and the red violin
took the boat for to do the
hoot-doo-ho-down
and the red violin
took the boat for to do the
hoot-doo-ho-down
mama jumped in a circle
and played a chuck right down
ha!
hoot-doo
do-shit-do
the devil chose to
take expressing
ha!
hoo-doo
through the fog
hmm
and a farmer's
floppy boots
stomp down
red-tailed
scream
the hot leg
kicked
and the fire
leaped and lit
red-tailed
scream
the hot leg
kicked
and the fire
leaped and lit
and when the boot
came up
the fire
went out
and hell
was just an ice cube melting off in the ground.
It fell in the wrong circle.
He had a sore red tail.
Once went red, now was pale.
Feet full of five thumb, he was summoned up from hell.
Booted down a spell by a square dancing farmer.
By a square dancing farmer, well.
That old bum was sticking out his thumb when the farmer drew up.
Said, listen, son.
Son, in the horse come paddies, hooves.
If you fall in my circle again, I'll tan your red hide and dance you on your tail.
And pitch you from now to now.
Pitch you from now to now.
In a hot lead kitchen, a fire leads to lit.
In a hot lead kitchen.
In a fire just leads to lit.
In a hot lead kitchen, a fire leads to lit.
In a hot lead kitchen, on a pile leads to lit.
In a hot lead kitchen, on a pile just leads and they can
The fire leads to lit!
Foggy breasts far down, to the ground.
Foggy breasts far down to the ground.
Fly me blue, storm down, to the ground.
Captain Beefheart and the Magic Band, friends from Shiny Beast.
Coming up, some ESO Swamp Radio from WCSB Cleveland
with Dances with Rockets' Lone Cow Dave
and special guest Dr. Legume and Vagina Jones.
But first, on our own show, Reverend Pat Robertson.
Ladies and gentlemen, what we have going on here in the Middle East
is a situation that is filling biblical prophecy from 2,000 years ago.
You dumb chief.
Sheila, Pat will point this out.
Sheila, that's a delicious cake.
Thank you for providing it, by the way.
I'm going to have to have another point.
It's really delicious, and we're going to share that recipe with our viewers at home here.
We can't wait.
But unfortunately, Sheila, we have a real difficult problem here in the Middle East
because, you see, those who bless Israel will be blessed,
but those that curse Israel will be cursed.
And Saddam Hussein, whose name begins with an H like Hitler
and whose name sounds insane,
like someone who's...
who's insane, is definitely cursing Israel.
And so we have what we call an obligation to hell.
It sounds like, you know, in those cities of the plain, Sodom and Gomorrah.
We have decided to send a good percentage of the money that you send
at that toll-free number at the bottom of your screen.
If you will just pledge that money immediately.
Because, see, friends, the anti-times are coming
and the anti-Christ, that is Satan, as precisely,
as the name of the book of Revelation, is here.
And contrary to what most people think,
Satan just is not going to wear a little red outfit.
He's not going to be carrying a fish for you.
He's going to look like a real person,
perhaps someone you know and trust.
Maybe even a televangelist who's always on the verge of constant laughter.
So please, send those pledges now.
You haven't seen any suspicious people hanging around lately, have you?
Well, if you have...
it might be the boy from below.
The man from the basement.
I mean the sub-basement.
Oh, that's right.
They have been seen to crawl out at these times and days,
and sometimes at the end of times.
And some call them gremlins,
others call them little devils,
but we know them as anti-bombs.
See what's on the radio, huh?
Yeah, see if ballroom dancing is on.
See, those guys on there doing that funny show?
Is that supposed to be some kind of...
I don't think it's supposed to be funny anymore.
Things are too serious.
As we stand here on the brink of nuclear Armageddon,
how can even someone think about it?
Yeah, and Armageddon's sick of it anyway.
Why don't they just drop it and get it over with?
In my book, One American Life is worth all the lives in all of Iraq.
I urge that we use the atomic option if it can be used efficiently.
And I urge that we do so now.
My constituents agree with me wholeheartedly.
So we can achieve a sufficient life.
Good boy, Krieg.
I don't know, impressive.
That's not the answer I asked you to give!
It doesn't come to that yet.
No matter how many days I look at Arun & Anu's relationship with automobile movers.
Their relationship's a huge part of what we're doing.
We value bilinguality so that no one's always has to pay their viability bills.
tools. The abortionists have got to bear some burden for this because God will not be mocked
and when we destroy 40 million little innocent babies, we make God mad. I really believe
that the pagans and the abortionists and the feminists and the gays and the lesbians who
are actively trying to make that an alternative lifestyle, the ACLU, People for the American
Way, all of them who tried to secularize America, I point the thing in their face and say, you
helped this happen.
Well, I totally concur and the problem is we have adopted that agenda at the highest
levels of our government and so we're responsible as a free society for what the top people
do and the top people, of course, the court system.
Amen.
That's right.
You asked for it.
Remember?
Remember, there's a big difference between kneeling down and bending over.
He's got $20 million in his heavenly bank account.
All from those chumps who was born again.
Oh, yeah.
He's got seven limousines and a ride-a-plane.
All for the use of his special friends.
Oh, yeah.
He's got $1,000 suits and a Wembley tie.
Girls love to stroke it while he's on the phone.
Oh, yeah.
And the House of Representatives, he's a groovy guy.
When he gives thanks, he is not alone.
He is dealing, he is really dealing.
IRS can determine where the hook is.
It is easy with the Bible to pretend that you're in showbiz.
And you are.
And the two.
They will get him.
They will never get him.
Pull them.
There is the naughty stuff that he did.
And it's best in cases like this
to pretend that you are stupendous.
He's got residential help all along the way.
He says the grace while the lawyers chew.
Oh yeah, they sure do.
And the Governors agree to say
He's a lovely man
He makes it easier
For them to screw
All of you
Yes, that's true
Cause he helps put the fear of God
In the common man
Snatching up money
Everywhere he can
Oh yeah
He's got twenty million dollars
In his heavenly bank account
You ain't got nothing, people
Thank the Lord
Man
Whoa
Yeah
Hey
I don't understand it
I was trying to change the subject
You people aren't American at all
Because the whole thing actually just bums me out
If I go into the real world for very long
I get so sick at heart and disgusted
And confused
That I prefer to stay in this little fantasy land
Of sick humor and subgenius artwork
I don't understand it
I try like baby
Surrounded by Dobbs heads
I am often crying
This world is so nauseating to me
They make me feel much more protected
What are you gonna do when a 757
Comes tearing through your wall
And tearing down all your Dobbs heads
Well even before this end
You have to worry about your hands are glowing
Sometimes parts of your body are falling off
What are you gonna do when Bin Laden comes after you
Come knocking on your door
You know Chas, Voltaire said
If you want to change the world
Cultivate your garden
Thomas Jefferson said
I think I'm going to go in my bed and go to bed
And the price of freedom is diligence
Yes, well I think I'll work on my own personal freedom
And my own personal kingdom
Liberty is a cracked bell
Which isn't very big
But it is mine
Oh screw it all
You sound like a bunch of spoiled brats
You should get back to the basics
The basics
Seek comfort my brothers
In the city
To me there's nothing like eating a pound of dog food
And all you need in life
Was that titty
Get back to the titty brothers
Back to the titty
How can anyone argue with that
That's what I said
That's what we said earlier
They're not getting enough titty
Don't worry about your job
Don't worry about
Terrorism
Or anything
Everybody's just got enough titty
They're uptight about the titty
Mammon is the mammary we suck
They can't just say
They're uptight about the titty
That's a beautiful titty
That's such a lovely titty
And just
You know
Leave it at that
Leave it out
No they have to cut it off
No they gotta
Or hide it away
Or get a little
You know
Put an airplane into it
And then
Sublimate it
They gotta replace it
With a
With God
Or some big ugly rock in the desert
What do they know of
The glories
Of the round soft things
That is the birthright
Of every primate
Every mammal nay
Indeed every mammal
Loves the soft things
Loves the soft round things
This is a hardwired
Instinctive thing
The teat is the friend
Of all living things
Men and women love the titties
Do they not
Now come on admit it
Just as the childish
How can
And yet
The mighty lion enjoy the teat
The gun is good
The penis is evil
The penis shoots seeds
Jesus Christ
No it's still coming
It hasn't even been touched
It's shooting lightning bolts from its eyes
The flames are being blown from the sky one by one
Trouble on Mars
How nice
Hey just sit down relax now
As I put your feet up on the table
Like you were the king of this smorgasbord
It's your day here
Open wide
You're a subgenius
Now you
Spread em
You paid your thirty dollars
And you're all
This will be a little cold when it comes in
Yeah don't worry about the feelings of you know
Like climbing up there
Just relax man
Just relax
Relax those muscles
Quite natural there W
Just hang on
It's okay
It's gonna be over in a second
You'll feel a little prodding
Now if your eyes begin to bleed
Don't move your fingers here
We'll just take care of it for you
Don't mind that squiggling inside
Alright you'll be seeing Bob any second now Mr. President
Oh yeah there's a lot of usually some intestinal discomfort
Yes of course
We're gonna be stepping back here a little bit
We don't think it's gonna get messy
Can you imagine what that wreck could look like?
The troops go marching into Kuwait
Preparing to liberate the innocent Kuwaitians against the evil Barakas, Khode and Sadani
They know that the Arakian army cannot stand up against the will of the Emperor's troops
The evil Emperor who has secretly moved his troops under the guise of a UN resolution
Into position to take over the planet
Alright check off-route mine infrared sensors
They know that only through the guise of liberation
Fire projectile targets when they reach optimum position
The will of the Satan who say
Improved surveillance, target acquisition, intelligence gathering and dissemination systems all checked
I don't think it's very funny to make fun of this war
Forward
Command control communications and intelligence
It's the...
3C cubed is the way the war is happening
Stand off engagement of armor
Composite armor, main armor, special armor elements, ceramic plate, carrier material
It's war I just, I don't understand this
Operation protection, bulkhead armor, external bulkhead, bulkhead surveillance and general bulkhead accuracy
C3L systems are likewise patient to successful implementation
The Joint Tactical Information Distribution System, JTIDS
Presently in development with 10 units purchased for testing
Will be deployed in 580 units by FY90 single channel ground air
Perhaps something dangerous
Why does an increase of muzzle walls seem like a corresponding to the increase of the armor?
The
The The
The The The
RAGE
calorie
Insane
crazy
Man who's saying here? We've got superior to
I could have sworn it was J.R. You shot him
Bob
If you are wise you listen to me
Eating as much as an elephant eats. What are you at getting terribly fat?
What do you think?
That I
Don't like the look
Of my
Love it
Oompa loompa doompadee da
If you're not greedy you will go far
You will live in happiness too
Likely
Oompa loompa doompadee doo
Doompadee doo
Bob?
Now shrunken heads for all occasions
Collect them, swap them, give them to your witch doctor friends
Nothing's coming
Nothing's happening to my brain, it's all dried up
It even vibrates
It was terrible, it was just terrible
I'll never get over it as long as I live
You on drugs
You'd be ashamed of yourself
Sounds like it's having a hallucinogenic effect
Not like a drug which is harmful and wrong and just say no kids
But spacey nonetheless
I won't go schizo will I?
We'll uh, we'll talk to Bob
Thank you Mr. Know-it-all
Ain't nothing better than when you got a burning love and a Blackhawk helicopter to let it out with
The drama is forced to sink off TDSA
Sign up now kids
North Africa
Get down to your local recruiting station there
Get Napoleon, think about T.D.
Sign your name on that dotted line
Do it tomorrow
Hey Chaz, hey Chaz, did you ever hear of this book called All Quiet on the Western Front?
The professor that sent all the kids off and they all died
They came back and they wanted to kill them and they couldn't figure out why
Oh that was World War I back when there was blood and stuff
I saw the Gulf War on TV
Nothing bad happens now
That's right there was no blood now
Go sign up
Smart bombs you know
Don't listen to them
Those things always work
Those doves though, those peace doves over there
There ain't no flapping people
Flapping your lips there
We'll get that madman Hoosen
Don't you worry about nothing
Here we go
Yee-haw
Hold it, hold it, hold it
Fire one, fire two, fire three, fire four and a half
Hey he's slap happy
Yee-haw
Here comes some tracer
Here's a self-destruction device
Here's a high explosive device
Here's an incendiary target
Here's a nose pad
We're ready for this all night
Yee-haw
Japanese Wada sees great computers
And we got a bunch of bullets
And we're gonna kick some
High-rope technically initiated explosive now
Oh my goodness look at that
A great big crater
Performance increase by transition from 80 millimeter gun to the 100 millimeter gun
And finally we should all sit up and listen to Jackie Jones, an army lieutenant
When she says
That's called upon Hollywood and Walter and J.T. and Jackie
As you can see dear friends, in the subgenius universe the war never ended
Maybe it never will
Get the war on man
This is ridiculous
We can't have war
This is the peaceful times
We've reunified Germany after all
Gorbachev is on our side
Our commission is worried that the war will damage the small ecologically sensitive community of monsters
And I had no idea
And my colleagues sincerely believe that military exercises should not be conducted in the vicinity of Monster Island
You are brothers
You must have these exercises in the vicinity of Monster Island
Because this is the only place that the Roidians can be had
You are a fool
If these exercises are held near Monster Island
I will not answer for the consequences
Oh his lips are moving at a different pace
The words come out
Order in the court
This is the only place where this can happen
I see what Tetsuo means
Yes
The third world war might begin any minute
We'll all be killed
Why should we bother about giant turtles?
Yes, maybe you're right
I know how much you love your turtles
But there are other things in life just as important
Like having friends
Our ancient legends did mention fire-eating turtles
Remember, the next time if you are naughty again
I'll shave your heads
And we can't waste any time
Because while they are sleeping
We'll eat their brains raw
Let's eat the kids later
And let's fix the spacecraft first
You are new here
And we don't expect you to believe us
When we tell you how bad it is
It is a flat scary jungle
Thick with scrub trees and tall grass
Hot and wet in intermittent rain
And strong tropical dragonflies
And Vietcong sniper bullets
You are a long, long way from Port Riley now
And there is no Jersey Cafe in town on Washington Street
Where you can sit around the counter eating hamburgers
And sipping coffee without having to be afraid a bomb might go off
Like it did at that restaurant in Saigon a few weeks back
You can get killed here
Get out while you are still alive
And before it's too late
Start to go
Or Presto
Can you control the Air Force?
ity
People are scum, humanity sucks, all you care about is your neighbor, it's who he fucks,
I know about you, you think you're tough snot, deep in your heart, you know you're not, you
are just like the next guy, full of shit, you know it's true, but you can't face it,
just like you and the crap that you spew in your high-minded tribe makes me want to puke,
think about you, what you think about me, I'm king of the scum, cause that's all I can
see.
But I love you anyway.
I love you anyway.
But upcoming, next, is a collage, and it's whatever, by the great, groovy Neptune.
I don't care who you are.
Head for the mountains, where the beer-fuzzin' fountain boys, drunk like a bum, countin' up
his countenance, astounded in the flip effect of a trip you rigged, whatever the set.
It's dissection of the insect intellect, boy.
Boy.
Bug brain go-bots, while the anvils they drop, one after another, that X marks the
spot.
Boys, I tell you, them brains are defected, with their master's blood out of my face.
With my son, you're headed for destruction, you're living a life through sin and corruption.
Ha!
You can suck a dick for talking that shit about the way I function.
It's all over.
Come on, child.
You can take my hand.
Damn.
Blessed is the day you give up your own control over your own lame brain.
Do you love the queen of pussies?
Pretending you know what the game is, but who really deals the cards?
You as long as me.
We're both retards.
Ah, yes, the great groovy Neptune, dear friends, from his demo album Demolition.
You can know more of the great groovy Neptune on the web.
Check out Neptune.itco.com.
Neptune.i-t-c-o.com.
And now, friends, a blast from somebody's past.
More of Willy Wonka's terrifying hell.
First.
Oompa loompa, oompa loompa, oompa.
I've got another puzzle for you.
Oompa loompa, oompa da dee.
If you are wise, you'll listen to me.
Gum chewing's time when it's once in a while.
It stops you from smoking and brightens your smile.
But it's repulsive, revolting, and wrong.
Chewing and chewing all day.
Love the way that a cow does.
Oompa loompa, oompa dee da.
Given good manners, you will go far.
You will live in happiness, too.
Like the oompa loompa, oompa dee doo.
Paranoia strikes deep.
Into your life it will creep.
It starts when you're always afraid.
Step out of line, the man come and take you away.
We better stop.
Hey, what's that sound?
Everybody look what's going on.
Stop.
Doesn't matter.
As well, we'll talk tomorrow.
Don't answer.
Oh.
Friends, if you're in any state of confusion at all now,
you're in...
Remember.
You're in state of confusion.
Free information.
The Bob.
Did you know you're in the state of confusion?
That sacred P.O. box which still exists in mysterious Dallas, Texas.
Even though there's nobody left there...
Wow.
It's still there.
Hey.
It's just a town that used to be there, but now it's just only a stick in the middle of town with a box on it.
And it's the P.O. sacred P.O. box because the rest of the city is gone.
I've seen the tape in that MTV tape, folks, that you saw on MTV so many years ago.
But one thing...
There's a picture of the guy that answers that box with his family.
One thing survives.
Out in the middle of the wrecked city.
And there you can see in the foreground a little box, a little mailbox.
The sacred golden box.
That's the mailbox.
It's made out of solid gold now.
It glistens in the distance.
As people draw closer to Dallas, they see the shimmering, gilded sky as they approach the golden P.O. box that is Dallas, Texas now.
Next day's coming.
That's Bob at Post Office Box 140306, Dallas, Texas 75214.
Order now.
Please shine the light of whatever.
Not available in any store.
Not on YouTube.
Sold separately.
Batteries not included.
Some assembly required.
Not stored in soles.
I'd almost forgotten that old saw.
That clever play on words.
Not stowed in sores either.
So sad not to have it anymore.
And friends, if you don't want to end up like...
Well, I shouldn't go that way.
Friends, if you must know more, check out www.subgenius.com.
Praise Bob.
Subtitles by the Amara.org community
.
. . . . . . . . . . . .
. . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . .
. . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . .
F
So don't fear when you hear a foreign sound to your ear.
It's all right, Ma.
I'm only sighing.
Make the rules for the wise men and the fools.
I've got nothing, Ma, to live up to.
For them that must obey authority that they do not respect in any degree,
who despise their jobs, their destiny, speak jealously,
leave them that are free, do what they do just to be nothing more than something they invest in.
I'm only sighing.