And here's a funny thought.
In the past he's been called the prophet of gloom and doom, the troubadour of trouble, the disciple of despair.
All real Americans love the sting of...
...bog doves!
...natural fluids.
Hello?
My destiny.
What?
You're doing this for the government?
Yes.
What? Why?
Because of the United States government.
And their unyielding commitment to the cause of liberty.
Oh no!
The preceding program was brought to you by Bob.
Your FBI hopes through this series of programs to enlist each of you as a volunteer in the army of women engaging in serious crimes like murder, robbery and...
The Self Genius Power of Swag.
Neither your FBI nor any local law enforcement agency can prevent those parasites from attempting to get easy money from you, the decent citizen.
Only you can do that.
Do it by always following Bob.
But that trick never worked!
There's a real problem here.
Political leaders have got to stop hiding brass tacks outside of the box.
And in fact, there's a real problem here.
Political leaders have got to stop hiding outside of the box.
In short, bureaucrats and diplomats can't take it further.
In short, there's a real problem here.
Political leaders have got to stop the box.
May it please the court, I would like to put on a dark wig, go to the Fidelity Bank, and try to get into Tom Gilrain's safe deposit box.
Objection. The witness is stating an opinion.
Sustained.
The Fidelity Bank
Liars!
Lost switch.
The Fidelity Bank
Joel Johnson
This is Trustees.
19 Wear, New Hall of Fame.
Haven't you noticed the way he's been behaving?
Honey, didn't you notice?
Well, dear, I've always had sort of a way with potatoes.
You know something?
You're sickening.
Oh, is that so?
Yeah.
Okay.
June?
Yes.
Oh.
Yeah, I suppose so.
As if you didn't know.
Good night, Wally.
Good night, dear.
Well, good night, Wally.
Ah, baloney.
Don't try to kid me.
Besides his own exaggerated human nature and the powers granted him by Jehovah One,
Bob also benefits from being the chosen broker on Earth for superior beings
from the furthest reaches of known space,
the so-called men from Planet X, or X-ists,
for they are nothing like men.
Bob has a covenant with these angelic beings,
a cosmic contract, a deal.
On July 5th, 1998, at 7 a.m.,
the X-ists shall make a mass landing on this planet.
The children of Bob shall be rewarded at this foretold rupture,
this day of judgment,
when all those who paid their church dues
will be lifted up in power,
and glory to gain new homes and bodies aboard
the pleasure saucers of the sex goddesses,
all the while watching the hapless pigs twitch and bleat and wail
in the death throes of their world.
And we faithful shall be transfigured into new enlightened beings,
superior mutants called overmen and uberwomen,
who will start a new Jerusalem
in the promised land,
the promised land of Dimension X,
Asgard, the zone of eternal slack and cytor-spasmic ooze-squirt.
Behold, my servants shall prosper.
He that exalted and lifted up on the pipe shall be very high.
He who kneweth the fools will prophesy,
for he shall be made overman.
Many will be astonished at him,
for his appearance is so mighty,
and his form is beyond human semblance,
that his form is beyond that of the sentient.
Oh, Jesus!
Oh, no!
We can't do much about those evil gods
from the other side of the cosmos,
who fly through the air
and through the nebulous darkness of space.
Space, my friends,
the infinite inky clouds of nebulae.
They fly on their membranous leathery wings,
holding in their coiling tentacles shiny steel cylinders,
each one containing what was once a human soul,
what was once a member of the church of the subgenius.
But enough of this.
You don't want to hear about this.
I must, and yet I cannot.
But I'll tell you what,
you'll be wishing it was that kind of aim.
At least you'll be wishing,
you'll be glad to have them on your side,
because at least they're not on your side.
At least there's two arms and two legs.
It could be worse.
It could be much worse.
And now the parade of manly men on the show.
There they come,
chests outthrust,
chins thrust forward,
each one holding a giant manly mug of myrrh,
hyper-caffeinated coffee.
Yep, to get them through the show,
they pour the Red Bull in their ear,
and off into the future they go.
Good one, don't you think?
I don't know about that.
Okay, caller, you know what?
This movie, is this the one that has Michael Pepe in it?
It's time for the pleasure saucers.
The sex goddess.
Oh!
Bitch!
What was I going to do?
Don't touch me, Mark!
Well, that's when we took our luggage,
and we packed up all our work,
and we packed up all our worldly goods,
and we made our way down to the pleasure saucers
of the sex goddesses.
And we had just enough wingnuts and lugnuts.
And when she said,
I want you to bring your battery charger,
I started getting a little bit scared.
They'll be in California.
Pleasure saucers will go,
although they don't like to go to California.
But they leave California forever into the necrophagous depths
of the Euclidean Isle.
We saw some of the sex goddesses last Friday.
Welcome to your saucer.
I am pleasure goddess CV456.
And 56,154.
Sexual gratification and desire for film
will begin in a moment.
First, we invite you to look out your window.
Say goodbye to the pinks who were left behind.
Now unzip your pants.
Just sit back and relax.
.