This all-time radio program was originally aired live,
long before the advent of high-fidelity.
As a result, you may detect an occasional surface noise or volume drop
due to transmission problems so common to old radio.
We hope, however, that any variance in audio quality
will not take away from your pleasure in listening to this,
one of the all-time favorite shows.
Bob!
He couldn't live, and neither could the others of his kind.
There was a voice on the radio while you were gone.
There are others out there.
Welcome to the subgenius radio ministry, Hour of Slack,
sponsored by the Church of the Subgenius.
The subgenius Hour of Slack that you are about to listen to
is specially designed for you.
Designed only to be played on radio station
and only in the city of...
Thank you.
Everybody, you mean..
You'll never see the loneliness there inside you.
Hey there, Georgie girl.
Or is it the clothes you wear?
You're always window shopping
But never stopping to buy
So shed those dowdy feathers and fly
Hey there, Georgie girl!
There's another Georgie need to find
Bring out all the love you hide
And oh what a change there'd be
The world could see
A new Georgie girl!
I'm gonna do the Georgie girl.
She won't let me alone.
Oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah.
Machines, machines, they keep right on moving.
Well, I've got to find a place to rest my head.
A machine, he'd smile at me and say,
I'm gone.
I'm gonna be all bad.
Oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah.
Machines, machines, we made them to serve us.
Machines, machines, we built them to serve us.
But till the day when I'm buried in my grave.
Yes, right until that day I know I'm gonna be a slave.
A slave, a slave, a slave to the machines.
Machines, they keep right on winning.
Machines, machines, they keep right on winning.
Machines, chains, chains, chains, chains一樣.
lymph and chains professional.
What a hard force to the machines.
And they keep moulded ironing us off the train.
like m damaging theisis not enough.
orろыв Surely, I can say everything I want.
Go uh, go.
Say them the line.
Remember is the smell of the barn, the dunga and the denim coming in from the farm.
A gap-toothed baby dancing in the straw, apple-headed mama just a-dribbling a chaw.
The slide and the shuffle and the spit on the ground, playing bluegrass music in a shithole town.
Shithole town, shithole town, playing bluegrass music in a shithole town.
The next thing I can tell you, next tune that I can play is at the Cowboy Palace down in Olathe.
I'd rather be anyplace other than here, a thousand-dollar boot and a three-dollar beer.
The ghost of Harry Carter is crying down, playing bad country music in a shithole town.
Shithole town, shithole town, playing bad country music in a shithole town.
Yeah, yeah, that's all I can remember, all I can remember, can't remember no more.
I drank up a boom and a bottle of twang, got my vaccination with a rusty E-string.
Traded my soul for one that worked and I got us all a gig at the Lutheran church.
Singing John Wesley Harding as the rain came down, playing rock and roll music in a shithole town.
Shithole town, shithole town, playing rock and roll music in a shithole town.
Baby, you got the Gitas, I got the nerve.
Everybody's just looking for somebody to serve.
Gonna play my harmonica until I wreck, that's right about now.
The last time that I checked, honey, here.
Here comes the train, here comes the sound.
Tonight we're playing music in a shithole town.
Shithole town, shithole town, tonight we're playing music in a shithole town.
Shithole town, shithole town, playing rock and roll music in a shithole town.
Yeah, yeah, that's all I can remember.
All I can remember, can't remember no more.
OK, are we gonna call Dave?
Yes, I suppose that you should call Dave, yes.
Why not?
I'm gonna call his buzz number.
You're gonna buzz him up on the buzz number?
I hear it.
I hear the ring.
Is there a buzz?
Yes.
Dave!
Dave, we've reached him.
We've reached the Dave.
And there's no buzz.
We've reached the edge of the sandwich, I believe.
I'm tired.
Who do you wish to speak with?
And there is no buzz.
We have zero buzz on the line.
You wish to speak with just a moment.
Zero buzz.
Hey, this is zero buzz.
He's fetching the buzz?
Is that what's going on here?
He's calling zero buzz right now.
There doesn't seem to be one here.
Oh, that's a shame.
You know, the listeners have actually been asking for more buzz lately.
Well, you know, Alexander Morbus was one of the first original kings of Deuteronomy
in the Hypnotic Bible of France.
This is during the days in the Rebellion.
If you were a Republican, that meant you could kill some aristocrats with your teeth.
You're a French Republican, right?
Right.
Then they transformed over into the social aristocrats who divined the future by their nasal hair.
No, I didn't mean that.
Dave, have you ever considered teaching history at that college level?
Oh, of course.
I have three classes.
Left.
Three classes scheduled this semester.
Working in close conjunction with Dr. Hunt and Dr. Forskin on the final approval.
And that was Dr. Hunt and Dr. Forskin.
Oh, I forgot to give credits.
Oh, no.
Yes.
The songs that I probably will have played would be, well, there's a new old Rudy Schwartz
project album out.
It's called Salmon Dave from about 20 years ago, but he remastered it and digitized it.
I can tell the difference.
Those first four cuts were from Salmon Dave.
And then the song about the machines, that was Lothar and the Hand People.
Do you remember that band, Dave?
Lothar and the Hand People?
Oh, Lothar and the Hand People.
Of course, they were famous.
Well, see, I never heard them.
I only heard the name.
I thought the name was great.
They were a band.
I never actually heard them.
And we were unpacking CDs and stuff, and I picked up one.
It was Lothar and the Hand People.
I didn't know where it came from.
It was Princess Weez.
And she knew it by heart.
She knew that entire album.
That was the weirdest thing.
I started listening to it, starting with that song we played.
And she was like, oh, Lothar and the Hand People.
She was singing right along with every single bit of it.
Yeah, well, at least you don't have to worry about the smell.
Sometimes you get up at like 4 o'clock in the afternoon,
you look out the window, and all of a sudden,
it's like this vast sea of inhuman faces staring back
like little gray-eyed monkeys or something like that.
Or what, the Hand People?
Well, no, not the Hand People, the Fish People.
They're related.
Never mind.
I'm sorry.
Oh, and the last song we played,
the one just before we called Dave,
Shithole Town by the Rainmakers
from their album Monster Movie.
And I figured we had to play that because it's okay now.
It's okay for kids to hear the word shithole.
It's good for them.
You can't just say shit.
It has to have some little softening agent like hole attached to it
because it's so much better.
It's much less vivid that way, right?
But since the president says it's okay to say it
and then say he didn't say it,
it's a dog whistle.
You know, only dogs and deplorables can hear it.
And people like me,
because I'm basically a deplorable dog myself.
I just happen to be more of a progressive type deplorable.
And so, yeah, it's okay, kids.
Everybody should call everybody else.
Shitholes.
Because it's okay.
But I didn't really say that.
That's the important thing.
I didn't say, I didn't use that language.
It's just a story that the dams made up.
It's like the language of origins.
Like you say,
Glen Road, Texas,
it's one shithole of a town.
It's the secret doctrine of reciprocity.
Well, you know, it is possible that I'll chicken,
out for the sake of the broadcast college stations
and go ahead and replace that word with the word Trump
as we have done before.
So it's a Trump-hole town.
Trump-hole town.
That's what I...
Everybody thinks, yeah,
yeah, they know that a lot better
than they would the other way around
because it takes too much confusion to get...
It's like a deer in a head.
I don't know exactly how that has to do with it.
Actually, deer run from the headlights.
We see it at least once a week.
We catch the deer in the headlights.
You know what they don't do
is stand there staring at the car.
They run like hell.
Yeah, they run like hell.
The problem,
they might run into the headlights
because they're stupid
and panicked or whatever.
But either way they run,
that hound dog buddy wants to chase them.
Oh, Disney, yeah.
He almost went right through the front windshield
the last time we...
Some deer crossed our path.
He did the same thing when he saw a cat.
The ancient people must have acquired
a real taste for manure and sandwiches
because it seems like
if you could train a dog to come and help you hunt,
that'd be okay for a collection of dingleberries
to somewhere in the Arctic woods.
Well, we collect dingleberries all the time.
I've got three mason jars full of them.
I just pick them off myself.
You're a Neolithic hunter-gatherer,
so why not gather some?
I don't have to go very far to gather that.
I can pick a few off of little buddy there.
Where is little buddy?
Oh, good, he's sleeping behind us.
Sleeping like an angel right behind you.
You said he had a little accident in mom's room.
Yes, he did.
And our dearest,
sweet dog.
But he didn't telegraph it?
He didn't like say,
hey, look, I need to go to the bathroom.
Come on.
He didn't run over the door
and like scratch holes in it?
No, no, no bark,
no scratch at the door.
But he did go in the bathroom, right?
He did go in the bathroom.
Well, see?
He's learning.
He knows a place to go.
Right.
The bathroom, unfortunately,
has dark blue carpet on it.
So it's kind of a...
Oh, well, that's enough about...
the Stag Ranch Radio studio facilities.
Well, you have heard about the kitty cats
that go poop in the toilet.
Yeah, there's cats.
Yeah, lots of cats will do that.
I'm sure you could train a dog to go poop in the toilet.
But it would have to be very carefully balanced,
I would think.
I think, yeah, I think that's the problem is because
Buddy's a rocket scientist and probably like
wearing a brown and Hitler's friends and stuff like that.
Uh-huh.
He's probably a full time scientist.
He's probably a former SS scientist.
The dog?
From the planet, yeah, from the planet Venus, maybe.
Or, you know, someplace where it's real warm.
Hey, you got to get your scientists from somewhere.
They're sure not going to be educated here in the United States anymore.
Right.
Especially, they're a bunch of Hindus who think they're Russians or something like that.
Well, some of them are.
I knew that.
So, yeah, you never...
You can't judge a book by its...
Cover.
You can't tell how...
What...
If that's really grass that looks so green on the other side of the fence there.
It may look like greener grass.
Yeah.
Or as Bob said that one night when he was sad after Connie cheated on him.
He said, the dicks are always bigger when you can't see them.
The dicks you can't see.
They're always bigger.
Something like that.
Of course, I may have to replace that word with another word.
Trunks.
Trumps.
Yeah.
Because he was thinking of tall, talking old geezers when the right time was...
He thought he was a...
Here, hold on.
Let me get a...
Let me get a quiet Trump here.
Trumps.
Trump.
There.
Okay.
There's my...
There's my old cut lines.
Trumps.
I'm glad you got those in there before...
Jimmy Swagger used to wear the same style underpants when he did his dirty deeds and stuff like
that.
He was reported to be a post-hypnotic policeman from Planet Venus itself.
That's at least what they thought when...
And that leads into the song by the Rudy Schwartz Project, Jimmy Swagger.
Jimmy Swagger got caught checking into a motel with a prostitute.
He said, you can't tell me where it is.
Jimmy Swagger got caught shaking into a motel with a New Orleans prostitute.
Did he try to save her or did he get his winky wet?
Jimmy got his pecker wet.
Jimmy Swagger got caught shaking into a motel with a prostitute.
A motel I said a motel
with a
a possible scenario
for Jimmy Swagger's pornographic
encounter with a New Orleans
prostitute in an appropriately
tasteful motel.
Although Jimmy has no
intention of actually violating any
of Gertie's well-traveled orifices
with his shriveled evangelical
wee-wee, he does hope
to engage in an assortment of
water sports, including a thorough
bowel cleansing with a three-quart
rainbow rubber enema bag
equipped with a tapered chrome
nozzle while Gertie
bellows out the old rugged
cross. Jimmy
asks Gertie to wear the blouse
and skirt of an eighth-grade Catholic
schoolgirl, suck a raspberry
tootsie pop, and beg
Jimmy to fuck her in the ass.
Jimmy masturbates on
Pat Robertson campaign literature
while warning Gertie not to allow
a pothead manipulated by Satan
to lure her into the work of the devil.
Gertie assures Jimmy that his two-inch
full erect penis is actually way
above average and well-veined
besides. Oh, God, Jimmy,
you have a big cock?
Please give it to me, Jimmy.
Give me that throbbing
hunk of manhood.
I've never seen one that big.
Really? No fooling.
Yep, that
sure is a big one.
As the three quarts of
steamy, soapy liquid
seizes control of his lower colon,
Jimmy evacuates
his purulent sphincter
into the crisper drawer
of a nearby refrigerator
and moans.
I have sinned against my
family and my Lord,
and I ask that he cleanse
my soul with his
precious blood.
Well, looks like enough of them
bought it for us to pay off
the mortgage. Looks like enough of them
bought it for us to pay for the rest of the jet.
Born-again Christians are dense
as a brick. Easy to do, but the package
is late. They've let us rape their daughters
as long as we sanctify all of their hate.
Wake up, you assholes.
Jimmy Swagger got caught checking his
new up motel with a prostitute.
And that
was the Rudy Schwartz project
from his remastered album
Sam and Dave.
Dave, what were you saying about Jimmy
Swagger?
I said he was a purposeful Nazi. He was full of
lust and thunder.
And he used to have dreams that he was
an aborigine, but one day he woke up and he
was in the wrong sphere.
The great preacher, Jimmy
Swagger?
Yeah, the late preacher, Jimmy
Swagger.
He was
a cousin of
Jerry Lee Lewis.
He was Jerry Lewis' third
cousin. That's why they both had sex with
14-year-olds when they were 35.
Not to mention Dean Martin.
Jerry Lewis, Dean Martin,
Jimmy Swagger,
Barney and Rubble.
Yeah, Barney, Rubble.
All crib fishermen.
Yep. It's a big, long, spastic
list of romantic,
giant seas, but I don't think we should
pay them too much attention
because they're already in a higher tax
bracket and make you have to
pay too much to begin with.
Hey,
I was going to tell you something.
Tell us.
I saw a funny review of
Neighbor World.
It compared it to
Infinite Death,
a combination of Infinite Death and
Neuromancer, and then it gave
a sideways slap in the face.
In common area treatment of
a...
Where'd you find this?
Was it like somebody added to
the Amazon listing? Somebody actually
reviewed it?
I think somebody actually reviewed it.
On Amazon.com?
I believe so.
You know, Dave's been a little
worked up because he got to
searching around on the internet for the first time
for himself and
found another guy.
Oh, I know.
I know.
He's like also being raised as a clone for the rich
popular cowboy
Dave.
Who's a friend of
you know,
who?
The manufacturers of the
prison ankle bracelets.
Well, it's true.
It's true financial overture.
Dave, you were telling me
something, some secret thing that you
learned and they're probably going to kill you for
knowing this.
But now they'll have to kill everybody who hears this show.
No, that's it.
Turns out I checked it myself.
And it's actually kind of old news.
It's a couple of months old.
And there's one reference that goes back all the way
to like around June of 2017.
So I hate to sound normal to explain that, but that's
the very, very truthful.
Well, what Dave told me earlier and can't explain now.
Yes.
I thought I got this right.
Mm hmm.
Um, the, uh, okay.
People who are in prison wear these ankle
bracelets.
Okay.
Yes.
Those ankle bracelets are manufactured by a company.
Okay.
It is a company.
It turns out that is close friends with president
Donald Trump.
And moreover, those ankle bracelets bear a remarkable resemblance to the slave.
Neck rings of the not all that distant past used in America.
So the implying that the, the more things that are illegal and the more poor people that
Trump can throw in jail, the more angst slave bracelets he can sell or his buddy can sell.
And of course it all kicks back into the, um,
What a lovely world.
Okay.
Those, those, uh, that line of hotels, the shit hole hotel.
Exactly.
One of those on you, senior.
You hit that one rail and nail on the head.
Oh, there was a guy who, uh, uh, projected, uh, the word shit hole on a Trump hotels.
He's projected a lot of stuff on her toast.
It's like, it's not graffiti.
He's not vandalizing and he didn't touch the building.
He's across the street with a projector, just like Dr. Argus Fox has.
And he just, yeah, just painted with light with light.
Right.
Yeah.
This just recently happened.
It happened this morning.
In fact, uh, cool.
Yeah.
There's a great picture of a Trump hotel.
I think the one he lives in with the massive letters in 5 billion pika size type that says,
uh, shit hole instead of Trump.
Trump hotel.
Now see, I'll have to change all that for WCSB and WORT and all the nice stations.
The other nice college radio stations.
The good stations.
Except that probably it's, it's like, I'm sorry, but all week every newspaper I opened
had that word on it.
Like, okay, well, if the president can do it, say it, let's say it.
I heard it on NPR.
They actually said one.
I'm going to say this one time.
And we'll all know what we're talking about.
And then he said the word.
The word.
I'm going to go ahead and say it again.
Just cause it's so fun.
Trump hole.
It's a Trump hole country in a Trump hole town.
It's a Trump hole town.
And he said, we should get more Norwegian.
He said, why can't we get more people from Norway?
Which is as quiet as you can get.
He said that.
Here's why.
Nobody in Norway comes, wants to come to the United States.
They have universal health care.
They have all the things that we don't have.
They have science being taught in schools.
They have physical education.
They have all kinds of stuff that's been dropped from the, the new United States in the last
25, 30 years.
Yikes.
So.
You can go to an expensive spa and not have to pay millions and thousands of dollars.
You just present your community card or something.
Damn socialist.
Right.
Yeah.
So why would they want to come here?
That's why he can't get any free stuff here.
Right.
Of course, people from Haiti want to come here.
Because there's food here.
They've heard that there was food and electricity.
People from Puerto Rico could probably, well, they were supposed to already be here in a
way, but it turns out here isn't really here depending on who's in charge at the, uh, pink
house.
The pink house.
That's what it really is.
Pinkness.
Pinkness, pinkness, pinkness.
Oh, I'm saving up a, I've got a clip of a good friend of mine awkwardly being talked
into endorsing Trump as an honest, honest guy.
And I'm waiting.
I'm just waiting to spring.
It's going to embarrass my good friend so very much, but he deserves it.
I'm just waiting.
Yeah.
There's been a big, a huge proliferation of those, um, you know, January catalogs except
for him wearing like, it looks like a baby birthday suit.
It's a pair of depends.
I don't know how, what we could depend on from this person other than a slack remark.
And I don't mean that in the positive, lovely way.
A slack remark.
It's an erratic spasmodic unification of worms and ideas.
Yeah.
Corruptigating worms.
Hey, did you hear the show where I played the, your old corruptigating worms rant?
It was a rerun, a recent rerun.
I know I was in the audience.
Do you remember, can you, can you believe he did such great stuff back in the old days?
I can't.
I can't either.
No, I mean, I listened to, I've, I've, uh, that happens.
In fact, I was listening to a puzzling evidence show tonight.
It was January 5th.
Puzzling evidence show.
I thought, oh, they'll probably be talking in interesting ways about the new year.
No, they were playing a tape of my first time on that radio station in 1982 or something
with a million sound effects going on and then talking at equal volume with it.
How Dr. Howell and puzzling evidence.
On top of it.
I couldn't understand either one.
But I know that it's an acquired taste.
That I can only acquire if I'm on a lot of LSD and I can't take LSD anymore because it
hurts my neck.
Well, you have, you have what's commonly known as fishmonger's spring, which is a part of
discoloration of the back of the neck when the sodium particle gets through all the way
to the, uh, evanescent forests of plunder.
And once this is magnified a couple more times after the sodium parts go in there, you actually
find yourself becoming a fishmonger.
Yeah, I'm becoming a salt.
I like sodium chloride.
That's a salt.
Yeah.
I like that.
That's a, you're just salting my feelings by saying those words.
You might as well be assaulting me physically just by making me think those bad thoughts.
That's a salt.
I think you're a degenerate, Chose.
Me too.
It doesn't really matter.
I've been assaulted by Dave.
I'm going to join the victim's church of the kid glove.
You better be careful.
You better join your kidneys with another super personality or else you're going to
find yourself a scrambled egg out of misfortune sometime.
I'm going to have to find a better chair for Tarzan's radio station or something.
Cause I got-
Tarzan's radio station?
Tarzan's station.
I've got the, I've got the rheumatism in my back these days.
I can't, I gotta find just the right position.
Which unfortunately is not the case.
I feel like if I'm standing right here, the chair seems to be standing straight upright
like a marine.
Then I'm perfectly comfortable.
But laying down, lolling about, leaning back in a chair, those things all hurt and getting
up from hurts even more.
So I feel like, Oh, I might as well just stay standing up all the time.
Well, if you recall, back in the day when we used to do the radio show down at WCSB
radio station, Dave always stood to do his part.
You're always standing up.
He never sat down.
In fact, I would wager to guess that Dave is standing right now.
No, I'm sitting down.
As a matter of fact.
Well, see, I could pull this mic out and spill that coffee and break all the equipment.
No, I can't.
I still can't.
I can't stand up because Tarzan's radio station is partly hidden,
is partly sheltered by a spiral staircase made of cast iron.
And if I stand up too fast, I'll bump my head on that again.
Yes, and a step will go jamming into your back.
I already broke my skull open and my brain spilled out in the car dealership parking lot last Tuesday.
So I've got kind of a headache that won't go away.
And the sculpture of a bull kicked you?
Yeah, sculpture of a bull.
You hit the soft little head twice in one week?
I tripped and fell against a statue of a bull kicking.
And where my head hit was the bull's kicking hoof.
So it was like the bull wasn't really moving.
It was a statue.
But I gave it life by slamming my head against that hoof.
You wish somebody had a camera or somebody was taking a picture.
Actually, I think that four car dealership workers were smoking a cigarette over in the distance.
I think they saw the whole thing.
And were kind of watching to see if I was really injured.
And when I got back up, they just snickered.
I felt their eyes on me.
Look at that old man fall.
I did have the dog with me.
And I could blame it on the dog.
Well, you did say you tripped on the dog.
Yeah, I tripped on the dog.
I did.
And got kicked by a static bull.
Right in the head.
That's how Bruce Lee died.
Dude, that's...
Two massive head concussions in one week means that you're already...
I could run for president.
Or for...
I've already forgotten how to spell everything, including my own name.
I could be president now.
No, you'd have to come up with some less vicious comments that are totally irrepresentable.
Like...
Woman, bring me a beer mounted on your head.
How's that?
Is that a proper rich presidential thing to say?
Oh, no.
Yeah, but he wouldn't be talking to his wife when he said that.
He doesn't even talk to his wife.
He doesn't sleep with her.
Did you know that?
I believe it.
They have separate bedrooms.
They make a lot of sausages and stuff.
That's at least what I heard from living in the Cleveland area.
Did you hear about his girlfriend, Stormy Waters?
Yes.
Stormy.
Now, think about that name, Stormy Waters.
And think about the...
Well, this is another thing you can say now.
The pee tape that nobody's seen yet.
It might not even exist.
But if he's already had to pay off one prostitute who goes by the name of Stormy Waters.
In other words, she'll stand above you.
Just as we were talking about Jimmy Swagger.
Jimmy Swagger paid.
He couldn't pay as much.
And he got in more trouble.
But it was the same thing.
It was like he would pay these scraggly, scraggly women in Baton Rouge to straddle him while he laid on the floor.
He didn't actually want to have sex with them.
He wanted to look up their dress.
And have them do nasty things.
But not actually have sex.
Just be real nasty and pee.
Because there's something about these powerful men.
That I guess...
Well, I don't know.
I don't know whether to be jealous or envious.
Because I've never really tried having a woman urinate on me.
Maybe I'd love it.
It seems to me, it seems like kind of a waste.
Oh, I thought you said you already did.
Perfectly did.
As far as I remember, you said one of your favorite things was the warm...
I was trying to make a point.
Now, you don't need to talk about this private stuff on the air.
I didn't say that, okay?
I didn't say that.
That's alternate fact.
That's fake news.
Why are you turning red right now?
It was already part of your body.
And it was like mother's milk, only it was warmer.
And you used this sweet, lovely fragrance of elves and Eskimos off in the distance.
Oh, I just kind of cried like a little...
You know, I think it was a Brazilian native.
Well, you know, women and men who specialize in providing...
S&M.
S&M bondage and domination stuff where a man pays them to treat them like crap and humiliate them and do things on them.
Yeah, I remember on that page...
They usually, they said the main customers for that are high-powered lawyers and mayors and city comptrollers and bankers.
Those are the kind of guys who are at the very top of the...
Who have a...
A hundred thousand employees that they can urinate on.
What do they want the most?
They want a mommy to punish them by urinating on them.
I guess they just didn't...
I guess they're just bad, strictly bad toilet training, to quote Robert Crone.
This is the joke you can make by saying the epistemology of golden showers.
Where did it begin, mommy?
I don't know.
Well, it's, uh...
Yeah, show me where I came from, mommy.
I'm showing you.
I've been down in that hole, Brother Roloff.
I know about that hole.
Once you get locked in there, you can't get out.
You sound like the darkness.
You're bucking and bucking and you'll be pulling and trying and humping around and you can't get out of that hole.
You can't get out.
You sound like the Texas version of...
That's all I can say.
I know, Brother Roloff.
I know about that hole.
You don't want to get stuck down in there.
No way.
No, no, I don't.
Not the punishment cone.
What if you...
The punishment cone, exactly.
I got that from the divas.
What if you go through endless cycles of rebirth and rebirth?
Rebirth.
I mean, what if?
Not what if, what if, what if.
What if?
Stephen King Villain was elected president.
And...
What if that isn't the right of the goodwillers?
That isn't the love of the unbid of genius?
I've just thrown in something I thought would be different.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, well, here's something different.
This music in the background is Tangerine Dream.
Oh, cool.
From...
A movie, a horror movie called The Keep.
Ah.
Yes, I've heard of that.
I never did see it, but I have heard of The Keep.
And, of course, Tangerine Dream.
The Keep was a very strange monster movie.
I don't even want to try to even explain it.
Was it a German fortress in there?
Yeah, there was a German fortress, only it had been a Russian...
I have seen it.
It was like an ancient...
It was like an ancient Coptic fortress built around a gigantic cave.
And, basically, Satan or something horribly evil was inside that cave.
Yeah.
And some guy comes along and lets it out.
Yep.
And it gradually, as it kills more people, it becomes more physical
and takes on a rather poor makeup job or monster costume.
And then a sad angel comes along.
And puts Satan back in his hole.
I didn't want to go back in that hole.
Don't put me back in that hole, Brother Broloff.
I learned my lesson.
I won't do it again.
I promise I won't do it again.
I feel sorry for Satan now.
That's what you said the last 10,000 times, my son.
Now, what?
You feel sorry for Satan?
Well, I was just thinking all the money that he's invested in all the United States and Americans.
And...
This used to be...
This used to be what we called the Western world.
And there's no east, north, west, or nasal pudding of any kind of sociopathic content.
There's just one long, blustering, illustrious line of stupidity.
And I'd like to get out of it if I could.
But I get the shakes off now.
And I'm yearning my deep ends.
I can always depend on that.
And I'm just flustered about trying to yank out a fresh comment.
You know what I mean?
Oh, it's getting harder and harder to yank out a fresh comment.
Because they'll say you're being fresh.
And then you're an abuser.
Then you're an assault.
Suddenly you're an assaulter.
Or a pepper.
Ian, you wouldn't want to use your...
Never mind, I forgot what I was not going to use.
You two are yanking out new expressions every few seconds.
What the heck are you talking about?
You guys are nothing but yanking out new expressions.
You're yanking out new expressions.
She is right.
There is definitely a market for that in the big league.
We're yanking?
I thought you didn't know about that.
I always wait until you're gone.
To yank out.
I have eyes in the back of my head.
Buddy told you, didn't he?
D-Doll was yanking.
He was yanking new expressions all over the place.
It was gross.
That does...
sound gross.
Once you think of it from outside of a staying body.
And different focus.
That's the only way to get new expressions.
You know, if that's self-expression, right?
I'm an artist.
Yeah, but you're not expressing anything.
A jack-off or J-O artist.
Yeah.
Now you've hit it right on the nostrils.
Or it takes some aim.
You've got to aim just right to get it right.
The punishment has to be right at the right angle.
And 33 degrees.
I guess it sometimes has to do with the pyramid.
Dave, you're going to have to speak up.
Speak up now.
I don't want to have to use the levelator on this show.
Something having to do with 33 degrees oblique transversal.
And the peppy, the lipu on the pyramids.
On the eye on the pyramid.
Now, did you hear that one?
No.
Say it.
The French and the Illuminati.
What?
The French Illuminati.
Not the actual Republicans of Corsica.
Joe Schmoe and Lefty Limburger and all those guys used to hang around the sodium shop.
But the French Masonic Illuminati?
Yeah.
Robespierre and Louis Cartier and not Louis.
What's his name?
Citizen 14th.
And you say they built the city of Paris as a giant Masonic symbol?
On stilts.
And in fact, they would use dinosaur teeth to keep the magnetic doors open.
Ah, dinosaur teeth.
Yeah, but the main thing is, you know, the stilts.
That's pretty low ceiling for a lot of French people.
They like to eat their dinners, go down the basement, you know, and hang out with the other refugees.
And just plow.
Go away at it.
Mont J'ai moi.
He's trying to change the subject, because he doesn't know what it is.
Well, of course I don't know what subject it is, because that's a self-defining process.
It's been freshly yanked.
We know that.
Whatever it is.
I've never seen anything like that.
Yanked from high French society.
I just started reading a big, thick book.
That G. Gordon Gordon gave me called The Master Game.
And it's a history of secret societies that are for real.
That have, these two authors, and we've all heard this before in kooky, kookier books.
But these two authors are basically saying that there's a continuity.
There really is a continuity from ancient Egypt through the Crusades through to Washington today.
Hmm.
And there's another conspiracy on the other side of the world that is wanting to explode.
And that these two cultures are inevitably going to clash horribly.
I'd hate to think what those authors think about the situation right now, because they wrote this book ten years ago.
Yeah, twenty years ago.
It was even worse.
That was even ten times worse.
So it...
You think the president, Emmanuel Smiley, was...
The vice regent.
He was portrayed by Hubert Downing Snapper.
Who was...
He also stole equipment from the Illuminati.
Or, what's his name?
Julian Assange.
Remember that?
Maybe that's where that stuff in Bob's storage locker came from.
Illuminati equipment.
That they stole from the aliens.
The greys, not the exes.
You got your Reiki and Hamburg?
Yeah.
And your whole...
You got a whole vegetable community, like a snappy...
A group of snappy toms.
Well, you get a lot of cool aprons for guys that like to wear aprons.
But that's what you do, you know.
If you're one of the Illuminati masons, you wear these special aprons and...
And trowel.
You have special trowels.
Yeah, but I'd never call them apes, even if they were wearing the wrong trowels.
Would you?
I mean, that's disrespectful.
They'll say, hey, look at me.
Hey, Mr. Mason, you're wearing a pair of trousers and blue jeans and...
Slacks.
Trowels and slacks.
You're wearing a pair of slacks.
With an apron.
Yeah, and you're an ape, too.
With Masonic symbols on it.
Yeah, you're a symbiotic illiterate of...
What's the call guy there?
You know, in some ways, I think that...
The real secret...
Secret society that...
On this side of the world...
Kind of...
Doesn't really believe in the gods.
They believe in man.
And the other...
The other culture thinks that they do, too.
But except that...
Because there's only their god.
And...
And there's...
As Charles...
Charleston always says in the show, Before Our Slag...
One...
I am...
One god.
One race.
The human race.
Unfortunately, there's not...
There's not one race.
The human race.
There's the subgenius race.
Which is...
I mean...
Although...
Okay, Neanderthals, it turns out, weren't a different species.
You could call them a different race, sort of.
But...
They apparently could interbreed with our other ancestors.
Did I tell you that my brother took a fancy DNA test?
And it turned out that at least he and I...
Assuming we have the same mommy and daddy...
Have more Neanderthal than 70% of the other people who have taken this test.
So we got an extra dose of Neanderthal.
And we also learned that we're solid British Isles.
There's not even...
Hardly any French or...
What you might call French or German.
Although everybody in the British Isles is French and German and Norwegian and Roman.
They've...
You know...
Everybody's had England.
But since...
The time of the British Empire...
That's...
Apparently, that was the last time any Frenchies...
Or Krauts...
Married a Stang.
Which is weird, because Stang is a German name.
But Smith isn't.
It's an unusual job description, too.
But I was going to say...
If you...
You know...
Wanted to be one of the very first...
You could, like, put a Hitler mustache out and come out and go...
Ein Reich!
Ein Volk!
Ein Führer!
Like that, you know?
And then when you say...
You take a little protractor to the easel once you say...
Ein...
Ein Führer...
You know who the Führer is going to be, don't you?
And...
Ein Führer!
Like that.
And then you have everybody pretending like they're making Krauts sounds.
And going...
Stuff...
Yeah, stuff like that.
And they think they ate too many hot dogs and drank too many beers.
And now they're going to have to go to the bathroom!
Man.
Dave, you take my mind to some dark places.
Mine, too.
They're so...
They're so dark, I can't see them at all.
So I don't know whether they're good or bad.
That's why I don't like your own special this week.
Well, what time is it here on the show?
Oh, my God, it's time to end the show, believe it or not.
How can it be?
It is.
We've been talking for 40 minutes.
My goodness, we must have been having fun.
Yes.
We're going to hear some Jimmy Ryan to take us out.
He has a new album, Fall Instrumental Power Guitar Things, about two minutes.
It's long.
And Jimmy Ryan will have us flying.
21st Century Riffology is the name of this thing by Reverend Jimmy Ryan.
So, of the Flying Ryan Brothers.
But now he's like a solo guy.
I think he said his brother wants to do cover songs and Jimmy wants to do original stuff.
So anyway, friends, you're listening to The Hour of Slight, number 1,657.
I say that.
Say that just like I know it.
From the Church of the Subgenius.
And if you want to know anything more about any of this, which is possibly unlikely,
it's subgenius.com on the internet.
And if you don't have an internet, you can send a little self-addressed stamped envelope
to subgenius at P.O. Box 807, Glen Rose, Texas.
Subgenius.
76043.
2-1-0 blast off.
Yeah.
And you can buy Lonesome Cowboy Dave's new novel, Neighbor World.
From us.
Or just type in Neighbor World, Dave.
You'll probably find a catalog listing for it.
Anyway, friends, Jimmy Ryan.
We'll see you next time.
Bye.
Okay, that was Jimmy Ryan,
and now we can do that final 10-minute part
that we do after the official shows.
10 minutes?
When we're starting to get kind of tired.
But what is it we need to tell them
that we can't tell them on the broadcast version?
Well, become a subgenius minister
by spending $35 on the ministerial pack,
which is quite a giant package of stuff.
It's got two 16-page booklets.
The 16 pages doesn't sound like
much, but each of these pages
is like five normal pages.
I would probably need
a magnifying glass to read it.
Now.
Especially if there was like
this psychotic dirigible orb,
you know, that goes flying around
in the middle of the night,
seeking people to chew up
like wolves in the darkness.
Man, that's some...
That's some...
That's some psychotic underpants
right there.
You can get those subpsychotic
underpants from the Church of the Subgenius too.
You can also get t-shirts
of many different designs,
actually dozens and dozens.
But the main one that most people want
is just your classic Dobbs head
portrait of J.R. Bob Dobbs,
a trademark owned by me personally, by the way.
And that reminds me,
I found a cafe press type company
making bootleg Bob stuff.
And they haven't responded to my,
my legal threats.
That's assault.
That's trademark infringement.
Anyway, friends.
That's salt and pepper with a,
with a sodium particle.
But I think they ought to read my,
I think they ought to buy my book
because I had a dream of somebody else
was seeing stuff from my book
in a way that somebody else would see it.
Huh?
And that really, not only frightened me,
it was very gratifying, of course,
and illuminating to be absurd.
And there's no real part of it.
I mean, I think that's the,
that's the approach we need for the standard of excellence
increased by the lack of the temperature
and the fact that the brain is just too small now.
Speak for yourself.
It's a wonderful book and it's hilarious
and it's frightening and it's everything you want a book
to be, especially when you got a half an hour
to spend in the bathroom.
It has pictures.
They're not very sexy.
I've got a, no offense, Dave,
but your drawings of the weirds,
I haven't, that's not Yankin material.
Oh, but that was too complicated,
that last concept, Dave.
I'm just, I can't wrap my brain around it.
Which? Which, which concept?
That last one.
The last one that you were trying to describe.
Whatever the hell it was.
Man, I'm really losing my,
I mentioned the word temperature,
so maybe I was getting caught and frozen at the same time.
You know what I mean, Dave?
I don't know.
Climate's very unpredictable.
Weather's unpredictable.
And unpredictables are the most unpredictable
of all. So,
prove us wrong. Go ahead and
buy stuff from us. We've been saying
nobody does. Make us a liar.
Actually,
people do. That's how I pay my half of the
mortgage, but
friends, yeah, there's
the book of the subgenius is still in print.
If you haven't
memorized that, what's
wrong with you? You better just
go home. You probably voted for
Trump.
It's not only
necessary reading. It's a
growth manual, you silly
people. It's an interior
exterior lux
of growth
manual. And if you get the little $10
metal Dobbs head pen,
it's really small. I mean, it's like half
an inch high, but it's really
metal and colored, and it looks
really, really cool. Oh, the cloisonne pen?
Yeah, the cloisonne pen. That's what the
French Masonic
Illuminati
wear.
If you wear one of those Dobbs head pens,
you can walk into any board meeting in
the whole world. They'll just make
you president, CEO, because you
got that cooler Bob pen than they
do.
They just have the little logo
button. They don't have the cloisonne
pen.
Cloisonne pen rules.
That's also called a badge
overseas
in Great Britain and the British Isles.
A badge instead of a pen.
Sometimes they'll just wear a piece of
Canadian bacon over their left titty.
And they'll take like a
magic mark and inscribe whatever
a captain
or a fisherman or a policeman.
He said titty.
And he said Canadian bacon and
almost peed my pants.
Hey, don't do it until
call the president if you're going to do that.
Don't waste it.
Oh, I say, you're wasting it.
That's a line from
a British Pea Party
tape
that was sent to me
by the author Rudy Rucker
and which I then
copied on VHS and would
label each one my favorite
tape and mail it to my
friends.
I'd address the package also to their
wives so that
the wife would open it and there'd
be this
Oh, no, it'd be like
if G. Gordon Gordon's
wife opened it that she'd find a tape
that said
Gordon's favorite
tape. And she'd go, oh, what is
this? And put it on and it's British people
urinating on each other
for fun.
The funny thing is there's like five parts
of that tape that were each half hour long and all
had different people urinating on
each other.
They're all in the same apartment.
Man.
Stop and think.
By the time the fifth sex party
happened in there,
they must have been ready to, you know,
drop the lease, get out,
move away,
go make their Pea Party's tapes
in another apartment.
There's nothing more exciting and more fun than
a fart lighting contest.
Pyroflatulation
is a subgenius
forbidden science taught
at Dobbstown University.
And you can judge them in
a few ways.
You can judge them by their shape,
their color,
their expansive qualities,
you know, like one's a ten,
another one's a twenty.
They all have
but sometimes they don't have keystrokes
instead of just numbers.
Well, in our pyroflatulation contest
at X-Day Drill,
after the chili cook-off,
about six hours after the chili cook-off,
we have
a special chamber where we can measure
and film each crepitation
and ignition.
And analyze them for color,
stench,
and that includes piss stench
or psychic stench.
Clarity or opacity
as the case may be.
Right.
Yeah.
And of course, distance
that the flame goes,
temperature. There's so many different
things, so many different elements that go into
a fine pyroflatulation.
Right. The lightness or depth
of scent.
All these things are judged.
Yes.
You should hear the jargon that goes with the judges.
Oh, an excellent afterbite,
but not such a good nose.
Let someone turn on the fan.
It's weird.
You know, guys got those pair of shorts
that they got to pull things in the back
and it automatically exposes
your
place Trump was
talking about.
Um.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, the little flap in the back of your pants.
Yeah.
I'll tell you something.
The commotion must be better and easier.
I was in
China, mainland China
in Beijing,
the city of Beijing
in
1986.
And of course,
about 90% of the population
dressed exactly the same
in those blue male outfits.
Except for
the
the little clusters of
mentally disabled people,
the differently
intelligence,
autistic folks.
There'd be this gang of guys
that look kind of, you know,
a little happier than they should be.
And they were dressed just like everybody else,
except they all had flaps
in the back of their pants.
And most of them were unbuttoned.
They were
they were ready for a fart lighting contest.
Yeah.
They trained in China from the time
as soon as they determined that you're a special,
you know, mentally subgenius person,
they train you for the Olympics in pyroflatulation
because they're
that's the best kind of people for that kind of thing.
They have no shame or
they're innocent, purely innocent.
They just get a big grin on their face.
They just they can't operate the lighter themselves,
but they can sure.
They can sure bend over and spread them.
They're pure.
And let it go.
Let it go.
Because, yeah, they're pure.
I got it while I was in Beijing.
I also got a massage
from a blind man.
And I was told that
that's a real common situation.
They go, oh, this kid's blind.
Well, we'll train him to be a real masseuse.
And this guy had hands like clamps,
like mechanical.
He was so incredibly strong.
It's actually the only lobster claws,
just about the only truly effective massage
I've ever gotten
because this guy was so unbelievably strong
and so blind.
Right there.
My friend said, staying those noise.
You're embarrassing me.
Sound like you're having sex
because I guess I was vocally letting the masseuse know
when it felt good.
Kind of like.
That's good.
Oh.
Right.
We're totally disgusting.
You're a jigger.
Please stop.
And that massage, this was in 1986.
The American dollar was still strong against the yuan.
And it cost about a buck
to get that incredible massage.
That's the only massage I've ever paid for.
And the only, I've only yet.
Huh?
I was going to say right here in Cleveland,
there's a guy who does that.
He's not an acupuncturist.
He's an acupressurist.
And he makes people,
that's his favorite thing,
he's making people go,
oh yeah.
Stuff like that there.
Oh, sounds like a good guy to know.
I'm about to do that.
Oh, oh.
But this gives my lower back hurts.
I just shift,
I had to shift position.
Dave, we have to go because my back,
I swear to God,
I really am going to have to get a different chair
for the studio.
Yeah, but I'm going to have to get a different chair.
It's just like a woman.
Or I'll have to get a,
or we need to just set this table up on another table.
Then we can stand up and do the show.
Okay, but that still doesn't mean
You don't have to.
I'm a woman.
Because you're not here.
But this lovely music is so.
But we love it that you're there, Dave.
I'm in Medicine Springs.
I'm in Medicine Hat.
Uh,
and,
uh,
Nana.
Well, that's better than the Medicine Fish Hole.
Not very much.
Actually, the Medicine Fish Hole is just where you want to be sometimes.
I wish I was down in the Medicine Fish Hole.
Down in the Medicine Fish Hole.
That was a Doctors for Wotan hit.
One of the only ones we ever had.
Down in the Medicine Fish Hole.
Well, we can change the lyrics now.
And with that,
I will kiss good night to this long night,
or short night,
or fortnight,
fart night.
Night of the Pyroflatulation.
That's just the way I'll always remember it.
Night of Infartenance.
Alright, uh, friends,
uh, thank you for listening to another extra 20 minutes of this hour of slack.
The people listening on the broadcast radio don't get to hear this.
Don't you envy them?
Okay, I'm going to turn off the recorder.
Okay.
Cheer it, cheer it, be a melody your heart can touch up through the sky.
Cheer it, cheer it, be a song to sing whenever things have gone awry.
Cheer it, cheer it, be when you feel sad just longing for a little.
While cheer it, cheer it, be.
Cheer it, cheer it, be.
Cheer it, cheer it, be the world's little smile.
Okay.
Cheer it, cheer it, be.
Cheer it, cheer it, be the world's little smile.