My name's crazy, honey. What's yours?
Bernice!
The Stone Genius.
Our love.
As long as the wind blows and the rains don't come too soon,
we may live.
That is, if we're not destroyed by other forces.
What other forces?
Never mind that now.
For now I show thee signs in the heavens
and signs in the earth.
Blood fetches from the earth.
My lights in the sky
rebuke thee.
The children of heaven
and the angels from hell
are among thee.
Spreading lies and deception.
And we'll take some convincing
before I believe you're the man.
The man that our church wants
preaching at us every Sunday.
I thought we'd all be dead by now.
We're not.
Even Raddick got out of bed today.
Gives me the creeps.
Logically, he should have been dead by now.
For deadening his mouth and carrying on the way he did 2,000 years ago,
that not only crucified,
but crucified him again.
We'd probably see it on TV.
I respectfully disagree with that.
Sit on my face and tell me that you love me.
Weep, weep, weep, weep, weep.
I think that the commonality of the problems and the concerns
of people all over the world
should make us brothers and sisters
and not adversaries.
And if you believe that, you'll buy this watch.
Oh, we're dead serious.
This is all too real, George.
No, the Church of the Subgenius
is not incorporated, registered, licensed,
certified, approved, or anything
by any creature of man's so-called state.
It recognizes no head
except the Dobbs head,
secular or sacred.
Only that head of Dobbs.
It recognizes the lordship of Bob
as the only sovereign,
the king of kings, salesman, and judge of all.
It is a missionary effort, you see,
to educate both the masses
and those in high places
that Bob lives, Bob sells,
and Bob has a law that should be kept
obeyed and enforced as a society.
Well, we're back here
in the Cathedral of Monkeys
where the children are born,
full-grown, and can be
completely covered
in every bit of beautiful
hammocks, hairs,
some of them carrying the chicken bones
they try to eat and swallow
later in their own table.
Is this what the white people are listening to?
Yeah, this is what the normals and everybody
they're into this stuff.
I did it again.
I played with your heart.
Got lost in the game.
Oh, baby, baby,
oops, you think I'm in love.
Oops, you think I'm in love.
That I came from above.
I'm not that sinless.
I deal with the goddamn customers
so the engineers don't have to.
I have people skills.
I am good at dealing with people.
Can't you understand that?
What the hell is wrong with you people?
You know perfectly well
what is the matter with you.
You've known it for years,
though you've fought against the knowledge.
You are mentally deranged.
Ha, ha, ha.
You know perfectly well
what is the matter with you.
You've known it for years,
though you've fought against the knowledge.
You are mentally deranged.
And...
Ha, ha, ha.
You know, Patrick, you're out of place.
I'm not kidding.
You've known it for years.
Are you a portugese now?
You are mentally deranged.
And I should...
3.19 a.m.
I worship your penis.
End of message.
You know, Patrick, you're out of place.
I'm not kidding.
You've known it for years.
Are you a portugese now?
You are mentally deranged.
12.41 a.m.
I am wondering if you have time,
and if it's not too much trouble,
on your next outgoing message,
would you please slap your nipples up against the phone receiver?
Thank you very much.
We'd all appreciate it.
End of message.
That's it.
Hmm.
Who is that standing out the window?
What's his name?
Bob.
Ain't that a bitch?
You're dry in vain.
You can't explain
the charming, alarming, blonde women.
They fascinate.
They captivate.
Beware the amazing blonde women.
Be careful when you meet the sweet, blonde stranger.
You may not know it,
but you are reaching danger.
You're dry in vain.
You can't explain
the charming, alarming, blonde women.
End of message.
Oh, Bob and the Fighting Jesus, we're talking to you now.
And we can feel it coming through in the spirit.
And we know there's a lot of special laid-up members and people with genetic things that are all different.
And they're needing to feel the power of you.
And some of them got tumors, some of them got cancers, and some of them got things in their brain that won't go out.
And some of them see little bitty men everywhere that they don't think are real.
But we know they're real, and we want you to make them feel right with all of this.
You should be destroyed.
Good.
Now, Jim, it's important to us that he live.
But why?
I'm not sure yet.
Oh, yes, dear friends, a little bit of Media Barrage number five there.
It's a show of new songs, weird clips, Einstein's secret orchestra swamp radio, and rants.
Yes, rants, all kinds of things.
And we've got new people, well, relatively new people, contributing.
We're going to the show by way of alt.binary slack this week, including the good Godex, whoever the hell that is.
Probably somebody we already knew using a different name.
And the great Fernando Dande-Limor.
Normally a graphic artist has been contributing bits and clips and things.
It's fun, but it's a lot of work, actually.
And there shall be slack.
Not a good cover, is it?
No.
It's like a little reggae-ish kind of ska sort of Jamaican accent doing schmooze version of jet plane.
She's the worst singer that we can buy.
Just like we've got the best government money can buy.
Britney's example of our cultural malaise.
Why?
What's wrong with America?
Well, just being a little overly critical.
Well, if you lived in another land, wouldn't you think this was vapid?
But I don't. I live here.
So if you live where they serve shit sandwiches, they're going to taste pretty good after a while.
Screw them.
It's just got to say, screw them.
Yeah, screw them all.
That's right.
Don't let any more in.
Kick out some of the ones you are in.
Except me.
I think they should kick out...
I think...
How's this? Will this work for a plan?
Let's kick the...
The richest 10% and the lowest poorest 10% out of the country.
Why the poorest 10%? What did they do?
Did they take all the...
Oh, they're just stupid.
Yeah, they're just stupid.
I'm tired of giving them handouts.
Oh, I see.
And the upper 10%, which is...
All the rich people, because, you know, it's like 10% of the population owns 90% of the...
They don't really live in this country, do they?
Or are they the ones that have...
As before, yes.
Just kick them out.
Don't let them have any bank accounts or anything.
Kill them if you have to.
Speak angrily about everyone else except for them.
And talk about genocide on their own people's system.
Then you'll get all the middle management people will then take over the country.
You know, that top 10% would not be very many.
How bourgeois.
But we are bourgeois, aren't we?
When we think about it, we don't have the revolutionary zeal to pull it off or pull it out even.
Please don't eat the brown asses.
I'm warning you.
Please get off those towers.
I had long hair before any of you jerk-offs.
Get on off those towers, you hard-ons.
Don't eat the brown asses.
I'm warning you.
And somebody find me a whore.
Grandpa bought a rubber.
Welcome to...
...Dobstown, you sexy ass of genius.
Welcome to Dobstown, you sexy ass of genius.
Welcome to Dobstown, Big Boy.
You always wondered how computers have sex?
This is Hyle.
Prepare to be pleasured.
Welcome to Dobstown, Big Boy.
you sexy ass subgenius.
Welcome to Dobbs Town,
big boy.
Yes, dear friends,
we're all gonna go to Dobbs Town,
you know. Heart Ignition
knows how to take a person to
Dobbs Town, and we're
gonna take you on
down, down, down,
friends, because you know the Church of the
Subgenius is what, it is that
thing which is on the march to
restore order, virtue,
and perversion,
and put them back into their proper perspective
for the good and survival
of civilized society, my friends,
because the Church of the Subgenius is what
has been twisted, and all that
has been perverted by sick, demented, and
depraved minds is to return to
the source of order. Order comes through law,
and perfect law comes only from
Bob.
I don't know, I still find
American.
This radio by IRC,
internet radio chat, so he's
a little bit behind. Well, actually, I'm
doing it by fornicated hollow zig.
If you've, uh, the new technology
is the real stuff.
I'm actually hollow zig. I don't have any...
Every zig.
There's no form here, there's no real molecules
popping around, there's, um,
just a
big, fat piece of cheese
staring at you.
Staring blankly into space.
Crying.
To those Americans who just
will not stand firmly and
totally enough in support of whatever it is
we're supporting.
Well, we're supporting the drug war, right?
It's the war on drugs. It's the same thing
as the war on them.
Because them are drugs,
right? It's the same exact
thing. And drugs are not
beer and wine
and liquor, because those are legal,
so they're not terrorists.
I am the drugs. And coffee.
I am coffee. And MTV.
Yeah.
No, you are Salvador Dali. You are the persistence
of religion. I am
you are
I think that song kicks butt.
And why am I telling any of you this silly thing?
Why, for almost no reason whatsoever.
Except maybe to get a cheap laugh.
And when was the last time a televangelist or a Taliban
screwed and did that for anyone?
Okay, then.
It should also be pointed out that any comparison
between subgeniuses and animals
includes the fact that we both will drop a load
anywhere we please.
There will be a test later,
but it won't matter because we'll just
crap on the desk, hump the teacher, and then jump out the window.
So what if the South had won
the Civil War? What would have happened then?
Huh?
What if the
Spanish had won the Spanish-American
War?
Well, if the South had won the Civil War, we probably would have been
able to have another...
What if the Germans had won
World War...
Six?
Then we'd have to frat.
I think it's time to frat.
Okay.
All right.
I'm sure glad that happened.
Okay, uh...
I want to be glad.
The thing is,
the Civil War never ended.
It's still going on.
The South winning, if you haven't noticed.
It never started.
It started, all right.
No, no, no.
It was the uncertainty.
It was the Civil War that started.
There's nothing civil about that war.
Well, you got them.
That was a damnable war.
Romantic.
Yeah, but what would James Joyce have said about it?
What would Aunt Bertha have said about it?
What would...
Yeah, what would Aunt Bertha have said?
Jesus did not always stay a baby.
Although I think he must have been the most
adorable baby you ever saw.
Still, he was the kindest baby
and he grew, just as you
boys and girls have grown.
No, boy.
Don't say that to me.
You?
Oh, let go.
It is wonderful to know that Jesus
was once a child like me
and lived on earth and worked and played
in his home in Galilee.
Wonderful, wonderful Jesus
who was once a child like me.
Thank you.
Wonderful, wonderful Jesus
like him I want to be.
Before his parents could hardly believe it,
Jesus was 12 years old.
He was a fine lad.
And Luke tells us in chapter 2,
verses 41 through 52,
a beautiful story about Jesus
when he was 12 years old.
I'm sorry.
I hope you're prepared somewhat beforehand.
This is a mutant.
You've been breeding them here for ages
to do menial work.
Well, actually, they're similar to some of the
insect life on your own planet.
Larger, of course, with a higher degree of intelligence.
I beg of you, go inside.
Cooperate voluntarily.
If you do, I give you my word that you will not be harmed
or your minds changed in any way.
Do you believe him, Cal?
In this place, I wouldn't believe my grandmother.
.
Well, that's settled.
Let's order a pizza.
A what?
A pizza.
You know, round, flat dough with tomatoes
and toppings and cheese.
I know what a pizza is.
Well, how fabulous for you, darling.
Because I could use a little mortal pleasure.
You know, sex.
I don't get it.
I've seen a number of your porno movies, and I've noticed that the pizza men tend to be rather
Well hung and quite over sexed
No, they still like Bob
Good
Like this traffic light change
Suddenly realized within the last few years. It's more of a not what you know and what you do, but who you know game
The smell of success is never too sweet
Yeah, I think we're being sold a bill big bill of good oh
Yes, and he
Ain't he ain't got superpowers paint from another planet
Hey, he ain't some some something that we have to bow down and kiss to you can pull Bob's leg
And bobble bobble chuckle right along with you because Bob
Bob's been a fool just like you or me. He's been a he's been a pathetic fool, and I tell you friends
Say our Bob Dobbs will be a fool again. He's a fool today
He's a fool
He's a fool tomorrow. He's the same Bob the same Bob. He's always the same Bob, and he's working for you and me
Let's go out in the field
Look at all those lizards man. I didn't know they could enlist
Man, they're tall
Wow man tails and everything and
Man, I can't imagine they can get those helmets on those guys with those weird heads
They look like kind of just tied on underneath. They look pretty human from a distance from a distance man
When you get a man this this showing up straight-up lizards man beyond that
Man, so Dave enlisted so I guess now everything's really true that United Nations really
Taken over our backyards
The barbecue pit and everything they'll be coming for you dude pretty soon Dave pretty well to the top of their relations
I could lick one of those lizards really easy man. He said look all you have to do is blow some cool
And staying are really high up on the list
You how did you get off the list man?
Well known high places. Yes, he has a job ah
Princess we has a job so she's not on the list some people have jobs other people have to work well. That's different
Yeah, that's the difference between
Eloy I truly truly feel sorry for the poor schmucks after work. Yeah the people who have to dig off wallpaper and
Remove things from their buttocks every night
carve little tiny pixels out of the art mines tiny little cars actually lodged in their colons
people have to be to watch cartoons
They have to make them frame by frame and can't even understand the cartoons
Cobbling them together and the cave wall and then run through the cave real fast each guy with a torch. That's
That's how you get off the flickering of fleck makes it look like we're really bad multimedia, dude
blinking I don't really think they improve that
on it.
Well, the camp is Futurama,
so what's there to live
for? Please don't remind me.
I can't believe it. Actually, our man
on the inside says that that might not be
true, that every season they do that
to Matt Granig because the executives
at Fox hate
The Simpsons and hate Futurama
because, especially The Simpsons,
because it makes them so much money,
but the cartoonists refuse
to heed any of the
suggestions from the executives.
And that's what this is all about.
It's a guys who wear
suits in offices thing
and I wouldn't understand.
They're all mind-controlled as well, all those
executives in suits. Who do you think they take
their orders from? Who do you think is
whispering in their ears?
Just not.
Did they give you your gun yet?
I got so depressed last
week one day.
I was reading the news and
they said that one day
George Bush said,
we're going to continue
this war on drug
terrorists and
everyone who, you know,
the nail that
sticks up will be hammered down,
George said. And then they raided
all the medical marijuana
places in, not
all of them, but a lot of them in L.A. and San
Francisco. They've been making war.
They've been making war.
Those cancer patients
and aid patients have,
better drugs they can get hold of
that are conspiracy approved
and part of the Lilly Corporation
with, you know, the right
stockholders. We all know the Lilly Corporation
has many...
It's like a needle full of
Dilaudid. Right after that,
I read that
Futurama was cancelled
and then I read that we were
going to take over the world
and that this was the Death
Star. Don't you think it's odd that
Lilly, behind all that stuff,
we are looking over Dave's shoulder as he
has his first night
in boot camp. Trying to sneak up on a
lizard behind and see if
Dave, if you're good at this soldiering stuff,
they'll let you push one of the big buttons.
You can push the big button and you
won't have to be a grunt like this if you work your way up.
I have been pounding on this big button with my
fist. No, you gotta
climb up on the backs of your
fellow soldiers until you're the
last man standing on the button.
Hey, Stang, tell me again, which button
is it that we put when we have,
to eject out of
our injection into his,
our nano-injection into Dave's eyebrow?
That's the blue pill. Like when he gets killed
with the bullet, you know, and
when we actually need to get out of there?
Oh. It's the blue pill?
I know the evacuation pill's for y'all
and I'm sorry, you'll have to remain in the
corpse to run along with it.
He ain't gonna live.
No, wait a minute.
No, you wait a minute. I love that
area.
The heat stress is going to be
associated with it. Our current,
uh, uh, protective ensemble does not
provide for bodily function, so
there's any way around it, any way
you look at it, that we're going to
have suffering or degradation.
Okay, just keep driving slow.
Just keep driving slow, but don't...
Yeah, just...
Yeah, just keep cool. Keep cool.
All we can do is hope he doesn't
start shooting. Oh, no! He's shooting!
He's bustling out the back window!
Oh, look out!
Ah!
Stay down! Stay down!
Ah! Chill!
Get down, Philo!
Friends, we've been hearing a ton of, uh,
the old subgenius
media barrage called Media Barrage
Number 5, which I've been
remastering, uh, for...
What? What? What?
What?
Bob Dobbs.
El Hijo.
De una gran puta.
Uh, yes.
Bob loves you,
and he knows love from the
inside out.
The old media barrage
tapes being slowly,
uh, reconverted
digitally, uh, came...
Originally were edited by, uh, yours truly
with puzzling evidence.
Uh, Byron Werner,
the great Saint Byron Werner,
and, uh, oh, uh,
I think, uh,
uh, Reverend, uh,
Stevie Hambone helped on that one.
Helped Pope Huey.
Edited quite a bit of the original
old, uh, Media Barrage Number 5 tape.
Uh, bits and pieces out of that.
Came from his ancient show,
uh, from, uh, from Texas,
a state which has banned
all subgenius broadcast.
Did you know that?
You could have...
But this, this church started in Texas,
in Dallas, Texas,
and yet all of the independent
and, uh, college radio stations
in Texas banned,
the church of the subgenius for being...
Well, I...
I guess we didn't empower
the right people, you might say.
But, friends, this,
this church, this church
is not, uh,
uh, some, uh,
pathetic little, uh,
giveaway church. We're not trying to give away
our enlightenment. We're not trying to give away
Bob, because, friends, you get what you
pay for. And this is
an independent effort
of concerned citizens,
subgeniuses, not part of any associated
ministry or organization,
officially or otherwise, except
possibly in spirit,
the spirit of slack, and prayer,
the prayer of to Bob,
which is committed by
committing your name to the line
and the check, the check that goes to
Bob. My friend, we don't apologize
for telling it like it is.
The truth and reality of normalcy
and normality,
that is what is offensive.
The conspiracy did not,
bring this perversion into the open,
but now that it is in the open,
we have to deal with it. And the way to deal
with that is to deal with reality.
Yeah, and, uh,
and that reality is
this!
My pussycat was
scratching out on my back door
Scratched so long
Poor pussy got sore
sore pussy
sore
pussy
Just a friendly little cat
Friendly little cat
My pussycat was setting out
on the front step
Sat so long
Poor pussy got wet
Wet pussy
sore
wet
pussy
Just a friendly little cat
Friendly little cat
My pussycat was playing out on the back lot
Played so long, poor pussy got hot, hot pussy
Sore
wet
hot
pussy
Just a friendly little cat
Friendly little cat
My pussycat was rocking in the rocking chair
Rocked so long, he was in the rocking chair
lost his hair
bald pussy
soared
wept
hot
bald
pussy
just a friendly little cat
friendly little cat
my neighbor
and I out at the
clothesline I said
to my neighbor won't you look at
mine my pussy
soared
wept
hot
bald
pussy
just a
friendly little cat
my neighbor stole my kitty
but I did see
I said to my neighbor
said my pussy free
free pussy
soared
wept
hot
bald
free
pussy
just a friendly little cat
friendly little cat
here kitty kitty kitty kitty kitty
aww nice pussy
aww
now I don't want to sound too unaggregative
I know I could have wound up with my A-frame
wrapped around a bad case of scoliosis
been beaten by big black coat hangers
wielded by Bing Crosby or
been born a one-eyed one legged black lesbian in Somalia
where the price of a good nice hum is a slice of aged pork without so many flies on it later
it just gets hard trying to hold on as hard as you can
so as to keep from being thrown to the wolves when the last guy who grabbed the golden ring
left an unsightly trace of his disquiet on the damn thing and reverse graced me with a truly grittily case of bodacious ingracious magnine round the corner de-infestation of the fine tuning gland
as payback for my daring yet precariously
over the new style of take your damn chance you quivering quagmire across the land and then you're gone
the wires publish or die are published and die but just lay there and you'll die for sure anyway get an amen
amen
praise Bob
kill Bob
now it's a long running game show call let's make Jesus puke
it's like supermarket sweep except that you put your children in their dreams on a dice and hack at them with incense braziers
and badly produced video epics about burning in hell if you don't think the baptism before you even have full control of your own bladder
if a child with potential falls in the forest of bad thing and lost opportunities is God still meek?
if you don't get this well I don't know look around you
we are defining in practical terms the immutable ideals that have guided us from the beginning
or kill me these were the words of J.R. Bob Dobbs in that single sentence
Dobbs set forth the real problem facing all humanity
and it's an especially poignant one today for Americans
in a real sense it is a rephrasing of a statement made thousands of years ago to the first couple
and because that first couple embraced that enlightened redefinition
the course of humanity was forever changed
and J.R. Bob Dobbs and many others today in our society are still asking you to embrace the idea that we really know is a better way
that we can define good and evil based upon contemporary popular opinion
that you can define life and your relationships to others in your own terms
in essence that you will be like God
you
Determine the truth
Emotions
Doings
Pro остановi
Consume
Nie
Darn
Curse
This
denotes
Your
Boys with the horns get down and blow.
They rear back, aim their bells at the stars.
They said, feed me, Big Daddy.
Hey, to the bar.
I did not put you here to suffer.
I did not put you here to whine.
I put you here to love one another.
And the kid has had a good time now, now, now.
Let the people go now.
Don't let my people go, go, go.
Let my people go, go, go.
Don't let my people go.
What I say.
Now, Jesus went out for a walk with his mother.
The scribes and the Pharisees, plot and hugger mugger.
They locked him up and they threw away the key.
He said, why is everybody always picking on me?
I did not put you here to suffer.
No, I did not put you here to whine.
I put you here to love one another.
I did not put you here to have a good time now, now, now.
Let my people go, go, go.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hey, you gotta, oh, you gotta.
Let my people go, go, go.
You gotta let my people go, go, go.
Sing it loud, I'm feeling so proud about being alive.
Let my people go, go, go.
You know, I think we're putting it out loud.
Good time.
Let my people go, go, go.
Oh, yeah.
Let my people go.
Got to let my people go.
Oh!
All right!
Let my people go.
The Rainmakers, dear friends.
A great old favorite band.
A band of mine from the day.
They disbanded, unfortunately.
The subgenius-like person behind that band was named Bob Walkenhorst.
But you can still find the Rainmakers here and there.
I'm going to try to resurrect their great legend here on the Hour of Slack.
Thank you.
Can you think of a better gift than something that helps a guy look good and feel good every single day of the year?
Can you?
Yes, now that I don't have to worry about how good and woeful you all are.
Actually, with things like compassion, positive karma and stinginess, don't you think it's...
Palin!
Come to Max gets p vaya
Oh, Michael Jackson!
The Shaving Head.
Down go the Shaving Head.
That's all they're gonna do.
Give you a close-up shake.
Clean you up as you walk.
Love.
Cleans you, thrills you, may even keep you from getting busted.
What happened to...
This is certainly the end of the road.
Dave, were you up for the draft during the Vietnam years?
Yeah.
How'd you get out of that, man?
How the hell did you get out of that?
I faked crazy, man.
Did you really?
I went to an...
How'd you get out of that?
Because you're a prime age for Vietnam, man.
I went to a Navy psychiatrist and he said,
Get out of here.
I don't want you in no U.S. Navy or Army.
Yes.
He said I was not the type.
Dave's insane.
He's truly considered insane by the U.S. government.
Yes, that's true.
I was considered flat-footed.
Wow.
I was number 30 in the lottery.
And they gave me wonderful drugs that made me crazier.
Wow.
I see three things.
Yeah, that's a sure ticket.
It was a sure ticket to Hamburger Hill.
But...
And I went in and I'd heard, you know,
that you put peanut butter up the crack of your...
Well, if you want to do that...
And all of that, and you do a lot of...
Why do you do that?
You run your...
It's a fun thing to do.
This is if you don't want to be in the Army, okay?
Why would you put peanut butter up your bunghole?
So that when they...
Look back there.
...bend over and call...
They feel like a snack.
You reach back there and grab yourself a snack
and lick your finger.
And they let you out of...
They, you know, mark you for...
They do their duty as well.
But it's an old gag.
I'm surprised you hadn't heard of that.
No, that must be one of those Texas ones.
No, it's a draft dodger routine from the Vietnam years.
Well, up here in Cleveland, they just went across the border.
Yeah, well, we didn't want to go across the border where we were.
No, senor.
You don't want to come here, by God.
It was...
But I tried everything.
I told them that I was...
And they still drafted you.
Notice how they have the borders nice and tight now?
I told them I was a homosexual.
I told them everything that they didn't want to hear.
They didn't care about your personal life.
They laughed at me.
The guy said...
That's what laughed at me.
There's a lot of boys in there, buddy.
Hey, well, notice this.
The borders are nice and tight now, right?
In the name of national security,
don't want to let them in, right?
Don't let them out either.
Yeah, right.
Right.
Now they can bring back the draft
and we won't have what happened with Vietnam.
They won't be running over the border up to Canada.
You will not be living some...
Living in some...
...happy-doopy...
...pot-smoking...
...poison-spoken sex life up in Toronto.
Toronto, yeah.
You know, walking them blues to you, man.
Ain't getting away this time.
We got the borders sealed now.
Yeah, and the border seals are some of the toughest mammal carnivores
ever, ever enlisted from the Arctic forces.
They're not going to let any Canucks down here
or any Yohus up there.
No Canucks, no way.
Guarding against Canadian attack.
And no funny pink wigs either.
List county coast watchers.
I'm a member.
Yeah.
Yep.
And he's been dismembered for so long now
that he can't even...
He can't even remember where he left that scotch.
I don't trust them Canadians at all.
And I am one.
You are one?
Well, scotch-Canadian.
Well, I see what's going on here.
Everybody's loyalty in question.
And you're the Canadian.
You're the Canadian.
Yeah, I'm born right here on this side of the lake.
I thought you were a real Smith.
I thought I heard you say...
I am.
A scotter Smith is as real as scotter Smith's get.
Yeah, I heard you say a boot a couple times.
Not if they go to Scotia.
It comes right from Scotland.
Not if they go to Scotland.
They're filtered through the bladder of Canada.
The mighty bladder of Canada.
Nova Scotia is not part of Canada.
You come to laugh along with us
as we take a train to the bladder of Canada.
Get in the canoe, my friend.
We shall go down the urinary track
and get some furs,
and then we shall...
Oh, look.
I know it's going...
At least I can trace it directly.
You know, it's Cleveland, Nova Scotia, Scotland.
How the hell does Texas get in there somehow?
Well, some races have always...
You're like a wetback army dildo.
Some races have always been in Texas.
They...
Texans.
Ah.
You are one of the people of the core.
There's Angloid Texans.
There's Black Texans.
There's...
Krauts.
Mexican Texans.
There's all kinds of Texans.
Yes, how many Krauts?
There's even Jewish Texans
that sound just like me.
Yeah, they say,
Oy vey, don't you?
That's what they say right there.
And Chinese Texans
that sound just like me.
They say,
Gun hay, fai, choi, stang,
it's a year of the horse.
It's a type of...
It's actually a subspecies
of the human race.
It's kind of Chinese Texans.
How did they end up there?
The Texans exist to irritate
all the other people everywhere.
Except the Australians.
We're kind of in with the Australians
and doing the same
because they're in the same business
as the Texans.
Yeah, big tall guys growing up
beating the hell out of everybody.
Some Brazilians
from the United States.
from the fields,
the high plains area
are like that.
Yes, but Brazilians
are annoying in a different kind of way
than Australians and Texans
which are more like macho.
Yeah, they're kind of sexy.
No, they have a lot of sex
in the streets
and all that kind of stuff.
They don't have no carnival down there.
They're better looking
but it's not that much less uptight
in Brazil.
Oh, I thought you were talking
about the Texas carnival
where they wear the big chaps
and the 20-gallon hatchet
and they show their cuckoo
and dingy lingus.
In the woods in Brazil
they know how to party.
Oh, yeah.
Those wood,
the bark snuff puffers.
Bark puffers, yeah.
The yano puffers.
Bark snuffers.
You know my momma, people.
I smell a bark snuff puffer.
And I like it.
I like the National Geographic babes
that grow out in the jungle
with the little
mo haircut.
Oh, what was that?
That's a little bull.
The little unicorn thing
in the middle of their foreheads.
Red ochre makeup
they spread on there.
Oh, yeah.
And that's also when they die
they spread red ochre
all over their genitalia too
as a sign of,
I guess just like a road sign
or something.
And it's not running out
of their faces
because of the drugs
they shoot up their noses
with bamboo.
I'm not hearing
any of this actually.
I just seem to be
You want my nose, honey?
You can blow another punch.
I'm not hearing
any of this actually.
Slowly towards the bathroom.
I'm going to talk
to the god now.
A dog that's like
me and John.
He could tell
that he was occupied.
That means spirit
from doing them drugs.
I'm going to talk
Occupied by a foreign army.
Not only a foreign army
but an alien army.
Yes, an alien army
had invaded
his private inner sanctum
and has inched his way.
Saw the light
listening,
glimmering,
a chef
bursting out
and striking him
on the forehead.
He's like,
I fell down
and I'm on a sneeze.
And there it was
upon the throat.
And the,
the,
the visage
of the man himself
rammed
down
the face
of the
the thing
that,
that
incredibly
emaciated
the face
of the
We'll return
with
The Vampire
on the Block
after this word
from Selby Sotes
made from
real human hands.
You are
our soap.
My fellow Americans.
We have a serious
responsibility
to halt
all evil
everywhere.
Especially that evil
which is undefined.
You know what to do.
That can only be defined
in the mind
of one glorious
brilliant man.
A man who rose
much like Napoleon
on his horse
to the high reins
of highness.
George W.
Oh, I thought you were
gonna say Bob
Jub, Jub-ya-Dob.
See baby
we're on fire!
Why?
Who are you?
Seems very expected.
This guys is a
snob.
Ah
What are you waiting for?
Are you trying to
goFace my
yogurt?
You love
White gum?
Ona and Canobite for some of the scripting on tonight's show.
And you have been listening to the subgenius radio ministry,
Hour of Slack.
Praise be the stations that carry this godforsaken show.
Those which pay for it, and even those which don't.
But especially those who do,
such as the independent subscribers to this show,
the good doctors, and they actually are real doctors.
Praise Dr. Tillis, and praise Dr. Johnson,
the doctors, the surgeons,
who help support this show by subscribing to it,
just as if they themselves were radio stations,
and as a result they hear the untrammeled, uncut version,
sort of like on the internet version,
but in 44.1 kilohertz.
This is the subgenius radio hour of Slack.
You can address your questions in the postcards too.
Reverend Ivan Stang, post office box 181417.
Cleveland Heights, Ohio, 44118.
Thank goodness, there's this different kind of dinner roll.
J.R. Dobbs, Bob Dobbs, J.R. Bob Dobbs,
was on the number one list of frauds and phonies for Time Magazine,
and I didn't know who he was.
Exactly.
And J.R. Bob Dobbs is the creator of the Church of the Subgenius.
This guy, the Reverend Ivan Stang, is one of their...
Disciples.
Yeah.
All right.
You know, it's funny.
I don't think Jesus had a disciple named Dopey.
Or Bob.
Oh, my God.
What the fuck did you call me here?
Murder.
Liars.
Producers.
You'll probably Vale it way better.
Bitch.
You did it.
Elrond Hubbard, your sins against humanity will sacrifice your life force in order to
form a virus. To undo the damage you've created, your spirit will be turned into a word virus,
triggered by your very name. Every time your name is mentioned, your organization will
be destroyed, visualized, and lacked care and strength.
Sucking the spirit energy of Elrond Hubbard into it, becoming more and more solid.
Feeding upon the soul of Elrond Hubbard, destroying the life force of Elrond Hubbard,
so he is no more.
Now we crush that down into the size of a virus.
Smaller, smaller, infinitesimally small.
And we launch it. We launch it so that every time Elrond Hubbard is mentioned,
a penis of the Psychotology dies.
And we launch it to the world.
And we launch it so that every time Elrond Hubbard is mentioned,
The thought virus by the El Queso All Stars.
More in there. War against the Church of Scientology.
Just another rival cult for the great Church of the Subgenius.
And friends, you know, as our friend, champion Jack Codini also likes to say, kill them all.
I know that over the years, many of you have seen the pictures and news clips of the concrete and mortar,
the guard posts and machine gun towers, the dog runs and the barbed wire that is American.
We will, we will rock you.
Sing it.
Everybody.
We will, we will rock you.
Hail Kings of Feedback.
Say it again.
Slack.
You Slack the show.
Slack beyond your wildest dreams.
Right now it's Slack.
You have the power to fight.
Fight Slack.
Good something for nothing.
Credit cards are taken.
Slack.
Send cash.
I want more Slack.
Send your money now.
Conspiracy denied me again.
Send your money.
I will have my Slack.
Your Slack sale's been adhered.
Slack.
Buy more Slack.
Use Slack.
Look good.
Your very own.
All sorts of Slack.
Your Slack.
Every kind of Slack imaginable.
Slack.
Slack from the other side of the world.
The track.
Slack from right next door.
Here we go.
The Slack salesman.
Your Slack salesman ladies and gentlemen.
You Slack.
Buy it here, buy it now.
We have used Slack.
I'm the vinper, I want my Slack.
His we have used Slack.
One Slack there's tuition.
Use Slack.
Slack.
You know I'm pillar for all for campaigns.
But even you have a Youounding.
Of you have a chance you can have your Slack.
There is no cheating.
offverts like the deals with Swag.
or get it all from me for use Slack you can the case.
You're sawing but you're asking the question.
Slack
Something for nothing
Slack is great
Slack
Slack is government controlled
For your protection
I want more Slack
Slack is not for everyone
You cannot take my Slack away
Slack can be taken by prescription
Slack is for everyone
Go Decks!
Go Decks has contributed bits of sound
and that was John Carpenter from Ghosts of Mars
Well I noticed no one called tonight to
pick up or at least throw back or throw up
a little bit on our most
probably most
wasted concept here tonight
What will the Aborigines
of this land
Ohio, the native Ohioans
those of you who
ride the RTA every day
those of you stuck in
traffic, those of you who
can't pull up your pants without the help
of a trained physician
what will happen to you?
A doctor
E.L. Smits
of the University of Southern Colorado
had a few brief words
and this is what he said
Apparently the Texans
say they will inspect
good slaves of the Ohioans
during the
coming war
Thank you
Until next week
Keep your hat on
Keep your diapers snapped up
Keep your hat on, Tay
You're back to the wind
You're back in your saddle
You're back in your sack
Come here!
Bon voyage, Waylon brother
I'm gonna miss you, man
A race of Americans
Just like...
Just like you and I is
Red, white, and blue
Mamas, don't let your children
grow up to be lonesome cowboys
Die now
And pick up the inside
Take it from Waylon
Twinkle, twinkle
Little star
How I wonder
what
you are
And you're gonna want
Never give up
Whatever this life has taught you
You'll never give up
Keep your head up