Either of you men fear what I fear?
It's funny. They think you're YouTube-ing for everyone saying this when you take content.
I'm afraid she's right, Mr. Vandergilt.
But how can we be sure?
The self-genius, power of...
What?
That devil!
Good grief. I'm on my way.
I'm on my way.
Today is a very special day. It's X-Day.
And to help explain the significance of this day, allow me to read the Wikipedia entry
about the
X-Day is a traditional part of the Church of the Subgenius, a religion formed as a parody cult of extreme religious groups and their pamphlets and claims.
X-Day fell on July 5, 1998, the scheduled end of the world, and has been celebrated on July 5 each year since then.
From its inception in 1980, the church had prophesied that an army of alien invaders known as the X-ists, or men from planet X, would land on the planet Earth and destroy the world of normals, pinks, and glorps, while the members of the Church of the Subgenius would be rescued by the aliens and taken away into space.
the Global Mar galaxy may have신
The Arghottqang
The dinosaur
''Ofirst Life''
showing up
up
the Bozo Cult, until eventually their souls are devoured by the Elder Gods.
The book also tells readers that if they want more information, they should send $1 million
to Ivan Stang so that he can remake his 1973 film, Let's Visit the World of the Future.
First Event
When July 5, 1998 arrived and no alien fleet appeared in the sky, members of the church
began citing a large number of conspiracy theories to explain why the predicted end
of the world did not take place.
The most popular explanation for the failure of the prophecy in the church is usually summarized
with the statement,
The calendar is wrong and July 5, 1998 has not really arrived yet.
Because of this, the church has held annual gatherings around July 5 of each year since
1998 to celebrate X-Day and greet the arrival of the anticipated alien sex goddesses.
No flying saucer rendezvous has been confirmed as of 2013, but members of the church have
been undaunted.
The X-Day celebration has become well known in underground culture circles.
Many underground rock bands have performed at X-Day, and the event has evolved into a
festival similar to Burning Man, lasting for three to five days with rock concerts, artistic
events, bonfires, and parties taking place day and night.
Regular events at X-Day include a symbolic effigy burning of J.R. Bob Dobbs, the founder
of the Church of the Subgenius.
A baptism where participants have their sins washed and their sins cleansed.
Concerts and performances by underground rock bands and performance artists such as the
Amino Acids, theme camps, and an auction where participants are encouraged to donate strange,
unusual, and offensive items of all sorts, including themselves.
Burners familiar with the Burning Man event have been upset by the fact that X-Day is
not a commerce-free event in the fashion of Burning Man.
The band has been working on a new album called Burning Man, which is a new album that is
being sold to the public.
The band's members and participants at X-Day are, in fact, encouraged to sell their own
items, music, and CDs and albums and other paraphernalia.
The Church of the Subgenius has responded to these complaints with a statement that
it is not a non-profit church.
To quote,
We're for profit, we want profit, and we want to cast out false prophets.
However, the church's status as an independent corporation with no corporate affiliations,
is a
That was Reverend Flamegrape on the very first episode of his subgenius show, Fugue Segway,
which runs on Wonderful Wozo.
Or, I don't know.
W-O-Z-O-F-M in Knoxville, Tennessee on Sundays at 11 o'clock, which station also runs Hour
of Slack.
Praise Bob.
We're going back to 18X Day again this episode for the edited recordings of the horror of
7am July 5th, as well as the happiness of the Bob-tism.
And some discussion of the same recorded the night of July 5th on Dr. Sinister's show on
WCSB Cleveland.
Radio Synesthesia.
But first, a word from Father Joe Mama.
We all know vaguely what X-Day is.
Bob told us himself that it shall occur July 5th, 1998.
The X's shall land and whisk the good subgenies off to a never-ending pleasure cruise of
the cosmos.
But what of the peaks that remain on earth?
What will happen to the A-holes that are left behind?
Well, friends, as much as I hate to gloat over those things, I'm not going to go into
the details of what's happening.
But if you're a little less fortunate than I am, the fact is, they'll get exactly what
they deserve.
Now, to any real subgenie, giving a normal what he deserves is about the cruelest fate
a normal could ever receive.
After all, these are the same normals that have supported the conspiracy for centuries.
These are the same normals that have tortured us with their ignorance and defiled the name
of Bob.
These are the same normals that have taken the most free country in the world and turned
it into an ever-growing bureaucratic governmental monster.
This is a story of the best-ever-before.
I'm Bob Sargent.
that feeds on taxes, committees, laws, statutes, buck passing, and fill in the blank.
Then, once the creature's rot-filled gut sprues out the digestive combination
of all the vices before mentioned by the lawyers and liars that created this filth,
what's the result?
Why, the conspiracy, of course.
And this pile of stinking defecation we're supposed to kneel before
and worship and serve?
Never!
Bob will avenge us for the years of conspiracy rule
on that most dreaded of subgenius holidays, X-Day 1998.
Dreaded by them, but not by us.
Welcome to Synesthesia, a very special episode here.
I'm Dr. Sinister.
With me in the studio are Dr. Howland L.
Hello.
And Reverend Ivan Stang, back for the post-mortem
on yet another case of Bob leaving us high and dry.
On America's grisliest autopsies.
And the only time we want to be left high and dry is during a flood.
Yes, and you mean to say, harking back to that PSA,
that you have to buy special insurance just to cover yourself in case of a flood?
That seems a little bit...
It is true that most homeowners' policies do not cover flood.
Even if you live in floodplain terrace estates?
If you...
You get, uh...
Yeah, they'll make an exception if you deliberately move into a place
called floodplain terrace estates.
Floodplain terrorist estates?
But the deductible is half a million dollars.
Oh, that's a little bit too rich for my blood.
Anyway, out in Wisteria at X-Day,
no one is concerned with questions of realty or real estate
except Andrew the Impale.
And no one can hear you scream because everyone has, like, earbuds and so on.
Well, they're all screaming.
No one can hear you scream.
They're all screaming.
They're all so screaming at the top of their voices.
It's true.
During the subgenius rave,
where they get down on the ground,
eat grass like Nebuchadnezzar,
and foam at the mouth.
That was just last night.
And then, the very next morning,
we assemble at the saucer landing field
and give the countdown
and look up into the huge, echoing, empty dome
of overarching space
for the manifestation,
of the special Vimana,
the craft which will whisk us into a new paradigm.
One of these days.
Yeah, whenever it really is 1998, obviously.
It wasn't this time.
I'm asleep because I'll be all fropped to the gills.
I've got a bottle of wine in that green thing there.
I've got a big old bowl of frop in my pocket, already loaded,
so that I can just pull it up.
I'm fired up.
I have...
While I wait for the X's to land.
I'm gonna miss them.
My wife and kids.
I got memberships, right?
I hope.
Lily doesn't.
But she's automatically saved.
Because she's under the age of reasoning.
You're right.
She's like the innocence.
She'll go to the purgatory.
Where was it?
Limbo.
What is limbo?
There's all those technicalities in Christianity.
That's why it's never gonna succeed.
Shall I go get your jacket, mon frere?
I'll jump off this time.
I'll jack it off for you.
Yeah, pre-jacket.
Would you?
So it comes back only flaccid.
This isn't suitable talk for such an august moment.
Yeah, I'm augusted.
This is august.
I need to get out of here in order to run away.
I'm going up to there and get my coat.
He's gonna go get your coat.
Oh, he is. Okay.
That's what he was saying, you deaf old bard.
I can hear you fine.
Isn't that interesting?
That's because I have that voice, a certain voice.
The piercing, dromundian, overman voice.
It's a company by silent radio.
It's a voice that has been honed for years of interrupting people.
And talking over people.
I had to work on it really hard to make it do that all the time.
It's not that I'm rude.
Not that I mean to do that.
It didn't cause anything.
You're trying to talk over Wellman's background sound track.
I've never seen that type.
Look at all these subgeniuses waking up in early morning.
Yeah, I heard they use...
I see people staring and even moving slowly down the road toward the field.
Just running down.
So many people with so little faith.
Still lying around.
Taking their time.
So unenthusiastic about this great day.
You're here to be in a great day.
People still lying around in their hammocks and their nests.
Whirled up in their little domiciles.
Sleeping through the end of the world.
They're scratched together.
Beds of leaves and cardboard.
The world ends not with a bang but with a snore.
With a snimper.
With a simper.
Simpering end to the simpering world.
Stop snoring, sleepo.
You're waking me up.
Here, let me get out.
Here, let me close this door.
Philo, can you hold this tape recorder for a second?
I sure can.
I can't believe he's getting me to hold this tape deck like this.
It's such a hard work I have to do this without...
And I'm not prepared for this.
This work that Stang has me doing.
Holding the tape deck.
Where is everyone?
The losers aren't here.
What are we doing down in the woods over there?
They're outside the blast radius.
They've gotten lifted already.
Oh, now I get it.
It takes one of the good mobsters to understand.
So we look on the ground here and...
Oh, Sinfaltimus is costume.
He was lifted up.
Look at the ground.
Oh, no.
There's a...
He was eviscerated.
Gay for Bob.
Somebody wearing a Gay for Bob shirt was lifted up.
What's over here?
This is horrible.
Sucking the church world.
This is what it looks like after the world ends.
All the empty clothing laying around.
There's nobody over there.
Those people that aren't there, their clothes are here.
I was only a couple minutes late.
What time is it?
I thought I was on time.
We can't...
We can't have been left behind.
We've been left behind.
I think my watch was wrong.
Where's my right behind?
This one has a note on it.
So does this one.
The only missing thing is you, John.
Where were you, Stang?
That one asked.
Oh, I'm glad I looked down.
The missing thing is you.
I've been...
This is the second X day I would have gone through with my fly down.
Well, I'll...
If you want, seriously...
I'll put mine down to show solidarity if it's broken.
No, that's okay.
I managed to get it back up.
As it were, so to speak.
I leave mine down a lot.
Another note...
I found Susie.
Oh, Susie was definitely in this one.
I could recognize her foul stench anywhere.
Stang, we waited as long as we could.
Sorry we missed you.
Oh, man.
I think about all those naked people on that saucer and it's kind of hot.
Wait a minute.
That was a saucer built for 14 and there's at least 15 shirts on it.
It's over.
And there's a launched bleeding head over there.
I think that's Synthothemus's head.
Well, left behind.
That's us.
Too damn bad.
What an ignominious thing.
And somehow it just figures though, doesn't it, that Philo, after all of our work...
All of our hard work.
Hard, hard work.
We worked so hard.
To be left behind!
We missed the boat.
Well, why?
I don't know how I'm going to deal with this.
Our watches aren't running. Oh my God, it's only five minutes to showtime. Five minutes!
Five minutes and we can be back in bed aboard our escape vessels. There'll be much bigger beds.
Yeah, big, beautiful, big...
How big was your bed going to be?
My bed was going to be like 12 blocks long and 16 blocks wide.
Mine was going to be like Rhode Island.
Well, that's 12 blocks long by 16 blocks wide. It's a little state. It's very small.
I don't want to be left behind!
Oh, baby bear! Don't cry!
Wait a minute. I don't want to be left behind either!
I appreciate this.
I think we'd be kidding.
They left us behind!
Calm down now. I think actually, really, if you step back...
Fuck!
...for a second and just consider this, the absurdity of the situation, you'll realize that we're all victims of a cruel, cruel joke.
Joke?
Yes, this is...
Joke!
Yeah, this is just...
What kind of...
And the cruelty of it is so...
It's so deep off wood.
It's so deep. So deep.
Where are all those naked people standing over in the woods looking at these empty clothing?
Yeah, acting like they're...
Shivering.
Joke is right!
They're acting like they have clothes on!
They may have succumbed to the blandishments of a fake saucer which did not lift them up.
My God, what a grisly thought!
Well, none of them wear watches. Imagine if the Greys or some false aliens showed up at quarter of seven.
They wouldn't know the difference. They'd be lifted up and they're probably now in pens...
Being herded around, prodded with probes and...
Some will be kept as pets.
...cattle, mutilation devices...
Some will talk of the human pet boy who died so sad.
Whoa! Oh my God! We're standing around here jawing and once again it's two minutes till 7 a.m.
Oh, you've got... This is the first time we've ever had an accurate countdown clock.
What's the time?
That's because we're...
Flight C-TAUGE has this new technology.
We have new technology. This is the digital age.
So we'll actually hit the countdown right.
We've gone from pre-digital to digital.
You should leave that. You should start with the 10.
Okay.
For the countdown.
Oh look, here come the jokers back.
Ha ha ha!
So amused.
So amused now, huh?
I guess you're gonna show us a ticket stub and find your seat number.
They kicked us off the fly!
We were up there, they kicked us off the fly!
You got lifted up by the escape vessels and you got kicked off. Way to go Susie the floozy.
That's great. I don't suppose they're planning to come back or anything?
What time is it?
Less than two minutes.
Less than two minutes to find out whether they're going to come back.
This is rather a new twist on the thing.
Ha ha ha!
Friends, remember your life here on planet Earth.
How easy it is.
How easy it was. Everything just...
I guess it wasn't for the...
Oh wait. No, no. It was a crappy, tedious, boring life here on planet Earth.
And that will be over with soon. I have faith.
I had a vision when I was knocked out last night.
Yeah, that was what it was. Knocked out.
An epiphany?
Yeah, an epiphany.
So, and then I saw that everything will be just right.
Everyone's here.
Yeah.
Will no one be left behind? What's our time now?
Here we go.
Oh my god. Thirty-five seconds.
Thirty-five seconds. Oh, I'm so excited. I'm going to wee wee in my pants.
My pants are going to be damp.
This is right when Bobber gets left behind, asshole!
Ha!
Fifteen, fourteen, thirteen, twelve, eleven, ten, nine, eight, seven, six, five, four, three, two, one.
Ten, nine, eight, seven, six, five, four, three, two, one.
Five, four, three, two, one.
Fuck them all!
Fuck them if they can't take the job!
Oh, it's about a three.
Wait, I think I see something.
Nah, that's just shit in your eye.
Oh.
Oh, god.
Let me take that head. I'm relieved for myself now.
One more time, I heard that.
This is, I'm not going to, I try to drown my sorrows in bleeding head stump fucking.
I don't think I can even get it up, even for that next stump.
It's the twenty years.
Dr. Dark, maybe we should have stayed in bed.
The one thing that's been in common every time is him and me have been here.
One of us has got to go.
I think we should have just...
Just stayed in bed.
Only one can survive.
Fight to the death.
We are already dead.
That is pointless.
Huh?
With soda straws.
Fight to the death with soda straws?
Oh, yeah.
But you gotta use those flip flops right there.
Yeah.
There you go.
One of you gets the salmon, one of you gets the purple pear, and you just go at it.
Why does this seem so familiar?
Hey, look, your shoes have the same tendency as your checks.
I don't know if you're joining.
Yeah.
This seems just like I've been here before.
I'm having this horrible, depressing deja vu.
Hey, where's that Bob dummy?
I feel like lynching something.
He's a wise dummy.
He didn't see the reason to come down here.
It's Pease's fault.
Reverend, Reverend Pease.
Yeah, exactly.
Why didn't he come?
We're not Pease.
Oh, because he fucked up.
Pease fucked up.
Once again.
Well, anybody that's not here fucked up.
Pease, stop it.
Here's another fine mess you've gotten us into, Reverend Pease.
Been here, done this.
You know, there have been all sorts of people tinkering with the calendar over the years.
Julius Caesar, Omar Khayyam, the Pope.
They've just managed to get it all twisted around, so it's difficult for people to get
more 不要
Uh-huh.
I know.
I haven't seen him in a while.
Any times he comes, what is he supposed to be, like, Let's just fuck that up.
I meanろ
He just which is an idiot to, you know, that shit.
Well, you know beginning to work from a pharmaceutical să's.
Genius believes that, or a variation of it.
I just wonder how far off the calendars are.
Is it like a 10-year?
Well, no, it's more than 10 years already.
Far off.
A thousand years?
Right wing, dude.
The conspiracy's been working for at least a thousand years just to embarrass J.R. Bob Dobbs.
It's quite possible.
The devil is an angel and sees ahead with his infra-vision.
Yep.
If the devil and Superman fought, who would win, Dr. Howe?
Well, I think the theologians would have to say it would be old Nick, the Prince of Darkness.
I would think so.
After all, the mephitic evidence of evil permeates all parts of the cosmos that are not original chaos, the unformed, crawling darkness.
But there is a problem.
Which is that...
Supposedly, these demonic spirits are confined to hell.
So, how could he even get out to get Superman?
But the devil himself has an answer for that one.
Which Mephistopheles has often said to Faust.
When he said, you know, how come you're here when you're supposed to be trapped in hell?
The devil said, why, this is hell.
Nor am I out of it.
Honky.
So, there you go.
I mean, how can you fight that?
Hell is where you hang your hat, I guess.
Now, what if Superman fought J.R. Bob Dobbs?
Dobbs?
Dobbs would win because he's luckier than Superman.
He's lucky. He surfs the luck plane.
And Superman would run into some fifth-dimensional imp or lump of red kryptonite or something like that
that the plot writers would fire at him with their loaded quids.
Me bizarro Superman. Me hate slack.
And that's terrible.
Pipe smoke me.
Me have bad luck.
Yeah, I bet Superman would actually use his heat vision to reignite Bob's pipe if it were even capable of going out.
I'm sure he would do that.
The day that that pipe goes out, so is thy puny life snuffed out, mortal disbeliever.
Which is why we would need Superman.
And the Dottle. Don't forget the Dottle.
raining down like fire on the rooftops of the unbelievers.
It's going to be a terrible moment for everyone
except the subgeniuses who will snicker
as they watch from above in smug satisfaction.
And their snark saucers.
Mm-hmm.
That's what we've always been led to believe.
Only some of us may feel in these dark hours
that possibly some charlatan put something over on us.
But just a moment does this apostolic thought...
Now, Wyatt, are you saying that a preacher like Bob
might lie or be wrong?
I didn't mean Bob, Stang,
but it's quite possible that somebody
might be putting a whammy on us.
It happens in one's personal life.
It can happen in the life of an organization.
I don't know.
I mean, if Bob says it, doesn't that make it true automatically?
Well, it makes it relevant
because it's a person who's a Christian.
Bob sold it, I smoked it, that settles it.
Mm-hmm. That's it.
How many times have I said that phrase in the last couple of weeks?
As many as you need to wriggle out of an embarrassing conundrum.
That's right.
Sacred doctrine of erasability.
I didn't say that. I didn't really say that.
That tape, that's just doctored.
They Photoshopped that tape.
Make it sound like I said that.
You know, we've got more people every year.
That really says something sad about the subgeniuses
mentality.
It certainly does.
Yeah, more people are let down every year.
We're supposed to be lifted up.
And once again, let down.
At this point,
you've disappointed more people than I ever have.
Me? I'm not piloting
spaceships. Why is everybody
looking at me? Do I look like an
exist? Look, it says right here,
July 5th, and I...
Uh-oh.
Um...
Maybe we should
have looked at the fine print a little more closely.
Susie, you look really
pathetic again. Thank you.
Once a year, we all look
so damn lame and
pathetic.
Sad. It's so sad.
We could say
maybe next year, but that would
possibly be even lamer than ever.
Twenty.
It's never worked.
Twenty years.
Well, next year will be the 21st time that you do it.
Huh? Next year will be the 21st
time that you've done it. Well,
the first couple of times, we weren't expecting
anything to happen.
They were just drills. Right.
It turned out there have now been 20
drills.
Twenty drills.
You'd think somebody would get
a life.
Oh, well.
Oh, that's good.
Everyone step right up and get your rubber earth eraser.
It has a picture of the planet earth on it.
And you can get to erasing now.
I guess the X's aren't gonna do it for us.
Once again, the salesmen, the space gods, and everything else,
we thought they were gonna do our job for us.
Mine actually kind of looks like Hulu.
There's your earth eraser, since I'm a mess.
Grass patch.
Get to erasing, kids.
One human at a time, I guess.
One building.
Look at this.
They all have their hands out.
This is so sad.
I meant my eraser.
Can't I at least get one rubber eraser?
I spent 40 years and $100,000 on the church and the septenians.
I want my eraser.
I'm gonna go get my eraser.
This guy's shell shocked.
I think I bought 50 and there's about 10 left.
These are genuine Chinese erasers, so don't put them near your mouth.
Not guaranteed to work after the end of the checkout aisle.
At least we got earth erasers.
At least we got erasers.
I know.
It's lame.
Well, we wanna hurt ourselves on the sharp edges.
Bob!
Just don't eat it.
Why hast thou forsaken us?
This never stopped me.
Bob.
This is like...
When did Bob do this?
Then why does it fit in my mouth?
They were going to take us off, but when they saw that a prank was being attempted...
Yeah, that way you didn't have to buy extra poison.
Oh, is that it?
Hey, way to go.
Whose idea was this empty clothes here?
Sounds to me like the exes...
Princess Wee.
It sounds like the exes got here, looked around and went, oh, they've already been taken.
We can just skip this one.
No, just doe.
Doe.
Dang.
That's all I have to say, dang.
Thank you, Daniel.
Dad, blame it.
Uh-huh.
We weren't supposed to say blame.
That's a cuss word.
Yeah, consarnant.
But I'll say it anyway.
Dad, blame it.
Uh-huh.
Consarnant.
Easy, Stang.
Remember your blood pressure.
Tarnation.
Gosh, oh my, get out.
Gol darn it.
That was Walter Britt.
Heck fire.
Yeah.
Heck, I'll say it again.
Heck.
I'll express my frustration.
AG double hockey sticks.
Yeah, I'm getting hard.
I'm hardly getting.
Yeah, I'm hardly getting too.
Well.
Um.
Uh.
Yeah.
Yeah, I hear.
Somebody says that.
Kill the messenger.
Well, wait for somebody else to say it, okay?
It's not funny.
Come on again.
Laugh, Brian.
He's got a Jonestown shirt.
I've got a, what's his name's shirt?
Harold Camping.
Praise Harold Camping.
Yeah, well, did everybody have fun camping?
Does his style of camping work better?
Yeah, anybody jonesing?
Uh.
Jonesing for Jones.
Sure you got your heaven's gate zipped up?
Hey.
At least they're not still here.
What, the Jonestown people?
Yeah, I'll see them around here.
Wait, what's that sound?
Same difference.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
I do.
You're a low rumble.
It turns out to be a very low rent.
Low rent.
Come and get us in a truck.
Yeah, a honey dipper truck most likely.
All this time the extras were disguised as the honey dippers.
Honey dipper man.
Yeah.
It comes down to the chem toilets.
Turns out the honey dipper man was the extras.
Right.
Like, like to the subject truck.
There's a lot of.
We weren't, we were a little large to be sucked up through the hose.
Yeah, there's a lot of.
Story in my life.
Exes who are supposed to be hiding inside the freaking toilet.
Oh my God.
That's it.
That robot.
You first.
Only the shit is getting fucking ruptured right now.
All that Yeti shit.
God.
Oh my God.
The shit is getting ruptured.
Well, um.
Some shit is getting vexed.
The discordians are gonna laugh at us again.
The flying spaghetti monster assholes are gonna laugh at us again.
Discordians can go eat their hot dogs.
You know what this means, Princess?
We have to go through Starwood.
Damn.
Well.
I can't believe it.
He fooled them again.
After all these years.
I'm going back.
They still came out.
There's another thing.
Still got up.
Still looked at the sky.
Sometime.
We're on a real roll over here.
How long will it go on before they all sleep in?
How many more years will it take for everyone to sleep in?
How many more times do I have to play this sanguine game?
song over and over again.
Well I think people were encouraged by the possibilities of next year.
This morning.
Oh yeah, yeah, encouraged.
One more X Day.
One more X Day bites the dust.
One more X Day in the camp.
I hate that phrase, next X Day.
I hate that phrase.
Yeah, it's such a bummer.
Such a bummer.
So little slack.
I have so many Dobbs heads to take down.
So many Dobbs heads.
It was a pleasure meeting you both.
Sorry the saucers didn't get here this time, Matt.
Thank you so much.
I have faith.
Very little.
Well.
I think the message of course is that X Day could happen any second.
We don't know.
So we better be ready all the time.
Yeah, that must be it.
It's kind of like other things that could happen at any time.
Right.
Could happen.
That would be great if it happened right now.
Wouldn't that be, you know, they'd only be off by 20 minutes.
Ugh.
All right.
I have enough frop to drown my sorrow.
Is there that much frop in all the world?
If it's up the ass, yeah.
Quick River, it's staying.
They're all gone.
Let's board the saucer now.
Yeah.
They're all over that way.
What a day.
Oh, what a day.
I should mention that the main voices you hear in most of that recording are Dr. Philo Drummond,
Dr. Hal Robbins,
Dr. Dark,
and it's all doctors,
oh, and Reverend Susie the Flusie,
and Princess Wee Ardo,
and about 40 other subgeniuses,
the few dedicated enough to pry themselves out of slumber before 7 a.m.
Now there were many notable and famous subgeniuses there.
Yes, we had a good turnout,
despite the incessant rain, howling cyclones, and typhoon.
Dr. Philo Drummond, the overman, was there.
For real.
And his lovely wife, Chaosmic Mama Cat,
and Vuvuzela-blowing progeny, the incredible Lily.
Evolution Control Committee was at the judgment.
And they did an entire piece about pants.
That was amazing.
Yes, it was.
Apparently Trademark has been gathering samples from songs that mention,
and movie lines,
that mention pants for years.
I forget what the project was originally meant to be.
And they all fit together.
But for us, he pieced them all together
and played them out on his weird little sampler guitar warping device
for about 25 minutes of pants.
I'm surprised, sir.
It made me dance to listen to those songs about the pants.
Exactly. Now you're getting back into it.
Oh, I'm back, yeah.
Doctors for Wotan were there.
The original subgenius anti-music band,
which in the day was composed of Dr. Drummond, myself,
and Hellswammy Satellite Weavers,
and whoever else would join us,
but not our wives back then.
This time, it was Philo and me and our new wives,
who will Wotan.
And that was a lot of fun.
It was just like the old days.
The process of elimination.
Some people, for some reason,
thought that our concert was a joke.
It was funny.
I kept hearing that phrase over and over again.
I thought we were doing a rockin' show myself,
but I kept being told,
well, it was really funny, you guys.
Funny, peculiar, or funny, ha-ha?
Funny, ha-ha, I think, is what they meant.
We meant to be funny, peculiar,
but no, no, it was all, ha-ha-ha.
I guess they're joking.
We get that a lot here in the Church of the Subgenius.
They're joking, of course.
They're not occult kooks.
Joking.
I know these people.
Reverend Susie the Floozy was there.
Now, that's a real hot subgenius celebrity.
And, of course, the new subgenius celebrities,
like Baby Bear and Priestess Pisces and so forth.
We had Eggplant.
Reverend Angry Larry was there.
The great amino acids were in disguise
as the giant germs.
I believe you mean Lord Reverend Angry Larry.
Oh, that's right, that's right.
He changed.
He had a vertical promotion.
Yeah, Lord of Giant Germs was his new band name,
so now he's Lord Angry Larry.
Lisa Cheeks Marie was there.
And what about the festal couple that you joined forever?
Reverend Fox spelled foe, but pronounced fox.
Yes.
And the beautiful Aster.
Reverend Aster.
Meaning star.
And we know she's extra beautiful
on account of she got in the baptism pond with her shirt off.
Yes, and they were both simultaneously baptized by Reverend Stang.
The longest who was, the longest time.
Who stayed under the longest?
Well, the longest baptism itself was, again, Susie the Floozies,
which took an extended amount of time.
Well, that's because she likes me to heff the time.
I don't know if you're a hefft her.
But before I dunk her, so I naturally prolong the period of legitimate hefting as long as possible.
I pretend to forget that they're praising Bob.
It's part of the...
Forget his name.
...gland escaping that we have often promised.
Hello.
Welcome to the Bob Gizm.
You're on the radio.
Greetings and celebrations.
Oh!
That's it.
This is a good place to practice your mad science.
Now, are you sure at this point, feel down there, you're happy, you're together?
Reverend Angie, do you accept Bob?
This is her first baptism, so she's like a virgin to this.
This is an important one.
Do you accept Bob into your heart and mind and any other mutually agreeable whatever?
Orifice.
And reject the conspiracy in whatever form it may take in your life except this event.
Say yes.
Yes, I do.
Praise Bob!
How we doing?
That was a semi-long.
See, it's like being born again.
Something tweaked her when she went down.
He saw her face.
Give her her mask back in your niche.
There is a butt-biting fish in here.
We may not have mentioned the butt-biting fish.
You didn't see my post about that?
I see so many pictures of butt-biting fish.
I can't know one from the other.
Christ Tristan, do you accept Bob into your mind and heart and reject the conspiracy and so forth?
Hell yeah!
That's the way to do it.
Another soldier in Bob's army.
Alright, we need another apostolate.
Carol Christmas, she's another new one.
I am.
Alright, Carol Christmas, do you accept Bob into your heart and mind and reject, who are we rejecting?
Conspiracy.
Conspiracy, that's right.
Reject the conspiracy.
It works.
Hell yeah!
Praise Bob!
Woo!
Refreshing.
Oh man.
I really look like a yeti all over.
Well, that's one magical thing this pond has.
Yeah, it yetifies the hairless.
Even Baby Bear came out with a coat on her when this happened.
So, who is next?
We need more.
More.
Come on now.
Do you accept the conspiracy and reject Bob?
Fuck no!
Alright!
Okay!
That's a good one.
I was wondering what the correct answer was.
That's it.
I like it.
Okay.
You were standing there.
Dot, come forward.
Yes.
Do you, Reverend, new Reverend Dot, accept Bob into your life?
Professor Random Dot.
Just Random Dot.
Oh, Random Dot.
There you go.
Alright, do you accept the dots of J.R. Bob Dobbs, even though they are not entirely random?
Yes.
And reject the evil dots of the conspiracy?
Especially the red.
I do!
Praise Reverend Dot.
Alright.
That's the idea.
Generic subgenius clergyman, I know by definition you must accept Bob into your heart and reject
the conspiracy.
Is that correct?
Yes, I do.
Especially the NSA and all it stands for.
Fuck yes!
Oh, God!
Praise Bob.
Yeah!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Praise subgenius clergyman.
The Reverend Sparkling Oddity.
I think I'd be able to remember the oddity part.
Yeah.
But you sparkle and that just, you know.
Okay, sparkles.
Do you accept Bob into your life and reject the conspiracy?
Say I do.
I do!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Believe us.
Woo!
Praise Bob.
We should do Fox and Asper at the same time.
Yeah.
Want to do you guys as one?
Because they're getting ditched in about two hours.
Two hours.
Can you explain the facts of life to me?
Fucking wedding.
Separate parties.
I'm kind of figuring it out as we go.
I don't know what the hell these are.
Something's growing up.
I'll have to, I'll explain it to you by demonstration later.
All right.
Oh, what a romantic couple.
Fucking cool!
Look, they're covered with electro-stimulo-risk.
Psychological impact.
Do you both in unison accept Bob into your heart and reject the conspiracy and all jobs
that do not pay quite enough?
I'm not sure if I'm the only one who's going to have to try that.
Does it hurt?
Yes.
Then yes!
Yes!
Hold up.
There they go.
That is it.
Oh, it's so romantic.
See you, see you.
Isn't it romantic?
I see you standing in the corner over there hiding.
Oh, it's so cold.
It is cold.
That's cold.
Haven't you been in here before already?
Yes, I've been in here before.
Well, then it shouldn't seem so cold.
Oh, look, her nipples are shriveled up down to the size of Susan B. Anthony Dollar.
That's cold.
Well, that is sad, but we'll fix you up.
More like Eisenhower's.
Reverend Susie the floozy.
Now, wait a minute.
We have a tradition where we do this because I have to like do the laying on of hands.
Face to face.
This is why you're the chief, chief.
The hefting.
By Stephen King, America's most popular writer.
Susie the floozy, do you accept, what was it now?
What was it?
What's his name?
Fred?
Do you accept Fred?
It'll come to you.
Robert.
Bob.
You accept Fred?
You accept Bob into your, what was it?
There's some body part I can't quite get a grip on.
Heart?
Mind?
Yeah, your heart.
Your chest.
You accept Bob into your chest.
Yeah, both boosters.
That's easy for me to say.
And reject the conspiracy.
Whatever that is.
Yeah.
It's hard to define, but yeah.
All of that shit.
Okay.
Are you sure you totally understand?
Yeah.
Let me ask you one more time.
Are you in your right mind and you understand the question?
Oh, hold on.
Oh, I guess this is long enough.
Praise Bob.
Down you go.
She won't go down.
She's stuffed.
She's awesome.
Oh, my foot.
Praise Bob.
All right.
We have a caller here.
She has some great plans.
There is a caller.
All right.
Well, let's get that caller on right now.
Yeah.
Hello, you're on the air.
I'm on the air.
I'm in the air, too.
It's Princess We Are Doe, the queen of all the UFOs.
Yes.
Particles flying at the speed of light.
I'm calling you from the heart of darkness here in Southern Ohio.
Had a power outage?
No, it's just dark.
They call that place Ohio's Outback, that area, Meigs County, home of Meigs County Green.
Hmm.
The Outback.
The Outback, eh?
Ohio's Outback.
You've got Ohio Dundee out there.
Others call it Ohio's Outhouse.
The little house on the prairie or the necessary house.
Well, we call it the big house, the one we stay in.
That's the greatest bed and breakfast on the planet with the greatest hostess.
Yes.
Absolutely.
And they will be happy to provide pots and pans.
You just have to ask.
Oh, hi.
Princess Wee, is everything okay out there still?
Are the Starwoodians flocking in even though they weren't destroyed by the saucers?
Have the last subgeniuses limped painfully away?
Oh, no.
Lots of subgeniuses are staying the night.
I'm about to go down and see what I can see down there.
But it's apparently quite a good night.
Are they jamming?
No, I've got a phone call coming in from Kenny McGloskey.
I'm going to have to go.
Oh, well.
I'll be sure.
Call back later.
Take that call now.
Okay.
All right.
That was one of the mysterious Wisterians was calling and you can't just let that go
to the message.
Apparently not.
Well, not when you're running Starwood.
Wee.
I mean, me.
Well, at any rate, when you're running Starwood, you have to be on the ball.
You've got to run fast.
Yes.
And when the Wisterians call, you better pick it up because it may be your child who's being
dragged out of the road drunk.
Or left in the road drunk.
You know, I've retired from dragging them out of the road.
Well, if they're too big, I don't know how you can do it.
I'm not going to go to the trouble of dragging them into the road, but I used to drag them
out of the road and now I don't.
I've quit babying the subgeniuses.
These crazy kids today out there dragging in the road.
And now we have another call here.
Drag artists.
Okay.
Well, here's another caller.
So let's go to that call now.
And you're on the air.
I guess I blew it.
Man, you had such a perfect chance.
You had a moment and you got tongue tied.
Untie your tongue, dude.
It's just the pressure of the radio.
That's Dr. Drummond.
Yes.
That's phylo Dr. Drummond.
Folks, you're hearing the Overman now.
And you heard him screw up.
Well, he's.
Oh, I'm sorry.
It's just a courtesy to the human to be like them and fallible and make mistakes and fall
in the mud, disgraced forever.
So the ignominy.
But I guess you're practicing your cartooning chops while all this is going on.
Getting your lessons from KRK Rydon and other art professionals.
Yeah, you as well.
I've got the highest, the top artist of their day.
That's right.
I sent him through Dr. Howland Owl's famous school of adult cartooning.
Yeah.
Not to mention your special force that you throw in there on sex and success.
Success in sex and real estate.
Yes, it's true.
It's possible to move mountains with just a little elbow grease.
And I believe we is calling back now.
Welcome back.
Is Dr. Drummond in the house yet?
Yes.
He is.
He's right over there, officer.
This is kind of the way the hour of slack will sound when Philo moves to Kentucky.
And he'll be a phone voice on both of our shows, Dr. Howland.
Yes, don't laugh.
That's really happening.
Yeah.
It is true.
Philo's coming out to live in this bar.
Philo's coming, hide your heart, girls.
Yeah.
He's going to be house hunting maybe in your neighborhood.
For a big old place.
Have you guys given the X Day report already?
Big old barn and big old ... What?
Well, we've given some of the X Day report.
Of course, there's a lot of stuff we can't talk about because it was a little too special.
Yeah, some things were on the hush hush.
You know what I mean?
You don't want all of the hoi polloi rushing the gates at Wisteria wanting to get some
of that.
No, certainly not.
It's nice to have some things to yourself.
Yeah.
Well, I wish I'd gotten a copy of that cool Doctors's for Wozniak.
It's a good thing.
Because I'm not going to be a part of a Wu-Tang reunion gig.
Oh, Dr. Drummond, you'll be glad to know that I have heard the copy of the ... I can
give you a bootleg of that, and it's not bad.
There's a couple of places where that unearthly machine of yours was louder than my voice,
which of course is not suitable.
But most of it, my voice is at least as loud as your voice or your infernal machine.
So, I was pretty happy with it.
Oh, I wasn't sure if they could hear the machine even.
Oh, they could ... The machine was loud.
mic'd big time.
And Mike kept the volume
up pretty high on that thing.
It's kind of hard to hear Mrs. Drummond.
But...
She was more silent.
But you can hear the duet that
Princess Wee and I did
as we did it.
We liked to do that.
Of course, Mrs. Drummond
mostly is known for her
visual.
Mrs. Drummond is the greatest
dancer in the world.
Also the weirdest
The whole time
Trademark G's
Evolution Control Committee was playing
I couldn't look at him or his videos.
I had to keep looking at your
wife there, Dr. Drummond.
Was that a rabbit suit she was
wearing? What kind of a suit was that?
It was a green alien Avi suit.
It's an alien Avi suit.
Avi!
It's an Avi suit.
Yeah. I was Avi
and out.
But I didn't want to Avi out on stage
with her because she's so much
better than anybody else.
I Avi'd from the pit.
Yeah, that's kind of what I did.
From your seat?
Yeah, I was Avi.
I was riveted to my seat.
And boy, did that hurt.
Four stars and
a gripping night at the cinema.
Hey, let go.
Stick around, children.
I have a little tale to tell.
A little tale.
A cat of nine tails.
A chaotic bobcat of nine tails
to whip your ass into shreds.
Thank you.
I am here today
from the planet X
to invite you
to take part
if you wish
in an ancient
dark form
called
Avi.
Avi has a base
in Japan from the know.
I'm a
voodoo.
Because the arm form
of Avi,
if anyone would like to
come up here and join
me when you are so inspired.
Avi,
you go deep inside
with your sounds
and your body and your mind.
And it's the people
who are experiencing
your Avi
like your...
And they are Forever
rosser.
You don't need
Me!
You will never
Who Gracias
Never
Are you absolutely
No
Wen
D
From PR News in Washington, I'm the polygamous sex leader swept away yesterday afternoon in
New York at the end of the month. The Food and Drug Administration is at or near the end of its
useful life, which could cause problems. Cuban President Raul Castro is taking the unprecedented
step of ordering top-selling products from the market. Cuban President Raul Castro operated the
crane that crashed last week and killed at least 107 people in New York. Castro is banned from
future projects in the city. The investigation found in PR News blew the crane down. That's
according to a new report by major top-selling PR. Cuban President Raul Castro is
confirmed dead from flash floods along the Utah-Arizona border. The governor of Texas is
joining educators and students in paying tribute to the victims of a school in the state's largest
public school district in Washington state. The governors of New York and New Jersey are asking
the federal government to pay for half the cost of a new PR News under the Hudson River.
Phone number, paper, scrap, cheese, and old buttons,
scraped, pitiless orange peel, think they have won the war by a show of sheer numbers. I am no
suburbanite in hipster camouflage, not as lost in the details as in the inanimate think I look.
The carnelian in my belly glows out beyond the fuzzy edges, my skin. I remember lost
chips among the ticket stubs and dishes, regain them in bursts of confident orange.
Thank you for the cheese and buttons to Reverend Andrew Genis. PR News and our title sequence came
from Mr. Fernandin Andy Lemur, whose works, by the way, are on archive.com in all their splendor.
We heard the melodious Reverend Chaos McBobcat at 18X Day demonstrating the new art consciousness
form called A-V. I played Monster Hunter online with her daughter.
Thanks to WCSB and Dr. Sinister for lending us his show again for use on Hour of Slut number 1546
from the Church of the Subgenius, about which there is everything on subgenius.com,
including the last thousand some odd episodes of this insane show. That's subgenius.com. Praise Bob.
Oh, did we mention that Bob died? Our guru, Bob,
well, he's dead again. It was his own experiments that did him in this time.
He experimented on himself. Here lies the result. We mustn't think of him too harshly.
The things he did, and they were terrible.
All of us are capable of doing when we give free play to the basins, which is a part of everyone.
He tampered with things beyond his province.
Beyond what any man should do.
And if it was madness,
well,
those whom the gods would destroy, they,
they first make mad.
Better this way.