This is a work of fiction. Any resemblance to actual persons, living or dead, is coincidental.
Seems like money.
Legendary nuts and money.
Profit big money.
Call 13013 now and get free.
Cash now with no cash free.
Call now. Call 13013 immediately.
Get rich rich rich free money.
Call right now.
Call 13013.
You wouldn't listen?
Police Headquarters.
Officer.
Arrest this man.
And be careful.
Be careful. He's got a subgenius.
Power of smart.
This man. This man. This man.
Police Headquarters. Officer.
How does Slate contributor Daniel kill you?
Daniel can kill you by
inducing people into your life.
He's a man in California to damage the brain,
the kidneys, and other organs.
Contributor Daniel can kill you in other ways too.
For example,
email problems.
Many factors increase your risk of succumbing to the elderly
because their circulatory systems go somewhere cooler
or get a glass of sweaty tissue
to cool their very slow, small, obese brains.
And mentally ill obese people
can't lie on top of their fatty tissue.
And mentally ill elderly children
take drugs and die from an overdose
on a hot sweaty internal organ.
If you have a question about hot stuff pumping,
you're in serious danger.
Mama.
I want some milk.
Yes, dear friends,
we're in the studio tonight.
Lonesome Cowboy Dave
and yours very truly,
Reverend Ivan Stang.
That's a false dear.
You are here in the most false fashion imaginable.
You hardly exist.
You are a misfit.
big illusions.
Your shirt is like a hallucination.
Your head is a mirage.
At least you didn't stay stuck on my pants.
I'm really tired of that.
I've been stuck on your pants plenty of times
and you know it.
I've tried to forget it, friends.
It's an horrible thing to think of.
We're going back to X-Day
in the background of the show, here.
The music in the background is
In this case I think it's
Well, he's a roadie for the amino acids jamming.
We'll also be hearing some jamming.
He's an angry man, isn't he, Angry Larry?
Only on stage.
You know, a lot of people have said, Reverend Angry Larry, you just don't seem all that angry to tell the truth.
And he goes, I work it out on stage.
Well, also, the scowl is a little bit from all the weird amputated teeth and gum parts after that most recent experiment.
Well, they're one of those bands.
It gives the illusion of a scowl, you know.
They're an action band, the amino acids.
They like to tear things up, like their faces, their hands, and so forth.
Highly sexed and strangely appurtenanced.
Some people interpret that as low self-esteem, but I think what it really is is low audience esteem.
Yep, that's it.
A disdain for those who might look upon them with favor.
Speaking of terrible bands, also the Mondo Di Tardo.
The Tardos show up at some point.
The Tardos Mondo Band is on there?
Yeah, the Tardos Mondo Band.
Well, the jamming Tardos Mondo Band.
Oh, yes.
Listen.
See how disorganized they are?
Oh, that's them.
Pick a key for us to play in.
Yeah.
All right, thank you very much.
Good night.
M.
Okay, you know what?
This is M.
Fresh out of M, man.
M.
The key of M.
Three keys.
E, F, G.
A, B.
C.
E, F, G.
They wouldn't do Q.
All right, we can do something in E, F, G, I suppose.
The audience gets to compose the jam.
Francis Scott key.
Okay.
Yeah.
I said post-mellitus key.
We don't do any door keys, garage keys.
Door key is right.
Yes.
They got lots of door keys.
It's taking a long time to get to the key.
It's the key of Q.
Yeah.
That's it.
9X Day, friends.
When you go to a subgenius concert, it's like the visible show.
It's clockwork stuff.
You know, I mean, it's very, very highly professional, wouldn't you say?
Well.
I mean, it is art.
You know, a lot of people don't understand what's really so funny about this, you know.
Well, this is just sort of a boogie, isn't it?
I don't know.
I just did what I was told at that part because I'd lost control of my bowels and bladder,
so I was just...
They were just leading me around with my embedded tattoo thing that can read all the signals
and write them back out.
So you've kept up with the kids and gotten one of those inbred tattoos because I, you
know, I'm afraid to do that.
I'm afraid of the tattoo needle.
It's not that I look down on trendy things that date you to a certain year or tie you
to a certain...
They'll date you soon, and you know how?
Is that what you do to get a date?
You get a tattoo and then you get dates?
That's how you remove a fig from your eyes, senor.
This is going to be bad news in the future when people discover you with subgenius tattoos.
Can you imagine the concentration camp or the lack of focus farm you'll be heading for?
I've actually been imagining the lampshades that I could collect.
Well, they're fun to wear on your head, but not on someone else's.
Oh.
I've made that point also, you know, but...
My attitude towards tattoos is someday somebody's going to go, wow, you must have been really
cool in the 90s.
No, they're going to look in your brain with those tattoos, and they'll know that you're
a member of a criminal religion.
The Church of the Subgenius will be declared criminal in probably 2037 or one of those.
Oh, speaking of 2037, we have a tape, friends, from the year of 2136, courtesy of Mr. Sister,
the famous subgenius.
Also, Mr. Sister.
I thought it was IDMRSR.
Mr. Sister.
ID Mr. Sister.
I doctor Mr. Sister.
I thought it was Idiocratic Demon.
You know him.
He fixed your computer one time.
Yeah, he fixed it.
Good.
No, yeah, he did.
He did fix it well.
He made sweet, sweet love to your computer.
He did make sweet, sweet love to my computer.
And my computer remembers that, too, in a very, yeah.
Anyway, Mr. Sister, in the process of doing some time control experiments, which normally
we don't expect.
We don't expect this to work.
What should he, what to his reddening eyes should appear but this weird kind of tape
that he was able to run through his computer and extract the noise from it.
Now, I'm going to try to play this.
It purports to be an X-mas letter from the year of 2136.
Isn't there a crosstalk?
There's a crosstalk of between the years between, I think you said earlier, there might
be a little bit of crosstalk from like, you know, 2072.
No, this thing's pretty, no, he got rid of that.
That was earlier.
This is a clean one?
This is the cleaned up one, yeah.
So we have to be quiet.
We have to be quiet because it's, there's some details in here.
You've got, it's pretty, I'm not looking forward to new Iraq in the year 2136.
Anyway, we'll see what happens.
Happy holidays from the Johnson family.
Hope you had as good a 2136 as we did.
Our X-mas will be really joyful because you remember our three-year-old son, Johnny,
who drowned in the toilet in April?
Well, his clone will be hatched and matured right around December 25th.
So we'll be celebrating as a complete family once again.
My dear husband, Bob, is just getting over a bad winter cancer.
I don't know what it is, maybe the weather around here, but this is the third time he's
sprouted a disease.
He's got a massive tumor in his liver this year.
We went down to Walgreens and bought another bottle of Nye Cure, the nighttime cancer cure.
They have a new fresh citrus flavor, which tastes really good.
Maybe one day they'll improve on it because he's having a really uncomfortable week until
it kicks in.
Seems in this modern time, they should have something that gets rid of the cancer in under
a week.
This year, I splurged on myself and got one of those little sports hearts.
I so enjoy the smooth purr.
As it revs up to 200 beats per minute.
When my original heart failed at first, I got one of the standard replacements, but for
just a little more.
Adidas was having a special sale.
So I said, you only live 150 years.
Why not enjoy life in the fast lane?
We all had a two week vacation in August, which was really great.
We took the Jamaica pills this time.
Me and Bob and our daughter Arlene.
Arlene was so sad that Johnny wasn't developed enough to come along this year.
year. Arlene is studying hard because she wants to become an abortionist and open up a little shop
on Main Street one day. That's becoming quite a big business now that we've got Gates AIDS Off
added to our drinking water. I remember from history, some of the pioneers around here 200
years ago first started adding fluorides to prevent tooth decay. So this was a really good
idea along the same lines. Arlene didn't want to take the other program in junior high, covert
explosive detection. Too much emphasis on science and mathematics and all that dull stuff for her.
The weather here in Iraq outside the containment dome is pretty hot and dusty. When they have the
visual shields down for maintenance, we can watch the outsiders set themselves off. Once in a while,
one of them will sneak in and blow something up inside here. Our
neighbors are trying to get the outside of the containment dome to close down. They're
making a mess. The neighbors' clones will be ready soon, and the house next door is just about
rebuilt. But we had to endure another two weeks in disorder until all the stuff got fixed.
Right after Xmas, I hate to bring it up, but as you know, that's tax season. We have great news.
We've been assigned 16 more grandchildren. We were given an estimate of their future income,
which looks pretty handsome. We just have to commit that to Uncle Wally like all good citizens.
The good news is that we're going to be able to make a lot of money. We're going to be able to
keep a few percent of their income after they reach 37 years old. I'm sure glad President Walton
defeated that other guy, Bechtel, and we're finally to the point where we only have to
commit two generations' future income to taxes. But enough said. Never discuss religion and
politics with friends. Well, I could go on, but Grandma Johnson's fuel cells need refilling,
and I have to rush off to the Harvest Center for egg extraction.
And pretty soon, the prayer bells will be going off at the Wall Temple. Don't want to be late for
mid-afternoon prayer time. It's been a great year around the Johnson household. Merry Xmas and happy
2137. Bob, Melissa, Arlene, and Johnny Johnson, number two, your good friends from New Rumsfeld,
Iraq.
President's on the phone, talking to his mom and dad, saying, should I turn over evidence, or be a good old stone woman?
President's on TV, having a White House tea. He's talking liberty, but you and I agree.
This is a democratic country where they don't count guns.
And this is the crime. An offshore boat. And this is the point. That's no surprise.
The president of us, but you're the soldiers, mother .
There's a lot of treatment.
So you too, your repo, backed up as aqueer .
We dwell on these days.
And so, in doing so, peace .
You look like Jesus with his
Thank you.
The president's in your head.
then allowing the sofa to fall off with him on it,
and then him to slowly, to the point of wrinking himself to death,
extrude the vodka from the bottle and then set the couch on fire as,
what was the name of the art brigade?
That was the Austin Art Brigade, right?
Well, they took it to Burning Man.
That was Bob's idea.
Bob taught him all that stuff.
They were a bad influence on each other, Bob and Vat.
Well, anything under Bob is sub-genius, you know?
I mean, there's not much more you can say about genius.
No, actually, anything under Bob would probably die
because its nervous system wouldn't function at all.
It would forget to breathe.
Sub-genius, you know, doesn't have anything to do with intelligence.
Wow.
That should be fairly obvious.
Of the medulla.
But with sense, common sense, sense of humor, dollars and cents,
as we've said 18 million times before.
Well, maybe not.
That's the cerebral stationary plane, right?
Yeah.
Okay.
So, there are correspondences everywhere, my friends.
As above, so sideways.
And that is why the chemtrails above correspond to the crop circles below
and to the superhighways of the supersonic Nazi hell creatures
deep, deep, deep, deep, deep below beneath the hollow earth
discovered by Richard Shaver.
Who's Richard Shaver? I'm sorry.
He was a guy who discovered, that's the real name of the fellow,
who discovered the hollow earth.
Oh, the guy, Little Shaver, they called him?
No.
He's the uncle of DJ Shaver,
who will be featured on probably next week's Hour of Slack.
He's a popular sub-genius.
Actually, he's not so much a DJ as an actual performer.
Like one of the many...
He sings louder than the people are singing on the records he plays.
Oh, but how did, so that's his job?
That's his profession? Is he a loud singer?
No, he only gets to do that at X-Day.
The rest of the time, he has to play corny music at weddings.
Oh, he's a wedding DJ.
That's what DJ usually means, I think.
And he discovered these correspondences.
Why, in such a strange, out-of-focus place, would you discover anything?
Well, I forget where Richard Shaver was, I guess.
You know, well, you go down deep enough,
either in a cave or in your own mind,
and you will meet the supersonic Nazi.
Nazi hell creatures.
Either from the hollow earth or the hollow head, baby.
No, you know what I'm talking about, listener.
Little miss, I know you're listening to me, honey.
She's been suffering a long time, too.
They've got the grooves going on the top of her forehead now.
You know, about the time when her skull flap is removed
and they take the actual implant out,
the Church of the Subgenius will be outlawed.
Those little numbers, those little transporter numbers
that are inscribed into your skull,
the flap and stuff, they'll be able to read those.
But that won't stop us.
And say, you're going to jail for thinking of Bob.
But you see, when the implant comes out,
the Church of the Subgenius fills in the blank hole.
Sure, you may be in prison.
You may be in Camp X-Ray.
Or you may be on that drug called Camp X-Ray,
thinking you're in Camp X-Ray.
It's cheaper for them to just give you the pill.
Friends, you don't know.
You think you know.
But I know one thing.
You don't know.
I'm not going to tell you what it is,
but I know that.
And he said, that Bob said,
to tell you, it's going to be a bummer, man.
I don't want my skull flap removed.
I don't think it's necessary.
Oh, they all say that.
Sure, you know, initially.
But before the hour's out,
they've all signed the contract.
Every last one of them.
That's right.
No, no, no.
You have to put your name in there.
Sure, there's always some joker going,
don't do it, man.
Bob's just part of the conspiracy.
You're being sucked in.
It's a cult.
It's worse than a cult.
It's an anti-cult cult as a front.
But it's really a cult cult disguised as an anti-cult cult.
Would you care for some coffee now?
Just to relax in the lounge until your turn comes by.
You've been trapped.
Trapped in a con-infectionary your whole life.
Just soaking up the con-infections.
But yet you think it's so sweet and sugary.
Those sugary lies dripping down the inside of your ears,
down into your skull pan.
Oh, yeah.
And you feel the tickling triacral.
You think, oh, that's just so, so,
it's like candy inside my brain.
Sure.
You'll suck on that conspiracy teat forever.
Ever.
And they call me a kook.
They call me a kook.
It's a cold teat.
My God.
No wonder you look the way you look and smile the way you smile.
You've been shoving a convex teat in your eye.
You should be shoving the church of the subgenius.
I thought those were my glasses.
The church of the subgenius in your eyes.
I'm the man who thought his false teeth was his glasses.
Praise Bob.
I thought they were my.
Transmitter and my personal salvation.
Salvation.
Well, I'm starting to dry out and I'm losing my salivation.
So let's.
I'm getting sleepy.
Play some.
Let's go back.
If friends.
Time control.
Indeed.
To.
Well, actually, we're not going back that far.
Just last week's binary slack, I think.
And the very first minute here is by Norell Preff of Norell Preff dot com.
But then.
That.
Name reminds me of an excreted.
We go to Lee Murray.
Now, what?
Hmm.
Preff is a word for an excreted inflation in foreign countries.
It is.
Well, I'll be like a booboo.
Strangely evolved.
Maybe distant planet.
Foreign countries.
But a press like.
Like, honey, would you put some of that alcohol on my Preff?
Well, there's a pair of two and prats and proof.
And there's piff and pan.
There's Preff.
Really?
It's.
Yeah.
Well, that's some Italian thing that, you know, I think it might be Norwegian or oblate.
Perhaps one of the simian clashes that we can't communicate with yet.
But I know it's real.
I know it's real.
Yeah.
I feel it's real.
Okay.
Here goes.
It's seriously impressive.
Wow.
Fabulous.
Well, now you can tell when you have to trust one of the answers.
There's a movie.
Well, this alecich tarafos get lost, we love the.
young ladies SaveBye you want to call for moins,.
Two pointவ
moomooowowooow canopy I never live home never off,
Three pointhelov.
I wonder what it's like to walk around in a total blackout.
I never left home.
Bob, you've always wanted to go on a mission.
Why don't you go on this one?
Do you want to send Bob to fight the Germans?
No kidding, Bob.
If you know anything about radio, I'd be glad to let you take my place.
Pretty rugged, Bob.
We're doing all right.
Now here's a special program note.
It's Farts for Doe Show.
Yep, set your sights for A1 Entertainment with Farts for Doe coming up next on this...
So genius.
Power of Farts.
Farts for Doe.
It is now 28 minutes before the assassination of Dr. Martin Luther King.
Time to respond to your letters.
UFOs, kidnappings, and psychologists...
Her name was Laura.
What's her name? Maybe I know her.
Ask and he shall beep.
These words end with a leg.
Ready, go, go.
Uh...
Gee, go.
He slapped me and made me take the rattle back.
Her husband's sex has become more bizarre.
Once he started selling those sex toys.
You know, for Lauren...
Anytime it was really great.
Nice.
Um...
Did your husband's become more bizarre?
Yeah.
He would wear the top half of Julia.
He called it erotic art.
Yeah, he sure did.
Come on.
What happened then?
Strip poker.
Barge swing.
He's a sex runner.
Maniac.
Get it now with no credit hassles.
You and Alex finished each other off in the bedroom.
The no long-term obligation.
Weep.
Sunday.
That's right.
From PR News in Washington, I'm missing and killed a fifth earlier this month.
Ten inches of Iraqi civilians dropped on Houston today.
A group linked to Al-Qaeda in Iraq says it is kidding.
Secretary of State Condoleezza Rice says the same group says the U.S. military says the White House says PR News isn't over yet.
On Wall Street, 345678.
The Supreme Court has refused to say this is PR.
The justices say...
Pay plans.
Pension.
Pilots.
Public pension plans.
PR Sports.
Pensions.
Pay.
Pilots.
Profitable.
Pension.
Pensions.
Push.
Pilots.
Pension.
Plan.
Pilots.
Pension.
Plans.
PRs.
For the first time in more than 20 years, whales have won a vote calling for resumption of PR News in Washington.
Ladies, I'd like to tell you about golden kitchen fats.
Ladies, listen.
Be sure you do your kissing with a smooth, smooth kisser.
Shake.
Shave with used kitchen fat.
Spread this rich, fluffy fat over your skin.
Then get going with your razor.
No drying out or quitting halfway with used fat.
No aftertaste.
No unpleasant aftertaste.
That's right.
Right now.
Yes, right now.
Do it.
Used.
Today.
Get it tomorrow.
1, 2, 1, 2, 3, 4.
.
Get a jar of nourishing paste from your grocer and enjoy tasty paste right in your own kitchen
The vicious dog King ran ahead of the sled cutting tracks in the snow
Huskies hey there sergeant. Oh, oh you have and justice ruled triumphant
Let's go
Buddy you're a baker in this big. God you singing buddy. You're a young man in the show
Oh god, please buddy. You're an old man with you
I've got some please
We're calling him
Beat me to a pulpit. I'm praying
for some pain
I ain't got religion. I got a damaged brain
If I had a dollar for every licking that I took
I'd buy the pulpit that he gave
And buy the dirty pulpit
Beat me to a pulpit
I'm praying for some pain
Eh eh eh
Heh
What is it?
What what?
What what what what?
I think it's a jam
Yeah I think it's a jam and there's a Dave and a Princess Wee and a Reverend Angry Larry and a Reverend Phil
I think Reverend Phil was on drums by that point
This is a groovy jam man
All that stuff we just heard was uh
Well we heard the beat me to a pulpit by the loaming
What was that bull girl
Popular bull girl Dave Fowler
Loathsome cow pie Dave Fowler
The popular loathsome popular bull girl?
Yeah uh popular bull girl Dave Fowler and uh the Stardos or something like that
I love her name
I love her hairy armpits too
She's been braided by a tired champi-
No chim-
Her armpits were braided by a tired chimpanzee
I thought at least I would say it
Those chimpanzees go through hell for us
Think think of it
Think of all simians do for us and we can't re-reverse to our yeti nature
No matter how hard we try how long we try and meditate or whatever we try to do
We can engineer our social consciousness
We can refabric our genetic engineering badges
We can do practically everything but we can't get back to the original source
From which we flood from which we come
It's criminal the way humans treat us
It's more than criminal it's
It's very sad at least in my own personal case
Being experimented on so much
I was gonna ask you did they uh did they strap you into the centrifuge and like see how you'd undergo jeef stresses and everything?
No these these lacerations covering my body are from bowling night
No of course they did and of course it was awful
Look at the rest of the stuff they've done
Look at my hands it looks like a claw now
Yeah yeah
It looks like a bird like you know sci-fi looking bird claw thing man
That was where I yeah they uh my ankles are all messed up where they put the the uh needles to test to keep track of my blood pressure and everything
Yeah right
And then they and they had the the spot did you get the shocks in your feet?
The weird bag?
No the shocks like whenever you push the wrong switches you get the shocks
Oh of course I thought that was yeah
And if you push the right switches you got the pill
I didn't push any right switches
The banana flavored candy was what it was it wasn't really a pill
No banana flavored candy for me it was all
It felt like a pill because they'd quit giving you the shocks if you pushed the right switch
But if you were totally uncooperative they applied the shock machine to different parts more tender parts of your body
And then they'd start moving it into your into different parts of your nervous system that make you feel funny things not just pain
Man I hated elementary school
Oh yeah
I can't believe the stuff those teachers would do
I can't believe the way humans treat us
And speaking of like us being dominant while I don't think you are
I think we're speaking of it or maybe nobody really was but our domination by these so-called lizard people
Do they really exist? I don't think so
I think it's just something wrong in human nature I think they're just people that just shouldn't continue breathing
I'm sorry
Dave I don't blame you for being upset I think we're all upset
There will be a time when we're done
Everyone in this country with our within our range of IQ
Where's that?
Well from the nipples to the lap shall we say
The nipples to the lap area
Those with that other IQs focused there
I mean
We're all disturbed we're all uncomfortable with what has happened
But there's little we can do is there?
There's nothing we can do they will just continue and we can but watch and hope that they will continue
I hope they don't drag us too far along with them
But watching is fine with me I can do that for many years probably even when I'm in feeble
I'd so much rather watch bugs than watch elmers you know what I mean?
Yeah
I mean I'd rather sit in the dirt and watch insects than have to sit in the mall and watch the others shop
Well if you can sit in the mall
It's not that I'm jealous of the others it is that I just don't like it's like being a vampire in church
But if you consider me a vampire I'm not a vampire
If you sit in the mall and watch those people in the mall as if you were watching bugs in a vampire church
Then huh huh then I don't know what happens then
Probably same thing
Now do you think these people were probably harmed early in childhood like maybe their minds were re-connected rewired maybe
Well on the boxes they come in it says they were not harmed
In production but you know and I know from having been there that it hurts a lot
Yeah it's a different marketing group entirely yeah
And we all carry maps made of scars scars that they form little maps all over our body but there are maps to nowhere
They are maps to pain
There's no where's the map to slack
Where is the slack
If only we had such a fever
Perhaps somewhere on a mammoth
Deeply sheltered house
In cow skin
Or in parchment somewhere
Opening shut-off
In hieroglyphs
Where's the road map to slack
Well you provide that sir don't you Dr. and Reverend Eileman Stang of the church
No as a matter of fact we don't provide a road map to slack you have to find slack yourself
We could direct you to a type of false slack that we might find to be real slack
But for you it would be false slack because it was our slack
You could imitate us but that wouldn't give you slack
In fact it would cause people to mock you and drive you out of your village
Hence cause anti-slack and great suffering for you
We witches have had a rough road to hoe you know what I mean
Being the witches of Ohio having to having to
The witch nuts
The broomstick thing is not that comfortable
Okay
It doesn't feel good up in there
Oh yeah you can fly but so to speak
But it's all in your head essentially it's headology
Of course it's headology
Try growing a spare head out of your hip socket
With one of those little pointy hats and a pointy nose
Oh sure it's difficult now but wait until the year 2136 Dave
You'll have to you'll have to that's the only place you'll be they'll have
Be able to grow the cultures from to regrow you after they cut you up and use you for other little Daves and Daveettes and Daveenas
But we need more eggs
The whole idea of
We are running out of eggs
The idea that you can be cloned from a drop of blood or some hair or a bone is that's superstitious nonsense
However they need big chunks but they can make for instance ten clones of you by cutting you into two pieces
Ten pieces and each of those pieces after the injections of course
Then there's the guys who like cut you up and then give the injection to the pieces great
So you end up with ten hands ten lonesome cowboy Dave forearms you know ten cowboy Dave left legs
If you don't give the Dave the injection first the clones are all going to be just that part
And that's what your life is like if you don't have Bob in your life how can you be just an eye
Why do you doubt it?
How can you be just a nose?
You can't see anything
But that's what it's like if you don't have Bob in your life
You're just a part of one sense without the other senses
That's an unlimited number of cells from one bell saying I mean one cell bank
A one cell creature is infinitely I'm sorry I'm yelling now
Is infinitely capable of reproducing itself without having the assistance of a human
The evidence as I left ready for hypnosis had now entanged that that is in fact a
Man is just there waiting to be eaten And you're not at the threshold of dreaming
Right show is already done
mitospasm, or what's the term?
Cytospasm.
It's a mitoperoxysm.
And it splits.
Actually, it's just mitosis.
That's all it is.
Yeah, actual cell mitosis.
Cytospasm is part of the preparation procedure.
Which can be very, very difficult.
But once the brain has split,
there's not enough room for it in the admittedly limited skull.
And it'll infinitely split itself.
So you have to move it into a new skull.
But does it have to be a Dave skull?
Oh, no, no, no.
That's what you better start worrying about, brother and sister.
Even, yes, you sisters and you she-males and trannies
and such like experimental new races.
A Dave brain could be fit into your skull.
And if yours was removed and replaced with a Dave brain,
would you know the difference?
You'd just think you were still Dave, right?
You'd get in bed with your beautiful wife,
but it wouldn't be you that was making love to her.
It would be Dave.
Or one of the Dave.
Brains.
Do you really like that idea?
Are you...
How can you sit like that
and revel in the promise of years to come
when you know that's what's going to happen?
Were you so full of pus and nail polish
that you think that this is the future for all of us?
It's beyond your own personal feelings
and your own glimmerings of individuality.
Think of the future races.
The people, our grandchildren.
Our grandchildren!
Our great...
Whatever deeds they come to, these people...
The babies!
We must always think of our future functionaries.
And that means the products of our lions.
Loins.
The products of our loins.
The lemmings.
What this background music seems to be a repeat of what we had earlier.
There we go.
I think...
It's like...
It's as if this particular CD is...
Has a brain of its own.
Yeah.
Well, it's better off than some of us.
Well, upkeep of a monocelular brain isn't so bad.
You've got to think of it a lot of different ways.
You've got to think of components.
You've got to think of what you've got to buy every year
just to keep things up.
And how do you do that when you've got a bad brain?
That's the whole...
That's the catch-23 of it.
That's the...
As Robert Anton Wilson would say.
If you've got a monocelular brain,
you just go in and you get a brand new one
since they're reproducing constantly.
Brain new!
Get you a brain new brain!
Brain factory!
Step right inside the effedron's rail
from your own spleen.
Drink up and have a happy day.
Ha-ha-poo-bah.
The great poo-bah.
They shot all those people.
Poo-bah-bah.
Ba-ba-ba-ba.
Did you know that?
All those people were lined up
and some of them refused to stay in line
and so they just went around
and started slapping them
with anything they could find
and then they were all shot.
That's the new world we're looking forward to.
A world of poison, dangerous erections,
people with...
That was a great band.
Dangerous erections?
Yeah.
They couldn't shoot straight either.
I mean, it's worse than the fascist overtake
of our, what is the transmitter
or the actual transmission of the car?
That was another good band, Transmission.
They played at Starwood
and stayed in the trailer,
in the same trailer with us.
They're not shy, though.
They're just...
Well, they're invisible, aren't they?
They play...
No.
They're quite visible
and they play didgeridoo
and strange implements.
Not like Reverend Angry Larry
heard in the background.
Now, I got kind of lost there,
but I just remembered some news.
I'm a professor now, Dave.
Oh, you're an actual professor now?
Yes, I'm a professor
because I'm going to be teaching a course,
an online university course.
At the online place known as
MaybeLogicAcademy.org or com.
MaybeLogic?
Yeah, MaybeLogic.
It's, uh, MaybeLogic is what is the thought processes
that Pope Bob or Robert Anton Wilson invented.
Huh.
And these guys did a film about Pope Bob
called MaybeLogic,
which is really good.
And, uh...
I guess you could find out the bits and pieces of it
at MaybeLogic.com.
But if you poke around on there,
they actually have online courses
taught by people like Robert Anton Wilson
and Are You Serious Now, Are You?
And Douglas Rushkoff, I believe,
and J. David Brown
and various other psychedelic hippie types.
And guess they wanted me to teach them a course!
And it's called
How to Run Your Own Cult
Do's and Don'ts
or the History of the Church of the Subgenius
the First 100 Years.
Oh, that is just great.
To be a member of the faculty
and be able to shine your own shoes
and stand up straight and tall
when they smear spit all over your face
and to take your degree
and shove it up their swollen sphincters
and say, I'm a member of this faculty, Dan!
I get to write the history!
Get to write the history!
I get to make people into unpersons.
I get to be the Stalin
and, uh, and actually,
I've been Stalin for too long, friends.
I've got some Carl Stalin's music,
but we were gonna put on a comedy bit.
Now, did this have where the man was praising God
and swore not a hair of his head would be touched
and the lion ate his sphincter?
It's, uh, I don't know.
No, no, that, oh, I didn't take that out of the printer.
We, we, it's just before Dave and I left the Slacker Mansion,
we saw that there was news from Russia
of a man who jumped into a lion's cage
praying to Bob.
And the lion reached up
and severed his carotid artery with one claw
as he prayed to God or Bob or whoever.
He claimed slack would save him
and Bob was actually looking down,
watching in amusement, I guess.
Well, as I was saying,
that, that, that online course is in November.
And, but, uh, but, and it's,
the important thing is we've got this comedic material
by Scooter,
Scooter.
Who is, even though he's not a subgenius,
this is really good.
He sent it to us every day for eight years
and I finally noticed it the other day.
Uh, and it's, um, well, I'll just,
I'll just, uh, run it.
Well, and rather than us running our mouths.
Shadow on the sundial says once again,
it's time to turn back the hands of time.
Gather up all that stuff you don't understand.
Pack it up with the dance music and the new math.
Take it to one of your Catholic neighbors
and he can give it back to the devil
when he sees him on Sunday.
Get down on your knees, Wilbur,
and let the Holy Spirit of the mixed metaphor
emblazon your eternal soul.
In Jesus' name.
With your hope,
with your ghost,
Bill Denye,
the Creation Science Guy.
We'll be right back.
from the most plentiful substance on Earth.
Now, from the Research Institute of Theological Physics,
Dr. Hummer.
You know the two-thirds of the Earth is water?
And still yet, much of the Earth is water.
And you pour the water out
and just as soon as you pour it out,
the Earth takes it.
It sucks it in and it's never satisfied.
It never says it's enough.
You start the water in this building
and if you left it alone, it would not be.
It would not until every single thing in this.
And it would then begin to do its best
to leap over into another building
and begin to...
It would...
Do you understand what I'm saying to you?
And it would pour out and just...
Do you see desire?
Do you see how it's...
And it would pour...
And it's parched and dry.
And it wants more and it says the...
And it wants more and more
and it's talking about us.
That's the way we're supposed to be.
We're supposed...
I just...
We're not satisfied.
And then the water is never satisfied.
Did you ever notice that?
No matter how many people get swallowed up by water,
it still screams out and wants for more.
After the so many thousands gave their life,
it did not say,
okay, that's enough.
It just kept taking
and kept taking
and we're supposed to give
and give
and give!
And I want you to know
we will find water.
We cry give, give.
Glory.
Funny thing about desire.
The Bible said desire...
Uh-huh.
A woman's desire,
a wife's desire
shall be tribulation.
Watch this.
I'm gonna help you.
Mmm.
My desire shall be for your
daughters.
Their names are
give and
give!
My desire shall be for your husband.
And I dated my preacher.
We dated for seven years.
That was like the rapture.
And your husband's like the millennium.
And...
Hanging shriveled up,
withered,
and just...
barely hanging on.
Ha ha.
Glory.
Oh, God.
And that was, of course,
Dr. Isaac Hummer
from the Research Institute
of Theological Physics
in Backwash, Texas,
speaking to us
about the covalent forces
that bond the molecular structures
of water and desire
in bipolar field anointments.
Oh, yeah.
From the Holy Ghost Institute of Technology,
I'm Bill Deny,
the Creation Science Guy.
See you next time.
Oh, my God.
Ah!
Public corporations broadcasting
for public support
from viewers for public broadcast...
Friends, I must tell you,
that was from Scooter,
and you can...
Scooter does some intense shows
that are, in some ways,
very similar to this show,
and yet distantly related.
You can check Scooter's work out
at axisofevil.org,
but axis is spelled A-C-K,
S-I-S, not like you would think.
A-C-K-S-I-S, axisofevil,
one word, dot org.
Thank you, Price Bob.
You're listening to
the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack,
the voice of the Church of the Subgenius.
For more information on the Church of the Subgenius
and Bob and Connie,
check out www.subgenius.com.
Subgenius.com.
And, uh, and, uh, yes, it's, uh...
Or write to...
A post office box,
181-417,
Cleveland Heights, Ohio,
4...
411-8.
That's 44118.
That's 181-417 at 44118.
For those of you who can still 418...
I wish I could learn
to say the WCSB phone number backwards
like Dr. Sinister does on the Hour of Slack replays
of the Dr. Sinister show.
No, it's more like...
Oh, that kind of backwards.
And you can do that soon, friends,
because we'll be getting off...
Yes?
A fireplace poker well placed in the forehead
will let you learn what you need to know.
What changed?
It will let you lean on what you think you need to know.
Bob knows what you really think,
and you can pay to learn what he knows.
Or you can buy yourself a little Bob Nose
and make off into the woods with it.
Yes.
Scampering through the forests and the fields
wearing your little Bob Nose.
Collecting slack fungus.
Ah, yes.
Chewing on little funny mushrooms
that you find growing in your armpits and groin.
Sighting brain damage.
Hell, hell.
We will go away.
Goodbye.
Let's give him a hand.
Amen.
Hey.
Whoo!
Did that shock some of you fine sisters?
Well, if this kind of preaching would be preached
all the time,
you would be living like some old cheap heifer.
Amen.
That last cut was by Reverend Mayne Brainert.
And now...
.
Ben.
Wait.
No.
.
A white man.
Yes, it was true.
But my...
A, I was speaking generally.
I mean, uh...
.
What more could a white man have?
Possibly robbery?
Or if he were a very intellectual man...
.
No, it is too far-fetched.
That's because it's not refined.
But first, a word about the first super-wonderful, super-wonderful new special perfect repaired homemade beautiful new oil.
It's a new oil.
That's because it's not new oil.
All right.
What's the difference between a radio aerial and a clothesline?