Why are we here and where are we going? What is the meaning of life?
Your life is empty, looking for a meaning to personal existence.
Women, drinking, partying. I partied up a storm.
All this drinking, partying, and getting old. Drugs might be the answer. Why don't we try that?
Sounds like fun to me. Let's go for it.
I really got into drugs.
Acid, man, the way to open your mind.
I had drugs were expanding my mind.
You gotta promise me you'll try the LSD.
I had always told myself what a nice, loving, honest, trustworthy, Boy Scout kind of guy I was.
For your free packet of 666.
The Dow that can be understood is not the real Dow.
Man, I'm hurting.
Then I had nothing.
Decided to kill myself.
It's worthless.
Something went off inside of me.
You may not be here next week.
There.
Take this.
Bingo.
That's it.
So I got down on my knees.
I got back down on my knees.
But when I get down on my knees, it was dope.
I had to do it.
And I did.
Come inside.
The only solution to life's mysteries is to have women, drinking, partying.
Our lives.
Life.
Drunk.
Mr. Calhoun.
He said that when you ate the man, do you mind if I ask?
You said that afterwards your hunger was different than you felt wanton.
Yes.
Did you feel at all physically changed?
Stronger?
I seem to remember.
Something like...
that certain virility. Why do you ask?
You know, you look good in that chair, Bob.
Brings out your presence. Makes you look important.
Hey, well, y'all. House tricks anyway.
Not that I'm doing all that bad. I mean,
I'm not gonna be living the sweet life like you, Bob, but
I'm learning to deal with that. I can
deal with it, Bob.
Is the chair comfortable
enough, Bob?
Gotta tell ya, definitely you, Bob. It is
you and this chair connect, Bob.
You can lean back if you want.
I like the way it does that.
See? Do you like it too, Bob?
That'll be my wife, Bob. I gotta go
now, but good luck with the election. You're a winner,
right?
Right, Bob. You're a winner. Success written all over you.
Well, see you later, Bob.
See you later, Bob.
It's raining, Bob. Hallelujah, it's raining, Bob.
Amen.
It's raining, Bob.
It's rained, Bob.
God.
It's raining, Bob.
Good luck.
What? What? What?
Where is he?
Wake up.
He was licking me.
What?
He was licking?
No.
He was licking me!
A load of hemp and rum
and sailed to the west coast of deepest, darkest Africa
where a star man
eat the living brains out of the head of another man.
Gather round the radio, children,
and I'll tell you a story.
A story about cannibalism
and how I lost this dear old leg of mine.
I remember this one.
Now.
You know what cannibalism is,
do you, children?
It's when a man eats another man
or parts of another man.
No.
Now, don't be afraid.
Come up close to the captain.
The dildo man won't let any harm come to him.
If you want to give us a call, the number up here is 216-N-S-S-3-5-Val-
Phone lines are wide open and we are just aching to hear from you.
Uh.
One thing that really got me lately in the news,
this guy in Germany
cannibalized a man,
murdered him and butchered him and ate him up.
And he was given a sentence of like five and a half years because it was manslaughter
because the guy asked to be killed.
So it was really not considered murder, just manslaughter.
They called it man's laughter.
They called it.
So we're going to go to the phones right now.
They're lighting up fast.
You better call them.
Call while you can.
Hello.
Oh, hey.
Hey.
This is Reverend Stang.
What's up?
That German cannibal dude?
Yeah.
I understand from stuff I've been downloading off the internet lately that that cannibalism
is like a cool trend among high school kids.
Oh, come on.
Now that, of course, like, you know, of course I get into it now.
You know, I've been into cannibalism for a while and now suddenly all the cool kids are
into it.
Well, that's what I, that's kind of the impression I got that it had been something that was
just a few kids here and there, like, you know, I don't know, Hollywood type rich kids,
real weird kids, intellectual kids were doing it.
And then, you know, somehow it suddenly become really trendy and, you know, obviously there's
a health problem because if you got just anybody chewing off parts of each other, they're going
to get infected and stuff.
That's right.
We're going to see what another panelist might have to say on this matter.
Going to the other line here.
You're on the air.
Hello?
Is that him?
I don't know.
I don't hear anybody.
I think I, I think I psychically can tell you what happened.
Oh yeah?
Yeah.
The person that was trying to call you bumped the wrong button, like some kind of a chimpanzee.
I didn't bump it like a chimpanzee.
It was more like a, you know, a chimpanzee.
It was more an emotion of a gibbon, viper, I mean, you know, when I was looking at chimpanzee,
orangutan or something.
I mean, nevermind.
Orangutan.
But cannibalism is, is indeed growing across the land.
And a recent study in Nevada, teenagers, 15% of teenagers under 19 were found to have consumed
human flesh in one form or another.
We've got to form a partnership for human flesh free America now.
Yeah.
There's something really has to be done.
I don't know.
Just keep saying no.
There's a lot of infrastructure that we need really to rid ourselves of either this problem
or the motors or the demotors or, you know, any possible other evacuations we might want
to get out.
Well, here's a, here's a potential solution that I have to the problem.
Instead of this horrible problem of people cannibalizing their friends and neighbors
and you know, internet lovers like the guy in Germany did.
Well, it's the thing, it's all consensual.
So what, whose business is it?
Yeah, really.
We're all soiling green to each other if we want to be.
Right.
Well, I'm, I still say it's time to break out the glass tubes.
Yeah.
And start a human flesh farms.
We can grow an encephalic human bodies or, you know, farm raisin.
Don't.
Oh, we certainly, we could nano, we could nano grow human tissue without a soul.
Right.
Just for eating.
Soul.
Yeah.
But that takes the whole.
Tenderloins and so forth.
Drill out of it.
You know, things.
Color number three, you're on the air.
This is Dion.
Oh, it's Dion.
Good to hear from you, Dion.
What's your take on the cannibalism issue?
Did you, could you, could you be honest?
I think a raspberry.
Have you ever eaten a person, Dion?
I, I always wanted to.
He never did though, huh?
He never did, huh?
Yeah.
Never consummated the act.
But you know, there are support groups now too.
If you want to eat another human's flesh and you really can't find the right human to eat,
you can network and stuff.
And this, this is how it happened in Germany.
But we're talking about solving a problem, not about exaggerating it.
You know what I'm saying?
Uh.
What, could, could you eat a certain part of the body?
Oh yeah, you know, different parts are good for, uh.
Hey, why don't you call us up?
It's the SQ715.
Tell us your favorite body part to cook.
But keep it clean, folks.
We're not in safe harbor yet.
Hey, hey.
Color number four, you're on the air.
Hello, it's Hell Pope Huey.
How the hell are you?
Well, how the hell are you?
Oh, Hell Pope Huey is one of the earliest, most ancient living, still living subgenius
radio ministers.
He was the first person to play any subgenius tape on public airwaves.
And I'm older than me and crankier than anybody but Gigi Gordon, I swear to God.
Well, we were discussing cannibalism, which has become popular among teenagers and especially,
you know, it started in Germany and now everybody's doing it.
And, uh, the question was what body part would you most want to cannibalize off of your friend
or whoever you were doing it, doing the cannibalizing with?
Well, now it's easy enough to say you'd like to try some thigh off some of the women, but
that's really a wash.
I think I'd like to try a foot off some of them like legume.
I mean, he's kind of old now, but you want to slow some of them down because they're
dangerous.
So I think I'd start with the foot washed, of course.
Well, but this would be a, you know, somebody who would be a friend that was sharing meat
with you, I guess, you know, so you wouldn't be, it's just like, what would be your favorite
part to eat?
Just, you know, discounting whether you had to kill the person in order to eat them.
Well, I think it would probably be the calf off of Andrew because he's a dynamite cook.
And he'd come up with a good sauce because if he was a good sport enough to let me eat
part of him, he'd probably make a great sauce for it.
Don't you think?
Well, we don't, we don't know this, who this Andrew is that you're speaking of, but I'm
sure that his calf would probably be the finest if it was kept in the right kind of pen for
long enough without being allowed to move.
His calf would probably fatten up and be worth a lot more.
The fatted calf?
Like, and if you put them in a cast.
Oh.
A person who, uh, you know, you're not going to be able to eat them.
Well, if you're planning to eat, if you could possibly arrange that with someone who'd been
in a full body cast, it would be like having veal.
Oh yeah.
Well, now we could marinate some testicles, but then we'd get into that big homo thing
and that would lead an awful lot of trouble, uh, hard to discuss.
What is it, Pops?
Commies?
Eskimos?
No, son.
Eskimos haven't been a threat in years.
But well, you know, Ted Jenkins' son Wendell, don't you?
Sure.
From your company, Picnics.
But gosh, he's a great older than me.
He's a great older than me.
He runs with a pretty fast crowd.
That's a crowd your mother and I don't want you trying to keep up with, Bobby.
You see, Wendell was experimenting with...
Drugs?
Cigarettes?
Alcohol?
I wish it was alcohol.
Or even masturbation.
Wendell was experimenting with cannibalism.
His father caught him in the garage, eating his sister.
Cannibalism?
Gosh, I'd heard some kids at school had been trying it, but they were the kids from bad
homes whose parents didn't work as hard as you or Mr. Jenkins.
I mean, Wendell Jenkins, a cannibal.
Well, son, cannibals can come in any shape or size.
Some cannibals can run very fast.
Others are good at math.
Take the car tonight, Bobby.
It will calm your mother.
As a father, you have to wonder if the simple act of warning your child makes him want to
experiment.
Maybe we shouldn't tell teens anything.
Maybe then they'd grow up happy.
And then they'd be happy and safe.
So, Bobby, how was your date with Becky Sue?
Oh, uh, it was fine.
Well, goodnight.
Any problems with the car?
Ran like a dream, Dad.
Well, goodnight.
Say, Bobby, you and Becky Sue didn't experiment with cannibalism, did you?
Gosh, no, Dad.
Well, goodnight.
Son, what happened to your ear?
Oh, I, uh, caught it on a barbed wire fence.
Well, goodnight.
I couldn't put my finger on it.
But something told me that Becky Sue Johnson was leading my Bobby into a dark world.
Wait, you're cutting into his butt.
Well, what kind of piece do you want?
Well, not butt.
Four fat sausages sitting in the pan.
One went and another went.
Remarkable boy.
I do admire your courage.
Oh!
I think I'll eat your heart.
It's not what you think.
I was having a nightmare.
Your mind screamed.
I awoke.
I was on top of him.
My lips were on his wound.
Jesus Christ, I'm sorry.
Please, sir, restrain me.
Restrain me, Colonel.
I can't be trusted, please.
I insist.
Oh, my God!
What?
It's a cannibal!
Stay back, cannibal!
She's alive!
Hey, guys.
You know what I want from Bob Dobbs?
What do you want from Bob Dobbs?
I want to be something nice and something really warm and something really, like, wet.
A baby excrement you could probably be.
Well, it's not that nice, but it's certainly warm and wet.
You know what I want?
I want to be a baby.
Oh!
That's a good one!
I like that.
It is appropriate.
We could rent you one of those fainting goats for the weekend.
They're really warm and friendly.
Yeah.
They pass out at least four times a minute, buddy, if you're into that, you know what I'm
saying?
Well, sure.
Say, say, say, say, say ...
No, not all of them.
I don't think you should make fun of people who are differently sexed or, like, last
... differently abled emotionally.
Well, so far.
Well, darn, Dang, that'd be pretty cool.
It shut down the whole church.
I know.
I'm just kidding.
That's the problem.
You know, the minute you go, God, there's sure a lot of creeps and retards and weirdos.
And, you know, suddenly you look in the mirror and go, oh, yeah, there's another one.
I think they're fractured.
I think they have a dysfunctional view of life, many of these people.
They call in.
They complain about their sexuality.
They complain about the webbing between their feet.
Like, everybody has something wrong with it.
I mean, you know, not necessarily.
Well, something wrong with it, you know?
Well, I like my webbing.
It helps me to swim better.
Well.
You have to look on these things as pluses, you know.
Pretty soon you're going to be swimming around in a bowl of liquid helium, and it's still not going to make sense.
Yeah, there's nothing wrong with my webbing.
God just isn't finished with me yet.
Yep, I am as God made me when he was drunk.
When he was on glue and hollow.
Jimson weed.
Mmm.
Well, you know, there's a little stang in all of us, but you just have to keep swatting at it like a leg-humping terrier.
Trying to find some balance.
God, how disrespectful.
Don't tell Pope Huey.
He's always just making fun of me.
I can't say much because my farts are piling up like cannonballs.
I don't know what the hell I ate.
I've been stanged by a bee.
And it hurt.
You know what I'm saying?
It hurted.
It hurts.
When stang stangs you, you're hurt, man.
He stang people in the heart sometimes.
That's a...
God, come on.
You know that's not always fine.
Oh, it's a liquid vapid.
That's part of the satire, man.
Like the mental illnesses and the, you know, lawsuits and everything.
That's all just part of Bob's commentary on society.
It's for a bunch of miscreants who have very little left to do in life.
Oh, but at least they have this.
That hurt.
At least there's this.
This show.
At least there's that much left to us.
After everything else was taken away.
Dr. Sinister's show.
We've lost it all.
We've officially lost it all, then.
And Uncle QE's pelt.
We call this show Liquid Toppings about cannibals and things that are actually happening in this country right now.
This is not some sort of a bandwagon for a progressive movement.
This is not.
This is not some sly bag's cheek effect to get in a laboratory at night and do something weird to your fingernails.
This is an honest attempt to examine the social phenomenon that's going on right now.
Well, that doesn't mean you can't do the fingernails thing.
That's part of it, too.
But Lord loves ducks.
And that's why we have to at least consider why people are doing this stuff.
Well, duck is expensive.
People are cheap.
People have never been cheaper.
They're everywhere.
Wasn't there some news story about somebody bought some pottery at the discount place Mark's here in Cleveland,
and it had parts of human bones inside?
I read that.
You?
Yeah, it's like a skull hidden inside the pottery at this discount place.
Which made me want to run down there and buy up all the Virgin Marys and crack them open
and see if there was, you know, bags of cocaine and diamonds.
Makes you look at your sugar bowl a whole new way, don't it?
The ones with desiccated human liver give you a mortality.
It is a very, very, very old art.
Well, we're joking about how human is cheap and Soylent Green is people and only a science fiction comedy movie and so forth.
But really, think about it.
What is the most plentiful creature, edible thing going to be 50 years from now?
The cows are all mad.
The long pig dinner.
Young Christians, they'll be food and they'll also be money.
They'll be exchanged for goods and services by those who know to use them as food.
Now, help, Hope Huey, the whole world is not Arkansas where you're calling from.
Yeah, really, we don't have the slaughterhouse system going like you guys do out there in the boonies.
We've got a thing where we have to lure the guy down into the basement, teach him about butterflies and frozen hearts,
and then we, you know, make hamburgers out of them and stuff.
But we can't.
There's a lot of codes and stuff around here, you know, if you're not wearing a hat.
The inspector's on us.
You mean you just don't drive around in a truck and have one of your buddies grab him by the neck as you turn a corner and then just cook him on a grill?
Oh, the old good humor wagon doesn't work anymore.
That's too much work.
This is Yankee territory, help, Hope Huey.
Yeah, you know, they do things real differently up here.
You know, their eye is, one good eye is...
Oh, they have their own special way.
It's better than down south.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, it's much more sophisticated.
When they say smoke them around here, somebody produces a joint or a cigarette.
They don't, you know...
They don't sit their neighbor on fire or...
Yeah, they look down on you Arkansas people while you're selling them water for a dollar a sip.
Well, I must admit, I can't argue with that.
I've got a neighbor who's got a little poodle, and I think their IQs are about the same.
So I can't argue with that too much.
Well, you can make mishmash out of them.
You know, a poodle with a neighbor together probably maybe go for it.
Oh, I was putting down Yankees.
We've got to get out of here.
We have to get away with some other people.
Look, I know you're afraid.
I'm afraid too.
Whoa.
Cool.
Still no sign of land.
How long is it?
33 days, sir.
33 days?
We can't go on much longer, sir.
We haven't eaten since the fifth day.
We've just got to keep hoping.
Someone may find us.
Now, if the search has been called off, then we're on our own to save our lives, and we've got to eat.
Listen, champs, there's still a chance.
I'm done for.
I've got a gammy leg, and I'm going fast.
I'll never get through, but some of you might.
So you'd better eat me.
It means we should eat today.
Eat yourself?
Yes, eat me.
You're talking about eating people.
Ugh.
With a gammy leg?
You didn't eat the leg, Thompson.
There's still plenty of good meat.
Look at that arm.
We're talking about eating meats, but we don't die.
If I had a wound that was rotten and needed to be washed out, wouldn't you do it, even though it's disgusting, because it needed to be done?
Yeah, I would, but I wouldn't eat you.
What do you mean?
I said, it's just that...
Why don't you want to eat me?
Look, I don't want to talk about this.
Neither do I, Gustavo, but we have to.
We're starving and we're trapped.
I'd rather eat Johnson, sir.
So would I, sir.
I see.
Well, now settle it.
Everyone's going to eat me.
Now, if the soul...
If there is a soul...
We'll leave the body when we die, and the body is just a carcass.
Well, I'm sorry, but I can't do it.
Miss you.
Oh, go ahead, please, but I won't...
Oh, nonsense, sir.
You're starving, tucking.
No, no, it's not that.
What's the matter with Johnson, sir?
Well, he's got kosher.
That depends how we kill him, sir.
We shouldn't murder innocents to live.
What about our innocence?
What's going to become of our innocence if we survive as cannibals?
Yes, that's true.
But to be perfectly frank, I like my meat a little more lean.
I'd rather...
I'd rather eat Hodges.
Oh, well, all right.
I still prefer Johnson.
We should all stop bickering and eat meat.
Are you ready to go out there and cut flesh from a human body and eat it?
I tell you what, those who want to can eat Johnson, and you, sir, can have my leg, and
we'll make him stop from the captain, and then we'll have Johnson cold for supper.
Oh, yes.
Good idea.
Excellent thinking.
I enjoyed that.
Let's do it again.
Actually, what I wanted to mention was it's meaningful that none of us has mentioned this
game.
Well, Dave and Princess, we and I just went out to a restaurant, and everywhere we went,
people said, oh, game must be over.
Oh, how was...
It's just simply assumed that you were watching the Super Bowl.
Oh, yeah.
Now, on an elderly woman's...
In some genius land, they were asking questions like, Super Bowl, is that a meal at McDonald's?
What is that?
No, that's a really, really nice pipe for your frop.
Well, who won?
This incredible...
I didn't even know who was playing until yesterday.
Oh, yesterday?
And I am calling out Dr. Lance Underpants for spoiling it for me.
I thought I was going to go the whole year without finding out who was in the game, and
I came out on 669, and I did not expect to hear it, and I couldn't change the channel
before it came out.
Oh, man.
That's really disappointing.
WCSB is letting me down now.
Still haven't found out?
I did find out, unfortunately, who was in it, and I promptly went about trying to forget
it.
I asked my father this morning.
It was the Welsh Pomeranians, wasn't it?
Welsh Pomeranian?
Yeah.
Don't these teams really...
Aren't they supposed to stand for something?
Like, perhaps, you know, one team would all be eunuchs or something, and the other team
would all have...
I don't know.
You know, there's just really no meaning in sports anymore.
They get a lot of money, and they beat each other up, but...
Oh, but they get extra drugs now that turn them into super beings.
Well, how about a team that unfurls a red banner?
That part of the sport is how many drugs you can get away with without getting caught,
you know?
That's actually part of it.
Okay, the other team all has bad legs.
They're a little gimpy then, and they have to take steroids.
Right.
All right.
See, now that would make sense.
No, but part of the competition is how much can you get away with in terms of steroids
and all of that.
That's part of winning.
And how much can you get away with?
Rage.
I'm sorry.
That's sort of like the behind-the-scenes score among your fellow professionals.
Right.
Like, when these people all get arrested for public evacuation, where are they going to
take them?
They've already been there, you know, at least once or twice and stuff, so now they're talking
about making big camps, you know, turning the coliseums into places where there's more
than bread and circus.
There's a bunch of dead bodies laying around.
I can't really be interested in organized team sports until we have real rollerball with
spiked gloves and, you know, metal balls being shot out of a tube at 80 miles an hour and
some skulls being crushed because, you know, a mere broken pelvis just doesn't excite me
anymore.
I've done it all, seen it all, and I want real rollerball.
Football is for wusses.
Right.
If we're going to have capital punishment, let's combine it with sports.
That's a great idea.
Excellent idea.
Well, Running Man, you know, Stephen King, actually, I mean, that's been...
Oh, yeah.
They could make a discus.
...I saw for decades, but it's time.
The time has come.
Then we could solve the cannibalism problem, too, because the losers are grandly eaten
as heroes.
Well, you get both years, too, for all the side stuff.
Right.
Gladiator crap, you know, the ratings raising.
Nuggets.
Strips.
So forth.
You know.
Finger food.
Yeah.
It's reality TV.
It's a hit.
It's what all the kids in Seattle are into.
It's cool.
Good old Hitler's hand soap was made out of real hands.
I mean, you know, you can't go too far from the truth.
Everything is as clear as whatever it looks like a nose on your face.
So, I think we should proceed from there.
Turn your elderly neighbors into finger food.
Win valuable prizes.
Yeah.
Mmm, tasty.
You're thinking wishfully.
I'm thinking marketing, man.
I'm thinking like mega, mega push.
I'm thinking like maybe four states at first.
Top, maybe pinpoint target states.
And move on into like shirts, vacuum cleaners, deodorants, the whole smear.
How do you make a deodorant out of an old lady who smells like a foot?
Well, you give it a flavor and you say it's all natural.
Oh.
I'm a hamburger playing hockey.
You know you like it just as much as I do.
Mmm.
Chew it.
I'm a chicken.
Protein.
Well, we've been looking for someone with a crazy grudge and some kind of anatomical
knowledge.
De-certified doctors, med school dropouts, laid off mortuary workers.
From the precision of the cuts, yes, and his choice of souvenirs.
See, that's where we're off target.
He's not collecting body parts.
Then why keep them?
He's not keeping them.
He's eating them.
Now, listen, we were at Molly's parents for New Year's, and Molly's dad was showing my
son Josh how to carve a roasted chicken.
He said, the tenderest part of the chicken is the oysters here on either side of the
back.
I had never heard that expression before, oysters.
And suddenly I had a flash of the third victim, Darcy Taylor.
She was missing flesh from her back.
And then it hit me, liver, kidney, tongue, thymus, every single victim lost some body
part used in cooking.
People actually love chicken.
They're not going to live without a brain.
You can live without certain parts of the brain.
Oh, you can?
Yeah.
Actually, you guys, just today I talked to an old friend of mine from high school, who
last year was diagnosed all of a sudden with a brain tumor.
And he described to me what it felt to wake up with part of your brain scraped out after
the operation.
He had to learn how to walk all over again.
He said he'd look at his foot and tell it to move, and it wouldn't move.
So he had to learn how to walk all over again.
But now he's just fine again.
And he talks all normal on the phone.
But he's ready for the matrix.
He's ready for virtual reality because he's already got the socket prepared.
He's got a special plug, a hole ready to jack in.
Great.
It's kind of inspiring, actually, to talk to somebody who had part of their brain scraped.
I mean, you can develop a tumor, have it cut out, and he sounds just fine.
Or even a living brain is a great conversation piece.
Well, Dave here has only the one cell.
It's very big and heavy.
Well, not that big and heavy.
It's very dense.
It's dense.
And if he were to get a tumor on that, I mean, it would be the tumor.
Maybe that explains the big cell.
I think it is one macro cell.
I have a...
I think it is one brain tumor for a brain.
But I managed to carry on most function.
That's what...
That says a lot about the sad situation that humanity finds itself in today.
I had to literally teach my catalyzer to keep me from going into a...
Hello?
Yeah.
Sorry.
Caller number four.
Hello?
These guys, they forget their numbers.
Yeah, I can't...
I can't hear the ones...
The ones further down the line, I can't hear at all.
Yeah.
Where's the double salami and pastrami, number 35?
These people, they have no intricate, centric numbers.
Is it true the brain regenerates itself?
No.
Generally, no.
Is that true?
It could be made to, though.
Huh?
It could be made to regenerate itself under certain conditions, but under normal conditions,
no, it will not.
Well, let's say that part of the brain isn't cut out, but let's say it lost some cells.
Probably not.
I have another question.
It's a beer.
Call number four.
You're on the air.
Yeah.
What exactly is going on right now?
What the fuck exactly are you asking?
We're getting into a heavy philosophy.
We're talking about brains.
What do you mean by what exactly is happening?
I understand that you're talking about brains.
I mean, do you actually know people who have gone through lobotomies and brain scrapings
and stuff like that?
In our church, pretty much, that's how you get into the church.
Cancer surgery is no laughing matter.
We run it in the church.
You would not joke about that.
Oh, no, no.
I mean, I'm not calling you out or anything like that.
I just find it extremely interesting that you...
I mean, is this an actual topic or are you guys just seriously...
Well, say you were to call him out, what would you do?
Would you examine his skull once you had done so or would you guys begin to punch each other's
heads like perhaps a moose in heat?
I mean...
It would compare me to his phrenological bust for sure.
Yeah.
You're talking about...
Okay.
I have the occipital lobes of a common...
Criminal.
Yeah.
I have...
When I had my third nostril opened, I felt kind of cheated.
I thought I was going to be less aware and I thought I wouldn't have my math anymore.
I thought I was going to have an easier life, but really, all I did was kind of flatten
my personality a little bit.
And gave you a third nostril?
Yeah.
I still wasn't...
Couldn't qualify for welfare or anything.
I was...
Might as well have kept my money.
I don't know.
I can remember I don't even have much time for myself and not to say I'm not...
I was...
But that's how it is.
Yeah.
And you don't have to say whatever...
Se claimant monte climbed...
He sat down right at five and he said, you know, I've done it.
He said, let's not...
What's wrong?
wifi intet counsels.
Yeah, and then he opened it and then he looked in the window and...
And...
It was, you know, it was, as you said, it was nothing, it was a very violent thing.
Here he goes.
A rock, a brick.
Well, still, you know, I've seen kids hurt themselves hitting them.
They'll take those little ball-peen hammers and they'll put a rock on their forehead.
They'll consult the chart and then hit themselves in the head just in these right spots.
They're supposed to get them high or make them see God and whatnot.
These kids can't even read.
Oh, God, they're covered with bruises and bloody.
It's just sick.
As far as I'm concerned, the cannibalism really was a healthier trend.
There's not much diagram.
It depends on who you're eating.
Well, that's the thing.
People were not practicing safe, whatever you call it, you know, diet.
Safe cuisine.
Is it safe to eat the abdul-al-bongana?
I do not recommend eating any part of the human brain.
Abdul-al-bongana.
Or any brain, for that matter.
But, I mean, like, only under certain rituals.
It's not the sort of thing you can just cook up for dinner one night.
That's...
You can only do that on holidays.
The people who inspired the band Devo,
the whole reason the human race...
evolved was that we were originally brain-eating apes.
And as we slew our fellow apes and ate their brains,
that caused us to become more, quote, intelligent, unquote.
Yeah.
So that's why the original topping is always so much better than the first sundae.
We've come full circle all the way back to why people are cannibals.
It's in their genes.
It's in their sly pants.
It's in their...
Every waking moment, they can't get away from it.
But their ancestors were brain-eating apes.
Unless you believe...
What's his name?
Maharishi Terence McKenna.
He said that our ancestors were mushroom-eating apes
who would get their kind of vision enhanced.
You'd see a tiger hiding in the jungle better
if you were tripping on mushrooms
than if you were a normal non-mushroom-eating ape.
You'd see a lot of other things, too.
I think that's...
the product of a person who's eaten too many mushrooms.
Wonderful nourishment.
Real tasty.
Ten fat sausages.
I found your private rye cup, then.
All what was left of him.
You didn't finish.
Well, I can't blame you.
He was tough.
But then, uh...
a good soldier ought to be.
You know, not that long ago, I couldn't do that.
I could barely take a breath without coughing up a pint of blood.
Tuberculosis.
That, along with, uh...
fierce headaches.
Depression.
Suicidal ambition.
I was in pretty horrible shape.
I...
In fact...
I was on my way to a sanatorium to convalesce,
more likely to die.
When en route, this...
Indian scout
told me a curious story.
A man eats the flesh of another.
He steals his strength.
Yes.
He absorbs the other man's spirit.
And...
he's...
Well...
I just had to try.
Consequently, I ate the scout first.
And you know, he was absolutely right.
I grew...
stronger.
Later, through circumstance,
my wagon train grew lost in the Rockies.
I've heard this story before.
Hmm.
I ate five men in three months.
I was...
Tuberculosis.
Vanished.
As did the Black Thorns.
I reached Denver that spring feeling...
happy.
And healthy.
And virile.
Did you eat her, too?
Well, as a matter of fact...
You're disgusting.
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
Here I am,
one year later,
feeling more alive than ever before.
And that's what surprises me about you, Boyd.
You've tasted it.
Felt its power.
Yet you're resisting.
Why?
Because it's wrong.
Ah!
Morality.
The last bastion of a coward.
I'm sorry.
Did I offend you?
I was gonna ask you guys something.
Like, how long after, uh,
a human's death did they...
did their...
did their soul get, uh,
reincarnated?
Psh.
How long do you stay out of your body?
Depends on how hungry Bob is.
How long do you have to stay out?
Until you're so confused
you want to touch something
should you go back.
Well, no, and also how hungry Bob is.
It's like how...
you know, how...
how soon are you expected
at the dinner table?
Yeah.
When will you be sure?
When does he need someone new
to extract slack from?
That's right.
Bob's slack has to come from somewhere.
The suffering of humanity
is, of course, the greatest fuel
that produces slack in others.
It's also a great wing sauce, too,
in our bottles.
If you're eating six
sadistic others.
And so...
that... yeah, and the wine sauce, too.
Has anybody ever tried to eat Bob?
How would you answer that?
Well, I couldn't hear that, so...
Has anyone ever attempted to eat Bob?
Oh, boy.
Well, Beth, what do you think the...
Has anyone not?
...communication ritual is all about?
That's the...
that's where we, you know,
we join with Bob
and we partake of his slack
and of his smoke and his flesh.
Do this in remembrance of...
Wow.
...and his hairs.
I heard you guys had a problem
in your church with a...
with a soul reaver.
A soul reaver?
Yeah.
Reverb or the reaper?
No, reverb.
The reaper?
Soul reaver.
Somebody who takes souls.
You mean... oh, yeah.
Yeah.
You know, the soul suckers?
Did anybody ever try to suck his soul?
Um, geez, I don't know if you could suck Bob's soul.
It's so, uh, galvanized and...
and completely...
in...
How'd anybody want to?
Bob doesn't have a soul.
He's made of souls.
It's like the question of
who was the first man to eat an oyster.
Well, I think it would take a lot of, uh,
you know, maybe some frat boys would...
get real drunk and do Bob's soul on a bet.
That's the only way I could see that happening.
Yeah.
No way would a person in their right mind
even... even take a hit off of his pipe.
Yeah.
That's brought a lot of people down.
Those who would...
Yeah, Bob, can I have a hit of that?
Why, sure.
Up all the way across the room.
You're stuck in the madhouse.
Yeah, you're down the bottom of Ward 4.
And you know what?
Why doesn't the guy ever call up and make himself, uh...
know?
On the phone, why doesn't he ever call up and say, uh...
or make, like, a meeting on the phone or whatever?
You mean arrange for his voice to actually be heard?
Yeah.
You mean you haven't heard him all this time?
I haven't heard him on the phone.
We've been talking to him. He's been here.
Isn't that right, Bob?
Right.
See, didn't you hear him answer just there?
No, I didn't hear him answer.
Well, he was agreeing with himself or somebody.
Oh, that's great. No shit, Bob.
I mean, Bob, sorry.
Rob.
Yeah, you can't, uh...
be too careful when you got Eurasian compliments from, uh...
South Central...
Where was that guy from again?
Bob's right. Not everybody is tuned in.
You can't save everyone.
There's only so much slack to go around.
What, Bob?
Yeah, right.
You can't even provide for them a relaxing good night's sleep on an orthopedic bed.
You can't do anything for them except for shoot them and eat them.
So you might as well give in to the reality that we're...
mind-munching, brain-crunching...
simians, and there will never be anything else.
How about an Elastitch effort to take out other people?
How about if somebody were to inject themselves with poison?
Um...
I think you have a serious problem.
Listen, I can't... I can hardly hear this guy, but it kind of reminds me of the...
You know, with the kid in Catholic school, it's always going,
Hey, Fada, is there a rock so big...
Can God make a rock so big he can't lift it?
Yeah, yeah, right.
Yes, God can make a rock so big he can't lift it.
Okay.
We have a more serious question here.
Yeah.
Can Bob make some frot so strong even he can't smoke it?
They used to call it apologetics.
Can Bob...
Can Bob make a product so bad even he can't sell it?
Can Bob see his own eyes?
Can he... can he smell his own nose?
Can he hear his own ears?
Can he... can he... can he feel his own...
Gosh, Dad, what is it with you and this cannibalism kick?
Just because you find a dead body in my room,
you think I'm a cannibal?
Maybe I'm just a necrophile,
or I'm studying early for medical school.
You're right, son. I shouldn't jump too...
Say, Bobby, where's your leg?
I lost it during swim practice.
Legs aren't cheap, son.
You should learn to be more careful.
School custodians should have found it by now, and...
All right! I'm a cannibal! Happy?
I don't know how it started. It just did!
And now there's nothing I can do about it!
You know, son, I may be an old man, but...
I'm an old fuddy-duddy when it comes to...
experimentation, as those liberal therapists refer to it.
But your ear and your leg will never grow back.
You've got to learn restraint.
Right as usual, Dad.
From now on, I promise to only eat lower life forms and some sea crustaceans.
Good for you, son.
And that's how cannibalism almost consumed my Bobby.
I'm glad to say that he's ready to start his first year of college next fall,
and his episodes of cannibalism have reduced drastically.
Isn't that right, son?
Sure, Dad.
What are you cooking?
It's, uh... stew.
You need any help?
No, no, though, uh...
perhaps later you might...
contribute.
So you're gonna kill me?
No!
It's lonely being a cannibal.
Tough making friends.
Oh, I like you, Boyd.
Let me, uh...
I want to bring you into the fold.
You gotta eat.
And I wanted you to know
We were true, that we were big enough
As we quietly died in the snow
A place we'll never leave
A place we never wanna borrow
A place we'll call the final resting place
In pieces
So began this winter of call when we got started
So we end this winter, trace of us in spring
And knowing all I get before the better
If you just can't feel a fucking thing
Fall asleep and die
I wanted you to know
We were true, that we were big enough
As we quietly died in the snow
A place we'll never leave
A place we never wanna borrow
A place we'll call the final resting place
In pieces
In pieces In pieces
In pieces In pieces In pieces
In pieces
In pieces In pieces
Uh, I like you, boyd
you were thinking of
as we quietly died in the snow
A place we'll never leave
A place we never wanna go
A place we'll never find
A resting place in pieces
In pieces
Pills, pills, I want my pills
I'll get your pills
But you must take your milk
No, no, no
Pills! I want my pills! Don't use me the milk! Don't use me the milk!
Milk! You need your milk! Your milk is good for you!
You can have your pills as long as you drink all your milk like a good little man!
No! The milk makes this strange! It makes everything go crazy! So I want my pills!
Oh, come here! Come on, drink it!
Drink it! There! That's not so bad now!
Come on, you little...
Fart!
Ha ha ha! Ha ha ha ha!
Ha!
Fart! Fart!
Fart!
Fart! Fart! Fart!
Fart! Fart!
Another piece by Trash there.
Band Trash sent by Reverend Cardboard Box.
Milk treatment with Bob.
And now, Norrell Preff.
Hey, all you rocket jockeys.
I've got something new and sensational to tell you about today.
Chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug.
Hi, hi.
Chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug.
Chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug.
Every large American city has a threat of coming.
It's an insidious thing, dangerous, and a little bit frightening.
We feel that the threat is more than frightening.
It's a menace.
It must be stamped out.
It gives you a queer feeling.
You wonder who's going to be next and why.
And you find yourself groping for this disease.
Hi.
Every large American city has a threat of coming.
It gives you a queer feeling.
And you find yourself groping for it.
Some well-known Hollywood celebrity.
It gives you a queer feeling.
Every large American city has a threat of coming.
And you find yourself groping for it.
Blonde secretary.
Knocking yourself out.
It gives you a queer feeling.
Well?
I am about to demonstrate that your theory is cocky.
And you find yourself groping for this disease.
Dr. Sinister is a sex god.
No, I'm not.
Oh my god, he's the first honest man.
Diogenes, hurry.
I am the god of chastity and celibacy.
And all that ridiculous stuff.
Of course.
Oh, I'm sure.
That's by...
That's voluntarily, right?
That's by choice, I'm sure.
As a matter of fact.
Yes and no.
But anyway, that's neither here nor there.
You modern day kids.
You'll do anything to be weird.
You're just being different just for the sake of being different.
You're going to take one more call here.
They want to tear things down, but they don't have any plan for building things back up.
Caller number three, you're on the air.
Hello, caller.
Well, we'll let you get back to your music.
I'm sorry.
All right.
Well, thank you for calling.
Thanks for calling.
Bye.
Hello.
Show me.
Oh, yeah.
I just wanted to let you know this is probably the funniest thing I've heard on the radio
in a long time.
The funniest thing you've heard on the radio in a long time?
Yeah.
It's hilarious.
Really?
Thanks.
Hey, you're totally welcome.
Thank you.
You should listen to this station more.
You'll hear more stuff that's even better than mine.
I do, but thanks.
Thanks a lot.
No problem.
Brighten my night.
It's my pleasure.
Because that's what I'm all about.
Dr. Sinister is here to brighten your night.
You understand?
And I'm not even going to cheat and use one of those UV black lights.
I'm going to use actual visible light to light up your night.
If you die first, I am definitely going to eat you.
The question is...
If I die, what are you going to do?
Bon apptit.
Friends, you are listening to the Subgenius Radio Ministry, hour of slack number 933.
You can get more information about the Church of the Subgenius from Post Office Box 204206,
Austin, Texas, 78722.
You can email me, stang, at subgenius.com.
You can check out www.subgenius.com, which has everything on it.
And you can send me tapes or CDs or whatnot at Post Office Box 181-417, Cleveland Heights, Ohio, 44118.
Praise...
Arb.
Okay, well, listen.
I'm going to take Arb.
Arb.
Before I go, I want to remind you that if you want to get stinking, laughing, puking,
falling down, pee your pants stewed, then old Uncle Bob's combination arthritis remedy
and snake bite curative is the booze for you.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
End of message.
To erase this message, press 7.
To save it, press...
Bob.