Bog.
And now, the tras-tras-tras-tras-tras-tras-tras-tras-tras-tras-tras-tras-tras
Genius Hour of Slack!
Little Neepy is still in Devo Land.
And now, dear friends, after the Devo Convention or the Devotional in Cleveland,
now it can be told we're all Devo.
And we all trade our weird-ass Devo cover tune copies.
The one just heard was a Bach cover by Mark Mothersbaugh and yours truly.
We have Occupant coming up, friends, which will follow.
This mix by Reverend Greg Cheatham.
People had to amuse themselves or die, you know, spiritually die.
So that's why the particular kind of music came out of there.
It's like an inward imaginative music.
You know, it obviously wasn't based on mainstream currents or big beat hard rock and roll.
It was more like little clicks and whirs.
Brainwaves.
Inward imaginative music.
Little clicks and whirs.
Brainwaves.
Polyrhythmic experimental sound.
Not even real drums.
Just a crude forerunner of electronic drums.
Filled by one of Mark's brothers.
You know, within the realm of music there were obviously influences from Bowie and Eno.
And even just more pure electronic composers.
Well, I kind of feel sorry for Jimmy.
Yeah, but you don't know the whole story.
He wasn't a nice guy.
What do you mean?
Let me tell you.
Jimmy's in a wheelchair and I don't care.
Jimmy's in a wheelchair.
He used to walk his dog.
Didn't beat him good.
Like his pretty wife.
Now they're up and gone.
Jimmy's in a wheelchair and I don't care.
Jimmy's in a wheelchair.
Jimmy's in a wheelchair and I don't care
Jimmy's in a wheelchair
He was the president
Of a company
He kept his work as far
As he liked to steal
But with justice strikes
Every once in a while
He makes a bullseye hit
He used to yell and scream
Until his son would cry
He used to spank his phone
But he don't spank his own
And he don't spank no more
Jimmy's in a wheelchair and I don't care
Jimmy's in a wheelchair
But he got big and fat
And he was rising high
Making lots of cash
Trashing all the slides
Trashing all the slides!
Oh, with justice strikes
Every once in a while
He makes a bullseye hit
Jimmy's in a wheelchair and I don't care
Jimmy's in a wheelchair
Jimmy's in a wheelchair covered by Occupant.
Friends, if you need to know more about Occupant, and you do,
check out www.mp3.com slash Occupant.
You know how to spell it.
Okay, here's the story.
But aren't you going to molest me some more?
Dr. Piper, Bob?
Climb right up here on my...
That's right, that's a good boy.
Climb right up here on my lap.
Now bend over.
I'm going to have to give you...
Oh, boy!
Oh, boy.
Can I have a kiss?
Can I have my spanking?
We're all people.
Come on, boys.
Come on over here.
The doctor's going to give you a good spanking
and teach you about Planet X.
We're just cannibal eggs.
Huh?
And so, the poor little children were abused and abandoned
by the evil doctor.
Left to their own devices,
there wasn't much left to eat but rat meat and sundaes for the week.
Some of the little boys resorted to crying
but they knew they had to be bigger than that.
They had to stand tough and swallow back their tears.
And speaking of Devo,
there is a, um, the third of the Devo conventions
or the devotional, 2002,
is coming up August 10th, all day, on Saturday,
at...
The Starwood Center, Cleveland, Ohio.
Um, yes, the, uh...
And that's, again, that's all day, August 10th.
I think there's...
I'm sure there's some kind of a charge for it.
It's great.
I was at the last two
and they've never been able to get any of the Devo's out there
except the first, from the very first order,
the earliest evolution,
the first ones to crawl out of the water,
Jim, Jungle Jim Mothersbaugh,
the little-known first,
drummer, uh, uh, as, is there, will be there,
was there last time,
he's actually a real funny guy,
and General Boy!
Yes, the progenitor and sire!
A, a friend and a brother.
A monkey and a robot.
Occupant O-C-C-U-P-A-N-T
I'm a mechanical man
to mechanical arms
to mechanical legs
I'm a...
I'm a two plus two equals four man
tsk-tsk-tsk-tsk
I'm a mechanical man
to mechanical arms
to mechanical legs
I'm a two plus two equals four man
I'm a
mechanical man
to mechanical arms
to mechanical legs
I'm a two plus two
equals four man
We build swell, we work well, and we want what you want.
You want, you want, you want, you want.
I'm a mechanical man, two mechanical arms, two mechanical legs.
I'm a two plus two equals four man.
Me feels swell, me work well Me want what you want
Me want what you want
Me feel swell, me work well Me want what you want
Baby give me home, I 의미 evenly
Me feels swell, me work well Me want what you want
What you want
Me feels well
Me work well
Me want what you want
Me feels well
Me work well
Me want what you want
Baby!
Me feels well
Thank you.
You've got, you've got, you've got, you've got, you've got, you've got, you've got, you've got, you've got.
Wait a second. Did you rip off your own arm as a joke?
Nay. Like most of your followers, I was maimed building the great brewery.
Mechanical Man was covered by Occupant. That's Reverend Onan Canobite and Reverend Mitch.
And now, Mark Mothersbaugh of Devo has a little fun with the pinkest creature known to Bob.
In this case, the drive-time rock station DJ.
You know, Bob, it's time for the 5.30 phone call.
And today, we have Mark Mothersbaugh.
From Devo on the phone. Hi, Mark.
Hi, Mighty Wah.
How's Devo these days?
Oh, busy, busy. We just finished an album.
I don't know if you've heard it yet or not.
Yeah, we're playing it.
Oh, you're playing it?
Yeah.
Oh, good. Well, then I'm going to have to buy a radio.
Yeah, it's Shout is the name of the new record.
That's right. Actually, for us, it's a real interesting album because
this is the first one where we gave up total control
and let someone else do it.
And let someone else direct it for the first time.
I don't know if you're familiar with the Church of the Subgenius,
but I made friends with them in the last three or four years,
became a reverend in the Church of the Subgenius,
and now Devo Incorporated is totally controlled by the Church of the Subgenius.
And Bob Dobbs, who is our spiritual leader, makes all the decisions now.
Well, actually, with a little help from Jimi Hendrix.
Yeah, in fact, you guys did a cover?
Yeah.
And you guys did a cover version of Are You Experienced on the new record, huh?
Yeah. It wasn't by choice, either.
This was a surprise to me, too.
We actually hadn't planned on putting that song on the record.
We had a couple other songs we were going to put on,
and we were in the studio, and it was late at night,
and who should appear in the room in this big purple gas cloud?
It really didn't smell very good.
It had that sickening sweet smell of LSD.
And, you know, I didn't recognize him at first,
but it was Jimi Hendrix, and he chased us around the room.
It was.
He told us we had to record Are You Experienced.
It wasn't by choice.
Well, that's a pretty tough order to say no to, I guess.
Well, actually, we were pretty happy with the way it came out,
so we did use it on the record.
Now, what about these neon green Chinese-American friendship suits?
Oh, well, that's easy to explain.
In the last couple of years,
since we put out Oh No, It's Devoe,
we did five world tours and five albums and 22 videos
all in about four and a half years.
And so about the end of 1982, we said, forget it.
And we dropped out.
We went underground, and we got jobs at a fast food restaurant.
No.
Well, they were the outfits, and they let us keep them.
Mm-hmm, I see.
They matched.
What have you been doing besides recording the new record?
Are you making any more movies?
Well, like I said, we dropped out.
We've grown our hair, although that's computer hair you see in the photo.
We all have long hair now, and we've kind of...
We had never...
To tell you the truth, we didn't have time for drugs back in the...
prior to 1982, and, well, we decided we'd experiment in the last couple years,
and things are a lot groovier and more far out for us than they've ever been before.
You guys took some time out to do a Devoe,
a Devoe endorsement for Honda, I know.
How was that?
Is that fun, making commercials?
Well, Church of the Subgenius, once again, they made us do it.
It wasn't by our own means.
Oh, I see.
It was all right.
They fed us once every day and, you know, let us out at night.
So it was okay.
Mark Mothersbaugh from Devoe is on the telephone at WLIR.
Two of the Hondas have wrecked already are the Hondas they gave us.
Really? Two of them?
I have to tell you that.
Oh.
Yeah.
On Long Island.
Actually, I know that.
You think I'm talking to you from Los Angeles,
but in reality I'm in that phone booth at the 7-Eleven around the corner.
Oh, yeah, I know that one.
Yeah.
Listen, Mark.
I'm just putting static noise over, so.
What I really want to know is, since this is an election year,
what's the candidate that Devoe is collectively endorsing?
Well, to tell you the truth,
we're in awful disarray.
I'm disappointed that Larry Flint dropped out of the running.
He had our vote.
Uh-huh.
You know, I don't know.
I think, you know, you have no other choice.
You know, there's really no way to vote, because Republican and Democrat, it's all the same
at this point in time.
Well, you could still put him in on the write-in ballot, I guess, you know.
Yeah, well, I think General Boy may get a few votes out of us.
Other than that, I don't know what to suggest.
I don't know what to suggest.
Ugh.
Gag onto me with a spoon.
Malachi, it's high time I laid down a few commandments.
You got a chisel?
Take this down.
Oh, that's what I say, because that's what the word of Bob says.
I'll tell you, friend.
There's no slack.
I'll tell you, in this world, in this flesh, in this devil, there's no slack.
And if you can't whoop it, go ye down, my friend.
That's what I said.
Go ye down.
There's nothing that says you can't.
The devil don't have a rule book.
That's right.
The devil.
The devil does not have a rule book.
He is not humanistic.
He is not pacifistic.
And he owes you money, my friend.
That's right.
The devil owes you money.
And so does Uncle Sam.
You have to recognize the devil just like you recognize Uncle Sam.
Now, I'm going down there to pay taxes.
As far as I'm concerned, I might as well be paying taxes to the devil.
I'm sorry, but that's just the way things are.
It's a test of faith.
And that's why God put the devil down here to see if you can tell the difference between the devil and Uncle Sam.
Let there be slack.
My lord, the infidels on your back no longer believe in you.
They say their prayers go unheeded.
Of course they're unheeded.
How am I supposed to hear prayers coming out of my ass?
They talk of war against the faithful.
I beseech thee, rise up against them.
Smite someone who deserves it for once.
Malachi, every time I interfere, I only make things worse.
You're best off solving your own problems.
But, but Metalodeon...
My lord, what part of nay dothn't thou understand?
Armageddon!
Who says that I didn't?
Now, join me, Screamy Ted Horne, dude!
Screamy Ted Horne
We interrupt this program before the sound of the...
...the alarm of our naval unit's speed.
A large object traveling at supersonic speed is headed over the North Atlantic towards the
east coast of the United States.
Armageddon!
It's what we call a global killer.
The end of mankind.
Doesn't matter where it hits.
Nothing would survive, not even bacteria.
Armageddon!
The team from CX Massive Recommend Alert might recommend Alert 1.
The more you make a big deal out of denying something, the more possible it is to get
the most out of it.
The more people think it must be true.
You're on the air, Laurie.
If you read the Bible, Mark, you'd know that there won't be another thousand years.
Right now, we're in the last days as foretold in the Book of Revelations.
The last days?
You mean the coming of the apocalypse, right?
The rapture?
You only have to look at the signs.
There are wars and rumors of wars that...
Now, just so the rest of us know how much time is left, when is the rapture supposed
to hit?
Exactly.
Is it midnight New Year's Eve?
That's right.
Now, is that midnight L.A. time or Eastern Standard Time or what?
I mean, you're not going to be able to tell me what time it is.
What time zone has God in, anyway?
I pray for you all.
These people are nuts!
Skybird, this is Dropkick with a red dash alpha message in two parts.
Break, break.
Stand by for mind control.
Prepare yourselves for destruction!
Don't be crazy, Mr. Boy.
The best way to take our minds off the smell of burning flesh is to begin tonight's karaoke
contest.
I got a finger tune song now.
Do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do,
do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do,
As I was saying, the universe is just doomed.
Doomed.
Doom!
Just watch, guys.
It's time to embrace the horror.
Look, we got Fun Road tickets to the end of the Earth.
There's a 68.71% chance you're right.
That's the fact.
Yeah.
Just a minute, ladies and gentlemen.
I think something is happening.
Though I walk through the valley of the shadow of death, I will fear no evil.
It's seen him.
Thou anointest my head with oil, my cup runneth over.
And I will dwell in the house of the Lord forever.
It's a night zone that we don't know anything about, and I think we ought to stay clear.
See that the humans remain entertained until the end.
Armageddon, a mix by our friend Reverend DJ Epoch.
That's not E-popped, but E-pock.
It's all American, friends, and it's weird.
All Ameri-key.
Bob loves you.
Have any favorite Bob songs?
God, it's unbelievable.
The Bob Spangled Banner by Professor Mark Mothersbaugh of Devo.
And now in the patriotic spirit, to continue that spirit, the Rainmakers with Government Cheese.
Bust out the windows, put his family on food stamps.
Now he's a big spender, no food on the table and the bills ain't paid.
Cause he's spending on cigarettes and PGA.
They'll turn us all into beggars cause they're easier to please.
They're feeding our people that government cheese.
Give a man freedom.
He'll eat food and he'll figure out a way to steal more than he can eat.
Cause he doesn't have to pay.
Give a woman free kids and you'll find them in the dirt.
Learning how to carry on the family line of work.
It's the man in the White House, the man under the steeple.
Passing out drugs to the American people.
I don't believe in anything.
Nothing is free.
They're feeding our people that government cheese.
Cheese.
Government.
Get out!
Decline.
Fall.
Decline and fall.
Fall down baby.
Fall.
Fall way down there.
Decline and fall.
Come on.
Fall down little mama.
Decline and fall.
Oh, decline and fall.
Give a man a free ticket on a dead end ride.
And you climb in the back even though nobody's driving.
Too god damn lazy to crawl out of the wreck.
And you ride a rally,
waits up for the welfare check.
Gone to hell in a handbag.
Can't you see I ain't gonna eat no government cheese?
No government cheese.
No cheese.
And I'm hovering like a fly
Waiting for the windshield on the freeway
That's too realistic for me, guys.
Oh, that's cool the way he does it.
Yeah, but that's, that's nihilistic.
You know what I mean?
That's anti-chromatic.
That's re-fistulating.
That's totally imbibed, I think, if it's not drunk already.
You're gripping onto the waves of life and riding forward as fast as you can, right?
You don't want to sink down into that gray, neutral nothingness of squared-off, murky plainness and ordinariness.
You want to dive for the heights and float down to the lowest lows.
That means waiting for the windshield like a fly on the freeway.
Manic depressive.
Wait.
Waiting for the bus.
For the ups.
In the middle of the...
And downs.
Road.
The ups and downs are the number seven.
The ups and downs are the cross sound B.
The ups and downs are getting on without the change, right?
Getting up and down, getting...
They didn't tell me to take those pills, but I didn't take them anyway.
Bye.
I love you.
Let there
be light!
Yippee!
You're the best!
I got it, I got it!
Um, when you're writing the Bible, you might want to omit that last miracle.
That's right, doctor, this is how it be.
I can see you, but you can't see me.
That's right, doctor, now it's up to you.
Here's the gift of freedom, you know what to do.
Huh? Oh, yes, I remember.
Don't think I forgot.
I was having a little party the night that you were shot.
Shot right in the brain cells so that all that stuff came out.
All the evil ranting that you never knew about.
Yes, yes, the ranting.
That evil twist of fate.
Faces you thought you could never do, but now you have the hate.
Oh, that's right, doctor, soon there'll come a day
when all the rational civilized thoughts have gone away.
That's right, doctor.
That's right.
Yeah.
That's right, doctor.
That's right.
Yeah.
Oh.
That's right, doctor.
Yes, that is right, doctor.
You heard what I said.
We must watch TV
to hold our eyeballs to the rib.
That's right, doctor.
We must see other laws.
We must show our incompetence.
That ain't all I've got.
The walls are closing in.
The room is getting small.
I don't know where you've been.
It's too late to talk.
That's right, doctor.
Doctor.
That's right, doctor,こだ Dante, dr.
He's got a, he's got a doctor.
Doctor, doctor.
He goes right, doctor.
Doctor.
That's right, Doctor.
By Reverend Doctor
Hodge, Uncle Onan's
Wotan Band.
Onan Canobite
and Mitch there.
Praise
above.
Finding God. That's important, yeah.
But you know what might be a treat for everyone?
If you let me use the telescope to find my
lost friend Bender. I don't
know what to say other than
absolutely not. Your loss is
a tragedy, but our work is...
Come on. You guys have forever to look for God.
All I'm asking is one measly lifetime
to find my friend.
He speaks out of love for his friend.
Perhaps that love in his heart is
God. Oh, how convenient.
A theory about God
that doesn't require looking through a telescope.
Get back to work.
...
Thank you.
Gone two years and I don't know why
Now I'm happy all the time
I can't think I'm feeling fine
I've got feelings they don't show
Don't ask me, I don't know
Don't, don't, don't
All of us
You've heard this all before
Now here comes
Gonna hear some more
I know a place where dreams are crushed
Hope you're smashed
That ain't much
Are you stupid anyway?
We're all gonna die someday
Yeah, yeah, yeah
All of us
All the past
I live off my fucking
All of us
By Gajetto
Yes friends, Gajetto, Will Black
Performed at the devotional
And that song, All of Us, believe it or not
Is a really ancient Devo song
Before any of their albums came out
And
As we sign off for this week
The King
As I walk through
This wicked world
Searching for light
In the darkness
Of insanity
I ask myself
Is all hope lost
Is there only pain
And hatred
And misery
And each time I feel like
There's one thing I want to know
What's so funny about
This love and understanding
Oh
And as I walk on through troubled times, my spirit gets so downhearted sometimes.
So where I'd have gone and who I'd have trusted, where is the harmony, sweet harmony?
Cause each time I feel it slip away, it just makes me wanna cry.
What's so fun about peace, love, and understanding?
Sweet harmony.
Cause each time I feel it slip away, it just makes me wanna cry.
What's so fun about peace, love, and understanding?
Yeah.
Uh, they're dead.
All dead.
Who would have known playing God could have such terrible consequences?
Uh, yeah.
Yeah.
Ha ha ha ha!
Elvis did What's So Funny About Peace, Love, and Understanding?
And we have another classic Costello song coming up, after Mark Mothersbaugh once again encounters
the pink boy.
We've had a lot of Devo fans calling in the radio station all day long, Mark.
So I have to ask you, when is Devo coming to the New York area?
And uh, do you have any plans to come by and do some gigs around here?
yeah we'll be going between texas and la though for the next three months we'll be
hopefully we're going to make a video album that's our plans we're working with the church
of the subgenius they're located in dallas so we'll be flying back and forth and we'll do an
are you experienced video first um i don't know if it'll be out for halloween i think it'll be a
week or two after that but then i'll we'll do a video album between now and the end of the year
and hopefully by the first of the year we'll be able to make definite plans for a world tour
okay and probably start on the east coast well good all right well listen uh mark mothersbaugh
thank you very much and good luck with the new devo album which is called shout oh thank you
uh sure yeah mark before you go um do you know what the station is that dares to be different
i sure do w all right thank you mark
radio advised with every one of those late night stations playing songs bringing tears to my eyes
i was seriously thinking about hiding the receiver when the switch broke because it's old
they're saying things that i can hardly believe they really think we're getting out of control
radio is the sound salvation radio is cleaning up the nation
the
you better listen to the vice of reason
but they don't give you any choice because they think that it's treason
so you had better do as you were told you better listen to the radio
i want to bite the hand that feeds me i want to bite that hand so badly
i want to bite that hand so badly
i want to Make them wish they'd never seen me
some of my friends sit around every evening and they worry about the times ahead
But everybody else is overwhelmed By indifference and the promise of an early bed
you either shut up or get cut out they don't wanna hear about it
Sony inches on the reel to reel
and the radio was in the hands of
such a lot of fools trying to an expertise
to un denk
The way that you can hear your radio is the sound of salvation.
Radio is cleaning up the nation.
They say you better listen to the vice of reason.
They don't give you any choice because they think that it's treason.
So you had better do what you were told.
You better listen to the radio.
What a fall, baby.
My bless you, baby.
And there's the Devo convention coming up also.
And the Devo the next day.
Devo convention here.
It's in August.
Mass baptism.
You said there was going to be a mass baptism.
August 15th.
Reverend Ivan Stang.
Hellfire preaching by Reverend Ivan Stang.
Dr. Katahdin.
And Dr. Onan Kanobai.
He's coming out from Portland.
Yep.
Wow.
Yes.
It'll be good to see Onan.
He's a fellow rocketeer.
Yes.
He's a rocket man.
He's the oldest, youngest of genius doctors.
And St. Ann and Helen the handbasket.
She rocked.
I thought she was right on the mark singing her songs.
I thought for once.
That's going to be August 11th.
She not only nailed it.
But went into some sort of starter.
At the maximum level.
In Akron.
August 11th in Akron.
It's 207 South Main Street.
Yeah.
You could know about that.
Where the rubber meets the toads.
The day before that here in Cleveland is the devotional.
Devotional.
2002.
At the Starwood Center.
712 East 185th Street.
What time is that?
There's going to be a mass baptism.
Isn't that at that event?
That's all day.
That's like all day Saturday.
A general boy.
Just head down to the Starwood Center.
All day long.
Will be there.
The sire.
The progenitor.
Of all the devos.
Jim.
August 10th.
Jim Mothersbaugh.
And if it's like last year, there'll be home videos that Mark Mothersbaugh sends.
Well, this is Sunday.
I hope all the subgeniuses come out on a Sunday night.
After all, don't they all go to church on Sunday?
After the show.
Akron, man.
And have a big fat old chicken dinner underneath the city.
Rubber City.
Eight miles high.
And when you touch down.
You'll find that.
It's.
Stranger than no.
Signs in the sea.
That say where you're going.
Are somewhere.
Just being there all alone.
Nowhere is.
There a walk to be found.
A man who's afraid of losing their ground.
Way, way down.
Known for its sound.
In places.
Small places.
And now.
.
I see.
The.
Man 제가.
I should've said told me before my parents left me alone.
Actually simply the people.
City.
And I hated it.
I slept.
For a living.
Who doesn't have it all.
Yeah.
guitar solo
Down the stairs
A little store
Some laughing
Some just shameless
Boys
Sidewalks
And black men
Some laughing
Some standing
Alone
guitar solo
Eight miles high
by the birds.
Yes, the old-fashioned birds with a Y.
Friends, you're listening to the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack
with Doctors for Bob in the background.
You must write for free information if you don't already have that.
Or you can check www.subgenius.com
But, but, you can still write.
Write to Bob and request that information from
Post Office Box
204-206 Austin, Texas
Ah, yes, once again, that's Bob at Post Office Box
Ah, yes
Boy, oh boy
Boy, a boy
Too late I realized that me children are me only real treasures.
Bob 911