This is Dr. Howell,
railing in the night for that which lived, which is dead,
and for that which is dead, was dead, and in fact was never alive.
So we're moving.
We get back to that.
Thickering of the...
We'll just turn that down.
We don't want any of that stuff happening here.
In the swamp bongs the gongs of a throng of frogs,
while a knee-deep sheep bleats in a slippery stream
where slimy snakes whisper sinful secrets.
Let's go back to the knee-deep sheep dip, okay?
The knee-deep sheep dip dipped deep down below
the steep and chilly waters of the deep stream
floats on the surface
like the ancient Egyptians floated on the current of their belief,
for they thought they would never die,
but be reborn as gargling sarcophagi,
horrible mummies to march across the earth
and wreak and spew vengeance.
Give me the pyroflagellator.
All of the little tiny...
Yes.
...deities march down the side of the subgenius church
and now...
See it at last.
Within the great pyramid,
the secret chamber of the subgenius...
My God.
What light and steam come from the special effects department
located below the pyramid?
I hate Bob.
Bob made my daddy go crazy.
My daddy used to make money,
but now he just sits around all day.
I hate Bob.
He's a bad man.
I wish he would die.
He's part of the conspiracy.
I can't live this.
You've just been being...
Oh, I can't help myself.
My kids need black poop.
Eternal salvation
or triple your money back.
The Church of the Subgenius
bring you another 33 minutes
of condensed gargling function.
Over the quality audio-visual techniques
exacerbated and complicated
by the Church of the Subgenius.
Copyright 1985-86.
Oh, Dr. Sprit.
She said,
cutting her own legs off
in what was to be the foment
of a startling new trend
among the so-called...
...so-called...
...punk-detel-a-hantia.
Should any other shows
be heard from or contacted
in the course of this show,
the listener is advised
to remain calm
and only contact listed
or unlisted officials
in the event of any material
from this radio
or other listening device
being inhaled during broadcast.
Small animals or other children
becoming exposed
to the ultra-high
or ultra-low shocks
and brain frequencies
constantly scanned
throughout our program
should seek shelter
in an approved safety unit only.
This is Walter Teasdale
reminding you
that it's often a photon
that light releases,
but truth is,
not everyone gets the picture.
Hoping your time is all time
and all your unpervisable truths
are happy truths.
Happy truths.
Here is your host,
Reverend Ivan Stang here,
dear friends,
and let's sort out
all these little wellman heads
and cassettes and things
so that we know
what's up and what's about.
And friends,
it's about New Year's Eve.
Not when you hear this,
I'm sure.
But tonight,
as I record this show
in the offices here,
it is indeed
New Year's Eve.
And actually,
for us, friends,
it is not a new year,
but a last,
the last year.
Happy last year.
Happy, happy, happy last year.
All you good subgeniuses.
Actually, I guess for the,
those of us who are saved,
dues-paying subgenius ministers,
we will be lifted up
aboard the escape vessels
of the sex goddesses
on July 5th, 1998.
And everything will be cool.
But,
for the rest of you,
why I just,
I just don't know.
I don't know what to tell you.
Enjoy this January.
It'll be your last January.
Enjoy February.
Enjoy Easter.
This will be the last time
that funny little Easter bunny
comes hip-hop-hopping
down that bunny trail,
friends.
And the 4th of July,
you better enjoy
those nice, pretty fireworks
because there'll be
even prettier fireworks
fireworks.
So, mayhaps,
mayhaps, perhaps,
not,
yay, so nice.
Ehh, we'll see.
We don't know.
We just don't know.
But let's see what,
what we said the last time.
I, I can scarcely remember myself.
200 days, huh?
A form of confusion.
290 days.
200 days.
200 days from today.
200 more?
Mm.
That's all.
200 rock-solid days
of expectation and angst, nausea.
You just waiting for them
little babies to come down
and pull us out of here.
So there ain't really much
more to do, huh, Ivan?
We just sort of, you know,
we've, we've told all the jokes
we know to tell.
We've, you know.
Vestnary age.
Well, at this point, it's,
it's like if we, if we really
wanted to impress Bob,
we might, uh, try to take
over the world and, you know,
make the new world order
ourselves instead of letting
the pinks do it and so forth,
you know, but generally, as it,
as predicted in Book of the
Subgenius, we would go out and
recruit half of the globe and so
forth, but, you know, really,
with only 200 days left, I, I
don't see much point in
bothering with it.
It seems to be,
Yeah, it's kind of, it's kind
of.
that at this point, we can
just sit back and wait for the
exes.
Right.
To get here and go ahead
and, oh, they're gonna do,
they're gonna do a better job
of it, of the genociding and,
and so forth that, that we could
ever do.
Right.
That's what we're
Well, that's what we're
gonna do.
The Church of the Subgenius.
Normals are our competitors,
only until they become our
customers.
All right.
This is my story.
It's sad and long, involving
Naugahyde, sawdust, six guns,
and whiskey, but I ain't got
time to tell it to you now.
Well, I was driving in my
pickup truck when I looked up
and saw some lights.
There were thousands of flying
saucers destroying everything
in sight.
And the next thing I knew, I
was barbecuing, screaming
wouldn't help at all.
I was gonna send $30 to Bob,
but I just didn't have the balls.
But now, X Day is here.
You're being lynched by a mob.
X Day is here.
Don't you wish you'd sent a
check to Bob?
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob,
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
Ruby, has one of those
subscribers with that
nasty hair style.
I thought, is that baby
needy?
Hit 911, or
did your sidemiego go?
What did he come by
Louder, that's my man,
Louderly.
I had to go down to
the tune Allahu
Ku, they bring my
switch, I'll just
I thought they were pretty funny, but deep down I thought I was gonna have the last laugh because I wouldn't send Bob any money
But now they're off somewhere in those pleasure crafts
And I've been reduced to cosmic feces and it's much much too late to understand that they are the chosen species
Cuz X-Day is here, you're looking mighty glum
X-Day is here, don't you wish your daddy had more Yeti in his car
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, they hail from Lafayette, LA
they don't even hear this show
and yet they sent this tag Maybe they hear it on the internet or something
You can hear it anytime on the Internet
or on Sunday nights at 9 o'clock EST
on WC. s B dot or
WW WCSB
dot org.
And that's in audio active.
We have it on the sub site
in real audio.
Friends,
1998.
I can't believe it.
I can barely believe
that I lived to 1998.
I used to think of 1970
as the future.
Damn, yeah, back in the day.
Oh, by the way,
this music in the background is by
Seva.
The artist formerly known as Commander Dave,
now he's called Seva.
Oral surrealisms
in this CD
called Gravity Is My
Favorite Drug.
And it was sent to us
by Reverend Preacher in Knoxville,
Tennessee, but I don't know any real
details about it. So quality,
you have weird
freak out acid jazz background
music.
Dear friends, there's been,
these are the end times
and we're not the only cult,
so to, as they
say, we're a lot bigger than a cult
now, you know, friends.
There are a lot more
subgeniuses than there ever were
Branch Davidians or
members of the People's Temple.
How's that?
We got some records
to break. I understand that.
It ain't gonna be easy, but
well, it will be easy.
It'll be real easy come July 5th, 1998.
But there are others, friends, other cults
out there that, you know,
this millennialism is coming on
and I don't know about you,
but I've been boning up
on millennialism since,
well, for 20 years.
And now every time I open a magazine
or look at the newspaper, there's an article
about the turn of
the millennium.
Weird. End of the world cults.
How correct are their prophecies?
Will the Earth really be destroyed
by asteroids, tornadoes,
or giant Gila monsters?
On March 25th
of 1998,
God will appear on Channel
18 all over
the contiguous United
States. Every city,
no matter whether you have a Channel 18
or not, turn to Channel 18. It's called
Dead Series, by the way.
God will
appear and will announce
and as this man,
has already announced, that
God will come to Earth
in Dallas, Texas at
10 a.m.
March 31st.
God will appear and if he doesn't,
this preacher, this Chinese preacher
will kill himself.
Then he's saying the appearance of God will take time
at the appearance of the sign of the Ramses.
And I'm surprised
this hasn't made national news.
I first heard of it on the internet
and then the local news
people pounced on it.
Going, oh, great, another
saucer cult
dropped the body.
Yes, dear friends, there was, yes, the other
saucer cult here in Dallas that made
the news. Here's from the Dallas Morning News.
The white-clothed
cowboy-hatted people
have been good neighbors, area residents
say. They drive nice cars,
including Lexuses and
Mercedes-Eazys, keep their homes
and yards neat and cause no
trouble.
Their beliefs are unconventional.
At a news conference Tuesday,
they introduced two young boys as
the reincarnations of Jesus Christ
and Buddha. But
neighbors say that hasn't bothered them either.
Actually, there were some fun
clips on the local news
of these old po-buckers going,
well, you know,
maybe they're right. If they're right,
then I guess they're gonna have the
last laugh.
In the last week, however,
the group of 160
believers that calls itself
Chen Dao, or the True Way,
has been besieged by media attention
after rumors spread that its members might
commit mass suicide
in the manner
of the Heaven's Gate cult in San
Diego earlier this year, and the
Church of the Subgenius later on.
What? We're not... But subgenius members
say that isn't true. They do not plan to
kill themselves, and in fact, so revere
life that they are vegetarians
who only eat frop,
which grows on the droppings
of their abominable
snowman ancestors, they claim.
They say they have come to Garland.
This is where King of the Hill is based
on, friends. Garland,
which is where I live, which
their leader calls Godland,
to watch God come
to Earth and turn into a human being.
This, they say, will happen at exactly
10 a.m., March 31st,
at the home of
the crazy
old Chinese feller,
their Taiwanese guy.
And, uh,
their teacher, Hou Ming Chen,
a former college social sciences
professor from southern Taiwan.
So, friends, we are
just so full of
saucer calls and...
Let's see. We'll pull down the
save here a little bit in the background.
And, uh,
the...
Mr. Chen said, uh...
Oh, he introduced these two boys. He had a big
press conference in the driveway of his big
house, and he introduced these two
little chubby boys. One is,
uh, ages 10 and 9, and one is
Jesus, and one is Buddha. Now, I know,
I mean, needless to say,
this is a false Jesus, and probably
a false Buddha. We've got a Jesus,
and I've been thinking, maybe we ought to get
a Buddha, too, but, uh, they
say here, um,
uh,
the next-door neighbor, Charles
Amix, asked whether he should worry
that his life was in danger, since he doesn't
believe in Chen Dao.
You have the right to express yourself, Mr.
Chen replied. It doesn't matter.
Whether you believe or not.
The TV coverage is worse than these
nice neighbors.
They're lovely people.
Um, they're not
a whole lot different from any Christian belief
as far as God returning to Earth.
If they're right, we're all gonna look like
fools, now, ain't we?
So, Garland,
Texas, is the land of
God, because it sounds like
Godland.
And...
Come on, come on.
She may or might not love Santa.
Yeah, is that part of the subject? You got, like,
he's She-male Santa's going around? We've been seeing him in the malls.
She-male Santa?
No, he's She-male Santa.
She-male Santa.
She-Man.
Oh man, chicks with...
Yeah, right, you got it.
You get to, you know, impress a hot, jolly elf, and at the same time you're thinking about Pop-Tarts.
If you alone just get naked to make a sexy surprise,
don't say it's not so wrong.
To the girls who turn you down,
it always feels better, especially if you squeeze your stomach in with straps and don't...
Get out of the way!
Yeah.
Could you describe that? What happens to Timmy? We won't tell about Billy.
Well, it all started when Timmy had to tinkle.
He was visiting Niagara Falls and he felt an overwhelming urge.
Unfortunately, he didn't realize he was near a giant hydroelectric power box.
And the droplets connected him with the cosmic pulse which surges through the universe.
For a brief moment, Billy, or rather Timmy, was one with the stuff of the cosmos.
All the force of an exploding stuff.
And all of a sudden, Billy becomes the cosmos.
Yep, he became all over the cosmos. It was one titanic blast.
Oh, there it is.
A blast of the past.
It shook the whole station. Did you feel it?
And the entire state went into a...
Got a little one there.
I think we had an earthquake.
Four to five, it's a little earthquake.
A earthquake?
Gotta go check for sheer bolts.
I'm going to.
Hey, I'm not joking. It really did happen because we talked about a forbidden thing,
and our elders warned us not to bring that up on the show.
I think we're gonna have an...
Actually, you know, what's that next to the war starting right now, across to the other side of the world?
Did you feel that little temblor that we just experienced?
No, I didn't feel anything at all.
You know, that's something we've often discussed.
What if we're here doing our usual line of bibble babble that we like to bibble babble,
and something does happen, you know, we'll be the only people on the air who have to report to the world the onset of World War III.
It'll be perfectly evident as dream come true because we'll have it all on tape.
Yes, but only until the next EMP, the big electromagnetic pulse...
That's right.
...wipes the slate clean once we're gone.
Yeah, that's right.
And it's all just so much blank tape.
That's where I was talking to Trevor about that today, a couple days ago.
Now let's have less name dropping, please.
That's puzzling evidence. He's not worried about the heat blast or the radiation or anything.
It's the EMP that's gonna really screw him up.
Just the MPs. The MPs that are coming to screw him up.
Oh yeah, the MPs will come trotting in and confiscate all those blank tapes, yeah.
Listen, Parliament can't do that unless it's approved by two-thirds of the majority.
Yeah, Parliament gives you extra margin.
Good evening. You're on the air.
I'm on KBFA with Frank Zappa.
Uh, yeah, hi Frank. Greetings from the subgenius church.
Oh yeah, good.
Thanks for holding me.
How is old Bob?
Oh, he's doing good. He sends his regards.
You know one of the best things about Bob?
What's that?
He's a smoker.
Yeah. Yeah, a frop all the way.
Well, not really, but...
Brothers and sisters, this has been Prozac Free Radio.
Copyright 1997, the Subgenius Foundation and the EMP.
All rights reserved.
No animals were harmed during the taping of this show.
And it was a stray and it didn't have a collar on it.
It was a little black and white dog.
And so I threw it in the trunk of the car.
And I brought it home and I've been feeding it only the best food so it'll get fattened up real good.
So come this Thanksgiving, well, we can take it out to that old stump in the backyard and take out the hatchet.
Was that that thing that you had in the little crate that you wouldn't even allow to move around so that it wouldn't build up any muscle?
It'd just build up nice big dog fat?
That's right. That's the one, man. The one I keep in the dark, cold room.
Oh, the dog veal.
Yes.
It kind of smells because I never clean up after it or anything.
Well, we took the dog tags off of this fine specimen that we gave the roadkill to.
And we're trying to track down the owner so that we can sue for, you know, the damages they did to our car and the others.
So far we know it's someone named Ronnie.
But we haven't got the last name yet.
It's one of those vet numbers.
And the vet says his records are incomplete.
And he was angry that we called this late at night.
Yeah, he has better things to do.
But we'll get hold of this Ronnie character to make sure that we settle up our accounts.
Oh, yeah, we'll settle up accounts with old Ronnie.
Yeah, we hate a budget deficit with anyone named Ronnie.
We hate to leave it hanging.
Much like the carcass will be hanging out on my porch so that the blood drains from it real good.
So when I can take it in and dress it up and...
Make them little sausages out of it.
We'll see whose bark is worse than their bite when we meet up with Ronnie.
Yeah, I've been slaughtering my own animals since I was 12.
Used to be I did it for food, but now I just do it for fun.
Well, you know, at the Papa Joe Mama Risk-Free Wildlife Hunting Service Reserve,
we basically are trying to also recycle the animals that we use in the experimentation.
But you kind of forget that the animals are better for health.
And I'll say truthfully, all my works were for washing,
a year days .
Is it the same thing you do in the 2020s?
Yup, yeah.
See?
We'll be right back.
So it is all colors.
How about a hot tamale?
Warm and good.
How about hot buttered rum cake?
Taste a piece of pizza pizza.
Ten minutes till showtime.
Checking Bozo Boost.
Actually, yeah, Bozo Boost.
All right.
Check up Bozo Boost.
Here we go.
Old Father Time is giving back to his guy.
0-3-0-0.
53 minutes till showtime.
This is Boost.
Okay.
Now hold Boost off until.
0-3-0-0 off.
I'll boost you, young man.
Okay.
We need the Bozo Boost.
At that point, we will launch Bozo Boost.
Okay.
Say, I noticed you had kind of big shoes.
Yeah.
Those are Dr. Spob shoes.
Now, Changer, didn't you go into space once?
I am in space.
Using Bozo Boost?
Oh, okay.
Man, that cat's so far out, he's going to need a space cat to get back.
Man, you are way over the top.
Yeah, he's from All Right Village, I think.
Man.
You haven't seen the top, baby.
He's using the little Bozo Boost nose horn.
Are you looking for Boscus?
I'm a juice dog, Daddy.
Make me tingle.
I think you got that from St. Stupid.
Ground Control to Major Tom.
You really made the grade, and the papers want to know whose shirt you're wearing.
Over.
Do you copy?
Are you looking for Boscus?
Uh-oh.
There we go.
Cheap radio effects.
We've contacted space.
And we're flying high.
Music from the hearts of space.
This show is going to be beamed out into outer space.
Down.
We're having the hearts of.
Let us say.
Salad.
And of course, we're having iceberg lettuce for record.
We're scaring the UFOs away from invading us.
98% of the iceberg lettuce is below the surface.
We realize there's no intelligent life on the planet.
Well, they said that Chuck Berry, and both Chuck Berry and Johnny Cash, both shared the
mystic delights of a spastic colon over many a hardcore Pepsi and a Moon Pie.
And Brother Dave Gardner, who I say used to sleep in Stan's basement, also used to.
Oh yeah.
He was doing these damned verloren
Justifying one another.
All right.
Don.
space my people will follow the vanishing race she's vanishing race of course is the human race
is this the new religion based on the apollo space missions or is it the vapid attempts of some
misocular that's my new religion in the darkest parts of military intelligence and all these
other things who wanted to break this space and head off somewhere where we can't really go
one year my grandfather broiled his own foot
very good man the vanishing race see that's the spastic colon
there
is
i
think that's a psychomimetic device implanted by linens over here check these words out everything's
true dave everything's true but it's also damn false charles what can we do everything everything
is true i don't know why to me to me as we're caught everything's false everything's true
there's nothing you can believe in everything's true what do you believe this time of year you
know you didn't go sit on sanders lap did you no i haven't done that in
four days i give that up you know what i'm saying i'm a grown man i don't need the soft warm fudge of
a oven of an aging duplexer right i mean look what satan was doing satan was looking out for god he
was saying look hey man don't do this god don't do this because if you do this then you're going to
make it work nobody needs you anymore what's going to happen all the moon rovers on x day
yeah where they think they're going i want one you might get one next christmas yeah
that'd be weird or the the jettisoned lunar modules that have crashed landed back onto the
surface of the moon you don't want the oral defecations of the spud monkeys because those
those people when they release evacuations whole civilizations tumble down the whole
the visigoths that's why the visigoths don't believe in jesus and that's why they do not to
this day celebrate christmas see you said it yourself when you were in your sleep remember
that one time you were dying for me to heat you up with morphine instead i took it all myself in those pyramids
yeah the one that when you thought you were hallucinating the pyramids and you said why
is jesus and i couldn't say hey look man i they were you know i don't know apologetics
they were cool pyramids yeah they were blue they were vibrating blue man that's cool
floating around in your hair well i don't know i didn't see you describe it to me man what am i
talking about i am hallucinating blue pyramids you did though i did in my mind's eye james i might
have got me into it we all hallucinate the blue pyramid i thought you were dying there though bro
that's how you know you've achieved it that's that's when you reach the final bardo
is when you see and you see bridget the blue pyramid you see bridget bardo in her first movie
and she's wearing a pair of uh overheated wax wax wax panties bridget bardo but you know when we get
into layering like this what are some of the real christians supposed to believe they call in they
listen in they think it's a sub like as they were calling on them previous projects a sub gump
the church is sub growing a little thing yeah hey yeah but we're staying the reverend ivan stang
yes
blue johnny cash had the vision he knows about eurasia blue man he he knew too much about
eurasia blue and the spastic yeah he's a rare visionary he follows the banishing right vanishing
race into the space disappear into space i think it's pretty obvious it's the apollo mission this
xa it's uh it's the the cheyenne red
the ah the crisp
was this
seek
i
south
But
That here's a million months ago.
So this is unable to play Misery, so now if I pretty plush, this one was missing because them
that we are going from the convenience store.
They came and they got me.
They rescued me, Dave came and got me.
Dave, man, that suit of armor you got,
it's like it gives you superpowers.
Yeah, but he jumped out the window.
Yeah, you said Dave, you took the butt farmer
and he's eating a chip out of Dave.
And that white horse.
Yes.
We'll do credits, dear friends.
Let's see.
Starting from the beginning.
Well, we've had a bunch of Einstein's Secret Orchestra
from WCSB in Cleveland.
That's Lonesome Cowboy Dave and Chaz Smith
and in this case, Princess We Are Doe
and yours truly, Reverend Ivan Stang.
We've heard lots of bits and pieces
out of KPFA subgenius show from Berkeley,
the best of the sub G show,
number five, the Phineas Narco edit,
with Dr. Howell and Puzzling Evidence.
And we also heard KPFA show with Janer Hypercleets
from August 8th, no, 889, 97.
I have trouble with human dates.
This is, it's 880BX, okay?
Janer Hypercleets in space.
We heard some Prozac free radio with Dr. Legume
and Papa Joe Mama special guest and Reverend Ed Strange.
We heard some,
Frank Zappa, Salute Bob.
We heard about the occult in Garland
and in the background here, we have a saver,
formerly Commander Dave,
and the Gravity is a Drug CD.
Thank y'all.
The Church of the Subgenius
will sleep for you when you're too tired.
We'll be right back.
Y'all be driving around
these big expensive pink Cadillacs.
I know somehow you've been supplementing your income
by what y'all been growing in your backyard.
Now, those of you that want to contribute to the Church,
wrap up some of that in a plastic bag
and send it on up here to the pool pit.
Praise Bob.
Brother Tyrone.
I wandered around in Bulldada.
Not knowing just what it was, it was.
Then in a dream I seen Bobby.
And he cast out the prophets that are false.
And now I'm sleeping with Bobby.
Sleeping with Bobby.
Sleeping with Bobby by my side.
Sleeping with Bobby, baby, bye.
Yes, I've been sleeping with Bobby.
Sleeping with Bobby.
Sleeping with Bobby by my side.
Sleeping with Bobby, baby, bye.
Thank you.
Be seated, everybody.
Now, we has got a problem with the church across the street.
The Church of the Divine Christian Licking Saints of Science.
The preacher called me last week.
He said they had purchased a brand new manger scene from the Walmart.
They put it on the front of the church there.
And our own sister, my hair, your hump dog, Rover,
keep going over there urinating on it.
I told them to slack off.
Brother Tyrone.
I thought that all dogs went to heaven.
Until I looked out at the manger scene.
There's a bulldog a sniffing at the wise man.
And next I'll tell you what it was I seen.
I seen Rover pissing on Jesus.
Marking his turf everywhere he pleases.
Reckon that dog is heading for doggy hell.
Get my gun and I'll kill Rover.
Can't be pissing up on my savior.
In the name of Bobby, pass the slack.
Sing one more time.
I seen Rover pissing on Jesus.
Marking his turf everywhere he pleases.
Reckon that dog is heading for doggy hell.
Get my gun and I'll kill Rover.
Can't be pissing up on my savior.
In the name of Bobby, pass the slack.
Well, it's bigger than me.
It's bigger than you.
It ain't bigger than Bobby.
Yes, it's bigger than me.
It's bigger than you.
But it ain't bigger than Bob Dog's.
Nothing's bigger than Bob Dog.
Just fireball power.
Sweet hour of slack.
How great it is to become one with Bob.
So quit your job and get in line.
For divine immaculation, J.R. Bob Dogg.
Praise be to God.
His divine immaculation, J.R. Bob Dogg.
Thank you.
Now some of y'all in here be pornicating and pornicating and pornicating.
I like that pornicate.
guitar solo
Sometimes I'm here on the show, other times I'm just flying over the mountain.
But I'm always spiritually present, Jayner.
You are a spirit in your present.
Therefore, your presence
is a spirit in me.
Remember that time I did that thing?
Oh, that was great when you did that thing.
Life is nothing but a river.
Everyone was just patting me on the back,
and it was me. And I was just so successful,
and I did so many neat things, and it was me.
But it's just life is just a river, Jayner.
Life is just a river, and if you're gonna enjoy life,
you gotta just sit back and float on by
like a cadaver floating down that wonderful river.
Like my daddy used to say, it's yellow.
That's why it's in the water.
Anyone who doesn't understand that joke will be put to death
because they're only normal.
I love that humor.
It's really an easy joke.
Listen to him, it's really an easy joke.
Now, when you tell this joke, I want you to explain it
so everyone real understands it,
and then tell it over again in slow motion
so we can understand every bit of it.
Okay, he'll explain what he meant.
Then we'll decide whether it's funny or not.
Okay, what I really meant
when I said,
actually, okay, I'll clarify this for you.
Is that the funny part?
.
And we found all sorts of amazing things.
For instance, did you realize that a gunshot wound to the pelvis area of a dog,
that causes almost 530 degrees on the Mingler pain scale.
530 degrees!
Why, that's astounding, Dr. Malmo.
But we can reduce those degrees of pain by almost 10%
if we administer what we call an acupuncture wound to the forehead.
Go ahead.
This can be used with a blunt instrument.
It doesn't have to be anything really sophisticated.
But, you know, basically you're distracting the canine from its other injury.
Yes.
Tell me more, Papa Joe.
Well, I could get into the cat research, but right now that's kind of classified.
Oh, you can tell us about it.
Well, the only thing we can't tell you about it...
How many watts is the station?
400.
Well, that's under 500 watts.
That passes the, what we call the classification...
Threshold.
I think that would be safe.
Well, we discovered that, you know, amazingly, I mean, we had all grown up with popular myths.
For instance, a lot of people believe that cats will always land on their feet.
Well, we at the Mingler Research Center for Humane Population Control
can assure you that that is not always the case.
Yes.
Always is a very strong word.
And what we basically did was we started taking the cats up, you know,
first one story on the building and dropping them off, and he would land on his feet.
We'd take out two stories.
He'd land on his feet.
He'd land on three stories.
After a while, we said, this is ridiculous.
Let's at least find if there is a point somewhere where they don't land on their feet.
So we took them up in a small craft, dropped them out of the airplane,
and they did not land on their feet.
So then the question was, where between six miles altitude
and the third story of a building does the cat actually stop landing on his feet?
Now, I won't give you that actual answer because that is classified,
but I will say that it is somewhere between the third story and the six-mile altitude.
Yes.
And as for the last one,
when we tossed off the third story window,
if anyone finds a shaven cat with a number tattooed on its front foreleg,
please return it to the Papa Joe Mama.
Mingler Research for Humane Population Control.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't get that out.
I had a mouthful of veal.
Of course, there is a lot of positive research that comes out of this, too.
After all, many people say, well, you know,
how do we keep the population down in a humane way?
Well, some of our earlier experiments,
like, say, AIDS, which was intended to be a painless disease, by the way.
It got mutated over years.
We initially started a polio vaccine in Angola on the chimpanzees there,
knowing that it would eventually, you know, work its way into the population.
I won't get into the motivations of that experiment.
We're going to...
All right.
And, uh...
I think...
I think we're going to have to do something about it.
It's one of the damn Martian tripods in Akron.
And the people in Cleveland don't even know that we had a war with Mars.
It was...
Admittedly, it was 90 years ago.
90...
Exactly.
97 years ago, praise Bob, that we defeated...
And there's a crashed pyramidal spaceship in Mississippi,
and nobody talks about that, either.
Oh, they don't pay any damn attention to it at all.
They don't know that there are still Martians living up in the Arctic Circle.
So...
You know, it's...
There are some kids...
I talk to kids nowadays, they go,
you know, we had a war with Mars in 1900,
and the Martians all died of a virus, thanks to God's wisdom.
Well, great.
But they didn't all die.
The Martians up in the North Pole and the South Pole
are still there with their giant cities
walking around on huge tripod traps.
And, you know, any minute now, they're going to...
I don't know.
Only go by the conspiracy media.
Okay, Chaz?
If you only go by the radio,
you would think there had never been a war against Mars.
You would think that the war in Vietnam
was something that had ended 20 years ago.
You would think that World War II,
against the...
The Germans and the Japanese
was all cleaned up and just all taken care of
back in the 1940s.
Oh, yes, we don't have to worry about the Germans.
You would think that the Tunguska event
was just a vaporized meteorite.
Yeah, meteorite.
I wish.
We all wish.
Flattened out the trees in a spiral motion
for 4,800 miles.
Well, when they Tunguska the...
You know, when they Tunguska I-90
just outside of Cleveland...
Then maybe...
Maybe the students there at the universities
will get some kind of a clue
that maybe there's something they haven't been told.
Well, these freshwater lakes
that we're sitting on up here in Cleveland is...
The freshwater...
I mean, it's just...
There's pods down there that nobody knows about.
It's like, you know,
kind of like Invasion of the Body Snatchers,
only not really.
They're not snatching the bodies.
Oh, no.
There's not really any terrible monsters
controlling people's minds
and causing them to serve the alien overlords.
Oh, no.
Oh, there's no government conspiracy
to suppress all dissent
and kill any religious nuts
like in Waco and Ruby Ridge.
Oh, no.
There's never been a war against Mars.
No, none of that stuff ever happened.
Oh, no.
Gulf War.
Yeah, Saddam Hussein and those people were just a bunch of losers.
We've won that war.
We even fought it.
Oh, people just don't believe anything.
God, it's sickening.
It's sickening and sad, but, you know, at the same time, it's kind of reassuring.
It means that those with a good agenda, proper vision of the future,
could wrench control of the mass mind
and the world.
From the conspiracy, those with good enough showbiz sense
could probably convince them of anything.
Because God knows they believe now.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Mudder on, Stang, you poor old sap.
Poor pathetic old...
God, it's cold here in the office, friends.
Oh, I suppose...
Oh, my ears.
These cheap headphones, I'm sorry.
Everything's all just leaking in here.
I'll tell you what you've been listening to.
The music, for the most part, there has been by Seva,
an artist formerly known as Commander Dave.
I can't find an address anywhere on this album or this CD.
It's called Gravity Is My Favorite Drug,
and it was sent by Reverend Preacher.
But I can't even tell you what label.
It is that mysterious.
We heard some WCSB, Einstein Secret Radio, of course.
Prozac Free Radio, Papa Joe Mama,
talking about the pain of the kitty cats.
Janer on KPFA back in the day of 1997.
And also some Janer from years, years before
on KPFA Best of Tape.
And a special thanks, of course, there to
the First Church of the United States,
of Elvis in Bob.
That long sermon and song,
Sleeping with Bobby,
a sweet hour of slack,
and the hardcore Bob sample mix dub
are from the folks at Die Music
and First Church of Elvis in Bob,
right over there in Warren, Texas.
Oh, yes.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
I noticed about the stuff, Bob.
Me too.
It's Thanksgiving.
Coming up.
How do I roast my Thanksgiving baby?
You just tie it up, stick it in the oven.
About eight hours.
350 should do it.
Don't worry about the little eyes bugging out.
Just think about the theme song.
The show staff finally shows.
And, and, and, Leepo Abernathy.
All of the ones before
are be able to all better now on you.
That grinning man with the pipe.
The hail fellow that the dust spills.
And what they claim does not even exist.
People who deny the reality of Bob,
who is lower than that?
It's just like those wretches who would claim that Tarzan,
Sherlock Holmes, and Robin Hood are fictitious characters.
For surely our Bob is in their company.
A heroic, happy madman who won't quit fighting
until all humanity achieves slack,
or at least that portion of humanity which is tired.
Untrue Bob.
That which is Bob.
True.
So I'm going to turn you over now to our master of ceremonies
as the nobles of the Mystic Shrine perform their obeisance
before the glittering white throne.
What have you seen that compares with that, Ed?
Oh, I thought, I thought, I thought you were going to play the Eraserhead soundtrack.
I'm talking about this beautiful float that was sponsored by
the Golden Knights of the Silver Pestle and the Green Protector.
The prophylaxis of the lower Balaponga Canal.
And you can get more information about that from the address I'm about to give, dear friends.
Oh yes, just write for free information.
That's free information you understand from Bob at Post Office Box 140306 Dallas, Texas 75214.
Ugh.
That's really distracting actually.
Just write to Bob at Post Office Box 140306 Dallas, Texas 75214.
Or you can, of course, the self-addressed stamped envelope will help and so forth.
And www.subgenius.com and slack at subgenius.com.
And we, we'd love to tell you more.
You just ask.
You'd be surprised.
We're not going to kill anybody.
Alone in dark spotted mist.
Companion and pilot.
Embraced in a kiss.
She loves him and he needs to see her lightless.
To know that the shadows hide all that he is.
In time that means nothing at all.
In space.
Being her.
Yes.
Quiet and smart.
Then I thought I caught a glimpse of you.
Hiding somewhere in Eurasia.
Eurasia.
That's where I'd have gone.
trying that would really get into your wallet every night every hour and into
your wallet eat the dollar bill and then crap them all over the kids