I completely forgot! I did tell her though. We've been fluffing it and fluffing, but I don't know if they really came out fluffy enough.
Well, I really don't know if I want Mr. Dobbs to look at a house like this. It's such a mess and clutter.
My, my, my, what is this? I don't even know what it is. And it's all smelly.
You weren't supposed to see that. You weren't supposed to see that. Here, let me just put it away.
You know, you're going to have to stop this. You're really getting me hot.
Holy cow!
To fly in the face of age.
I hate this place! I hate the face! I need a razor! I need some more! God damn it, I need some more pills!
I need big pills! I need pills the size of Los Angeles!
Stop the song! Stop the song! Stop the song! Stop music! Don't make music!
Hey!
I want to cry.
That is really, really, really sad, yes.
Listen, you can hear them again.
There they are.
And they're about to call me on it. Thousands of them.
Oh my God!
I don't think we can run away from this. We better...
They're coming!
You pretend like you just started playing along with them because...
Yeah, just play along.
Oh!
Oh, gosh.
Welcome to the Subgenius radio ministry Hour of Slack sponsored by the church of the Subgenius.
I...
I just want the flag!
Those of you who would wish an audience for degraded mystic Bob must please sign in
and take a number.
Life is better than
on the other side.
You know, you're going to have to stop this.
You're really getting me hot.
Holy cow!
The Church of the Subgenius.
P.O. Box 140306.
Dallas, Texas.
7-5-214.
If you join, I'll let you spank my bottom.
Come on, Jose, let's go.
We'll sit in the anteroom together.
Now spread your knees.
That's right, spread them.
Spread your knees.
Everyone in the room spread your knees
as far apart as you can.
That's right, you too, father.
You too, sister.
Everyone spread your knees.
That's right.
Now when the knees reach all the back,
be waiting, that's right,
behind the back of your buttocks.
When that's happening,
you've reached a perforated form
we call the extunction-unction format.
Okay, now everyone ready?
And stand up
and breathe out through the air.
Keep breathing through the ears.
This way to the pleasure-ships.
That's right.
Keep breathing through the ears
as we step towards the crowd.
Keep breathing through the ears.
Open the third nostril.
You're only here.
And we notice a short trans-luminescence
around the shorty pie and the new cakes.
Some uprising in the kidney stew.
Some of you may be startled by the shape of the ship.
Of course, made as it is out of plywood and pieces of...
Well, you don't want to say the word because right now we're having a problem with rat feces.
But as you're on level seven, you won't notice the difference.
And there won't be any caustic or toxic shock to any of the...
You, you there with the nervous syndrome.
Put your hands down.
I can't.
They're stuck up there.
I just can't move them down.
I'm too nervous.
I'm too upset.
I'm so worried about seeing the bomb.
What's the matter with her?
Oh, no, no, no.
I can't deal with that right now.
I don't go on until two o'clock.
I ain't got nothing to do with this.
Just tell her to keep on breathing through her ears and focus on her third nostril, man.
I got coffee to drink.
It's so scary.
It's all so scary.
Linda.
Hi.
Do not be fooled by the blatant subgenius propaganda that you may have heard on this radio station.
Just because Jesus works in their mail order department does not mean that they are Christians.
They smoke unnatural herbs from Tibet.
They kidnap children and...
brainwash them into slaves for aliens.
They make it rain frogs.
Only through prayer, fasting, and chastity can we hope to overcome their sex vibrations.
Don't worry.
We'll do all the fasting and praying.
But you must not have sex until the subgeni are destroyed.
Because they can make your unborn child into a subgenius creature through their unnatural rituals.
The pipe of...
The pipe of Bob alone is enough to cause one thousand unnatural births.
We must kill Bob and make sure he stays dead this time around.
You must help us kill Bob forever.
Send one dollar to Ban Organized Blasphemy, B.O.B.
P.O. Box 140306, Dallas, Texas 75.
214.
A murmur of faith from the heart of the Bible Belt.
Amen.
Thank you very much.
When I'm with you, pussycat, who needs grass?
Marijuana.
Reef.
Cashy's choice.
Buckle pot.
Grab.
Mary Jane's.
Kind.
Chronic.
Bud.
The rest.
You just passed the high times test.
This is concrete.
John made a sin.
John told a lie.
In the name of the Father, the Son, and the Holy Spirit.
Amen.
The Lord's a-talking to me now.
He's a-saying, a liar is an abomination before mine eyes.
Speak, boy.
Where's it hit?
Speak.
Speak or I'll cut your throat and leave you to drip like a hog hung up in butchering
time.
I was just wondering.
I was thinking about my big blossoms the other day and I wanted to go out in search
to go wander around in the maze.
You remember the
Bob maze we did with the
gigantic pipe?
Oh, that was so much fun!
Look, you can see it from the air. It's like a crop
circle. Oh, and it's so
craftily woven right above
the eyelids. Look, it's saying
something to it.
Yes, it's saying...
It's saying
help me.
And friends, I know
exactly how it feels
because the crazy
women just finally let me
out of the closet.
I'm feeling like my
brain is divvied up between
four or five
cities all at the same time
and not any one
section is any too
smart in any
given town.
So I'm trying
to gather together what
wits I might have left
here in Dallas.
But man, it's all jumbled together.
The radio shows from Cleveland
and the crazy
women took the
deed to the church off to
Boston with them.
And everybody in
all those places was packed into
one little Austin
room the other day.
And that was fun, man.
That was time.
That was time control.
I left the hind part
of one of my lobes behind
the couch at Paco's
house.
Well, friends, we just got back from
the Austin devival
and everybody scored
last Saturday night.
Jesus married a
13-year-old boy.
Steve Jackson shoved a
beer bottle up somebody's butt
and kicked it till it broke.
Dr. Legume got to use my little
dog pudding as a way to get me out of here.
And Dr. G.
Gordon Gordon got a heart attack.
And then he shoved a beer bottle up
Death's butt and kicked
it until it broke.
And Reverend Ed Strange got a
free plane ride just for being such
a purdy man. And I got
poisoned by
Reverend Friday Jones
who got the church.
Yes,
she was the one who locked me in
the closet and took over the subgenius
foundation.
Which was great. It was a great vacation,
folks. It was wonderful.
The Austin show was great.
The Crystal Methodist
not only miraculously
got through to the
Christian radio talk show
repeatedly and got on the air
in Portland and on the speakers
in Austin, but so did a whole lot of
subgeniuses around the country.
Oh, and Satan's
cheerleaders were there.
Friends, it was a stone-fire
blast.
It was a real heart-plugger.
Who?
Friends, this is
the, uh,
this is the Crystal Methodist,
friends, their new CD,
New World Odor.
Wicked.
Every human being
by nature is wicked.
Oh,
oh,
So this is coming like a freight train.
We have to look at gun control.
They're moving rapidly to disarm the American people.
You've never had a country disarmed.
But it's gone into dictatorship like Russia, Red China, Cuba, Nazi Germany,
without first disarming them and taking their guns away.
And the gun control laws today are almost identical to the Nazi gun control laws.
As a matter of fact, I've written in recent months about the parallels between America and Nazi Germany.
The parallels are incredible.
The Nazis had a preoccupation with death.
They were big-time abortion, big-time euthanasia,
killing of crippled people and people they didn't think were worthy.
And, of course, same thing in America today.
The Nazis had an occultic dimension behind the Third Reich.
The Third Reich was essentially that the leaders, including Hitler, were Satanists.
They were Satanists.
They were worshippers.
And you find the same occultic dimension behind this whole plunge towards a new world order.
In our country today, they were animal rights and environmental freaks.
Back during the days of Hitler, just as we have become in this country,
they blew off their constitution, their traditional heritage.
They passed gun laws against their people.
They passed tens of thousands of laws, rules, and regulations
which made every German a potential criminal.
And, of course, the same thing is here today.
The parallels between Nazi Germany...
and the 1930s in America today are absolutely incredible
for anybody who would like to look at them.
All of this needs to be seen in context of the larger move
this is not happening by accident,
the larger move of the whole world towards what is called the new world order.
Ladies and gentlemen, every year thousands of landmines are abandoned by people
who just don't care enough to give their landmine the sort of love and attention it needs.
Under the mistaken belief that the landmine can take care of itself,
these poor explosives are left in deserted war zones and along interstate highways.
Most of them die of starvation.
Others are eaten by predatory wild hand grenades.
Those few that survive are ragged, pitifully hair-triggered creatures
who explode only in self-defense
and are often labeled bad
by media figures and the uninformed.
Please, we ask you, from the bottoms of our hearts,
with our hands laid on Princess Diana's freshly flayed skull,
take your landmines to a landmine adoption center
if you can't care for them anymore,
inquire about free landmine spaying,
and if your heart is big enough,
take a landmine into your own house
and make it a home.
Thank you.
Subtitles by the Amara.org community
The world order, or odor,
from their CD,
New World Odor,
is from Goidebaudgean P.O. Box 11877,
Chicago, 60611
For information,
we have also heard
little bits and pieces of,
well actually, there was some Frank Marino
from obscure psychedelic band Mahogany Rush.
Some of the guitar effects there in the background.
And drumming and spouting, dear friends,
from Einstein's Secret Orchestra,
recorded off of the Internet in several of these cases.
From WCSB in Cleveland,
which does indeed broadcast on the Internet in audioactive,
which was good enough for me to tape it off the air
and play it back and whip it around there
hearing a tape of a tape of a tape of a tape of a tape.
With Chaz Smith, Lonesome Cowboy Dave,
and special guest Crazy Woman, Princess We Are Doe.
Don't know, I'll have to check with her, ma'am.
I'm really sorry, ma'am.
I wanted the best prop for Mr. Dobbs.
You know he is a stickler for the stickler.
The church air is here, though.
Ma'am, we have gotten the church air.
It's all secured.
The church airs?
I didn't order an organ player.
We've already got someone playing with his organ over there.
Ma'am, you know Mr. Dobbs always wants the church air.
Well, all right, then.
I suppose we'll have to have it.
But what about the buffet?
The buffet?
The shrimp.
They're all smelling.
Oh, yes.
Well, we've been smothering the shrimp.
But, you know, the shrimp...
Damn, these aren't even...
These are dead prairie squids.
Ma'am...
Ma'am, they were supposed to be the best shrimp.
The buffo's ready.
Anybody ready to lick the buffo?
And get all fluffed up?
The celebration's all started without me.
I'm just...
Buffy.
Buffy, that's enough.
I'll have another little teeny lick.
Look at those.
Look at that fine, healthy...
Look at these fine, healthy toads.
Wow, these are prize-winning giants.
Oh, my.
Giant toads.
Get off my toad.
Sonoran Desert toads.
That's my toad.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we have spared no expenses at all
to raise the finest buffo for...
Look at that little one.
He's got human legs.
They're gene splice.
They're specially treated
to create the finest in Tock.
Now, see these toxins secreting from the warts
on the back of the little toad.
That's it, Princess Wee.
Oh, shit.
See how princess we are, though,
is scraping and sucking the...
The sour.
...the toxin droplets off of the pores,
the rather large pores on the back of the toad.
Be careful.
Now, some of those aren't pores.
Those are egg sacs.
You don't want baby buffoes growing in your stomach.
Oh, wait a minute.
You look real close at them.
Look at them.
Put your glasses up to me.
Look, man.
There's thousands of little severed heads
that are on top of each.
What?
That's not a scale.
They're little tiny micro-heads.
Screaming.
Look, they're screaming.
That's right.
If you look at the back of one of those kind of toads
close enough under a microscope,
you'll see that the tiny droplets of toxin
that get you high
are actually composed of tiny one-celled heads.
One-celled golfer heads.
The brain, or so to speak,
is the nucleus,
and the skin forms the outer shell
or epidermis or scaly rind.
You go ahead and peel it.
Dave, don't eat it yet.
Peel it before you eat it.
It's on drugs.
You have to track the shell.
Please forgive this milk.
Right in my throat and right in my fillings.
Mmm.
Yum.
And those are...
As the tiny dandruff pill pie becomes engorged,
the rest of the organism waits for the sperm
to impregnate the whole lip.
Would you like some E. coli with your sperm, sir?
Mmm.
I'm not using my own...
And parmesan cheese?
That is some really tasty frog smegma.
Mmm. Yum!
Would you like parmesan cheese with your...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Dump a lot on there.
Put a lot of cheese on there.
You got pepper, too?
Dump a lot of pepper on there.
This is my last snack.
I'll have you know once I finish this.
Whatever the hell it is, I'm checking out.
Buffo glandulars?
Have a little snack.
This is not what it is.
And how long you guys been serving up this crap down here?
Oh, this is...
Oh, not more than ten years.
This is relatively fresh for fossilized food, sir.
What's the lady of the house say about it?
I noticed she was, like, going into some weird hysterics
and her face was changing colors.
I don't know if she was eating the same stuff as me.
Oh, no, we were having a birthday party back there.
It's just...
It's a custom on our planet.
All right, all right.
Okay, just load it up real good.
But I want to know about it.
Am I going to have any, like, side after?
Mix or something?
No, no, no, no.
That is just our custom.
That's what we do on our planet.
We hurt each other and then we cry.
It's a custom.
It's just our custom.
Yeah, we do that at home, too.
No.
No, no.
No, go on.
No.
Don't tell me no.
Stop it.
Get back.
Back of there.
No.
Stop it.
Weird.
Psychedelic stuff.
Friends, I like weird psychedelic stuff because that's what was the most bad when I was in
high school.
I mean, I'll admit it.
And Lonesome Cowboy Dave there and Princess Wee and Chaz on Einstein's Secret Radio certainly
were weird old psychedelic youngsters that night.
Indeed.
And sure, it might sound kind of terrible today, but it also sounds kind of crazy.
And I think it's a little bit crazy because ancient psychedelic music from them the day
was.
It was, friends.
And, uh, yes.
This is a band called Lothar and the Hand People.
We're going to feature them tonight.
Sex and violence.
Psychology.
Muscle like
six, six, six.
Sex and violence.
Of sex and violence. Sex and violence.
Sex, sex, sex, sex, sex, sex, sex, violence.
Pretty horrible, isn't it, friends?
Well, at the same time, you know, the fact that this dates from 1966 should make you understand that indeed this at the time was what you might call totally rebellious.
Like real hardcore punk rap or something might be today.
But, you know, electric guitar special effects had just been invented and so had street LSD.
So when you combine all those elements at the time, you did get a certain fanaticism of weirdness in old mid-60s psychedelic music that I think still rings true today.
As exemplified in this beef heart like Lothar and the Hand People tune.
This is the end of the record.
The record has faded by this point.
I'm saying kids are little people.
Where are you over here?
Where is it?
Where you are?
Here's our little people.
And when I was a little person kid, I went to see my cousin Roberta at the far away and
exotic Cleveland Institute of Art.
And she played music from that album you just heard.
And I thought it was the coolest, coolest thing I'd ever heard.
Roberta or Bobby to her friends, she left the institute a week or two before graduation
to follow a guru.
And I thought, well, I'm going to go to school.
I'm going to go to school.
And I thought, well, I'm going to go to college.
And I thought, well, the rest is pretty strange history.
But she left me with.
I just wanted so bad to be her.
And I bought that album.
And I really tried hard to wear its grooves out.
It got lost at a party somewhere along the way.
And I've yearned to hear it for years.
And they finally rereleased it on CD 30 years later.
Anyway, I still think that Lothar and the Hand People are a little too much.
Lothar in the Hand People is one of the coolest things that happened in the 60s.
This is Princess We Are Doe, and Reverend Stang,
I think you ought to spin another Lothar tune so the kids can rock it good.
This is one of my favorites.
Lothar in the Hand
Oh yeah!
Machines, machines, they keep right on moving.
Well I've got to find a place to rest my head.
A machine he'd smile at me and say,
I'm gonna be all bad.
Oh yeah! Oh yeah!
Oh yeah!
This right here, dear friends, is huge voodoo,
not ancient psychedelic music.
Huge voodoo with Bruce Grant and PK Jones.
Where do I stand without my body, huh?
Extremely interesting and extremely worthwhile artistic performances.
Here in the laboratories, we've wasted no time
in bringing you the best of the best.
The finest semen to impregnate your young ladies.
Icons of culture like the Reverend Ivan Stang
and their sperms have been cryogenically frozen
and await you for a minimum cost.
The depleted organs of Janer hyperglyphs
and others of...
...genius vanguaria
are also on sale during this limited-time-only sale,
so shop now.
Test mantra.
Test.
It brings out my testosterone.
Testify, brother, to your testosterone.
When I see that Friday Jones,
it pulls out my testosterone.
Testosterone.
No, that's not what you usually pull out, Reverend.
Um.
Wednesday night prayer service, please go worship Baal.
So you need to really get on fire for the Lord.
Rise.
And rise.
Taxi.
.
Empires and those civilizations, they-
As a woman, before you went into surgery.
I was really disgusted with myself.
At one time in my life, I weighed 260 pounds.
I-
I'm not gay anymore.
To become a girl, he tried to castrate himself.
Leave.
I am the true underground messiah.
When you come to my show, you're going to a war.
.
As soon as you turn your back,
everything in the universe snaps itself inside out
with a hideous sucking motion.
.
The only reason you cannot call the world impossible
is because it is only through the world
that you know the concept of impossibility.
.
You have been led to believe that everyone feels he or she
may be the only living consciousness.
But you are in fact the only one for whom this is true.
.
The fundamental structure of reality
is totally transformed every instant.
But it provides you with a phony memory
that it hasn't always been the way it is.
. Since you want some water getting water, justальной, water get over it.
are always at the exact center of an infinity there is no such thing as a movement location space or
time you are a row of electrochemical events taking place in your cerebrum
nothing has meaning in itself but everything can support any meaning if you could glimpse
for even a moment the real meaning of existence your brain would be neuroanatomically destroyed
you cannot conceive nothing for which you do not have a word
everyone's perception is radically unique it leads them to believe it is more or less
similar for everyone else you have always been listening to this tape
you can
not remember a time before you were born because there was no such time nor any other
it has always been this moment death could occur inexplicably any second
the oddness of the world exceeds the imagination by an infinity
it has produced this talking about it this talker this labeling of it this labeler the concept of
the blame
the concept of oddness the word oddness the concept of a word the word word the word concept
and the concept of a concept consciousness is not a continuous state but a momentary
surfacer for variable periods at random points your next awakening could be 20 years from now
nothing can be proven to be possible
be true. Because reality is composed of infinitesimally small moments, there is no such thing as an
event. The reason people are untrustworthy is because their cerebral processes are fundamentally
random ones. During the night, every ego in the world changes bodies, inheriting also
the memory. Old age is not a gradual, but a catastrophic process, and could strike at
any moment. Dreams are the reality for which the real world is a dream. There has never
been a time in history when men have voluntarily used less than the greatest possible military
technology against their enemy, and allowed a great technology to fall into disuse and
ignorance. Therefore, there will be a full-scale nuclear holocaust. You are dreaming this moment.
The universe will continue to expand until there is not enough matter per unit space
to provide the gravity necessary for regeneration, and it will slowly die out. When you finish
listening to this, everything will be different.
You may not remember it from the way it was when you began, but again, your new memory
will conceal this from you. All events occur at random. The universe is one of an infinite
number of universes, the closest of which is undetectable, being a billion universe
lengths away. Only what you are experiencing right now exists.
Love is the feeling that another person is really yourself. You are about to make the
first conscious decision of your life.
Uh oh.
You in big trouble now, dear friends? You now have the power to change the world. You
are the power. What are you going to do with it, eh?
Well that was Pope M. Ho-Pep, innocent, the third, or Reverend Michael Pepe, and you are
listening to the Hour of Slack Radio Ministry here on KNON.
We built them to serve us. Machines, machines. We built them to serve us. But till the day
I'm buried in my grave. Yes, right until that day I know I'm gonna be a slave, a slave,
a slave, a slave.
Machines, machines. They keep right on grinning. Machines, machines. They keep right on grinning.
Yeah.
Bow, bow, bow, bow.
Bow, bow, bow, bow, bow.
Yes, we built them to serve us. And these boys sure do make awesome use of them. We
are Doe here again, and if you just tuned in, that was one of my most favorite old bands.
Lothar and the hand people. Lothar is what the hand people call that theremin. The tall,
slender, silver, very, very sensitive rod that makes the grooviest, grooviest sounds
when hands enter its energy field. Toss in a couple of Moog synthesizers, Ampex tape
decks, a linear controller, and some pretty righteous guitar and keyboards and you're
beginning to understand this thing, this Lothar and the hand people thing that I love so much.
Reverend Stang will be sparking your eardrums with more Lothar throughout this show.
Bye bye love, bye bye happiness, bye bye happiness, bye bye happiness, bye bye happiness, bye bye
happiness.
Hello loneliness, I think I'm gonna cry, bye bye love, bye bye sweet caress, hello emptiness,
I feel like I could die, bye bye my love, goodbye.
There goes my baby with someone new, she sure looks happy, I sure do.
She was my baby till he stepped in
Goodbye to romance that might have been
Bye-bye love, bye-bye happiness
And no loneliness, I think I'm gonna cry
Bye-bye love, bye-bye sweet caress
And no emptiness, I feel like I could die
Bye-bye my love, goodbye
I'm dying. By the time you see this, I'll be dead.
Kids, think about it before you sign that piece of paper.
Praise Bob.
Remember any defects from the sperm?
Some of the Reverend Ivan's stang are not considered negotiable.
Your attention, please.
The views expressed on this show are taken from the word of God.
They do not necessarily reflect the views or opinions of this station,
their staff, management, or advertisers.
However,
they are beginning to come around.
Please,
the information given you on this broadcast could save your life.
Listen with care.
We will preserve and we will enlarge the American dream.
We will nourish and we will refresh the American spirit.
We will enhance the quality of life for all Americans.
And we will prove once again that in America, the voices of despair are ultimately stilled
by the clear fact of progress.
In closing, let me say simply that I'm growing terribly weary of America's noisy detractors.
Housewitz! Housewitz! Housewitz! Housewitz!
Subgenius is for sale.
They will not save your soul.
They will eat it.
They will not get you into heaven.
They will pitch you into hell and roast marshmallows over your smoking carcass.
Your money will be spent on Thailand pleasure houses and their vast weapon stashes.
While your children starve in the subgenius sweatshops printing out pamphlets and making bizarre ritual garb.
Not only do the subgenius turn their faces away from God, they actually moon him.
They worship God.
They worship whatever they want to.
They wear their shoes on the wrong feet and even go barefoot to imitate their Bigfoot fathers.
They like bad movies.
Truly their evil is never ending and infinite.
You must help us silence evil ones.
Send one dollar to Ban Organized Blasphemy.
B.O.B.
P.O. Box 140306.
Dallas, Texas.
75214.
A murmur of faith from the heart of the Bible Belt.
Oh.
Some pleasure.
I kit off некотор
and from my
incestuous
But friends, you know, there's one thing that we've got that the all those other of
the Rival religious nuts don't have.
Sheer total unbridled hate.
Oh yes, cause we can at least admit it.
We're not gonna sit and try to pretend that we love you.
The jerk's T.V., each and everyone of us always wants the T.V. T.V. T Title.
Christians, they're really into loving their enemies.
I think we all know how that works.
Yeah, it could kind of make your brain kind of funny.
Especially when you start rubbing your cha-cha, you know, sometimes, you know, most of the time it's not the same.
That's really true.
Sometimes you make your cha-cha very dry.
That's right, boys and girls, Bob wants to rub your cha-cha.
That's right.
And your cha-cha can be anything you want.
You'll still love it.
Cha-cha-cha.
It could be a fluffy thing.
It could be a very firm thing.
Bob's in love with you.
He wants to marry you.
He don't care if you're a boy or a girl or an animal or what.
He wants to marry you, baby.
He wants to give you a big, big kiss.
He loves you.
Come on over to Bob.
Bob's going to be loving on you, baby.
Oh, Bob wants to father your child.
He don't care if you're a man.
He don't care if you're a blue whale, a male blue whale.
He's in love with you.
He's a love god.
He's a love whale.
I got pictures of Bob.
Come on, girls.
You know you want him.
Come on.
Oh, yeah.
This is a sex cult, man.
Bob is a sex god.
You look like a bug of urges.
Come here.
He's a sex god.
Oh.
Oh, he's Bob the purveyor of a psychic holocaust.
Psychic holocaust, bug pornography, and Einstein's secret orchestra.
What do these have in common?
What links these otherwise disparate and discarnate disembodied spirits and ghosts, shades, pathetic
leftovers?
What have you found yet?
I dropped порядedylum of classify in elements within cause and pushed into a componiy that
in call incredible Fell Puisque немножко corri ruling in which those remains of Beneven
which were honor reinforcement to self as a mean of
하죠.
paljon.
For the last big leap.
The last Einstein secret orchestra.
It's huge, a creature so large that its own weight
could crush its bones if it left its hideous swamp.
Every step it took, molten lava would pour out of the hole
it left in the ground and so deep.
So heavy was this.
The Einstein secret orchestra source.
30 miles an hour, 90 feet of jump.
I'm sorry.
Holes flowing.
No one ever saw it, and no one ever had a treat.
And someone said it looked a lot like Mr. Greed.
Mr. Green.
A little bloody.
It looked like a Pachycephalosaurus
mixed with a cross within an Elasmosaurus,
crossed with a Pterodactyl, crossed
with a Brachyotherium, which is a giant mammal,
crossed with a trilobite.
Well, I know what the Pachycephalosaurus
is.
But the thing was miles tall.
Dunkelosteus, crossed with a Clevelandohioceendesis.
And a Dobson's swamp.
It's a swampus.
It lived in the swampus.
It was dripping with a malodorous fluid
that it made in its thorax.
But no one knew that it was really a pretty neat critter.
I mean, it billared young, and it took care of them
until they were teenagers.
That's right.
It raised its dead.
It raised its own young.
And it did not devour them until they were 18.
At which time it licked their necks, looking for the microcyclic
They threw them out of the house and instantly hunted them.
They called it an Einstein secret orchestrasis.
They called it the Mistress Einstein Secret Orchestrasis.
It was sort of a, what were the padram?
A double, a psychic double.
It was part mammal, part reptile, part fish, part dinosaur, part bird, part single-celled creature,
part plant cell, and part bacteria, and part virus.
Part cheesy, watery thing.
And half crazy.
Half sticky purple button.
Half crazy with its own philosophies.
It was half werewolf, and half dragon, and half tarantula, and half Frankenstein.
And half Frankenstein.
And it was scary.
And it didn't have a face.
It was so big and small that they shrank.
They didn't have a face.
Big, big perspirations.
It needs a billowing out of the body.
The most interesting thing was the cloaking device it used.
That's why it didn't have a face.
Is that that Floakon thing?
There were creatures that had built, that actually had a biological cloaking device.
The Einstein secret orchestra was so huge.
And large.
It required a series of sub-brains along its spinal cord and down in its toes because
it was such a great distance.
The microcephalo pod.
Walnut-sized brain.
The tiny head pod.
And its cranium.
So there was a series of, as Hal Robbins identified them, small primitive calculators, adding
machines, placed along the spine of the creature.
And each vertebrae of this animal was the size of a microcephalo pod.
And the size of the entire university here.
This was a big, as Chaz said, the Einstein secret orchestra with each footstep sunk all
the way to China.
And each one encased in a bubble of glass.
Those were the days of food.
I remember those days.
It's pretty place to see.
It was before this orb was even shaking.
It was so long ago.
It was before time.
Actually.
It was from the land before all time.
You mean there's an actual place that's before everything starts?
It is, yes.
You said land before time.
I assume you're talking about a place.
Yes, there was a place.
Before there was time, there were places.
But they didn't last very long.
They were instantaneous.
They were just flickered.
As they came into existence, they just came out of existence because they were just in
a house.
And they rode off.
They rode off into the airways.
Each one like a little bubble that pops, since forgotten and useless.
Just like we're going to do.
Just like us.
Just like the blank tape we thought we were recording everything on.
Which reminds me.
We were, actually.
But remember, if you want the Chalupas, you got an hour or two or at least...
I'm sorry.
I forgot what I was saying.
My name's Chaz.
This is ESO Radio down in the swamp.
I'm Barry White.
Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
Prince as we are due.
Reverend Ivan Spang.
Linda Lovelace.
Linda Lovelace in the corner over there.
Linda Blair in the other corner.
How many Lindas do we have here?
There was Linda Knight here.
And Gary Kruper.
Gary Kruper.
Kruper.
Wiki Fromm as Benji.
Until next week, keep your hat on tight.
You're back to the wind and your sack in the saddle.
We'll see you next time.
Don't let Bob end up getting your scrotum for one of them death pouches.
No scrotums were tortured in the production of this program.
Hurry Bob.
I almost twisted a little bit.
Goodbye.
We are now going off the air.
Well, not completely, dear friends.
You can stay on the air by writing for free information from Bob.
Bob Dobbs and the Church of the Subgenius.
At Post Office Box 140306.
Dallas, Texas 75214.
Also known as Slack at Subgenius.com.
Have a great weekend, everyone.
Have a great weekend.
Bye.
This is a villain tale to Mr. Chaz
Here at the Church of the Useless Neck Brace Cathedral
And tonight I hope you're all empowered
By the orbiting skull crystals and testifiers
Yes, yes, dear friend
We're gonna tell you the truth
We're gonna tell the truth and heal you
If you're just feeling bad
That's the only one you have
I wanna take a breath of life
I'll go out walking in the rain
Watch the flowers go to bed
That's the man inside my head
I'm gonna tell you the truth
Spirit never have to leave
All you gotta do is believe
The faith in God
Ladies and gentlemen, I can heal you
Who is licensed fully by the state of Ohio, Pennsylvania, New Jersey to heal you?
None other than I and why myself
So please step forward and let me let Cabotrol
We're happy to help you
Oh no, let me let me let Cabotrol on your head
I can't heal you
I have the power to heal you
I'm all in you
All you gotta do is breathe
Your body's gonna stop the feel
Finger drips and holy fire
Everlasting sweet desire
If you're mad at what the doctor said
The evil man you steal away
Immortality for two
Miracles they come for you
The faith in God
Can I put my hands on you
Yes friends, I'm not talking about hate
No friends, I'm not talking about hate
I'm talking about dinner date
Yes let's eat
Oh, the glory and the convenience of food
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
A mighty hot dog is on the road, I forgot the rest, I'm trying.
Wake up, hope and charity.
Simple relativity.
It can make you understand.
All you gotta do is take his hand.
Remember what someone said.
Pass the man inside the head.
Finger drift, simple name fire.
Everlasting sweet desire.
The faith in us.
Can I put my hands on you?
Can I?
My hands on you.
Now when you see the flash of light, don't run from cover.
Drop your knees.
Hey, that's right, that's right.
That'll do you just fine.
Nothing's gonna save you from the suborbital skull-drister and testy fire.
Your balls are gonna be fine.
There's no way out.
Unless you, unless you look to me.
Yes, that's right, you look to me.
Because I can heal you.
Can I put my hands on you?
Can I?
Was it from a having sex before this?
It's not a fucking movie.
No way.
Maybe it's just when I life changed.
Bigbly.
Can I put my hands on you?
I'm helping on the seat in the back of a car.
I'm sitting on the seat and I haven't gone too far.
Oh, Lord, please, Lord, please.
Can I put my hands on you?
Alex Harvey, remember him?
He died. He died.
He died.
They found his decapitated head in the swamp.
Yo, you're making my cha-cha.