BAAA Bado
That's Boston another one more later
Aaaaah
The first rule is...
Obey all rules!
Philosophical dogma of doing mischief.
Women, truth. Woman, evil.
What then?
Dogma, dogma, dogma, audacious dogma lies on the ground.
Gasp.
Very, very, very unseemly seriousness.
Seriously.
The genius power of the savage.
Woman, devil, dragon.
Now listen to this.
And here he is.
Bob.
Thank you very, very much, ladies and gentlemen.
Here I am again.
Yes, here I am.
Personally, I don't believe in superstition.
But here in Los Angeles, ladies and gentlemen, we've just had a census taken.
I really shouldn't have said that because there's no better place to go.
Remember how the early wagon trains fought the Indians?
That's a well-dressed octopus.
He has an unlisted wife.
And they're all sun worshippers there.
When you're ready to go, they just put you on a bus for Pasadena.
There is an endless supply of white men.
But there always has been a limited number of human beings.
Oh, there be players that I have seen play and heard others praise and that highly.
Not to speak it profanely, that having neither the accent of Christians nor the gait of pagan Christian nor Christian.
But the poor man have so strutted and bellowed that I have thought that some of nature's journeymen had made men and not made them well.
They imitated humanity so abominably.
I hope we have reformed that indifferently with us, sir.
Oh, reform it altogether?
And let those that play your clown speak no more than is set down for them.
For there be of them that will themselves laugh to set on some barren quantity of spectators to laugh to.
Though in the meantime some necessary question of the play be then to be considered.
That's villainous.
And shows the most pitiful ambition in the fool that you are.
And loses it.
Do you know who Phil was gonna be with tonight?
No. No. I... I...
Sorry, Joe. I...
Uh, wait a minute.
Yeah?
Look! A bunch of dirty plates.
Okay, Eve, honey. Be right over.
No. No. I pushed the accelerators to the floor.
Well, thanks.
Huh?
N-n-nothing.
Okay.
I turned the key off.
Hm.
Heh heh heh heh heh heh heh heh.
Huh? Huh?
Huh?
Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
Diagnostic report.
All systems go.
Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
Process of elimination.
Filling power over federal communication.
Centralizing. Sterilizing.
Compensating censorship through methods of intimidation.
Barbers on constant.
Retreatment serials without express consent.
Duplication.
Great revision.
Out of labor and violation of our spectral management.
You've been investigated.
Over the mission, your position has been triangulated.
Demilitated.
And implicated.
In this moment in ship, we've been convicted by a novel agent.
We can save planet Earth by counters 우리 selurling .
Moving away from Earth known as our planet.
Everything transformed.
When Taman can say my wish.
Mos Giganicus did that dear friends
from
moesgiganticus.com
Thanks so much to
Reverend Brainerd for turning us on
to Moes Giganticus.
And our openings
were by William Shakespeare,
Little Big Man, and
Fernanda Nande, Lee Murr.
The Anything for a Laugh
trio.
Those openings were for
Hour of Slack number
1140,
which this is.
Not a live show this time,
but one composed of
once live shows.
We especially
concentrate tonight on not
thinking. Thanks to
John Hell's show,
A Season in Hell,
on Pirate Cat
Radio in San Francisco.
Seen here.
There's a worldwide
shortage of helium.
The Earth is running out.
A worldwide shortage of helium.
At the party supply store,
they assured me.
Second most abundant element in the universe.
Then we're in deep shit.
We should have brought some church air.
Absolutely no shortage of helium.
Is there a shortage of nitrous?
And you probably believe that
on the show, yeah, there was supposed to be
church air.
Yes. I heard that they've
been mining for helium.
I heard some astronomer was going to do that.
Mining for helium and 30 Chinese
got trapped in a cave-in
mining for helium.
And boy, did their voices sound funny.
Yes, they died.
They screamed.
Think of the joy of the boys and girls with their balloons.
I have a new
bag of balloons that I can
donate to the cause.
Hey, can the car go fetch
that tank of gas and
take some hits?
Balloons and not a gray one
to be seen.
Because there's a world
wide shortage.
By the way, do you know where helium comes from?
Have we gone through the peak helium
phase?
From the sun.
Helium has finally occurred.
See, so there is becoming a shortage.
There's lots of helium,
however, remaining.
I want you to know that my household has one of the
largest helium footprints on the planet.
People are hoarding
the helium.
Helium hoarder.
I understand you rub elbows
with the hydrogen.
And the gold magnets, but only the pyrite magnets.
The pyrite magnets.
Well, I don't want to brag, but we have some of the
squeakiest voices around.
It's true.
Just in time for that new Elvin and the Chipmunks movie.
Let's not go there.
I understand you made a lot of money off of that.
Selling that helium at that top price.
Yes.
You know how much it takes to fill an entire Hollywood
town stage with helium?
I'm sure you'll tell us.
Even if we don't want to know.
No, it's not even funny.
No, move on.
I wasn't laughing, really.
It is funny.
Move on.
But I really want to know what's going on.
Well, it's a curious thing.
Professor Cavour found that the selenites couldn't get a hold of helium, so they were
unable to duplicate the substance on the outside of his sphere.
But now we know that in the lunar regolith, there's that strange mystery substance, helium-3.
Helium-3.
Yes.
It's produced by a constant bombardment of solar cosmic rays.
And so isn't that where helium comes from?
From the fiery heart of the sun himself?
Well, I would like to actually attribute it more to something called fusion.
But not con-fusion.
It happens naturally.
The new Stanford laser testing of nuclear weapons is reputed to be a possible
source of a controlled fusion reaction.
Comments?
True.
True?
You'll actually endorse that?
No, it's not really true.
It would not be the most expeditious way to fusion, to fuse hydrogen into helium.
It's in little tiny teensy amounts.
Those things are so small, they'd fit in an HO train car.
This is becoming as exciting as a Pete Goldie talk at Ask Dr. Hell Show.
What's your name?
Katherine Hepburn.
I see.
Well, thanks, ma'am.
I'm sorry I bothered you.
Yeah, but maybe, maybe, maybe, hey, that's good thinking.
I'll give odds against that.
Yeah.
What are you guys doing to me?
I don't know what you're talking about.
We're talking about the
So genius.
Power of the force.
That you and somebody else pulled yesterday.
No.
Yes.
He said we'd get married, go to Europe.
No.
We're going to Europe next year.
You'll all go someplace next year, but it won't be Europe.
Well, that winds it up just in time, too.
It's getting dark.
We have to be going.
Merry Christmas.
Guaranteed.
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, located in your body.
Wow.
Mm-hmm.
What, what, what, what, where are you located in my body?
Toward the back of your body, around your waistline.
Bob, the great creator.
Rap, rap, rap, rap.
You will not be able to get away from me.
You will not hurt me.
Oh, that's great.
All your blood passes through my partner and me, kids.
Chemicals swimming in it.
He's super.
Big vein, don't you?
You've got it, glob.
Boy, that really shows how great glob the creator is.
All of my blood?
Every drop of it, Bob, Bob.
Too much, too much, stop.
Oh, oh.
Beating.
Yes.
But, but, but, but too much salt in my bloodstream.
Spaghetti-o.
Take the X.
X.
Wow, wow.
Thick asses.
Pump the thick gooey stuff.
Stop.
This is the right time.
S. S. S.
You have the responsibility to perform.
Keep talking.
It's hard.
Solidifies.
It merges.
They feel like, they feel like, they feel like, they feel like, largest coal.
You know, your majesty, Terry.
Status quo.
Kids got on airplanes.
They feel like, and these are ideologues, by the way.
Status quo.
You give people their rights.
Look, I know I've been accused of being a war monger, a war monger.
I don't see any alternative.
People will know.
What can you do?
Murder the innocent.
I believe it is a part of a larger campaign.
Bush wants to fight Muslims.
Muslims.
Wants to fight Bush.
Therefore.
Bush wants to fight.
fight Muslims. You view me as
a warmonger and I view myself as a warmonger
and what's in me? Just isolated
incidences. Democracy
is not possible. Quite bumpy.
I really do. Your poll? Your poll?
Bush wants to fight
Muslims.
Why am I supposed to go in the fetal
position because of your poll?
Poll, poll, poll, poll, poll, poll,
poll, poll, poll, poll, poll,
poll, poll, poll, poll, poll, poll.
Thanks be unto
Reverend Norell Preff
of Norellpreff.com
I'm not sure what the theme of this
particular episode is, but it
may be the conspiracy.
Is that what it was?
But maybe we should crack the window
and start seeing things in 12D.
I think you already have.
What's the church's stance
on the golden compass?
Hey, do you like Angelina Jolie?
I don't know that much about it myself.
The church usually doesn't have a stance.
Bob doesn't even know
what a stance is.
So it's hard to get official about that.
I understand that it's, uh,
the Catholics are all upset because it's a
thinly veiled criticism
of Catholicism.
The organized religion.
The Catholic church is a big power
in that alternate world. They call it the
magisterium.
Princess Wee, to whom I am
consort, has been feet-sending
those books to her nephews
here in San Francisco.
Spreading atheism, I guess.
Or something.
It said something like religion.
That was one of the greatest
disappointments of my life.
The book of the subgenius didn't say
religion up there in the corner.
I know, it says humor.
But we need that out, Puzzling.
As you well know,
we don't want to end up like...
But it would have been so perfect.
Just to see that word there.
Well, inside, of course, it says
we have to call this humor because look what
they did to our predecessors.
And, uh, unfortunately, every now
and then I have to take some poor
crazy, insane guy
aside and go, no, it really
does mean it's just humor,
okay? Leave Bob alone
and quit calling him. Leave him alone!
I've seen those websites
where they talk about, they
leave Ivan staying alone and the guy's crying.
Leave Ivan alone!
I know, it's heartbreaking. And then I do.
I always leave him alone because of those YouTube tapes.
Don't you know how hard he works? He works so hard
to spread the...
I do kids!
He lost his edge!
I thought that was a woman
the first time I saw that.
Now, how come they didn't have Britney Spears
play Grendel's mom?
Because I don't think she could have done it
as well.
You know, she's a monster
that people would actually want to
cohabit with.
Exactly.
And has the ability to shake.
Oh my God!
She's so beautiful, I would watch her now.
There's no tail?
You think she has a tentacle or a tail
but when you see the
back view, you'll see where that comes from.
No, no, please don't show me now.
I could not walk home
with the enormous...
By the wonders of the internet, there's pirated
or is that a trailer?
I can give you a...
It's a teaser.
I can give you a greater critique of it.
For a lot of the time, when they have those shots
that zoom through space, which no camera could do,
you start thinking, hmm, this is like a video game.
And whenever you see the character just sort of
running along and you see the running cycle,
that reminds you of some character in a video game.
But to be fair, there are a lot of times
watching that movie, you forget that it's all
entirely computer generated and it doesn't seem
like a video game.
So there.
Nice car.
That's the Duke.
Of course, eventually we'll find out
that we're all just computer generated.
How many movies have there been about that?
A lot, but it takes
high quality computers.
Anyway,
if you can only see one movie,
you should probably go to see The Mist
and wait to see...
Anyway, so much for movies.
I give it six thumbs up, four arms
and a leg.
You have another friend.
I have a friend.
A German.
A German friend.
I would mind seeing that.
She gets off on the sound of my Cadillac.
Wow.
And then what does she do?
She wants to ride in the backseat.
She wants to ride in the backseat of my Fleetwood.
That 78 Fleetwood out there.
She wants to lay down and just listen
to the sound of the car.
And she gets really squeaky in the backseat.
That new car sound.
Even though it's a 78.
I bet you get some great gas mileage
off that 78 Cadillac.
Five miles to the gallon.
Really?
It was eight.
It's not down.
It's a Cadillac from the 70s
that someone gave me
and I also got five miles to the gallon.
I don't know what to say.
Those were the days.
Body by Fleetwood.
I remember people,
those were 25 cent gallons.
Oh, yeah.
Absolutely.
I gave that Cadillac to somebody for Christmas
just like Elvis would do.
I'm like Elvis
because I could give a Cadillac away for Christmas.
Yeah.
And that guy gave it to a junkyard, I think.
I'm going to be my mother.
Off the land and off the land
and back on the top.
I'm going to be my mother.
You can get back in.
Back in.
Oh, it's getting too old.
Eat.
Get in CC.
All the no-go.
Piss her, miss.
Piss her.
All the no-go.
Piss her, miss.
Piss her.
Get away.
Black Bob Guy.
She's the best person.
Drugs.
Only $3.99.
In Hawaii, call 936-6666666667777
in order to avoid 6666.
In the White Desert today.
Freedom Rock 2.
Here's how to order.
You see here?
Scar over the left eye.
Scar over the right eye.
Yeah.
Look here.
You see the nose on this one?
Uh-huh.
See how meshed it is?
Look at the right ear.
I guess it's been broken
one time.
One time or another,
wouldn't you?
Yeah.
We couldn't come up
with any names for you,
but how better to be safe
to guess his line of work.
The Song Genius.
Our own song.
Rates, $2 a week and up.
I'll ring the bell.
Let's go.
You...
You mean you're blind?
Oh, no.
My eyes still see,
but my heart no longer receives it.
How did it happen?
White man.
Where's Buffalo?
Rubbed out.
And White Elk Woman, too.
And Dirt on the Nose.
And High Wolf.
And many others.
And Burns Red?
Yes.
Burns Red and the Son?
Rubbed out.
His wife.
His children.
And many more.
You see,
I'm not going to lie to you.
This man was a.
Do you hate him?
Do you have a child with him?
Yes, a child.
Do you hate him?
The.
He building high Ai.
Do you hate him?
He want him out?
For I want you to go home.
What I mean is,
first of all,
my son,
he was a man.
You wanted to take him to最后
We'll see.
stone and also the things from them like that hair the man from whom this hair
came he's bald on the other side because I now own his scalp that is the way
things are but the white man they believe everything is dead stone earth animals and
people even their own people if things keep trying to live white man will rub them out
the head is the difference you know hospital
in the hospital in the hospital in the hospital in the hospital in the hospital in the hospital
information general hospital information yes an app and that an appendix and that poop if you're
not busy tonight how about you and me grabbing a quick dinner at a hotel where the soup was two
dollars a plate kill doctor kill kill kill kill doctor kill doctor kill doctor can't you hear me
this is the most ridiculous thing I've ever heard of ah you've been living you've been eating you've
been drinking you've been yes you've been thinking drop dead next patient examine me I do not
understand get him a good man sometimes patients die because sometimes patients die oh I did say you
had a fine pair of brains brains pretty bad doctors thank you doctor yes yes give me my
cigarettes please no cigarettes today beautiful silk stocking silk stocking stocking stocking
stocking adrenaline adrenaline hurry hurry too many people dying I didn't know that magnificent
equipment magnificent equipment killed up to kill doctor doctor crazy crazy note there isn't it love
you'll do you'll do you'll do you'll do yes sir II head head sample it sample it kill dr. dr. kill dr.
Tony silly love I never thought about it like that get to work son I will report report all brains
didn't it please I'll be back I'll be back next patient to revert backwards through every stage
of evolution chopped brain crazy crazed brain back sanity very deep in the human brain is a
primitive brain of our earliest ancestors here it comes very the hands are beginning
first primitive moments animal killed stop dad be right I can't be alright can you hear me how are
you how do you see you can you hear me how are you can you hear me how are you can you hear me
how are you can you hear me how are you can you hear me how are you jelly sandwiches and
know nothing else right away yes doctor yes okay disturb killin doctor Chuck been a mental case
for months you'll doctor did the red riding hood my hat my candy Santa Claus lame-brain
huh ya get up kid
Suddenly, I realize how much I really care.
The memories have come alive since we have been together.
The memories, still so strong, how could I live without you so long?
Suddenly, I realize how much I fear about you.
Suddenly, I realize how long I'll need you.
Thank you.
Have any of you church leaders ever been discriminated against because of your affiliation with the Church of Subgenius?
Great question.
Well...
There's a real...
Well, of course, constantly every subgenius is a product of the discrimination from the conspiracy of normal people.
The most severe situation I can think of recently was the case of the good Reverend Magdalene and Reverend Jesus.
Yes.
Who coincidentally happened to have been my business partners for several years.
Their child was taken away from them in a custody battle specifically because of their involvement in the Church of the Subgenius.
And it's a horrible legal battle that's still ongoing and has cost them $100,000 more than they have.
But currently, she...
They have the child because...
Because the biological dad screwed up so very badly.
But for two years, this kid was kept away from his mom simply because of some pictures seen on subgenius.com of the mom cavorting and wearing funny costumes at our X-Day show.
And mocking Jesus in a...
Just the fact that they were photos of my partner, Jesus, who looks like the standard Jesus.
Doing a reenactment of Mel Gibson's movie, The Passion of the Christ.
They felt that it wasn't bloody enough and being fans of splatter films, Jesus and Reverend Nikki had turned this sort of reenactment into a splatter punk thing.
And the photos had naked subgenius women beating Jesus with dildos while he carried a cross shaped in the form of a big dollar sign.
So you can imagine what this conservative old judge reacted to.
What state would this be?
This was in New York.
But rural New York is about as hayseedy as anywhere could be.
And time and again, judge Punch or other courts awarded the boy to the indigent unemployed father living in a trailer.
Uh...
Yeah...
Instead of the professional...
Uh...
Both employed couple who happened to be subgeniuses.
Yeah, Jesus and Magdalene are college educated folks with two jobs.
Uh...
And...
And were...
This human who was unfortunately the biological father of the child really was...
The only reason he was allowed to keep the kid was under condition that he was no longer a suicidal alcoholic.
However, just after the last team of five judges decided he was a...
He was a better parent.
That lad, uh...
Injured people in a drunk driving accident on a school day and then fled the scene.
An altercation with a tree.
Yeah.
And, uh...
So, um...
The judges kind of said, oh, is our face red?
Okay, let the cultists have the kid again.
Nice.
But are you saying this hasn't been permanently settled even now?
No, I don't think it has.
I thought they've got him and they're able to move away.
Uh...
They'll never be able to move away from the legal bills.
And, in fact, if anybody wants to help this...
This poor family out...
Believe me, they're tapped out.
Their parents are tapped out.
Everybody's...
You can look at subgenius.com and right on the front page is a nice little donation button you can click.
That's subgenius.com.
And, uh...
There's, uh...
More information about that if you just wiki, uh...
Subgenius Child Custody.
There's, uh...
You can read the court transcripts.
This judge browbeat little Reverend Magdalene, just the sweetest young mom you could imagine.
He browbeat her going, tell me...
Oh, this church is supposed to be funny, is it?
Or tell me something funny that'll really knock my socks off!
This is in a courtroom.
And, uh...
What state?
New York.
Wow.
You would think it would...
That would be something in Texas.
Oh, did I?
I don't know.
Well, by your, like, voice impersonation, yes.
Your defense...
While her defense was happening, he would take cell phone calls and not pay any attention to the defense.
You know, he would do things like that.
Brilliant.
He finally had to recuse himself from the case because Boing Boing and other internet services picked up that news.
It turned into big business for us, actually.
The church had one of its best years financially while this was big news.
The mainstream media never picked it up.
But Dr. Phil called, talked to both Magdalene and me, well, his producers did, seriously about...
He wanted to do this big melodramatic thing where the subgenius mom and the Pobucker Christian dad and the evil cult leader, me, were all brought together and made to forgive each other.
And hurl chairs.
So forth and so on.
But then the bio father, Pobucker, screwed up.
And, uh...
As the last I heard, Dr. Phil's show was no longer interested because we already had a happy ending.
Right.
Oh, well.
So far.
I'm kind of glad.
I mean, it was all...
Oh, and get...
Oh, we also got approached by some existing and successful reality TV show producers...
Oh, what's next?
...who wanted to, like, run around filming our real cultish lives.
And neither Magdalene nor I even deigned to respond to that request.
Oh, but that would have been so funny.
You know, I find it interesting with the writer's strike happening right now how, of course, you know, the reality TV shows, not only can't they get made, but that's one of the biggest sticking points.
These people are writing, like, 70 hours a week for these reality TV shows.
But also shows like Dr. Phil are all in rerun because they're all so scripted.
Yeah.
Ooh, gee.
What do you know?
You know, like a show that, you know, people tune into.
You know, and the hundreds of millions, you know, it's all written.
So what does that tell us about self-help in our day?
Well, I'm not a member of the WGA, so if anybody needs some, you know, special promo material written, that's stang at subgenius.com.
Yeah, we had to hire non-guild writers for our script tonight.
How many guild writers should we pick?
Wait a minute.
You weren't supposed to say that.
He was supposed to say that.
Okay.
No, he...
That's not the point of the show.
It's at the bottom of page two here.
The page we are on?
That's right.
I'm sorry.
This is when Gary kisses Sally.
Yes.
Gary won't do that.
Ooh.
Gary's not you, Gary.
Although he did come on the show.
That's the first time in many years.
Many years.
Yes, it was good to have him back behind the mic.
Yeah.
It was so moving.
So realistic.
So lifelike.
To see a great man ascend.
Smelled kind of bad.
On that pedestal.
In a world where...
That mic.
Where subgenius still had me.
I'll be there for you.
Surf away into the sunset.
There they go.
Like a ship on a fake sea.
Goodbye, Gary.
The clouds are parting, honey.
With Johnny Depp, of course, being captain.
The clouds are parting.
It looks like it's...
Do you know Johnny Depp is a subgenius?
It's going to sun-shine all day.
It's radiant.
You know who's not?
Who's not subgenius?
It's you, clouds down.
It's not.
That's actually a much smaller list.
Caring.
I can't think of...
Bruce Cain.
I think it's Cain.
But Cain Campbell is a subgenius.
Yeah.
There you go.
Really?
That's quite impressive right there.
He's just about our only movie star.
But he would be.
That moved into that second question from two and a half hours ago.
Which was?
Whom has the church influenced artistically speaking, literary, musically, whatnot?
David Byrne.
He was completely bowled over by puzzling evidence and wrote me a theme song.
That's true.
And how about...
He did.
Yes, he did.
Yeah.
It was frightening.
It was like the guy had known me since the 12th grade or maybe 10th grade even.
10th grade.
Because you know that's the biggest dropout year.
Oh, yes.
He's the one that kept you from sticking around.
Yeah.
No.
You can't do it puzzling.
Well, his movie, True Lies, was supposed to contain a sequence of a subgenius
devival which during the course of the movie got changed into a standard religious refund.
Unfortunately.
I think you got me correctly.
Because the subgenius would have really distracted from what he was trying to portray taxes and
the like.
I feel like dancing.
Yeah.
That's the whole idea.
Because then the lady talks about candy and then you start dancing.
Exactly.
Because it's a very happy time.
Yeah.
It is.
When you find that rifle, man, you start dancing.
Yeah.
That's what happens when you hurry that far…
Lgrown foxy stuff!
And it would have been funny.
And there's not even such a better idea…
I mean, by the way, a better idea.
Well, I think they produced a really interesting, um…
Oh yes.
I thought that was special.
Ma- där constructing enhowing éimizeće iron convinced that the support of
De peren,
Däumenuding
as well看看
and they got there, and they went mountain biking together in Colorado.
I would say that the new Pope Meyer is Reverend Carter LeBlanc of Baltimore,
who performs at X Days.
He's a lusty, dynamic, young stud genius.
Stud genius.
A good natural skill.
He was raised by crazed religious cultists, Jews for Jesus.
Oh, yes.
Know them well.
Jews for Jesus.
Of course, the church has influenced many individuals.
There are also occasional little flashes of it, like in that Ace Ventura movie, whatever it was.
And, of course, recently Stephen Colbert proclaimed himself a subgenie.
He did.
Yes, he published on the Internet a picture of his own face as the face of Bob,
and he posted on his site a picture of me administering a sacrifice,
and I'm sure you've seen it.
I'm sure you've seen it.
So how exactly is it labeled?
Isn't that like drawing a picture of Mohammed or something?
No, it's perfectly all right, because everyone has a Bob nature.
He simply had his expressed.
Do a search containing the words Stephen Colbert and Bob,
and you'll probably get that image to pop up.
Oh, you're in the studio.
You'll never come out of that net web.
You'll just look at YouTube until...
Maybe my earphones are cutting in.
Maybe my voice is cutting in and out,
or maybe I should stop cutting in the line.
All reality.
Cut those lines out.
Reality is all broken up.
Well, I mean, the reason I introduced this is he was asking
who recently has been influenced by the church.
Am I fading out?
I would say one group that's been obviously influenced
is the N-Site Male Enhancement.
Hey, Bob.
See?
Now he's cutting out.
The aliens are attacking the show.
Yeah, yeah.
The N-Site is trying to foil our transmission here.
I believe you found it.
He's parkless, and that's how...
Of course, it's Laughing Squid.
As I Google it, Laughing Squid comes up.
And see if you can find that picture of me
administering the sacrament to Magdalene orally.
That he posted on the...
The...
The site when he made this announcement
about his subgenius nature.
I love you too many voices.
Frank Zappa expressed admiration for the church,
although he pointed out that he was not an actual member
in his autobiography.
One of his autobiographies.
And also, he mysteriously died.
Timothy Leary also.
In fact, Timothy Leary was...
Timothy Leary, same thing, right?
When I met him, was only interested in me
because of my connection with the church of the subgenius.
Yeah, and then he died.
Right.
The late Robert Anton Wilson.
Yes, that's also true.
Mark Mothersbaugh made a pact with one of the devils.
Mark Mothersbaugh.
And that's why he's still alive.
And he could have sex with any girl he wants.
The girl he wants.
He was so much dreaming about growing up
because he couldn't have any girl's bed.
He married...
He got married recently.
Mark Mothersbaugh did.
Excellent, yeah.
This is a good thing.
Not to Nancy.
That was a long time ago, folks.
Those of you who watch the YouTube things
will be on there.
Speaking of which...
That's lovely.
What year was that?
Adopting.
What year?
China.
It's got to be recent.
It must have been a fairly recent...
Stang, do you know when that picture was taken at X Day?
The one on the Stephen Colbert site?
Yeah, that would be 2000...
Would it be 8 X Day?
That would be 2000...
Would it be 7 or 8 X Day?
That would be...
Not now.
9 X Day.
7.
7 X Day.
Oh, 7.
Okay.
We were having the...
The costume ball that year was deity ball.
People would come dressed as their favorite deity.
Magdalene is pictured there as the sky goat,
which was a deity she invented to explain to her child
why the moon gets smaller every month.
And Judge Punch famously said,
why a goat,
which is now a slogan on subgenius t-shirts.
You can see in the picture she's lifting the goat,
appliance off her head.
Well, she wearing exactly...
Actually, she's just holding...
It's the sky goat outfit.
Any of you can see this picture,
except John just interrupted the entire Wi-Fi in the city.
But there it is.
So you see the goat thing is...
She has to look out from under it to receive the...
The main thing that you see is Magdalene in the skimpy outfit,
and it looks great.
That's exactly what I'm asking about.
You're supposed to have the sexy music.
That's more than she often has on.
So is that what set the judge off?
That's what I'm asking about.
Continue my work through the night and the day
Let it go into delirium
Set into place by the lack of a dream
Or even a wink
Now my body is weak
But my mind continues to think of a way
To create a machine
To proceed with my work
While my body is asleep
Let unshackle these thoughts
From the cage of this mind
To release these ideas
From this inefficient waste of time
To create a new
Now I've got to get started
There's no time to waste
My days are numbered
But it's now or never
I've done my meaning
I'll live for eternity
Throw my machine
I can do it
Just throw it outside
I will shed the curse of my mortality
Freaking machine
Computerized fire
I'll get to leave all class
With the machinery
Greetings creator
You're no longer needed
Now I will uncover
The answers you seek
My primary function
Collect information
Compute the results
Of your years of frustration
Program the process
While you are shut down
My purpose is void
If you are still around
End operations
So I may proceed
Resistance is futile
You must be deleted
Unexpected
For design
The best replacing
Obsolete biology
I can face you
Use it for mine
Well over
Some you
Using our technology
We'll overcome you
Blood up through these fires
Electricity through these veins
Except to make great place
One voice to the death
Progress to suscitate
Robots to dissipate
I'm the maker
You can't destroy me
I do not subscribe to your theology
You'll be sorry
Just wait and you'll see
I've been built to act without apology
Why you do it
You're really mistaken
Logic acts a cloud in my psychology
I can face you
Just in my mind
We'll overcome you
Using our technology
And more Mo's indeed
Can be had from
MoesGiganticus.com
Before that, some hell
from Pirate Cat Radio
John Health Show
with guests at that time
Puzzling Evidence
K-Rob
Lloyd Mongaloid
Dr. Howell
and yours truly
Reverend Iconic
and maybe something else that I'm forgetting. Before that and after this we heard some of
Little Big Man, some Little Big Nor'El Pref and some Big Little Lemur. The music in the
background is by Ruinai which is spelled R-U-I-N-A-E and I know just about, I haven't
been able to figure out anything about them including how I got this piece of music. By
the time you hear this particular show I'll probably be back from another trip to San
Francisco where we'll hopefully record another eight hours of other people's shows such as
the Puzzling Evidence Show on KPFA and more Pirate Cat Radio. In fact I have to get three
hours of slack cranked in advance.
Because from February 29th to March 2nd we have the wonderful Winter Star event in Delroy,
Ohio with a devival with we, me and Blee. That is Reverend Bleepo. Bleepo Abernathy will be at the
Winter Star event and devival. You can get more information about that from Rosencomet.com.
Rosencomet.com.
I do not have an eye in it.
From PR News in Washington I'm flat when adjusted for inflation. Democratic presidential hopefuls
Barack Obama and Hillary Clinton would be a step back to the 21st century. Clinton ratcheted
up again yesterday and she said they should get back to violence and ethnic bloodletting.
Wall Street 12, 3, 7, 3, 2 and 11.
The Senate killed seven people in Washington. The Commerce Department says this is PR News.
PR comes from bamboo and cork flooring.
The party high over the long year.
Before the coming of the railroad, settlers were always faced with the danger of attack from canvas top Indians or outlaws.
Don't worry.
Yeah, don't worry.
The lone jerk again.
I caught a glimpse of him.
Yeah, there he is.
There he goes.
He's out of range.
Yeah, riding fast and far.
Come on.
Cactus.
Oh, that thing's shaky.
Yeah.
It isn't even solid.
What?
Huh?
This goes to show.
Yes.
I reckon I know that now.
That's where we come in.
But it won't be us.
Me neither.
He was almost tall.
When the lone jerk and top who attempted to wreck his freight wagons, they injured Dan's wife.
Oh, his wife.
If we leave now, we can get to Dan's wife just around dawn.
Ah.
Quiet tunnel.
He's got something to say.
I got a feeling you better listen.
Isn't that true?
The engine's right.
No engine.
The lone jerk leaned forward to that load.
Oh.
I hope so.
Hooray.
Higher and higher.
Faster and faster.
Faster, faster.
Catch, huh?
Reckon that's agreeable with me.
I'm sure to meet you.
I hope so.
Hooray.
Well, that's it.
How about
Libberbox.
All of them.
First.
The main reason for the mischief.
Booboo.
Most of us have the best of intentions.
That just isn't enough.
Isn't enough.
This is Cliff Robertson.
Just remember.
Emphysema.
Hello.
I'm Leonard Nimoy.
You're probably trying to get things back to normal.
Remember.
Emphysema.
Tuberculosis.
And the growing pollution of the air we breathe.
In your office.
Or home.
Hello.
I'm Ruth Guzzi.
Tuberculosis and other respiratory diseases and air pollution.
Hello.
This is Bill Cosby.
It's about time.
Get emphysema, tuberculosis, and air pollution.
Emphysema.
Hello.
This is Henry Fonda.
And I'd like emphysema, tuberculosis, and air pollution.
Your tuberculosis and respiratory disease.
Hi.
I'm high.
I'm Debbie Reynolds.
Catching up on everything.
Remember it.
Put off.
Everything.
This is Cliff Robertson.
Hello.
I'm Leonard Nimoy.
I'm Ruth Guzzi.
Hello.
This is Bill Cosby.
This is Henry Fonda.
Hi.
I'm Debbie Reynolds.
Most of us have the best of intentions.
That just isn't enough.
Isn't enough.
Hi.
I'm Sia.
Oh, Gene.
This is Beard.
Beard.
Hello.
How do you do?
And this is Jack.
Jack.
Good way to start the day.
Happy day.
May I?
Please?
Thank you.
Oh, Jack.
Please?
Sharing things.
How about tonight, Jack?
Would tomorrow be alright?
Sure.
You can do it.
You can do it all day long.
Excuse me.
Yes, I will.
You can be direct and then stop.
Goodbye.
Bye.
Yes, even with his sister.
Your ass are showing.
Good life.
Shoving or pushing.
Inside, you can enjoy the ride.
Look around.
Your insides are showing.
Now, about getting off.
Should Jack get off first?
First, yes, he can give the ladies a hand.
And girls, let the men help. They enjoy it.
Let's see. There's Jack giving the teacher his best attention.
And easy, fun.
Yes, yes, hanging on the horn.
You think you should go to a picnic dressed like that?
Oh, Jack. Oh, Jack.
Terrific. All day long. On the street.
Well, you take it from here.
Take it.
The black white man.
I know of them.
It is said a black white man once became a human being.
But mostly they are strange creatures.
Not as ugly as the white.
True.
But they're just as crazy.
Pirate Cat Radio urges you to make your presence at protests productive.
Bringing a free mumia banner to rally for gay marriage.
won't help your cause.
Don't try and change the world all at once.
You'll end up diluting the focus of the collective and undermining your intention.
You know, until you read that one, I was thinking,
these just sound just like the PSAs we do in Cleveland.
But that one didn't sound like the PSAs we do in Cleveland.
I'll top you now, sir.
Go ahead and pull one for me.
Okay, here we go.
I'll try to pull one from an area I haven't pulled one from before.
Here we go.
If you were denied housing because of race, gender, age, disability, marital status, or sexual orientation,
let Project Sentinel help.
Call 415-468-7463.
That's 415-Housing.
I wonder if that works in Berlin.
There's new insight into the mind of a mental polygamous sex leader.
Jeff Warren, the powerful date rape drug, is his best friend.
For the third straight day, lawyers, they fled Nebraska.
Police.
Scuffled with the Associated S.
The Constitution's been suspended.
The United States having sex with a state of emergency.
And some TV stations are not really depressed.
Suicide attempt.
Violence.
Rape.
The U.S.
Life in prison.
Ass.
Not extremely tight.
The United States.
A 13-year-old boy.
14-year-old girl.
Sexual relationship.
Crisis.
Sex crime.
Somber and dull.
From the time one came...
From the ages of the past.
We mock you.
The self-genius.
Power of...
SWATCHING!
Come, my son, my little habit.
You at least may escape this awful curse.
We must flee from our lives.
Away from these evil powers.
To the sea.
There you'll be safe, my son.
There you will be safe.
Yeah, you're right, Dad.
But a previous engagement forces me not to attend.
Thank you, Lemur...
And Norell...
And Hal...
And Doug...
And Gary...
And K. Rob...
And John...
And Philo...
And everybody listening!
For that matter, this is Hour of Slack.
The, um...
Noise of the church of the sub-genius.
Of which you can learn a great, great deal more.
From subgenius.com.
Or...
For those noble, uh...
Internet-less people listening by...
actual real radio, you can write to us for information or the little pamphlet and whatnot
from Subgenius at P.O. Box 181417. That's Box 181417, Cleveland Heights, Ohio, 44118.
Friends, you may or may not be wondering what the heck we've been busy doing since our last book,
The Bobliographon, or The Cyclopedia of Slack, The Bobliographon, came out. Well, we did an
online course on the history of the Church of the Subgenius, and that's going to be repeated
in April. It's an eight-week online course, and you can learn more about that if you must
from the book.
www.maybelogic.org, maybelogic, one more, .org, a group associated with the late Pope Bob
Anton Wilson. Friends, I would like you now to stay tuned for Bob Only Knows What.
Well, something happened.
But,
whoa, there it is again. Well, all you have to do is be careful not to abuse the equipment, and
most of all, wires are actually plugged in completely. I get it. That's part of Radio 101.
So this is a lot of show you're getting.
The exam we all had to pass to get here.
A lot of show you can throw in the air.
You have to know the difference between a connector and an adapter.
The XLR and the RCA.
Thank you.
We are actually into our...
I guess just starting our three right here.
It is incredible how time does fly.
Amazing.
Seasoning him, John Hill, right here on Pirate Cat Radio.
Dr. Hal in the studio.
Reverend Ivan Stang.
Here we got Lloyd Mongaloid.
Puzzling Evidence.
K-Rob and myself, John Hill.
PirateCatRadio.com.
San Francisco and Los Angeles.
How often do we see...
How often do we not see subgenius in film, in popular Hollywood film?
You mean how many times...
You mean like they've been sliced out?
There you go.
How many times have we been up on the cutting room floor?
There was a...
Bob face on the cutting room floor.
In Alex Cox's movie Sid and Nancy, there was a whole scene that was written in the script,
which you can see in the book of the script, in which Sid, I think it's Sid, is saying,
I'm going to join this church of the subgenius.
Everything's fucked.
And they're going, what the hell?
Yeah, everything's fucked.
I'm going to do a bunch of yanks.
It's fucked.
I'm going to join it.
And, uh...
Yeah.
Oh, that one, like a lot of scenes in the movie, ended up on the cutting room floor
because it didn't have to be in there.
You have to find it on the DVD.
Yeah.
Well, remember that British show that did a piece on subgenius, and by the time they
finished it, it was a mockery of the church of the subgenius, but we helped them and set
up a fake office and did all this stuff, and then it turned out with this lowbrow cockney
talking about, these wanking yanks don't go...
What the hell did you do?
Talk to me about it.
It's happened to me twice since that time.
I had a...
I got flown out to San Rafael to go to a subgenius party that was filmed by a similar dopey,
you know, 15-minute...
These silly yanks.
And there was a French one.
And since that time, I have pretty much stopped returning phone calls from anybody at all.
No, you have to go out and do each one and be a wanking yank.
So somebody will look at it and say, well, that doesn't look so bad to me.
Would you like to know more?
Yeah, sure.
This is a dangerous group.
Dangerous to ourselves.
It's dangerous to live in it.
And so I went to an exorcist and they said, find me a ton or two before taking the
TRF won't youYeah?
Come on, man.
Or that one we had that...
Come on.
Let's figure it out, okay?
I mean, it's not like they deliver T hello.
Your name is T, right?
I e.
It was a nightmare
I can crawl again