This is an emergency. All stations position red.
Godzilla alert level three. All personnel to action stations.
Hey, what's this?
What's that?
It's a...
Subgenius Power of Swag.
Get from me!
Son of a bitch!
Hello. Hello, sir. It's lovely to see you again. Are you well?
It's a Godzilla-saur.
What's a Godzilla-saur?
Hey, wait. You can't come in here. It's off limits. You can't stay here.
Yeah, I'm sorry about that.
Absolutely.
It seems dogs don't leave places like this.
Please even a statue of Godzilla will not gradually come to my service.
Mongoloid, he was a Mongoloid
And the other knew him
And he determined what he could see
Mongoloid, he was a Mongoloid
One from his own too many
And he determined what he could see
And he wore a hat
And he had a job
And he brought home the bacon
So that no one knew
Mongoloid, Mongoloid
His friends were unaware
Mongoloid, he was a Mongoloid
Nobody even cared
One from his own too many
Mongoloid, he was a Mongoloid
And he determined what he could see
And he wore a hat
And he had a job
And he brought home the bacon
So that no one knew
Mongoloid, he was a Mongoloid
And the other knew him
And he determined what he could see
Mongoloid, he was a Mongoloid
One from his own too many
And he determined what he could see
Mongoloid, he was a Mongoloid
One from his own too many
He said, wait, not yet
Please, not yet
Hoping on a Videos hop
So he was was And he said
On the way to America
Long reached the moon
And he, he said
A ton of former friends
Didn't want he do it
All right, so long
Robin Hood brought home the taken so that no one knew
Manga Lloyd
Manga Lloyd!
It determined what he...
It determined what he could...
It determined what he could do?
Alright! Next up, it looks like I've got Manx on the ramp.
Come on up here.
Everybody say hello and welcome, give a round of applause to Manx.
I was gonna write something, but then I didn't.
This seems to be the next day of...
Fuck it.
Fuck it!
Fuck it. I'm too busy. Fuck it, I'm too broke.
Fuck it, I...
Just don't feel like going out into the world and camping.
But you know what?
I had a sickness in my heart.
I know you felt it too.
A sickness that can only be cured with one kind of medicine.
And that's coming here to fucking X-Day and hanging out with you yeti bitches.
That's the one!
Fortunately, I have a very good doctor.
His name is Dr. Bob...
J.R. Bob Dobbs.
And he gives me a prescription for slack.
As well as other things, uh, excuses and doctorates and such.
But, um...
Bob is a great doctor because he knows better than to try to force businesses...
to compete with the medication department.
He doesn't need to do any of that shit.
Because he's...
He's already got that covered.
In other ways, backdoor channels like he does.
But, um...
But I'm happy being here, being with you guys.
I needed it.
I spent a whole year just aching to be back here with you guys.
Woo!
Because...
Being out in the world, I gotta tell you, it's...
It's a frightening place.
It sucks!
I spend way too much fucking time on Facebook and it just depresses the shit out of me.
You just wait two more days!
That's right, that's right.
It's coming, it's coming.
But, um...
Partially I've been depressed because I...
I took a statistics class and I...
I know what my odds are.
I know what my odds are in the world of actually finding some true slack and some...
Some true companionship with a...
With an Uberfem.
I gotta tell you, the odds are pretty slim.
You gotta...
Really find that one person out of...
What, a hundred...
One person out of like a hundred and fifty million fucking people.
It's insane.
But you know what I did a month ago?
I fucking found one.
Yeah!
Tell us!
Who are you?
I met her at all places at a fucking karaoke bar.
Because she was singing my fucking music.
And I told her about Bob.
And she said, that sounds neat.
And I showed her a rise.
And she said, that's fucking genius!
I said, no!
It's subgenius!
She said, is there a book?
I said, goddamn right!
There's a fucking book!
I got four of them!
She said, give me that shit!
And you gave it to her!
I did!
You gave it to her good!
Hell fucking yeah, I did!
Yeah!
Praise Bob!
I gave her that book of the subgenius and she said, oh my, this is gonna take me a while
to get through.
There's lots of little pictures and diagrams and shit.
Yeah, you had a lot.
But not only did I find an Uberfem, I found myself.
Because, you look at all these dating sites out there on the internet and all these companies
trying to hook you up with somebody.
There's an old adage that's full of shit that says opposites attract.
No dating site in the world goes out and looks for our opposites.
The entire search for a dating partner is only a search for yourself.
Yes, sir.
So if you're looking for somebody to complete you, guess what?
You're already fucking completed.
Yes, sir.
Good luck to you.
You just gotta look in the mirror.
You just gotta look at yourself.
That's what you need.
That's what you want.
You just wanna fuck yourself.
Yes!
The entire search for dating is just masturbatory fantasy.
Woo!
But with the opposite gender.
Everybody go fuck yourselves!
Hooray!
Okay, now what?
You wanna watch?
I don't care to watch.
If you feel like shit, I don't care.
You don't have to show it to me.
Knock yourself out.
No, I'm distracted.
Thank you.
Thank you for that.
I appreciate that.
Peace be with you all.
Oh!
Somebody's getting laid tonight.
I'm gonna get stiff just like my leg.
Gonna get some roll aids.
Woo!
So don't give up the fight because the fight is not…the only thing you got is keep
it going.
Everything that Anders said is fucking true, is gold.
I'm in the teaching program.
I see that shit every fucking day.
Woo!
So hail Reverend Anders.
Yeah!
You'really inspiring.
Yeah.
You've got it right.
You need more funding.
They should have cut his funding.
They should have tripled it!
Woo!
Trip prodded or actually added.
Added.
added.
So, I'm going to turn
the mic back over to whoever
is next on the podium, or on the ramp.
I see somebody.
And Pisces will go first.
So, raise Bob!
Hey!
First of all, I want you to give
Manx a round of applause.
Thank you, Reverend
Manx Darkpaw,
ranting at 17
X Day Drill.
Before that, we heard Devo's Mongoloid,
covered by Static
Department. And this
is Hour of Slack number
1494.5
XXX.
Another of those really loose internet-only
specials containing material that's too
rude, crude, and unattractive
for our beloved broadcast stations.
But, certainly
good enough for you podcast
downloading ne'er-do-wells.
We're nearing the end of our stash of last summer's
X Day recordings. Every summer, we record enough
material in one week to stretch across the next six
months of Hour of Slack. In minutes!
And yet, we still have a few
hear-worthy remnants left.
Coming up, music by
Reagan's Polyp, who weren't at X Day, by the way.
They just have CDs out.
Plus, a few more. But, I'm going to give you a little bit of a sneak peek.
Sermons from 17 X Day Drill by Pisces,
Reverend Wilhelm Stahlhelm, and Reverend Spike.
But first, this parable about Moses by
Reverend Richard Scull, as read for the
kiddies by Priestess Pisces. Incidentally,
this piece is specifically making fun of
the bigoted ravings of the renowned
subgenius hater and anti-semitic kook,
Michael Alcandor.
The Jews were
forced by the Freemasons to build pyramids for the
pharaoh of Egypt. The pharaoh, with her
willowing blonde hair, was worshipped by
the Glorps of Egypt, who did purchase
posters of her and watch her TV shows.
But the Jews were not happy. Their bagels
were stale, and they weren't even making
scale when hauling big boulders up over
the sandstone all over the friggin'
desert and piling them in front of MGM
Grand in Vegas. To make matters worse, the
only entertainment they were allowed was
a Wayne Newton show. Finally, the Jews got
to see their shop steward, Moses, to talk to
Pharah. He approached Pharah in a commanding
voice and said,
In the name of Viacom, pay my people's
scale. Go shove it, replied Pharah, with a
whip of her luscious hair. I'm a star.
So, Moses promised Pharah a course of seven
plagues. First was the plague of TV guides.
The TV guides for North Platte were sent
to Las Vegas by mistake. Then there was
the plague of Yugos. All the cars that
Pharah's people drove were forced into the
shops, and they all had to drive Yugos
for a week. It got worse. There was the
plague of Shatners, the plague of wiener
dogs, the plague of man boobs, the plague
of having the Dallas Cowboys as your
favorite team, and still the Pharah would
not pay Moses' people scale. The TV guides
were not able to pay Moses for the plague
of the Jewish people. Finally, Moses brought
forth the worst plague of all times. He called
the head of all Jews, who was also the head
of Viacom, Summer Murray Rothstein Redstone.
And using his great powers, he brought forth
the plague of being out of vogue. And lo, the
Pharah was replaced by a young girl with much
bigger tits on her TV show, and the masses
did not buy the Pharah's merchandise, and the
Pharah was no longer able to buy the merchandise.
The Pharah was no longer featured on the cover
of People magazine. With this, the Pharah's
powers of bargaining were destroyed. The people
of Moses were released from their contracts
and moved out to Los Angeles. On their way,
they faced the waters of Lake Powell, and there
was a worry of what to do. So they camped out
at the Holiday Inn while Moses went up to
the mountain to ask for directions. While Moses
was away, his people wandered down to the bar
for a happy hour. There was much drinking,
dancing of disco, and vomiting into toilet paper.
The people of Moses were all
in the same boat. Moses was angry, for Moses
was not invited to happy hour. So Moses held
up the tablet of his iPhone and cast it down
upon the ground. And lo, the iPhone did him a favor.
He put the tablet of his iPhone in his mouth,
and he put his eye out. And Moses was sued and
lost in court. And while the Jews moved on to
Hollywood, where they did make trashy, obsolete
leftist propaganda disguised as entertainment,
Moses was stuck being a busboy at the truck stop
in Needles. The end.
Now, there's another line I wrote down.
Oh, there's more?
Yeah, from Charlene, our hostess up at the
top of the hill. Charlene is one of the founders
of Wisteria, and she's put on a lot of festivals.
She and Princess We were talking about putting
on festivals as a programmer. And the line was,
when it rains, programming runs around with
Muppet arms screaming.
Right, because like you see when it's raining,
you can't have your festival.
It made me envision those arms on little sticks,
you know, they have their arms on little sticks.
Right outside a gas station, you know, waving
those arms.
Or a used car lot.
And that's what happened last year when it rained.
Pisces was running around with Muppet arms screaming.
Hmm. Grover and what was the other one?
Cheers to Mordor and Corpse, I'll tell you your flaw.
So perhaps your soul will hear me.
You had a chance to join us.
You had a chance to be here near me.
But you choose to keep your ways among the pinks now in their graves.
I gave you a chance to be saved.
And you laughed.
And now I laugh.
The warrant was signed in frobs, smoke, and blood.
Ending coming with death from above.
So tell me more, dear, about your God's love.
Because I'm not a saint.
Is he sitting with me laughing?
Can you hear him laughing?
I'm watching you flailing, wasting your breath.
Hoping and praying to stop what comes next.
But your accounts are closed.
You're writing bad checks.
And I'm here to collect.
I'm here to collect.
Hello?
I think I have another rancher up here.
So come on.
Come on.
I'll coax you.
Everybody, give a round of applause for Wilhelm.
Woo!
Good evening, fellow musicians.
I have no script.
I'm going to improvise.
I do read the news, and I'm aware, and I see the propaganda, and it saddens me.
I mean, I'm doing okay.
I have my slack, but it saddens me that there's so many that don't have slack
and so many that Bob has not found.
Unfortunately, Bob did find me.
I guess I'm more here to testify than I am to rant.
Testify!
I'm here to represent the quiet people.
And as you know, or if you don't know me, I'm a pretty quiet guy,
and my vocabulary may not necessarily be rocketing.
Rocketing!
Yes!
Thank you.
You speak some genius.
What do you mean?
And I just wanted to share with you, for those of you that may have hard times
or difficult times, there is hope,
and you can draw a lot of strength from your faith
and by your hard work.
Thank you.
And I do.
About a year ago, my place of employment was infiltrated by a picture-perfect definition of pink.
My place of employment became absolutely miserable.
I mean, being there, it was a real drag,
and this guy was on a mission to drive everyone there down,
and it was bad news.
And I reached a point where I wasn't sure if I was going to hang in there or not.
I'm talking about keeping my job.
And I remembered a really, really swell book.
A lot of you have read it.
A lot of you really know it well.
Yes, sir!
Well, this is an interesting thing.
Number one on the back of my truck, my truck cab, I have a beware sticker.
Yes, sir.
And I take a lot of pride in that, and it's got a picture of Bob,
and I'm proud to have it there, and if people want to raise an eyebrow, it's all right by me.
I got my thing.
If you don't, tough luck, duck.
Thank you.
So on lunch breaks, I made it a practice to get out of the shop and get away from this guy,
get away from the negativity and the bad vibes.
And every lunch break, I would reread the book.
I've been through it, and I enjoy it.
It's meant a lot to me, and this became my routine to go out and reread.
I started from the beginning, and I was just working my way through,
and something really awesome happened.
About six months of putting up with this guy, maybe it was eight months, he was dismissed.
Yes, sir.
And life got better.
Yes.
So if you're down in the dumps and things are going bad, man, you got to hang on to your slack
and be proud you're a subgenius and draw strength and have faith because you can pull through, man,
and things can get better.
Yes, sir.
And so I'm here to testify.
I represent the quiet people, and I want you all to have a good night,
and I want you all to enjoy the next day, and that's it.
Thank you.
Amen.
We love you, Winona.
Woo-hoo.
One more round of applause for Wilhelm, by the way.
Are you moving softly and carrying a big...
Yes, yes.
With the new Cream Rabbit, you can give someone an orgasm while standing up to 600 yards away.
If you have good aim.
Cream Rabbit, Cream Rabbit.
Load them fire.
Cream Rabbit, load them fire.
Cream Rabbit, Cream Rabbit.
guitar solo
Here you go, hi stupid, why'd you want to go get pinned?
Ah!
Oh wait, look at this.
Last to start!
So I don't have anything prepared, um, I just have to say this is my seventh year here,
and I've finally gotten to the point where Ivan and Pisces have actually know my name,
because I hang in the background so much, and that's kind of my thing.
But, I know I enjoy everything.
So, I got to say thank you to this man.
to everybody who has given me slack
for the past seven years of me coming on
and showing up and not really giving anything back
to everybody. And I feel a little bit
bad about that, but you guys all rock
and this is the greatest party ever.
So I just had to come up and say that.
So yeah.
That's slack.
You guys all rock and I enjoy hanging out
with all of you and I can't see anybody up here
with all the fucking lights, but that's okay.
And I've come to say that. So thank you!
Thank you!
There's so much love.
It's like one great big cuddle.
Except it's a sweaty cuddle.
And one of you didn't bathe.
Thank you.
Everybody give Spike
another round of applause.
Real quick.
Great bullshit!
You're blockers!
Suds, it's bitch,
not witch. I can't fly this.
And Vice-Attach is right.
One of the things that you have to remember
is that
you can't go to
the giant machine
head on and just bang
on it with your fists.
On the other hand,
you can put superglue in the gears
when no one's looking
and let the machine destroy itself.
Suds Bishal was right.
We have a conspiracy to fight,
not each other.
Zealoth, Zeal Zealoth Hunter
slash Reverend Scapegoat.
He was right.
This is a cool party.
I'm not going to lie.
And there's a lot of love
I'm hearing from guys like Spike.
Good Reverend Roger
is explaining to us
via the voice of Stang
the actual complications
of what we are up against.
But we're all here
despite all of the
setbacks and losses.
We are here
and despite
all of the ways
the conspiracy has attempted to stop us.
If there is nothing else you gain
from showing up to X-Day,
even if Bob screws us again,
even if the saucers don't come,
if you go home
realizing that you have allies
in the war against the Khan,
if that's all you gain,
you're going to be in trouble.
You've gained a lot.
And in a way that's slack too.
I'm going to do another call for ranters.
You can start wandering up here.
I can't see you by the way.
As every ranter said,
you guys are,
I can see the guys on the wall.
And I can see the sound booth.
And that's it.
Is there anyone else who would like to rant?
Because if you don't,
then I'm going to do a really horrible acapella song.
A cover of an Elton John song.
Are you guys serious?
You gotta do a jig with it.
They're all taking part in the sacred doctrine of raceability.
They want to be erased.
Eraseability?
I take total blame for this one.
So, I'm an Elton John fan,
which is probably...
I don't know if that's surprising or not.
So, I also have a problem with taking songs that are,
a little back story on this.
I have a,
and we've seen some of my horribles,
and I've posted them in groups.
I have this problem that if I get a song stuck in my head,
I can turn it into a Bob song almost instantly.
So, but I can't sing on the podium.
Hold on a second.
That's not a problem.
That's a fucking hell of a talent.
Yeah, I can't sing.
I can't sing with it on the podium.
Actually, if you put that one back, I can do the other one.
Oh, you're gonna live the other one?
Yeah, let's do that.
So, hold on just a second.
Are we live?
Oh, yeah.
So, the other day I woke up,
it was about two weeks ago,
I woke up, I was getting ready for work,
and Sud says,
and Bob lies bleeding from the head.
And I said,
give me three minutes.
And this is what I came up with.
The froth that's in his stash box,
it's gotten harsh and dry.
Everything about this guy feels like a fucking lie.
Oh, it doesn't seem a year ago to this very day
that I gave my money to the big smiling face
and waited for X day.
And Bob lies bleeding from the head.
Oh, I killed him before he could fuck us all again.
Cause I met him on the road and asked him what he said,
but his smile was just too much and so I shot him dead.
And Bob lies bleeding from the head.
So I wonder if this bullet will leave a scar on your head.
But because your pipe still burns,
I'm sure that we are through.
Cause you'll resurrect like every other time.
I know I'm happy now.
But if you were me,
you would've done the same, Bob.
You'd kill you anyhow.
Sing along.
And Bob lies bleeding from the head.
Oh, I killed him before he could fuck us all again
Well, I met him on the road and asked him what he said
But his smile was just too much and so I shot him dead
And Bob Lyle's bleeding from the head
We talked about doing that, but Elton John is like an acquired taste
And I don't know many people who can play that on piano
I probably should have asked
So now that I've embarrassed myself
It was wonderful
I came
Three times
I keep telling you I only have one wet neck
I mean, God
God
I might have some baby wipes or something, I don't know
I don't know
Sometimes he was on bass and drums
And sometimes Suds Peshaw was on guitar
Anyway, the song is Peabrake
To be followed by a flush
And then after that, the band Monkey Hive
Now with Suds and Pisces
Doing the song rant called
Hate, Subgenius Style
But first, Reverend Angry Larry with Peabrake
We'll overcome this
But if it isn't always good
And if it is, then there's a reason touched
Joe Cheevar
In 2006, vimos by Father Joe
Over time at John Modena's Marines
At минимum speed
Thank you.
I really have to pee.
I'm not kidding.
My bladder's getting big
from eating all the privy.
Whatever that means.
A lot of the booze
needs to come out.
guitar solo
It's Devo, Devo
laying out there.
He's laying on the rocks.
He's got a boner.
He doesn't have much
hair.
But he's wearing tan shorts
like every angry Larry.
guitar solo
Pisces just took a whiz behind the stage
She thought it was funny cause I just was talking about
Devo Devo and me
She's wearing a red blue shirt
I'm not color blind
I'm eating a bite cause I can't tell if you can hear me
Can you hear me?
Okay, those guys over there can hear me
Oh, and two beats can hear me too
If I had blood I'd blush
We're the dirt piles
I'm not talking about a pile of dirt
I'm talking about when you get piles from sitting on some frozen concrete
And your ass gets all fucked up
And then it was just sand shoved all over to try and make it better
We're real doctor music
Not like those fucking
Other
Alien fucks
Like alien amino fucks
Can't even show up
Don't fucking clap
No
You all
You all have to clap
You're such an asshole
Your girlfriend's an asshole too
Don't walk away yet
I'm not done
Hating you
I hate what's for dinner
I had hate for breakfast too
Hated my morning coffee
Hated bedtime too
Hated what comes natural
Hate for all the yetikins
Hate for the old
Hate we got plenty for you so
Hey, fuck you
Come again
You know something douchebag
I'm pretty tired of your spit
Things are changing
Right about now
Hello fan
I'm pretty tired of your spit
Meat and shit
I can tell one thing
You're missing out
About wow wow
And I can tell you another thing
You're wasting my time right now
Oh Jesus fucking Christ
Are you still talking?
Bitch you yeast
You dried up cunt
An incarnation of rectal itch
Oh yeah motherfucker
Just cause you think
You're hot shit
Didn't help the fact
That you're a big dumb fuck
Whose lady ran off
With his best friend
He was smart enough
To pay his thirty five
You needle dicked
Incompetent fucktard
Let's go for a ride
You and your
Twat booger girlfriend
Can go back to
Padunkerville asshats all
Before I shove your head
Down your throat
And out your fucking ass
Asshole
I'm gonna count to three
So you better start running
Shit for brains
Pink ass motherfucker
Cause I'm about to unleash
The rage of a serious round
Of uber femme
On your candy ass
Hate you're such an asshole
Hate your girlfriend too
Hate don't walk away yet
Cause I'm not done hating you
Hate sweats for dinner
Hate for breakfast too
Hate my morning coffee
And some hate at bedtime too
Hate for breakfast too
adelmś Vielleicht!
Oh excuse me
Were ya talkin'?
Cause you sounded
Like a chicken squawkin'
Let's be honest, you're just a sheep
A conspiracy of play toy, blind and weak
Bow wow wow, the wolves are loose
Let me give you a little rope and you can make your own news
I have no pity for the pinks or their kind
Too bad this movie has got no rewind
Perhaps they'll regret the laughs and the taunts
The false sense of security they so love to flaunt
I've got no pity, nor any remorse
They get what they deserve, the plot has run its course
They took from my brother
I'm not a fool, I'm not a fool
I'm a man of pure yeti blood
And they stole from our sisters who share Connie's love
They don't deserve any less than they get
They choose the path and now the pinks will die by it
So brothers and sisters, my partners in slack
Raise the glass while the earth's turned black
We lost many battles, we lost many lives
We lost many battles, but we won the war
There's no turning back, no unlocking the door
Enjoy this vengeance so saccharine and sweet
Inhale deeply the smell of burnt pink meat
Those who fucked you, now they are undone
The journey of eternal pleasures for us has begun
To take you home, to take you home
Need them pills for Bobbin, did you write?
Look out the windows and bid the earth goodnight
Relax and lean back and smile with Bob's grin
Cause tonight, my brethren, the real fun begins
Oh, yeah, I feel like I'm in heaven
I feel like I'm in heaven
Oh, yes, yes, yes, friends
Hate subgenius style by Monkey Hive
Next we'll cut to the Starwood Festival
Actually the one from 2013, not this last one
With some business wherein I, Reverend Stang
Read some salacious details about where little subgeniuses come from
That was all originally written by Nenslow
Did I remember to say
Wake up, sleep, and die?
Sleeple?
Yes, I did
Princess Wee coined that term, sleeple
I was bitching like I do every three days
About people who call everybody else sheeple
I must see 50 times a day in the internet flame war columns
And at the bottom of all the news articles
Wake up, sheeple
God, can't they think of something more original?
It's off like
Wake up, sheeple
You're all the same, sheeple
And they're all saying that
The first time I heard that used as an insult, sheeple
I think it was Chaz Smith's radio show in the early 90s
And I thought it was pretty clever the first time I heard it
25 years later and all the sheeple are calling each other sheeple
Gee
That's a great advancement
Okay
What, what
Oh
We did the early days of natural philosophy
That's what they called science
Before they thought of the word science
We covered
Oh, we didn't cover where little subgeniuses come from
And this will be just perfect
I may have done this one last year under the title
Why sex feels good and pain hurts
It's sad that we have to accept that
But it explains stuff like that, isn't it?
Now if you don't believe these, some of these creatures
Some people think they're mythical
But if you go up to Caffeina's
You'll see that they sell maps of wisteria
That show where you can find these very species of animals
But this is where little subgeniuses come from
Now if y'all aren't married yet
You better know that you're not married yet
You better not try this
Now wasn't there somebody here who needed to get married
They wanted to try it, so they needed to get married
Right, Reverend Anacron and
Marie
I'll just, anyway
If there's anyone here who objects to the binding of these two
In wedded bliss
I don't want to hear about it
Go away
Just shut up
I'm a holy man and you're married now
Now shake on it and say
It's a holy man
It's a deal
I do
This is a 24-hour marriage
Luckily, this is a short-duration marriage
You know, Bob is a short-duration personal savior
We do everything
Keeping in mind the built-in obsolescence
So anyway, for the next 24 hours
You will still be without sin when you do this stuff
To make little baby subgeniuses
When I
Are they still alive?
Are there any children here?
I guess I really do need to explain where little baby subgeniuses come from
Okay, I'll use the
I won't be able to play this one on the radio
When a face-fucking bat attacks a male yeti subgenius
And ejaculates its poisoned sperm down his throat
And the yeti is not promptly treated with face-fucking-bat-sperm-antidote pudding
It must find a prairie squid to fuck
Or it will die
When a bat-sperm-infected yeti male fucks a prairie squid
The prairie squid empties him out like a man-shaped condom
Leaving only the undamaged skin lying on a heap upon the ground
The prairie squid stores and mutates the yeti sperm
And ejaculates it into a female yeti on not-infrequent occasions
The prairie squid-mutated yeti sperm
Swims up the tube and gets into the yeti's body
And impregnates the female's entire lifetime supply of eggs all at once
Transforming her into a vast egg bag with a little human torso on one end
The thousands of prairie squid-mutated yeti sperm-impregnated yeti eggs
Hatch out into thousands of face-fucking-bats
Who seek yeti to face-rape, etc.
This isn't about where baby subgeniuses come from
This is about where face-fucking-bats come from
God, no wonder there aren't more baby subgeniuses
And there's so damn many face-fucking-bats
Oh, one hint, friends
If you stand on the hilltop up there waiting for those bats
With your antidote pudding
Do us a favor and make sure that antidote pudding is in a plastic jar
So that you don't get a heart attack from it
So that you don't, like, drop it and break it
When the bat wraps itself around your face and starts doing, you know
Yes, I'm leaving myself time for one last rant at the end
But I wanted to do, like, a Q&A
Those are always fun
But I am losing my hearing
And I'm going to buy a Wii U before I buy a hearing aid
So if you're going to ask me a question
You're going to have to come right up here and yell it in my face
Reverend Ben, you can yell real loud
What did I get myself into?
Asks the newly ordained subgenius
Wouldn't you like to have to ask yourself that question, friends?
I know you would
Hadn't the best times of your life
Were when you woke up the next day going
What have I gotten myself into?
And the next thing you know, ten months later
There's a bunch of little baby subgeniuses running around
Go figure
Anybody else have a question?
Mervin
I have to translate
Why are you?
That would speak...
Spell...
You-ruh
Right?
Why are you?
You-ruh
Or I suppose it could be pronounced
I-ruh
I am just another robot
Like everybody else
But I'm the robot that's been programmed
To tell everybody that they're a bunch of robots
But they're programmed to pay very little attention to that
And I don't blame them
Because what are we going to do about it?
Anyway
Being robots
Oh, I got up this morning
Or actually just before we came down here
To set up the sales table over there
I looked at the internet news to see if that horrible battle between the humans had been decided
The Zimmerman trial
Um
And it hadn't been
But I noticed that...
that the Texas legislature had gotten back together
and gone ahead and passed that bill
that's a disguised anti-abortion bill,
and poor state senator Wendy Davis,
the new subgenius saint,
had to sit there and watch it happen.
I don't know if everybody here knows
about what happened in Texas.
This lady, Senator Wendy Davis,
did a 13-hour filibuster
to prevent this abortion bill from going through,
which she did.
Actually, the Republicans found a way
to disqualify her about half an hour
before the deadline was up,
but the civilian witnesses in the building
chanted shame, shame, shame
at the Republicans so loud
that it obstructed the thing.
The Republicans did what they wanted to do anyway.
I'm not going to tell,
I'm not going to tell anybody
what's the good guys and what's the bad guys
because I really don't understand
how the world should be run all that great myself.
But I do know that,
okay, I've been standing here for almost an hour.
She had to do that for 13 hours without peeing.
Now, I've got this little jar here.
I've been able to pee six times while I was standing here.
You couldn't even tell, could you?
Well, she didn't have a pulpit.
In fact, they brought her a back brace
to help her stand up because, you know, it hurts.
And they disqualified that.
So you notice I'm not in a huge hurry
to move back to Texas.
But I wouldn't be surprised if in about four years
they're calling her Governor Wendy Davis
and then I might move back at least during the winter.
Great job.
And so, since I didn't get any more Q's and A's,
now don't be shy.
But by the way, you know, if anybody wants to like
have a conversation with Princess Wee herself
or Reverend Stang himself, we're fairly approachable,
especially if you talk to us at the sales table.
But we'll be around for the rest of Starwood for sure.
And we're always down at the bonfire.
They used to have Princess Wee and me
lead the bonfire lighting parade.
They did that two years in a row,
but they learned their lesson.
Don't put a subgenius in the front
because they will lose their way
and just kind of meander off to wherever the nearest
smell of dead skunk is.
I don't know why that is.
They always seem to go that way.
Friends, you're listening to an extra long hour
or more of Slack, internet only.
We'll be back with more of the latest news
from the radio station.
And we'll close with this poignant rant
from Reverend Frodis Suds Pasha,
which you can also see him deliver more forcefully
on YouTube.
But in this case, at 17X Day,
which is more of a laid back situation this time,
it was delivered somewhat more gently,
considering the subject matter.
The next ranter is Suds Pasha.
Hi, I'm Suds Pasha.
Is this gonna be a vomiting performance?
Unfortunately, no.
What's in the bucket, man?
Give me a second.
I wasn't quite prepared to do this tonight.
Oh, but I had this great rant coming in here.
It's all full of fire and brimstone
and all the nice, nah, but I don't know if I want to do that.
No, seriously, it's like,
everything that's happened over the last couple of days,
it just doesn't feel right.
There's a lot of shit.
Yeah, there's a lot of praising Bob going on here,
and I don't think it was appropriate.
Everybody treat this man like shit for the next 24 hours.
However, I do still have what I was going to say.
I just may say it a little differently.
That's fine, son.
I mean, we come here having survived our baptism of conspiracy fire.
We face down the scorching winds of pink,
sandblasted by the harsh reality of the conspiracy.
We've stood strong against it.
We've faced the blazing inferno of the conspiracy.
I, myself, have watched loved ones punch their final ticket,
getting themselves an early window seat on those escape vessels.
And I know that many members of Bob's brood
have gone through their own specific trials and tribulations
to be here at our most sacred ground.
How you doing, Teeter?
How's that foot, man?
It is lovely.
Bob gave that to me, and I'm enjoying it.
Thank you.
Bob gave an excuse.
I mean, each of us wear the scars from a long battle
against the oppressive machine of pink dominion.
And each of us comes here today with a soul full of slack
and stupid grin as proof of the power of divine's teachings.
So I have to ask this gaggle of retards one simple question.
Why?
With all this reservoir of slack and collective creativity at our disposal,
why must we continually turn our Dobbs-given hate and derision upon each other?
It appears that the old conspiracy wiring continues to affect many of us.
It seems that the conspiracy indoctrination we struggle against continues to influence us.
But here, here what I've seen the last couple of days,
it's like, I don't see it.
So, I see nothing but slack going on here.
And it's, everybody outside these walls, man, they're going through their own shit.
But, my God, we had such a hard time getting here this year, many of us.
But we're here.
We found a way to do this.
So why didn't they come?
Why didn't they come here and experience this with us?
I mean,
does it mean their slack is more important than everyone else's?
I mean, that joke may be funny as fuck, but they're the only one laughing.
I, you know, maybe they think that they're better than Bob, but I got some bad news for you, sunshine.
No one is better than Bob, because it's Bob who reminded you that you had slack.
The Church of the Subgenius!
It's, it's, it's, it's the last place to be if you're the, it's the last place to be if you're one of the
cliques of circle jerks and, you know, who think they can pick the chosen few who come into this thing.
All it takes is 35 bucks.
That's really all it takes.
I mean,
they think it's some sort of clique, like it's some sort of cool kids clubhouse that,
you know, hey,
you can come and knock on the door, secret handshake.
Nah,
because let me tell you something.
Me, you guys, me especially, we were not, nor were we ever, nor will we ever be,
one of the cool kids.
Because we are subgeniuses.
We are the outcasts among outcasts,
destined to eat by our
goddamn selves in the cafeteria of life.
But you know what?
Everybody here,
we're all eating at the same table.
Yeah!
Scrapple!
You can usually tell when natural selections, it works when they found they're the only ones laughing at the joke.
And, and, and, you know, maybe we're a bunch of bullies or something, you know,
trying to get you to,
I don't want to be here anymore.
I'm sorry.
That, you're just not worth that much effort.
There's too much slack to be had.
I'd rather put my effort towards that.
So, I mean, maybe they've convinced themselves we're the problem.
We're out here having a good time.
Fuck this.
I'm stuck at home with all my problems.
I can't be out here.
Sorry, fuck-up.
We, we came here because, damn it, Bob,
told us to.
No excuses!
There is no excuse.
Well, there is an excuse, but
it's really only good for Bob.
You know?
You see, they, they, they, they think that joke is so funny and they've hidden behind that term,
fuck them if they can't pick a joke.
A lot of them have really rehearsed that line to the point where it's, it's, it's reflexive.
But here's the thing about comedy.
If you have to tell somebody that it's a joke,
it's not funny.
But, fuck them if they can't take a joke.
That's really more of a guideline than a rule.
Because there's only one rule.
Only one that demands to be followed in this church.
Only one that demands adherence, and that is the subjugious must-have slide!
Yeah!
Yes, sir!
The Church of the Subgenius is here to show you the steps of sacrament to slack.
Do you know them?
They've been told to you more often than I can think of.
Step number one, get off your ass.
We did that.
We're here!
Yes, sir!
Rule number two, bust your ass!
Hey, look, we got the fucking lights working!
We got sound!
Woo!
Three, get others to bust their ass for you.
Hey, you motherfucking monkeys out there who've been helping us through this, praise you,
motherfuckers, seriously.
Yeah!
What the perfect system.
You're still sitting here?
You're classy now.
Ha ha ha.
Oh my God.
Listen, say, are you free today, Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday, Friday, Saturday, Sunday
All along.
No big deal.
Okay,태ué?
Hey, you're free again tomorrow?
slack that slacks mine because you see if you have to go out of your way to
steal the slack from your fellow mutants in order to fortify your own you
committed they Cardinal sin in this church the inside joke a sin so horrific
you can get your name X out of the book of life I've seen it if you've used some
of these people as fucking target practice on Facebook you know I'm talking
about right and car you know exactly who I'm talking about mr. sister you
know who exactly who I'm talking about
but the all-inclusive excuse it only works for Bob because honestly when you
stand on your pillar of contribution of art music and sermons and think you can
piss on everybody that's below you I'm sorry there's only one person in this
church that's going to come to church and say that's what I want you to do and
that's sacrosanct, and that's Philodromon.
Well, and maybe I haven't
staying, but I don't think he's got the phone call yet.
But I mean, just stop and look
around you. Everybody that's out
here, I can't see shit, all I see is a couple of
blinking lights. Everybody out there,
look at each other.
You're under no obligation to
like any of these people.
There's no doctrine that says you have to
agree with any of these people.
In fact, some doctrine
even says you're encouraged to hate them.
There is nothing that says
any of these subgenie
should or would be your friend.
But
for Dob's sake,
they are your allies.
They are your brothers
in arms against the collective
might of the conspiracy
and their agents.
None of us in our right mind
could ever hope to actually hurt
or stop the conspiracy,
but this group of idiosyncratic
abnormals has the power
to make the agents of the conspiracy,
those pink pricks that
gleefully robbed the true subgenius
of their slack for fun and profit.
We have the power
to make them regret
they ever heard the name
J.R. Bob Dobbs!
But nope.
They still are content
to fling their feces at each other.
And I'm proud of this.
I'm proud of this.
I'm proud of the fecal mess
they contribute to.
And while they're laughing
and sniffing their finger,
the pinks continue to get away with murder.
All right.
You've paid your money to Bob.
You've got your membership card.
You've hung the clipart on the wall
of all inclusive excuse.
You've done all that.
You come to X-State.
You're hoping for that big fucking saucer
to come out of the sky
and wish you to paradise.
But maybe, just maybe,
maybe they've been so busy
sticking a poop-cake finger
in the eyes of their brethren
that they've overlooked
or simply flat out ignored
a few simple details.
Because you see,
once you take and put down
the book of the subgenius,
once you've taken the clipart off the wall,
once you've destroyed the art,
once you get rid of the propaganda,
once you take off the mask,
once you get beyond the joke of the mass,
once you get rid of the church of the subgenius,
you end up with one glaringly obvious fact, folks.
The fact that I have to spell it out for you today,
since it's been spelled out to you
for over 35 goddamn years,
it shows how little some folks
have actually been paying attention.
This is Bob's party!
And you and me
were nothing but a guest
who paid an admission fee.
Yes, sir!
If you think that Grant's permission
to kick over furniture and shit in the Kool-Aid,
well, let's just say
I'm not gonna be the one drinking from the punch bowl.
But I guess you got your membership card, right?
I guess for some of these people,
you just have to say,
well, Ivan Stang said it best,
some people are just too stupid,
even for subgeniuses.
I guess they just need to pay a little bit more.
Get a little closer attention.
Praise Bob.
Happy X-Day, everybody.
Whoa!
Ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay.
Woo!
Yeah!
Yoo-hoo!
Ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay.
You've been listening to
You're listening to the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
For free information, write to P.O. Box 181417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118
or see www.subgenius.com
Praise Bob!