Dear friends, and praise Bob, we'll be on the air live tonight.
Buzzy should be calling in after a while, and no one else.
We have a different show.
We're mostly going to be playing funny music tonight by Princess Wee's Boyfriends.
Hey.
Oh, sorry.
Now you can say it.
Hey.
Well, she's just a big fan of some of these people.
Actually, it's mostly my boyfriends.
It's mostly Rudy Schwartz Project.
Yeah.
But your boyfriend is Ted Ganger and Jonathan Colton.
My boyfriend is Rudy Schwartz Project.
Yeah.
And his little buddy, Waldo.
Do you have anything by Ken Nordean?
He's my boyfriend.
Ken Nordean?
I broke up with Ken Nordean.
Oh, you guys broke up?
Yeah.
Didn't work?
Well, actually, I guess I played all of his stuff.
For the first time.
First 10 years of Hour of Slack.
And then we...
He actually used to send stuff directly to us.
Oh, wow.
And we would send stuff to him.
Then I got mail from his son, who was a UFO believer dude.
I don't think he quite understood our type of UFO belief.
They're more unidentified to us, most of them.
Yes.
So we're not trying to second guess them anymore.
No.
Because we know.
We'll be here December 21st, 2012.
Right.
It's just that we don't know what the real date of today is.
Anyway, now...
Meanwhile, gaseous rhetoric and stupid, bombastic, empty speechifying.
The subgenius of Hour of Slack.
They need Jesus.
Yes.
Well, come on down to Barbecue Bud's
Won't you come on down to Barbecue Bud's
There's a corn dog special at Barbecue Bud's
So won't you come on down and let Bud fix you up with a corn dog
Whoa, sweet patootie, Bud's got a beauty
Bud's a slinging corn dog, so come on down
Bring all the kids, cause there's lots of balloons and prizes
Jump inside
Jump inside of the corn dog wheel
Take a spin and Bud's big corn dog wheel
Round and around and a swirly birdie do
You might win a date with Pia Zadora
She's got lots of fascinating stuff she wants to say to you
Swirly birdie do
Oh, Pia, bring me that corn dog, won't you, darling?
It's somecular sugar
Oh, I'm very very curious
I never heard of this business
Don't you believe me?
Oh, I'm very very sure
It's worth seeing
It's good
It's solid
Cheers
Are you OK with the school's opening song?
It's my favorite song
I heard as a pioneering best writer
Though it hurts me to say this, it is on my mind
Cause it really is true, though it isn't polite
Most people are stupid, though they don't hardly nose
Most people are stupid, that's the way it goes
Their minds are so narrow, there's nowhere to go
And nothing you say can change their point of view
Cause they know what they like, and they like what they know
And they think that they think, but they haven't a clue
Most people are stupid, no they're not very smart
Most people are stupid, but they have a clue
They have a good heart
They don't reach for things that are not in their reach
They just want to eat and drink and fuck and sleep
Maybe go on vacation and roast on the beach
And they might take a book if it isn't too deep
Most people are stupid, and they're on the same team
Most people are stupid
They could make me scream
They talk about nothing and work on their tan
It's not really clear why they would need a brain
But that's how it has been since the world began
They'll inherit the earth and they drive me insane
Most people are stupid, from their head to their toe
Most people are stupid, and they run the show
Most people are stupid, just admit that it's true
Most people are stupid, sometimes I'm stupid too
Most people are stupid, all except for a few
Most people are stupid
Of course I don't mean you
Most people are stupid, just admit that it's true
Now I know that for many of you, you do things you know aren't right
That's okay, you have to let your failures define you to act right
And I am just so glad that you're stupid
And that's why I succeed
So today I want to ask all of you
Most people are stupid, just admit that it's true
What's your problem?
From kindergarten through twelfth grade
You're stupid
I know that feeling
It's a fact
Stupid people have stupid children
If you're stupid, please, don't have sex
If you insist on having sex, then please, have sex with animals
Preferably animals smarter than you are
That way, if by some biological fluke you and the animal actually have offspring
Odds are the offspring will be less stupid than you
One more thing
Don't assume the animal is protected
If the animal has a condom
Or a female, some sort of interuterine device
Insists they wear it
Please, help stamp out this mindless mindlessness
Keep your stupidity to yourself
This message brought to you by the Council of Concerned Citizens
Who are smarter than you are
oru
This things is all happening for you gamer
I gave a shattered radio revivalist
And with the boss man I've never been missed
Me so stupid
What is my IQ?
What is my intelligent quotient?
I could've been the Golden Gate Bridge
Or Einstein's nemesis
I could've been the Dirty Jacka
But it's all come down to this
Me so stupid
So stupid.
Me so stupid.
What is my IQ?
What is my intelligent quotient?
Me so stupid.
What is my IQ?
What is my intelligent quotient?
Mm-mm.
That's so wrong.
And my little 11-year-old child, I think his mentality is much more alert than the 16-year-old boy.
The point is...
Stupidity is all around us, and it's not worth getting upset about.
It is not a thing a sane man would do.
The doomsday machine is designed to trigger itself automatically.
But surely you can disarm it somehow?
No.
It is designed to explode if any attempt is ever made to un-trigger it automatically.
It's an obvious comedy trick, Mr. President.
We're wasting valuable time.
Let me make water.
We're getting ready to clobber us.
Stupid.
Stupid is there.
Large.
Polluting.
The time-space...
...discontinuum...
...with J.R. Bob Dobson!
Subtitles by the Amara.org community
Come on, everyone, join the fun
We've got tanking on the run
The Earth is circled by the sun
Creation science podcast
Science classes in our schools
Taught by superstitious fools
Jerry Falwell sets the rules
Creation science polka!
The universe was fabricated in six literal days
The humans and the dinosaurs shared a condo in L.A.
Carbon dating makes us cringe
We're the right-wing lunatic fringe
Jesus died for us!
Our sins!
Creation science polka!
We're free!
Superhuman!
Infinite Will
The Bible says the Earth is only 6,000 years old.
Why did you fall?
Deny and Jesus Christ will roast your balls on burning coals
Come on everyone, join the fun
Ignorance has almost won
Get geology from a nun
Creation Science Polka
Take your children out of school
Homespun dogma is so cruel
Prop them up, watch them drool
Creation Science Polka
Ah, yes, and of course there's always Dave
Dave?
Hello, lurking
This buzz is enormous now
You mean you had Dave right there?
Let's listen, is the buzz there?
It's enormous on this end here
Oh yeah, I can hear the buzz
Can you limit me?
A little bit?
Yeah, everyone shut up for three seconds
Let me have some buzz tone, okay?
Three, two, one, now
Okay, that should do it
I'll just, I'll put some more buzzy music up
I have to do the credits, friends
I'm listening with pride
The, let's see, what are we, what are we
Oh, Creation Science Polka
And the opening song, Barbecue Buds
Is by the Rudy Schwartz Project
You can Google Rudy Schwartz Project
Schwartz is spelled S-C-H-W-A-R-T-Z
We played, this is unusual for us to play
What we call conspiracy music
But it's ZZ Top, so that doesn't count
No
Me so stupid
And the song Most People Are Stupid
Was by Ted Ganger
Who's an American who teaches music in Germany
He's the brother of the American
He's the brother of Sister Melodious Chops
The famous subgenius songstress
And the leader of my band
Right
In fact, we have a very sad and yet hilarious song
By Ted Ganger that we're going to be playing for Dave
For Dave?
I can hardly wait, my pants are already off
The shoes are on my ears
Oh, it's not going to do you any good once you hear this song
It's going to be a lot of fun
It's going to bring back sad
I'll bet you it brings back some sad memories
I hate sad memories
Why are you doing this to me?
Ted Ganger is a vocal coach
And a piano coach
And teacher, I believe
I'm mean
In Germany
That's the bottom line, I'm mean
I'm the mean one
Princess Wee is the nice one
I love hearing that, even if it's not true
Nor are all Germans mean
It's all true
Some of them mean a lot more than you expect
Like that Schrodinger guy
And what's his name, the philosopher
Wittgenstein, that's another one
Dave, you're sounding really lonesome
And you should talk as loud as you can
I'll scream if you need
No, okay, that's what I wanted to know
Yeah, when you talk clearly and loudly
It overpowers the buzz a bit
We just wondered what the variances might possibly be
And you know, I don't know if I'm going to be able to do that
And now we know
You can speak up above the buzz
I will try and endeavor in every moment and every way
You can kind of like kiss on the microphone like you do
Okay
Make out with it
Ew, gross
Ew
I feel like I just made out with Lonesome Cowboy Dave
It smells right, my microphone
It does smell right
Because, you know, you always make that noise
When you're making out
Of course
No, no, say you two
God, I'll leave the mics on for half a second
And they're going at it like monkeys
No, don't let your voice get away from that phone
I won't
I'll put right up your words
Yeah, that sounds good
Yeah
I have to keep on using that same stupid voice whenever I go
I think I'll do a French waiterage
I will move my mouth much closer to the microphone
Yeah
The actual mouthpiece here of the telephone
I will jiggle some more wires
And perhaps hopefully in the background
Oh, oui, oui, monsieur
Oh, if I know your buzz, Dave
It'll go away after a while
And then just when we least expect it
It'll go after I hang up, that's what it'll do
Well, yeah, but it'll come back
But we're going to play music a couple of times
In order to hide the buzz
I do have music in the background here
But it's
It kind of fights
The buzz fights it a little bit
It's Rudy Schwartz' project
From that same
He did a new release of his album
Don't Get Charred, Get Puffy
Yeah, yeah
That's good advice
You know, if you're suffering from fourth degree burns
All over your body
Dave, I can't hear you
Rudy Schwartz is full of advice
You know, I think I'm going to take
The Rudy Schwartz project off
And put on
Witch Disco
I'll put on Witch Disco
Or I actually have some
Flying Mayan Brothers, you might say
Oh, that would make more sense
Because we're going to explode here
In the next month coming up
Right, in a very Mayan way
So Flying Mayan Brothers would be great
I don't even know what this sounds like
I'll go ahead and put it on
And we'll see what it does
The little twelve jaguar presents
Quack, quack
Two ducks
How ducky
I'll read a Mayan prophecy
Over this Mayan music
And this isn't
By the way, the world
Probably won't be ending
We call December 21st, 2012
Because it ain't even 1998 yet
Right
If X-Day comes tomorrow
Then we know we'll still have
What, 14 years left
Before the Mayan end of the world happens
Right
And that won't affect us
Because we'll be off of this world by then
Well, by 9189 probably
Now here's a Mayan prophecy
About the year 2801
And it's not good news
It's not good news
I'll read it
Fifteen baktuns and no katuns
No tuns, no oinales and no kins
Two nothingness
Eighteen ununinium
Thursday, June the 28th
In 2801
At the sun's pubescence
At his third thirteenth
The solar hurricanes
Erase nine billion bright consciousnesses
Morning is our birth day
And the sun is the sun's third
And so I guess a solar explosion of some kind
Will wipe out nine billion people
In the year 2801
Well, the idea, I guess
What you were expressing there
These are prophecies for after they predicted
The end of the world
Yeah, I know that
But the prophecies are based on the belief that
When the sun does all that stuff
And screws up the electromagnetic field
There's some physical damage to the earth
But most of the damage is done to the earth
And the actual psyche of humanity
Which can't remember how to drive a car anymore
Or even their own names
Because of the gravity
That makes sense
Cool
Of the, you know, the electromagnetic shift
It's like, you know, in the old days
Of analog recording
When you'd erase something
And that's what happened
Will happen, they claim
Well, it could be worse
What if, as an old Powell Anderson novel posits
What if all this stuff is just a dream?
Of time, the world has been
The earth has
And the solar system has been
Inside of a cosmic cloud
That slowed down subtle electromagnetic
Reactions such as
Inside your very brain
Yeah
And the world passes out
From under that cloud
And suddenly not only humans
But animals all become ten times smarter
I'm trying to remember the name of the novel
They made a terrible movie of it
Called Day of the Animals or something
What a strange evolution
In the novel, it's the end of the world because the people of normal intelligence become super smart,
and they get real depressed and want a lot of them to die.
The retarded people do really well because they become what we would call normal.
And this would be people with severe disabilities become mentally about like us.
They do fine.
And the chimpanzees do pretty well.
They just shot off my buzz. I'm sorry.
Yeah, sure enough.
All right.
It's the Mayans.
Oh, it's not Mayans now.
I shouldn't say Mayans. It's Maya.
Maya.
This is Azerbaijani music.
Azerbaijani be good.
This was a big hit in 1475.
Oh, and we've got after that, there's some Maori music.
Maori the Marrier.
In honor of our friend Dr. Dark, who was at the...
Sounds like rabbits with big, big teeth.
Our friend Dr. Dark was among the Maori recently.
Did he paint his nipples like the rest of them?
Oh, if I know him, I'm sure he did.
That's a male ritual. You have to paint your nipples blue.
He probably ruined the ritual.
He probably ruined the ritual with his puns and heckling.
Yeah, his one-liners and his two-liners and his too-many-liners.
No, not...
His eyeliner.
Now, according to this book on the Maya that I just finished about 10 minutes before we came to the show,
the world will be saved from ending.
There, I just spoiled the story for you.
But it will come to an end on Thursday, October 12th.
47.72.
After that, the big nothing.
The big nothing.
Yeah.
The thing we've been waiting for for so long, and they're going to have to put it off forever.
I certainly hope you don't subscribe to that idea, especially since you have your own ideas.
You know, the sad thing is I subscribed to The Onion, and they quit printing it and mailing it.
We're so sad.
The Onion is no longer something I get in my pocket.
I have a post office box, which, before I go stand in line,
and that means that there may be a mass killing at the post office because of me going postal,
not having The Onion to read while I stand there waiting for these nitwits.
No, no.
And I don't mean the postal workers.
I mean the people in line ahead of me.
That just means you have to bring back issues.
So are you saying they're exclusively online now?
Yes, they're making us read it online.
No, but The Onion has always had a printed version in some city.
It's like New York and Chicago.
You can find The Onion for free at newsstands.
And they may still be doing that, but probably like us, they decided the postage just was too much.
Church of Subgenius quit publishing and mailing stuff because of the postage, not printing.
I am called to mind of Funny Times.
We're living in.
You're based here in Cleveland, which continues to turn out print paper media.
Rather than you can't even submit online, which is the weirdest thing I ever saw.
But they sounded quite jocular.
To the Funny Times?
Yeah, we used to subscribe to Funny Times.
They just sent us a freebie hoping we'd subscribe again.
They used to sign POs as me.
I've subscribed to them off and on.
I sometimes walk into the post office and there'll be an old hipster my age and same kind of hairdo walking out.
And after I shudder.
And shiver at how scary old age is, I think.
I wonder if that's the Funny Times guy.
I bet it is.
Raymond Lesser.
The old chimpanzee suit always worked well, too.
Now we've had a hard time with digestion, but that's to be expected at his age.
Well, I've been playing the game, the sacrifice game, which if you sacrifice enough, it's just I just use animals.
And that works OK for me.
Yeah.
I've been able to make predictions.
And I know where Princess Wee and I are going to be on at the time of the last Bakhtun, when the last Bakhtun ends on December 21st.
You're going to be having a Christmas party.
No, not not quite.
No, we're going to be on our way to Stang Ranch, but we're going to be exploring Enchanted Rock in Fredericksburg, Texas, which we've been to before.
Big piece of pink granite.
Oh, the hideout spot when the big Kazanghi hits.
Yeah, there's a cave there.
Huddled under the rock.
There is a cave.
The rock, Enchanted Rock is a gigantic, solid piece of granite.
And when you go into the cave there, you would be safe from many ends of the world.
However, the kind where the whole universe disappears.
Nah, forget it.
That's too bad.
The whole universe needs to disappear briefly, just so long as it reappears.
Not too long after that.
It's going to be pretty much the same way.
Right.
It's kind of a blink.
It may be that.
National shifts.
They just get you all tit-hardly and way out of this, you know, sub-scroll, you know, get your concept.
I'm sorry.
Well, now, as you were saying that maybe the scientifical end of the world on the 21st would be a pulse, a space pulse that wipes out people's intelligence.
My question would be.
How would we be able to tell the difference?
Yeah.
What would really change?
You know.
Definitely the question.
How would we know?
That is the question.
I mean, aside from the fact that.
And look out the window and presume everything was fine.
But the thing is, I guess it'll be so bad that the cerebral cortex itself will begin to shrink and then re-expand, I guess, after the.
I just had a bad thought.
And people.
What if it all.
They might be able to remember how to go to the bathroom or get a drink of water.
They will not know how to walk to the faucet to turn the water on or go to the refrigerator to get the refreshing spring water.
They'll just, you know.
You mean even dumber than now?
Because I was going to say, how do we know that hasn't already happened?
Well.
I mean, it being so relative.
I would say it's.
Well, you know.
Well, yeah.
The ideogularity beat the singularity into existence.
Distance or.
It beat the singularity into brain damage.
Actual lacerations on the.
On the.
Now, I have been on a kind of a Maya kick.
And it's not because of the prophesied end of the world.
It's because of two great sci-fi novels by a guy named Brian D'Amato.
He's got a little apostrophe.
After the D.
It's like D'Amato.
D'Amato.
I don't.
There's a vowel there.
So you don't want to necessarily go D'Amato because you're kind of saying that anyway.
D'Amato.
I love these books, but I hate this author because he's really good.
He makes me feel like a loser by comparison.
He's a well-known artist, too.
I read earlier.
That really taught art history at Ohio State.
At one point.
We're jumping around on stage at the same time doing really wild guitar moves and stuff
and then playing the keyboard at the same time and then jumping off and drawing a picture
and using a.
Yeah.
And then writing this bestselling, you know, Hugo Award winning.
These.
Flying on the keyboard to none of this.
The books that I just finished.
They're really.
One big long story that takes two books to tell.
The first one is in the courts of the sun by Brian D'Amato.
And the second one is called the sacrifice games.
And it's it's about people of the modern times discovering that the Maya had a an incredibly complex game.
It's like turned a human into a computer.
Drugs were involved.
And there's a great description of.
Playing the game.
I'm going to read this.
OK.
Let's see.
I'll put on.
I'll put on the Einstein Secret Orchestra.
They'll be speaking.
I'm pulling through that.
Now this.
This is a long paragraph.
So.
Hang.
Hang in there.
And then we'll play a song, I guess.
My knuckles.
Really, I'd been using myself as a monkey all this time.
That is to really play the runner.
That is the skulls.
You have to have some fear there.
Even if you're playing.
For a client.
You don't much care about.
You have to scare yourself.
You need to look around you the way a prey animal does.
Seeing a predator in every shadow.
And as your field of understanding widens.
Instead of feeling more powerful.
Your fear increases.
It becomes fear not just for yourself.
But for your fellow prey animals.
The members of your herd that you now see.
Are all around you in too numerous to count.
Instead of spotting escape routes.
You realize how many prey.
Animals surround you.
And how far it is to any safe haven.
You start comprehending how unlikely.
And contingent your consciousness is.
And the farther you get up that staircase.
That sense of tenuousness just keeps increasing.
You start seeing more of the present.
And more of the past.
And even then some of the future.
And then more possible futures.
And possible pasts.
All the trillions of times you weren't born for instance.
And then.
Even counterfactual presence.
And non-existent futures.
And impossible worlds.
Universes where light is slow and local.
And gravity is fast and far reaching.
Where two plus two equals one.
Or even where two plus two equals say grapefruit.
And it's not intriguing.
It's terrifying.
Like I said drugs are involved in this game.
They have this amazing drug that they.
The.
The Maya priests make from.
It's like this certain frog.
This certain frog has to be eating these certain chemicals in a certain cave.
And then the.
Oh no it has to be eating.
It has to grow on a certain tree.
And then the frog that lives on this tree has a certain drug in him.
He's eaten by a certain water fowl.
Who also carries another unique kind of drug.
And has to be bitten by a spider that has a certain kind of venom.
And when you add all that stuff together.
You've got the Steersman.
That's their name for this drug that sort of turns you into a human computer.
That can remember things that haven't even happened yet.
Yes.
And logically work out the most likely possibilities.
And that being that the universe will implode on December 21st.
Uh.
2012 or.
15 Ocelot.
Bactoon 49.
Ixion 3-5 or something.
Uh huh.
Um.
Anyway I cannot highly enough recommend these two books.
In the Courts of the Sun and the Sacrifice Game.
No relation to the Hunger Game friends.
These aren't.
They're really funny.
This guy's like a modern.
He's like a new Kurt Vonnegut almost.
They're donkeys.
They're like a dark humor that is sick.
Partly because the Maya apparently developed tortures that are so incredibly cool.
Did I already cover all this on some previous show?
No you didn't cover the coolness of the tortures.
Well you did cover the coolness but you didn't allude to what they did that was actually so cool.
I didn't uh.
I wish I'd marked the page in this book where he lists the books of the books of torture.
I didn't.
I just wanted to show the tortures that they have stashed away.
A library.
A veritable library of books on torture.
But the Maya.
The Maya had so many books on so many things.
And when the Inquisition got there.
They said where's Jesus and all this.
You guys come on.
You know you're forgetting number one.
So they all.
It burned them all.
Well plus by the time the Inquisition got there.
Oh yeah it was later.
Half the indigenous people were dead from measles.
And so.
Smallpox and such.
It was a little bit later than the rest of the conquista.
Yeah.
Right.
They were hiding by them temples.
Well actually the Maya were pretty much gone by then.
It was the uh.
As tribal people they continued.
Right.
Right in fact they're still around.
In fact for all I know my grandsons are half Maya sort of.
They're carrying some of that.
Some.
Yeah they wouldn't be.
They would be partly Spanish.
And they're half.
And they're half subgenius too.
Which is subgenius can come in any flavor.
You can get.
You can get them.
You know.
Pretty much any color.
Age.
Ethnicity.
Poor things.
Yeah refugee status.
Smallpox.
They're like smiths.
They're every.
Somewhere there is for every human activity.
Somewhere there is a smith who has done that.
And a mild nipple it was all Tuesday.
Just because of that.
All Tuesday.
Because there were so many.
They were spread across the land like.
Like Lincoln's butter.
Well there weren't as many.
There were never as many smiths as there were Lee's.
There was some guy named Lee in China who was hornier.
By thousands.
Than any smith in Scotland.
And so does.
You think of smith as an English.
Scotland huh?
You think of smith as an English name.
But there's really more smiths than Scotland.
And I'll tell you a secret.
It only won't be a secret now.
Smith is a fake name.
It's really McNutt.
Get out of here.
It sounds funny.
But it's a name.
You'll occasionally.
In fact in the south there's a lot of McNutt funeral homes.
Are they making fun of me?
I don't know.
No no it's just the idea like you could have said McPeanuts or something.
Right.
Or McTesty.
Yeah.
McNipple sounds good.
Or does that sound like a new dessert from fast food joint?
Yeah a place where you can take.
I'll have a chocolate McNipple.
Oh no.
I don't want chocolate.
Oh I don't know.
Do I want vanilla or do I want strawberry?
I just don't know.
Help me make up my mind.
What do you like?
Do you like chocolate or vanilla?
I know there's people in line behind me.
But I just can't make up my mind.
I'm not making fun of you Princess Wee.
I'm making fun of that silly woman I saw in the post office.
Oh that's right.
What was that all about?
I didn't get my onion.
I had to kill her.
I'm glad you did.
And that's me who was having a really good laughy time holding everyone up in line.
I know it's taking me so long.
But she was using the automatic postage machine.
And I'm really fast at it and I have to kill the people who are there if there's somebody there ahead of me.
I have to get them out of the way because they're just too slow.
They squint and they read with their lips moving.
or in this woman's case, she narrated to everybody
while not listening to what she herself was saying.
She'd always push the wrong button.
God, I left.
I just up and left because I didn't have an onion
and I really might have done some damage.
So I went to Wally World and came back later
when they were closed and there wouldn't be any silly women there.
Yes, this is a very, very, very unnerving type of personality.
We encounter them everywhere.
We encounter them in the supermarkets
and in the bassinets and the child play areas
and most of the great seniority centers throughout the land.
Don't eat your onions, you want to kill them.
Yes, indeed.
Speaking of silly women you want to kill,
that leads us into the next Ted Ganger song
and this is the one I wanted Dave to hear
because it's so depressing
and yet it's kind of funny in a way because it's so true.
Luckily for me, I've never been there.
Well, it's just that you and I are always telling each other
how old we are now.
We're so old.
And then when I heard this song, I thought,
oh, I can't wait till my husband hears this.
Well, I couldn't wait till Dave heard it
because you're going to be crying at the end of it, okay?
No!
So I'm going to play this song.
I'm going to pot us all down.
Goodbye.
Well, we've come to the end of our story
The saddest story ever told
It's a story of love and hate
A story about, well, me
And of a guy who is just too old
You're too old
Old, old, old, old
What we had was really beautiful
But you're too old
You were full of illusion
So I had to burst your bubble
And I could have been nicer
But it wasn't worth the trouble
So I thank you a lot
For Ben and Jerry's and the movie
And I got you a new job
To admit that our bedtime was groovy
But you're too old
Old, old, old, old
What we had was really beautiful
But you're too old
Well, you gave me your love
And you really understood me
And you gave me a chance
To be the way I really could be
But you're not what I want
And I told you before
So get out of my way
While I act like a whore
Cause you're too old
Old, old, old, old
What we had was really beautiful
But you're too old
Ted and I got together last year in March.
I told him it wasn't really what I wanted
Cause he was too old to have a family with
Which is like the only purpose of a relationship, right?
But we started up anyway.
It went on until July
When I decided I'd had enough.
So I fucked a student of his
Cause he was there, you know
And it had to be somebody.
And then the next day I dumped Ted.
And a few days after that
I fucked this other guy I'd been interested in too.
I'd actually liked him more to begin with
But I'd gone to the party with the first guy
I mean the student
So I had to wait with the second one
But not very long
And right after that I went to Israel for two months
I did a few guys there too
Including a cousin of mine from New Jersey
Who I'd had a secret thing going on with for years
When I came back in the fall
I can't really say what I did
Because I didn't take any of his money
I told Ted about this time
And he's the one who wrote this
But I did have these big dreams about a future
With my New Jersey cousin
Who's an accountant by the way
Still around October I started seeing Ted again
He coached me on some songs
And he was still in love with me
So I figured I might as well
Let him get back into my pants
This time things were really good
I told him I somehow didn't need to be such an asshole to him anymore
Because I'd already done all that
Over Christmas though
I flew to New York
For two weeks to visit my cousins
Including the one you know
I'd already planned the trip
Before Ted and I got back together
So of course I had to go through with it
Didn't I?
And so my cousin and I fucked
Like every night I was there
Except for when I got my period
When I got back again the shit really hit the fan
Duh right?
But I cried a lot and promised Ted
I'd really work to build a relationship with him now
And I really wanted to you know
And so he took me back
But I kept thinking
Nah he's too old
So after a couple of months I started getting distant again
Which is how I do it
Until he finally asked what's going on
And one thing led to another in the conversation
Which is sort of what I wanted to happen anyway
And suddenly we were saying goodbye
And that was it
Of course I'd already been lining up the next guy
I mean why waste time right?
And so just three weeks later
I was able to change my Facebook status
From single to interrelationship
It's the real thing this time
I just know it
We're gonna visit Israel together and everything
This is it now for sure
No really
Well you did what you could
And you told me the truth
And it's true you're very youthful
But I'd rather have youth
So I got a new guy now
And although you say whatever
I know this is for real now
And it's gonna last forever
You're gonna have a new girlfriend
You were just too old
Old, old, old, old
What we had was really beautiful
But you're too old
Well please believe
me when I speak it once more
You're too old
I know your hearing's
getting weak so once more
You're too old
You were just too old
Old, old, old, old
That was fine and lovely.
It made my toes curl up, made my eyebrows singed.
It was normal.
It was absolutely beautiful.
How do you think it was?
It was fine.
It was funny.
I laughed my cryogies off.
And I thought of the times when people walked up to me and go,
Dude, you look really old.
And then I thought, well, I may be old, but at least I...
Then I counted all the things that I was that they weren't.
Well, what I like to...
Getting fat.
I get that a lot from the haters on the Internet.
You're so old, Stag, and I get to say things like,
Well, I guess you don't have to worry about that, do you?
I guess you don't have to worry about that happening to you.
They don't like to be told that.
I've thought of that answer myself, informing them.
It makes me...
You feel better to say it.
And your parents would say,
Oh, well, when you get older, you'll see.
And you go, Oh, no, I won't.
I'll never get older.
Well, some of them won't.
That's true.
Quite a few of them won't ever have to worry about getting old because...
There'll be little floaters out in the pond.
Yeah, they'll either be too stupid or too unlucky.
I mean, a lot of times it's just bad luck.
You know, Tom, the reaper...
Pulls your name out of the basket.
It's time for that aneurysm.
Boop!
Suddenly you're dead.
One minute...
You're not even thinking about such a possibility.
And someone reminds you from the vast conspicuum of abnormality.
I mean, space.
Oh, well.
I have a funny...
Now, that was a song about sad sex.
But I have a funny song about bug sex that's much, much more...
Jolly and inspirational.
And it's by Rudy Schwartz Project.
It's by my boyfriend, the Rudy Schwartz Project.
So I'm going to play...
It's only two minutes long, though.
But you can listen to this one, too, Dave.
Do-wop-de-mega-mega
Do-wop-bop-bop
Snuggly mega
Cuddly mega
Strip mega
You sweet mega
Pretty children all clap and sing
Strip mega
You sweet mega
All the bong beans smack and ring
I get so hot
Watching brown eyeballs rot
Strip mega
You sweet mega
Lovely mega
Oh, so sweet
Well
Strip mega
You sweet mega
All the stars are shining bright
Strip mega
You sweet mega
Two mezzanine for a new eye
Shopping
Strolling down the lane
To a happy refrain
Strip mega
You sweet mega
Lovely mega
Oh, so sweet
Do-wop-bop-bop
Gorgeous white dipped hair is larva
Larva
Chirp spreading grub of my dreams
I'll pour the wine while you court me with your slime
Smugly mega
Social opium
Smugly drug
Mule
Pelicule
Escapade
rises
Annotation
I got Fortnite
tool
MONA
history
You sweet maggot, pretty maggot walk by my side
Strip naked, you sweet maggot, gonna make you my maggot bride
Mend all my socks while we do the maggot rock
Strip naked, you sweet maggot, lovely maggot, oh so sweet
Strip naked, you sweet maggot, lovely maggot
Maggot, oh so sweet
Oh so sweet
Really short project there
I enjoyed it very much, I'm sure you do too
Don't you, man?
Hey, uh, Principal, while that song was playing
What flavor of maggot?
The texture was wow
It was sweet
And to the teeth and give you a funny face when you looked in the car mirror
Dave keeps drifting away from the phone line
We couldn't hear that one, Dave
The sweet, creamy, maggot
I was right on the microphone
See the Interpol or the Universal Space Police
Are interfering with the actual transmission
Speaking of radio testaments
Princess Wee handed me this book I've never seen before
Called The Radio Dictionary
And for some reason she opened it to the page
It really is a dictionary
Between Drop-ins and Dry is the word drugola
Defined as the illegal and immoral use of drugs
Given to program directors or DJs in exchange for favors
And I want the listeners to know that I'm disappointed in them
We had an open house right here at the station
And we met several of the listeners
And in fact it's like a regular convention of the Senate and the Senate
We had a lot of people in the room
And there was no drugola to be seen
Not a speck
Dr. Sinister just walked in
Not even the tiniest sniff
It was actually really scary seeing my dad here talking to No Money Mark
And he was trying to cop too
I looked in
No!
Let me save you
Imagine the
How I felt
The very first World Subgenius Convention
1981 in Dallas
All these subgeniuses are mostly young hipsters
With some exceptions standing around
And in walks my dad
In full Naval Reserve Captain's uniform
With his three other Navy buddies
To the idiot stoners
It looked like the cops
It was a blue uniform
You know
Now
Who was
The people who were the most
Most scared
Were the three guys with my dad
Those three old Navy reservists
Looked like they were literally
In a den of lions
You know it's kind of like how
Humans and scorpions relate to each other
You know like you see a scorpion
And you're probably going to be afraid of it
But that scorpion's much more afraid of you
You can't imagine how many times
I've had to explain that fact to Princess Wee here
Many, many times
Over and over throughout the time we've known each other
Of course I've never even seen a scorpion in the wild but
I've never even seen a scorpion in the wild but
Come to Stang Ranch in Texas
You can just look behind the bed
I've actually got an outstanding warrant in Stang County
So I'll pass on that
Oh well join the crowd
Yeah but you're kind of a fixer in that county
Yeah he's the go-to guy so to speak in Stang County
No actually that's Pappy
My Pappy
Oh okay so
He is the go-to guy
You're taking over the throne
And that doesn't mean me you know
Oh I could never do that
Is this our wife in the rocket factory playing in the background?
Come on
Yes it is
I can't believe you know the names of those tunes
Yeah we're playing the Witch Disco album by Einstein's Secret Orchestra
Oh I'm going going going going I can hear myself
Yeah that's you on guitar Dave
It's you doing it
Yeah this one this tune has a little mark next to it
Like this is an extra good one
Yeah
Go figure
There was some fine jams
Yeah
Really
I'm sorry I can't say anything more erudite than that I'm just realizing how
Well you know what it's almost the end of show and this is
Well it's a good time for my brain to shut off
Yeah well and the buzz is that that's the buzz's cue to come back isn't it?
Well yeah I guess if it's off when I hang up then it'll come back but usually it just it won't
It refuses it will not
Well now I have to decide whether to play for the very last thing
My Boyfriend's Secret Orchestra
Again a
One
Two
Three
Four
Six
Seven
Eight
Nine
Twelve
Ten
Twenty
I simply think that the lyrics will fly by, so you'll have to go online and hear it again.
But I think it's the best song I've ever heard about being married.
Isn't that sweet?
If that's what it's about, it's hard to tell.
Okay, Dave, we're going to have to tell you goodbye.
We're going to play the romantic Princess Wee's romantic song.
My heart's all aflutter.
We'll play it.
Yeah.
And we'll scrape you off the highway this Thursday.
Scrape you.
Okay, man.
Every evening's in.
Hold your hands in the street when you walk them off to school.
A box too full to shut.
Cardboard paper cut.
The bleeding edge of a picture of your parents when they were cool.
So much to say, I forget to start.
There goes a day, fading as it passes.
Forget the gray, let it all just fall.
Fall apart.
It's so gray.
Okay, I like you in glasses
Shovels in the sand, I played a winning band
A drowning princess in a tangle of towels on the floor
An old familiar ache, the little pills we take
The thoughtless kindness of a coffee cup waiting by the door
So much to say, I forget to start
There goes the day, fading as it passes
Forget the gray, let it fall apart
It's okay, it's on the board
Someone's been double booking
I've got time
How is your next week?
Looking
The house shifts into place
A little breathing space
The radiators and the floorboards will argue while we sleep
There's water in the walls
The stairs make waterfalls
Down in the basement
The soft sound of a river digging deep
So much to say, I forget to start
There goes the day, fading as it passes
Forget the gray, let it fall apart
So much to say, I forget to start
There goes the day, fading as it passes
Forget the gray, let it fall apart
It's okay, I like you in glasses
Shovels in the sand, I played a winning band
Subgenius Radio Ministry hour of SLAAACK!
For FREE information write to
P.O Box 181417 Cleveland Heights OH 44118
Or see www.subgenius.com
SEMPLY KNOCK ON THE BUTTON YOU COULDN'T GUESS
Praise Bob!
Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slaaack! From home toast salam!
Oh, no.
I like you in glasses.
No, it's time for Dr. Sinister.
Aren't we supposed to be doing your show?
Yes.
There we go.
He's so scary when he does that.
He makes me laugh.
Oh, you're talking about scary laughs?
Laugh laughs?
Princess Wee has the scariest, scariest...
Especially when it's a sincere laugh.
I can mean it up.
No, Sid.
I mean, Dr. Sinister, you should come over here and put your wave cards...
You know what?
I don't mind if I do.
I will take that invitation.
This is WCSB Cleveland, by the way.
Oh, yeah.
Yes.
And we were happy to see the listeners and our fellow DJs at the little party today.
I always dread things like that.
I always have fun.
That was great fun.
And free pizza.
That, too.
But no coffee.
No.
I have an issue about that.
They had that instant coffee, but I guess they didn't put it out today.
Right.
I couldn't even find the instant coffee.
I was going to lower myself to that.
I don't know who exactly is responsible for that, but there was like a...
I don't know.
It seems to correlate with the years that Sarah...
Sarah was GM.
That there was always instant coffee available.
Well, and there's tea.
They have tea.
All kinds of fancy teas and stuff.
But that's tea.
That ain't tea.
I didn't know tea bagger.
They have hot chocolate, too.
A big woo.
That's my favorite.
Look, I just want to get back to the sacrifice game.
I have my own computer version of the sacrifice...
The Maya sacrifice game.
Where I sacrifice little computer characters.
You know, the last time I went to Mexico, you could...
And this was an Aztec thing, of course, not a Maya thing,
but you could still climb to the top of the pyramid at the sun,
and up at the top, there was a guy there who, for 20 pesos,
would actually carve out your heart with an authentic obsidian dagger
in an authentic Aztec ritual for only 20 pesos.
It was a great deal.
I couldn't pass it up.
Would he email you the pictures later?
If you live to tell the tale, yes.
After being bludgeoned?
I don't know.
I understand obsidian...
can be fantastically sharp.
Like a molecule in width or two at the...
Monofilament?
Yeah, like that.
And just breathe on it, and it cuts you in half.
Wow.
If it's done right.
That's sharp.
Yeah.
Of course, this is all from a fiction book about the...
All my science comes from science fiction.
All my history comes from historical fiction.
You kind of got to...
Well, you get...
The heroes are more interesting.
Actually, that's not true.
When I...
I read the biography of Peter the Great by Robert Massey,
and that was weirder than any science fiction or horror novel
I had ever read, and it all really happened.
Oh, my.
What got me interested, my friend Sterno was reading it,
and he showed me this paragraph that described the newly crowned...
Czar at age 17.
First thing he did was start the Church of the Subgenius.
Only he didn't use that name.
It was called the All-Drunken Synod of Fools,
and it was a walking, living takeoff on the Russian Orthodox Church,
which any other person in Russia would have been beheaded for doing.
But he was the czar.
He was the czar.
And he and his buddies, who were all foreigners,
would parade around town,
dressed up in giant headdresses,
mock Orthodox Church bishop hats and stuff.
Go around cutting people's beards off, too.
Launching.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, he outlawed beards at one point,
or put a tax on beards.
At that point, most of Russia decided he was the Antichrist.
Don't tax my beard, bro.
He was the worst president even than Carter.
And he was a Kenyan treasonous Kenyan,
Muslim communist.
Peter the Great was.
But he did introduce concepts to Russia like a navy.
They'd never really been good at that.
And as a result, their asses were always being kicked by Sweden and the Turks and such.
They still have very bad luck with submarines to this day, though.
I think probably more like Russian sailors had been killed in naval accidents than in wars.
Wow.
I could be mistaken, though.
See, again, I get all mixed up with movie Russian submarines as opposed to historical
ones.
You know, Hunt for Red October.
I'm thinking of the Kursk.
The Kursk.
Das Boot.
But that's the wrong country.
No.
Yeah.
Krauts, not Ruskies.
That was a great movie, though.
I understand that there is a director's version out.
I mean, the one I saw on cable was two and a half or three hours long.
Apparently, there's like a four-hour version.
That would be fun.
Oh, well.
So many things to watch.
So little time.
Oh, I wish I would get crippled so I didn't have to work.
I could just sit and watch shows all the time.
Careful what you wish for.
Yeah.
Well.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
He was making a funny
That was for the audience, not for you?
Yeah.
Oh, well.
Hey, look.
We need to go home and
Oh.
end this charade.
This farce.
Synesthesia must begin.
I can taste the color.
Now, we're planning tolike we did last time, we went on a long trip.
We're going to call the show More Than Normal.
I'll be looking forward to it.
All right.
We'll be looking forward to it.
You see, these other colors I have to work with, you see.
Yeah, we were
I taste the colors.
We pressed the flesh with them.
Colors, not just colors.
Oh, I don't want to taste the colors.
Only the colors.
Pressing the flesh.
That reminds me of a song I'm going to play later.
Oh, yeah.
Pressing the flesh.
Hmm.
We better listen.
Okay.
I'm out of here.
This is WCSB Cleveland.
You come over here and take a seat.
Oh, okay.
Because I can't stop.
You know, one of us has to be the captain.
Somebody has to be manning the controls.
Actually, that's the scary thing.
There's nobody at the controls.
That is a scary thing.
Quite a scary thing.
That's the scary truth about life.
Well, hey, I hope you will all stay tuned.
We got some kind of show up for you.
Yeah.
Thanks.
Can't really make any promises except for the fact that at some point you will want
to turn off your radio, but you'll regret turning it off after you did.
You'll kind of miss it after you do that.
Friends, we're glad you listened to this show and we're even more glad that some listeners
have donated enough to help us keep on going for another couple of months.
And not just this show, but subgenius.com and all the other archive sites.
But if you truly love Bob and want some of that slack back to rebound to you, you should
go to subgenius.com front page or especially the radio page or the catalog store pages
and help out financially as best you can.
Now, we know what it's like to be on the brink of total poverty and we don't want any subgeniuses
to make their own situations worse.
But some of you still have jobs.
Even five bucks makes a big difference, even if it's only once a month from enough of you.
Fifty bucks makes an even bigger difference.
All we're saying is that blow jobs could go the way of Steve jobs if you don't pay
Dobbs.
We also take checks and money orders to subgenius foundation.
P.O.
Box 181417.
Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
Thanks for anything you can do to help let there be slack.