Ich bin ein...
...Au...
Ah...
...Ja, liebe Freunde.
Es ist wieder Zeit für einen Rerun.
Aber ihr werdet durchaus glaube,
dass wir nicht den gleichen
alten
Drei Weihnachts-Hour-Schlack-Show-Reruns
in einer Reihe machen werden.
Nein, ich werde den Lauf.
... in nur dieses eine intensive, totale Rerun-Show.
Außer, dass es nicht die ganze erste Hälfte ist.
Es wird mit einer neuen Weihnachts-Sickheit verbreitet.
Für die Weihnachten und die Heiligen Tage.
Und die Heiligen Tage, wie es für einige Leute ist.
Eigentlich muss ich doppelt arbeiten, weil es die Saison der Verkaufszeit ist.
Das ist so schrecklich!
Du würdest nicht glauben, was die Elfen in diesen subgeniösen Katalogs gemacht haben.
Aber, äh, äh, äh, ja, glücklich, äh, was auch immer du tust.
Ah, äh, ja, diese Musik im Hintergrund ist von jemandem namens Kenny Wayne Shepherd.
Ja, es gibt ein Album namens Merry Axmus, ein Gitarre-Axmus.
Es ist cool, Mann, cool!
Und, äh, äh, äh, äh, Praise Bob!
Und, äh, hohohohooooooooooo.
A
H
I'd like to find the guy who done me wrong
and stuck my butt upon this Christmas tree.
I'd like to find the guy who done me wrong and stuck my butt upon this Christmas tree.
Weihnachtstree
Es könnte sein, dass sein Kopf gerade aufgeschritten wurde.
Genau so.
Die Glauben eines Kindes.
Spende all das Geld, das du hast.
Oh, Jazz gibt Dave die Show-Pillen.
Was soll ich mit dem Laufmann in diesem Schuh tun?
Ich brauche das Show-Bath.
Das Show-Delousing.
Oh, Dave hat nicht mal Headphones.
Das ist genug.
Ich habe auch die Part von meinem Pancreas, die ich dir jetzt zeigen möchte.
Es ist in der Mitte gesteckt.
Oh, dein Pancreas sieht toll aus, Dave.
Schau, es ist schwebend.
Ich werde mehr Pillen für alle machen.
Oh, diese Pillen.
Sie machen meine Mund fühlen, als wäre es auf Feuer.
Und mein Gehirn fühlt sich an, als wäre es ein Puddel von liquefierter Kristalle.
Ich bin überrascht.
Die roten Pillen sind wirklich gut.
Ich würde gerne die roten und die blauen nehmen.
Ja, die roten und die blauen.
Am Sonntag.
Da kellst du in und aus gehen.
Die Wolken sind zu groß.
Es ist so hoch, du kannst nicht concrete.
participate
很
oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
In Excellency's name.
Barbie-Dogs.
Women rape and memorialize their lives by role-playing with Barbie.
We have devised a marketing scheme for children's toys.
They will empower us to resist us.
You will use your children.
As a vehicle to bring these toys before the public.
It will be a battle for kids.
But how will the battle of good against evil be represented in your marketing schemes, human?
Good have lots of muscles.
Good.
The primitive earth society.
The scientists should accept this value judgment.
Good will have pre-physical attributes according to human desires, sexual desires, latent in children, brought out through the vehicle of this so-called.
So far we're told these toys have church batteries.
She's not good.
She's new.
From Kenner.
When?
The illusion is the ultimate weapon.
We must buy our toys.
Yes.
The old subgenius toy marketing scheme.
Recorded there at Dockstock 1984.
And me and Palmer Vreedys.
Angels We Have Heard on High.
It was by the Philistines.
The collage called All the Money You've Got.
Is from the great obtuse.
Christmas Collage Album.
Which you can get for free.
Get this.
Check out this website.
Obtuse.iuma.com.
That's obtuse.
Excuse me.
Ah yes.
And next up.
The real story of Christmas by Michael Shelley.
Once upon a time.
There was a little girl.
Was the baby Jesus.
And he had two eyes made out of coal.
And he was stuck up a partridge in a pear tree.
And he wanted his two front teeth.
And he got McDonald's gift certificates.
And he had a dog named Santa's little helper.
And he took all the presents from Whoville.
And his friend Yukon Cornelius came with the three wise guys.
And he wanted to play the drums.
And be the little drummer boy.
But he couldn't.
He wanted 10s and 20s.
10s and 20s.
And he got McDonald's gift certificates.
And he got Zuzu's pedals.
And that's the real story of Christmas.
You can go anywhere on Christmas.
So that's how it's done.
And this is where our show begins.
To the show and this is where our show ends.
And I'm truly sorry you're going to miss it.
That's it.
Bye.
Jetzt bist du in meinen schmutzigen Händen, Bob. Ich werde diesen MTV-Bombardment nutzen, um dich normal zu machen.
Halt, pinker Junge! Keine Ahnung, ich werde nie mehr für die Verschwörung verkaufen.
Schau dir ein bisschen meiner Rocket-Pipe an, Alien-Tool.
Bob Dodds kommt mit Rocket-Pipe, Head-Launcher, Janger-Device, All-Yakutism, Fightin' Jesus und anderen Actionfiguren,
die alle separat sind. Einige Assemblies sind benötigt, Batterien sind nicht eingeladen.
Diese Story wird in drei Tagen ausgeschlossen.
He-Bob!
Und die Bastards des Universums.
Zu viel ist immer besser als nicht genug.
Ich werde nicht mehr für die Verschwörung verkaufen.
He-Bob und die Bastards des Universums werden zurück nach diesem Messer.
Santa Claus!
undELL
coordinates
There's another Hy Dang
Untertitelung des ZDF, 2020
Toller hanging was been classed,
coming through town.
...
Sieves of broken amendments,
chocolate twas,
gonna find out whose
Das war's für heute.
Und was değint mir, Santa Claus kommt heute Tag.
Das Hebrews-weet is coming, Mama.
Oh, sorry. Wir hatten auch gestern Nacht Xmas.
Ein Dankeschön zum Weihnachtsgesinn, das den Stark beim Tanzen hat这座
...toxic things.
...material plants.
Biological agents
who only take 15%?
...material plants.
Shop as usual
and avoid panic buying.
...material 1890s
...material scientists
...in environmental physics
Sometimes I think all that Santa Claus is just bull.
Who's the head man?
Santa Claus.
He was a huge, beastly, bulging man.
He was so real. How come we didn't get squat last year?
Yes, the birth of the baby Satan on July 4th.
And now you can have it all, all pure 100% vinyl chloride CID.
The birth of our baby Satan.
On television.
As told by various authors.
Authors and eclectic scholars from around the globular unit.
Including that announcer.
This announcement has not been a perfunctory announcement.
An announcement of the blessed anointment and birthday of our Lord.
Zinua.
For one bright Christmas morning.
Was born in a cradle.
The rave Jesus.
To a rich man's family.
Oh, I know the rave Jesus.
I'm part with the rave Jesus.
Have yourself a merry little Christmas.
Let your sight be light.
All your troubles will be out of sight.
Have yourself a merry little Christmas.
From now on we're miles away.
Once again.
And old and.
Today happy golden be miles away.
Let your heart.
Be out of sight.
Have yourself a merry little Christmas.
To a rich man's family.
Von Mutated Christmas, Freunde.
Have yourself a merry little Christmas by No-L.
Before that, some year old ESO and Michael Shelley did that real story of Christmas
from the Tarkin Records All-Star Holiday Extravaganza.
I'm playing a lot from that.
So check out www.triage.com for that one also.
The Tarkin Records is also on www.triage.com.
And now, the Jethro's.
Jethro's Christmas
Und, äh,
amazing.
More from Corporal Blossom.
I am really impressed by their
editing work, and that's on Corporal
Blossom and the mutated
Christmas is on the
Illegal Art label.
That's www.detritus.net
slash
Illegal Art.
www.detritus.net
slash Illegal Art.
And now, more Jethro's.
Yeah!
Ja!
Untertitelung des ZDF, 2020
Untertitelung des ZDF, 2021
Wie wir sagen, unser alter Trinkkollege hat nichts gegen Jesus.
Es ist nur sein Fanclub.
Und jetzt, wir sagen nicht, dass Bob der Asche auf Gottes Schlaufe ist.
Er ist mehr wie der Schmierer auf Gottes Handkerchief,
wie du oder ich.
Aber die uptight Rival-Kulten,
sie denken nicht, dass Gott ein Handkerchief hat.
Nein, nein, nein, weil Gott perfekt ist.
Er schnauft nicht mal.
Wir sind in seinem Bild gemacht,
außer wir haben all diese dreckigen Teile an uns verbunden.
Wir müssen in die Geheimtüte, in die Klammer,
um schreckliche Dinge zu tun.
Aber Gott ist sauber und pur,
wie sie sagen.
Und er ist männlich.
Aber er schnauft nicht Jusse und Schmerzen
und schmierige Dinge aus ihm, wie wir.
Weil wir schnaufen.
Wir schnaufen alle.
Wir sind schlecht, wir sind unwertlos.
Wir sind nichts Gutes an Gott,
ohne dass wir einen Kontrakt mit seinem Agenten signen.
Wir unterbrechen dieses Programm
für eine besondere Promotion.
Wir schalten.
We還有 loneliness.
bei diesem Sport색al.
Das ist das
Denn wir wollen dann nicht
unserenмотри respektieren.
dannewohin Scriptures advent,
CoinSense doesn't make money, money doesn't make money.
SELSISτεin
米しのヤUmok Signal
Guy
N
Just like the ones I used to know
When she stops smoking
And she'll be the same to me
In my downstairs room
I'm dreaming of a Caucasian girl
And if everyone can call me
I'll find the right
May your days be rich and short
And may all your dogs spend you right
May your dreams be true
Oh, holy night
The stars are brightly shining
It is the night of our dear, sad, youthful earth
Long lay, long lay the world
In different and unbinding
Not a pin in the stone of this world
A thrill
A hope
The weary world rejoices
Beyond our grace
A new and glorious morn
Fall on your knees
Oh, hear the angel voices
Oh, night
Tonight
When Christ was born
Oh, night
Unbekannt
You are divine
Have yourselves
A groovy little solstice
Mithras won his fight
Ho ho ho
Come on, come on
It's He-Boss
Hey Kids, you can help the mighty Satinus Rice overthrow the evil normals with new Bobcops action figure with rocket pie.
What I wouldn't do from Bobcops.
Get new more chocolatey pebbles from you.
I'm a chocolate space cadet.
Life support system down to zero cocoa.
Feeling spacey.
Have some of my new cocoa pebbles.
Now so thrombody.
Smells coconut.
This cocoa liquid.
Boil.
What do you think?
Is it the nativity of Santa Claus that we're trying to celebrate here?
Or is it the horrible death of the Santa Bob?
The Santai Bob.
As he's been referred to in some early prescriptures.
Musik
The Jethro's friends.
You need to know where to write to the Jethro's.
They're at.
They did that wreck the halls.
So many other versions we've been playing.
The Jethro's are at.
At 212 and a half Miller Avenue.
That's 212 and a half Miller Avenue.
Portsmouth, New Hampshire.
Portsmouth N H.
Santa Claus is coming to town.
Was by Corporal Blossom.
Information on that.
Uh.
Mutant Christmas is available from www.tryagemusic.com.
Or www.detritus.net slash illegal art.
I'm Reverend Ivan Stang.
Friends, you can reach me.
Send me tapes or whatnot at Post Office Box 807 Glen Rose, Texas 76043.
And for the Jethro's.
Friends, as always, the hour of slack is brought to you by the church of the subgenius.
www.subgenius.com
It's all Christmassy right now.
There's a bright green bob in the window.
Is there a glade out there?
And Christmassy lights.
Is DJA out there?
And devilish artwork that's Christmassy.
No, that's something just left for DJA.
It's all Christmassy.
It's all wrapped up in perfumed ribbons.
Ribbon wrapped present.
Under the tree.
Smell that cinnamon.
Open the door all the way so we can see if he comes in.
And the sugar plums.
Something's up the chimney hole in Satan's, isn't it?
Yeah.
Of Santa, I mean.
Otherwise, gosh.
I guess we have to wait till Santa comes, Dave.
Oh, beloved Santa.
I have wanted to put your bag down for a minute.
It's always so ready to like be dressed like.
Yeah.
I have given him the highlight.
LoneCow, Babe, don't you know what they're doing to yourself?
So good as a monkey dear.
It was the night before Christmas and all through the house
Not a creature was stirring, not even a mouse
»Diesel supervision«
Merry fucking Christmas
Show you!
Oh, oh, oh
Mary fucking Christmas
Merry fucking Christmas
Musik