This is KNON 90.9 FM, Dallas.
I'm Robert Wisdom, you've been listening to the American Music Party.
Praise the wisdom of Bob!
The boss told me to do it this way.
Ah, yes, dear friends.
It's time to open your heart, unzip your pants, close your mind, and bend over.
Because you're about to receive the word of Bob!
Ah, yes, friends.
In answer to your second question, can Bob give you a job?
First, come, a big gibs a golly goshin', better puke your peat on full throttle potentate.
Elsewise, your wants will be wagging down on mammy's hind nanny.
Why can't your peaser pop a squeezer when the gushers are going all north?
You know, you're a normal like.
Got your old geisha sense in your sneezin' chamber, boy?
Heistin' an empty platter in your bean bag?
Where's your roller balls, eh?
I can't grok me no love-grow on this loo-joo moo-joo band.
You're gonna have to spreach English, Jake.
Get right with your muscle snake, snunk monkey.
Quit spritzin' your plizzerer lessen its snowin' white lute juice, baby.
Elsewise, your pleatin' bleeder's blowin' hot water.
You go blind or please your neither tryin' not to.
Either way, you're gettin' up on the wrong orbit for this kinda free-needin' bleedin' side trade, eh?
Well, aren't you gonna just stand there like a dammy nickel slug, or you gonna plus your plimper in righteous hargany, P-boy?
You got weeny rivers and your fluter tubes, don't you?
Join gumption's with the true and the see-through.
Be brave and pee for Bob, man, and send your jeans.
Buy out the gland owners with what you earned with your skinny peelin' face of paint.
This has been your enunciator.
Thank me.
These words were not to you, but already on the computer beater.
Ovenia's a wonderful life.
No trouble.
Just get set and get goin'.
Amen.
Recording.
Everything's goin' fine.
No trouble.
This is Doug Smith, radio operator.
I'm gonna bring you a piece of that green cheese for sure.
I am Bob Lundin!
Bob?
This is K&O and 90.9 FM, Dallas, Texas.
I'm Bob singing.
We're gonna have fun, kids.
Yeah!
We're gonna have fun!
Daddy, say your name!
This is Reverend Arvin Stang!
Yeah!
Okay.
That's just thunder, kids.
Don't be scared.
Yay!
My thunder!
Okay.
Now, we're gonna sing some K&O-ing songs.
Bob days are Bob days.
K&O in the Bob days.
The Bob days add K-A-N-O-N.
Today!
Ba ba ba.
Ba bah bah bah b of a' acknowledgement for the 2025
annual June 30z Infrastructure and quakeавать
program at KYAC.
K。
Today!
Daddy, we're acknowledented!
Hope you can sing!
Oh, yes, dear friends.
This is the hour of slack.
Once again, this is our...
Let me bring Dr. Mother's Ball out for a second here.
This is the hour of slack, back to school and overwork special, kids.
Bob Coutures.
I must not fear. Fear is the mind killer. Fear is the little death which brings me...
And, oh, tonight's the beginning of our 11 to midnight time slot,
which means many of you may not be listening now.
But it also would probably mean a lot less technical problems for us here at the station, friends,
at the hour of slack.
Since only the 11.30 to 12.30 time slot is haunted by the old dead radio evangelist.
So, we'll only have to deal with the poltergeist then during the last half of the show.
Praise Bob.
Help me, somebody.
And the new show, now, Monday morning will not be on tonight.
That has moved, Norm Ward, Monday morning, without Johnny Horton, unfortunately,
has moved to 8 o'clock Friday mornings.
And at midnight tonight, you'll be getting Soul Oldies, a new show from Ron Lindsey.
And that Soul Oldies, that sounds like a good follow-up to the hour of slack,
because you're guaranteed to get some slack off of that, dear friends.
Now, last week, this all wasn't true.
Those of you, friends, who heard the hour of slack last week
must have been either on drugs or on drugs.
Or hearing a false satanic imitation.
Because, yes, KNON went totally off the air last Sunday, just before our show.
Mm-hmm.
Because someone cut the transmission line.
Someone deliberately, friends, denied you your due slack.
The original slack you were born with.
And you dare to say that the conspiracy is just a metaphor?
Oh, yeah.
Ask Sterno if the conspiracy is a metaphor.
Ask Jane-er.
Ask the Conspiracyism Metaphor.
Ask me!
Ask yourself!
Ask the network censors.
Ask Ronald Reagan.
Go ahead.
Call him up.
Why not, dear friends?
Bye-bye.
Bob!
It's a Bob world after all It's a Bob world after all
It's a Bob world after all It's a Bob, K-N-O-N
It's a KNO, it's a KNO, it's a KNO, it's a KNO, it's a KNO.
That's just a crybaby. I'm just a crybaby.
This is a dog. Now, we're gonna have fun here.
Who cares what it's about, as long as the kids go.
As long as the kids go. So I'm not gonna tell you, you gotta get on me.
There's only one thing we can say. How do I know I'm here?
Not in some very good way.
Not in some very lonely place.
How do I know I'm not on a star spinning in outer space?
It's free and you can answer it.
I'm not gonna tell you.
Break out of that glass box.
And join the Church of the Subgenius.
In a country where freedom of religion is guaranteed by the Constitution, anything is likely to develop.
Enter the Church of the Subgenius, billing itself as the weirdest cult on Earth.
What do they believe in? Everything.
Who do they believe in? A mysterious character named Bob.
If he's typical of the monsters around here, we have nothing to worry about.
It's the gelatinous giant.
And what have we here?
Ah, I see, breakfast.
Wait, I have a better idea.
An idea?
If there's one thing I can't swallow, it's an idea.
Well, it just so happens that I have a bag full of all the ideas in the world right here.
No. No, no, no. Don't open it. Leave one of them alone.
Don't take chances. Keep things as they are.
Ah, changes are so frightening.
No new ideas.
Praise Bob.
Praise Bob, dear friends.
And if you don't want to open the bag of new ideas, then don't listen to K-N-O-N on Sunday.
We're going to be doing Sunday Sundays with the all-new Sunday schedule.
And it's true, the time slots have been shifted around a bit, but they'll probably be almost semi-permanent.
Believe it or not, this station's been on the air for, what was it, three years?
Yes, yes.
Well, anyway, get your pen and pencils ready, friends, for this lesson in biblical K-N-O-N scheduling.
Uh, at noon on...
Now, this is the Sunday schedule, folks.
Next Sunday at noon, tune in beyond bows and arrows for American Indian information and music.
And that... I'm going to. I really will, and I have reasons for that.
Uh, then from 1 to 2, listen to Lambda Weekly with news and music of concern to the gay community.
Varied Voices, K-N-O-N's program of music interviews of, by, and for women, will now be airing from 2 to 4.
I don't sound like I'm reading this, do I?
Followed by Eduardo Young from 4 to 6 with Latin American music from many different countries.
And even more countries on K-N-O-N's Celtic music program, Celtic Crossroads, from 6 to 7.
From 7 to 9, don't miss Leo Perron's Cajun Music Hour.
And then, of course, Robert Wisdom at 9, followed by us at 11.
From now on, us, us, friends.
Do you dare to think you're watching?
Every one of us.
And then, soul oldies at midnight tonight.
So, stay tuned.
Praise, praise, praise Bob.
Praise Bob.
Bob is the culmination of that to which man has aspired throughout his long and slackless history.
Bob is what will bring slack to planet Earth.
This is a church that does not play games.
The other churches talk about love and think hate.
The other churches do not talk about money.
They take your money.
You don't see the gold-plated temples in the church of Bob.
You don't see Cadillac convertibles in the church of Bob.
You don't see Jensen Interceptors in the parking lot of Bob.
You see slack-filled smiling faces in the tabernacle of the Bob.
Bob founded the church mainly to help unmask the conspiracists.
We're talking about the conspiracists.
What next?
Just believe in the power of the dogs.
I believe.
Believe in Bob.
Reach out for him.
I believe.
Feel the healing power.
I think you killed him.
See, there you go.
See, now, do you remember anything?
Does it hurt?
No.
See, no problem.
No problem with Bob, right?
Yeah!
Are you sure you're having a fun time all with the kids?
Now, what we're going to do is say K-N-O-N.
When I say to say K-N-O-N.
You are listening to the Hour of Slack on K-N-O-N.
Praise Bob!
Yeah!
Right!
Basically, two factions out there right now is us and them.
Friend, have you ever heard the expression, there's no slack in this world?
A lot of people have to ask me what slack is.
And that's sad, mister.
They were born with slack.
Oh yeah, you were born with slack.
But the conspiracy took it away.
The conspiracy made you want to be normal.
That's what the conspiracy is all about.
The conspiracy is a patchwork of different things.
Some are nations, some are products, some are hypnotic television shows, some are bad pills.
You'll find this if you find Bob!
And you better find Bob right now!
Now, Bob!
About wave purpose.
Now, the
sufficiently
And eventually,
you started talking.
What it's talking about?
Did it give you any ideas?
Your mental and physical health are suffering!
Is there any escape?
The most beautiful things of all to me,
I long ago decided,
Cannot be seen,
They only can be heard.
Rack!
Wham!
Boom!
Noise!
Beautiful noise!
Wonderful deafening ear splitting noise!
Whistles and squeaks!
Screeches galore!
Jingles and jangles!
Oh, how I adore all that noise!
Noise!
Marvelous noise!
Horrible hideous!
Awful insidious!
Noise!
You don't look well, my boy.
Here, let's have a look at you.
Just as I suspected,
You are suffering from a severe lack of noise.
Now, this will fix you right up.
Honking horns, screeching trains,
Bells, shouts, shrieks, gurgling horns,
And all the rest of those wonderfully unpleasant sounds we use so much of today.
Now, here, take this and you'll never have to hear a pleasant sound again.
No.
No, thank you.
I don't want to be cured of pleasant sounds.
Well, now, that's very unusual.
However, nothing odd.
I'll just give it to the awful dint.
The awful dint?
The awful dint.
Ah, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Ah, that was good, master.
This is my assistant, the awful din.
Gee, I don't think I've ever met an awful din before.
What?
Never met an awful din before?
Oh, you must be mistaken.
When you're playing in your room and making a lot of noise,
what do they tell you to stop?
Why, the awful din.
And when the street is being repaired with about 50 jackhammers going all day,
what does everybody complain of?
The awful din.
Right.
And now my valued assistant will show you various examples
from my collection of rare, exotic, and seldom heard noises.
Din?
Did you ever hear another fantastic?
Dance on a tin roof late at night?
That's noise.
Beautiful noise.
Did you ever hear a centipede crying when his shoes don't fit it right?
That's noise.
Beautiful noise.
Did you ever hear a hungry dinosaur hiccup on a windy day?
Did you ever hear a nervous butterfly nibble on a cheese souffle?
That's noise.
Ah, yes.
Noise is very fashionable today.
Why, I can hardly fill the orders for noise pills, racket lotion,
clamber salve, and hubbub tonic.
Years ago, why, everyone wanted pleasant sounds.
But today, all they want is...
Bop, boop, boop, boop.
This is Doctors for Bob, dear friends.
The most amazing of all church bands out of Little Rock, Arkansas.
Look for them soon to reform and once again play Dallas.
This one is called Dobbs Approved, and this song is approved by Dobbs.
Dobbs Approved
Approved by Dobbs
Removal from the universe of every molecule
vaguely resembling that of Dobbs
Duck Approved
Fanning from the English or any other language the term Dobbs
Fanning from the English language the term Approved
Duck Approved
Fanning of the linking of the word Approved with the word Dobbs
Doc Approved
Death of dogs, approved by dogs
Destruction of dogs, approved by dogs
Cremation of dogs, approved by dogs
Destruction of the letter D, O, P, G, and S
Approved by dogs
Dogs approval no longer needed
Approved by dogs in 17 years
And no one has ever met Bob, the leader of our church, no one has ever met
Because as you know, all cults, their leaders are usually pretty hard to find
And Bob is no exception
Bob will help you
Dig your own...
No weirdness
I was getting messages in the back of my brain
And I just kept hearing the word Bob, Bob, Bob
They said your mind is in this jar
And then they poured it down the sink
Subgeniuses are the class of people who can't be classified
Bob has taken winos on the street and turned them into millionaires overnight
By the same token, he has taken...
This isномonet viewer
Am Excuse me
This isorg
He is not the one
Which means the word, L
The former
I think the world needs a new haffод
And I would not claim to believe
Thatata
love
This show all killed
So there
the saint of sails. It's actually a mystic sails ability. Bob was given powers and has
been given messages all along by alien entities, intelligences in outer space or maybe all
around us that are literally fingers of the stark fist of Jehovah One, alien space god
from some thin galaxy.
Bob can stop the aliens from killing me.
Doctors from Bob's stallion are trying to get to the stage now to sue the crowds.
Bob can save me but will he?
Word 10.
Bob Dobbs came to town to set you free! He came to town to set you free! You got no business
being sick. You got no business being in bondage. You got no business being in bondage.
business living out of sin. You got no business living without sight.
Fortunately, this is the one true church. Bob protects me from
demons, and I got a lot of them. Bob will protect you.
Bob is protecting the genetic
future. Let him. Let him into your life. Let Bob protect you.
He wants to protect you. He must protect you. Don't forget that Bob
has prophecy at the end of the world, July 5th, 1998.
Yeah, start smoking, start drinking, and live it up.
Start fornicating as if your very life depended on it.
Bob is saying if we must be lied to and cheated for reasons,
let us do it to ourselves for our own reasons.
Let us realize where the real deceit lies.
Let us have a choice in how we're being screwed. Some ways
are fun. But Bob, and doctors for Bob
let you keep the entire...
mind all the way down to the base of the spinal cord. Now, sure
they might want a couple of these little links in your spinal cord, but they...
...to turn to the subgenius
with a concept of slack. You can do what you want!
He makes the subgenius into a wild, wild thing
that cannot be comprehended. There are thousands of
paying dues, paying subgenius members, but the three of us are traveling around,
working on the book of the subgenius.
This book can make drunkards sober, and prostitutes pure,
and harlots holy, and rich men poor, and...
It's, uh...
The Book of the Subgenius. From McGraw-Hill.
Before it's too late.
It's a Bob world after all. It's a KNO after all.
Now it is time to have fun.
I hope you had fun fun. I hope you had fun fun.
I hope you have fun fun.
Mouse. Bob. Clowder. Tears.
Look! Bob and Spider-Man are coming back.
Here, let's open the shields and let them in.
Real quick. As soon as the fire stops.
There. Here he comes.
Okay. He's in.
Bob, what can you tell us?
Bob! Bob!
Bob, come back!
Come back!
He was in a big hurry. He ran off. Look! The aliens left!
They're taking off! That's incredible!
God, they're gone!
Where'd Bob...
I don't get it. He went into the men's room and the aliens left.
What now, Captain?
We should dick.
We should what?
Dick their tail.
And fix them that up.
Fix the tail. I mean...
Fix it.
You wanna go to Echo Town?
Mm-hmm.
Oh, no, you don't?
That's a bad town.
That's a bad town?
Mm-hmm.
Echo Town.
Echo Town is a bad town.
We didn't wanna go to Echo Town.
Echo Town was a weird, weird place.
Everything was sort of slanted wrong.
Sometimes buildings are all leaning from...
And it was full of mean ones.
Yeah, it was full of mean ones. Great big mean ones.
I see Bob over there.
Up on there.
Is there Bob? Is that Bob over there?
Up there.
Look, Bob!
Bob!
Bob, come on down. Help us.
We don't like it here in Echo Town.
Bob?
Look, he just turned away.
I wonder what he's doing.
Is he gonna help us?
Look, he's back.
But there's another Bob.
And there's another one.
And another one.
There's hundreds of Bobs.
They're all just standing there.
What should we do now?
We should pull them.
One off, and then two off, and then one more.
You want to push them off?
Uh-huh.
Push them off that mountain?
One Bob at a time.
Should we leave one Bob left, or should we push them all off?
What is your verdict?
We should throw all the Bobs.
We should destroy all the Bobs.
And then some more to destroy us, to call some aliens to help.
We'll call aliens to help against Bobs?
Uh-huh.
Do you mean the Bobs in Echo Town aren't good Bobs?
We can separate the good Bob from the bad Bob.
It didn't help.
There's still hundreds of them up there.
Well, should we start pushing?
Uh-huh.
Let's go.
Oh, yes, dear friends.
I was trying to get this cartridge up here to play.
Ain't getting nary and nothing out of that thing.
Well, yes, dear friends.
This is Reverend Ivan Stang, and this is the Hour of Slack Doctors for Bob Back to School Special.
And for those of you who just tuned in, yes, it's true.
Your hour, your single hour of Slack this week is already half over.
That's right.
Last Friday, I was in.
I was informed that we would henceforth be starting the show at 11 o'clock rather than 1130.
So, that's right.
Hour of Slack is now 11 o'clock to 12 o'clock.
And Monday morning is moved to Friday morning at 8 o'clock.
And at midnight tonight, we have Soul Oldies, the brand-new show from Ron Lindsey, whose promo will not seem to play because the Poltergeist just clocked in.
Friends, that's right.
We were free of him the first part of the show.
Now, many of you have been wondering, I think, where Pastor Buck Neket is.
Yes, the mighty Buck.
He is back from Malaysia where he was taught, apparently taught, a completely new technique for mystic soul travel.
And Buck is here in the station.
He's about to try and experiment.
Whereby rather than actually talking or inflicting his voice on us, he is going to attempt to actually broadcast his physical self across the ether waves and into your radio and heart.
Or full force against the backside of your britches.
Dear friend, so take it away, Buck.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Say it.
Hi, girls.
This is Pastor Buck Neket.
I'm with Dr. Chaos.
Yeah.
And right now we've got me strapped down on this big cot at K&ON Studios.
I'm speaking to you just before the show began tonight.
And what you're hearing right now is Dr. Chaos is shaving the soles of my feet, huh, Doc?
Actually, I'm shaving the sole of your foot.
I'm shaving his sole.
Hmm.
Well, that's a...
We didn't want to save it.
We wanted to shave it.
Right.
Well, anyway, what the point of this is is that I'm going to be on the radio with you,
and yet you won't be able to hear me.
But you'll be able to feel me.
Because tonight I'm going to be out there with all the little particles, the little
Bob-eons, and...
Hey, what's that?
What's that?
Well, I figured I'd take care of this callous.
I'll just push the button while I'm at it.
Ow.
All right.
Really, what I go...
That sander always works good.
What I go through to be on this show, folks, you would not believe.
Anyway, we're going to...
We've already put a little terminal in my head for the antenna, and now we've got to
loop some wire around and plug in my mystic sole gland in my foot to get the whole thing
rigged up so that I'm pole to pole.
And I'm going to be actually in the air with the signal coming out, and I will be yet connected
to that in my head so that I will be listening to all of you and...
Praise Bob!
Yeah.
Okay.
I wonder where I am.
Huh.
The... Encore!
Ahhhhhhhhhhhh!!!
We are the Lethargians.
I'm very pleased to meet you.
Could you help me, please?
I think I'm lost.
Think?
Don't say that.
It's against the law to think in the doldrums.
That's ridiculous.
Ridiculous.
Everybody thinks.
We don't.
And most of the time, you don't.
And that's why you're here.
You weren't thinking.
And you weren't paying attention either.
The people who don't pay attention often get stuck in the doldrums.
That's silly.
Stop that at once.
Laughing is against the law.
And smiling is permitted only on alternate Thursdays.
But if you can't laugh or think, what can you do in the doldrums?
Do what?
You can do anything.
As long as it's nothing.
Everything.
As long as it isn't anything.
So don't say there's nothing to do in the doldrums.
Don't say we do it.
Days.
We don't.
No.
We don't a little bit.
And then.
Yeah, and then we.
We lie for a while.
And then we get.
We gather our strength to start anew.
And all of the lawful around you.
We still love you.
We love you.
Yeah.
Ah.
So, don't say there's nothing to do in the doldrums.
It's just not true.
Oh, I can see you need a rich and productive life.
Don't say there's nothing to do in the doldrums.
I'm ready to dig away the changes I am
It's the terrible watchdog
Run, run everybody, hide
Oh, the terrible watchdog
Terrible watchdog
Terrible
Watchdog
Here, watch this
What are you doing here?
Oh
Just killing time
Killing time?
Look, son
It's bad enough wasting time
Without killing it
Come on, get a hold of yourself
You can't spend the rest of your life
In the doldrums
How did you get here anyway?
Oh, it was easy
I guess I just wasn't thinking
Precisely
You got here, boy, not thinking
And now you've got to think your way
Out
Go away
I want to sleep
Besides
It's just a lot of thing
There's something inside your head
They say you lost the ability
To the one thing
That your tiny little brain
Moves down the kitchen sink
They say that you bought anything
That they turned away
That you're missing the everything
That's right beside the plate
There's something inside you
CIalls
electricity
I got a hardball
I think you like it
Like it
To be called
One, two, three
Ain't that true?
I
Think you're better
Better
Or
Stuck on this
Without your head
Yeah
They say you're stupid
That you're too young to worry
They say you're the son of anything and everything
Shut down your world
And they say
You're doing it
They say
Right now
You're doing it
They say
Sit around
You're doing it
They say
Hit the ground
You're doing it
They say
Like a big wheelie
You're doing it
They say
What is that doing?
You're doing it
They say
That it's over baby
You're doing it
They say
Take a look
There's something inside your head
It didn't matter
Ohhh
We matter
It didn't matter
Ohhhh
Ohhhhh
We didn't matter
It didn't matter
Ohhhhh
Ohhh
You didn't matter
Oh, oh, oh
They matter
They matter, they matter
Oh, oh, oh
This is K-Land 90.9 FM
Thank you, Tevis.
That was Oingo Boingo.
I don't know what's going on now.
We're getting out of this.
This is a lot of fun.
The board here is just running through all these other radio stations.
I just don't get it.
This is nuts.
It's that Poulter guy. Sorry.
Smarter business move today.
My heart's broken.
Oh, oh, oh
Don't let the system fool you
All it wants to do is to rule you
Pay attention
What's up?
Thank you, Bob.
I know
Thank you.
Say no
Let the fish fry proceed.
They're not that guy.
That's an obvious common trick, Mr. President.
We're wasting valuable time.
Look at this water.
We're getting ready to clobber.
Is money more important than people's lives?
And in their pursuit for private interests,
a lot of chemical companies will not accept legal or even moral responsibility
for the results of chemical waste pollution.
until absolute proof shows that a specific chemical from a specific plant caused a specific disease.
The treatment you receive when you do business with these industry giants,
it's frequently frustrating, and to make matters worse, they don't seem to care.
You won't find this attitude at Bill King's Breco.
Well, I'll tell you what, everything I take here is a hazard.
It progresses as the years go on, and eventually we'll never be able to control it.
If you take a look at those maps that show concentrations of various forms of cancer,
you can pick out the industrialized areas of America.
Are you trying to drive me crazy?
Oh, oh, there, got it.
Finally got control of the show again here, friends.
Oh, it's great to be back in school, ain't it, kids?
Yes, friends, this is the Doctors for Raw Back to School special.
Finally!
Find out as much as you can about what's going on in the world.
Let Pacifica News fill in the blanks left by the rest of your news, the blanks in your cranium.
That's Pacifica News every weekday from 4.30 to 5 p.m. only on The Voice of the People,
KNON Community Radio, 90.9 FM.
Right, Buck?
Praise Bob! Praise Bob!
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Yeah.
Hello.
This is me again.
You know me, don't you?
I hope you do.
Well, I'm going to tell you a story.
This is about Bob.
Bob.
And the said geniuses.
When you hear this sound like this.
You turn the page.
Okay?
Um, this is a true story.
It happened a long, long time ago.
There was a little tiny hut.
And there was a little tiny hut.
And there were five other big buildings.
And these buildings had little people inside.
And everybody who lived in the hut didn't know anything about them.
They called them the subgeniuses.
They were very, very weird and strange and funny.
They could play songs and sing songs.
They made, they made up a legend.
There's a legend about Bob.
And some of their music would sound like this.
Now to talk to the subgeniuses.
As sounded by
And sounded by
Now I know that music sounds pretty funny.
Well, it might, maybe not, but that's what kind of music they would play.
Their music was very, very funny.
Whenever they came out, out of their big weird buildings,
they would knock on the door of the little hut,
and all the people would come out and say,
Hey, you, you guys, you guys are terrible.
I hate you. Get out of my house.
They thought that those subgeniuses were really mean and weird,
but they never knew that they were the most fanciest people in the whole world.
And they had these little vehicles that were like,
they were like little cars, and they could,
and they had a whole bunch of buttons on them,
and some of the buttons would make hands come out and reach for you, like this.
And some of them would just sweep or do things like that.
Um, there were books.
They had these weird books called the Book of Subgenius.
It was all about subgenius things.
And what?
One time, the legend of Bob became true.
And some people looked up and said,
It's the Book of Subgenius flying.
No, maybe it's, maybe it's a date of 1832,
when the legend was made.
That's what all the villagers said.
And then they said,
It's Bob!
And then they all started to say,
Praise Bob! Praise Bob! Praise Bob! Praise Bob!
Why did you do that?
Because it's real sick.
But I have to do that because you realize, boys and girls,
that the universe is entropy.
And can you say entropy?
Entropy.
Nice try.
You're listening to people who didn't compare all state rates
before buying car insurance from somebody else.
Penguin.
utches might be affiamo cInce you are
in law and cycle,
you know you took a card from a card.
Absolutely wrong.
If you didn't igenrate,
it would mean you lose.
If you didn't explain it.
Bye!
Kid!
Bye, bye, bye, bye.
Stupid kids.
Hello, B.W. Playhouse, B.W. speaking.
Hello, is Mr. Knucklehead there?
Mr. Knucklehead, hold on, I'll ring for you.
I'm sorry, there doesn't seem to be any answer.
I know you are, but what am I?
Well, I know for a fact that I'm a really neat guy.
I'm more hip to forgive than take an eye for an eye.
But I'm not so swell that I'll take any lip.
I'll put some giant turkey on an eagle trip.
And any mean mamma-jamma gives me...
Any gum in my own playhouse can just get out.
Hello?
Hey, I forgot to ask, is your refrigerator ready?
Oh, I think so.
Well, you better go get it then.
It's so funny, I almost forgot to laugh.
Yeah, well, you're just a big-ass kid.
I know you are, but what am I?
This is my playhouse, everything in it's mine.
Stop that straight, we'll get along just fine.
There's no names you can call me that'll make me cry.
Cause I know I'm cool, I wear a Red Bull tie.
Besides, I'll just say, I know you are, but what am I?
Girl Scout cookies!
Can't you read? No girls allowed!
Now get your stupid cooties out of here!
Pee-wee Herman, I think you're a rat fink.
What do you think about that?
Baby, I'm the rubber.
I know you are.
Everything you say to me, bounces off and sticks to you.
But what am I?
Look up.
Look down.
But what am I?
You see my thumb?
Gee, you're dumb.
I know you are.
But what am I?
Well, I think so far it's been a very swell day.
And I've just decided to go outside and play.
I won't even pick up my toys.
And if my crabby old mom gives me a ride,
I'll just ignore her and just go do what I want.
Hi, Pee-wee!
Hi, Abby.
Hey, Pee-wee.
Where are you going?
Crazy, what a cub.
Yeah, you're a heck of a guy.
I know you are.
But what am I?
I'm Chris Pee-wee!
Get away from me!
You're ugly, and your mom addresses you funny.
I know you are.
But what am I?
I'm Pee-wee.
Yeah, Lester, get out of my sight.
I know you are, but what am I?
You're a nerd.
You're a fan.
I know you are, but what am I?
I'm not.
I had to do it!
No! No!
Stop it! Stop it!
Stop it!
Stop! Stop!
I told you I was wrong!
Oh, ha ha, ha ha, dear friends.
Yes, stay tuned to the next four minutes for Soul Oldies,
who will indeed be coming up.
Now, oh, I should mention that Pee Wee Herman song.
I just played there.
Now, I got to credit Jay Condom,
who will be a future co-host on the Hour of Slack, by the way.
He's out of town this week.
Jay Condom did that music for Pee Wee's early TV show.
And I mention this because many subgeniuses hate Pee Wee Herman
because he's such a total nerd.
And I was the same way until I saw his movie,
which I thought was just hilarious.
He's one of those comedians
who's lying,
but his lives become their character.
They embody the sacred juvenility of childhood, friends,
and refuse to abandon the same.
Many would-be subgenii are actually nerds,
but, friends, nerdship can be transcended,
and you can achieve the state of nerd triumph.
But other subgenii, of course, are never nerds,
but are so inherently superior in their subgeniusness
that none of this matters in the slightest.
Now, well, I didn't get to,
get to the other Doctors for Bob tape I was gonna...
And it's the song about the squirting universe.
Huh, the pretty song.
We'll be playing that next week, I guess.
Uh...
Oh!
I'll see.
We're, we're, uh, for those of you who are wondering
where your stark fist of removal newsletter from the church is,
well, we've been a bit overworked at headquarters
answering your requests for more info spurred by the Prairie Squid Show we did a while back.
Hey, you be getting some good news.
Prairie Squid, I know it.
Doing mail all day, sending out video and audio tapes
and sacred brochures and such like.
Uh, oh, one of the things we got in the mail was, uh,
Bob Larson requesting, uh, subgenius representatives
to come be guests on his conservative talk show.
So, which is a national thing. We'll see about that.
Um...
Oh, my gosh. There went Onan Canobites' mighty song.
Just, just petering out there at the end.
So, get set next week for the pledge drive, dear friends.
Uh, we're gonna need, uh, some volunteers, like three or four volunteers
to show up about five minutes till 11 exactly to take calls.
But it can only be people that I know.
So, now the way I can figure that out is if you know my telephone number
of Reverend Ivan Stang, and you can't find it in the book,
call up tomorrow or sometime during the week and volunteer.
And if, if you know me but don't have my phone number, send a postcard by Wednesday,
and I'll get it by Saturday, because we need you to answer, um, the,
not next week, but September 22nd, the pledge drive starts.
And we'll need you to address envelopes, the sacred pamphlets,
which we'll use as envelopes after the show and to take calls.
Special thanks, uh, this week to our, our extra special co-hosts,
Zandy and Tevis and Idnax and Sivit, the, those young subgenius prophets
who, uh, who, uh,
who spent, who took time, played hooky from school and came in to do the show.
Remember, next week, Hour of Slack is on at 11 o'clock from now on, dear friends.
And, uh, coming up, oh, well, next week, I believe we're gonna do,
you'll love this one, the anti-drug show.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
And, hey!
Rawr!
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Things kept going from bad to worse, but we all put our shoulders to the wheel,
and it wasn't long before I was flat on my back again.
Any questions? Any answers?
Any rags? Any bones? Any bottles?
Today, any rags?
The meltdown.
Hear equal parts of music,
subliminal guideposts,
and dirty talk.
This week in the story...
The story of the...
The...