Musik
was die Elfen in den subgeniösen Patelogen gemacht haben.
Aber, äh, anyway,
happy, äh, whatever you do.
Äh, äh, yes,
this music in the background is, äh,
somebody named Kenny Wayne Shepard.
Yeah, there's an album called Mary Axmus,
a guitar axmus.
It's cool, man, cool!
And, äh, äh, äh, äh, äh,
praise Bob!
Oh, oh, oh!
Weihnachtstree
Rothschild
Bit
zwei
mistress
七
Oh, can I borrow the brain cells tonight?
Yeah, he brought back the chainsaw.
Yeah, I ain't gonna let you use the brain cells
till I get the damn chainsaw fixed
and back in my arm the way it was Tuesday.
Now you boys be good
and I'll give you some of this here.
It ain't no good of a child.
That dog's running off with them brain cells.
Can you do something about that, boy?
I'm gonna have to...
It could be his head wasn't screwed on just right.
What?
Eric Cranston!
What we as manufacturers sell you is fun.
The faith of a child.
Spend all the money you've got.
The Christmas Trough.
Oh, look.
Dave's dressed like Santa Claus.
He's like a cowboy Santa.
How jolly.
Oh, Jazz is giving Dave the show pill.
Boy, I really...
Was soll ich mit dem Laufmann in seinem Schuh machen?
Ich brauche das Show-Bath.
Das Show-Delousing.
Oh, Dave hat nicht mal Headphones.
Das ist genug.
Oh, er hat Headphones.
Ich habe auch die Part von meinem Pankreas, die ich euch jetzt zeigen möchte.
Es ist in der Sache erhöht.
Oh, dein Pankreas sieht toll aus, Dave.
Schau, es ist schwebend.
Ich habe die Möglichkeit, 190 IQ-Brand zu haben.
Ich werde mehr Pille für alle machen.
Oh, diese Pille, sie machen meine Mundschutz auf Feuer.
Und mein Gehirn fühlt sich an wie ein Puddel aus liquefierter Kristalle.
Ich bin überrascht.
Die roten Pille sind wirklich gut.
Ich würde gerne die rote und die blaue nehmen.
Die rote und die blaue.
Am gleichen Zeit.
So gehst du in und aus.
Die Wartemix ist einfach.
Und aus.
Die ist so hoch, du kannst nicht über sie gehen.
Angels, wir haben auf hohem Flugzeug gehört,
singen über die Berge.
Und diese Berge, in Antwort,
sagten, wir wünschen, wir hätten auch einige.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
In Exelsis Deo.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
It excels this day.
Barbie Dolls.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Women rape and memorialize their lives by role-playing with Barbie.
Barbie Dolls.
We have devised a marketing scheme for children's toys.
They will empower us to resist us.
You will use your church as a vehicle.
Bring these toys before the power.
It will be a battle for kids.
But how will the battle of good against evil be represented in your marketing schemes, human?
Good have lots of muscles.
Good.
Good!
The primitive earth societies should accept this value.
Good will have very physical attributes according to human desires, sexual desires,
latent in children brought out through the vehicle of this so-called...
So Farmer told these boys at church, batteries not good.
She's new from Kenner.
Where illusion is the ultimate weapon.
Oh, we must fight.
We must fight our toys.
Yes.
The old subgenius toy marketing scheme.
Recorded there at Dockstock 1984.
And me and Palmer Vreedys.
Angels We Have Heard on High.
It was by the Philistines.
The collage called All the Money You've Got is from the great obtuse Christmas collage album,
which you can find on the Internet.
Get for free.
Get this...
Check out this website.
Obtuse.iuma.com.
That's obt...
Excuse me.
Ah, yes.
And next up, the real story of Christmas by Michael Shelley.
The Real Story of Christmas by Michael Shelley.
Once upon a time, there was the baby Jesus.
And he had two eyes made out of coal.
And he was stuck up a partridge in a pear tree.
And he wanted his two front teeth.
And he got McDonald's gift certificates.
And he had a dog named Santa's little helper.
And he took all the presents from Whoville.
And his friend Yukon Cornelius came with the three wise guys.
And he wanted to go to the movies.
And he wanted to play the drums and be the little drummer boy.
But he couldn't.
He wanted 10s and 20s.
10s and 20s.
And he got McDonald's gift certificates.
And he got Zuzu's pedals.
And that's the real story of Christmas.
Well, that'll be in the next episode.
Good night, y'all.
See ya' in the next one.
Ciao, hey, everyone!
See ya.
Remember to turn on notifications!
Turn on notifications!
Now you are in my evil wardrobe.
Ich werde diesen MTV-Bombardement nutzen, um dich normal zu machen.
Hör auf, Pinkboy!
Keine Ahnung, ich werde nie für die Konspiration verkaufen.
Schau dir ein bisschen meiner Rocket-Pipe an, Alien-Tool.
Bob Dodds kommt mit Rocket-Pipe, Head-Launcher, Janger-Device,
All-Yakutism, Fightin' Jesus und anderen Actionfiguren,
verkauft separat, einige Assemblies benötigt, Batterien nicht inklusive.
Diese Stäube wird in drei Tagen ausgeschlossen.
He-Bob!
Und die Bastards des Universums.
Zu viel ist immer besser als nicht genug.
Von Bob Dodds.
Bob Dodds wird separat.
Gorgeous.
He-Girls can blow from head to toe.
John, everything you see here.
Ken Dodds will separate me.
He-Bob and the Bastards of the Universe will be back after this message.
Santa Claus.
Well, Tommy knew exactly what he wanted for Christmas.
He wanted an electric train.
He had the whole thing in his mind, even to the table,
and his door was going to it.
That was what he knew.
He had the whole green prize,
so when he bought Taw masala he knew exactly what he was gonna eat.
Ned was ge Trung and everything heicação Babalik in his head was here!
G € 4.88 million in Six这个 worth 18해 170万,
G € 4.88 million in Six эта $ 2.80 million in S A  Military
Sin Dynamitik und Verkaufs возможно Giant Travel表示,
Musik
So rad, that you might think Tommy was waiting for something that just didn't exist.
But Tommy knew what he was wishing for.
It is turnover.
The time of the year.
All things sell.
The end of the year sale.
So come and get it, everyone, and just buy our products.
I'm a little confused about what Christmas is all about.
Are we celebrating the birth of Santa Claus or his death when they nailed him?
Well, that's the ancient, ancient subgenie.
But the present subgenie try to make sure that we have our inventories cleared by now
and sell everything to the pigs.
Oh, yes.
Once a pagan holiday.
And now a shopping season.
And it was something else in between there.
But before it was, after it was a pagan holiday and before it was a shopping season,
it was something else.
But I think they started to war over it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And then at the end of the year, the name of Santa Claus got into that.
And Spruch am Gaben.
Was ist das denn, dienadisch?
Oh, what I was .
All this children, telling tanto way to nobody.
Oh, who will motivating me?
Oh, who will legislation?
Untertitelung des ZDF, 2020
E офien Oepurz.
Euroform, Worksana.
Сейчас bist Du形.
He is missing, Peni.
Sometimes I think all that Santa Claus is just bull.
Santa Claus is real.
Who's the head man?
Santa Claus.
He was a huge, beastly, bulging man.
He was so real. How come we didn't get squat last year?
Yes, the birth of the baby Satan on July 4th.
And now you can have it all, all pure 100% vinyl chloride CID.
The birth of our baby Satan as told by various authors.
And eclectic scholars from around the globular unit.
Including that announcer.
This announcement has not been a perfunctory announcement.
But an announcement of the blessed anointment and birthday of our Lord.
Zinua.
Pray Zinua.
For one bright Christmas morning.
Zinua.
Was born in a cradle.
To a rich man's family.
The Rave Jesus.
Oh, I know the Rave Jesus.
I'm part with the Rave Jesus.
Have yourself a merry little Christmas.
Let your sight be light.
From the...
Three七 new year old god.
And all your troubles will be our sight.
Poor little penis.
H D E V E
Have yourself a merry little each one.
B E T E
From now on a few miles away.
Papaya, baby cheese.
Me once again as an old pathetic baby,
Happy Golden Day, Happy Golden Day,
be miles of us,
let your heart
be out of sight.
Out of sight.
The Jackson Five,
wanna wish everybody
a merry Christmas,
and a goopy, goopy day.
From a mutated Christmas, friends,
the Have Yourself a Merry Little Christmas
by No-L.
Before that, some year old ESO
and Michael Shelley did that real story of Christmas
from the Tarkin Records All-Star Holiday Extravaganza.
I'm playing a lot from that.
So check out www.try-it.com
For that one also,
the Tarkin Records is also on www.try-it.com
And now, the Jethro's.
The Tarkin Records
living
Power
ereal
Ja, ja!
Und...
...err...
Das war's.
www.detritus.net
slash
illegal art
www.detritus.net
slash illegal art
und jetzt im weiteren
Jeff Rose!
Untertitelung des ZDF, 2020
odm
Mark Certainty in the fuzzy place called the Twilight Zone.
Das ist das Leben von Brian, oder?
Oh nein, ich schau einfach noch mal…
verlust reagiert
und ich komme keinem zu escola
im
Sophie
trink
mi
das
noch
eine
neue
Wenn
everyone
can
find
a
light
May
your
days
be
rich
and
short
And
they
all
your
dogs
and
you
lions
The
Price
the
New
Act
on
your
knees
Oh
hear
the
angel
voices
Oh
night
electronic
Oh
night
ушка
Oh
Christus ist geboren, oh nein, oh nein, oh nein.
Komm schon, komm schon.