I don't want to be anymore.
I can't be in my dream.
The Obama administration will have to ditch Bob and hurry.
He says here plain as day, no slack.
The subgenius.
Bob.
Not enough.
Too much is always better.
Too much is always better than not enough.
Hello.
My name is Bobby J. Dobbs.
Dude.
Hello.
Meet Groucho Marx.
Here's your first question.
You have $20.
How much will you bet?
We bet $35.
What happened on October 12, 1492?
Fresh.
The French are right.
And they wind up with a grand total of $1.
Mm-hmm.
13 is an unlucky number.
If 13's unlucky, then so should the letter BB,
because B looks like a scrunch together 13.
Hello.
What is your name?
Bob.
Get the hell away.
Bud Light presents
The Soul Genius.
The power of the soul.
Real American heroes.
Today we salute you, real American heroes.
Don't stay in too long, or everyone will shout.
Finish quickly and come back.
Man, I love church.
I just love church.
Bob.
Love church.
Totally.
Yes.
Giving.
Bob.
I love this guy.
Come join the fun.
All of you have heard of Bob.
Love church.
I gotta tell you, it makes you feel real big.
Go, go, go.
Love church.
Bob.
Yes.
Giving.
Love church.
Bob.
Yes.
Okay.
Yeah, it's a lot.
Yes.
It is hair.
Right.
Yes.
That's right.
It's a lot of hair.
It is.
told to leave California's Yellowstone National Park. President Obama is a Jewish teenager. Bob
is traveling with the president after being beaten last night. Meanwhile, Bob jumped a river and it
will be secured early this week. Iran has expanded its mass trial of PR news in Washington. And boom,
Bob's your uncle. It's like having a countercultural Wikipedia in a non-linear narrative,
fictional form. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Fifteen pounds. Thirty dollars, twenty euros. Decently large.
John Wayne is ancules and is one of the Chinese.
John Wayne has received Renee 400 dollars in不會 får người không sği đool.
A soon because Joe kelvin mask on down to可以 để K어가
swelling, ykתinois Morgan Britain at work, indo official
Tehran, ind trio
ph ох
KEHissimo
and mustaches.
Yeah.
I don't think you get
what this whole portraiture thing is about.
This is how we want to be remembered.
Like Nefertiti and things like that.
This is not what actually happened to our...
Well, I'll get my head shot
that I did for the famous...
We're going to shuck.
These are...
This outside thing is not what I am.
So we're just going to unzip it.
We're going to unzip our external shell
and show the glorified self,
that glorified state
that we all want to...
Forget about the glorification.
About the romance.
I admire, too.
The romanticification.
Forget about it all.
Okay, I forgot.
Not with the real life.
I forgot.
Freezing Bob and stuff like that.
Not that useless stuff
that you are used to
in your everyday mundane,
stupid life.
Murder us.
The normal life.
The Bob way of life.
The way that Bob sees you
and your...
The life.
My hair.
Would you like to be like that?
Wouldn't you like to be like that?
Oh, he's taking over.
What is that?
Those free wings.
What was that?
Well,
that was an enlightened caller,
but I don't know what happened to him.
Yeah, I think he went around the dark side.
How refreshing it was to him.
I hope he's going to be
at the beautiful little
October Portland thing.
Me too.
Because, uh...
Yeah.
Hello, hello.
We're here at the devotional.
It's winding down.
The Spud Boys are playing.
Unfortunately,
Bob Casale had to leave early.
Things got a little delayed
and he didn't get to play with the band,
but what's the difference?
They sound just like Devo did anyway.
Fantastic show.
Great show.
My favorite part about the devotionals
are all the cute nerd girls
with big glasses.
Trans doivent.
I hope you enjoy it.
Came...
We touched everything together
and you were as mellow and mellow
and my mom's back.
We seem completely sort of
on the same track.
It is so much different than what was performing
a year ago all along.
We as bongs like an ape, bongs like an ape, do what a monkey do.
Just make men, but a monkey's right to do.
We are Devo.
We must repeat.
Okay, let's go!
Something out the way you taste
Makes you wanna clear my throat
There's a message to your number
It really gets my gut
I'm in the city lightning
But you're right to the core
I had to say that I could take it
No, I can't take it no more
Got a good feeling
Feeling
No, no, no, take me no
Not that Nestled
Me, not that Nestled
No, no, no, don't need you
A tim 탄
A python
Whとか
Thiin
Wh melts
No, I'm lucky
Dono
Doner
Thang
Da
Thank you.
Next week, maybe, we'll play the introduction that explains the mystery of the Bergie Boys.
I have a poopy, necropondy song.
In fact, I have two of them queued up.
Oh, I called too early then.
No, no, you didn't.
I won't play them anyway.
Well, I just, I was looking at...
I'll play them next week, or maybe at the end or something.
I was looking at Mark Monkey Ball's little red book here, which he used to wave around like a mouse and stuff.
And there is a, not a picture, an old-style medical stool, school, medical stool, illustration of a small baby man crawling into a female orifice with something hanging off its back.
And I just wondered, you know, there's Boogey Boy and Boogie Boy.
And what that has to do with Bob, for crying out loud, if anything.
The evolution.
They're both...
The Church of the Subgenius and Devoe are predicated on a deteriorating mental environment.
Well, a perfect example of...
And dirty pictures.
Yeah, a few pages after, this is a perfect example of a deteriorating mental...
There's a huge potato having sex with a nurse.
Right.
Yeah, we reprinted some stories from that and Mark's illustrations in Three-Fisted Tales of Bob, which is out of print.
It had all...
It had the most famous writers in it.
William S. Burroughs, Robert Anton Wilson, a couple of rock stars, several science fiction famous guys, John Shirley, Lou Shiner.
Nobody bought that book.
Our first book that's done entirely by nobodies is in its 20th printing.
So go figure.
That's the subgenius way.
Scrawled on what you call a paper, on kindergarten paper with some paint.
That'd probably sell the best.
Also, our friend Reverend Steve Sinek was at the devotional.
He's always everywhere somehow.
There's all those cute college students from Ex Day, one of whom you said is in a class with you.
Was in a class.
Right.
It was a class on hirsutism.
We were all learning what makes people hairy, what makes them calvo, as they say in Spanish, or palau, baldies and stuff like that.
And I don't think that has anything to do with Bobby.
I thought Dave was in a class all of his own.
Yeah.
I am.
Someday they'll teach a class in Dave.
I look a little bit like Melvin Laird.
I have a master's in Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
Third degree.
And then they would speak all in Dave speak, much in the way in your movie everyone will speak in Stang speak.
Well, we have to weave the Dave speak and some normal speak in between.
Because if it's all in Stang speak, it'll be like a rise, which is like being hammered.
Our subgenius.
Our subgenius video, a rise.
It's.
Altering behavior.
What?
Extending our control over mind and body.
We wire the animal.
We wire the human.
With every new step.
Behaviorism.
The consequences for human life become magnified.
I knew this was about behaviorism and Pavlovian research.
I knew this all along.
Well, you're right.
I have been reading interesting articles about the placebo effect lately.
And I read.
I read an article today about the Internet creating more literacy.
Well, and now it's funny, though.
Think about it.
Let me actually.
Of a new speaker.
Right.
I get this.
I hate to admit it, but I read this in Wired magazine.
Oh, well, they're the protagonists of such a thing.
Well, yeah, but there's.
OK, when the Internet.
When I first realized what the Internet was, I had a theory that that turned out to be somewhat wrong.
And now it's turning out to be right again.
Somewhat right.
My theory was this is going to change everything.
And that part was correct.
But I thought it's going to divide the world into those who can read and are literate and those who can't.
Because at that time, the Internet was text based.
In 1994, the most brilliant subgenius computer scientist that I knew, when I asked him if I could make a flushing noise on my website.
When somebody pushed a button, they said, no, absolutely no way.
There'll never be enough bandwidth for music or sounds on the Internet.
Of course, now we watch TV on the Internet.
When it started turning into TV, I thought, oh, no, there goes that literacy thing.
But as it turns out, despite all the pundits griping and complaining about how texting is going to ruin these kids ability to write.
Somebody decided to check it out.
And they did a study at Stanford University.
They had a.
Big project where they looked at all the student writing samples of all kinds for five years from in-class assignments, formal essays and journal to e-mails, blogs and chat sessions.
And her conclusions are stirring.
Now, don't get upset, Dave.
She says, I think we're in the midst of a literacy revolution, the likes of which we haven't seen since Greek civilization.
So Greek.
I wonder what that has to do.
Anyway, she says that people young people today.
Right.
Far more than any generation before them, because so much socializing takes place online and it almost always involves text.
Thirty eight percent of the writing kids do take place outside of the classroom.
Now, before the Internet came along, most Americans never wrote anything ever.
That wasn't a class assignment unless they got a job that required producing text.
When we know how much those pay, Dave.
They'd leave school and virtually never construct a paragraph again.
But now everybody's writing.
They actually have an audience.
We didn't.
You know, if you were a normal American, you didn't used to have an audience.
You write a letter to one person.
Now you actually have a reason to write more stuff.
And what they discovered was out of all those essays and things, they kids aren't really using text abbreviations in their school papers.
However, they don't.
They don't quite understand why they're doing the school papers because only one person reads them.
The professor.
Well, I don't suppose that's a point well taken at all.
I think that people are over mediated.
You have to agree with me, wouldn't you?
That Americans are the most mediated people in the world.
Well, a lot of the ones that I deal with certainly do seem to spend more of their life watching other people have lives than they do having a life.
Yes.
That's permeated with media, eh?
Okay.
So they're over mediated.
They're saturated with all this material.
But it's the material that they're being fed.
Now, in some cases of the wild and free Internet, they're being fed things that we would find quite delicious and delightful.
But on the other hand, they're being fed a lot of pablum and other soft cereals.
And so what they're writing about is basically soft cereal content.
So although they can write them letters real good, maybe the content.
And maybe their grammar is even kind of good, but the content is still stupid as hell, you know?
Well, we're back to Devo again.
De-evolution.
So a whole generation of retarded Hemingways.
Devo was right about everything.
Everything except for what the Church of the Subgenius was right about that didn't overlap.
And then that part confuses me too much to know what you're talking about.
Well, it's not one envelope.
It's a vast series of interconnected cyber envelopes.
And in your case, you have access to all their material.
They have access to all yours.
So you can plagiarize each other.
It works for me.
What the hell?
Onan knows I plagiarize him all the time.
In the background, we faintly hear the Gadgeto album.
I guess Gadgeto will be playing.
He's playing at the Portland DeVival.
Onan!
And Princess Wee's going to get to go to that.
Yeah!
But she's not going to be with the famous keyboard masturbator himself, is she?
Who, Onan?
Yes.
Not for...
No, I'm going to keep...
I'm a bird dog, that stuff.
Yeah.
You know I'm always a bird dog, that stuff.
You better keep an eye on your own, you know?
Yeah.
Now, it was at Princess Wee couldn't go to the devotional last night, and everybody
asked about her.
They asked after her.
Oh.
Because they love...
Everybody loves Princess Wee.
Oh.
As I heard Rob say on his show one time, a lot of people like Princess...
They think Stan's a jerk, but they like Princess Wee.
I'll never forget that.
That's at least the second time I've referred to her.
I don't think you'll ever forget that, no.
But...
Oh, yeah, Dave, I'm sorry.
You couldn't have been there either, because you probably would have...
You were always ready to enjoy the DeVos, weren't you?
I...
The last one I was at was like...
I was at the DeVos, like, five years ago.
But I certainly enjoyed it, and I enjoyed all of the bands that sounded and looked just
like DeVos for the brief moment of time they did.
And the culture that came, that was everywhere, the atmospherics of the place brought back
something and recreated something and created something new.
Those guys were pretty influential.
Mm-hmm.
They influenced me to break my toe last night.
Right.
Doing the doo-doo dance?
Get...
Here's the names of the bands that played that I saw.
I didn't get there till 3 o'clock.
I missed KRK Rydin's thing.
But we just played a clip from Fart Barf from L.A.
The Mutant Mountain Boys, you know.
They've done Bob songs, and they're the best-looking of the bands.
The Weird Paul Rock Band.
That's the name of a band.
And they did great old-school Devo covers.
But there was no Weird Paul, though, was there?
Yes, I think there was.
I think...
But I don't know which one he was.
Now, they...
You know, like most of the bands that I ended up getting to know, they all wear masks and
have funny names.
Now, wasn't there one year where they were all dressed up in, like, Betty Page and stuff
like that?
No, I think you're thinking of GWAR or the Amino Acids.
They dress as Betty Page every now and then just to surprise everybody.
The Bergy Boys.
The Bergy Boys played.
They had bergy hats, or bergy hats.
But what is a bergy or a bergy?
What's a bergy or a bergy?
It turns out that...
And Poopy Necropondy explained this to me.
A bergy or bergy is a type of flag.
And the Ohio State flag, unlike all the other square flags at one time...
Is it bergy?
...was kind of...
It's like it had a V-shaped wedge on the far end of it.
And it also came kind of narrowed down.
It wasn't a perfect square.
It was like a pennant.
Yeah, like a pennant.
Pennant.
Very much like a pennant.
And these guys had copies of these old flags on the top of their bergy hats.
Because it's true.
If you're going to play at the devotional, you really have to have some kind of a funny
uniform and goofy names and all that.
And yes, it was great.
Oh, I got a recording of some idiots finding my tapes.
I got a tape recorder.
Well, that sounds very interesting.
Yeah, I haven't had a chance to edit this stuff yet, but they...
I mean, I just had left it sitting on a table recording the bands while I danced.
And somebody, for some reason, decided it must be lost since there wasn't anybody sitting
next to it.
I'm a trusting idiot, you see.
And I got to hear them have an argument about whether to smash it on the ground.
And then they decided not to because that would be bad karma.
Well, that's when nylon...
Zafat Intelligence is taking your equipment and implanting it with different kinds of
devices that they can either listen to you or look at you or just maybe at some time
implode your house while you're away or there.
Well, I really should just start tying my tape recorders to the top of my head.
Don't tie your shoes together anymore.
That didn't work.
Well, I can't.
I got a broken toe now.
I taped my toe to the other toe as a splint.
That's actually what you do, by the way.
way, kids, listeners. If you
bust your toe,
the doctor will x-ray it just
to make you feel better, but
really about all you
can do is just tape it to the next toe over.
Put a popsicle stick in between
each one of them, half of a popsicle stick,
and then tape your toes together.
I think that's for fingers and for your
tongue. If you break your tongue,
you put a splint on it.
Then you talk like this.
I've been surprised how
many people get into radio
who have a 50-pack.
Sometimes it works
for them, though. I mean, look at Barbara Walters
and some of those newscasters.
Well, some of them have a
palate cleft and so forth, but I
guess what those sticks are very best for
is for uterine enslavement.
Oh.
Some people still have that.
I know it's 2009,
but American health care isn't that great.
What? What? What?
Say that year again.
Irrigational
It's 2009, did you say?
2010 it is. Now I forgot.
Which is it?
10 or 9?
Number 9?
I don't know whether
I've been in the future or the past.
You're still smoking the Holy Sevens?
Seven Heavens.
I've been visiting the Seven Hells
and I try to see the pipe smoker.
I try to see his face
in my mind to see if that'll
give me any form of slack
and it doesn't work.
Just turns into another demon head
just like in one of your graphics, man.
Bummer.
Would it do you any good if I sent you
a nice 8x10 of Bob?
Heck yeah.
Did you ever actually send your $30
into the Church of the Subgenius, Dave?
I sent you $45 and you said
don't worry about it.
Oh, good. So I didn't send you anything.
You gave me money and I didn't do anything.
I like that way best.
You know, I was griping to Bob Casali
about how the other Devo guys
had not actually paid their money.
They kind of, you know,
they might have done soundtracks
for our videos and stuff like that,
but they never actually paid that $30.
I did. I actually did that one time
just before in 1997.
And we were such a big company
then I didn't even have to endorse the check.
Yeah.
We're not requesting anything like that
from our listeners, by the way.
This show is completely...
completely free.
Free, free, free.
Free of everything except restraints.
Free thought. Free association.
Free laundry.
Free toes.
Free utilities.
Free paychecks. My paycheck is free
that I get from the station.
Unfortunately, it has zero on it.
The zeros are in front.
Yeah, right.
But that's the best kind of radio to do,
you know, because
if somebody's paying you,
they're going to want you to say certain things.
Right.
And all we have to do is be careful
not to say certain things.
And we get unpaid.
They give us demerit points
and we have to sort albums and stuff.
And say you actually owe money
for a piece of material or music and stuff
that wasn't yours, even if it was,
or something.
I tried not to think about that.
Oh, by the way,
speaking of legal ramifications
of using other people's...
Mark Hosler
from the infamous
appropriators,
Negative Land, is going to be speaking
at the CIA,
Cleveland Institute of Art,
not the Home Security people.
Not the Culinary Institute of America.
Right, no.
On Wednesday night,
it's CORE.
It's for something called CORE
and I don't know what CORE stands for,
but he's going to be talking about legalities
of sampling and all that kind of stuff.
But Negative Land kind of
made their fortune on you, you might say,
after they were completely crushed
and destroyed by the lawyers of U2,
the band U2.
Not you and Princess Wee,
but those Irish guys
that are incredibly rich
and sing about how sad it is
that so many people are incredibly poor.
I've never actually heard any of their music,
to tell the truth.
But I do know that they let their lawyers
crush my friend.
In Negative Land.
Who, by the way, did their second live show
of all time the night Bob was shot
at the Subgenius show in 1984
where Bob was shot.
That's why Bob doesn't come to the devotionals
hardly ever.
I've seen him at Amino Acids.
Right.
If he comes to a pure Subgenius show,
you know, I mean,
he himself told us,
if you see me on the highway, kill me.
But he does show up
occasionally at Amino Acids
concerts.
He's not as tall as I always expect him to be.
Well, it's perfectly right.
His head is huge.
It's gigantic.
It's just enormous.
Yeah, he makes Reverend Back It On Up,
the famous big boss Subgenius woman,
look like a pinhead by comparison.
Bob does.
His face is so...
It's not just his cranium.
It's his whole face.
It's just gigantic.
Well, you'd have to say his face is bigger than his cranium.
He looks like a big boss.
He looks kind of dwarfish,
but yet he's normal height.
He looks like a macrocephalic.
Come on and admit it.
Yeah, exactly.
A big-headed...
I can see why his portraits
that are spray-painted all over Cleveland
only show his head.
A lot of people thought that Bob was nothing but a head.
Yeah.
Because they never saw a body.
I've actually seen...
I'm afraid I've seen Bob undressed,
and it's about as scary
as seeing Mark Mothersbaugh undressed.
Which is another thing I saw one time.
It's etched in my...
My God, I wish I hadn't thought of that.
And you know that guy gets more...
Oh, what's the polite term?
Nookie, I think, than anybody.
You have to have an enormously scary body
to get lots of nookie.
I think that's what women are attracted to.
They'd like to be frightened by your body.
They like to go,
uh, uh, I'm going to run away,
and then, you know...
That explains a lot.
That's why I envy monsters
You know, you're right.
Every time...
Every monster movie poster,
what's the monster doing?
Carrying a girl around.
A nice-looking lady
with her clothes ripped up.
Right, because it was in the days
when it couldn't actually show
full frontal sexual activity.
You couldn't see the monster
actually engaging in coitus
with one of the mini-bevvies.
But you can...
Not back then.
Now you can.
Yeah.
In fact, now you have to.
They had to sleep in separate beds.
Hard not to.
Rodan swiped that one
Japanese babe and stuff,
and they had her in the motel room.
They had to have twin beds
because of the standards
and practices.
Right.
And in Mothra,
they had to have three beds
because they were twin,
little, tiny, miniature
monster singers.
And they could never show them
in a close two or three or four
or whatever it was
because it would, you know,
look like perversion.
Like, what's that big, big monster
going to do with those...
Those six-inch-high little
islanders.
Mothra islanders.
Finger candy, I guess,
is what they would call it.
Well, I've told you how I wish
King Kong would use me.
But I have a thing for Kong.
The Peter Jackson Kong.
So you want to be abducted
by a large gorilla.
A large male gorilla.
A large male gorilla
taken off to some mountain lair
and fondled for hours
with a hand that is
bigger than your whole body.
I don't want to go into
too much detail because
even though it doesn't involve
bad words, it verges on obscenity.
And that's not cool.
So I'll just leave it up
to the imagination of the listener
as to what I want King Kong
to use me for,
which will probably be a lot worse
than what I was thinking.
You should read the fine print.
Maybe he just needs to use you
for endorsements.
I think you probably,
maybe you got that in your head.
He wanted to use you.
When you read the letter
from his legal staff
that he wants to use you
and that way you were just
kind of projecting
your own adolescent feelings
towards being fondled
by a big monkey
into his thoughts of saying,
hey, all my Kong friends
think Slack is cool.
Praise Bob.
I, you know.
King Kong?
Well, yeah.
He still exists in the mind.
He was the last of his kind,
unfortunately.
Even before Skull Island
vanished beneath the sun,
the waves in 1940,
that Mega Primatus Kong
was the one that they had
in New York that was killed.
That was the last one.
The only fact...
I can smell the Studebaker
in the background
rising at the tree.
I heard you say that.
The, uh...
What I was saying was
that the only...
It's hard to imagine,
but the only fossils
that remain from Skull Island
are the skeleton
of that giant ape.
At which you're at the basement
of the Smithsonian now.
But there were three expeditions
after the famous
denim expedition,
and they were...
Hardly anybody survived.
And now it's gone.
Now it's at the bottom
of the ocean.
Did the Blue Jeans...
The Levi Strauss Company
back that denim expedition?
I...
It seems to me
there would be a lot
of opportunities
for something...
This is Carl Denham
for Denim Slacks.
Check me out
and look right behind me
in the beautiful foreground.
There's a huge, huge
paleolithic-looking animal
with plenty of hair
all over his body.
He's about to grab me,
scoop me up,
and put me in his denim.
The eighth wonder of the world!
And then you'll really have slacks.
This is Bob Dobbs
for Hellman's Mayonnaise.
Don't just eat that, Hellman's.
Eat the hell out of it.
Man.
Yeah.
That's a fake ad
that would be in our movie
to show how the church
has sold out.
That's, I think,
worth pursuing.
But the cool thing is
we might be able
to get Hellman's
to actually, you know,
give us product placement money.
Yeah, just think like,
you know, five, ten years,
you're driving
through New York City
or you're driving
out in the country somewhere
and there's a billboard
and there's a little boy
eating a sandwich
and there's a dad
kind of like
in the Devo,
little red book
and stuff overlooking
over his shoulder
instead of pointing
to his anus
or whatever he did there
saying,
your anus is over there, son.
He's saying,
don't just eat that hamburger.
Eat the hell out of it.
Man.
Oh, no.
I'm sorry.
That was wasted air time.
Oh, no.
Not wasted air time
on the hour of slack.
I was just thinking,
Hellman's,
we talked about
Hellman's Mayonnaise
so much just now.
They should pay us
for product placement
for mentioning
on this,
uh,
syndicated college
radio show.
Yeah,
technically it was illegal
or necrophiliac
or something like that
to do it on the air
without saying
We were joking, though.
Right.
We were doing a subgenius.
This is just part
of the satire, friends.
We do not
import any product
other than slack.
Yeah, the lead enemas,
that's all just part
of the satire.
As Bob said.
Before we laughed
at satire,
instead we
Isn't this church
a joke or something?
No.
How did,
how did it be
if Bob were to give you
a lead,
hot lead enema
as part of the satire?
You want to see
how funny it is, buddy?
Bend over there.
That's right.
I had to do it.
I had to go through that.
You did?
I was trying to make sure.
Did I drop all the names
I was supposed to
about who was at
the Devo show?
I said,
I mentioned that one guy.
I mentioned,
Reverend can't remember
his name right now.
I mentioned that girl
Princess We is jealous of.
And, uh,
superhero,
uh,
Oren from WCSB.
I just wanted to make sure
I got all my plug.
Oren was the only one
that you hadn't mentioned.
Now you've done him justice.
He's always at that
Greek festival.
I wonder what that means.
Maybe he's in the hood.
Maybe he's twisting his oranges.
Yeah, it could simply mean
he lives in the same
neighborhood as us,
I guess.
But I prefer to think
that there's a
deep conspiracy
of the dry core show
against the hour of slack show.
Well, you have claimed
that you've seen him
staring at his palafi,
his cut to palafi
for hours,
mumbling weird things.
Well, everybody does that
at the Greek festival.
And they're sequestered,
taken away
and put in little rooms.
I don't know why
you guys still keep going
after being, uh,
sequestered,
so to speak,
so many times.
I have Stockholm syndrome.
I like being abducted.
I think that's pretty clear
to the audience by now.
Well, everybody loves
to be abducted
by elderly Greek ladies.
You know how to make moussaka.
Actually, there's, uh,
there's a little Greek lady
that I have trouble
taking my eyes off of.
I have to really be
disciplined to not stare
because, uh,
have you ever heard
the term gilf?
Gilf?
Yeah.
Like gilf only
with an F on the end?
Sort of.
No, G-I-L-F.
It's related to the term
milf, M-I-L-F.
But at our age,
we probably,
we probably should set
our sights higher
age-wise.
Well, that was very obtrusive.
No, no.
I'm saying, you know,
I go to, say,
I'm at X Day or Devotional
or one of the,
or Starwood.
Those are the three places
that I leave my house for.
Or here.
I'm a guy.
I'm a regular guy.
I got an eye for the ladies.
Princess Wee has to keep me
on a leash.
And, uh,
actually, she doesn't.
I only have hands,
for Princess Wee,
as I have told them.
But I do, I do, uh,
but it's,
it's not usually
the young ladies
that I'm eyeballing.
It's usually their moms.
And if you think about it,
what that means is
I'm well-adjusted.
Because I'm,
I just turned 56.
Aren't you about
to have a birthday?
You're going to be like
89 or something?
I'm going to be a bird.
And, uh,
our, our pre-host,
uh, Charleston,
just became a bird.
He became a daddy again.
Oh, my God.
He's get,
yet another little child
that is born
with the same name
as all the little,
all the little boys
in my family.
And my family.
And close to the same birthday.
Yeah, and her family.
The exact same names
as my family.
They all have the name
with an X in it.
And Zix, Zix, Zix, Zix.
I thought that was
a little weird.
He's stinking.
Xerxes.
Xavier.
Zix, Zix, Zix, Zix.
Yeah, Mixel,
Mr. Mixel Splix.
Zix, Zix, Zix, Zix.
I don't think
I'm pronouncing that right.
Only Hal can pronounce
certain things right.
Did you know that Cthulhu,
the famous monster
of Lovecraft lore,
is actually in,
Lovecraft pronounced it
Clulu.
Clulu?
Yes, Clulu.
Clulu.
I was Clulash of that.
Yeah, it sounds silly.
It's a silly name
for a monster, isn't it?
I, well, what if you
would like to go back
to the ancient Greek theater
where you call
Agamemnon,
and you're like,
eh, eh, eh?
Let's go back
to that ancient Greek theater
now and look in
on this strange play
with half of the characters
wearing concrete smiley masks
and the other half
wearing concrete tragedy masks.
And look above there.
You'll notice far above
the actual proscenium itself,
there's hundreds and hundreds
of people with masks
ready to descend
as a part of the
Foctus Dei
or the Agnus Magnus,
whatever it's called,
when the large flying machine
comes down
and saves
zig-zig-zig-zig-zig-zig-zig-zigs
from Thermopolis,
the overheated
pretender to the throne.
Although he was doing his best
and wasn't pretending.
If you can't come up
with a good ending,
just have God appear.
Isn't that what we're doing
with our movie thing?
Only it's not God,
I don't think.
It's Jehovah One
and the Exus
and all the alien space monsters
that pretend to be God
to come back.
Kooks.
Well, the Deus Ex Machina
actually is a God machine
coming from the land of X
right into your dining room table
and ready to evacuate
your entire neighborhood.
Right.
It's an old trope
with a grand history
going way, way back
in theater.
We can even speculate
that perhaps many of these,
you know,
the Feast of Three Monkeys
and the Isle of Women
and all these other ones
by Sarfra Cleese
and Agamemnon
and Socrates
and all these different
wonderful playwrights
or maybe we just mentioned
philosophers anyway
that the actual machinery
they used
was created by these
Exus themselves
and perhaps,
perhaps Greek mythology
is a cargo cult
of not of Bob,
what should we say,
of the knowledge,
the knowledge
their lack thereof.
Yeah, sure.
Whatever you say, Dive.
Well, do you think that too?
Of course.
Could be possible.
What if in the days
of Idiad and the Olysees
and them guys like that
were all hanging around,
shailing around
and the Exus appeared to them?
Testostocles
and his men
and the Barfonauts
searching for the
silver toilet paper
on the Tree of Knowledge.
Mm-hmm.
The toilet paper of the gods,
softer than a gooseneck.
And nay, that Hecate
would come down
from a mountain
to spill her ideas
upon these poor lost men.
Oh, for they might
never return
to their beloved homeland,
but instead turn,
turn, turn in the ocean.
I have a friend
who was, um,
turned,
it was reading
about Greek mythology
that turned him
into an atheist.
Because, uh,
he was,
I'm actually talking about
St. Palmer Vredes,
just about the most famous
of all the
subgenius illustrators.
When he was about six,
he read about
these Greek gods and stuff
with all these monsters.
And he made the connection.
He went,
this, okay,
this is ridiculous.
So how,
what does that tell me
about Jesus
walking on water
and coming back
from the dead and all that?
Now, I'm not saying
that didn't happen.
The church's subgenius
has a Jesus.
I have a Jesus.
I've got a woman, too.
Way across town.
Treats me good.
I don't, I don't,
I don't need no Jesus
because I've got Leora Watt.
I think it's,
I didn't have any
Wise Blood quotes
to play for this show
so I had to do them
from memory.
So you remembered
to bring the blood clots
tonight?
No, but I did pick up,
I bought the book
Wise Blood
by Flannery O'Connor
and read it
in about two days
and it is hilarious.
That is one of the funniest
books I've ever read
in my life.
While I'm doing book reviews,
I also should mention
that if you're from Texas,
Larry McMurtry's Texasville
is absolutely hilarious.
I understand they made
a terrible movie of it.
But I got to reading,
I found it at my dad's house
and I started reading it
going,
everybody in here
talks like my family.
They're the most sarcastic
bunch of Texans
you ever saw in your life.
Dry, but sarcastic.
And I thought,
this is it, man.
No wonder Larry McMurtry's
incredibly rich and famous.
I never read any of that guy's
books before.
Yeah, that's part of it.
There's a lot of text.
You know, I'm not really
a Texan, Dave.
I wasn't born there.
You were born in Connecticut?
I was born in the belly
of the beast
in Washington, D.C.
You know, the Antichrist
will be born
in the seat of government,
the prophecy says.
I was a part of the diaspora.
You had a mauled foot
and your aunt and nanny
took care of it for so long.
She milked you every day
and wrapped you up
in gauze bandages
and gave you a lot of milk.
They put little fried eggs
on your head.
And if it hadn't been for her,
you wouldn't be there.
Actually, it's my dad
you're talking about.
He's the one who had a nanny.
A nurse, a nursemaid, I think
he even had.
An actual nursemaid?
Yeah, he was,
he grew up in South Carolina
in the 1920s,
which was sort of like
growing up in South Carolina
in the 1820s.
Pappy knows his southern cooking,
that's for sure.
I can,
I could use a nursemaid right now
and she doesn't have to be lactating.
I mean, I would prefer it
if she wasn't.
I was thinking about that very thing
about eight times today.
And just think of the many
different strange vegetables
they make down there
as a part of the solar cuisine.
The soul food land?
Yeah, well,
Mammy will chop up some collards
and mix them with her own mother's milk
so the children grow up strong and brave
and can fight for the confederate viewer.
My Mammy,
I actually,
I was raised calling my mother Mammy
and my Pappy, Pappy.
When I say that,
I'm not kidding.
I used to be embarrassed
when I was a little kid.
We'd be in the grocery store
and I'd want to call out,
Mammy, I want this toy.
But I was afraid to say it.
And I'd go,
I want this toy.
And she knew that I was doing it
and then would humiliate me even more.
But then that's where I learned
how to humiliate.
Yeah, well, you're not,
you're just not just a nut.
You're a pecan, I guess,
or something like that.
Well, you know, now I've got a,
now my kids called me Dad.
I had them call,
they called us Mom and Dad.
My father, Pappy,
was disgusted with that, by the way.
That we didn't, that he,
they called him Pappy,
but I wasn't going to have him call me Pappy.
He was Pappy.
I'm D-Doll.
And Princess We is Weemaw.
Weemaw.
Actually, we're whatever
the grandson pronounces.
Whatever he ends up calling us,
that's probably what will be called
by all subsequent descendants.
Yes, I'm Yee for Ye Old Man.
Yee.
Note Yee Dave yonder.
He is a lean and hungry man.
Like Falstaff.
Oh, no, Falstaff was tubby.
Yeah, Falstaff was fat and happy.
Who was the lean and,
Cassius.
Wasn't it?
John Cassius is that guy.
It's been a long time
since I read that comic book.
Yeah, I thought he had a staff
and he looked yeomanly
like he was guarding a plow
or something like that
and he was staring at the stars.
I've got the,
we've got a copy of the
Marlon Brando Julius Caesar.
You do?
Yeah, yeah.
I haven't, haven't looked at it.
I haven't seen it since high school.
Wow.
Friends Roman countrymen,
lend me your ears.
And after he was stabbed mortally,
he went, not my night,
not my night.
I ate too much Brutus.
That's a joke.
And I thought my jokes were bad.
I'd like to go bob hunting someday
and strap on AK-47,
which is my right under the Second Amendment
of the First Christian Articles of Faith
and Humorous Dispatch.
That's right.
And see if I can see that big head walking around.
I mean, who needs to wait?
For the highway to bring forth a bob to shoot
when the bob is probably hiding in your backyard somewhere.
That reminds me.
He might show up at that Dragon Con thing in Atlanta.
It's a big geek fest.
It's more geek,
more comic book and monster fans
than it is subgeniuses.
Although obviously there's a certain amount of crossover.
I, by the way, am a monster fan,
not so much a comic,
but a comic book fan.
I make a real distinction between those two groups.
And I'm not going to go into the reason for it
because it would sound homophobic
and I'm not really that way at all.
But it's a great joke.
Here's okay.
I'll go ahead and say it.
What's the image?
We were talking about this earlier.
What's the standard monster movie image?
A big monster carrying a cute girl.
What's the standard comic book image?
Two guys in tights grappling with each other.
Not that there's anything wrong with that.
I'm probably missing out on something.
No, I think you're pointing right at the right vesicle.
I think many of our superheroes
are latent heroines.
They sure turned me on some of them.
They said pretty boys.
That bulge.
They got such power.
Who was it that had the bulge?
The bulge.
That was the name of the...
He was a villain that fought the Hulk.
It was called the bulge.
He was a short-lived one.
A marvel didn't really go far with the bulge.
His short hammock was bigger than Batman's.
And was...
Hence the...
The snorkel.
But I...
No, I remember it was Daredevil or some...
One of the X-Men wore one of those real tight body suits.
And it had a large package visible to all the...
Soon-to-be homosexualized young men.
It was just...
It was horrible.
That's why I'm glad they had the comics code.
Hey, man.
I've still got that first issue.
I'm sure you do.
It's not in very good shape because, well, you know...
Pretty dog-eared by now.
I'm kind of page-stuck, you might say.
I'm having to click my tongue much too much on this show.
Well, just don't put your heels together and will your guys to another state.
Hey, speaking of which, it's time for this show to end.
What do we have here to get out with?
What music were you playing?
Was that you?
Was that some of your music, that last one?
Was some of your cut-ups?
That was pretty nice.
Well, last three of them.
No, everything I've had on the background was Gadgeto, which is probably at Gadgeto.com.
G-A-D-G-E-T-T-O.
The other stuff I was playing is all from the devotional, basically.
Friends, in my religious fanatical excitement, I forgot to credit the collages that were at the beginning of the show.
A lot of that was by The Large.
The very first thing was Gadgeto, with a little G. Gordon Gordon in it.
We heard some Lemur, especially in the titles, and Norrell Preff collagery.
And there was a clip of the Puzzling Evidence show with Dr. Philo Drummond there.
Friends, this is the Hour of Slack from subgenius.com.
Praise Bob.