This appeared into the New Age movement for six years.
Like all shaman before him, he had traversed the wilderness,
and now he was returning to his people a changed man.
He brought with him his confidential report, which he called
The New Earth Army Manual.
The New Earth Army is a banner under which the forces of good can gather,
the courage and nobility of the warrior blended with the spirituality of the monk.
The Jedi warrior will follow in the footsteps of the great imagineers of the past,
Jesus Christ, Lao Tse Tung, Walt Disney.
The role of the New Earth Army is to resolve conflict worldwide.
Jedis will parachute into war zones utilizing sparkly eyes technique,
carrying symbolic flowers and animals, playing indigenous music and words of peace.
As Lin drove on, I wondered what the hell I was doing.
I wanted to go back.
This wasn't me, this was crazy.
And so was Lin.
But by then it was too late.
Welcome to the subgenius radio ministry Hour of Slack.
Sponsored by the Church of the Subgenius.
The subgenius Hour of Slack that you are about to listen to
is specialized in the world of the subgenius.
Fully designed only to be played on radio station.
And only in the city of...
What's your name?
Bob, sir.
Oh, that's a great name. I love Bob.
It's a sacred name.
We all have sacred names.
They're given to us in the service of the church.
Sacred Bob.
More like scared Bob now, eh?
Yes, sir.
Ah, good.
Scared keeps you fast.
Anyone in this room who isn't scared is a moron.
Carry on.
This is PRR.
I'll feed you a bite of structure.
Yeah, you know, uh, uh, uh, not, not, not, um, but, uh, with, with, uh, what, uh, uh, and, and...
On the other hand, um...
Well, and, and, and, uh, to, to, and, and, uh, there, there I can, we can, uh...
We can uh...
I, uh, um...
And, and...
And...
Um, but...
Well, that's uh, but if, but if you could, uh, you could 10%?
Uh.
Uh, uh...
Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh...
Uh...
Uh.
Yeah, in the, uh, in the uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh...
Uh, um, PRR.org.
With physical filth.
Support for this program comes from...
Childrens.org.
One reason I shot the video is so I could see him better.
You know, blown up real large.
One reason I shot the video was so I could see him better...
better. You know, blown up real large.
Let me ask you something.
What color were the chairs in the hotel
bar?
Um.
You were there for hours. What color were the chairs?
Green.
Beige. How many lights are in this room?
A super soldier
wouldn't have to look. He would just know.
Super soldier? A Jedi
warrior. He'd know where all the
lights were. He could walk through a room. He could tell you
how many power outlets there were.
People would walk around with their eyes closed.
At level one, we were trained
to instantly absorb all
details. What's a
Jedi warrior?
Look at him. You were a
Jedi warrior? That's correct.
I don't...
I don't know what that means.
I'm Sergeant First Class Lynn Cassidy,
Special Forces. Retired.
In the 80s, I was trained at
Fort Bragg under a secret initiative.
I was a cop.
Codenamed Project Jedi.
The objective of the project was to
create super soldiers.
Soldiers with superpowers.
We were the first generation of the New Earth
Army. You've got
superpowers? That's correct.
Wait a minute.
You...
What you're saying is that you
were a psychic spy like
Lacy. We prefer the term remote
viewer.
How does that work? Well,
different Jedi had different techniques.
Mel Landau used to visualize
packing all his troubles into a little
suitcase to clear his mind.
Steve Tuttle would recite
Bible verse, which was...
What about you?
I find drinking helps.
And if I'm listening to classic
rock. Oh yeah? Like who?
Like Boston.
Boston.
Boston. Friends,
we're here in the studio.
And it's more than a feeling.
And
uh...
That clip and the one we
started with are from a wonderful movie
called The Men Who Stare at
Goats, which is
based on the true story of the
New Earth Army, which was a
serious attempt by the U.S. Army
to create psychic
soldiers. Psychic warfare,
remote viewers, and so forth.
The movie's wonderful.
We'll be playing some more of those
clips. I identify with that
because I
consider myself the world's
only Vulcan Jedi
mentat.
I am a
Jedi, but I'm a
Vulcan Jedi. In fact,
I'm the Sherlock Holmes of the
Vulcan Jedi mentats.
We also
heard a clip from the new
Doctor Who with
uncanny lines about
Bob and
sacred names, thanks to
the great
rambager for that.
And I've got
three anti-drug
songs in a row to play.
But the first
one, I brought Princess We
in here to critique specifically
because, well, the song is called
Three Drunk Newts.
I forgot to check who
actually did this song.
I don't know who performs it, but Princess
We is a newtist.
That indeed is true.
She's also a newtist,
but I don't want to
go into that. I'm not.
But I have been keeping a newt for
over 30 years.
Yes, we have a newt that is at least
30 years old. It could be
a thousand and thirty.
But it's
a good newt. He doesn't abuse
that we know of. He doesn't do
drugs, and he doesn't
drink. He doesn't listen
to Boston.
He does watch Lost.
Yes.
But he doesn't have much choice about that, actually.
So, let us
proceed with this
educational song. It'll be followed
by an educational song,
an oldie by Canned Heat.
And after that, a song
by my son
and his friend
Jonathan Payne.
But now, the newts.
Woo!
Three
Drunk Newts.
Three Drunk Newts.
See how they crawl.
Creeping down your legs
and feet. Looking for
a snack to eat. They can't
even keep the beat.
Three Drunk Newts.
Three Stump
Newts. Three
Stump Newts.
High as a kite.
Yes, high as a kite.
They rumble
in the parking lot. They scored
a little seedless pot.
Really hope they don't get caught.
Three Stump Newts.
Three Wild
Newts. Three
Wild Newts.
Causing a scene.
They're rowdy and mean.
They licky, sticky,
loony juice. They're all to
punish and abuse.
Look out, cause they're on the loose.
Three Wild Newts.
Look at their
tails.
Aren't they pretty?
Look at their tails.
Izzy, Cindy,
wish I had a tail.
I have a tail.
But I don't.
Why
am I drunk?
I'm
really high.
Let's
find some
women.
What's up?
Power
Monday!
Let me tell you a
tale about a trio of hot
newts on parade.
They had Saturday Newt
fever, and they was
burning. But they got
a little too hot, dig?
Three Dead
Newts.
Three Dead Newts.
See how they rot.
Left out in the
noonday sun. Dry and stiff
and too well done. That's the end of their newt fun.
Three Dead Newts.
They're gone now.
They lived life too hard.
Yeah.
Bye, newts.
Goodbye.
Bye.
Sleep good.
Puzzled dreams.
Yeah!
Ha!
Well, sad.
That's the fate.
Didn't that happen to all the other newts besides...
Yes, they started out as the gang of four, and two climbed out immediately and dried,
exactly like in this story that we just heard.
They probably partied first.
They probably did.
It was like going to Burning Man for them.
They climbed out of their tank, started partying, got dehydrated, over the top, and then they
overheated, passed out under the couch.
And that was all she wrote.
And you found them weeks later.
Mm-hmm. They were little dry sort of crisps.
But two newts did not leave the tank, right?
That's right.
One grew bigger and bullied the little one for years.
For 16 years.
And I still have him in my freezer so that I can bury the two of them alive.
Dead together.
He did die, right, before you put him in the freezer?
Yes, he died before I put him in the freezer.
And so now when the last one, Fig, who strangely enough is the smallest of them all, still is small.
The other one was Newt Rockne.
If Fig can die, he'll end up being buried with...
Newt Rockne.
Yeah.
Well, okay, now, friends, there's a moral to all this.
You better be careful.
This is a real oldie that I really wasn't all that familiar with.
But when I heard it, I thought, well, this is the most realistic song I've ever heard about methamphetamines.
It's an old canned heat song.
This is a song with a message.
I want you to keep my word.
I want to tell you all a story.
About this chick I know.
They call her methamphetamine Annie.
She's always shoveling snow.
I sat her down and told her.
I told her crystal clear.
I don't mind you getting high.
But there's one thing you should feel.
You might, might think it's flying, baby.
On those little pills.
But you ought to know it's dying cause.
Speed kills.
But Annie kept on speeding.
Her health was getting poor.
She saw things in the window.
She heard things at the door.
Her mouth was like a grinding mill.
Her lips were cracked and sore.
She was a little bit of a grumpy.
Her skin was turning yellow.
I just couldn't take it no more.
She thought her mind was flying.
On those little pills.
She didn't know it was going down fast.
Cause.
Speed kills.
Yeah.
Speed can kill you too, baby.
Don't let that happen.
Oh, maybe so.
Yeah.
Speed kills.
chce
When is
pretty close.
Well, as I sat down and told her
I told her one more time
The whole wide human race has taken
Far too much methadrine
She said, I don't care what a limey says
I got to get it on
I'm about into the scene of the man
Who dropped from across the pond
She wouldn't heed my warning
Lord, she wouldn't hear what I said
Now she's here in the graveyard
And she's awfully dead
There's people who don't
Love me
I've always loved whiskey
It's never loved me
Shoulda listened to mama
And just let it die
Time-tested and true
Was her sage advice
But I was too stubborn
Now I'm paying the price
Started with sipping
And moved up to shots
I keep on drinking
Till I sinned
And I'm out of spots
That's when I'd order
Just one more round
That's why I'm no stranger
To waking up on the ground
Didn't matter that I'd drink
Till I couldn't see
Cause that amber liquid
Would call out to me
And follow that voice
Is just what I did
Oh how I wish from
That voice I had heard
I'd be able to hear
I've always loved whiskey
It's never loved me
Shoulda listened to mama
And just let it be
Time-tested and true
Was her sage advice
But I was too stubborn
Now I'm paying the price
I don't remember robbing that liquor store
Or shooting that man
Behind the cash drawer
Then at my trial
When the jury saw the tape
I knew a guilty verdict
Was headed my way
Now in my jail cell
I wait for the preacher
To pray with me
Lord, please forgive this poor creature
I should have let mama
And you be my teacher
When they strap me in that chair
I'll be coming to meet ya
I've always loved whiskey
It's never loved me
Shoulda listened to mama
And just let it be
Time-tested and true
Was her sage advice
But I was too stubborn
Now I'm paying with my
Life
What other powers would you practice?
Invisibility
Invisibility?
Yeah, that was level three
Like actual invisibility?
Yeah, that was the goal
Eventually we adapted it
To just finding a way of not being seen
But once you understand
The linkage between observation
And reality
Then you begin to dance with invisibility
And that's what I do
Like camouflage?
No, it's not like camouflage
We also practice phasing
Crossing from particle to wave
From physical to energy
Solid objects seem to pass right through ya
That starts with a breathing exercise
You go
And then you think black
That's a nothingness
Got it?
It's
This is...
I don't know what...
Praise Bob!
And friends
Yes, that was a little bit more there
From the men who stare at goats
Why goats?
Because they're cheap
And they're trying to find out
Find a guy who can kill a goat
By staring at him
And it turns out to be the Clune
Yep, that's his super power
The Clune could kill a goat
By staring at it
And boy, they ended up with a lot of goats
To experiment with
Friends, the song
Is called
There I've Always Loved Whiskey
Was strangely enough by my
By a guy that
I guess I've known since he was about
Ten years old
My son's buddy
Jonathan Payne
And my son
We'll call him
Ednax Stang
The Hollywood director
Did all the music
He did the drums and the guitar
And the bass and keyboards and stuff
And I think they did it in separate cities
They did it like
Online or mailing files back and forth
Yes
And before that
The ironical song
Amphetamine Annie by Canned Heat
What makes it ironic is
I think that
Either the singer or the bass player of that band
OD'd on downers
They were smart about the speed
But they were kind of dumb about the downers
Downers kill too
Princess Wee, I can't hear you very well
You can't hear me?
I can hear you
I'm here
I have to talk again
Okay
That's a lot better
Alright
You just don't have a lot of testosterone in your voice
You little space princess
I guess I don't
Friends, it's been a long day
And the main subject of this show
Is actually not going to be
Preaching about the bad pills
But
As opposed to the good pills
But mainly this whole show
I'm going to gripe about how ticked off I am
That my lawnmower is broken
I'd say that's a good subject for the hour of slack
Right?
That ought to get everybody feeling real slackful
Oh I felt real slackful today
Actually I
I had to move fast
Because I knew it was going to rain this afternoon
Princess Wee was off working
Now that she's retired
She works really hard
Volunteer stuff
And I thought
Well I'll mow our yard before it rains
It's about to get out of control
The dandelions and monsters
And triffids were about to get out of hand
And first I had to crank up the Batmobile
You know Gotham City is based on Cleveland
And there is a Batman
But he's old and decrepit now
And we keep his car
The Batmobile
In our garage for him
And I had to jump start it
To get it out of the way of the lawnmower
To get the lawnmower out of the garage
And I finally get the lawnmower going
And I mowed the backyard
And I started on the front yard
And I hit a root
I hit a root
And here's the thing
This is the second time I've used
This brand new lawnmower
What is this cheery music in the background
That makes me sick
Where's Dave?
And he believes it's a fail
It's a total fail this injury
All of a sudden
All I had to do was get mad and yell
Where's Dave?
And there he appears
Well you said
You remember the time you mentioned
And so I was trying to keep to the schedule
Although I'm a few minutes floating
You see
Not too long ago
I had a visitation
I was in my side yard
Right out by the driveway
And I looked up and uh
I think it's gonna happen, Stang
You're gonna fix my lawnmower?
No, I think an extraterrestrial being
Perhaps some vapor type of astral projection
Perhaps is going to fix it
Well on next day
Everything will be fixed
But good
But you won't have a lawn on next day
Yes
You'll have some freshly new mowed grass
But you're not gonna be able to find any turtles to put in
If you know what I'm saying
Well it won't be all gnarly with roots
It'll be
It will
My yard on my escape vessel
Let's see
What will it be like?
I guess I should think about that
Princess, what would you like?
We won't have to mow it for one thing
I think it should be
We'll have goats that mow it for us
Space goats
Yeah, one-eyed goats that stare back at you
Remember that show Space Goats?
That was great
Yeah
And uh
What?
Yeah
It was a talk show
Space Goats
Did the goat inflate things with its uh
You know its uh area back there?
How they do at the state fairs?
You know you place a balloon in the goat's rectum
And it will bark and blow it up
And it also plays songs on a bicycle horn
With different pitched bicycles
Oh in Texas they always used uh
Psychotic goats
Animal cruelty
Well other animals
Pigs
Can Dave stare at a lawn mower?
And get it to come back?
Right
Oh if only I could
I'm missing one valuable, valuable lesson
And then I could proceed to uh
Take apart the middle spindle
And uh the entire apparatus if you'd like
Straighten the crank?
Yeah the crank
Men who stare at lawn mowers
That's too, that um
In the underworld of uh
Conspiracy theories
What you just said was rife with meaning
Whatever the hell that means
Oh yeah?
Really rife
Well lawn mowing is known to be like
Giving a haircut meaning you
You blast somebody with uh
Different types of rays
Whether ELF or PFM or whatever types
Not PFM
ELF or whatever types of
Hmmmm
Uh substantial uh way you want to destabilize
The character
Of the character
Or just destabilize you know
A lot of people like to make pudding with it
Well so uh aliens will come and fix everything
Now I read in the
In the conspiracy news today
That Stephen Hawking
Uh whose mom I think is a character on Lost
Is uh
Stephen Hawking was saying
That he thought when the aliens came
They'd probably be bad news
Because they may very well come in the form of diseases
Like my little friends that I study in my micro aquariums
They would be
The aliens would be
What we call diseases
Now they might see themselves as Vulcan Jedi Mentats
But to us they would be fatal
I think
Dr. Hawking used the
Example of Columbus
And the Native Americans
Well I've been to Columbus quite a few times
And I can tell you the bacteria is just rampant down there
Especially on High Street
But what you were saying about Hawking
It doesn't have good bacteria
Or Hawker as some of us like to call him
Is he just spat upon the wrong wall
Because extraterrestrial biologically
We've been bombarded with viruses
And uh
And um
Disease things for
Since the beginning
Well some people think that that's how life got started here
Was uh
Came through space on comets
Because some critters can actually survive
As tons
Little dried up shriveled things
In out of space
Personally
I don't find that a necessary explanation
But I'm not expecting a necessary explanation
Only unnecessary explanations
A platitude
That's what this church is all about
A turgid heaping helping of a platitude
A big platter of platitudes
A buffet's worth
That's what any good religions were about
Things that make you
Things that sound good
They don't have to be good
They don't have to be true
They just have to make you feel better
Oh Listerine take a look at that
They've got the sweet and sour bobs head over there
And there's the general sours chicken
I don't know which I'm gonna try first
And they're all so different
And yet so alike
See
When you follow a metaphor down it's logical path
You often get stuck in some place that's really scary
And surrounded by like pointy sticks and stuff
So
That's why we don't let amateurs do this show with us
Well
Technically speaking we are amateurs
Well we're amateurs at some things like suicide
Well at the Art of Radio perhaps we're wank amateurs
But maybe our rank is higher than we think
I prefer to think of us as wank amateurs
Yeah unfortunately
There's a lot of excited substance that gets out there
And doesn't really fertilize anything though
That's why I stare at goats
And lawnmowers
Yeah
Working lawnmowers
Well why would anyone want to live in such an awful world
Where all the devices had brains of some sort
And were all
You know how they can create conceivably
Smart phones
Nano life
Yeah smart phones, smart lawnmowers, smart nano bots
That's just what we need
Smart sky
What's that
The super satellite that takes over the world in Terminator
Skylift or Skyhook or whatever it is
Skyhook
Skyeye
Skyball
Skybrain
Yeah
Skyburnetics
There we go
The ancient, no that's not an ancient art it's not even an art
Scrying that's what you're thinking about
Scrying
Scrybabies they would tell the future
Well it's like rolfing
With their screeches
It's like rolfing once you release all of the negative emotion that you've been storing in your body for the last 30 years or something like that
Not to mention the body
The three bottles of wine you drank that night
You have to rolf those as well
Regularly
Into the porcelain
Prayer altar
Which is pretty much what we're doing right now we're giving up offerings to the porcelain god
Nothing that's coming out so far is I would call it anything but waste
Actually I have something that's sort of interesting that came right through the ethers through
My telephone
That lets me know that anyone who is interested could go to this website and learn about Rocknar being going into politics
Oh that's right
There's a website
Governor Rocknar the sub genius who frequently calls synesthesia following this show and thus ends up on our slack
Oh my god
Rocknar had a he's running for congress in Kentucky
On the progressive anarcho syndicalist
Well he was
I don't know but he was pushing Dr. Hal to run in San Francisco
I think he just run as a sub genius
And he got tired of pushing so yeah he started he's he is actually and he was going to speak on the 22nd
Yes
I was I was wondering how that turned out
We don't know anything about it but maybe there's a report at http forward slash slash tiny earl dot com r vance v a n c e 2010
Oh tiny earl dot com r vance 2010
Oh okay
Forward slash yes
Oh well
I was hoping there would be like a lot of flower type like flower drum girls and stuff and people like that
People waving red flags wearing shorts that you can actually see the crotch area and stuff
And tea makers I understand that the people who make love tea come to these events nowadays
The nice tea makers or am I confusing them with the homosexuals who lay their parts upon the faces and tops of the heads
Now see Rocknar was into that too
He didn't know he was
He wasn't so much tricked into it but he volunteered for the wrong thing
He was a blind robin
He volunteered for what some somebody else had been set up for the sacred tea bagging ceremony at X day a couple of years ago
And the guy who was going to be the victim who didn't know that was what it was going to be
Thought he thought it was he was going to be getting a haircut
Well that guy had to leave
That guy had to leave
Well Rocknar thought well I want the free haircut and they're going to videotape it and everything
So and he didn't think much of me
He didn't think much was out of hand when they duct taped him to a lawn chair
Oh he should be in a good sport
But then when all the men well some of the men of X day and one or two women lined up behind him
And laid upon his bald pate the progenitorial sack one might say
It was a tea party a tea bagging party in the old school sense
Okay now I'm imagining proboscis filled with delights from Sri Lanka and so forth
But you're actually talking about the Mons Venere some sort of insect or something
Well it's one of those you had to you wouldn't want to have been there things
You had to have been there but you really wouldn't want to be
Yeah noise information so to speak
So let's skip let's just skip right by the tea bagging debate
Yeah let's just skip right by the tea bagging debate
Well I just have one fine point
Just one fine very fine point
Wasn't his pate embalmed for this ritual
Didn't he start with a full head of hair and they first they took the hair off
And then the okay I may be I may be completely wrong
We were way ahead of those right wing cranks let me put it that way friends
We were so many years ahead of the tea party bunch
As usual they see sub geniuses do something just as a satire
And fringe insane people take it to heart
And will imitate us but they're not kidding
Where do you think Fox is getting all their ideas
Don't you check out the people or checking out your website all the time
Keep your enemies close and your friends closer
That's what Apache I mean Arapaho always said you know the guy
Yeah
Yeah and so don't think I mean don't you know
The Cheyenne they would be very they would stay shy
And destabilizing too
And just watch
Watch in a destabilizing way
So you're saying that Fox News people they tune in on the hour of slack
And read subgenius.com and that's where they get that stuff
Do you think they have any original ideas of their own
Do you think they're capable of original creative thought no
I kind of thought that
They must scour there's a name for these kind of people in New York City
Well they're good at making things up I know that
Well just you have to consider the source and consider the resource
There used to be in New York City a long time ago near Tin Pan Alley
Was a bunch of buildings filled with so called producers
In your film racket you're in
Yeah
And they would just regularly solicit scripts ideas anything they wanted to do
And they promised the world and give back nothing
And of course New York State did investigate them and it propped up elsewhere
Hollywood yeah
Yeah
And the rest of the world and into the infinite sky
So what you're saying the church of the subgenius is what everything in the whole world
Has inadvertently been imitating and copying from
And discarded in many cases you must say that
Well sure because it would be insane to try to live that way unless you were a subgenius
Now see a pink trying to live like a subgenius is going to look like an idiot
Well I guess anybody living like a subgenius is going to look like an idiot but
Duh
Definitely
Yeah why do you think they call it subgenius have I already used that one this year
Oh no
I bet I have yeah
Yeah
I'm sorry Bob
Did you do the thing about the yeti with the purple mohawk and that cultural studies thing that was done in 1949 I guess
Did you go through all the whole smear
No I think you just did though
Well yeah that's the pretty much the is all and be all of the thing me
We're only allowed
Put a purple mohawk on a yeti to see what the cultural disadvantages would be within his in group meaning other yetis to the great northwest or is it south east
But they can grow their hair into all kinds of elaborate things
Yeah
They can change the color of their hair at will they can shed all their hair instantly have it grow back in patterns they can be striped dotted mangy if they want to look that way for pity you know if they're feeling sorry for themselves
It is bad
Yeti they can alter their bone structure takes a while I understand now I've Mark I've never seen this happen
Yeah
But among the sub yeti
Among the sub yeti well yeah
Many of them are just incapable they're challenged they can't regrow their own hair at will and they can't regrow their own bones well they try and sometimes they manage to feel a little bump over there or look there's a little patch of peach fudge growing there but they never succeed the same way that the ancestors do
Well we've our bloodline's been watered down you know there's hardly any full blood yetis left and
I guess we've all
You know
Had
What do they call it we've been we've been touched with the human paintbrush
Yes we've been talked
At the human
Paintbrush
Tainted
Yeah
We've all got some of the human taint
We've been played
Our taints have even more of the human taint
We've been burnished over as well
You know when it's time to look at this
Anxiety
I can't go and talk about it no more
The rabbits
The clois
We're going to lose
What are they
Coming apart in the back.
Therefore, I think this is what's coming undone.
Now, when the X-Men, or the men from Planet X, or the sex goddesses, whatever you want to call them,
when they come here this July 5th, morn, at 7 o'clock in the morning,
we will be given the powers of our Yeti ancestors,
and we'll be able to change our physical appearance at will.
And have you thought about what you're going to do, Dave?
Dave? No, Rob Nahr, a long time ago, said he was going to keep his same large, clumsy body.
Well, I'm going to keep my large, clumsy body, only it's going to be indestructible.
Kind of indestructible.
Oh, so it doesn't matter how clumsy you are.
Oh, well, if I'm indestructible, it certainly is, and it's going to be whoever I clumsy into.
Right, right.
You bendy bones.
And to keep that at a minimal, I was going to originally say at the beginning of the conversation about, you know, lawnmowers and wood spirits,
and things that go bump on your lawnmower, that, like, I was going to have sylphs and sylphides,
of which I don't know the difference between them.
I was going to have sylphs and sylphides be my actual greenery in my space vessel.
Are you one of them pagans that worships the green man?
You know, that's really Satanism.
I know that the green man is...
Even though the devil is red and the green man's green, it's still, it's a colored man.
That means the devil.
And they both have horns.
Funny colored man.
But the green man is not considered.
The devil everywhere in the world, it's considered a nature spirit.
Right.
Only idiots consider that to be the devil.
But there's, idiots actually outnumber pagans.
And although they include quite a few of the, a rather large percentage of the pagans within that number,
pagans are, I suppose, idiots are a subset of paganry as well as everything else.
Could we say that many pagans, as well as those, especially who assail...
Assail them for the beliefs are not fully aware of everything they should be.
Now, pagans are not to be confused with pegging or pagan, which is an act, some sort of a sex act that I don't even know what it means for sure.
It's something that pagans do when they get naked.
You see how the E changes to the A, linguistically deterministic and so forth.
I know, I know a pagan who needs to get pegged.
Pegged.
But, um...
Can I ask you a question about Mars?
I know it's not the right time because everyone's having sex again back there in the booth and stuff.
Obama's from Mars.
He's not even an Earth man.
I want to see, I want to see his planetary birth certificate.
We haven't got one until the globalists take all the way over.
That's right.
Yeah.
But, uh, I...
I have...
I had heard that, um, the human race was, as we know it, was a modified gene that was somehow transcripted by the dying Martian race, which looked a bit different than we do, um, to those, you know, perhaps of the Yeti bent and others of the primate families.
The ones at least having family reunions regularly.
And that those were the ones who escaped from the, uh...
Ancient astronauts.
Well, is it true?
Uh, everything is true.
Oh.
Eventually.
Sooner or later, at some point in a galaxy long, long ago and far, far away, everything happened.
That's called quantum physics.
Or will happen.
Well, no, I'm not talking about anything quantum.
I'm just talking plain, straight history.
It's just that we don't know about all of them.
But it is quantum physics, too, because there's less than a zero probability of any damn thing there could possibly...
be happening just by the nature of there being less than a zero possibility.
Oh, Dave, now come on.
That math stuff is just a bunch of hoo-ha dreamed up by scientists to scare stoners and little kids.
All that infinity stuff, all that quantum, that's just to confuse stoners.
That's just something...
You know, it's like religion.
It's just something the mathematicians came up with to...
It's a control thing.
Well, I'm glad to hear that at least...
They're turning out some stone-confused kids there in our educational system.
Well, have you done the math that leads up to E equals MC squared?
Well, I've...
It reminds me of my favorite little button that Nenslow had printed up.
It said...
It was a little button.
I bought ten of them and gave them out for Christmas.
It said, what part of E equals MC squared don't you understand?
That was a good bumper sticker.
Or still is.
Thanks to Nenslow.
If we were butterflies, you know, within the Japanese psycho-psyche,
if we could come and go as we will, between dimensions and so forth,
then, and only then, would we be, you know, doing that.
Doing what?
I was listening to the music and not you.
I forgot what you were talking about.
Hide it.
We'll find out when we play the tape back.
Well, I think what I meant was, if we're speaking in terms of haptics or perhaps morphosis,
metamorphosis becoming like being able to merge into different dimensions just with a snap of an eyelid.
But you were talking earlier about metamorphosis being a path that you don't want to go down or something like that.
Or were you just talking about going down?
I was talking about pedagogological.
Not pedophiliological, but pedagogical.
God, you know it.
Maybe we're getting in a little bit over our heads, Dave.
You like gynecology.
Are we wading in a little too deep?
Sure.
Are we swimming into waters that subgeniuses are banned from for good reason?
Yeah.
They don't even know what an obstructed...
An obstructed...
Because subgeniuses will get into this deep intellectual water and then we...
We'll get into this deep intellectual water and then we...
We in it.
Yeah, you'll immediately see if you examine any of the websites and so forth.
The websites, they call them.
They start to make these grand pronouncements and back them up with a curious amount of information and research inside it as well.
And then they say, oh, poo-poo panties, and then give a funny name and sign off.
You know?
I mean, I'm sorry I had that, you know, there.
I guess I felt embarrassed about saying that, but...
I'm sorry, too.
Oh, me three.
And what about my lawnmower?
Oh, God!
Oh, my God!
Joe Hoover won.
There ought to be a warranty or something.
Calm down, Mrs.
Just do that.
Just calm down.
Relax.
Get here in the dental chair.
The dental chair pickin' air.
That's right.
The dental chair pickin' air will just take apart all those loads and cares and worries that you're wearing.
And you're wearing around your neck like a folded lettuce.
Somebody called this show childish.
Well, somebody was...
It's only money.
They called us childish.
Me.
Copyright 1982 Puzzling Evidence Show.
That's a sign that puzzling evidence cannot grow old.
Puzzling evidence will be at X Day.
Dr. Philo Drummond will be at X Day.
Oh, my goodness.
Dr. Hal Robbins will be at X Day.
Reverend Susie the Flute.
Susie will be at X Day.
Lonesome Cowboy Dave will be at X Day.
Although we may have to drag him on a chain behind a truck to get him there.
The Amino Acids will be at X Day.
Fat Man Dean will be at X Day with Tommy Amiibo.
The Duke of Uke will be at X Day.
Fat Free will be at X Day.
Priestess Pisces will be at X Day.
Dr. Katadla Yume will be at X Day, but he'll be taking it easy, I think, this time.
This is...
This has got to be the year.
The Queegee Bowl Cartel.
The bad-beating Reverend Chris Lee will be at X Day.
All the playas.
Yeah.
X Day.
In fact, every dues-paying subgenius will be on the saucers on X Day, my friend.
And will receive this luxury egg bowl and deep-fried batter dip.
And compliments of the chef here, Mr. Harry Pockwater.
The Lord!
1998. That's this year.
Oh, it's already?
It's only 1998?
We don't know. We don't know. We'll find out, won't we?
At X Day!
But you're one of the spottings of my shoes are smoking.
Oh, by the way, I have an announcement that has to do with X Day.
I finally got the X Day page done.
The new X Day page on subgenius.com.
And we're one to look at subgenius.com and click on the events button,
since X Day is a subgenius event.
They would find not only all kinds of lies and truth about what we think might happen this X Day,
and directions and so forth,
but we have these wonderful pictorials of past X Days.
And now I know some people out there don't like to see young ladies,
photographs of young ladies with their shirts off,
and they shouldn't look at subgenius.com.
Enough said.
Sometimes.
Some of the ladies took off their shirts,
and there was like a suit of armor underneath their shirts.
Well, no kidding, man.
There's some high-maintenance ladies.
The character armor...
Sure, their skin may be nude,
but the character armor is hard.
It's hard bark on them.
Like a gillemonster or some little tiny lizard-like creature that lives in the desert.
You know, and their skin is so rough and tough,
you couldn't even chew it off if it could manage to hold it.
things neck down long enough to get bited from behind.
And it's not just Susie the floozy, friends.
Well, in some ways it is just Susie the floozy, but yeah, I get what you're saying.
So, you know, I've had a couple of the girls of X-Day, we'll call them in a sexist manner,
have called me up and said, Reverend Stang, remember back in 1999 when I wrestled on the
giant American flag covered with blood and I was nude?
Well, I'm trying to get back with my family again now, and can you take those pictures down?
And I did.
So, friends, that means you better look at year 2000, 2001 before the girls from those
years tell us to take their pictures down.
Right.
That's right.
Take your pants off.
Take your pants down before we take those pictures down.
If you weren't so homophobic.
What?
Huh?
Pardon me?
The only thing I'm homophobic about is I'm phobic about homophobes.
I fear people who fear queers.
You fear people who fear queers?
Yeah.
I'm afraid I'll catch it.
I'm afraid that homophobia is somehow contagious.
See, then you believe in karma.
And you know they're always going...
Those homophobes, they're recruiters.
You know, they're always trying to recruit young kids to become like them.
Well, remember...
The homophobes are.
In the old days, they used to have what they would call the latent homophobic.
And he's always, like, dressed up as a policeman or one of those, you know, guys exploring
in the jungle and stuff.
And then he would start killing...
Or he would be a Nazi and stuff and start killing people.
Because he had too many X chromosomes or Y chromosomes.
I mean, we're only supposed to have one of each, aren't we?
Well, and some people are just insecure.
That, you know, what you're going to do.
That's what it boils down to.
But some of them do have two X's.
And that doesn't mean, like, double X day or anything like that.
Some of them are just genetically...
All my X's are in Texas.
It's actually true in my case.
I can...
I'm stuck in this bar trying to find my car.
And all my X's are in Texas.
You sound old, Dave.
Oh, I feel old right now.
Every neighbor and thing.
I was just about to say how young he sounded.
I sound like a...
Oh, I forgot what you were talking about.
What were you talking about?
The days in the old El Paso?
I was talking about that music we had on.
And the background was Perry Kingsley.
The old-timey Space Age bachelor pad music.
Thanks to Mr. Sister for loaning us that.
Thanks for the lounge job, Stan.
Yeah, it was a lounge job.
Yeah.
Which is better than a sleeve job anyway,
if you're working second shift.
Believe it or not, I'm looking at a new Devo album
that we found when we walked into the station
called Fresh.
It's not really an album.
It's a demo or a promo thing.
It's got a side A is a three-minute song called Fresh
and side B is a three-minute song called What We Do.
And it shows a blue power dome
full of blue plastic fruit on the cover.
And I was tempted.
Just because I haven't heard this,
it's like, well, I've got Bernard versus the conspiracy.
I've got El Paso All-Stars Hour of Slack sign out.
I've got Men Who Stare at Goats excerpt three.
But I'm tempted to go out with this Devo song
just because I haven't heard it.
Do you want to listen in and hear the new Devo song
and maybe just ruin it while we talk over it?
Are we close to the end of the hour?
Yeah, we sure are.
It's like five minutes.
I'll be, I'll be, I'll be, okay.
The other thing is,
I haven't played an actual record,
a vinyl record in this station ever.
And we'll just see what happens
if I push all three of these buttons right now.
Oh, it's like magic.
One of them's working.
Is it a 45?
Sort of.
Oh, it's an old EP type thing.
It's actually, it's a full-size vinyl album and it's...
Okay, now let's listen to the new Devo song.
Listen carefully.
Yeah, carefully.
Carefully.
Don't be...
Okay.
Careful now.
Don't repeat any of the lines like...
Mania?
I wonder if this is supposed to be a 45.
Maybe it's a 78.
Yeah.
Dude.
He meant to do that.
I think he means to have a second brain.
And for nothing could be better, right?
Like a man who went to heaven.
So fresh it almost makes me want to cry.
So fresh it's giving me a second life.
Man, I wish everybody'd see Reverend Peg dance to this.
It's all over the studio.
Go hands down.
I won't even think twice
A man in the world of a 45-year-old woman
A man of his own
He's gonna come around the corner waiting just outside the top
Drinking, drinking, sweet and tangy
Daring me to track him down
And this guy, I know
He's black and he's a high-rise tower
He's blasting through the sands of time
It's useless to resist his power
He's now or never
So fresh
I'll search it till I find it
I'm closing in behind it
So fresh
Nothing could be better
Like a daddy went to heaven
So fresh
It almost makes me want to cry
It's giving me a second
Love
So fresh
It almost makes me want to cry
It's giving me a second chance
So fresh
Well, that is amazing.
Fresh.
By the Devos.
And it sounds as fresh as 1980.
It does sound fresh as night.
When you first played it,
I thought they were actually going in a different direction
and this expressed their newness.
Yeah, me too.
It's going, well, that's great.
They've got a new sound.
And then I realized it really is a 45.
Actually, it's a blue-colored, the size of a regular 33 RPM vinyl record,
but it's printed on blue plastic, and it is a 45.
Yes, that's part of the vinyl revolution is to come up with the silliest format.
You could think of a 45 as big as a wedding cake or something like that.
Well, you know, if I was cool, I'd go, well, this is just a dance mix.
You know, this is what clubs get.
But they did have it.
They're higher res at 45 RPM, just slightly.
Oh, well.
Well, res is important, at least if you're from this place.
Yeah, if you're from, well, like I used to live on the Rosebud res.
And what's the res around here?
Rosebud was near Wounded Knee, the Wounded Knee res.
But, hey, look, it's getting time to stop.
You made me think about Orson Welles.
I was wearing a funny hat when you said that.
Well, what do you think this is, some kind of stream of consciousness show?
I hope not.
For the love of God, what could be worse than that?
For the muggery of blobs.
Remember, free association is not free.
Hey, I've been listening lately to I Was a Communist by the FBI.
It kind of makes me feel creepy, man.
Well, I've been listening to the Hour of Slack, but we can't listen anymore,
so we have to go bye-bye, Dave.
Okay, we're listening to the FIB.
Uh, thank you.
And, uh, we'll, uh, talk anonymously.
Anonymous, you mean.
An a-hole.
How'd you find us, Lynn?
I told you, I remote-viewed you.
If this is a psyops base, what are you doing here?
I said it was primarily psyops.
They're individuals in the current administration
who are looking for creative solutions to the war on terror.
They're far more open-minded than their predecessors,
and they've outsourced experimental research to my company.
Sick.
It's pronounced psych.
Psychic Systems International Corp.
Psych.
Phil's looking into subliminal messaging.
Oh.
This is the one we designed to play to our own troops
before going into combat.
Push play on that.
There's a subliminal message in this?
This one's called
Don't Get Drunk Before Firing Heavy Machines.
We're gonna have to get rid of the machine guns.
We got all sorts of new ideas in development.
Give them one of our new ideas.
Airbag mine?
Airbag mine. Non-lethal.
Boom!
Catapult her right into the air.
Give me another one.
Uh, blast target with pheromones and then release attack bees.
Excellent.
Attack bees. The forces of nature.
Another.
Project Achilles. We mutilate enemy corpses.
No, we're not doing that one anymore, you idiot.
The point is, we got a budget, we got supporters.
I'm rebuilding the New Earth Army.
Everyone this time without all the hippie crap.
IT'S CHEYENNE
It's cheyenne-like very well, right?
Yeah.
All right.
My-my-my, now what.
I'm  expelled from the Quake Applications.
The ended result
The LK Show All Stars.