Ah, friends, you ever get a song in your head that you just can't get rid of no matter how hard you try?
And you just keep thinking about it and it just won't go away. I have some like that.
A human puppy is in the club.
A nude is club has a certain sense of moral decency.
What hypocrisy, what rampant evil and undisguised form raging like a giant monster.
Hypocrisy.
We're going to buy you a magazine.
There's got to be a certain amount of hypocrisy.
And a certain number of callers. And if you call 848-442-5128, you'll be able to talk to me.
The lower archivist of Dini Church.
I don't get much lower, friend.
Where who's talking?
Because they call 848-442-5128.
He's up there.
Northern County.
Oh
We're all sitting around in a circle and I see that they're all like waiting for something really to happen
So then my aunt grace does something to my aunt Ruby
and all of a sudden she's talking with other voices and
Tell them things that nobody else could know if they was normal
And all of a sudden Aunt Ruby points right at me and says that Aunt Grace has to give me
13 guardians to take care of
They're gonna protect me and tell me things nobody can know
It was it was strange
Everything that was going on, but I couldn't do anything about it
It was like I was tied to the chair only
There wasn't any
Holding me there
She says these guardians are the spirits of 13 of my dead ancestors. I
heard it most of them before
they were kind of
honey heroes like
Some have been hung for murder and things like that
And whenever I'm in a tight spot
They help
They really do. They're in your mind Bob
The only help they're giving you is straight to hell
Don't start talking about your
Loving words
And your loving ideas
Permanent
Bob's
Black wine
Raining
His glitter
Death lines
All of these
Don't like
X or Y
The meaning of
What works
Is what
Do this
Where we're wrapped in a
Fossil
Because of
I know what it feels like when she comes
She said never to tell about her
She doesn't even want me to talk to you
You're a
Listen to me
Try to grasp what I'm saying. She can't touch us your Bob
We're sleeping here. We have the protection of Almighty God
To listen to me
She isn't here. She doesn't exist
Look at me
I'm not scared
I'm not staying
I'll talk about it like that
You don't know her. You don't know what she can do. You don't know the power she has.
I know the power Jesus Christ has, Bob.
I know the power.
I guess it goes for a day or a night.
He doesn't know how to sing.
He doesn't know how to rock.
They speak in different languages.
Well, you know, there's a little of both.
There's a little of both.
There's a lot of one of them.
Well, dear listeners, we had a lot of calls from people who weren't expecting to hear the Hour of Slack this time of night.
And I can understand that.
You know, you tell them, what is this? What is this? Hey, hey, hey.
Well, this is the Hour of Slack.
Oh, I should have known, they keep saying.
And that's right. You should have known the second you heard it.
Well, another song now.
And this is by that group that I play way too much.
But this is a special one because this is one that's helped me out a lot this year.
Not to get too personal or anything, but when things go wrong, and they so often do,
I would just reflect upon the message of this song and feel better.
So here they are. Hope you like it.
I'll go let somebody in.
I don't know why I feel this way.
I don't know.
I don't know if it's right or wrong to laugh at this fortune.
Darkness can never last too long.
And every time I think I fall, there's nobody around to hold me up.
And it seems like the world has come to an end.
I look before my eyes and try to face this crisis.
And I don't know if it's all or nothing at all.
And every hole is a raging fire.
I try to come.
I try to fall.
But there's no way.
And next thing I know, I go down.
It doesn't matter.
It really doesn't matter.
It doesn't burn.
And I don't feel a thing.
It doesn't sting.
It doesn't hurt.
It really doesn't matter.
It doesn't burn.
And I don't feel a thing.
And when I find myself falling, and I hit the body.
It only makes me laugh.
When I go down the hall and I hit the body.
And I still met a fellow.
And love is not the honey but the mountain sour.
The woman became a monster.
And everyone I knew had become a stranger.
Then the roof went black and I loved the worst thing.
Floor opened up.
Down I went.
It doesn't hurt.
Ooh.
It really doesn't matter.
It doesn't burn.
Oh.
I don't feel a thing.
It doesn't sting.
Oh yeah.
It really doesn't matter.
It doesn't hurt.
Ooh.
I don't give a damn.
It doesn't burn.
Ooh.
It only makes me laugh.
You give me down.
Oh every time I play.
When I fall, I would die.
It doesn't matter.
If I fall, I would start fryin' that I ate.
Yeah I feel like a phase out of nowhere.
Just a little pain
Whoa, whoa, whoa, yeah
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa
Remembering when I was a young man
Everything seemed to turn against me
I didn't know solar was an alien place
The sun was covered by a dark cloud
Though I tried, I couldn't find a way to escape
The only way to go straight down
Doesn't hurt, oh, it really doesn't matter
Doesn't burn, oh, no
I don't feel a thing, no, it's the same, oh, yeah
It really doesn't matter, doesn't hurt, oh
I don't feel a thing
When I find myself falling and I hit the ground
It only makes me laugh, only makes me laugh
When I go down the hall and I hit the ground
Only makes me laugh, only makes me laugh
I don't know why I feel this way
I don't know if it's right or wrong
To laugh at misfortune
Darkness can never last too long
When you laugh in this place
Oh, yeah, when you laugh in this place
I don't know why I feel this way
I don't know if it's right or wrong
To laugh at misfortune
I don't know why I feel this way
Darkness can never last too long
When you laugh in this place
Oh, yeah, sorry.
That was Oingo Boingo with Only Makes Me Laugh.
And it does.
It only makes me laugh when I think of all the people
that are tuned in unexpectedly to this.
Oh, and they don't like it either.
They'd rather be listening to something else.
Well, you'll hate this too, then.
Paradise you try to attain.
And the wind's coming up.
Oh, there's a storm a-coming.
Hurricane Bob batting down the hatches.
Keelhaul the porthole.
I don't like the looks of that cloud there.
There's a storm a-coming.
It looks like a big pipe sticking out.
Run for the cellar!
Into the storm cellar!
Popo, Popo, where are you?
Get in the house.
Oh, my gosh, we're being carried up.
Carried away.
To a land of giants.
Oh, oh, oh.
Have some more church air.
Hmm, Bob.
Look, we landed right on that man.
Where are we?
I think it's the corner of Grundoon and Simoleon.
It's the corner of Breadbasket and...
Who is that man?
I would like to shake his hand.
He made my baby fall in love.
That's right.
We landed right on that man.
He's right on top of him.
Oh, no.
And he's still smiling.
Ping-pong the bobbits.
We spare no expense on this wonderful show to bring you the finest in audio techniques.
Why, yes, we have our one record and one speed and one turntable.
And one brain between the whole six of us in here.
But I figure that some music is better than no music.
And, uh, we, and Wellman's gotta get here eventually.
And so now let's move to the next, uh, topic on our, uh, discussion.
Um, should, uh, bicycles be allowed on the other side of the road?
That's right.
Let's, uh, open the discussion with, uh, Dr. Yagrundis Quimby, president of the Armenian
Bicycling Association and for a long time a charter member of the Velocipedes Against Racism.
Dr. Yagrundis, uh, he broke off in his bicycle.
Oh, yes, that's right.
Uh...
He had to go back to, uh, Nebraska to get a new one.
It's true.
We're not able to have Dr. Quimby speak to us directly, but perhaps by a phone hookup,
even through this terrible storm...
We can channel him.
And if we can't do that, let's go ahead and run this film.
Oh, that's not working either.
Oh, we have massive sprocket damage here.
The projector blew away in the storm.
Oh, well, the audio visual aids department...
Here, we...
Try down the...
Instead, let's play this old cassette.
Oh, that old log blew away with the cassette strapped to it.
Well, let's think of something to say.
It reminds me of...
No, there went all the words.
What can we say, friends, that hasn't been said already?
Yes, you're listening to the subgenius radio program and...
Uh, uh, uh, uh...
Sure, it's more than an hour.
And this morning, it's certainly less than a radio program.
Well, you know, we try to do what we can to bring you, the listeners,
the type of broadcasting that you especially abominate and love.
That's right.
Now, I noticed we received some mail this morning,
as I looked into the old subgenius box, and if it's not too evil and...
I'm sure I'm glad we're in this other room with a couple of pieces of shielding
between us and him opening those letters.
Oh, ignore that ticking noise.
It's just my epizootis.
I snap, you know, when my fingers are on the ground.
Okay, put the cassette on of the letter being opened.
Yes, this is from a little, uh, Elmer Quigley out in Ferndale.
Born in Brule in 1891, present place of residence Cologne, just beginning his 30th year.
A fine presence, very intelligent.
Pants not so...oh, paints not so much for art's sake as from laziness and millinery tradition.
His coloring is sometimes perforated, sometimes tubular.
His concretions are full of vestiges of plants and animals, dehumanized.
His nickname is Pointed Buttercup.
The gouty, the impotent, and the shipwrecked can always apply to him for details of the depths of the sea and the Arctic currents.
Well, uh, what's your interpretation of this, Dr. Stang?
I don't know, I'd, uh...
Oh, if I stanged through the...
Take him out and shoot him, I'd say.
Well, that's one thing that can...one thing that can be done.
Yes, that's true. If you seek him by night, he is in the light.
If you seek him by day, he is asleep.
Moral, let us not be afraid of falling into the...
He was once a little green dab of clay.
Gumby!
But you should see what Gumby can do today.
He can walk into any book with his pony pal, Pokey, too.
And he'll find fun where there's none, if you'd like him to.
And if he likes, he can change into something new.
Gumby!
He makes toys, too.
He can do things they could never do.
Gumby!
What you see is a mystery, but he makes it all come true.
If you've got a heart, then Gumby's a part of you.
Gumby!
What you have is a road in which gumby and cucaシ can aqua free natuurlijk lumor REPORT When you read the story of Keanu Reeves Partners,
you're on the right track.
You'll have so much fun today up here.
¶¶
¶ If he likes, he can change into something new. ¶¶
¶ That's Gumby. ¶¶
¶ He makes toys, do the things they could never ever do. ¶¶
¶ That's Bobby. ¶¶
¶ Yes, being green can be really keen, ¶¶
¶ especially when you are blue. ¶¶
¶ So if you've got a heart, then Gumby's a part of you. ¶¶
¶ If you've got a heart, then Gumby's, ¶¶
¶ Gumby's a part of you. ¶¶
A theme from Gumby by Frank Sinatra, Jr.
And it's just a CD they just happen to have sitting around here at the station.
That's the kind of thing you often hear when you've got two hours to fill.
¶¶
¶¶ ¶¶
¶¶ ¶¶ables ¶¶¶¶
Is that the kind of message that we're hearing?
It's just a question of faith.
I don't know.
Can we all say...
I think we should all believe in a flow of love.
Instead of B-O-B, maybe F-O-O-V.
A crying child became a gallon.
The infant child was snatched away from mom to him.
He was becoming a pigeon.
You know, there's so many stories.
It's hard to tell which one of the two.
I suppose one of them is the best.
You know, the one that only the one who knew.
It's not the one.
Everybody loves King Corkus.
But who is B-O-B?
Who is Bob?
Did you ever stop to think for a second that Bob spoke backwards?
Bob?
I think that's very interesting.
I think that probably compared to McWally.
It's easy to see why.
Why did Bob get some of his faces as a music agent?
Obviously, it's because he's a castaneta.
Yeah!
I'm famous.
I'm a man who's got a man who's established himself.
I'm a man who's got the juiciest joke.
I'm a man who's got the manual!
Woo!
To touch the eternal.
To understand the mysterious.
To find out who we are.
It sometimes takes several hours to get a word out.
Meaning for life.
I don't judge.
I'm a gentle nature.
The game is only just the answer.
You listen to the answer.
You're alive.
so that the life-spirits of Omni will have resonance within,
that are those of our own inmost being and reality,
and so that we actually feel the rapture of being alive.
That's what it's all finally about,
and that's what these clues help us to find within ourselves.
Myths are clues to the spiritual potentialities of the human life,
what we're capable of knowing within and experiencing within.
I'd like you to change the definition of the myth
from the search for meaning to the experience of meaning.
Yes, and Joseph Campbell changed that definition even later.
It wasn't even experiencing the myth.
It was experiencing that man.
That man, I've had to explain him to a lot of people.
A lot of new, either new listeners or, you know, one-time listeners,
and this may be the only time, but they want, who is Bob?
Well, I hope you know by now.
But if you don't know, well, what's my theme here?
I didn't understand it at all.
What's he doing? What's the message? What's he trying to say?
I heard this so many times tonight.
That's the message, that he's not trying to say it.
And that's what I told them all.
That's my theme.
Will's theme.
What was the theme of the show?
You got me.
We always figure the theme out when we're listening to him later.
Well, gentle listeners,
and those of you who'd rather be listening to someone else right now,
tonight you've been listening to the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hours of Slack.
We did two of them tonight.
We made it through virtually unscathed here at the radio station.
Apparently, we scathed a few people out there in the listening audience,
which is apparently a lot bigger than it used to be.
We got a real nice call from Arlington, as a matter of fact,
and we don't get a lot from there.
So, for all of you who have never listened to the show before
and just happened to catch it tonight by accident,
what an accident it was,
I hope that your appetite has been whetted,
or if nothing else has been whetted,
I hope your appetite at least was whetted tonight
for more of this kind of stuff.
And believe me, there is more of this kind of stuff.
More than we could even begin to...
I don't even have time to tell you all about the Stark Fist of Removal
or Book of the Subgenius or Three Fisted Tales of Bob
or High Weirdness by Mail or Bob's Favorite Comics
or Arise, the Subgenius video, the movie.
I just don't...
I don't have time.
Nowhere near.
There's only four minutes left.
But if you want to find out a whole lot about
the Church of the Subgenius
and that man, J.R. Bob Dobbs,
there he is
on camera two.
Bring it up, okay.
And fade to...
two.
No, no, no, no.
Close up, zoom in.
Ah, there he is.
If you could just see his face,
those of you who spent the money,
you can see his face.
Nope, nope, no.
Well, he's gone.
That's Bobby for you.
If there's anything else about him you want to know,
I think it's been a fairly self-explanatory show tonight,
as they all are, really.
But if there's anything else you want to know,
feel free to write to the RPO box
and we'll send you some free information.
Every bit as free as the radio show you've been listening to.
Except it's not free, friends.
How about those pledges, huh?
Get them things.
And some of you have.
I'm happy to say.
And those of you that pledged your $60,
we've got the videos in as of today.
So those of you who pledged $60 and over,
we're going to be sending those videos out to you real soon.
And if you haven't paid that $60 or more or less pledge,
get it now, man, because we got the videos.
And if you want to pledge now,
if maybe you weren't listening to Pledge Drive Night,
if you will pledge $60 or more to this show,
we will send you a copy of Arise, the subgenius video,
the movie, a pristine cherry copy.
So be aware.
Oh, and that address.
Write to Bob at P.O. Box 140306 in Dallas, Texas.
And the zip code is 75214.
I may have said that too fast for some of you.
Please write to Bob at P.O. Box 140306 in Dallas, Texas.
And the zip code is 75214.
Thanks a lot for listening tonight, friends.
Hope you enjoyed at least some of the two hours.
I enjoyed just about all of it.
So thanks a lot.
Stay tuned to KNON for an excellent show or a cart.
Yeah, stay tuned for the cart,
which following the cart will be a fine show.
So thanks a lot.
Praise Bob.
His promise rings true.
Thank you.
© BF-WATCH TV 2021
forever tell me where my friends go i join the shadow dreams together tell me where my friends
go i try upon the disbelievers tell me where my friends go i'm scared of them into the sea
tell me where my friends go when winter comes i'll keep on moving tell me where my friends go
to build a couple of this night tell me where my friends go
tell me where my friends go
my hesitation is strong today the indications of what the way
to something better for everyone
there's
something
i'll follow you until i die tell me where my dreams go
with that stretch dance into the sky tell me where my dreams go
when all is said and done i'll follow you until i die tell me where my friends go
i sit and chime and gun tell me where my formalities
will your Columbus
my
home
the
well
know
my
An hundred men behind the faces
Well, bark at night and wake the neighbors
And tell the world about adventure
My hesitation is strong today
The indications all point the way
To something better for everyone
Everyone has something gonna break
My revelations have lost control
My better judgment
Has been broken
And it's not the way
Our revolution is full of holes
And has something gonna destroy
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Tell me where my friends go
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah From where different for darkness
Tell me where my friends go
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah