🎵
Genuinely beautiful.
Giant.
Perfect.
Cool.
Special.
Cheered.
Elaborate.
Easy.
Ultimate.
Best.
Natural.
Growing.
Special.
Nice.
Quicker.
And much more.
Ah, yes, dear friends, it is rerun time again, but you'll be glad to know that we're not
going to just do the same old three Christmas hour of slack show reruns in a row.
No, I'm going to compress it all into just this one intensive total rerun show, except
that actually it's not.
The whole first half will be largely peppered with a new Christmas sickness for the holidays
and holy days and the hole-in-head days, as it is for some people.
Actually, I have to work double time because it's the season of salad.
Selling.
Yes.
Oh, you wouldn't believe what the elves have done over at the subgenius catalogs.
But anyway, happy whatever you do.
Yes, this music in the background is somebody named Kenny Wayne Shepard.
Yeah, there's an album called Merry Axmus and Guitar Axmus.
It's cool, man.
Cool.
And praise Bob and the whole world.
Oh.
I'd like to find the guy who done me wrong and stuck my butt up on this Christmas tree.
That's the English translation of the lyrics for our Q&A and it was 같아요 .
I really enjoyed this song because it caught you walkingcio specifically into this panorama
Ch Baldur Du B father.
This is my don't have to be a student to go Bilbao7 face slop eBay.
My mom does because that has outside of myives angle, vnity and turtleneye are real.
I don't know that my mom is shit, but that really is why I posted this diary on Instagram
as well, because I remembered to say hat and his best friend who's entire break in the
country.
And left me stranded on this Christmas tree
When this angel heard
A dreadful fear went right into my heart
Those pine tree needles sting me
Ram-a-jam-a, ram-a-jam-a, ram-a-ding-dong
You'll never know how much that smarts
So who put the stump in my romp-a-bomp-a-bomp
Who took and jammed it in my ram-a-lam-a-ding-dong
Who stood the wood where I boop-sheep-boop-sheep-boop
Who put the stick up my hip-a-dip-a-dip
Who took that bush and crammed it in my tush
He made this angel beg for mercy, please
Too tight, too tight
And I'm gonna say to you
It's already 9 p.m.
Don't go looking out in the backyard to dog-aid him
Don't go walking down to the bar
Cause old Frankie died last night in the backyard
I mean, I'm gonna park my store and look at the credits
And in the right
Oh, can I borrow the brain cells tonight?
Yeah, he brought back the chainsaw, yeah
And I ain't gonna let you use the brain cells
Till I get to bed
I have chainsaw fixed and back in my arm the way it was Tuesday
Now you boys be good and I'll give you some of this here
Apple mango pie
You ain't no good of a child
That dog's running off with them brain cells
Can you do something about that, boy?
I'm gonna have to, I'm gonna have to
It could be his head wasn't screwed on just right
No!
But still possible king
And this is my christmasness
Christmas
Where do you get them?
Oh my god!
Christmas
Dave's dressed like Santa Claus.
He's like a cowboy Santa.
How jolly.
Oh, Jazz is giving,
gives Dave the show pills.
Boy, I really need one of those.
What am I going to do about Laundromat and his suit, though?
I need the show bath.
The show de-lousing.
Oh, Dave doesn't even have headphones.
That's enough of that.
Oh, he's got headphones.
I also have the part of my pancreas
that I'd like to show you now.
It's been increased in size to...
Oh, your pancreas looks lovely, Dave.
Look, it's swelling.
I actually have the capability of a man
with 190 IQ's brain.
I'll put more pills out for everybody.
Oh, those pills.
They make my mouth feel like it's on fire.
And my brain feel like it's a puddle
of liquefied crap.
I'm shocked by the...
The red pills are really good.
I like to take the red one and the blue one
at the same time.
That way you go in and out.
The warp mix is easy.
It's so high, you can't go over it.
Angels we have heard on high
Singing about mountains
And those mountains in reply
Sing about mountains in reply
Like then we wish we had some too
Who are you?
Oh oh oh oh ooh
Oh oh, a warrior
In excelsis deo
Oh oh oh ooh
Oh, a warrior
In excelsis deo
Sam's Cr Heidi
to Your Boyfriend
and to every artist
before y'all
ever get anywhere
saUT
the X
Barbie Dolls
Women rape and memorialize their lives by role-playing with Barbie.
We have devised a marketing scheme for children's toys.
It will empower this resistance.
You will use your church as a vehicle to bring these toys before the power.
It will be a baller for kids.
But how will the battle of good against evil be represented in your marketing schemes, human?
Good has lots of muscles.
Good. Good!
The primitive Earth societies should accept this value judgment.
Good will have great physical attributes according to human desires.
Sexual desires.
Latent in children.
Brought out through the vehicle of this so-called farmacle.
This place is a church.
Better is not good.
She's new. From Kenner.
Where illusion is the ultimate weapon.
We must buy our toys!
Uh, yes.
Uh.
The old subject.
Genius toy marketing scheme.
Uh, recorded there at Dockstock 1984.
And me and Palmer Veedies.
Um, Angels We Have Heard on High.
It was by the Philistines.
Uh, the collage called All the Money You've Got is from the great Obtuse Christmas collage album,
which you can get for free.
Get this, um, check out this website, obtuse.iu.com.
I-M-A dot com.
That's obtuse.
Excuse me.
Ah, yes.
And next up, The Real Story of Christmas by Michael Shelley.
Uh.
Once upon a time, there was the baby Jesus.
And he had two eyes made out of coal.
And he was stuck up a partridge in a pear tree.
And he wanted his two front teeth.
And he got McDonald's gift certificates.
And he had a dog named Santa's little helper.
And he took all the presents from Whoville.
And his friend Yukon Cornelius came with the three wise guys.
And he wanted to play the drums and be the little drummer boy.
But he couldn't.
He wanted tens and twenties.
Tens and twenties.
And he's, and he, he got McDonald's gift certificates.
And he got Zuzu's pedals.
And that's the real story of Christmas.
Iml poss 거죠 to say hi.
Huguett Basqu'il says주세요 onӚ
Thank you.
Da-da-da-da-da, da-da-da-da
So separate, so separate, so separate
You from Tunker
Now you are in my evil clutches, Bob
I'll use this MTV bombardment to turn you normal
Shut up, pink boy!
No way, I'll never sell out to the conspiracy
Taste a little of my rocket pipe, alien tool
Bob Dobbs comes with rocket pipe, head launcher, jayner device, all your cockatism
A fightin' Jesus and other action figures sold separately
Some assembly required, batteries not included
This toy falls apart in three days
He-Bob and the bastards of the universe
Too much is always better than not enough
From Bob Dobbs
Gorgeous secrets can blow from head to toe
Drawing everything you see here
Ken Dowsell separately
He-Bob and the bastards of the universe will be back after this message
Santa Claus
Well, Tommy knew exactly what he wanted for Christmas
He wanted an electric train
He had the whole thing on his mind, even to the table where it was going to set it up
Santa Claus
He would dream so hard that the whole thing would come to life right before his eyes
Of course, Tommy was a pretty strong wisher
And what he started wishing for was a pretty fancy looking train set with locomotives and freight cars.
The station and the gateman.
The mortar tower and all the kinds of wonderful equipment and accessories.
So grand that you might think Tommy was waiting for something that just didn't exist.
But Tommy knew what he was wishing for.
It is turnover.
The time of the year when all things sell.
The end of the year sale.
So come and get it everyone and just buy our products.
I'm a little confused about what Christmas is all about.
Are we celebrating the day?
Birth of Santa Claus or his death when they nailed him?
Well that's the ancient, ancient subgenie.
But the present subgenie try to make sure that we have our inventories cleared by now.
And sell everything to the pigs.
Oh yes.
Once a pagan holiday and now a shopping season.
And it was something else in between there.
Before it was, after it was a pagan holiday and before it was a shopping season.
It was something else.
But I think he started.
He started a war over it.
Yeah.
And I've had extra sense
I've had extra sense
I've done my seems
I've done my sensory
Slides laser
It's my first time
Who's the head man?
Santa Claus
He was a huge beastly
bulging man
He was so real
How come we didn't get squat last year?
Yes, the birth of the baby Satan
on
July 4th
And now you can have it all
pure 100% vinyl
chloride CID
The birth of our baby Satan
as told by various authors
and eclectic scholars from around
the globular unit
including that announcer
This announcement has not been a perfunctory
announcement, an announcement of the
blessed anointment and birthday
of our Lord
Zeus
Praises
for
one
bright Christmas morning
was born
in a cradle
to a rich man's family
Oh, I know the rave Jesus
I'm part with the rave Jesus
Have yourself
a merry little Christmas
Merry little Christmaaaace
Let your sight
be light
from the harder
troubles
will be
out of sight
Ha
Have
yourself
a merry little
yu
s
o v
h
from now onien g
On a miles away
Once a day as in olden
Say happy golden
Be miles apart
Let your heart
Be out of sight
Out of sight
The Jackson Five
Wish everybody
A crystal merry Christmas
And a gloopy gloopy day
From Mutated Christmas, friends,
the Have Yourself a Merry Little Christmas by No-L.
No-L.
Before that, some year old ESO and Michael Shelley did that real story of Christmas
from the Tarkin Records All-Star Holiday Extravaganza.
I'm playing a lot from that.
So check out www.triage.com for that one also.
The Tarkin Records is also on www.triage.com.
And now, the Jethro's.
1, 2, 3, 4.
Go!
.
. .
. . . . .
. . . . . . .
. . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . .
. . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . .
Redrum, Stang.
The Weirbobs and Ima,
those who have the psychosis that convinces them
that they are the Santa Bob.
Or that they're Santa Bob by night.
And they go shuffling through the snow
on their nameless, hideous errands.
The grin of Bob and the beard of Santa Claus
and the pipe of the Lord stuck on their face.
They stop using the locks of their doors
and they just kind of float into the keyhole.
Oh, friends, it's tough.
And, you know, just going to church ain't enough.
You gotta send your money to the Santa Bob.
As a matter of fact, the people across the street from me
told their kids that Santa Claus
bills them for the toys he brings.
Can you believe that?
The kids were asking if their parents,
maybe Santa Claus will bring us two He-Man erector sets.
And the mom said, no, no, he won't
because he bills us.
We can't afford that.
Santa Claus sends us a bill after Christmas.
Yeah, but at least he totes the note.
Let's see.
Oh.
Oh, boy, too.
And, uh, amazing.
More from Corporal Blossom.
I am really impressed by their editing work.
And that's on...
Corporal Blossom and the Mutated Christmas is on the Illegal Art label.
That's www.detritus.net
slash illegal art.
www.detritus.net
And now, more Jethro's.
Now you're blaming Jesus.
You're blaming our Lord.
I sort of understand because...
I understood the way any old fool would understand.
There was no Jesus.
No flatulent old woman waving her panties on the hill.
It's not that you don't want to.
It's that they won't let you.
No, there's just a crime in wilderness.
They're ashamed.
And the hot pursuit of wolves everywhere in the back.
I'm ashamed of them.
It's cold.
I'm leaving that city life behind.
I can't get my finger off the paper.
I can't get my noodle back in the pan, Jen.
Come on, cowboy.
No, man.
I was trying to hear a can against this here tree.
And it started whispering to me, man.
Oh, you've been drinking.
There's the face of Madonna right up there.
There's the face of Virgin Mary.
I swear to God, look at it.
Isn't it?
What?
It's her.
It's your Christmas witch coming true.
It is.
A Christmas witch?
I'll be whole.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, I guess it does look a little bit more witchy than angelic.
I know she must be a true witch.
I guess you could call her that if that's what she's talking about.
She's for real.
She's running by hovering Christmas ornaments.
It looks like a radar device.
What?
Yo.
Yo?
It's her.
What up?
Nothing.
What's up?
What a deep voice.
First Christmas witch.
Grrr.
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
Ha, ha, ha.
Grrr.
Thank you.
It was.
flying Coca-Cola drinking Christmas,
not a crack-smoking, rubber-snapping Christmas.
It was a...
When your little brother fell through a hole in the ice sling,
and you went and saved him,
you didn't laugh at him and huff some more glue.
It was a wonderful life back then.
I remember when Uncle Bud would come in with the candles,
like most people have.
And he would have that smile on his face.
But today, Christmas has lost its meaning.
Scott, you made your choice.
When you rejected my word, you rejected me.
And to your eternal soul,
you have found that only could you afford
to give to God that which was his.
But you could not afford to do otherwise.
The Senate still stands.
Into outer darkness,
where there is wailing and gnashing of teeth.
Sir, please give me just one more chance, sir.
I don't want to go to hell, sir!
Sir, no!
I don't want to go to hell!
No!
An Innocent Men Defer Jordan
Asklaş
Strange lights appear in the skies all over the world.
The wife of a carpenter experiences virgin birth and a baby is born with a head that
glows like a fluorescent lamp.
Dare I ask it?
Yes.
Was the infant Jesus neither man nor God, but merely one of the countless aliens that
visit the earth each and every day?
The answer?
Yes, definitely.
Take that and shove it up the tube mark certainty in the fuzzy place called the Twilight Zone.
Merry Christmas to all, now you're all gonna die!
The night Santa went crazy, the night Saint Nick went insane.
Realized he'd been getting the wrong heel, something finally must have snapped in his
brain.
Well the workshop is gone now, he decided to vomit.
Everywhere you'll find pieces of Cupid and Comet.
And he tied up his helpers, and he held the elves hostage.
And he ground up poor Rudolph into reindeer sausage.
He got dancer and prancer with an old German Luger.
And he slashed up Dasher just like Freddy Krueger.
And he picked up a flamethrower and a barbecue glitzen.
And he took a big bite and said it tastes just like chicken.
The night Santa went crazy, the night Santa went insane.
This grain go and done, now you can't hardly walk around the North Pole without stepping
in reindeer guts.
There's the National Guard and the FBI.
There's a van from the eyewitness noose.
And helicopters circling round in the sky.
And the bullets are flying, the body counts rising, and everyone gets gotten out.
Everyone's dying to know her Santa wife
My, my, my, my, my, my
You used to be such a jolly guy
So be good, for goodness sake
You better watch out
You better not cry
You better not pout
I'm telling you why
Santa Claus is coming to town
Have yourself an advanced dogmatic brain
Who gave the Lord the Claptrap?
Who made him talk in funny riddles so that we cannot understand?
Who made him so succinct and blind that he is actually blind?
My one good little thing
Yeah, we're now officially in the Jesus season
The time of the Lord
How many before you reach your limit?
Jesus season
Jesuses?
Yeah, how many can you bag?
How many messiahs can you bag?
Hail Jesuses
If you're doing it in season
If you're doing it out of season, you need a special permit
Oh, you never do that
And you can only take one
You never bag the Lord in C, you bag the Lord in B-flat so you get that kind of rough sound
But when they're in season, it's every god for himself
This is the season for the fighting Jesus, obviously
We are between a rock and a hard place
Did you know the Lord walked through Chaldea in the old age and he got a very, very hard foot?
And he got elephantiasis of the rectum
You know, it's not something well known by many Christian scholars
Messy, messy, messy disease
But I think the phrase in Hebrew was
Well, I like the story
I kind of like those stories where the Lord dies and then comes here to America and settles, you know, tames the West
I like when he moves into a trailer park and cowboys walk with his dog
Jesus!
Jesus fought for the Confederate Army
The Ranger, I like the Texas Ranger
Jesus, Texas Ranger
Johnny River was a Jesus
I could see Jesus for the Navajo police, for maybe the Hopi police force
Billy Jack was the Indian Jesus
Man
The white brother who came to instruct the Indians how to be liberal
Well, what about old peacemaker, the Jesus of the Iroquois who was actually Huron, a Huron
You didn't know that, did you?
I got you!
Thin rye
Jesus!
Elrond
I got a Jesus like no other Jesus you've ever seen
Oh, it tastes like butter
A new Jesus, a different Jesus
It tastes like crappie
A future Jesus
A pipe-smoking Jesus
Hey, Dave, you know where it is
Go kick that window open
I already kicked it, I'll kick it again, though
Kick it good this time
We don't mean nothing by this Jesus and God
We hope that we thank you for all the nice things that you've done for us this Thanksgiving
We appreciate all that and we're just trying to insult your fan club
That's all, that's why we do this blasphemous stuff
But we knew that you knew that because you're in all things and everything, right, Jesus?
Right, I could hear him say that
Praise God and Bob and Jesus
Next topic, terrorist insurance
Could you see Jesus as a terrorist?
And science
Well, that's the life of Brian, isn't it?
And Greek mythology and Norse mythology
Listen to the sounds of hell
Jingle, jangle, jingle, we're on a sleigh ride to heck
Santa and his reindeer are really wicked
Wrapped in wrapping paper
We're gonna break our necks
Gotta rock it!
Put in my pocket on a sleigh ride to heck
Sleigh ride to heck
The elves are full of cheer
The kids are tucked in bed
Santa ain't coming
We're on a sleigh ride to heck
Their dreams are filled with toys
But they're out of luck
Cause Satan's taking Santa on a sleigh ride to f**k
Sleigh ride to heck
Santain this sleigh ride
Santa is administering notices
Santa shows off his supreme gift
But army ends in a row
Santa is in a clean crew
Santa is grateful
Schön broughtazz
only can accept somebody making fun of Bob, stomping on a picture of Bob, he'll do it himself.
He has so much trust and faith in Bob. Bob is such a good friend that he can insult Bob. Now,
we subgeni, I hate to get on my soapbox in the middle of a bunch of entertaining tapes, but we
subgeni may be bad, but our way of bad is holy, is holy compared to the evil of so, not all,
by any means, but so many American fundamentalists, charismatics, evangelicals,
et cetera, in general, of course, they and their corresponding types in Iran, Russia, Libya,
South Africa, et cetera, if you ask me, are actually the ace up the devil's sleeve.
Wolves in sheep's clothing, friends, just like Jesus warned about. Jesus and Bob, like we say,
our old drinking buddies, got nothing against Jesus. It's just his fan club,
now, we aren't saying that Bob is the ace up God's sleeve, he's more like the smear on God's
handkerchief, just like you or me, but the uptight rival cults, they don't think God has a handkerchief,
uh-uh, no, because God's perfect. He doesn't even sneeze. We're made in his image, except that we
have all these nasty parts attached to us, and we have to go in the secret room, the bathroom,
to do awful things, but God, oh, he's clean and pure.
According to them, oh, and he's male, but he doesn't excrete juices and sweat and smelly stuff
out of him like we do, because we sin, oh yeah, we all sin, we're bad, we're worthless, we're no
good to God, unless we sign a contract with his agent. We interrupt this program for a special
promotional announcement. We turn. He-Bob and the bastards of the universe will be back after this
message.
You
Overconfident, I've spent
Just like the ones I used to know
I'm going to stop smoking
And it should be the same
To be a man that's in the snow
I'm going to stop smoking
Dreaming about the days you don't spend
When everyone can't find my life
Make your days be
Short and short
And they all will be your
Dumbstant new lives
By Fernanda Nande-Lemar
Oh, holy night
The stars are brightly shining
It is the night of our dear Savior's birth
Long lay, long lay the world
In danger and refining
The pit and the stone on its way
A thrill of hope
The weary world rejoices
Beyond the grace
A new and glorious dawn
Fall
Fall on your knees
Oh, hear the angel voices
Oh, night divine
Oh, night when Christ was born
Oh, night, oh, night divine
Have yourselves
A groovy little solstice
Nithros won you spite
Ho, ho, ho
Come on, come on
It's He-Bob
Hey kids, you can help the mighty
So Genus Rice
Overthrow the evil normals
With new Bob Dobbs action figure
With rocket pie
What I wouldn't do for Bob Dobbs
Get no more chocolatey pebbles from you
No, no
Buy my chocolate spice cadet
Life support system down to zero cocoa
I have some of my new cocoa pimples now so trumpety.
Mmm, smells coconut-ish.
This cocoa liquid is...
Blow.
Well, friends, what do you think?
Is it the nativity of Santa Claus that we're trying to celebrate here?
Or is it the horrible death of the Santa Bob, the Santai Bob,
as he's been referred to in some early pre-scriptures?
The Jethro's.
Friends, you need to know where to write to the Jethro's.
They're at...
They did that Wreck the Halls and so many other versions we've been playing.
The Jethro's are at 212 and a half Miller Avenue.
That's 212 and a half Miller Avenue.
Portsmouth.
New Hampshire.
Portsmouth N.H.
O-3-8-O-1.
Santa Claus is Coming to Town was by Corporal Blossom.
Information on that mutant Christmas is available from www.triagemusic.com
or www.detritus.net
slash illegal art.
I'm Reverend Ivan Stang.
Friends, you can reach me, send me tapes or whatnot at
Post Office Box 181417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
And friends, as always, the Hour of Slack is brought to you by
the Church of the Subgenius.
www.subgenius.com
It's all Christmassy right now.
There's a bright green bob in the window.
And a...
Is there a light out there?
And Christmassy lights.
Is there a DJA?
Is DJA out there?
And devilish artwork that's Christmassy.
No, that's something just left for DJA.
It's all Christmassy.
It's all wrapped up in a perfumed ribbon-wrapped present.
Under the tree.
Smell that cinnamon.
Open the door all the way so we can see if he comes in.
And the sugar plums.
Something's up the chimney hole in Satan's name.
Yeah.
Of Santa, I mean.
Otherwise.
Gosh.
I guess we have to wait till Santa comes, Dave.
Oh, beloved Santa.
I have wanted to put your bag down for a minute.
Besides, I'm so ready to let him be.
What?
For so long.
Hi, Bob and Mary Xmas!
Lone cow babe, don't you know what they're doing to yourself?
Don't despair, just because it's Christmas Children there are so gay at Christmas
All the children on the street Hope they get something good to eat
But for me it's not so great
Fuck Christmas!
Merry fucking Christmas Merry fucking Christmas
Merry fucking Christmas
SHOW YOU!
Merry fucking Christmas!
Merry fucking Christmas Merry fucking Christmas
Merry fucking Christmas
Merry deixar eu saber
Merry Crowd
Merryogen
Merryogogogogo
Merryo
Merryaren
Merryogogogoggogogogogo
Merry your fucking Sim, Merryogogogogogogogo
Merryogogogogogogogogogogogogogogogogogogogogogogogo
Merryo
Thank you.