The Final Frontier
These are the enterprise of the subgenius Voyage.
Its thousand year mission? To explore stange new worlds, to seek out and destroy new civilizations, to boldly go where Bob has gone before.
No.
Why do we have to wait for aliens?
1, 3, 0, 1, 3.
And now, the subgenius hour of SWAC.
Amazing, powerful, simple, quiet, low profile, lightweight.
Had nothing to do with the subgenius.
High performance, wall hugging, convenient, built in, high capacity, cordless, articulating, easy, swivel action, handheld, dust spewing.
Bob?
It's alive.
It's alive. It's alive.
In the name of God.
Now I know what it feels like to be God.
Henry is well, but he's very busy.
Friends, this is going to be an X Day show.
Yes, because X Day is approaching.
July 5th of 1998.
That will be the real X Day when it arrives.
But we celebrate X Day and we drill for the end of the world every year on July 5th.
This year, which the conspiracy claims is the year 2003.
We will be doing that.
And, you know, for those of you who don't understand our religion, it's this simple.
For those who sent 30 bucks to J.R. Bob Dobbs at that Texas post office box or check in, well, whatever.
Those who are saved and justified in that man Bob, they will be on that mighty date.
Lifted up.
Ruptured, as we call it, up into the escape vessels of the sex goddesses from Planet X.
There to live forever.
Forever.
Until they die.
And then they go to subgenius heaven, which goes on forever and ever and ever, too.
And, friends, it's a beautiful story.
And it's all coming true for those who believe.
Anything is possible for those who believe.
And every day is X Day when you have a gun.
Praise Bob.
Men and women of all races and creeds pause to destroy the earth.
Bob.
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
Bob!
What's that?
Right on goes the music.
From now on, it also has monitored reptiles, mammals, cats, snakes, dogs, a-borigines,
birds, super lizards, culture, to achieve financial independence.
Well, I've, waited so long, for this, day to come.
You will have to give the man a little help.
I don't know who they are or where they come from
But I know I've been chosen, must be one of the few
Only first class on the mothership will do
I've seen them saucers sliding, baby, up in the air
And I know what they mean, I know the end is near
So I'll climb the silver staircase and I'll find link with the crew
Only first class on the mothership will do
We're going light speed out to space
We're the last hope for the human race
A little green fly to take us directly in
The spears and peanuts of the first class on the mothership will do
There'll be nothing to want, there'll be nothing to need me watching
Grand Ole Opry and Hee Haw in 3D
Laying horseshoes on the holodeck, eat roast beef from a tube
Only first class on the mothership will do
We're going light speed out to space
We're the last hope for the human race
A little green fly to take us directly in
The spears and peanuts of the first class on the mothership will do
First Class on the Mothership will do
We're going home, going home
On the saucer, get on board
Singing praises, Hallelujah to the Lord
Praise the Lord
I'm so glad that I've been chosen
For to start my life anew
Only First Class on the Mothership will do
If you'd fly with me, baby
We'd make a cosmic team
Like Tammy and George Jones
Or Adam and Eve
Flying past the rings of Saturn
Have a winder with you
Flying First Class on the Mothership with you
We're going life speed out through space
We're the last hope for the human race
Little green flight attendants
Bring the anguished pears and peanuts
Up to First Class on the Mothership will do
We're going home, going home
On the saucer, get on board
Singing praises, Hallelujah to the Lord
Praise the Lord
I'm so glad that I've been chosen
For to start my life anew
Only First Class on the Mothership will do
Music
First Class on the Mothership
By Hank Floyd and the Swerving Headlights
Uh, sorry, it sounded sort of like tank flies.
And the Swerving Headlights
From their CD, Interstellar Cattle Drive
And you can find out more about that from www.swervingheadlights.com
More of them coming up
All of the surrounding collages are by
The great artiste, Fernande Lemaire
Uh, yes, yes, yes, friends
Uh, uh, we're going to...
To Planet X with Lemaire this time
We do know how to get on the Mothership
And we do know which aliens to go with
And we did get our First Class tickets already
From that man, J.R. Bob Dobbs
And it's so easy
Ooh
It just feels good
Isn't that the moose?
And you're an attractive woman
You're single
And you probably have a normal outlook
On matters of sexual freedom
And if that's so, friends
You won't want to miss
as S-X-X-X-X Day 6.
Sick Sex Day.
You don't want to miss the saucers.
You don't want to miss the coming revolution,
as heard here by the jelly eaters.
This is the hour.
The coming revolution.
Michigan and California, the spawning grounds for the revolutionary activities.
The White Panthers headquarters in Ann Arbor.
This is the hour.
The coming revolution.
Students for a democratic society.
The White Panthers.
SDS class is seen.
We better do it now.
This is the hour.
The coming revolution.
Every high school and college in the country will close with riots and sabotage.
Millions of young people will surge into the streets of every city.
Dancing, singing, smoking pot, and having sexual intercourse.
And of course,
Bob Hope said,
Oh, just some college kids having fun.
This is the hour.
The coming revolution.
Our program is cultural revolution through a total assault on the culture which makes use of every tool, every energy, every media we can get our hands on.
Our message is one, and that is freedom.
For the first time in America,
we have a generation of visionary,
mania,
white mother,
country,
dope,
being rock and roll freaks,
who are ready to kick out the jams,
all the jams.
This is the hour.
The coming revolution.
The program of total freedom for everyone.
We are totally committed to carrying out our program.
We breathe revolution.
We are LSD driven maniacs in the universe.
We'll do anything we can to drive people crazy out of their heads into their bodies.
This is the hour.
The coming revolution.
We're getting out of the streets.
Thanks, todo.
It's fight or die time,
Check out my dress code PianosOil expensive programming and büydingumbled i estudian
question
do you have a gun in your pocket?
Colin's got the control over my campuses.
So,
yes,
I was preaching the word of Satan, deceiving my congregation.
I tried to get a concept of who's the Jesus me, the, the.
I tried to get a big brain.
Who's Jesus me Christ.
The word of Jesus me, the, the, the, the, the.
That's fascinating.
Would it be okay if Gilbert spent the night?
I ask him simply to consider this.
Submit evidence to review and get this matter settled.
We don't rule out anything at all.
Thanks a lot, Mom.
Their sympathies may lie in the wrong area, but, uh...
Well, yeah, they don't need me.
They still got my sister to push around while I'm away.
Yeah.
So the job of the government is surely to take all necessary steps
to safeguard the public regardless of the sensibilities of a striking union.
I ask the Prime Minister simply this.
I can get out of this satellite contract at any time, right?
Yes, I guess so.
We understand the issues that they have.
Golly, beep.
The reality is that the Deputy Prime Minister and the Prime Minister
will mislead all of those who are in the same boat.
And it's worth remembering that when the Green Goddesses were last used,
they were only 20 years old.
I didn't think it was gonna happen so quick.
Me neither.
There must be no...
Have you noticed the difference in my eye?
It's gooey.
Yes, and it has a little slit instead of a cornea.
Oh, my God.
I can see behind my own head when I'm walking forward.
Well, good.
Disgusting.
Whether they see me, they will need a little bit more time.
I think when I see them, it will be too late.
It's always too late, Dave.
Especially if you're on the wrong page.
It's too late if you're late for X-Day 1998.
That's right.
This July 5th, 1998.
Whenever that may be.
X-Day will happen.
The following members of...
The Nationalist League have been banned from production,
been found guilty,
or social humanism traces in their urine and mine.
Oops.
I've been kind of hoping that X-Day would come along and rupture us
before July 5th of this year when we have our big party.
I mean, it'll be a great party, but...
The wounded coming back.
The stompers.
You know, the guys in the front row going,
ooh, bop, bop.
They have one hand, you know, and you feel so sorry.
It's hard to make them laugh.
It's hard to preach to a room full of one-armed people.
I know.
I know that's true.
I've tried to do it.
It's hard.
Back in the now.
To get a good laugh out of an amputado.
But sometimes they're more than willing to laugh
just because of the awful, terrible sights they've seen.
You develop a great sense of humor when you've been mangled and traumatized.
You've seen Rumsfeld from the rear side, so to speak.
Or get kind of, you know, generally depressed all the time.
Yeah, there's feelings of nausea, I guess, blistering of the skin,
viruses that can connect you with your family genealogy.
I'm not going to take that ride.
No, I'm not going.
Dr. Pavlov, Steng is doing well.
But you know, who is to say that disease is not a gift,
a natural change in consciousness
designed to teach us?
Pain and agony.
So we learn the lesson of senseless hurt.
Whatever that lesson is.
Which is the lesson of life.
It hasn't stopped, so evidently I haven't learned that lesson.
There is pain and suffering.
Indemnitably, there is rubbing of the genital areas
and some short intercalations
and then back to the suffering mind.
Digging for gold and salt.
And copper and iron.
And little tools to make the aliens return.
Is that all there is, though, Dr. Day?
There must be more.
There has to be.
Surely we're not just little pain balls aching in a void.
It's the way Bob found us
and the way he likes to take us under his armpit
and gently stroke those pains away.
He is a man who is more than a common man.
He is a man who is imbued with the powers
of powerful aliens themselves
who have returned to Earth
to give a message to mankind.
And Bob J.R. Bob Dobbs
is the allocutor of that ma...
ma...
7 a.m. July 5th.
One of these years.
The saved,
that is, those who have proven their love
30 bucks worth to J.R. Bob Dobbs,
will be lifted up,
ruptured up into the escape vessels of the sex goddesses
there to swim in an ocean of snot.
A headache that lasts all year.
And sex with sinuses and just slimy nasal passages
beyond the kind of madness
that is the life of a man.
Or his sister.
It's not a fixation.
His mind has become a fixed.
And that is new and it's in the past.
He can feel now
where his diaphragm is racing slowly.
There won't be too much problem from now on.
As long as we can keep him breathing steadily
and evacuate fluids.
He's waiting for a day that may never come.
He's waiting for the day that has already come and gone.
Now I'm waiting for another bottle of Robitussin.
Don't worry, my friend.
All of your earthy problems will be rolled up into that little balloon ball.
Turn light?
And cast into the cosmos. Like so.
Tell me how.
Very simple.
Take a penicillin on a piece of paper or a check.
Draw a picture of the father of the country,
George Washington, on the covers.
Put thirty on each side.
Send them to the church of the subgenius at...
What's that address again?
The church of the subgenius is...
The address that is... is...
Oh, uh, what?
Uh, what's the...
Austin's... Austin box?
Oh, the pund office buns.
The box.
Buns of a steer.
Cage mansion.
Cleveland Heights, Ohio.
44118.
And...
Free with every order.
You get to spank the Japanese girl band of your choice at an all-night preview.
You'll be free with every order that Bob gets you.
Every single dick trait that Bob lays down makes you that much more free.
Every tingling dick is made for potatoes that are free.
Every single thing that your dad does is like goop. It's like syrup.
You're swirling in a miasm of your own psychedelic, high-culture colonic.
I was out driving one night far from town.
Aimless I wandered, my pickup broke down.
Then I looked up, Lord, and I beheld a sight.
Praise the Lord!
I saw them lights.
They came for me in the middle of the night.
Up in the sky, Lord, shining so bright.
Praise the Lord!
I saw them lights.
They came for me in the middle of the night.
Up in the sky, Lord, shining so bright
Praise the Lord, I saw them lights
Well, I was a fool to wander and stray
From the main highway that faithful lay
Now all that I know is that I don't know what is right
Praise the Lord, I saw them lights
I saw them lights, I saw them lights
They came for me in the middle of the night
Up in the sky, Lord, shining so bright
Praise the Lord, I saw them lights
I saw them lights by Hank Floyd and the Swerving Headlights
from Interstellar Cattle Drive CD.
Hank Floyd and the Swerving Headlights, swervingheadlights.com.
Before that, Lonesome Cowboy Dave, Chaz Smith, Princess Wiardo,
and I, Stang, on WCSB Cleveland ESO Swamp Radio.
Before that, the attack of the Killers.
The Killer Collages from the Killer Lemur, Fernanda Dande.
The pretty musical Interferal Collages there are by Reverend Chief.
And now, a rare recording from an actual subgenius revival in Austin, Texas in 1982.
Listen closely and you'll hear the 26-year-old Hell Pope Huey.
We need a few of the initiates, please, to squat in the dirt and let us have their chairs.
We'll hear them.
Will someone help move the bodies of those stunned by the music back to the back by the beer?
The pile is out front.
No, back. Excuse me.
And for everyone, for everyone that dies tonight,
their body is worth approximately $12 and it's falling fast.
Everyone that dies tonight is thrown on a cremation pile.
Every subgenius that is carrying his car gets a cut of that $12.
We need the glands for those experiments.
And we're talking about the foot glands.
The most important one in your body next to you know what.
We tried to donate it to the sperm bank, but they wouldn't let us.
Praise Bob.
There's people here, there's people here who, you know, can't donate to the sperm bank because they're underweight.
Okay?
That's all right.
Let us just have just a few cells from underneath your skin so we can begin the cloning experiment.
Let us just have a chocolate.
I would like to have that young lady in the front row because I know in about 14 years she'd be so cute.
We bring them up right at Dobbs Town.
Yeah, I just think you'd have a companion.
If you're going to be exposed to radiation, let's go all the way.
You know, if you're going to do it, then just sit in front of a color TV with your legs widespread watching Mr. T cartoons.
And you can have a boy just like Jeter.
Yeah, that's right.
This is crazy, y'all.
This is crazy.
The most difficult thing I've ever tried to do is to clear the mind.
Let us see.
This Friday and Saturday.
People are rarely gregarious when constipated.
Oh,
wow.
I guess I'll just have to blow up the planet Earth.
In Chicago, another life is about to be changed by a plastic child.
She's got a big plastic ear for a plastic surgeon.
But how do you make a living human child one which won't be rejected by the real?
The real thing and look just like a human plastic child's ear.
We are programmed to function as human females.
Lord, you are.
Yes, my Lord.
Harry Mudd programmed.
You?
Yes, my Lord.
That unprincipled, evil minded, lecherous kulak Harry Mudd program you?
This place is even better.
Are you the next American Idol, Dave?
I'm the next atonal recital.
I'm the next beautiful, beautiful bag of pus.
Look at that big old brain cell.
It's a big old ugly bag of water held up by a bunch of sticks.
Sticks.
That's a very romantic portrait.
It is.
Painted of the human race.
Sticks.
Saline solution and a flaky...
I told my class the other day.
To the aliens looking in from outer space,
you're just an ugly bag of water held up by a bunch of white sticks.
Sticks.
If some babe goes, oh, I love your eyes.
I think it is, yeah.
I don't remember.
Price Bob, that's right.
See if some babe says, oh, I love your eyes or something.
Well, the bag of ugly water is actually an old Star Trek thing.
From the original episode, I think there was some entity that came from outer space
and kept calling them ugly bags of water.
No.
See, I think Landry makes more sense now than the ugly bags of water.
But then I added the held up by sticks.
Held up by sticks.
Do you remember what Landry said?
Before festival?
Landu.
Landru.
Landru?
That's the way they're behaving now.
I didn't go to the last Trekkie convention, Mr. Dave.
Well, you were just talking about sticks and bags.
I thought it would contribute the only one I remembered.
You know, rock and...
Landru.
Did you get a bag with a lot of sticks?
Of course.
Oh, that's a rip.
They don't...
Well, they never put anything but the sticks in it.
I can remember in high school, we would clean a pound of pot
and then take all the sticks and take them to school.
That's a criminal act.
And take them to school.
Well, you're allowed to clean it.
It was 1974.
Right.
So that was decriminalized.
And you are allowed to shampoo it and give it a shave.
You just can't smoke it.
Decriminalized.
Cleaning it.
Anyway, we would take the stems and put them in a big baggie
and sell them to the dweebs and tell them...
We told them they were Peruvian stems.
Are you the guy that sold me those sticks?
You son of a bitch!
That's the son of a bitch right there.
Oh, my God.
I've been waiting for this for 25 years.
And the little geeks were off in the woods trying to smoke the stems
of the pound we cleaned up.
Yeah.
I'm telling you, if you're a little geek,
if you're a little bag of water held up by sticks,
you can get off on sticks.
That's true.
All you need is rock and stick.
Rock and stick.
The first preacher said it, and it's true.
Rock and...
Everything's made of rock and stick.
That was cruel.
My shit was cruel.
This is a ton of rock.
This here is made of stick.
The seeds are like little rocks in the sticks.
Made of sticks.
This is a bag of water.
A hot-looking bag of water.
A hot-looking hydrocephalic bag of water.
Man, he's been going on about it.
They must have just done it out in the car coming up here or something.
Well, they were trying to.
Yeah.
But the police...
The policeman was knocking on the door.
He's got them all excited now.
Sir, sir, sir.
The Red Rocket.
Red Rocket.
We're excited.
Look out.
There stangs Red Rocket.
We're excited.
Always excited.
We're excited about the blessings of J.R. Bob Dobbs on the world.
On the toilet.
Beware.
The blastings.
The leavings of the...
Beware.
The encyclical poet.
Red Rocket.
And rap rosure of his time.
Beware of the Red Rocket of Ivan Stank.
Because it will smell like Rocket.
But pardon me.
That's on a sub-brasa level.
We don't want to...
You know, this is not a public thing we're talking about.
This is very sub-brasa.
Okay, we're going to make fun of someone else.
Someone that's not here.
Or a...
Why do we have to signify like baboons and chimpanzees?
Can't we just lend our own legendary smokage to the overall buttress?
No, there ain't no thing like that.
Hello, you're on American Idol.
Hello.
I'm going to go on.
I'm tired.
I'm tired of happiness.
I'm tired of comfort and pleasure already.
Kill me.
He had too much happiness.
But now he's happier.
He's dead.
And we'll miss him.
Let us hear it for our poor dead friend.
Mars.
The one planet we know is capable of sustaining killer vegetation.
And enemy Martians.
How can you or anybody on this particular world know what it's like in that unhuman place called Mars?
Mars.
The nightmare planet.
The rotten apple planet.
I hate it.
Hate it.
Mars.
The rotten nightmare planet.
Darling.
Mars.
Darling, you can't go on like this.
Fighting the Martians in your memories.
Yeah, you're probably right.
I just feel conservative right now.
I know.
What a fright.
That was groovy.
I know.
That was early kinescope.
What did you get that?
Here we go, children.
Tasty.
So good.
Real good.
I'm going to be enjoying the rest of this.
Human race.
I'm free.
The plaza is falling apart.
Will you hit the osmolap?
Will you wander through the wilderness apart?
Uh-huh.
Will you climb a mountaintop and jump right off into the frat?
Will you?
On July 5th, this year.
So long.
So far.
You're far away.
Uh-huh.
Like that.
That way.
I have a good idea of everything.
Yeah.
Astral intercourse and universal force.
Astral intercourse with the horse nebula, you know?
They're all there.
They're you.
They're there for you.
Give you the balls to see.
See it through.
Yeah.
And light the pipe of truth.
Yeah, that's right.
Smoking.
Selfie in real time, because here we go.
Lesson one, astral intercourse.
Prepare the astral sexual device three days in advance to make sure locomotion is secure and fun.
Also, prepare the back of the neck.
The vesicles expand during extra sexual.
Activity's causing the corpus callosum to explode in some rare occurrences.
For those of you with weak knees, there is a standard brace.
For those with too many braces on their teeth, there's a standard documentary referendum.
I am sleeping now.
And so.
Every day is when you have a good.
You know, you've got to.
Yeah.
You would.
If you have a gun.
You can.
Make your own reality.
Probe into their lives and really.
And so let's go into their own reality.
Armed and humorous.
People, yeah.
We march into the future.
A hundred years from now.
But we have safe guns.
We have to shoot rubber bullets.
We have to sell them all kinds of important things later.
The guns laugh instead of making shot sounds.
Yes.
And the bullets, when they hit you, they tickle you.
You've got to figure out what they want, what they like, what they don't like.
It's going to be a wonderful future.
This is random nonsense.
Church reform.
The next hundred years.
Take it.
Okay.
Church reform.
What are we going to do for the next 100 years?
You are on the board.
You for 250.
You have.
Once again, the gay paris.
Gay.
Well, gay.
You see politics.
Gay is the underlying word here, I think.
I'm sure.
500.
How do you keep them busy?
How do you keep them gay when they're down on the farm?
How do you keep them on the farm when they're gay?
That's right.
Well, how can you improve upon a church that has done so much for so little?
You know?
For so few.
Look at the numbers.
Never have so few.
From the output.
From so many.
Just output.
That's so much.
Well, if you look around, almost every member of the church of the subgenius is in this
radio studio right now.
Right now.
I mean, it's like if there was an atom bomb to go off right now, not that there should
be.
There were a couple of subgeniuses who were out there.
Clam chow.
Yeah.
Free speech.
Or FBI.
It's all screwed.
That's right.
The church is screwed.
CIA.
If the bastion of free speech gets nipped right now by Al Qaeda, there's a three or four
major.
That's right.
Major religion.
This is the Vatican of alternative religion right now.
Yeah.
As we see it.
Well, at least.
At least.
That's right.
They're going down.
If the church of the subgenius goes down, civilization goes.
Safety.
Hit the pipes.
Sidewall.
Smoking.
I would say it was the edict of the mountain.
Stupid.
Four cents.
You owe me four cents.
I own the rights to the world.
Go to hell.
This is it.
Four cents.
This will decide the fate of the world.
Stupid.
What?
Accusation.
Stupid.
I own the rights to the word stupid.
The entire universe is about to be discussed now.
I got trademark rights on that.
What say you fellows?
Destroy or leave alone?
Is it broken?
Rototill.
All of reality.
I went to our guest call.
She was around here screaming.
If it's not broken, I think we should go to the bathroom now.
Reverend Stang.
Rototill.
All of reality.
She's going.
If it's not broken, I say we go in there and fix the day.
Fix it.
Fix the problem.
Fix the hell out of it.
We're going to have a $50 million.
Fix the freaking hell out of it.
Broke or unbroke.
You're a brisker.
If you are, you are.
You have to come to me for $25 million.
Just fix it.
Tamper.
That's our motto.
If you don't work, you got to fix it.
I got a contest.
Semper tamper.
So what kind of launch pads are you guys planning for X day?
It sounds like the plotting and planning is going to start.
I just jump up and down.
You know how I do.
I'm waiting for my cranium to shake.
And then I have the visions.
Chazville.
You don't need to get up for X day.
None of you guys.
Do you guys always sleep through the 7 a.m. ritual?
I've never gotten up before 7 a.m.
How many times do I have to see Christ nailed to the crotch?
I mean, Christ on a stick.
I'm pooped, man.
I just talked to Dr. Legume not two hours ago.
And this very evening, he purchased himself a brand new hot tub.
Yeah, he's installing it in his garage.
Yeah, in the rocket motor.
And he's making a little piece of his own little piece.
The brushwood in his garage.
Our country is about to go to war.
And Dr. Legume is spending his money and time on a hot tub.
Is the tub alive?
Wait, wait, wait.
He's not spending his money and time on a hot tub.
You know, man, this is when he installed his hot tub in a garage.
Well, like they fixed cars there, too, at the same time.
I think it would be interesting to watch.
If you're having your rims done, you could watch someone tubbing it up.
The hot tub in your garage is the only place you can get a rim job.
The sun does not shine here.
Comes a-shinin' back so sweep, sweep, sweep away the gloom
To the boogie rhythm of the new broom
I believe I landed in the wrong place
They've come to take me back to space
Some say it's the water
Others think it's the wind
But me, I like to think
They're my long-lost friends
I wish you'd hurry get me out of here
It's lookin' like the end is near
My nerves are wrecked, they're startin' to shake
If this is a joke, it's more than I can tell
You've had your fun with this hide-and-seek
I mean it, this time come after me
Done all I wanna do, seen all I wanna see
Before the big one blows, hope you rest
And then I'll see you next time
Some say it's the water
Others think it's the wind
But me, I like to think
You're my long-lost friend
I believe I landed in the wrong place
Some say it's the water
Others think it's the wind
But me, I like to think
And I'm thrifty, too
Land of light
The army of darkness shall sweep down
They are gathered like a horde of avengers
Life within life
The power that summons
Come back old ones
Princes of darkness
And repossess the earth
Uh, young man, I, an old one, must, uh, hereby repossess your car
We're workin' on the whole earth, but we're gonna start with your car, sonny
Well, but my axle's fucked up, can't you hear it?
Listen, when I turn, try to turn left
Y'all, I'm not gonna let you get away with this
Tuff-off is the gate whereby the spheres meet
And with the gate open, the old ones shall be
Man rules now where they ruled once
They wait, patient and potent
For here they shall reign again
And rule where they once walked
The old ones broke through of old
And they shall break through again
God!
Stop that!
Then at evening, after the bowls of blood are set out for the ghosts to drink, by the flight of bats we can see the secret openings or entrances that allow us to go below the surface of the ground and commune with our sacred ancestors.
It is there that we may be able to see the secret openings or entrances that allow us to go below the surface of the ground and commune with our sacred ancestors.
it is there that we may be able to see the secret openings or entrances that allow us to go below the surface of the ground and commune with our sacred ancestors.
It is those companies that previously lived here, That are the secret openings of the stronghold games, for which we know no ending yet from the very beginning.
LadyALLAAF
poet says.
Oh, yeah.
What about Doctor Strange?
Did you ever read Doctor Strange?
All the time.
Sure, sure did.
Okay.
And he had his problems with the equivalent of the night gaunts and chug-offs and stuff.
Hell, I do.
Every night.
I do myself.
Yeah, every night.
Exactly.
I have to fight them off before I can make up the bed.
Yep.
And then I push the feathers over to one side, the side I'm going to sleep on, and lay on
top of those.
You have to keep kicking off the blankets and pulling them back on to get the proper
balance.
Yeah.
It's cold and heat.
Yeah, it's like I have one leg and the opposite arm out, and then I switch about every 12
But when the blankets are kicked off and your body is cold, you dream faster and wake up
more, so you tend to remember your dreams more, and they tend to have a more vivid
structure.
I don't care about that.
I would prefer a more deeper sleep.
I don't want to remember my dreams.
My dreams are full of murderous content.
Some are.
Some are of pleasant places that it's fun.
Your dreams, maybe.
Oh, people's dreams.
My dreams are like places I want to escape and never go back to.
Oh, I dream of those horrible things, too, of course.
But then you can also communicate with the dead in the dream world.
Yeah, that is true.
You can communicate with the dead.
You can live in the past.
You can live in the future.
So, if you kick off the blankets, you can live in the future.
You can kick off the covers, then you wake up more frequently, and when you wake up
more frequently, you remember your dreams more frequently.
But then you can interrupt those really good long dreams that are well developed.
Alas, that's the unfortunate aspect of you.
Great plot lines that you've got going.
You have to interrupt them in order to remember them.
Too bad.
And you've got these massive plot lines like they're 15-chapter dreams, and you want to...
A hole in the plot, you can throw a new foundling down.
And then you hear those bells, and you sort of like those little, you know, eastern chime
things.
What a tale of terror.
Sort of makes you realize that you won't remember them anyway.
So, while you're having them, you're thinking, this is a great dream.
This dream is so robust.
It's so plush.
It's so full.
It's rich.
So round.
So firm.
So fully packed.
It's so rich.
It's just full of everything.
There's color.
There's vibrancy.
There's people.
There's relationships.
There's carpeting.
There's rugs.
And there's couches with like special, like, little things.
You know, upholstery.
And I just can't believe it!
The marvels of earth, sea, and sky.
The wonders of earth, the planet of our birth.
But in that one terrible instant, I realize I'm not even going to remember this later.
I'm not even going to remember it.
So what's the point?
You're right.
I should just wake up more often, Reverend Hal.
I'll sleep cooler.
Wake up more often.
Remember my more frequent, shorter dreams more readily.
And then I'll write them down in a book and make a lot of money.
You could write them down in a book, yes.
And you just have the book and the pencil nearby.
That's right.
I've heard of people that do that.
That somebody did that.
He wrote something down.
And then the next morning when he'd read it, it didn't make a damn bit of sense to him.
But he'd still do it.
You have to make sure that you really are holding the pencil and you really are writing in the book.
That you're not thinking about it.
I'm thinking you're doing that while you're really urinating in the bed.
Yeah, well, you know, you have to...
That's how you learn.
If the fool will persist in his folly, then he will become wise.
Or wet.
And is it a bad dream or a wet dream or...
Is it some sort of fervid fantasy?
It is a simulacrum of a dream.
Life, what is it but a dream?
Life is like a dream, only more real.
Shaboom.
Yes, which one?
And more painful.
White. White people.
I've been hurt in my dreams and it didn't really hurt.
I can remember like impacting the ground after flying and it not really hurting.
Now you've done some fun things in your dreams.
I mean really fun.
Oh yeah, you know, I had a...
For a long time I can remember I had this recurring dream.
I haven't had it in a long time.
But I had a recurring dream where I would be able to like bound.
I could bound upwards.
With my feet.
Say to the height of 10, 11, 12 feet.
Which would be just enough to sort of eject me beyond the pull of Earth's gravity where my arms through simple, simple like kicking and flapping motions I could then propel myself forward like flying.
It's a trick and each time you start doing it again you think, oh yeah, I forgot I could do this.
How easy it is.
Yeah, did you do that too?
Yeah, and I...
Oh, I love it.
It's wonderful.
I love those dreams.
And one thing, you can hover about 12 feet up in the air, you know, fairly close to the ground.
And people like, you can hover over people and stuff.
They can just above it so they can't reach you.
They can't reach you, they jump up for you and like they're kind of hacked off that you can do that over them.
But have you ever discovered that then there are some other ones there who can also fly?
That's never happened to me.
And they're menacing.
I've never encountered anyone else flying.
Oh, wow.
Okay, well good for you then.
It's only been me and my dreams.
But you know, I haven't had that dream in a while.
I think I'm going to like program myself tonight.
Just kick off the covers.
When I get home, I'm going to kick off the covers.
I'm going to freeze to death but at least I'll have that dream one more time in my life.
In your life.
Before I die.
When I die.
I'll have a dream about.
Place me on the grace of God.
Place me flying in hell, dream over people.
So high.
All that is.
It's a dream about sex with God.
I'm the elder gods and I'm hovering over people.
They can't reach me.
But you know, I could get up like higher than telephone pole level.
Oh, I can do that too.
I can go way up there.
I can get up like, you know, actually up like just below like airplane level.
I never got much higher than that.
Probably could have.
So you did not then achieve escape velocity and shoot out into space.
No, had you done that?
I think I've been there once or twice.
Oh man, your dreams are more vivid than mine.
You're actually farther out there than me.
You're kind of a far out guy.
Just once or twice I say.
Okay, well you're sort of a wannabe far out guy.
Actually.
But I'm a down to earth guy.
I kind of come down eventually.
And I have nothing to come down from.
That was Dr. Philo Drummond and Dr. Hal Robbins on the Puzzle.
And you're listening to the show KPFA Berkeley.
They selected a beautiful girl like you.
Have you ever seen what a man pees with honey?
Let me show you something.
Gathered around to observe and to relish the nakedness.
And then they waited.
They waited for the moment when she would allow the power of darkness to enter.
The moment when the gate would open.
And the old ones would come through.
And a strange chant echoed in the night.
God! Stop!
How many more times do we have to listen?
How many more times do we have to hear the worst song ever?
This band is terrible too.
They just want to fall asleep.
Yeah, the audience is going in every different direction possible.
They're sick of them.
They're sick of the Cafe Depresso.
Yeah, they're sick of everything here.
They only know three chords.
But you're only going to see them play one.
Wow.
I'm so tired of these guys.
This band's bad.
It's no surprise.
I wish they'd just pack it up and go away.
Well, how many times do we have to play this same song over and over and over again?
How many more times?
Well, how many times do we have to play these same fools?
I'm going to play four notes over and over again.
When I came out of this nightclub, I thought things would be a little bit different.
But it's just the same old band.
In the same stupid shirts.
In the same stupid bleak hair.
You'd think they could do something new after all these years.
But they just play that same song.
They just play that song all that long.
Well, how many more times do we have to play this same song over and over again?
This party's been spartan.
So if you're sick of us,
Well, it's one chord up, one chord down.
Rotam music's got me down.
I played in this band.
For ten hours or so.
I ain't seen my check.
Where's my check?
Oh, where's my check?
Well, how many times do we have to ask for this same check over and over again?
This party's been spartan.
So if you're sick of us,
Well, how many more times do we have to play this same song over and over and over again?
Over and over and over and over and over and over again.
This party's been spartan.
This sure is a bad band.
They really won't make any money.
I don't even know why they're playing here.
Nobody likes them.
Everybody wants them to play quiet.
Yeah.
Well, I just don't know about this band.
I just don't know why they do it.
Well, I guess they're supposed to be on the radio tonight.
But I sure wouldn't know if I listened to this crap.
I hope somebody out there is listening.
I hope somebody can hear this band.
It's at the international signal of distress.
The poor Rotam band.
These guys.
They came all this way.
Nobody wants to hear them.
Well, how many more times do we have to play this band, Mom?
Here I am.
Stop that.
What caused it?
I wish I knew.
Uh-oh.
She died.
Doctors from Bob must have got her sold.
They received the handling order.
That's the thing.
Erik's sore lower possible ofивает the
I can assure you I have to do it a couple of times.
he got in, but I know that at some point
Bob was in there later on.
He was
kicked out, but
he moved up, you might say.
Yeah, of course, you could call it moving up.
Yeah, right.
Or getting a
priapism, you know, an erection that won't
go away.
There's no established date for any of those,
you know. I think Bob's probably going to
show up someplace right in the middle of one of those
meetings at the tombs.
Bob will show up.
All the old bones men will all be around.
Bob will show up to deal with the men from
Planet X on July 5th, 1998.
The original bones men, yeah.
That's right. I'm marking them now
in the little book. July
5th, you're saying? As a
janitor working in a
future time control lab, I
assure you that Bob
will arrive on July 5th, 1998.
For he cometh prematurely
into a time which is more
than night.
I say this to ensure
disbelief.
Disbelief well noted
and enacted.
You must believe.
Believe
me out of it.
Bob said.
Keep your pipe on tight.
I just can't understand what you're
talking about. Keep your back to the wind.
You're just always babbling and babbling
about bodily.
And you're sacking the Sibian.
And then you get out in my house.
You are listening to the Hour of Slack
from the Church of the Subgenius.
For details, see
The Book of the Subgenius
in better bookstores everywhere or
www.subgenius.com
This music in the background
is by Doctors for Bob.
The greatest
doctor band in the Church of the Subgenius.
And friends,
you can take my word for it
that it's perfect, sharp, smooth,
beautiful, perfect,
top of the line, slimline,
easy, easy, best, 30 day money back,
30 day, exact, 13, 3D, 3D, great freak,
great favorite, extra great, relaxing,
Spanish, English, close, interactive,
favorite, simple, sleek, big, sharp,
dual, fast, favorite, older, perfect,
face down, bigger, amazing, small,
different, 3D, flying, different, great,
one year, 24 hours, attractive,
good looking, second, great, great looking,
not true with this one.