Who's there?
The subgenius power of SWAT
Now I know all about everything
What? Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Well the one that was playing before the air conditioner one I don't think made a loud enough noise to interfere
It was coming on the recording
The recording picked it up
Oh yeah it was
We shut the big one down we just turned the box fan on
Right, yeah and this one is on over here too so that probably is good
We have so much trouble with our fans
They're such
Fans?
They're such a, they're so delicate
Yeah that's right
You have to be so careful what you say to them
They get butt hurt, their butt skin is so very thin
They're either loud fans or loud fans
And shaky as the day is long
Shake, they shake and vibrate
And it just happens
So I had to battle an unkillable hornet in my cabin
And what other strange signs and portents
Oh you have a cabin! Oh lucky you!
It's a cabin in the sky Pops
But I was just wondering
They keep me in the bilge
Other people had perhaps seen things that were unusual
Which might contribute to the eschatological array of things
That are happening
Moles
What Hal means is it's the end of the world and weird stuff happens
And we want to know about all of it
It does, you should keep your eye open for weirdness
Something startled a small mole this morning
Like stuff disappearing out of my suitcase
In fact I was going to mention that to you Stang
It was some kind of noise was down that way
Over, and for those who can't see where I'm pointing
I'm pointing down towards the Green Man Tavern
There was a noise and then this small mole just took off
Running like he was running from something like really dangerous
And he came running all the way into
We were all sitting here, we were, you know
Most of the time moles don't come around people
But whatever was in those woods
Scared that little mole enough to come around people
Well don't they normally hide underground?
I would say that indicates there's something lurking underground
I don't know but it was in a hurry
It was in a hurry
I hope they don't all panic
You don't want to see them all galloping through the campsite
No
A mole stampede is not a pretty sight
And they don't smell that great either
100,000 moles friends
No you don't want to get a mole on your skin certainly
And then they become moldy moles
Moldy and so
I'm not sure that really comes to the level of miracle status though
Though it is a portent like rats leaving a sinking ship or something
Well that's what I was thinking actually
I was watching that mole running from that back wood line
And thinking, well that's weird
That's so strange
What would drive a mole from underground into the dangerous hands of the humans?
It was a weird noise though Stang
It was something I, you know, I'm country enough
The mole made a noise or was fleeing from a weird noise?
No the noise that the mole was fleeing from
It was fairly, literally indescribable
It's the first time in my life that I could say
You know I can't really describe the noise
It was indescribable
It was unsettling
Too bad Fat Mandy isn't here
She could probably imitate it
Probably
She's got a pretty good brain
She'll be here before the world ends
That's right
She'll be here
And I did remind people earlier
If you are walking by your fellow subgeniuses
They do need to be banded and dosed off
And tagged
So they do need those green or orange bands
Who else are among the galaxy of entertainers and stars
Who are going to appear here
That's pretty funny
At Subgenius World
Well actually once you register
You will receive a very nice handbook
And in that handbook there is a schedule
Nobody looks at those
Well that's probably true
Well that's because they need to be distributed
Distribute them
Hand them out
People will look at them
If they are in a box
It's true
Nobody reads them
I have a good little story
When I ran up there in panic
To get my PayPal thing working again
There was an email from
Well let's just
Maybe I shouldn't give his name
He's an earnest subgenius
A earnest subgenius
Who really wants to help
And obviously will believe anything
And doesn't continue reading
Because he must have looked at the online version
Of 17X Day Schedule
Which isn't quite the same as the final version we have here
And he wrote to me and said
Stephen Colbert really
Stephen Colbert is going to be on the Hour of Slack
Can I possibly
Is there some way
He asked I can get a recording of that
And can I use it for my project
And so forth
It's like
I felt like
I'm not going to write him back immediately
But I felt like saying
I'm surprised you're so excited about Stephen Colbert
And you didn't even care about Penn and Teller
Or the Blue Man Group
Or the Rolling Stones
Or Pink Floyd
Or the Beatles
Who were also all on that schedule
To be playing here
So he apparently was only impressed by Stephen Colbert
Oh and he wanted me to know if
Steve could give him the address of
John Stewart
And Rachel Maddow
So that he could get comments from them
About the Church of the Subgenius
And you know the sorry thing is
I was actually on John Stewart's show before
It was the Daily Show
That's right
And if you were to ask him
He'd probably say
Who?
Stang was a guest on John Stewart's show
Back in the day
And Rachel Maddow
Well Bob was on her show
Yes this is right
So
Yeah she's Maddow too Bob
Yeah so I guess this guy is a little bit behind the curve
But so often I observe that
People only read the first line of an email
And then get busily to work
Tapping and typing and answering and adding
When they really should proceed to the bottom of the sheet
I did actually say that that
Copy that special online copy of our schedule
Was a test
And see they just don't pick up on it
Especially when some of them
Are just writing in the office post
You better be ready to read between the lines
Because some of us are mean
And we will be setting you up
To make a fool of yourself
In case you don't read all the way to the end
Where it says
Oh by the way that was just a dream
Why are you mean?
Poor little subgenius
Well Bob isn't finished with me yet
And my butt still has a little bit of room left
To be cram-packed full of
Punishment so
Why is Bob mean?
Oh he's not mean
Because in his world there is no good or bad
Or mean or nice
There is only instinct
Pure instinct
And whatever the hell he feels like doing
It's not that he wants to take away our slack
It's just that he naturally absorbs
Any slack he can
That is around
It is up to us
To then reabsorb it back from him
When he sees slack
He instinctively moves to secure it
It doesn't matter whose it is
Don't ask me for his Facebook secret name or anything
And I can't
I don't get invited to those parties either
I can't be a Facebook buddy
Of all these people who name themselves
Bob Dobbs
I will befriend no Bob Dobbs
And they wait and wait
I don't know who they are
And obviously
You're not even writing Bob correctly
And I should be your friend
Why?
Right
And one of them is the great Fernand and Andy Leamer
But even Leamer must be banished from my friend list
Like damn near everybody else on the planet
That's an extreme admirable doctrinal correctness
Of the Torquemada variety
Pisces is one of my Facebook friends
But that's because she's a co-administrator
Of one of those troublesome pages
Or ten of them or something
A lot of them
Yes
And they're all troublesome
And they say I'm mean
By the way I
You are mean
I'm mean
Why am I mean?
Why are you mean, Bob?
Maybe they're trying to say that you're a meme
I am a meme
Am I a meme?
Now I will be
What is the memeing of this?
You're mean, you're mean
You're a big time meme
What is a meme?
A garter snake to all those worthless worms
You had memes
We didn't have memes when I was a kid
We just didn't call them memes
A virus to those pathetic silly little germs
Well yeah I was using one of our memes
On the radio show the other night
And you all can do it too
Look up
Look down
Look all around
Stick up your thumb
Gee you're dumb
But none of them did it, see
They're just staring at it
They're just staring, passive
They've ceased to take orders from the subgenius hierarchy
We did our job too well, dammit
You taught them too much independence
They won't even stick up a thumb so I can say gee you're dumb
It's an edumacational mission
We're trying to teach the unteachable
About what no one wants to know
Teaching the retarded about Bob
There is in fact a schedule posted
That right over
That's right
Those in the radio audience can't see
Reverend Feit-Satage pointing to it
But it is over where Reverend Feit-Satage is pointing
If you are in the radio world
Which you probably won't be
It doesn't know
Because the world is gonna end
No because we cut all the talk about scheduling out
Because
It doesn't make any sense
No, no
Do you think we're doing this show for the five people sitting in front of us?
Hell no
It's for the five and a half people listening on their internet radio radio show
a month from now.
Damn straight.
Hi there.
On the saucers.
Hi there, MP3 listener.
Yeah, that's right,
on the saucers, sure.
Right, right.
Well, they won't need to listen.
They can just access
the Akashic Records directly.
That's true, that's true.
They can just be here
as if, you know,
a fly on the wall.
Be here then.
But only,
as we were discussing
before you arrived,
we were discussing
the importance of
getting the bigger saucer
and what you have to do
to get the bigger saucer
is to spread the word of Bob
because for every soul you convert,
it increases the size
of your personal saucer.
You're making that up
off the top of your head.
No, I'm not.
It sounds good
and it's a good way
to encourage him,
but really,
your saucer,
no matter what,
is as big as your imagination.
Infinitely elastic.
Which means there's no guarantee.
It may end up looking
like your crappy apartment.
You see...
It'll be your own fault.
There is the doctrine
of personal subgenius infallibility
where anything
that's subgeniused
says is unquestionably
to be admitted to
part of the rest.
Or it can be not.
Doctrine of erasability.
All from the book
of the subgenius,
the first volume
in a series of
instructional tomes.
Volume two and three
now out of print.
You have to scramble
onto the internet
and order the last
few remaining copies.
Too late, I got them all.
Which means that you need
to get your subgenius stuff now.
Not just before it goes out of print,
but before the world ends,
you need to get your subgenius stuff.
Get your subgenius stuff in order.
Or don't.
It's either way.
It's your last chance, man.
You know?
Maybe we're not hard sell enough
because it's always like,
yeah, buy that stuff now
or don't.
You know, it's okay.
I mean, I understand.
Some people may not have
the cash right now.
We don't want you to feel bad.
Well, it's always difficult
to bark commands at people
and tell them to buy things
when they have already paid
just to be here.
We don't have anything left.
I have with my show.
So, anyway,
it is generally understood
that these things are
incredible liquid assets.
Even if one were to speak
quasi-heretically and say
whether or not the iconoclasm
does occur,
you still have something
which can be translated
into vital wealth.
This is true.
And whether it can affect
the fact that you may need
a new T-shirt.
Oh, I'm sorry.
You were meant...
That's the different use
of the word.
My apologies.
And there are all kinds
of T-shirts with this,
that, and the other on them.
And little subgenius pins
that you can stick
onto yourself.
And even subgenius cufflinks.
This amazing,
I thought I was bringing
home a pin.
It was one of a pair
of cufflinks.
Now, what subgenius
wears French cuffs?
Only French ones.
They only sell in France.
Oh, really?
Yeah, we don't...
You have to be a dapper
reverend.
Bob Dapper, maybe.
Yes, yes.
I was thinking of that one.
Does he have a pair?
I believe he does.
All right.
Or you have to be
a snazzy dresser,
someone like yourself.
But you still would need
French cuffs,
which I don't have.
Anyway, the point is,
let's buy all of the T-shirts now
before Scotty gets here.
Scotty makes his own Bob shirts,
and I don't think I've seen
a penny from those things.
I don't want to pester him
because he plays such good drums
and lets us use his equipment.
So, you know,
don't tell him I said that.
Please, of course.
I'll have to remember
to erase this part.
Erase it.
Yeah.
These T-shirts are much better
than Scotty's.
They're made of...
Just because they're cleaner.
Yeah, that's it.
They're cleaner.
Semi-compatible.
Cotton material.
And they come in
all the regulation T-shirt sizes.
Small, medium, large,
extra large, extra, extra large.
And they're sold by such
happy clerks.
Elephantine circus tent.
You can visit the happy clerk
and he'll smile and wave.
You can make conversation.
And take your money.
Feel social.
And on the internet...
Is that all we do
on these radio shows?
Is that what churchers said?
Is that what genius is?
Is trying to get people
to buy one $15 T-shirt?
That's what Bob told me to do.
Well, tell us this, Spiceys.
How...
Do they want to hear
in future days
on the saucers
or elsewhere
about the lineup tonight
at the stage?
What's happening on the stage?
No, I'm going to cut
all everything
about the schedule
of these shows, okay?
So let's get that
over with quick.
Dr. Dark is showing
movies tonight.
That's it.
Right.
After the movies,
there may be
some general fuckery.
Now, what...
General fuckery
will be here.
He's showing what?
The Wrestling Women
versus the Aztec Mummy?
I don't remember.
I failed.
Okay.
I think he is showing
Frankenstein's Army.
At some point.
Oh, yeah.
If you haven't seen it,
it's a very imaginative
World War II monster movie.
Even if you hate things
with Nazis,
you'll still probably like it.
Yeah, you'll be rooting
for the Nazi monsters.
Oh, no, you'll be rooting
for the Russian soldiers
that are up against
the Nazi monsters.
But, boy,
the Nazi monsters are cool.
You'll wish you were
one of these Nazi monsters.
Will you be
Jackhammerhead the monster
or Propellerface?
How about the one
with the elephant trunk
like Proboscis attachment?
That's Vacuum Cleaner
Nazi monster.
Not Vacuum Cleaner Face.
No.
They're all down there
in the tunnels
in Frankenstein's Army.
Well, I thought you
hadn't seen it yet.
I haven't.
I'm only describing it
from what I've read
and accumulated
in my reading
and knowledge.
The nerd magazines.
Yeah, right.
You know, friends,
the only reason
that Hal comes to these events
is that my house
is loaded with
real nerdy
monster magazines.
The Slacker Mansion.
He has trouble
finding them
in San Francisco.
Yes.
I, uh...
You'd have to pay for it.
Yeah, scary monsters
and film facts
and all that stuff.
Scary monsters
is a pretty good magazine.
Yeah, if you're old.
It might even
subscribe.
If you're a real old nerd,
they're really good magazines.
But the question
inevitably arises.
You can read all about
these old
Poverty Row
monogram monster movies.
When are you actually
going to see them?
When are you going to see
Bela Lugosi
tangle with the
East Side kids?
Or are you just
going to read about it?
Google it.
Chances are
you'll be looking at it
in two minutes.
Okay.
That's what happened
to me with
King Dinosaur.
You actually watched
some of King Dinosaur
online?
Yeah.
On YouTube.
Unfortunately,
there were these
snarky hipsters
throwing him.
Oh, and their
robot silhouettes
down at the bottom.
Yeah, yeah.
They were talking
all over it.
Nothing could save
that picture.
I do that myself.
That's the worst
dinosaur movie
ever made.
Even worse
than Unknown Island.
I have something
really important
to say in defense
of the terrible
movie King Dinosaur.
Let's hear it.
It caused me
to look
at it
every other
monster movie
after that
for the scene
where the fleeing
female
pretty girl
gets her dress
ripped
so that more
of her leg
shows.
Just before she
falls down
and has to be
picked up.
They wore
kind of long
dresses,
but when they
got kind of
compromised,
you know,
back in those
days,
just seeing a knee
was kind of
extra.
You'd pay
extra for that.
That crappy movie,
it puts you to sleep
up until the point
where the girl
falls down
and rips her dress.
And that made me
as a 10-year-old boy
into a man
instantly.
Well, the same thing
happens in
Killer Shoes.
I went into puberty
the minute that dress
ripped
when I was watching
that on the late night
sci-fi.
Yes, that ripping sound
was not entirely
from the screen.
And that's why we are all
here today.
So the shin drove you
to sin?
That is ultimately
is what put me
to work for Bob
in the end.
Okay, well, you see
the...
The patella sends you
to hell?
It's funny what will
turn a person
into a subgenius.
The value of bulldog
can never be
overestimated.
Right, exactly.
You never know
when some seemingly
meaningless pit
of crap culture
will turn out
to be the one thing
that sticks in your
little perverted
10-year-old head
and makes you
permanently
into a real weirdo.
And I don't mean
somebody with a
funny haircut.
I mean somebody
who's waiting
for that dressed
to rip
for the rest
of their lives.
Do you remember
when they did
the creature
from the Black Lagoon
in 3D on television
all across the country?
I do.
Okay, I'm glad
one of you does.
I was a wee little
Pisces at the time.
They showed it in 3D?
Yes.
The little red
and blue glasses
you got at the store.
The two red
and blue glasses, yes.
Yeah, and they showed
it on television
when I was a wee
little Pisces
and my aunt was
supposed to be
babysitting me
and she wanted
to watch it
so she told me
to go to bed.
And that was
the first
horror-ish movie
I watched
because I
snuck out of bed
and hid behind
the couch
where my aunt
was watching the movie.
Classic.
Traditional.
And when she was
watching the movie
I didn't have
the 3D glasses
because I couldn't
ask for them.
I'm supposed to be
in bed, right?
So I watched
the first time
I watched
that movie
I watched it
in 3D
without the glasses.
In ice-draining
triple color.
Yeah, the multiple
where everything
was sort of
like overlays
with each other
and I watched
the whole movie
that way
and then I was
older in my teens
I watched it again
and I was like
something's not right.
What is wrong with
it was different.
It doesn't have
that scary blur.
Yeah, and that's
what it was.
It didn't, you know
of course I guess
to be fair
I was really little
and maybe shouldn't
have been watching
such
nonsense.
Everyone should
watch the
at all ages.
At all ages?
Children know
themselves
what is scary
and don't need
to be protected
by adults
who are completely
out of step
with a child's
imagination.
Watched a lot
of Twilight Zone.
Kids censor
themselves.
If they're scared
they'll put their
hands over their
face or hide
under the movie
seat like I did.
If I'd seen
Creature from the
Black Lagoon first
instead of
King Dinosaur
my whole life
may have been
very different.
Maybe.
It would have
been built around
one piece swimsuits
instead of
ripping.
Yes.
In skirts.
Where the monster
like swims
under the girl
in the one piece
swimming suit
you know
and he's down
there watching
her in the bubbles
and reaching up
and then he actually
does touch her ankle
and cut to a shot
of her up
on the surface
going
and somebody
That's when my
dates always went bad.
Right.
When you touch
their ankle?
When I touch
the foot from
underneath.
Oh then you
didn't get away
with it.
You don't start
with the ankle though.
Well the creature
is in murky
water in the
Amazonian Lagoon
in the
chlorine
swimming pool.
You can't get away
with it as easily
unless the sun
is at the right angle.
But there is a
murky pond.
That actress
Julie Adams
is still around
and she goes
to the
Monster Bash
conventions in
Pittsburgh
every year.
Because she's
a damn good sport.
Actresses that
appear in
monster movies
are not
mean
and haughty
and proud
but are friendly
and outgoing.
She must be
90 years old
and there'd be
young spring chickens
like myself
lined up.
How about Julie
Newmar who's in
her 70s
but still
is just as
powerful
a presence.
She's got
silver hair
but she's got
the same figure
and the same face.
Don't mention her
around Susie the Flusie.
Susie's got a
real problem
with Julie Newmar.
What's the matter?
Something happened
between those two
that just
don't go out.
You put
Catwoman next to
Susie the Flusie
and there's
a cat fight
that you won't forget.
If you want to hear
some really nasty stuff.
Ask Susie about
Julie Newmar
and retire
to safe distance.
Right.
Well,
that's another
thing we can
look forward to.
When is Susie
coming in
to
X-Day
to be among us?
She's here.
She's here now?
She's been here
for a few days.
She's just
on her own.
She's on her own
schedule.
She's camped
with Philo, right?
Um,
yeah,
maybe,
well,
is Philo
camped in
27B?
I don't know.
Well,
he has to have
the special
power hookup
for his special
powers.
I think that was
in 34A.
So who's
in 27B?
Uh,
maybe.
There is no
27B in this
campground.
You should know
that people
are not
supposed to
park on top
of the hay,
right?
They're not
supposed to
park on top
of the hay.
Yeah,
you're supposed
to stay
off the straw.
Stay off
the straw.
It's like,
stay off the,
you know.
Take my advice.
Stay off the hay.
Yeah.
Keep off the straw.
Keep off,
it's hard stuff,
man.
Once you try
your first straw,
it won't be
the last straw.
Let me put it
that way.
This is,
as Bean said,
families have
been destroyed
because of the straw.
So stay off
the straw
and,
and this is
a family friendly
event.
If you have a straw
problem,
if you have a problem
with being on the straw,
please contact
one of the staff
and,
or one of us
and let us know
if you have a straw
problem.
Well,
what do you think
those grotty
old homeless hippies
are always saying?
Hey,
man.
Yeah,
yeah,
they want some of that.
They've got a straw problem.
They are saying that
because they need
silage forked
their way.
Mr. Ed was originally
a human college
professor.
Eventually,
the metamorphosis
made him
completely
an equine.
But the voice
is the last to go
as we know
from watching
Pinocchio
and other scientific films.
is the first to go.
No,
they,
they remember
the,
when the candle wick
changes
and those others
they're screaming
human voices.
In fact,
they found one
That traumatized
the hell out of me.
They found one
that could still talk
and they separated him
from the other
jackasses
that were going
off for a life
of slavery
and they put him back
with the still
transforming
bad boy.
And that was just
for smoking cigars.
And breaking
stained glass windows.
Yeah,
and being a wise,
a wiseacre.
Yeah.
Talking back
to your elders and such.
Think what they're
going to do to you
when you get
to Donkey Island,
friend.
If you stay here,
you'll have to go
to Donkey Island.
But if you come
with us,
yes,
a wiseass
like Lucius Apuleius
in Metamorphosis.
Right.
An ass that is gold
and knows everything.
My parents had to
carry me screaming
out of Pinocchio
because of that scene
and out of Snow White
because the witch hunt
at the end
with the dwarves
are hunting the witch
and there's thunder
and lightning
and it's...
And the vultures
slowly circling down
to feast
on the old
crone's remains.
It's interesting.
It's another thing
that makes you
a subgenius
is your parents
exposing you
to pornography
and you're
like,
I don't know
But maybe...
Such a young age.
When the witch
crashed on the rocks
off camera,
she turned back
into the voluptuous queen
only all dead
and everything
so the vultures
had a better meal
when they got down there.
I like to think so.
Well, that's sweet.
You know,
also in Snow White,
you probably
haven't even seen
this scene
because they
adjust the aspect
ratio wrong
so you can't see
what's at the bottom
of the screen.
They make it look
more like a
contemporary screen.
It was shot
more square screen,
right, Stang?
So when the witch
transforms herself
and she stamps
out of her castle
on her way
to give Snow White
the poisoned apple,
she passes by
this pathetic scene
where she's
tortured some victim
and the skeleton
is reaching out
through the grid
for a vase of water
and a loaf of bread
and she says,
oh, you want food
and water?
Take it!
And she kicks it
and the bread
crumbles into dust
and the jug breaks
and a huge spike
and the spider
runs out
and runs away.
But you can't see
that spider, friends,
because they won't let you.
The conspiracy
masks off the bottom
of that screen.
They're afraid
to show you
the truth of the spider.
Well, they're afraid
to show you
the true grizzliness
and grimness
of Walt Disney,
which is one
of the secrets
of Disney's success.
Well, also,
they wanted to look
cool and widescreen.
I think that's
the main thing.
That old boxed-off
of ratios.
their heads,
chopped off,
especially in
small towns
where there's just
robotic projection anyway.
I saw Rossellini's
The Rise of Louis XIV,
or rather,
I saw a third of it.
Couldn't see
anybody's heads.
Just a bunch
of fancy
royal costumes
walking around.
Fortunately,
Louis himself
was shorter
than everybody else,
so I got to see him.
Yeah, the
Toulouse track movie
was no problem.
Their heads
chopped off.
Yeah, tall people
always get their heads
chopped off.
Happens to me
all the time.
Remember the tyrant
of Athens
who said,
how do you keep
a fractious population
in control?
Look at that
field of wheat.
You see there's
some stalks
that stick up
above the others?
Well, we chop
those off,
so they're just
as high as the others.
So short people
have an advantage?
Well, it's just that
don't stick your head up
if you don't want
to be chopped down.
Right, the nail
that sticks up
will be hammered down.
Yes.
Thought about getting hammered.
To quote Nance,
who now claims
that he was never
a subgenius.
Yes, Nance has gotten
crotchetier and crotchetier.
But he's...
That's hard to imagine
because he was
the crotchetiest
young man in the world.
He's always been crotchety.
You know,
when I was in his house,
I visited him.
He had a coffee table book,
you know,
like most people
have a coffee table book
about flowers or something.
You can look at
the beautiful pictures.
He had one entitled
Weeds.
And it was a picture
of weeds.
And sure enough,
the book was like
a coffee table book
treatment of weeds.
That was a...
It turned into a hit show
though, didn't it?
Well, it wasn't
the same thing.
A different one?
I get confused.
Isn't it called Weed?
Or is it called Weed?
No, I think it's called
Weeds.
I don't know.
I don't watch television.
I haven't seen it, actually.
Oh, you're too cool
to watch TV, huh?
No, it's too dumb.
It's expensive.
Yeah.
If you have it,
you feel guilty
for not watching it.
No, I'm the weird mutant
because the only...
Mutant.
I'm the weird mutant.
I'm the weird mutant
who only likes sports
on television.
That's all I watch
You are a weird mutant
in that respect.
Most of us are, you know,
wimps that wouldn't get...
We were the last one
picked for the volleyball team.
How about those giants?
Traumatized by that stuff.
I've been checking
the World Cup scores
between getting...
running this stuff here.
I've been, like,
looking and going
and seeing who was winning
in the World Cup.
You know,
but that's the great thing
about subgeniuses
is that each of us
is differently screwed up.
Well, also,
subgeniuses
didn't have a team
on the field
for that event.
Just imagine
how a team
of fully accredited
subgeniuses
would do in this.
I think Germany
would take them out,
but if they had to play
against Bolivia,
they would probably
do all right.
I know that a true team
of Yeti players
could definitely handle
what I saw
from England earlier.
They're fairly close
as it is.
Wasn't one player
repeatedly censored
for biting with his teeth?
Yes, that was...
He took big bites
of other players.
That was his third
biting,
and usually that's a problem
with preschool.
Three bites and you're out.
No real American
watches soccer.
Hmm.
Well, that may be
about to change.
There's no such thing as...
Ann Coulter
famously announced
that you're a
damn sissy
if you had any interest
in soccer.
I thought that...
You know, you see,
that's one of those cases
I think they call...
Was that a death wish?
I looked at it
and I was like,
that's got to be
an Onion article.
Nobody is that bad.
Oh, she is.
She does it too.
And that's the problem
is that the conspiracy,
you know,
just keeps getting
dumber.
It's harder and harder
to tell an Onion article
from a straight headline
and even subgeniuses
are asking me
when Stephen Colbert
is going to be here.
So what you going to do?
Well, you'll just have to
shake your head ruefully
and pocket their money.
Well, Colbert is camped
in 20...
No.
12 G.
You can find him in 12 G.
But he can't come out
during the daylight.
Are you some kind of
Aspie or something
that remembers
where every single
campsite is?
You're just making
these up, aren't you?
There is no 12 G.
Are you calling me a liar?
No, I'm calling you
a member of the church
of the subgenius.
It's different.
We call it a spouting.
Are you suggesting...
It's not lying.
It's a fake spouting.
Are you suggesting
that I pull stuff
out of my tail
all the time?
Well, don't let us
keep you back.
Well, you know,
I mean,
that would almost imply
that I was...
I just made up
all the schedule and...
You might even have
made up this entire scene
and us...
You did actually
literally make up
the schedule.
I wish you didn't
use Excel for that.
Those are hard
for me to read.
I'm sorry.
That's okay.
It's all right.
We're all screwed up
in different ways.
We are all screwed up
Are you pouty about that?
I want everybody
to be screwed up
the same way.
No, that makes it boring.
No, actually we don't
because then they'd all be broke.
Every one of them.
At least there's
one subgenius
who still has some money.
Who is that?
Not me.
I better not say his name.
He's not at the campground here.
It's a couple, actually.
Let me put it this way.
They're catching
all of the Devo Tour.
The last Devo Tour.
They're bringing
They'll be at every show.
That's the only subgenius
that has any money left.
And after these Devo shows,
they'll be broke too.
So don't even think about it.
Maybe.
It's all right.
He said,
I think Mark Mothersbaugh
probably is.
Comments?
Is rich?
I wouldn't know.
I haven't seen his taxes.
He doesn't return
my phone calls anymore.
Aww.
I haven't called him.
He was funny.
When he first started out
as a rock star,
he didn't know
what the drugs were
or the right way to take them.
So was he snorting
the marijuanas
and smoking the cocaine?
I guess we're supposed
to take those
packing the coke up
as exit when
mixing it with vodka.
But that's how we discover
new things.
By experimenting.
Some people need to realize
that rum and coke
is a drink recipe,
not a sequence of events.
There's a Woody Allen movie
where somebody offers
Woody Allen's character
some big bunch of cocaine.
He's supposed to just carve up,
but he just sneezes in it,
blows it all over.
Annie Hall, I think.
That really happened
with Jane or Hyperclete.
It would.
Oh, I can't use that
on the show either.
Oh, no.
I thought we weren't
supposed to mention.
I know, I know.
No, but every now and then
something that's supposed
to only happen in the movies
in a stupid,
stupid comedy movie
really happens
in the church
of the subgenius.
Are subgeniuses?
No.
Stooges.
No, no, no.
I was wondering
the 300 Stooges.
You were making me wonder
if possibly that my life
is a stupid comedy movie.
Well, let me put it this way.
You would be a Moe,
like me.
I would rather be a Groucho.
Well, I guess you sort of
have that option.
I'm not a real big fan.
I thought in terms of
Moes, Larrys, and Curleys.
I'm not a real big fan.
They always love
the stupid one best.
See, women don't,
tend not to like
the Stooges anyway,
but older fans,
here's an interesting phenomenon,
they may start
by hating Shemp,
but later,
after they watch
and watch,
they'll start thinking,
well, you know,
Shemp was actually
pretty funny.
He was pretty subtle.
I did Shemp wrong.
Shemp, more of that, please.
Yeah.
Shemp was a stupid,
very stupid,
Shemp was Moe's brother.
Yes, that Shemp was a Stooges
before Curleys.
I just didn't get,
I was more of a
Marx Brothers girl,
you know?
I guess, you know,
when it comes to the Stooges,
I'm against it.
Well, Marx Brothers is
vastly more cerebral.
Most of their humor
was spoken word.
Well, and we've
talked about this.
Stooges are just
pure theater of cruelty.
Right, right, right,
and we've talked about this.
I have a thing for Breen.
I have a, you know,
a slight thing,
You know, what I mean by thing.
Can we see it?
I have a thing for things.
Oh, well.
I'm just a thing thing.
I have a thing.
You have a thing for things that have things for brains?
Well, it's like Princess Wee is a people person.
I'm not even a thing person.
I'm a thing thing.
You have a thing for things for things?
It's not even that.
It's just things don't have things for things.
The only thing they can do is things.
Oh, okay.
It's action.
Action.
It's slack through action rather than faith, you might say.
But, of course, just any action is not slackful in its effects.
You can't just flail and fling around.
You might receive slack, but there's no guarantee that you're going to convey it to others in a subgeniously way.
It must be the right kind of slack, which we call sal-ack, and not the wrong kind of slack, which we call sack-ack.
Isn't that right, Stang?
I'm glad you remembered what the second one was.
The second one, which is generally symbolized in our sacred documents by a picture of a broken TV set, sack-ack is the wrong kind of slack.
One wants sal-ack, which is symbolized by rolling a perfect strike while bowling.
Make sure that that question is on the quiz.
So, make sure you write that down.
You'll see that it's written on the board.
And remember to take it.
Take your notes.
Why every schoolboy knows.
The quiz will be tomorrow at about 3 o'clock.
You know, I need this cram.
Stop.
Turn in your books.
Every now and then people will start asking me about something in Book of the Subgenius.
And it gives you a cramp?
I have to make up some kind of an answer or honestly go, did I say that?
I guess you better pick up on it then.
What about the doctrine of mutability?
Right.
Why?
My problem is I haven't read that damn thing in quite a long time.
I probably should.
You don't have it?
I mean, because most...
I didn't memorize it like everybody else did.
No, no, no.
I mean, I did at one point, but that was a lot of brain cells under the bridge.
You don't have it in the excrementation chamber?
Book of the Subgenius?
Right.
Nope.
No, no, I don't.
I do have quite a varied amount of reading, but I've already read the Book of the Subgenius.
In fact, to tell the truth, I typed...
I typed...
I typed all of that on a typewriter.
I didn't mean I wrote it all.
I was working for Bob's Memos and stuff.
There, there.
It's all right.
But I had to type it.
And glue the damn strips of text and the little pictures down according to
Hel Swami Satellite Weaver's instructions.
Or worse, Paul Mavridis.
Those guys are like, they're too...
They can tell you where to lay everything out, but they're not going to glue it down themselves.
I mean...
Are you telling me that your whole existence in life has been following others' instructions?
That's right.
I'm the chimpan, the sacred chimpanzee in the Church of the Subgenius.
Speaking of...
A nutless chimp could do my job.
Do you...
What?
I never could afford to do...
What about when the Book of the Subgenius was being put together?
No, we didn't have anything like that.
As you wish.
I had my first and last quaalude.
As we finished the last chapter, I thought it was like a Valium and it was supposed to keep my foot cramps down.
But I went to jail.
Valium of the dullards.
And never, ever, ever touched those pills again.
But at least...
Never, never, never.
Those policemen were right to say, sir, you're going downtown with us.
At least you weren't on the straw.
No, I was not on the straw, which is so powerful that...
They call it a recreational...
A drug, which is fine if your idea of recreation is waking up in the gutter wondering whose head you have on.
I ripped that off from Terry Pratchett, by the way.
He got it from L. Frank Baum.
Really?
The Princess Languid Weir.
Oh, right. She could switch heads.
Well, this is like you don't even know which head you put on after you do the straw and wake up in the gutter.
You wake up with somebody else's head.
It's probably somebody you don't remember meeting.
The only problem with people with multiple heads is they seem to be so two-faced.
You can ask Lonesome Cowboy Dave about that.
He has a parasitic twin hanging off the back of his head.
A heteropagial twin.
It babbles.
It's the minor. He's the major.
When you get two-headers, there's always one that dominates.
There's no such thing as a two-headed person with each head that equally contributes.
Why do you think he wears a hoodie?
No, I feel really bad because I think I'm...
I might have been talking to the wrong head.
That two-headed teenage girl, I forget her name.
One of the heads, the less dominant head, operates one side of the body, and yet she runs effortlessly around.
That means the left side is operating the left foot and the left arm.
But otherwise, that head, you may notice if you see her, is sort of leaning.
By the way, I have dibs on those girls.
Boy, those...
Come accident.
Can you imagine this teenage...
With boobs?
Blonde hair and...
Actually, Mavridis and I are going to end up fighting over that.
Yeah, because they first made Life magazine when they were only about 12.
They were on Oprah.
They look pretty good.
They look...
They're pretty good now, except that the upper body has to contain two sets of lungs and two hearts, and so is somewhat larger.
And I only have half a brain.
Spreading upward this way, but still, you know...
You have half a brain?
I've only got half a brain.
I have a brain cell.
Well, no, I have half a brain.
I know, we're doing good.
We're doing good.
I have half a brain, but I share it with three other people.
Holly Brain Marissa.
Oh, man.
And I never know.
It's like, okay, just...
Who has it today?
Or do they have parts of it?
I can't keep track.
And then the problem with having half a brain and sharing it with three other people is that when one of them has it, you don't have the brain to remember they have it.
And then you don't have enough brain to find out who has the other half.
Half the brain.
That's not your job.
Somebody else has to keep charge.
It's always my job, Hal.
It's always my job.
Well, maybe you take on too much.
Well, you know, somebody has to do it, though.
Somebody has to do it.
It always has to be done.
Someone has to do it.
Somebody has to take care of it.
Like, could I hear...
No, I guess not.
I'm accustomed to doing radio with headphones.
It's a...
I guess I don't get to...
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
It's a...
Oh, well.
The other one had a bad connection.
How many times have I heard that before?
Yeah.
Oh, look at this.
That's what he told her.
Image of slack.
Yes.
There's an...
Reverend Susie the floozy is almost in the house.
And she's almost the only person in the house.
You should swap with me for a little bit, Flooze.
On my head and be a scratch
Actually, I was going to say...
I was a hatching if I only had a brain.
We only have...
We can only run three mics up here.
Well, I mean, I'd love to be down here...
I want everyone to know that if somebody really wants to...
With the thoughts...
I'd be thinking I could be a lovely Lincoln
if I only had a brain.
For a while.
I can't say how long.
Oh, I...
I had to leave that big shepherd's crook at home, by the way.
Oh, that's okay.
I understand.
We have new methods now.
We make...
I apparently...
I have the disappearing talent.
I can make people disappear.
I don't know how I do it, but apparently I can.
I'd be gay.
I'd be merry.
Life could be a ding-a-dary
if I only had a brain.
Doodle-a-deedle-a-deedle-a-deedle.
I kind of wandered off there into a little happy space.
A little happy space with little happy trees.
Of idealized imaginary brainlessness.
If I only had some slack.
If I only had a dick.
If I only had a butt.
I wish I had a scrotum.
If I only had $16 million.
That's the one.
That's the keeper.
So, what you were saying is that
you have no problem
with somebody swapping out on this
live-hour slack if they had something they wanted.
You couldn't make a movie with that.
Well, you could.
Well, it wouldn't be a top-drawer, top-flight Hollywood spectacular.
Or you wouldn't be able to advertise it.
Therefore, nobody would see it.
No matter how good it is.
Except unless Dr. Dark found out about it
and showed it at Dr. Dark's Drive-In.
Awesome things happen at Dr. Dark's Drive-In.
I got engaged at Dr. Dark's Drive-In.
Wow, really?
Yep.
Really?
Yeah.
I lost my virginity at Dr. Dark's Drive-In.
Aww.
I think it was 11X Day, yeah.
Yeah.
That was wild.
Embarrassing.
Messy.
It can be.
I think that was what happened.
Wait, wait, wait.
That's what he told me it was.
That's what Bob said.
Was it the...
Congratulations, Stag, you just lost your virginity.
The other virginity.
Is that what it was?
Oh.
And he left me.
50 cents, too.
50 centavos.
Christ, Bob.
Well, that just shows you got something for nothing.
And he took away my virginity for only 50 cents.
How about that, ladies and gents?
Oh.
Not the oh.
Somebody, we sold Doug Wellman's teeth at one of these things.
I sold Doug Wellman's teeth.
Something like that.
I was the auctioneer on that occasion.
Let's not forget, there's going to be a Bulldada auction.
There will be a Bulldada auction.
Is there really?
Really?
Because did anybody bring anything to sell?
Oh.
I'm sure that they will.
Oh, well, if they...
That is assuming they brought the incredible wealth of the Indies.
I didn't.
There will be auction things.
Jewel-dripping caskets of Alibaba's cave.
I know of at least one thing that will be auctioned.
Which will auction off for a buck or two.
What is the one thing that will be auctioned?
I'm not telling.
Oh.
Oh, all right.
It's a secret.
Can I keep secrets, please?
I like secrets.
You'll learn what strikes only uncover.
Everybody's always like, you know, you have to tell me everything.
Come on, you Pisces.
What about this?
Can't you give them a hint to make them a slaver?
Why can't I keep a secret?
Why do I have to tell them?
Do they have to buy it first to find out what it is?
Because you could raise a lot of money.
It's a secret.
A pig and a poke, huh?
Why can't I have a secret?
In the back of comic books, they always showed a package.
And this is the surprise package.
Just order it.
We can't tell you what it is, but we guarantee it's a hell of a surprise.
Anybody ever offer a secret?
Send only $5 to Bobco, Box 10, or Cambridge.
New Jersey or something like that.
Is that Deathless Hornet's mate buzzing around my head?
Bobco is not in New Jersey.
I love bugs, but the bugs love Hal the most.
They love me more than they love old stringy Stan.
It's because you're so sweet.
Yes, it's true.
I must admit, I am toothsome and delicious.
And so, unfortunately, the insect world has taken note of this fact.
I probably taste to them like their own earwax tastes.
To them.
Like an earwigs earwax.
Which might taste really good to us.
We don't know.
Possibly.
We also have trouble with bugs.
Earwigs are foul creatures.
I think I remember we having trouble getting eaten by mosquitoes.
But earwigs, you've got to draw the line somewhere.
They won't touch me.
Those things are foul.
Although, earwigs?
Earwigs, yes.
Dermaptora.
But the thing about them is that, is odd, one of the things is that they are great parents.
They take great care of them.
They're disgusting young.
But otherwise, they're unbelievably foul.
Insects that raise their...
Earwigs.
Oh, yeah.
They're insects, right?
Earwigs.
Yes, they are insects.
Well, I guess, yeah.
Ants take good care of their little eggs.
Ants just set them in motion and tell them to get to work.
Well, you mean earwigs?
Earwigs spank them if they're bad.
Tell them not to run into the parking lot.
They, you know, I read this.
They're good parents.
They change their diapers.
They don't wear diapers.
That would be difficult given the anatomy of an earwig.
You know, one of the worst things about them is when they turn their butts around,
spread those forceps and squirt a hideous fart cloud of earwig juice at you.
Have you ever seen them do that?
Call Starship Troopers.
They'll handle it.
Earwig juice?
Yes.
I think I saw that at the 7-Eleven.
It comes out as a cloud, but it's a nasty gesture.
It's a nasty act.
I did see that at the 7-Eleven.
Did they really get it?
Did they get in your ears or they just called that?
That's just an old hag's tale.
Yeah, they don't get in your ears and sew them closed with their pinchers.
No, they don't.
But on the other hand...
Well, they don't have any thread anyway.
Some insects do get in your ears.
There are some that do.
Who knows what lives in those woods?
I've known of one case where a motorcycle riding guy going down the road had an enraged
hornet sucked into his helmet by the airstream and it went into his ear.
And stung him again and again while he was trying to ride his motorcycle at 70 miles
an hour.
And he actually meant to make it to the hospital in a condition which made people think he was
an insane man.
And they were able to reach in with the forceps and pull out the still alive hornet.
And then he went on his way.
We had a bug in the ear tragedy at an early X-Day drill.
And what happened on that occasion?
Very early one.
There's a recording of Sister Decadence going, somebody find one of those squeezy bulbs.
Get a squeezy bulb.
Somebody got a bug in his ear.
And it was not a joke.
It was excruciating.
It was awful.
It wasn't a stinging bug.
Well, it's a hole.
It looks like a nice place to hang out.
Yeah, but couldn't get it.
But then, you know, those get in those hairs.
You get all caught in the ear wax.
And I know I've lost shoes that way.
In ear wax?
Big ears.
Don't you trim all that stuff out as part of your grooming cycle?
Well, I do.
I'm not talking about my ears.
I'm talking about ears where I lost my boots in those hairs in ear wax.
Oh, oh.
I was a little confused there.
You know, I was like, well, whose boots?
These boots?
Those boots?
It was just part of the dream.
They're like the insect shoes.
Twas brilliant.
Six at once.
Except in the case of the...
The centipede, which wears more.
There's some pretty strange creatures out in these woods.
There are.
Including the...
And you know, like deer and coyotes, they're becoming more bold around humans.
The giant huntsman spider.
I heard something that...
Now, it could have just been a raccoon.
I had a picture of one.
It seemed to disappear.
You never know.
But something left paw prints on Susie's mirror.
Who would be pawing Susie's mirror?
Little paw prints or big...
She says it was a raccoon.
But you never know.
I don't know.
A raccoon, eh?
There was a raccoon at the other campground that would steal Playboys.
Right.
Only Playboys.
Playboy magazine.
And...
Ukra was in her tent last night and heard something sort of clawing at her tent, trying
to get into her tent.
That was rock bottom.
Pretending to be a raccoon.
I didn't...
Well, I mean...
Nobody seemed like him.
I mean...
Nobody.
You think he's just like a...
It could be.
No, it's not a raccoon.
You think he's haunting the woods like some werewolf...
He'll be here tomorrow...
I worry.
He isn't here already?
So he heard some weird noises in the woods...
On the other hand, Philo and I used to creepy crawl campgrounds.
Not at subgenius events.
When we did our book doctor camp outs, actually.
My friends, I have heard strange animal noises in the woods and at night walking along the
road...
I've heard the crashing of heavy body in the near brush and breathing.
So something.
Are you sure it wasn't just people having sex?
It didn't sound like it.
It wasn't the right...
It wasn't the right heavy body breathing thing?
It's like some big clumsy thing crunching and breaking things.
Rocknar.
Well, anyway, this wasn't this year, but I haven't been here this long so far.
One never knows what creatures may be present.
I mean, I've made the mistake of camping next to the wrong Yeti couple,
and that sounds awful lot like certain Yetis together.
Yes, when the bull alligator reaches orgasm,
it makes its resonant musical bellow that can be heard for mile after mile over the cypress swamp.
How about elephant seals?
They're noisy. They sing.
Well, they do that just for fun, apropos of nothing.
The sounds are related to sex.
I wonder if they're getting it off.
If they attack, they don't roar.
The alligator does not roar as it attacks.
It only sings for love, you see.
Oh, that's nice.
When they go for you, they're silent.
Yeah.
They might hiss.
They aren't going to sing.
Singing is reserved for important things.
But what if an alligator wanted to do surprise butt sex?
Would he still sing?
Because it wouldn't be much of a surprise then.
It's not supposed to be.
It's the way the birds in the trees also celebrate.
There comes your patience.
The alligator is the same deal.
Everyone sings for the lady love.
The bowerbird brings gifts and like that.
So that's basically what rock and roll is all about.
Yes.
That makes sense.
It's not, as some critics would have it, the cry of the rabid baboon.
But rather, a simple song of love.
Oh, love songs.
Oh, wow.
Hey, I could do the poem I couldn't do on the hour of slack the other night.
Better pile it on because this is the hour of the moment.
Yeah, this is, well, it doesn't even have any terribly dirty words in it.
It's just that the concepts are obscene.
A poem should be palpable.
Yeah, I don't use it.
I usually write poetry or songs or anything, but this just entered my head.
It's a love poem.
Domino's old medallions to the thumb.
Okay.
Turn down Dracula.
By James Bernard.
Nerd.
Oh, here it is.
Okay.
Nard.
I fucked a gorilla by Reverend Ivan Stein.
All right, everybody.
I fucked a gorilla.
Name?
Hummus McGrew.
The stuff in her pussy tasted like glue.
When I'd finished my business, what did I do?
I hosed her down good, took her back to the zoo.
That's it?
What do you mean?
That was like four lines.
I thought that was the standard of an epic two.
That's it.
Yeah, that's it.
I don't do those stuff once every ten years.
It says it all.
Okay, all right.
Well, okay, okay.
I mean, it's a good.
It's a good effort.
Yes.
I fucked a gorilla named Hummus McGrew.
That's not.
I thought that was a cute name, Hummus.
Hummus McGrew.
Yes, it is.
Everybody wants to eat hummus, another word for dirt.
And something had to rhyme with McGrew, and it happened to be glue.
And zoo.
Next thing you know, the spirit of Rudy Ray Moore took over.
All right.
That's what it is.
From the Dolomite Mountains of Italy.
That's right.
What is the time?
I can't see it from here.
Well, I.
It's the end of this hour of slack.
It is the end of this hour of slack.
Friends, if you'd like more information about the Church of the Subgenius, the hour of slack,
or anything we've played on this show, you're welcome to look at subgenius.com.
For all the good it'll do you.
Yeah, right.
Or you can write to Post Office Box 181417, Cleveland Heights, Ohio, 44118.
Thank you.
Your complaints are important to us.
Please leave your name.
Number.
And a brief message at the sound of your tone.
Unfortunately, due to high volume load of processing your complaints, we are not immediately able
to process them unless you ease the way with a sizable emolument.
A donation.
You can press the PayPal button.
Yes.
I was listening to that message for hours the other day.
The press the PayPal button thing?
Or the.
No.
When my office phone went on the blank.
I tried to call AT&T.
And man, I was told in every language in the world that it was going to be 30 minutes before
I could talk to anybody.
So why don't I use the website?
Thank you for calling the Subgenius Foundation.
They did get it fixed in about three days.
Remote.
As I knew they would.
The next available operator will be with you as soon as possible.
You know, my phone.
As long as she's available.
My message machine used to say, for a brief time, it said, please leave your number.
Say the number twice.
Slowly and clearly.
Clearly.
Because so many people go, yeah, remember me?
I'm the guy with the weird T-shirt.
So call me at two, one.
Right.
Like he's reminding me of a number that everybody has in the tip of their tongue.
But when I did that, every subgenius had to be a comedian and leave their number real slow.
Just like whenever you say I'm part.
Pardon me.
I'm a little hard of hearing.
I always go.
What?
To be taken literally.
Press three.
Every single.
All of you have done it.
To be ignored.
Wait till it happens to them.
Then they'll be sneezing out the other side.
To be taken seriously.
Hang up.
I was just being polite.
I think there's an echo in here.
It's a wave of the future.
Please continue to hold.
Wave of the future.
A subgenius operator will be with you shortly.
Hold it right there.
All right.