Test, test, test, test.
Yeah, boy, howdy.
New microphone.
Our prayers were answered.
Jesus answered my prayers.
Friends, last week I was really getting sick of using that bad mic.
And I still have bad headphones and bad decks and bad this and bad that.
But at least Jesus answered my prayers.
Yes, perhaps Bob was too busy.
But Jesus, Jesus came through with a new microphone for...
The Self-Genius Hour of Slack.
Oh, don't mind me.
I'm just making my rapist noises.
This is Joe Offer.
Of the Order of Dionysus Abasios.
And you're listening to the Hour of Slack with Reverend Ivan Stang.
A horny wizard.
A horny, horny, horny, horny.
Yeah, that's the problem.
Too many organs and not enough cloth.
Too many jiggling obscene bunches of...
It's the mutations, Doug.
Well, the first time I went to Theme World, I got completely lost.
I was in a very pretentiousness plaza.
And if I hadn't been able to see...
Hey, it's all made of plastic, isn't it?
Yeah, if I hadn't been able to see the giant slack generator at the Tower of Bob towering over me,
like a giant landmark on the horizon,
I think I would have been extremely diversified.
Good morning. You're washed in the pee of Bob.
Oh, not again.
Uh, yes, I'm afraid it is true again.
Yeah, it is.
It's so good to be back.
Back again and again.
But what is it with this sibilance?
I noticed some sibilance in our new microphone.
Well, I'm sure that's all right.
You won't...
It won't make any difference to you, dear friends.
Oh, it does feel good to hear it batter inside my own head.
It gives me the feeling of the power.
The power of the subgenius.
The rightful power that every subgenius should feel.
You should all feel as if you were being...
Your voice were being amplified over gigantic loudspeakers at all times.
Thank God our thoughts are not likewise broadcast, eh, brothers?
Nudge, nudge, wink, wink for surely.
They would slay us all if they were smart.
Luckily, they're not.
And if only we weren't quite so smart.
Smart ourselves.
Maybe we wouldn't get ourselves into so much trouble.
But it is of our subgenius nature to get ourselves into so much trouble.
I can dig it myself.
Well, friends, we have...
We have quite a show.
I have a...
Because I can speak again now.
I'm still sick.
I still have the flu.
But I can...
I don't care.
I don't care anymore.
That's the difference.
I have a big stack of notes and many...
And it's listener time.
It's time for the listeners to...
For us all to share the contributions of the listeners.
In fact, here's a song from a new subgenius band.
I guess you could say.
A band called Mr. Smiley.
Demo number one.
These guys, if guys they indeed be, are from San Francisco.
San Francisco.
Out of all the songs on this tape, this one was my very favorite.
Because really, it's the most to the point.
And yet it is also the most poignantly heartfelt, I think.
Thank you.
We are subgenius and we must have class.
We are subgenius...
We are Dark Genius and we must have class.
Oh, friends, listen to that amplifier buzz in the background.
That's part of their song.
Hear that eee noise in the background?
Now that is what I call to truly devote, dear friends.
This band does obviously harken back to that Jaco homo sort of a time in the olden days.
It hurts my ears too, but it's beautiful.
It's the kind of tape that you should take home with you and listen to over and over again
in the privacy of your own home.
Oh, here's a little address for them.
By the way, the pretty music in the background is amazing.
Of course, Zug's Rift from his CD Villagers.
Um, okay, the horrible Mr. Smiley is available from 445 Webster Street, number 3, San Francisco,
California, 94117.
And if you missed that, then you should have been typing and you should have, oh, actually
you shouldn't, because you're not supposed to do that.
It's a law, dear friends.
The law says, Johnny Law.
You know which law I'm talking about, Johnny Law, the man's law.
It says that no subgenius can sell or trade without the mark of the beast
emblazoned upon their microphone or upon their transmitter.
But you think our church has problems?
Let's look at some of this news here.
On wafer watch, I clipped this out of the Dallas Morning News.
It says here,
In Slidell, Louisiana, churchgoers partaking of Holy Communion at St. Charles Catholic Church
in Picayune, Mississippi, had better swallow.
Two guards are posted nearby to make sure nobody walks out with the sacred communion wafer.
The guards, usually church members wearing suits, took their posts a couple of months ago
after a half dozen instances of people walking out of the church with the wafer.
At Mass, the bread is changed into the body of Christ, said Rev. John Noone.
The Satan worshipers want to get their hands on the host, and they desecrate the host.
And the problem has spread from Mississippi all the way to lovely Slidell, Louisiana, he said.
Well, friends, you know, if every time they said the magic words
over a cracker or a Nella wafer, say, in a subgenius church,
and it turned into a bloody old hunk of Bob's body,
I guarantee you the conspiracy types and the Satanists would want to steal that, too.
They'd want to get a chunk of Bob's body to clone their own evil version of Bob,
as if, you know, anything that they could possibly do would in any way be against what Bob wanted.
If they succeeded, it would be because of Bob.
Because Bob wanted that to happen.
And likewise, if a Satanist were to steal the holy body of Christ
after it had been converted from a Nella wafer into, you know, meat
that somebody was about to have communion with and consume of his flesh,
and the Satanists ran off, cloned a new Jesus,
only raised him, you know, like Rosemary's baby or something, to be the antichrist,
I don't know, anyway, from time to time,
there are teenagers that will decide they want to be a Satanist for a day
and get hold of a stray animal and kill it and leave a messy scene,
and a layman will stumble on it saying it's ritualistic, but,
and this is illegal, but I'm afraid this is a question for the clergy and not the cops,
is basically what the police had to say about this.
But at St. Charles Catholic Church, the communion guards must see someone swallow.
They'll say, look, buddy, you're gonna have to either swallow that meat of our savior
or give it back, because we don't want you to take it home and clone it,
turn it into the new Hitler, the new Larry Flint, the new Jim...
Oh, whoa, what the...
Was that a Satanist attack? Was that a Satanist attack, friends?
Now, see, if I was Bob Larson, I'd say yes,
but because I'm Reverend Ivan Stang, just a mere subgenius, not a guy,
a genius like the great Bob Larson,
I can admit that it was merely my file folder hitting pot, slider pot number six there on the right.
Okay, now, we'll continue with this Dr. Bronner's soap opera
that we call life here in the Church of the Subgenius.
All right, shall we?
Maybe if I turn those headphones down, it'd be a little bit less sibilance, huh?
And maybe if I turn some background music up, then we'd have some kind of a show.
Oh, it's Dr. Imat Zephon and the Cosmic Triad jamming and noodling in the background.
Friends, it's 500 days to X-Day.
That's not the right music for an X-Day rant.
It's 500 days till X-Day, dear friends, 500 days until the end of the world.
And, you know, I think that it's kind of...
I mean, on the day that I'm recording this, February the 19th, Wednesday,
it's 500 days till X-Day, and odd that today the conspiracy would suddenly release in every theater in America.
The Empire Strikes Back.
You think about it, yeah, it sounds like a bunch of crackpot silly stuff.
Maybe, maybe, maybe you.
By the way, dear friends, I know that our listeners, if you're listening,
are on pins and needles just dying to know whether I've managed to continue not smoking like a...
I promise, like an idiot a long time ago.
And I haven't. I have not touched a cigarette.
But, you know, you know, it's so...
Sure, you can quit smoking, but how many of you can quit peeing?
I've tried. I'm gonna, I'm gonna... That's what I'm gonna do next.
Now, I'm announcing it on the radio in public.
I have not urinated since last night.
And I'm gonna try real hard not to.
I know how bad the first day is.
And know that the third day is a thousand times worse.
And it's nothing compared to the third week.
And that's where most people break down.
It's happened to me.
You try, you get up that day going, I ain't gonna pee today.
No problem. One day at a time.
Next thing you know, you're standing in a 7-Eleven, and you peed.
It takes over your mind.
It's because the urge, you know?
It is so difficult.
Anybody out there who's trying to quit, believe me,
if anybody sympathizes, it's me.
Jesus is trying to quit, too.
We're both trying to quit.
And we're... If you are, too, we're with you all the way.
I know how it... You just feel like you're gonna die if you can't
just at least go outside and have a pee.
Hell, you can't even do that in most airports now.
No peeing anywhere.
Not even in... You know, you have to... Literally have to go outside.
Outside the airport, sure.
Outside, there's a whole line of healthy, suntan people
standing there just whizzing away.
I don't know.
I don't know, friends, but we're gonna try.
I'm not just gonna... I'm gonna just... I'm gonna rant on.
I'm gonna rant on and not even think about it.
Oh, some other new news.
We invented a new salute in the church.
Oh, we're not on television. I can't exactly demonstrate it,
but basically, if you form an X with your arms in front of your face, more or less,
it's very militant-looking.
You cross your arms in the middle of the elbows with your hands making a fist,
as I'm doing now.
Hold it up in front of your face and go...
The time is not yet for their arisal.
Now, admittedly, it's probably hard for most of y'all to make that
eee-ah-ee-ah-ee-ah sound without your...
using your finger on your throat, but it can be done.
Oh, other news.
Church of the Subgenius is selling out.
We've, uh...
You know, well, we've always been trying to,
but the conspiracy has started to make offers,
um, and we are now taking advertising on our website.
We're taking advertising on the radio show.
We'll take... I don't care even if these are non-commercial radio stations.
We're taking ads.
Um, uh, like, Absolute Vodka.
And we're selling our sacred slogans of Bob.
Why not? The world ends in 500 days.
We might as well...
You know, it's like, imagine Absolute Vodka ad.
Absolute Vodka.
You'll pay to know what you really drink.
Um, Levi's.
The Subgenius must have slacks.
Marlboro.
Bob sold it. I smoked it. That settles it.
Um, you know, camel... camels.
Or, uh, no, Miller Lite.
Too much is always better than not enough.
Repent. Quit your job. Slack off.
But don't squeeze the Charmin.
Uh...
Oh, give me my Camel Lites or kill me.
And of course, the tried and true one that you can use for any product...
Bob says, eat Cheerios.
You know, Bob says, uh, buy Acme.
Because, friends, in my estimation, in my experience, in my vast experience, I've found, yes, that magic...
The type of magic that you're thinking of, with the M-A-G-I-C-K, with the K at the end, magic...
Magic may be real, but if so, judging by its practitioners, belief in it defeats the purpose.
Pardon me, the poor pose.
Um, but, uh, not to put down our, uh, magic practitioners, friends.
The point is, we're all slaves to the conspiracy of the normals until that day, as we free ourselves from them, and just say no to jobs.
Just say no to jobs.
How's that for a bumper sticker slogan?
Here I am, just giving them away for free like a crazy man.
I oughta just say no to Dobbs.
That's what I oughta do. I oughta just say no.
Say no, Dobbs.
Ain't gonna take your... take your lives.
You're cheating. Salvation ain't salvation at all.
Okay, I told you all about the, uh, the X-Day drill, uh, coming up in July.
The, the, all subgeniuses must attend the X-Day drill in rural New York, July 5th, 6th, 7th, um, at Brushwood Folklore Center.
Uh, there will be a snake hunt, the human pinata, the baby Jesus will be set aflame in the nativity scene, and you will be able to be born again!
Born again, dear friends, by crawling out of the giant vagina that we will have constructed there, because friends, the world owes you a living.
Oh, I don't know about you, actually, I don't know about you, but the world definitely owes me a living, dear friends.
And I want my money back. Right now.
In one lump sum.
Oh man, I wouldn't mind getting me some of that lump sum right now.
I could really use a little bit of that lump sum right about now, dear friends.
I think I'm about on the edge. On the edge of my creaky chair.
Yeah, but that's okay. That's okay. It's just, it's the problem, it's, you know it's rough being self-employed like I am.
I know most of you wish you had my job, sitting here blathering like an idiot to thousands of adoring fans.
Uh, just waiting to get on my souped up leg.
I'm gonna get my Lincoln Continental computer and speed outta here.
But you know, it is the problem of being your own boss, or I've worked for Dobbs, but really, I'm, technically I'm self-employed the way things worked out.
You're caught between a whining slave driver and a pushy slowpoke.
That is the problem.
You've got the laziest employee in the world, and you've got the nastiest slave driver of a boss.
Friends, how do you do that?
Here's some mail we got from a listener in Memphis, Tennessee.
Testimony for Hour of Slack.
You know, that's funny because I don't believe we're broadcast anywhere in Tennessee.
Or Texas, for that matter. Except by internet.
Well, maybe this guy does listen by internet. Let's see.
A letter from a listener.
Dear knowers of Bob,
My name is Lane Deibert.
I am a 35 year old white woman.
Old man, either woman or white male.
Same thing.
From Memphis, Tennessee.
My purpose in writing this letter is twofold.
To order my membership ordainment.
Praise Bob.
Welcome aboard, brother.
And to give you my testimony in how Bob saved my life, literally.
Okay, now listen to this, friends.
By the way, the music in the background is ambient music from huge voodoo.
It's Bruce Grant and DK Jones in the background.
However, I'm going to pause them out right now while I read this man's letter.
Then we'll go back to tapes.
I'm sorry.
But we have to do this.
Without going...
This 35 year old...
person says...
Without going into the totally senseless details, there is no doubt in my mind that if it weren't for Bob's influence, I would be very dead now.
My ex-roommate...
is very unbalanced and cannot function without his medication.
He obviously wasn't taking it the night of October 5th, 1996 because as I lay asleep on the couch after a night of juking at the local rock joint,
he came in and shot at me point blank with a 12 gauge shotgun with number 5 shot.
If it wasn't for Bob's protective shell, my head would have been blown, quote, off, unquote.
There's a tiny little note here that says,
Instead,
I was grazed by one pellet...
to my head,
which caused minor blood loss and some stinking.
This is a true story.
Note that this is before I became ordained, although I did purchase Revelation X and Book of the Subgenius.
And here's the question.
If the ability to deflect shotgun blasts has been imparted on me for merely purchasing the book,
what wondrous...
miracles await after I become an ordained minister?
The mind boggles.
Thank you, Bob, for preserving my life.
I vow to praise you with my every, quote, deed, unquote,
and follow you down every meandering, meaningless path.
Praise Bob.
And he threw in an extra $10 just for the heck...
Well, he crossed out the bad word and wrote in the heck of it.
And that is so...
How come more of you ain't doing that, friends?
Here's another...
Here's another letter.
This one came in email from CosmicJizz at AOL.com.
Um...
Actually, this guy is in that band that we have...
That horrible band that we have played.
Dear Poop Stang,
I am oozing and waiting for Jesus to get my order for more hour of slack shows.
It's so hard I could blow my wad right through your monitor.
Oh, God, I am...
Oh, this guy sounds sort of like Joe Offric.
Oh, God, I am so horny.
Even a Dobbs head looks good.
Okay, I shoot globs on Dobbs' head frequently.
It's part of my sex magic rights, so there.
Hey, when is Bob going to play Cupid and find me a Yeti uberfem?
I'm tired of dating these nice girls that won't join in our six perverted rants
and run screaming before I get the handcuffs and the sex toys out of the closet.
You better come to the X Day Drill, my boy.
Okay, it will happen.
I can feel the lat plane tilting in my favor these days.
Praise Bob, I have faith that passes all understanding.
I want to steal the pinks' metaphysics and make them Dobbs approved.
Beat you to it, buddy.
I could have walked on water, but I am no show-off like Jesus was.
What is... was?
Jesus is still a show-off, friends.
If every man and woman is a star,
why ain't my head shining in the sky?
In the dark.
Rev Paul.
Well, Rev Paul, it's true.
I don't know.
And now here is another way that you, the listener, can help.
Friends, I want you to send in your list of X Day-related songs.
It doesn't have to be by subgeniuses.
It doesn't have to have originally been written about X Day.
It just has to be of an apocalyptic or else a cosmically gigantic,
earth-shattering subject matter.
Not flying saucer rock and roll or a purple people-eater,
because that could be about the greys.
Things like... things that are more vague
about the end of the world and the redemption of the saved.
Examples that I hurriedly wrote down were
Gwar's Ragnarok,
Apollo 69 by Thrillkill Cult,
and Hey Baby by Jimi Hendrix.
Of course, those are all things that I've already overplayed.
So send in your suggestions.
Any band, any time.
And if you think I probably don't have a copy, which is possible,
if it's real, real modern and not fairly famous,
just send a tape.
Okay, you've got the special event Sunday, 12 o'clock,
Morning Mass and Nude Orgy.
1 o'clock to 3, Healings and Sickenings by Appointment.
3.30 to 4.30, Excremeditation.
5 to 2 a.m., Preview of the Day,
and the previous Saturday's Time Control Lessons.
Monday, 12 o'clock, Morning Mass and Nude Orgy.
1 o'clock to 2 o'clock, Acubeating.
3 to 4 o'clock, Live Alien Autopsy and Bring Your Own Scalpel
because we ain't supplying them.
People steal them every time.
4.30 to 5.30, Excremeditation.
That's when you are allowed to go if you haven't quit.
5.30 to 6, Meet and Greet with Millionaire Bob Dobbs.
Yep, Bob will be available Monday, 5.30 to 6 o'clock,
and that's in room 506.
And don't say we didn't tell you, friends.
It's been there all along now.
Continuing in my notes because, man, when I turn this mic off,
this wonderful mic off, I ain't going to get back on.
CD-ROM, Subgenius CD-ROM, just a fast-paced spew of sub-site,
and when you see something you like, then you stop it.
Otherwise, it's a media barrage video like Arise with a soundtrack.
The website is embedded in the frames of the video.
That's one Subgenius CD-ROM idea, vision.
Censored, censored, censored.
That's another, no, wait, they would be the ultimate soldiers.
Movie, story, neighborhood, stores, jobs,
Bob's whole reality slowly changes for main character
as Subgeniuses and Bob open his eyes
from futuristic North Dallas type of modern rich person thing
to Pobuckerland to Road Warrior desolation
and ends with Mutantis.
And it turns out that this character was changing all reality,
all of reality.
All reality and time control through,
Bob was changing all reality and all the world
by changing the way this one character sees the reality and the world.
See.
So that's my sci-fi story I need to work on.
Oh, some more CD-ROM, the required reading list.
Oh, I have just so many notes here.
And here's the secret about the Oklahoma bombing.
I could read to you for another hour about how the popular conception
was spun off by the press corps like a clay urn that McVeigh,
a volatile minute man, was so bitter after failing to make the Army's
elite special forces, so stuffed full of froth at the Turner diaries
that he vented his rage on the Alfred Mura Federal Building in Oklahoma City.
But could it just as easily have been that he was a robotic soldier
with a chip implanted in his head?
It turned into a mad bomber, as Joseph Mengele once said,
the more we do to you, the less you seem to believe we are doing it.
And, um, yeah, I have to take implantable brain computer interface chips
a little bit more seriously because I have to give a talk on that
at South by Southwest.
They've decided that I'm an ex-
I didn't know what email was two years ago, and now I'm an Internet expert
and an expert on implantable brain chips, which, in fact, I am because I've,
if only because I've counseled so many individuals who've had the chips,
who they were, you know, either when they were prisoners or when they were in the military,
all these subgeniuses and friends of mine and kooks out there have had these chips
implanted in the side of their head, and it tells them all this stuff
about how not to send $30 to Bob, don't praise Bob, don't do what he says,
what Reverend Stang says, that's all they hear all day long.
And it's in the fillings in your teeth, uh,
but actually it's not just the fillings, it's your whole teeth.
There's a resonance that works with your teeth.
In that movie, um, The Twelve Monkeys, the business about,
pull your teeth out and that's where they have the radios.
It's true. If you pull your teeth out, that will help.
That's not where the chip is, but they help with the resonance you see from the chip.
Now, you may think that I sound like a crazy man,
but I'm, maybe I am, maybe I'm crazy.
Maybe I'm crazy like a fox.
Maybe this Church of the Subgenius ain't quite, quite a silly little joke.
Sure, it's a silly little joke. It is a silly.
It's a bunch of nerds that like to pretend they're praising Bob.
That isn't all it is, though.
It's many things. It really is a sex cult.
Where people, swingers get together and do stuff you probably just are dreaming of.
Going, why come I don't get to meet those cool subgeniuses?
Well, we just explained the process to you now, didn't we?
If you didn't pick up on it, that's your problem.
Ah, yes. Oh, it feels so good.
To have a decent microphone.
It makes one not want to shut up, not for a second.
Whoa.
It makes one want to express more power.
These occurrences are pure figments of imagination.
Any abnormal sound?
Normal.
Bob loves you.
Well, yes, women have offered me sex for any tidbit of knowledge about Bob.
Just any little Bob story I might tell them, they would offer me sex for.
So I just, I generally avoid that subject.
Oh, Cord, I know what you mean.
And friends, we're back with Suzy the floozy's incredible, uh, subgenius collage.
It is absolutely, absolutely positively...
Perfect.
Perfect for this cerebral affair.
He says he'll help me to project some things he's got his eye on.
Oh, I've got my eye on you, Suzy.
About that he could even cure this crazy quilt I lie on.
I'm a doctor, Suzy.
I love that man.
He has me in his power.
Each romantic 50-minute hour.
Oh, slap.
God, yes.
I know he'll be my dear of dears for a minimum of 20 years.
When the IRS comes.
I love that man, that man.
I love that man.
Well, you are talking about me and not Bob, aren't you?
Oh, Bob.
Yes, Susan. Connie?
Connie?
Connie!
Connie bitten no claws.
Prepare giant torpedo for Connie.
Yes, we're on the USS Puzzling Evidence.
We're going to sink Bob Dobs.
I will personally deliver this torpedo myself.
We're diving.
We might as well get down together, eh, Connie?
Seaman Bob.
So good to see you looking in the pink.
Shut it, Quirk.
You're not going to be glad to see me at all.
Behold!
Look at the bright side, Seaman Bob.
At least there won't be little Seaman Bobs running around.
And there ain't going to be no more Captain Quirks running around either
because I plan to...
I'm going to let my wrath fall on you!
I don't think you know what you're dealing with, mister.
I got a starship up there with enough power to...
To do what, Quirk?
I'm a genetically altered human being with big plans.
Big plans, little man.
And they start with taking over your ship.
Taking over my ship?
Nobody takes over my ship, mister.
Well, how do you plan to stop me?
Like this.
You may call me Connie.
You did once during the storm, remember?
You said, uh...
You might as well go down together, eh, Connie?
I like the way you said Connie.
You like a sock in the jaw?
Plus I touched your heart, huh?
No, Bob, and I'd appreciate it if you wouldn't touch my arm.
Now the bouncing...
The ball will be bob, bob, bobbing along, along
And all that you will do is just keep singing with this sweet song
Be like a kid again, doing what you did again
Burst into song
Now let's all start singing while the ball keeps bobbing along
Now, honey, don't mess with the red phone.
Hello?
What?
What's going on up there?
I ain't seeing you since Selma.
My friends, Bob is a political prisoner.
I want every loyal listener to do everything they can to get him out of jail.
All right, you heard the man.
One grenade each.
Now come to rid the earth of these pigs, perverts, and pugs,
which are a pestilence upon the land.
I'll tell you, if you don't straighten Bob out,
you're gonna have a big problem.
Dobbs doesn't want followers, only their money.
And so we must purge our ranks of the unclean.
Deprogram our own zombies.
The methods he advocates are drastic,
for he hath commanded,
you shall do as I say
and think for yourself
or kill me.
This squad is correct, Captain.
The ship is being bombarded by large globs of ejaculative substances.
It's that same Bob, Jim.
He's taking pot shots at us.
The shields can't take much more than this, Captain.
Arm the condom torpedoes, Mr. Squad.
Condom torpedoes armed, sir.
Messed coming in from the planet, Captain.
On screen.
You can't escape my wrath, Quirk.
One more orgasm and I'll knock you out of the sky.
Fire a condom torpedo.
Tracking the condom torpedo, sir.
I'm ready, Captain.
Five seconds to contact.
Four, three, two, one, now!
Direct hit, Captain.
But Seaman Bob's inflamed penile cannon has been tapped.
However, he's trying to launch another burst.
If he succeeds, we're all dead, son.
He's rupturing, Captain.
Brace yourselves.
Greetings, Mr. Sperm.
Fascinating.
He blew a left testicle.
The result was a mega-spill of sexual fluids.
And I am no longer reading any life forms on the planet's surface.
Oh, Captain, how awful!
Yes, Lieutenant, it's awful.
Seaman Bob drowned in his own semen.
It's ironic.
After serving a great vigil through numerous floods,
Mayor Bob never missed a flood.
Then the waters came in the fall of 73.
The river started to flow.
The water started rising.
The people started worrying.
Where's Honey Bob?
The crowd went out.
The word finally came from all around.
Mayor Bob is out of town.
Oh, we can't have a flood without the Mayor.
We gotta have him on that phone.
He's gotta make those calls to check the rise and falls.
Oh, we can't have a flood without the Mayor.
Where's the Mayor?
We gotta get him fast.
Where's Mayor Bob?
Where's he at?
Let's move to the mountains!
Climb up in a tree!
The bear's not around to help you and me.
If we had a helicopter, we'd get him right away.
But the Mayor's in Cincinnati, on this tug river floodin' day.
We've got to go to Bob!
One week after the shooting, we're coming to Bob again.
I understand.
I understand completely.
My God.
Oh, where is Bob when you need him?
I'm gonna get him.
There he is, right on the fountain.
resembling what it would add to the movie ndernment of next year's great flick.
I think he round up inaux io scratch aluk cyllis sauting ways of wind in an
air of sleeve heat as fourth goosebumps float off of the Fix's dragon.
Wow, good answer!
Ellen Bolts!
I'm Andy Smash for Klumpau.
Joe Note for Lynn's
Nextcause
Up in Wex
media swamp with Bob and Connie and yes, mayhaps even...
...Conneaghy.
.
This is a bad little girl. This is Jessica Cain.
!
.
Hanging off the rear
Dogs are chewing off her clothes
Bills in the caboose
Dams ran down the block
Scots a critter in his sock
Soccer in the sucker, dear
Maker, make your supper clear
Love is universal
It is our love
It doesn't do anything
It is keeping children round the world
Hello
Hi, Grandma
Hi, sweetheart
How are you?
I'm fine, how are you?
I miss you
Oh, I feel like I haven't talked to you for so long
I know, I've been thinking about you
Well, I've been thinking about you too
It seems like you would call, then I would call back
I know
Then you'd call Bob
That's good
She's...
Not good
French is a bad, bad girl
She's not what she looks like
But I'm going to die
Before the jaws of the moon
No need to laugh
I wish the world saw me
And you'd be the moon when I'm dead
No one else will ever know
This is she
I'm dead
Oh, is that the end?
Well, what do you want?
Mom, take me home
Just like your mom
You're the first one
But, you know what
She, to her un food
You gave up
That'd be nice
Don't foot
Just throw it away
P.O. Box 1256 Old Chelsea Station. That's P.O. Box 1256 Old Chelsea Station, New York, New York, 10011.
The things that we get in here, oh, and I should, while I'm, now we don't even know Jessica Kane.
She's not a friend of ours, and that's not graft or anything.
We just, we do get these strange tapes and CDs in the mail, and we listen to them.
And we, when they're weird enough, we certainly feel that we should share them with you.
Now, this one is, John Shirley is a science fiction writer whose latest book is Silicon Embrace.
But he's also known for the Eclipse series of cyberpunk.
He also has done a lot of horror movies and so forth.
But the evil John Shirley also is a rock star.
And his current rock star band, the Panther Moderns, has come out with a CD, which, why not?
This is socially relevant music.
Now, see, some of you are thinking, well, this is subgenius stuff.
It's nothing but these people just being crazy.
That's all it is.
There's just no relevance in there.
Now, that, only a normal person could say that.
But for, this is not to say that John's hellish songs are in any way normal.
But to pacify those of you who think it's all silly, okay?
You see theaaa blurb?
Esatested In your precinct
Translated from English by Victor J. B.xans et bereau ein aprendiz . New York apartment without heat for hours on end.
postalhamelnizatobastartovar
L.A. traffic
The world's a Chicago train
You never will outlast it
The world takes your name in vain
You're the only reason
To put up with the scenes
You're a stroke of color
That turns the gray back into green
You're a vindication
For the human world
The world's a casting director
The world is in my face
My set is not erector
And we're soon gone
Without a trace
The world's a bedroomatic
Slicing, dicing
All our plans
The world is automatic
It's software
It's pure chase
You're the only reason
To put up with the scenes
You're a stroke of color
You're the only reason
James Gray back in the green
You're an vindication
For the human world
Oh yeah
You're the only reason
That we're up in this world
Yeah
You're the only reason
You're the one by good
You're an vindication
For the human world
You're the only reason
That we're up in this world
The world's a safe disposal
In a second to flip the switch
The world is too emotional
The world keeps losing on its pitch
The world's a vigilante
It's slicing dice at all our plans
The world is automatic
Its software is pure chance
You're the only reason
To put up with this scene
You're a stroke of color
James Gray back in the green
You're an vindication
For the human world
No olvidation
You're the only way
ToWhich everyone will blossom
You're a succeed
iper
While all mankind
May not amaze
You just may not be
The same as you
We're
You take all of the
While everyone else's a Dusk
depending on how well you can get it to notice you, friends.
And because 87% of Americans believe in that invisible monster,
there is one that we have to deal with.
Wouldn't be there if they didn't believe in it.
But friends, you can fight back.
Yes, you can fight back by writing for free information about the Church of the Subgenius,
the one true faith that will indeed fight back against these alien space monsters
from some corporate sin galaxy.
And that address to write to, of course, as always, dear friends, is...
And we'll just switch music for this.
Just write to Bob at Post Office Box 140306
Dallas, Texas.
Once again, dear friends, that's Bob at PO Box 140306
Email is slack at metronet.com
And our worldwide website is at www.subgenius.com
Yes, it actually is now.
And...
As we go out...
Hold on just a second.
I'm going to pause this, and you won't even know.
There's no time past at all.
See?
Time control, friends.
Okay, let's see.
There's a subatomic particle called the Iamton.
Physicists, they speculate about it.
But the middleman knows.
The middleman works for the spirits of the urban wilderness to use their baloney.
And the fetish broker works for the middleman.
See, he was a cutting-edge hotshot at Stanford.
He isolated the Iamton using a wetware subatomic scanner
that recreated the thing in his natural cerebral imaging equipment.
And when he did, it spoke to him.
It spoke to him!
Can you fade that?
A subatomic particle that tells you,
Hey, you!
Yeah!
You found me!
It didn't speak to him in English, but he heard it in English.
See, what it was, what it actually was,
was all the Iamtons on the whole planet that spoke to him in the local macro-octave.
Spoke to him through the group of them he had contained in the tokomak field
and scanned with the electron microscope interfaced with his wetware.
You know?
Interfaced with his wetware.
Anyway, he changed big time after that.
Now he wants other people to know what the Iamton can give you,
which is why he lets people spout off all about it like this, like I'm doing right now.
Because he wants to empower people, the ones that have the capacity, like you, see?
He wants them to use the knowledge, to find their way to use it.
But so far, almost no one has.
Not everybody's a shaman like the middleman is, you see.
And the middleman, he's sort of stuck where he is,
because he lost the way back to where he is,
because it's like biting your own teeth or licking your own tongue.
Once you're there, you're too inside to...
Well, he's got to find people on the outside.
People like you, and...