And now, the subgenius hour of slack!
What?
The subgenius hour of slack that you are about to listen to is specially designed only to be played on radio station.
And only in the city of...
Should any other show be heard from a contact in the course of the show,
the listener is advised to remain on the contact list of your own initial positions
in the event of any material interference on the listening device being in the old broadcast.
First arrangement.
The first arrangement.
To sit down slowly, making sure the head muscles don't move too much,
causing the brain to move around in the brain case.
Making sure all the...
The brain's are connected so that no one knows.
No one knows.
Oh, yes, dear friends.
Welcome to another subgenius radio ministry hour of slack.
This one is actually, what, number 787.
That's all.
And, uh...
Well, we finally finished moving the subgenius archives into the new tomb castle.
But I'm getting married in four days.
We did everything back-asswards, friends.
Princess, we, and I.
First, we bought a house.
Then we went on our honeymoon to Amsterdam.
Then we got married.
Next, we're gonna start dating.
And I guess, uh...
Someone will introduce us.
Wendy, so...
Since I've gotta go, uh...
Get ready...
Get fit for my tuxedo and, uh...
All that kind of crap.
Uh, romantic crap, friends.
Uh...
See, I've been there, done that.
It's my second time, too.
Although Princess We is very excited.
She's never been married before.
And she's never gonna be married again.
Because, my friends, I'm gonna announce to you right now...
In a subgenius on-the-air wedding ceremony...
That I'm gonna bird-dog that stuff.
You hear me?
I'm gonna bird-dog that stuff.
So don't even think about it, boys.
And subgenius girls.
Don't even...
This is...
Reverend Stang is bird-dogging that stuff.
And, uh...
And in so doing, I've gotta rush through this show.
Of course, there's tons of Einstein Secret Orchestra...
Uh, recorded from, uh...
The DeVival at Euclid Tavern.
And maybe some ranting.
And tons of Brandon...
New, uh...
Saint N.
And Helena Handbasket.
And, uh...
Little Theodore.
I've got some Little Theodore here that, uh...
You probably haven't heard.
That's wonderful.
And, uh...
Oh...
Lord only knows what all.
Oh, Morning Forty Federation.
That's this, uh...
Sloppy band in New Orleans that I kindly like.
But, friends, this is, after all, the hour of slack.
And who better to explain certain...
Heretofore unexplored areas of slack and slacks
than the great discovery of our friend Pope Phil Monty,
the pope of all northern England.
And, uh...
Phil Monty discovered this local artiste
by the name of Fat Harry White.
And so, dear friends, once again on the Hour of Slack,
we are so pleased to have you here.
We are so pleased to present to you
slack as...
explored...
the conceit of slack
as entertained by the great
Fat Harry White.
Praise Bob.
Baby.
Slippin' into my new skin-tight jumpers
for you, honey.
And dressin' up...
for the leaders...
for the love.
Come over here, Maureen.
Hey!
I'm talkin' about dressin' up right reminds me
of when I worked at Slack's R.O.s.
You know, eh?
Next to Jessop's, the grocer's.
It was the first time I met Foxy Fiona,
my very sexy lady friend.
Never forget it, she walked up to me at the counter
and in a very sexy voice,
asked me what I had to offer in the trouser department.
Apparently, she wanted to buy some flared crimpling slacks
for her long-legged, tight-fitting, slacks.
It was my great-father's birthday.
Very partial to bright colours, it was.
Anyway, I told her I was almost certain
I'd have something with a good length
that would satisfy her,
and asked her to follow me upstairs.
Well, after going through me trousers,
she surprised me by saying that she really fancied
the large pink pair that I had.
Not only did they hang well,
but she thought they looked really attractive,
particularly the way they swung about loosely
when I walked.
Mind you, she wasn't too sure of the size at first,
and had me lay them out on the counter
so she could measure them up.
She also ran her fingers admiringly down the crease.
Well, she decided to go for it,
asked me how much.
I says three and a half quid.
She asked me rather cheekily if I would go down.
Well, you know, thought about it, long and hard,
decided to drop them for her,
which I did there and then.
What fun, backwards and forwards, over the counter.
A good bit of haggling, and no mistake.
And I was thinking about this, right,
because I'd been back to that shop,
because the weather's beginning to change a bit,
getting a bit parker, isn't it?
Well, I tell you what, I went out the other morning,
and me buns was so cold it started to change colour.
I'm not kidding, when me very sexy lady friend,
sexy Sam, saw me coming towards her,
me purple hat sticking out me coat,
she told me to get it covered immediately.
So I said, I'm going to the shop to buy a hat, a fur one.
Well, when I got there, you know,
I asked sexy Salea,
the very sexy lady friend hat assistant,
to show me what she had, you know, in her fur department.
She said she'd be only too pleased
to show me what she had downstairs,
and led me to the basement,
where I could see everything she had on full display.
I tell you what, you wouldn't believe how much she had.
She had every kind of fur that you could imagine.
I was going to go for a fox fur,
but as soon as sexy Salea said she had a particularly nice beaver
that I might be interested in,
immediately changed me mind.
Well, you know, after getting it out for me,
I've got to say I've never seen such a big bushy one like it in all my life.
Well, when I asked her if she could, you know,
try it on for size, she said,
I might find it a bit tight at first,
but if I buried my head deep enough,
then it should stretch a little to accommodate me fully.
Tell you what, she weren't wrong,
and when I looked at it in the mirror,
you know, sideways on,
I could see it had slid in perfectly.
Well, you know, after that, she then said she'd
summat round the back that I might be interested in,
led me into the storeroom,
to show me a selection of gloves that had just arrived.
Well, I was obviously interested,
but as I didn't know what size I was,
I had to get sexy Salea to measure my hand.
Well, after asking me to, you know,
give her a finger, which I promptly did,
she then asked me to stick my thumb up,
no problem at all.
Within minutes, she declared,
as she was holding her measuring tape,
that I was extra, extra large.
Well, then she had to take a phone call,
but while she was on the mobile,
I took the opportunity of rummaging in her box
until I found the perfect fit,
and when I withdrew,
sexy Salea nodded appreciatively
at my great big leathery pair.
Dressing up for the ladies, yeah.
I'm a-looking in the mood for love.
Oh, yes, Fat Harry White, dear friends.
And from his album,
well, actually, it's Fat Harry White
and the Love Limited Orchestra,
from his album,
Mmm, Baby,
on Anxious Records,
thanks to Pope Phil Amante.
Oh, yes, friends, you're listening
to the subgenius radio ministry,
Hour of Slack,
the voice of the church of the subgenius,
the only real religion,
because it's the only one that admits
it's so totally full of crap,
that makes it pretty much the only valid religion.
It's the only valid one, don't you agree?
Anyway, you can always get more information
about this church by checking us out
on the internet, www.subgenius.com.
And what's it about?
Well, it's about the great super salesman,
J.R. Bob Dobbs, who discovered in 1953
that there was a conspiracy of normal people
robbing away the slack of all the weirdos,
abnormals, disbelievers,
or those who'll believe anything,
which is what we're looking for, friends,
those who can join us in this nameless fight
against that conspiracy of normal people.
And how are you gonna get slack,
and how are you gonna fight the conspiracy?
Here's our secret.
We won't tell you.
It's up to you,
because only you know what's best for you.
So, praise God,
I don't even know what's coming up next.
I gotta get this show done in a hurry,
so I can go on to some serious, serious slack.
I understand that when you get married,
you can have sex,
and I've heard a lot about that.
I was just so anxious to check it out.
Well, so I'm going to let the older tapes
take care of the rest of the show.
Praise Bob.
Bob, Bob, Bob.
I heard Mojo almost had mutiny in New Zealand
because he kept spewing Bob.
And we have people that work for the company
who actually go to church and stuff.
Well, I guess that's their problem.
And they got absurd by the effective way.
They got the effective Bob upon their cataclysms?
Yeah.
Oh, my dearth.
So they felt threatened by Bob.
Their God.
They felt like their God wasn't standing a chance
against Bob Dobbs.
They might be listening right now.
They were feeling a little sick.
A little, you know,
there's some people that have the kind of God
that needs help from his followers.
A weak, pathetic, sad God
who can't take a joke,
who can't take an insult,
and whose followers have to thrash those
A God whose hands and feet wounds have never healed,
nor that long-kneed spear in the side knicks.
Then you got old Bob.
They'd been festering for thousands of years,
and even before the hams came out.
No, old Bob, he's a better sport,
and his followers are a pretty good sport.
They listen to him.
Check it out.
Bob's being tortured.
Some sport with hams right now.
They average about 27, 28.
Inches.
Oh, my God.
That's a new record.
Well, it's old for brownies.
Oh, I see how you could get it that way.
The Muscovites are all girls whose first few marriages didn't work out,
and they decided to get back into uniform.
Fortunately, we sell enough cookies to keep a roof over our heads.
March, march, march, march,
over our heads.
Door to door.
No, most of the girls sleep right here in the barracks.
No, no.
Dobbs Town.
Cookies.
You sell the cookies door to door.
Oh.
Bob cookies.
Yes.
We go out every night at the stroke of midnight.
Oh, stroking at midnight.
Yes.
Well, there's no time during the day.
I give my lectures during the day.
Oh, I can see.
I teach my girls the basics of a happy, successful life.
Things like cooking and...
No, dum-dum.
Things like alimony.
Oh.
And then one week each month...
And shaving their vaginas for Pazuzu.
Uh-huh.
Each girl has a tent all to herself,
and each one has her own message.
A blanket, bedroll, and a flashlight.
The girls just love it.
Oh, that sounds very interesting.
Where do you have these in Kansas?
Fort Dix, New Jersey.
Fort...
There you go, Dave.
Fort Dix.
Man, Dave, he...
Dave exploded there.
I'm sorry.
I had a bad vision.
Dave, that was pretty weird there.
It was intense, Chaz.
It scared us.
It was like right in my prefrontal lobe.
Your mother sucks Bob in hell.
I could see it right in the front of my head.
Stang and I were both actually like scared when you did that.
Well, I'm sorry.
I thought it was going to come out of my head and leap onto the turntable for the love of
Dobbs.
Like a Harryhausen animation.
Yeah, like one of those...
It's pulling Dave's forehead open from inside and leaping out from little...
You're homunculus.
With kind of a Dave look to it.
Tiny little man, come out.
And a big, prehensile...
...like, tentacle-like appendage, baby.
The world is a ghetto.
I'm not a ghetto.
Remember, folks, in Sector 49...
But you could put a nice little horn soundtrack to it and it's not so bad.
Come on, baby.
Yeah.
Get on down.
When the windows are open a little bit.
Sit down next to me.
Let me tell you about old Bob.
See, just like you can't imagine me as Shakin'.
You need a light.
Like, all I see is hot buttered corn right there.
You know what I'm saying, bro?
I mean, I can't see you as like the dulcet tone, you know, any one of them kind of singers,
you know, like...
I'm not a good singer.
I'm a good singer.
What, you mean I'm not doing the Isaac Hayes thing right?
Well, I just can't see you.
Hey, baby.
Well...
The Isaac or Barry Jones...
Hey, I just made a musical joke.
Hey, Chad.
I just made a musical joke.
I said, the Isaac or the Barry Jones...
Hey, baby.
My baby, baby.
He's my baby.
Sector 49.
Necks will be shaved at 3 p.m.
The world is a ghetto.
Ring my bell, baby.
There will be no forehead paintings.
There will be no absurd behavior
among the Lungerlesions and the Bungerhesions.
The world is a ghetto.
Lesions.
There'll be no smoking in the gas chambers.
There'll be no puffing in the town of hogs.
Please go to the restroom before you are strapped to the table.
Run slowly.
Do not walk with your head lifted or your eyes skyward,
but run slowly to the nearest convenience area.
Step on stopping blue line.
If your family wishes to witness your execution,
make sure they...
They have the pink backstage palace before they enter the death chamber.
Security to aisle B.
The Kmart special tonight is a floundering of ham,
some pieces of old-estute periodical from the period before this propaganda...
The world is a ghetto.
Something wrong.
That is true.
Ah, Dr. Muffy, the walls are clean now.
All the blood's been washed into the sewer.
The old box is a ghetto.
All the barbed wire's down now,
and everything looks like it used to look here in Cleanville.
Before the bungalows exploded.
I don't know if that's really true.
I think we still have problems here in Topstown.
It's a very, very deep cycle.
It's a logical problem.
Dobbstown is a ghetto, baby.
The world is a ghetto.
That's terrible to see.
Dobbstown is this world.
Ah.
You ain't in the world until you've been to Dobbstown.
And you can't escape the world until you have escaped from Dobbstown.
Subtitles by the Amara.org community
September 13, 2018
Neben Esteban
Women's Zombies
Watch the entire program exclusively on PBS.
What's your story?
Watch as it chooses to be your business code.
Is it a game of the overwhelmingly better,
or is it a game of a Bunun worthy,
How about some subgenius techno?
This new material here from St. Ann and Helena Handbaskets, C.D. Hale-Conney.
This is a new material from St. Ann and Helena Handbaskets, C.D. Hale-Conney.
Do we trust Mr. Conney?
Mr. Conney?
Divine domestic deviation.
Conney is our inspiration.
Our lovely leader in fighting love.
This is Mr. Conney.
Do we trust?
We trust.
This dude is a loyal friend.
Connie.
Sister Connie.
Saint N and Helena Handbasket, friends.
You can check out www.mp3.com slash saint n or www.minitrue.org.
Likewise, in the realm of subgenius techno, we now experience Lampre Systems' latest,
which is copped off of alt-binary slack from their new album, Rave Till Bedtime.
This is Lampre Systems' Brain Hat.
Stand by for mind control.
Rave Till Bedtime.
This spore penetrates the flesh and devours the body from within, turning it into a human fungus.
I've got images in my brain I'll never get out!
Rave Till Bedtime.
No 9,000 computer has ever made a mistake or distorted the information.
We are all, by any practical definition of the words, foolproof and incapable of error.
I will not be pushed, filed, stamped, indexed, briefed, debriefed, or numbered.
Have you ever jacked in? Have you ever wired tricked?
Brain is gone.
Lampre Systems.
And...
Friends, you may have been wondering what this beautiful music in the background,
has been throughout this subgenius radio-media ministry of slack.
This is a band called Final Back, from here in Ohio, northern Ohio.
Final Back.
The name of this album CD is Operation Coop Strap, or Co-op Strap.
And you can email them at lundgren at ocu.com.
lundgren at ocu.com.
O-C-U dot com.
Oh, praise Bob.
And now, for the great Morning Forty Federation.
Alright, boys.
Yes.
, I'm a drunk, a drunk.
I miss you.
Mom, but I'm a drunk, a drunk.
I love you, Mom, but I'm a drunk, a drunk.
Spend money, Mom, cause I'm a drunk, a drunk.
Just send me money for a bottle or two.
And then I'll tell you that.
Woo!
I miss you, Mom, but I'm a drunk.
Matt Sozial invited me.
Lonely American Dwarf is in town.
sujetid.com
Men of everything.
Why?
There's more.
Well, you treated me well
And you fed me my grease
It's not your fault, mama
That I can't stay clean
Hey, I'm not shooting dope
And I'm not snorting speed
So won't you send me about $40
For a little of what I need
You heard me
Just send me money for a bottle or two
And then I'll tell your dad
I love you
Come on, kid
I'm on a million and a thousand and two
Yeah
Sorry, mom
But I'm a drunk
A drunk
I love you, mom
But I'm a drunk
A drunk
I miss you, mom
But I'm a drunk
A drunk
Send money, mom
Cause I'm a drunk
Drunk
Drunky donkey
I'm
Drunk
I need a little beer, a little wine, a little hard liquor.
But none of that's important, mama.
What's important is that I love you.
You love me too?
I love you too, baby.
Your papa was the same way.
Oh, mama, that means so much to me.
I love you too, baby.
What the fuck?
So now I ski and watch TV.
Of course, that's a lot more fun and relaxing.
That's what I really want to do with my time.
Art gets old when no one pays you or even understands.
What's the point?
Unless I was going to do it just for me.
But I'd really rather just ski and watch TV.
Of course.
That's a lot more fun for me.
And I might as well have fun.
Because that's what life's for.
You know, grab more of a gusto and all that.
And I'm alive now.
But someday I'll have to die.
And then I'll be dead for a long time.
For a long, long time.
For a long, long, long, long time.
For a fucking forever in fact.
So I might as well ski.
And watch TV.
Now, while I have the chance.
Don't have time to waste.
On art.
And I don't believe in God.
I'm not that dumb.
So what's art even for if you don't get paid?
And I'm sick of torturing myself.
And of wondering if it's done yet.
And I'm sick of hanging out with all those dumb flakes.
Who think they're so smart.
And I might as well just listen to the music that I grew up with.
That's what I'm doing.
The only music that ever really moved me.
And who's stuff's just a trend.
It's not real.
And now I can get all those old great songs again.
On CD.
Cause they sound better.
And last longer, I think.
Oh, I'm so glad to be alive.
In this modern age.
And that's why I don't want to die.
But there's not a whole lot I can do about that now.
Except maybe eat more vegetables.
And I think I better marry my girlfriend.
Cause it's such a risk nowadays.
Even though I'm not one of those people.
And I'm probably safe.
But you can never be too sure.
And so we can marry.
And ski.
And watch TV.
Together.
And feel free and happy.
Without having to worry about art.
What a pain.
Glad I'm through with all that.
And now I've got all I could really reasonably expect to get out of life.
Anyway.
What the fuck.
Little Theodore from his album
Idiots Are Closer To God.
Truly a subgenius anthem.
You can contact Little Theodore
at
Raleigh Street
That's R-A-L-E-I-G-H
Street.
Denver, Colorado.
Or
Little Theodore at
yahoo.com
The Theodore part
is spelled with an F.
Or check the new weblink pages
at
www.subgenius.com
And for that matter
you can write to Subgenius Foundation
for that free information.
Post office box
140306.
Dallas, Texas
75214.
And now back to the Euclid Tavern
in Cleveland
where that
D-Vival with Einstein's Secret Orchestra
is already in progress.
Now we can get back
to what we started at doing
which is saving souls
from themselves.
Yes friends
we're going to do
something to save souls
from themselves.
To save people from the false
slack that they chose
by default, just by ignorance
following the man
just because they didn't recognize
the power of their
own slack.
And slack friends
when you truly
take the attitude of slack
you have a power that the
Pope of the Vatican would kill for.
And has killed for.
The power to fail.
The power to fail my friends.
If we were geniuses
we'd call it the Church of the
Genius.
But this is the kind of church
that's a little easier to qualify for.
As the great
subgenius Pareto
whoever the hell he is once
said, give me a
fruitful arrow
anytime full of
seeds bursting with
its own corrections.
You can keep your sterile
truth for yourself.
And friends it's true
false prophecies
abound everywhere.
For instance, everybody
thought that whoever got the
most votes would win.
Prophecy
failed.
Sorry days are
gone here again.
Mr. Big Dick Cheney
says it's time for lots more
nuclear power.
See who we got on the board.
We got Tom Lisa Rice. She works with
Exxon. We got Cheney.
He works with Huffer Puffer Pelley and
Swank Incorporated.
We got Dim Char and Dimwit
working for the oil companies.
We got oil, nuclear power.
We got the
Caesars.
We got a
DeC Constitution properly
being dealt.
We got an
oil and gas
We gotクコ
power runs.
What did I
say?
One, two, three
Boa's
But just to stay alive with the other man
One, two, one, the other man
One, two, one, there's no more running through the middle land
No more pay a visit
Shake the holy hand, oh the man
Shake the holy hand
The barium, a two, four, eight
It's mainly sterile, arcane, procreate
And the plutonium, one, four, seven
A silver approach, I'll see you in heaven
But the iodine, one, three, one
The iodine, one, three, one
There's no more running through the middle land
No more pay a visit
Shake the holy hand, oh the man
Shake the holy hand
Looked at over two million dumb pollutants
That can cause cancer
Skin lesions
Brain tumors
Thoracic confusion
Possible Republican identity
Congregations in the Middle East
Disconnected rumors
The long-slimming thing on DNA
When the sperm is fired
Chicken egg spasia
And what the fuck is the use?
The iodine, one, three, one
All the run and the krypton
When it fires
It's making it hard to stay alive
Iodine, one, three, one
The iodine, one, three, one
There's no more running through the middle land
No more pay a visit
Shake the holy hand, oh the man
There's no more running from the little man.
No more running from the little man.
Shake the party hat.
The party's a man.
Shake it, baby.
Thank you.
Boys and girls gathered here in the name of freedom.
I know some of you have hardly reached your 14th birthday.
Some of you are wearing those pearl cockled necklaces given to you by your ancient grandfathers.
And we know the nuclear devices you will be carrying into town today will cause you instant sainthood and martyrdom.
You will be lifted on high so there's no reason to cry, children.
Each one of you are a little boy.
Come, armed and ready to pop.
It's not going to fit in here.
I feel like I could pop all night, baby.
I don't know if I can walk to town with this.
You're my radar love, hon.
The implantation devices make sure that each child walks the straight and narrow path
to his dream.
The target is known at control is to make sure that each child removes itself as it removes
the target.
So there are no witnesses and no disclaimers allowed past the curfew now.
Damn it, Dave.
What do you think, Dave, about the fact that...
Damn it.
They're not even going to hide anymore, are they?
No.
No, they're just right out there.
We're having an oil problem right now.
We're not making enough money to who knows what.
They're just not even going to hide it anymore.
Nope.
They're just going to rape everything they can in the four years they have.
Or only two, really, because they know they're going to lose the Senate.
Oh, Jeb's son will be the next Bush emperor.
And then...
Jeb's son?
You mean the little Puerto Rican kid?
Yeah.
The one granddad called the little brown one?
His father called him the little...
Really?
Yeah, George Bush Sr.
Oh, is that the little brown one?
The little brown one, right?
Well, I'm glad he's spreading his genes around and kind of like one of the folks now, but
that's good to have a brown child.
I'm learning...
How did that happen?
You know, I realized that I was serious when it sunk in that I really was trying to learn
Dutch from that little Berlitz book.
You mean you're saying you're actually...
You're actually thinking of repatriating the species?
I...
Well, you know...
I don't want to be part of the empire.
I know what you mean.
You know, I don't want to be on the Death Star.
I know.
I want to do...
I grew up believing that America was the rebel forces.
And now I'm a peanut in a big huge drum.
And now it's like, well, the rebel forces, this is the Death Star, man.
Howdy, folks.
Come on down to America, Inc., where you'll be forced to pay for everything.
But it's not.
It's convenient, friends.
Ah, memories.
This is the most convenient.
They used to shoot at us.
Now they shoot near us.
Well, I heard about the softer, the more friendlier bullets that they're using on the kids these
days.
Well, they don't think they were using friendly bullets in Cincinnati.
I heard they use the little bouncing bullets.
No.
Not in the West Bank of Gaza, they don't.
No, no, no.
They're using really lead bullets still.
Yes, there's still lead.
And even the Army.
What do you think about this?
The Army has switched to a...
Orgasm gun.
The Army has switched to a bullet that is environmental friendly.
It's some sort of other...
It's not lead.
It didn't buy degradable bullets.
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
The family still has to pay for it.
So that we only kill humans, not the earth.
They probably got a big conservation tax break for that.
Yeah.
The idea, of course, being, you know, this is the way...
Think of the research that went into that.
Gentlemen.
How much money cleaned up.
Cleaned up for years and years and years.
Will be a clean war.
A war that you and your children can stand to fight.
An effectively deadly bullet, but yet...
You know, somebody had to not repent.
Easy to mop up after.
In order for that bullet to be developed, somebody had to not repent or quit their job or slack off.
That's the age-correct way of thinking of it, yes.
There was a point where somebody could have repented, quit their job and slack off, and then somebody else would have had to develop that bullet.
Said, no, sign the check and put it in my rectum right here.
Well, if I don't develop this bullet, somebody else is going to do it, so I might as well not repent, quit my job or slack off.
I got to tell you guys something.
I'll be known as the guy who developed the environmental bullet.
The environmental bullet.
Yeah.
You know, the guy in the Doobie Brothers who's supposedly a missile defense expert?
Bend over and spread them, baby.
Here comes my environmentally cool bullet.
Bullet.
Thank God I've been shot.
I can almost see the future of America as my life oozes out here on the sidewalk.
Thank God for the safe, clean bullet that just ended me.
Ended you?
Did I?
Did you end?
Did I end at that moment?
No, you know, we have a friend who was in a band who's kind of like...
This song is just important today.
Why aren't kids, like, marching and stuff?
For what?
Yeah, they're not shooting them yet.
Stop.
Once they start shooting...
You're thinking of the old America.
This is America Incorporated.
Right.
We don't actually...
I mean, come on, man.
Do I have to spell it out as many of my employers?
There are no disagreements in corporate America.
Come on now.
Get with the program.
Read from the same page and remember the talking points.
Point number one.
Things are better than they've ever been.
And worse.
All the kids know today is they want their job.
Well, that's all there is.
There's the job and there's...
Endless drudgery.
The life.
Well, sort of.
And the job and...
Well, the job.
I'm not gonna rock the boat.
I want the job.
Chaz, you told me you're not only gonna rock the boat,
that you were gonna rocket butt that boat right into another world.
Rocket butt that rocket boat.
I mean, I'm just...
You're getting wanted to go.
You're wanting to really climb on there and go to a world
where people actually think normal or something.
I don't know.
Yeah, definitely.
It's becoming very important.
To get off.
I mean, very, very, very important now.
Yeah.
I want to get off.
I don't want to...
I only hope...
Stick around here.
Exactly.
I just did build...
Buy a house in Cleveland.
I'm building my own Amsterdam.
Yeah, but you also built yourself a nice canal boat in your mind.
You know?
With the little hair and green thing in the front.
I'm also learning...
Foreign languages.
So that they'll let me go there.
Are you learning Enochian babble?
Well, I've been living in my house for five years.
And for five years, I've been installing...
Each day, I dig out a little area in the foundation area.
And put in another composite rocket motor.
So the house is about two-thirds now
completely surrounded and strapped with rocket motors.
So in another year or two...
But the timing is so fiendishly important.
I have to.
I'm so devilishly tricky to get every rocket to go off at once.
Mm-hmm.
You don't...
What happens if half of them go off and the other half don't?
Oh, you have to kind of...
You've got a tilted house, dude.
Really?
The Mish Fire is just going to send that thing...
Might end up in Arkansas.
Well, you would hope it would end up in Arkansas.
Well, I'm not middle of Lake Erie.
It doesn't matter.
As long as I reach seven miles per second in any direction, that'll be...
Even down.
I'll be able to get Earth orbit.
Chaz, I'm afraid...
You don't want to go seven minutes per second in any...
I mean, seven seconds...
You know, that speed in all general directions,
because that would be...
You would be exploding up if you were, you know, not ahead of direction.
It can't happen here.
I've been checking it out for a while, B.
I'm telling you, my dear, that it can't happen here.
Camtus!
RFA!
I've been checking it out.
Did it?
Check that out.
A couple times.
Yeah, it's happening here right now,
and as we watch the sun go down on our democratic freedoms,
the freedoms that we've taken for granted for so long...
Oh, no, but we still have all those freedoms.
They're even more convenient than ever, as long as you...
As long as you tow the line.
As long as you want what they want, you can have anything you want.
We want what they want.
What Bob wants.
I want what we all want.
I want a worldwide cataclysm.
I want chocolate pudding delivered to me by aliens,
and I want some female chocolate pudding delivered as frequently as possible,
as the old salivary glands can move.
Sometimes they don't move.
Of course, that's not the first part of it.
That's the end of it.
The first part is much more laconic and obscure.
I mean...
Well, that's more artistic, you know, when you're obscure and hard to understand.
That's more artful.
And, you know, Dave, if we were a little more artful,
we'd probably be getting paid a little better.
But instead, we're...
You just...
Low-grade showbiz clowns.
We might as well be the guys that sweep up behind the elephants at the circus, you know?
Well, we do that, too.
The dwarfs with the little pooper scoopers.
Well, we also do...
We do that.
Yeah.
I mean, at least I've been going back.
I don't know.
Some people think they're too good to work.
But, you know, as long as I'm getting a paycheck,
I don't mind what tumbles out of there.
I've seen worse things, and I've picked up worse things.
You've stuck your arm all the way up worse places than where that came from.
Yes, that is true.
I don't want to go into the grim details.
You tried to get your head all the way up into worse places, but I...
I was almost a microcephalic baby from that incident.
And I was almost returned to my native home in Canada
and buried alive there for the whole incident.
It was just...
I don't know.
In London, it struck a compromise.
That's in England, you know.
Dodger Stadium, it struck out.
In Munich, it struck first.
Take your head down.
Very interesting.
Chaz is trying to bring back the...
Rebellion of the 60s, which, of course, was actually a co-op.
From the very beginning.
Okay, you start.
The John Lennon glasses were trademarked before John Lennon was even born.
Well, Jack Kerouac and Cassidy and all those guys...
All planned out ahead of time.
...were actually mind-controlled for quite some time.
Yeah, but what good did it do?
It was early in the morning.
The energy was so, so weak.
The poor people below could hardly stand...
...to look up.
Their necks were craning, but still, it looked like it was...
Wait.
This is...
Dave, you're stuck in the 60s, man.
No, man, I'm not stuck in the...
Get with it, dude.
It's the 90s.
No, wait.
It's the...
The aughties or the zeros or the...
Yeah, it's the new...
It's the modern age.
What is that feeling?
It's contemporary.
It's new.
It's now.
It's when muscles rise up in your neck and the back of your brain tingles...
...like there's a little teeny...
...chameleon in the back of your neck.
What is that feeling when your shoes drop off as you're walking down the street...
...and they wave goodbye to you?
What is that feeling?
What's that blue stain in your undies?
Have you been keeping bad company again?
Have you been hanging with those who hang too far?
Yeah.
Today I bought a new car.
Today I bought a new horn for it.
Herb Alpert.
Yeah.
Sick thing is, Rowan and Martin's laugh-in was actually kind of...
...the hippest thing going at the time.
I can hardly afford to buy my groceries.
Horrible nauseas.
Possessed us in the morning.
First a chilling feeling that Dean was not going to go on.
His arms were too scrawny.
His ears...
Well, his ears were full of gray...
It's yellow matter.
Yellow matter's coming out of his ears.
All of a sudden...
Then...
Put out all the lights and play Robert Goodway...
No, said Bill.
...to like it.
I've been standing here for three hours with my panties upside down and no one's noticed.
I scream.
Dean hopped up about a minute convulsively, anxiously pulling on his arms.
It made me wonder if the college boy had thanked him,
or what he was trying to do with all strange, strange radio equipment.
Well, actually, it's an idol.
Would you mind saying that again?
Idaho?
That's frightfully interesting.
We've been...
Oh, I've always wanted to make a cowboy.
I mean, meet a cowboy.
Really?
I yelled across the river.
Well, you won't see me to...
Yeah, there was a mist and men are tonight,
and the streetlights didn't come on the freeway till Vine Street,
and me and an old friend were talking about Allegheny and pulling boats,
and there was people hanging themselves down steps, I guess,
but mostly good things.
Good things.
And, uh, hello, J.D.
Hello, Robbie.
Hello.
Hello, everyone.
Um...
My parents say I don't know what good clean fun is.
And they're right.
I don't know what good it is.
The spasms lasted for three and a half hours.
By the time we got Grandmother all quieted down,
she still had somehow gotten it into her brain that Grandma was going to...
Grandpa.
I'm sorry.
Grandpa was...
You had the right idea.
It's just a shame that polygamy never caught on among the married.
People of this country.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
They should have had more polygamies.
They can't help it if they're not tall.
Wah, wah, wah.
Hey, did you have a joke on Wirefin last week about holding pig meat in your nostrils?
Feeling that the long arm has gone through and brought back one that we could slip under the door.
Wah, wah, wah.
Oh, I couldn't have said it better myself.
Oh, yeah.
How about that?
Your name's in big lights up there on that marquee.
So is mine.
Yeah.
Now we had a number of circumcision marks.
Talk about history.
Some of them were covering our heart.
No, but there's a great party in 1537.
Nearly psychic circumcision marks.
Why don't we go to that one?
The kind of young men like to make that.
Oh, there go cues from that bit.
The marks are purely coincidental, and I think the problem was he might have fallen down before he entered the elevator.
No, no.
It's not the same guy.
This man was confused.
He was pointing and asking questions, and I just couldn't answer what...
I had no idea what he was talking about.
We really learned the three R's.
Reading, writing, and rhythm.
Specifics, barking, and playing with ourselves.
These are the new rules.
This is the new regimen for a new human race.
One that will not only conquer the stars, but conquer the...
And you'll be behind it.
Standing there, guarding, standing tall for America.
Really.
Man, that really moves me, Dave.
I'm so glad that...
It's just a tear gas.
You can't say such a sincere...
No, man.
It's a tear gas in the mind control, man.
I don't know what I'm saying.
I'm crying.
Oh, man, I...
Get it together, man.
It sounds like Mambo music.
You're on the air.
Come on, come on.
None of this emotional baloney.
Get it...
Hey, guys, you know, I was wondering,
the funny thing about doing a late-night show like this
and getting a lot of, you know, really out-there callers.
Last night, little Jimmy Spliff called three times,
and he was, you know, doing his own variety of rocket science.
But here at, you know, the Kingdom Dome,
there's a lot of complaints, you know.
We've had problems before,
but we're going to hang in there as long as we can.
I mean, as far as I'm concerned, the gallows have been built,
so let's keep hanging.
And nobody's going to talk about your shoes
or say that, you know, you left the eggs in there too long
or there's just, you know, some problem with you.
You know, everyone's going to just be cool with that.
Hey, who were you hot for on the Laugh-In,
Rowan and Martin Laugh-In show?
I liked Goldie Hawn.
Chaz.
Yeah, I figured you'd be the Goldie Hawn.
There was Judy Karn, which is a little cute English chick.
Nah.
I liked Joanne.
Joanne Worley.
Me too, man.
I was really into it.
I understand.
She was kind of large and kind of heavy-boned
and loud and obnoxious.
But that wide, wide, wide mouth just invoked...
The Queen of Hearts look.
You like that Queen of Hearts look?
Off with their heads.
I know.
And referring to your structures down there.
Yeah, I don't know what it is.
I can't put the two and two together.
Her laugh was just very infectious.
There's no doubt about it.
I wonder where she's at now and how large and old.
And she's in the old actor's home in Pasadena, California.
Sitting out in the backyard watching the Cupid pee in the pond.
Yeah, she's had her last turkey sandwich for today, though.
She's going back in sight.
For her meds.
Does that little boy ever finish peeing?
Or does he just pee that forever?
Keep your back to the wind.
Keep your hat tight.
Keep your sack in saddle.
Quedan tus cajones en el...
The rebel forces, this is the fucking Death Star, man.