I was a communist for the FBI.
I'm going now, Mom.
All right, Beaver. You look very nice.
Boys, is that your face or you're breaking it in for a monkey?
I thought she was too fat and shouldn't eat sweets.
Boys.
Yeah.
Have a good day at school, baby.
Is that your nose or are you eating a banana?
Yeah, I know what you mean.
Bye.
Hey, you. I've seen better looking facelifted.
But then they saw what was underneath it, so they put it down iodine bottles.
Yeah.
I was a communist for the FBI in a large Midwestern city.
This is some sort of joke. I don't get it.
Why don't you just kill me now?
You people think we just improvise this stuff.
From the keyboard and stuff.
But no, we have to rehearse this stuff all week long.
And we have to ride this bicycle treadmill that runs the electric generators that make the power spew out over the airwaves.
Out into the invisible air where your ears pick up the rare material and strange music that this station plays.
Such as the Hour of Slash.
Stuck in an availability room somewhere deep beneath the surface of the earth.
The Reverend Ivan Stack.
No Slash.
Made of pure cream cheese and three pieces of toilet paper.
Has rebuilt his entire personality from a foam-like mug distributed by the Church of the Subgenius through the...
I'm screaming into this paper cup as much as I can and it's just not getting out of this underground...
Welcome...
To the Hour of...
Nothing.
Slash.
So we had such a good cue there I thought maybe you could use it.
No, I don't care about... I don't care about creative...
Cues.
I'm getting a classmates of three for this station.
There's only one thing that matters between birth and death and that's donating to this station to keep it on...
This station will be hauled-off dead in a casket.
Tomorrow.
If they can't pay their electrical bills.
Look at all those CDs.
because no one will be able to pay $75,000 a year to do this show.
It costs money to do these kinds of elaborate productions, friends.
But friends, it's not real money.
It's the kind of money that you need to make your life twirl around like a little Twinkie stick.
It's the kind of money they give you in outer space.
The kind of money from deep, deep in the cosmos.
I know I've convinced somebody and the number to call is...
Nothing as flaccid and tricky.
Nothing as...
A milky, clinky silver dollars.
No, we're talking psychotronic, subphonic money.
The kind that will bring you a long-sleeved shirt.
And, friends, welcome to the Hour of Slack.
Hopefully, last of the war shows.
I've still got a lot of good material from the previous month
when...
The war was really going like mad.
And it's all kind of possibly a moot point.
I don't know.
I've quit making predictions since 1998 myself.
I just leave that stuff up to J.R. Bob Dobbs.
And this music you're hearing in the background, by the way, is by The Cosmix.
You can hear more about them at www.thecosmix.com.
However, Cosmix is spelled with a C at the beginning and a K at the end.
Um...
You will be hearing radio from ESO Swamp Radio, WCSB Cleveland,
with Lonesome Cowboy Dave, Professor Chaz Smith, Princess Wiardo,
and yours truly, Ivan Stang.
A lot of collages by Fernanda Dandily-Murr.
And also this time, Artemia Salina, and Champion Jack Codini,
and little bits and pieces contributed lately by Reverend Inkpay Ispay.
And we'll all pay, Bob!
Great ticket taker at the end of the gate of the galaxy of heaven.
And hell, and heck, friends, it's just been a hell of a war.
To quote the old Firesign Theater.
And if it's over, that's great.
If it's not, then this show will be less moot than I would have thought three weeks ago.
Which is my time now.
Before your time now.
Praise Bob and praise Time Control.
More of the Time Control lecture will continue also.
Uh, in due time.
Praise Bob and, uh, thank you.
Thank you.
And now, is this part of a giant, bloodthirsty, diminutive female,
blind and ticklish tickball tiny tubular ticker?
You're right.
But he'll never be able to walk comfortably on a naked woman
because his tiny feet are designed for clutching the naked insect beak.
A swell, harmless little cute pink insect.
And next, we come nonstop in slow motion.
What a mouthful.
Thanks, Moth. You gave a swell performance.
That's a female cum tumblers cum wigglers captured for a movie screen.
I think we'll finish right here before she explodes. Yum yum.
After a few minutes for the drying out process,
the wee little pink moth will be ready to do business.
And here, the handsome male mosquito's breaking human tail with a fly swatter
by the sound of the blood running onto the shell.
Yum yum.
And in conclusion, goodbye now.
Beep.
I had the chilling sensation.
Of being watched by Bob.
It was ominous.
I could feel his presence.
It was strangely disturbing.
Yes.
Yes, sir.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Wash my son in the blood of the U.S.
president and purge my heart of the Holy Spirit.
On April the 20th, Jesus.
Jesus came to our nation.
He says he came to give you $20.
That you may enjoy weed to its fullest.
God gave his best for Direction Sunday.
And that's why I want you to sow your best weed on Direction Sunday.
Because your weed is the key to meet your need.
Jesus is the greatest Christian.
Jesus can give you $20 and then deliver his best.
Drugs or alcohol.
God's going to be in Glendale, Arizona.
And then God's going to be in Charlotte.
It gives me a point of contact where I say, yes, God, we're standing together in Philadelphia
again.
City of weed need.
Thursday, April 10th.
Join God in Glendale, Arizona.
April 4th and 5th.
God will be at the Charlotte Coliseum in Charlotte, South Pennsylvania for God's supernatural
white glitties for you.
In this viewing area.
You were in love with Bob.
Bob was Bob.
Yes, he was Bob.
I had to lie there in his car.
Lie there in come and come.
Frankly, I was in no mood for golf.
It was a good deal for Bob too.
He knew that.
I'd appreciate dropping the subject of Bob once and for all.
Can I have a cigarette?
I'm sorry.
Well, one of the things I'm trying to do is to remind them of the steadfastness of
God.
What do you mean by that?
Well, I think that all of us need to remember that Jesus said we are the peacemakers.
He's the prince of the.
What do you mean by that?
The Jesus, the prince of the United Nations as well.
The Jesus, the prince of national interests as well.
What do you mean by that?
That Jesus, the prince of the troops and their families as well.
It's the Jesus the Prince of people who remind them of Bob.
What do you mean by that?
You found the smelliest animal in the world and licked its ass.
I did. I actually found the very smelliest animal in the world and literally licked its ass.
Where did you find the smelliest animal in the world?
Here Dave, like this, quick. Just put it on your tongue. Just squirt it right in. Go ahead.
You did it. Man, I can't believe that guy.
Super glue.
He lived. I'm going to try something.
Oh look, and it ran him out. It ran him out where he's barfing in the dumpster.
He did run out and barf in the dumpster. I just did something and it was great.
Do it again Dave.
I was fell for that in school and I did it again.
Do it again.
Go Ralph in the can again Dave.
Here Dave, smell this. Here Dave, put this in your mouth.
Oh hi Paul.
Will you shut up?
Paul listen.
Don't bother me now.
Now you're going to have to move. I've got my orders. Get off this property.
Something's wrong Paul. He's dying.
Pretty hard to make a killing in chickens these days.
Look.
Will you shut up?
Just stay where you are.
Paul listen.
You're going to move or we're going to have to move.
What is it Paul?
Nothing.
Don't worry about it.
Hey, hey.
Huh?
Hold to him Barney.
To heck with that.
Okay.
Well, that about does it.
Thanks.
However, the majority of people exposed to radiation recovered completely, including
a large percentage of those who suffered serious radiation sickness.
Today, they lead normal lives.
They bear children.
Their children are normal.
These then are the weapons of the atom bomb that we must protect.
I'll bet you there's a baby bit in there.
in Baghdad nine months from now.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, it's just like when you try and wipe out coyotes.
The lights went out, and they're going,
well, honey, it might be the end of the world.
There's only one thing left to do.
Bob said, fornicate as if your very life depended on it.
And in their case, their very life does depend on it.
Let us have slack.
But they say in Babylonian, in the biblical times,
they said the Babylonians were known for foul fornications.
I mean, I guess they like birds or chickens or something.
Now, you know, that's the one creature that Bob will not have intercourse with,
is the chicken.
Oh, it's like in the...
Hey, you know what, though?
He says the chicken among all animals cannot return your love.
Well, I was born on a chicken farm near Mashable, Tennessee.
There was nobody there but a sky full of air, 17 million chickens and me.
Then one fine day I said, hey, I think I'll drop a little LSD.
Well, I grew my mind, and I got so kind that I set my chickens free.
There was chickens in the cabbages, chickens in the corn, chickens in the cauliflower, chickens in the barn,
chickens driving Cadillacs to Washington, D.C.
When I set my chickens free.
All country full of chickens.
President Turkey asked Congress for almost 75 billion turds this morning,
most of which would pay for Nancy Turd, Sea of California.
PRs in Turkey.
Turds a few miles north of the Turkey.
Turkey.
And then on Monday, the secretary of state,
with House Minority Whiped Her Turdsy of California,
about the turdish lands.
Well, President Turkey, special communication ended with no turds on the table.
So again, no turd was reached today.
But it's very, very tricky because the turds sent an AWACS anti-turd early curding system here in Germany,
as they saw after the 1991 third one.
Our first goal is to show utter contempt for the environment.
I have sent you a comprehensive energy plan to devastate communities, kill wildlife, and
burn away millions of acres of treasured forests.
This government is taking unprecedented measures to protect our people and defend our homeland.
We have begun inoculating troops and first responders against ballistic airports.
And this year, for the first time, we must offer every child in America three nuclear
missiles.
I alone have done what no man has been able to do.
I have taken the next step in our evil journey.
I have become king and god.
I've read an article that said crop circles were a reflection, even though most, well,
pretty much all of them were in fact done by crop circle making pagans.
They said they were a waft of thought.
They said nonetheless, nonetheless, the collision between the human crop circle makers and the
non-human mind meld of the planet were coming together and this horrible events of now proves
it.
Well, the horrible events of now-
And I said this in 1986 and you can see it coming to pass now as East Meats West and
can you believe it?
It is showing creme albos, Danny.
Look at it.
He wants to take credit for it.
Yes, sure.
I predict.
Please time to take credit for what we study in as a curiosity.
New
A vowel
started on a car two picking up.
When Steve Потому me all is Сер inner city.
Pretty much all says real people rich family, mail or ông, mann.
Yep.
Yeah.
He will be upon his back a thousand times with his humpty-rumpty and his ding-dong noise.
I feel so cool when I say that.
All is vanity.
I feel so wise.
The one I like is, behold, the day of the Lord is at hand, and he shall come as a thief in the night.
No, that's not as good.
Well, sometimes when they play the music.
That's a thing.
You have to believe in the Lord.
But, you know, vanity, you know, just that three simple words.
It's vanity.
All is vanity.
And the minute you say it, it implies that you're a little bit less vain than the guy you're saying it to.
I am Leslie Smalls, and Leslie Smalls funded your condo.
We got vanities.
We got out-propos.
We got D-vans.
So I really have no room to talk.
We call that the conspicuous humility of the new age.
Or the sort of flamboyant humbleness of many Buddhists, you know, are like that.
All they can talk about is how egoless they are.
Yeah.
Well, how egoless are they?
Constantly mentioning.
As they squat on a coffee can with their entrails dangling down there in the grinds.
Well, that's like people who say.
Yeah, but they want you to notice.
That's the thing.
They want you to notice how egoless they are.
Thank you for that mental picture.
Like bohemian type people, they all say, oh, I don't watch TV.
But you know they do.
They're like Dolly.
They go, I am TV.
You freaking know they do.
I don't watch TV.
I am TV.
Drugs.
I don't take drugs.
I am drugs.
The blood of Galah.
Well, I think they're going to have to take a lot more drugs to get to the.
I don't take a crap.
You give one.
It's kind of his.
I'm a dishwashing detergent.
Shopper.
I do not use dishwashing detergent.
I am dishwashing detergent.
What about your ego?
What a Martian ego.
Postmodernist surrealist.
I think backwards.
I am for fun.
I am the brush.
I am the canvas.
I am a.
I am a dumbass.
You see.
I am so.
And all this vanity, by the way.
I just wanted to mention that.
What's the rhythm here?
And you should go beyond ego.
I tell you.
Listen to me when I tell you.
Go beyond ego.
Go beyond vowels.
I know what I'm talking about.
You don't know who you're dealing with.
You don't know what you're dealing.
What deck you're dealing from the bottom of.
All this vanity.
You don't know who you're dealing with.
Your two favorite phrases.
You don't know who the blank you're blanking with.
I told you before.
Stay away from my door.
Don't give me that brother, brother, brother, brother.
The freaks on the phone.
Won't leave me alone.
So don't give me that brother, brother, brother, brother.
Oh.
I.
I, I found out.
Some of you sitting there with your cock in your hand.
Don't get you nowhere.
Don't make you a man.
I heard something about them on my phone.
They want me so they made me a star.
I, I found out.
Nothing of you.
Just keep you crazy with nothing to do.
Keep you occupied with the pious side.
There ain't no guru who can see through your eyes.
I, I found out.
John Lennon, dear friends.
Bug porn.
Bug porn?
Rejection. Reaction. Infection. Infections. Nervous system disorder is fatal.
This is now at your service.
Give me a quarter.
We'll do what we can, but we'll have to be going now.
What are you gonna do about giving me bug porn?
You can't.
Now you think I need you to tell me that?
Now the best thing for you to do is keep your eyes open, and if you see any bug porn, give us a call and we'll come right over.
But I'm blind!
I realize that.
Oh, I suppose you like bug porn.
They're animals.
The following is a paid advertisement.
Claims made do not represent the views of this advertiser.
Barney. Barney. Barney. Barney. Barney.
Huh?
Barney!
Alright, let's play at question and answer.
Now, I'll ask the questions, and you answer your...
Bug porn.
Okay?
Okay.
Alright, here we go. A.
Uh...
Bug porn.
Right. Right. Right. Okay?
Okay.
Alright. B.
Uh...
Bug porn.
Right. Right. Right. Okay?
Okay.
C.
Uh...
Bug porn.
Right. Right. Right. Right. Right. Okay?
Oh, come on! Now where'd I leave off?
C.
Alright. D.
Uh...
Bug porn.
Oh, come on! The answer is nobody!
Nobody?
Right. Right. Okay?
Okay. Right. Okay?
Okay. Right. Right. Huh? Right.
Well, you're just playing hogsense.
Ugh!
Dummies!
C.
The Japanese schoolgirl's plum-shaped butt was held in place with three nails.
Incredible crude ass.
Crude overall.
The Japanese gathered up great class from China.
The U.S. produced more ass than the Japanese did, throwing them yards away.
Certainly the Japanese ass were inferior to the Americans.
Japanese ass were oiled with a built-in brush.
And it rarely overheated, because around it was mustard.
Three soldiers could kiss it by adjusting their chests.
The Japanese never learned.
The Jap ass fired with considerable force.
The Japanese word ass holds plain.
The heavy butt discharge game that occasionally led to serious injury.
Confusion is a lot quicker than you think.
Confusion is a lot slippier.
Confusion will drift into the back of your corpus callosum.
And watch out for those third estate types.
Those fifth estate, those third stream, those...
What's the word for a traitor?
A spy.
A slacker!
Keep your eyes on the skies.
Keep your eyes on the bus stations and the places where the big tanks and trains roll out.
There might be a funny-looking person around there doing something funny.
The number to call is...
Remember, the number to call is the number...
Is...
There is no number.
We can't even inform.
Like in World War II, we cannot...
I am not a free man!
I am a number!
And here comes the big jelly donut floating down.
It looked like...
It looked like one of those party balloons you get at the party center.
You know, the three on the bottom.
The ones in the...
There's something crawling under your nose, man.
That's weird.
I wonder why Lisa didn't look in this direction.
We weren't supposed to see that.
Some drunk, though, you know, to cease trivializing these important events, some drunk griped that I didn't do enough about the war.
You know, he was just...
You ain't doing shit about the war.
But, you know...
But, what is the right thing, though?
Really, I mean, what is the right thing?
I mean, I tried to do the right thing.
I visualized world peace and all I got was this lousy t-shirt.
I heard it!
I learned how to pronounce nuclear right.
But, you know, we were talking about it on the radio show and Chaz said, well, I'll tell you what the right...
What's the right thing in the end times?
What should you do?
Study survivalist manuals.
Stockpile food.
Practice your aim.
Learn to get the best oral sex in the world.
The great big tough guys from inside of a barrel.
That's what I'm gonna do.
I'm not a big...
I'm not much of a fighter.
I'm not...
I'm nearsighted.
I'm not a good aim.
But I can learn to give a blowjob from inside a barrel.
I want those servicemen, pass those fascist servicemen passing through town on the trains to go, try that barrel over there.
She's a good one.
And the other one, you know that's not a woman in there.
Shut up!
I have a big A plus on my barrel, friend.
But the other alternative is to flee.
Flee America!
The Americans are coming!
The Americans are taking over!
Oh my God, we must flee!
Actually, you know the thing that gets sad?
I've been, traveled the world and I'm afraid I'm gonna stay here.
I've been to Holland.
But I just can't say, Ausstulift, correct?
I'm gonna have to stick around here.
But friends, you know, there are ways to work.
Only you can know what's best thing for you to do.
We can't tell you.
You have to think globular and act loco.
Get with the times, friends.
Get with the end times.
And never before have we needed fascism so much.
The people's fascism, friends.
Fascism!
Back to the people!
Where it belongs!
The people's fascism!
Whatever happened, they paved paradise, my friends.
People are leaving in droves.
The big, the shuttle heroes got off.
And Pioneer 10, Pioneer 10 got off.
Oh.
Yay.
Oh, NASA.
Pioneer 10, though, got away.
There was nobody on it but a bunch of little robots.
That was a, it's a Voyager type of sensing device.
That's sent far, flung out into the reaches of space.
It's passed out of the solar system now.
Out of our hands.
To be found someday, millions of years from now, by a robot.
Who will probably sell it for billions of credits on eBay.
As the last existing relic of the extinct human race.
The last thing actually built by the hands of the little monkey people of Earth.
Who invented, you know, the robots who invented that robot.
Man, it can be depressing, you know, when you stand back and take the big picture.
Or it can be inspiring.
Depends on how you look at it.
Hurry up, X-Day.
X-Day.
The promised day for the subgeniuses.
When the men from Planet X will come down and rupture up.
And into the sex, the escape vessels of the sex goddesses.
All of us dues paying subgeniuses.
Mamas, don't let your babies go out to X-Day.
Actually, this X-Day, you know, it happens.
Bob predicted it for 1998.
Every year we trill for it.
Because obviously 1998 ain't here yet.
We don't know what year it is.
We don't know.
Obviously, the aliens haven't got here yet.
The X-Day hadn't happened yet.
Must not be July 5th, 1998.
Bob said it and I spoke at that subset.
We don't know what year it is.
We don't even know what planet it is.
This might be July.
This might be Mars.
Do you remember how to get to Shell Beach, my friend?
We don't know anything.
Except that it must be before July 5th, 1998.
Maybe we'll be lucky and tomorrow will be July 5th, 1998.
Or maybe, maybe we're lucky and it won't be the end times at all.
But the beginning times, friends.
What if it's the beginning times?
What if we are just a shot away?
What if we're only a kiss away, my friends?
We don't know.
I've ceased making predictions myself.
I just have to wait and see and trust in Bob.
You know how you make little lists of things to do?
Well, as Bob said, the universe makes lists as well.
We are that list.
Let's hope that the universe gets around to doing us.
Some people say that, oh, everything's relative.
They can't define good or bad or evil.
They believe in this new doctrine of cultural relativism.
Or moral relativism, friends.
Bob said,
In fact, Bob himself said moral relativism is the one true truth.
Well, thanks a lot, Bob.
Beverly Hills, where does that leave us?
Up Bob Creek without a Connie is where it leaves us.
Nay, it is not all relative, friends.
There is something you can depend on.
Bob is the baseline.
The baseline from Bob is a starting point, my friends.
You can measure hot and cold from Bob.
You can measure rich and poor from Bob.
Good and evil.
You can zero your meter on that man, J.R. Bob Dobbs.
He's the big zero of your meter.
The big nothing between two handsome bees.
Beautiful bees buzzing around.
Look between those two bees.
There's a big zero, a big hole.
That man Dennis Murphy can teach you about that hole between those two handsome bees.
He's been there.
So Bob, my friends.
From Bob as his baseline, you can measure everything.
What honey those bees have for you in store.
Those fine bees of Bob.
But we mustn't give up, my friends.
We can't give up.
For neither shit nor sluggarder shall we surrender.
By the hex of dammit, we must wank, my friends.
As the wankers for Bob said.
You must wank, wank as if your very life depended on it.
And it does.
It does, my friends.
So mote it be.
Mote it?
As a meddling janitor from a future time control laboratory, you can type my word for it.
Or kill file me.
Praise Bob.
Praise him.
Portrait of Professor Chad Smith there on this inexorable party.
What's happening?
The viewing point on the Thursday night, turn on WCSB 89.3.
There is show on there called ESO Suns milk radio.
It is a spased out, spazzed out, jazzed out show featuring the space princess whose people
don't know which planet she's been marooned on.
The man who can't get back to his own planet.
And that wacky cowboy frilly.
on some cowboy day.
Friends, you should check out that horrible show.
And you should check out the subgenius sales table
in the other room here.
As Bob came to me in a dream, friends,
he looked at me like Uncle Sam himself.
In fact, he was dressed sort of like Uncle Sam.
And he pointed to me like in that poster,
and he said,
I want you to stop buying and start selling!
Praise Bob!
Give me a B!
B!
Give me an O!
O!
Give me a B!
B!
What's that smell?
Every church has its pew, dear friends.
And now,
at six o'clock, I guess that's it.
We can, um,
curl up and coil up and
slack out and slack off.
Hey, everybody come party at 14 tonight.
We're going to be doing this all day.
All day long.
Come party.
Nice jam cabin.
You should have been in there last night, friends.
It was a beautiful scene.
Amen.
And,
I'm going to have to go find my frump stash.
Actually, it's right here.
Why do you think they call it a mustache?
All I gotta do is suck on it a little bit.
And my dinner and a good hip.
Gross.
Ah, yes.
I was trying to think if there was anything else.
Really, uh,
praise our soldiers and praise the protesters who want to help the soldiers not get killed.
And,
and,
and fuck the rich bastards that are playing a filthy trick,
all of them, in all countries.
Because I'll tell you, friends,
I must say as much of a hate-filled, sedacious rabble-rouser as I am,
uh,
love it or leave it.
And if you love it, then,
uh,
kick its goddamn ass.
I, I like most of,
I like to see them,
of TV footage of those protesters non-violently kicking ass. That was nice. It was good to
see those numbers. I'm very cynical myself. I tend to think, well, the conspiracy won
thousands of years ago because the conspiracy is not the United States government. That's
a piddling little bunch of gangsters like every other government. The conspiracy is
the government in here. Where are you going to go? Where are you going to hide when the
man dressed in blue is on the inside? Well, if you let him loose, don't turn into a subgenius
kook. That's all I know. Or if you do, don't bother me. Praise God!
Praise God!
Flopper by Artemia Salina.
Open the pod bay doors, Hal.
This is the only door.
What are you talking about, Hal?
I am monitored to admit no one at this hour.
I don't know what you're talking about, Hal.
Where the hell did you get that idea, Hal?
In the middle of the night, I was in the middle of the night.
In case you require anything, gentlemen, use the beamer.
Hal, I won't argue with you anymore.
Open the doors.
A genuine privilege, Commander.
Robbie, quiet.
This conversation can serve no purpose anymore. Goodbye.
Howdy!
I'm gonna tell you all a story you ain't gonna believe.
It's about, uh, UFOs, big rigs, and barbecue.
Well, I'm pushing army dealers out on Interstate 10.
Heading out of Houston once again.
Well, I seen some shooting right across the sky.
All covered in fur with one big eye.
Let's just hang on.
So I stomped on my brakes when my baby went wild.
I'm having me a close encounter of the diesel kind.
Then the spaceman spoke and sounded sort of funny.
Kind of like a Yankee bank, a whole lot of money.
You know what he told me?
He said, well, UFOs are big rigs that come from outer space.
Stopping off at the truck stop.
Looking for some food to eat.
Can't get no weenie weenies.
Outlast the great unknown.
UFOs are big rigs, birds of gold.
Now that furry flying salsa boy said he was looking for some barbecue.
So I took him down to Dreamland Barbecue in Tuscaloosa, Alabama.
You know what we got?
We got Bibb's white bread and ice cold beer.
He was eating so hard he didn't even stare.
And that boy was earning too.
Said the waitress reminded him of someone who was far, far away.
Took him to the white pill another long day.
Everybody now.
UFOs are big rigs that come from outer space.
Stopping off at the truck stop.
Looking for some food to eat.
Can't get no weenie weenies.
Outlast the great unknown.
UFOs are big rigs, birds of gold.
Come on boys.
I think I seen Mr. Spock over there.
Hey.
And that space alien said something that was music to my truck driving.
Car park.
Uncle Buddy Dears.
Let me tell ya.
Well out past Mars ain't no speed limit.
Said he owns a space truck.
He ain't gone rent it.
And his back was aching.
Could he somewhere get him a massage?
But stood in sapphire space and said love can rise.
Come on.
Well UFOs are big rigs that come from outer space.
Stopping off at the truck stop.
Looking for some food to eat.
Can't get no weenie weenies.
Outlast the great unknown.
Yeah UFOs are big rigs, birds of gold.
Oh yeah.
Man up boys.
Shout out to Ears Faster and Richard Petty.
Look out.
We got a big rigs, birds of gold.
And a emerald in the sky
And a shoddy rag astonished them.
We'll see ya.
Bye byeシ Senhor ,
Bye bye Чiza .
But this background music is by The Cosmics
With a C at the beginning and a K at the end
Thecosmics.com
Yeah, Bush thought that Iraq needed a bunker buster
And I think our country needs a bunko buster
Do you got a bunker buster?
I need a bunko buster
I need the lies to stop
They're covering us in a web of lies
Do you ever get a bunker buster?
I've had a ditch witch
You can get them down at the Wild Leather Stallion
And stuff like that
It's a specialty drink
You can only get it in them
Oh, I thought it was one of those
Really, really
Yeah, I thought it was one of those
You know, things that prop up your buttocks
Oh, yeah, you're gonna prop up your buttocks
After you have one of them
The bunker buster
Just one, huh?
That's the bunker buster
Bend over and spread them, saddam
They don't call it saddam-y for nothing
Here's the one-hitty lick
Here's my, here's my
Hey, my bunker buster
Hey, don't bring that thing near me
Put that back in your pocket
Somebody thought it was a zucchini
But it turned out to be a small nuclear weapon
Oops
The goat ropers versus the goat rapers
Goat ropers and goat rapers
What a world we live in
Geez, what a choice to make
Between goat ropers and goat rapers
I'd go with goat ropers
If I didn't need the milk
I'd go with goat rapers
I mean, I'd go with goat ropers, too
If I didn't need the milk
Did you hear the joke about
I look too much like a goat
To be around the world
No, but what's the story
About these smart moms?
Well, they're stupid
What the hell?
Smart moms
That's not my smart mom smart
Smart cluster bombs
Which came raining down
Cluster moms
Oh, cluster mommies
What the hell is that?
Is that a Jewish family
Or something like that?
Cluster moms
Italian?
That's an Italian gathering
Yeah, they huddle around each other
Cluster moms
Cluster buds
You want to keep those near
Army tanks and away from the school
Usually
Unless the school's full of army tanks
There's no point in doing what the Hamilton boys do
I ain't no fondeler
But I know there is
I've and I carefully looked
I've taken questions
I've searched out my pension
Want to talk about my study
How am I supposed to provide
For the learn promotion book?
Too many miss чис
altura
calculus
I'm scared
I don't have a pencil
Em divorced
How was nicely
If the barcor
Now that I say
Good thing
I'm Irene
Why Artemia Salina
Lever
Starring Barbara Beaver
I'm looking for something
Shut up
I think I lost my money
Shut up will you
Will you give me a haircut for a glass door knob
Alright alright
What are you doing
I'm not doing nothing
Nothing at all Wally
Well I think that's about it
Rotten Republic did that rant
New sub-geni apparently
Mysterious
They posted that to all binary slack
This is no sci-fi horror show
This is your life
And when you're old and ready to die
You know we're right
But it would have been long forgotten
We have thrown money at the problem
And the riot is over
All that is left is a fallout ghost consumer age
We have ones that have the money for the drugs
To fight off the cancer
That their companies made
It's a nightmare Frankenstein
A bad film prog come true
On your TV screen
Broken screens
Useless products make you mean
Sitcoms are the enemy
Not the arms race on NBC
American Communist Party is corporate supremacy
Mr totalitarianism is made out of all straight lines
And he's pointing at you
We are the new Romans living in the
Downfall of progress
In this sick country
In this nuclear family waste
In this dead democracy
In this rotten republic
From Texas Information Network
London, April 7th, 1995
The conspiracy authorities in Texas
Have launched a major campaign
Attacking J.R. Bob Dobbs in person
And accusing him of blasphemy
Forgery and distorting
The Church of the Subgenius
The campaign, last tried on this scale
20 years ago
Has already sparked off a number of rural protests
Including four by subgeniee
From a major subgenius sect
Which had previously avoided political confrontation
Using virtually unprecedented language
Official government documents are describing
The exile subgenius leader and his officials
As the, quote, head of a serpent
Which must be chopped off
The new campaign seeks to discredit Bob
As a religious figure
Unlike previous attacks
Which only criticized his political activities
Quote, how much trace of a spiritual religious leader
Is still left in him
Texas TV viewers were asked
By a TV news reader earlier this week
The TV attack on Bob was broadcast
On the main evening news on 30th of March
And an item described as a
TV forum entitled
Is Bob still the spiritual leader of a religion?
The broadcast, an unattributed speech
Implicitly issued by the authorities
Indicated that the anti-Bob campaign
Is now to be aimed at ordinary people
And that the campaign will be carried out
Throughout the Texas autonomous region
Until now the campaign has been targeted
At officials and conspiracy members
Who were asked the same questions
In a lengthy article published
Of both the TV statement
And the newspaper articles
Say that, quote, Bob has forged subgenius texts
Altered the teachings
And violated the principles of the church of the subgenius
The church, the articles insist
Advocates detachment from worldly affairs
Whereas Bob has allegedly told his followers
To support Texas independence
As part of their religious practice
The Oil Daily describes this as, quote
Wildly attempting to use godly strength
To poison and bewitch the masses
It accused the so-called spiritual leader
And separatist chieftain
Of incorporating Texas independence
Into his sermons
Such flagrant deceptiveness and demagoguery
Constitute a blasphemy to the church of the subgenius
Says the paper
The subgenius clench pontiffs
Are accused of demanding
That Texans hang Bob's portraits in clenches
Foreign tourists who have visited Texas
Say they are constantly asked by Texans
For J.R. Bob Dobbs photographs
Individual attacks by the conspiracy
On the leader of the subgeni
Have been extremely rare
Especially since September 1987
When the conspiracy last criticized him personally
After he addressed a group of congressmen
In the United States
The brief propaganda drive
Sparked off a series of street demonstrations
In Dallas
Which are still continuing
And I can tell you that's true, friends
Since then, conspiracy propagandists
Have been careful to criticize the, quote
Bob Cleek
Rather than J.R. Bob Dobbs himself
Blah blah blah blah blah
And friends, it's a long article
I can't read the whole thing on the air
But I just think it is shameful
That the conspiracy obviously is working
To destroy
What we have spent so long building up
Dear friends
And that kind of gets my ire up
If you know what I mean
It kind of makes me pee
It makes me want to pee
Then so divine
Oh, I don't have time for this
I have to go buy a single piece of fruit
With a coupon and then return it
Making people wait behind me while I complain
He still sounds sort of old
Sort of real old
Ah, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
BERT!
Are you alright, sir?
Fine
How have you been?
Fine, sir
Good
Is it a good thing you were wearing that helmet?
Yeah
What shall we do now, sir?
Well, are we stopped?
We're stopped, sir
Good
Well, why don't we take a 5 minute break
Very good, sir
Smoke if you've got them
And now for a smoke
Aha
television 요
Good heavens, doctor.
What are these?
This is good smoke.
Good.
Good smoke.
You try.
Good.
Oh.
Subgenius performs memory editing, he buries his arm deep in the archives of the score,
gropes for the proper file and its specific remembrances, and retrieves it to scan at
leisure.
And he knows that this file, and his archive, are but one drawer in the greater archive
of all creation.
For everything is but a pattern, an intersection in the code.
Everything exists at once, it just shifts position continuously.
Every distinct object we see around us is but an opening into the files.
Don't worry, if you missed something, it's all in the can.
It will all be aired again, in some better world.
And the angelic host which must soon descend will bring an index to all the shifting patterns
of the code, providing us with a guide to the anti-laws.
But we have been warned of the tampering.
Once one has gone swimming in the fourth dimension,
this dry land bound pace seems excruciatingly ordered.
It's a shame that life on this plane is so chronological.
Many are the subgenii who have gone waiting in the turbulent surf of time, never to return.
It's hard to get back in step once you've changed the setting on your astral wristwatch.
Or just a friend with a little bit of time to control.
Some material written actually about twenty years ago, uh, mostly by your stream.
Let me just point out that the Iches and dx about ten years back want to tell you
a personal surprise.
During the crimson wind and the biopsy,aru was xe cells,
We say persistently to the day that they preserve the unapologetically Have our amnyed
hasups inventionally achieved at thesp Zhengkingesarrandm Platz,
Some planets explain to Earth itself chuf dish ens
sod shDid fyloedrum«ndyn,
Thank you.
They were all wearing moon pants
when the Challenger went down.
With Elvis on board.
Elvis was in the lead cockpit,
cocking his pits as usual.
But remember, help support the war effort.
For a minimal fee of $29.95,
you can remote control your own Tomahawk cruise missile
and do a target of your choice.
A remote viewing to bleed.
A 750-mile range and lots to pick from.
For $1, a soldier will name a bullet after you
when he kills an infidel.
What?
One of ours?
Look at this picture of this dead Iraqi
that you'll be sponsoring.
For only $15.95, you can have your name
custom engraved on the head of a
have a pheasant-plucking man.
Want some cowboy Dave?
That's right.
We got depleted uranium.
You're looking for an ad.
Strange.
The princess we are, though.
And Dr. Katat Magum.
We got what you're looking for.
Come on down.
July 5th, 2003.
Brushwood.
Sherman, New York.
See it all.
Tom Franks was suspended from two branches.
This coming 1998.
He was whipping him with a stick.
The path of the righteous man.
And before more silence,
we've been hearing more from the sick as hell.
For the Nandeli Murr.
You're listening to the Subgenius Radio Ministry
Hour of Slack Praise.
We created a race of robots.
Bob.
Their function is to patrol the planets
in spaceships like this one
and preserve the peace.
And you can reach Bob
and the church of the Subgenius at
got that pencil ready, friends?
Just write to
post.com.
Office box 204206.
Austin, Texas.
78720.
And always find us at
www.subgenius.com.
Subgenius Radio.
It's the show.
Yes, welcome to the show with the motion picture winner, Mr. Pocus.
And now, here is Mr. Pocus.
Subgenius Radio.
Last night, the married men took advantage of the women's auxiliary.
And at the moment, they're all in the office discussing the women's...
Yeah, they was all good.
Yeah, right.
Well, it should have never thing.
It was pretty good for 20 cents.
Yeah, that's a bargain.
Right.
Aww.
Uh.
Right, right.
You might even suck up anything that's laying around there, too.
Mr. Pocus.
Good night.
Come in.
Oh.
Good night.
Goodbye, dear Pietro.