Hello! I'm scared! Let's hear a new echo!
Good evening and welcome to the subgenius radio hour of slime.
This is the end of the world.
The end of the world will come in July 1999.
Perhaps in the form of an atomic holocaust?
Such a forewarning of ultimate doom could generally be dismissed out of hand.
The lighthouse will confirm an order.
The first target will be the initial landing place outside Los Angeles.
Those missiles have all gone off!
They pushed all the buttons!
You know what that means, don't you?
Either we fired first and they're going to try to hit what's left,
or they fired first and we just got our missiles out of the ground in time.
Either way, we're going to get hit.
So what are we still standing around here for?
Of course, since all human life has been under the surface of Earth for 16 years,
there was no actual loss of life in the sense we know it.
What's this?
What you get?
What the hell do you expect?
What do you expect?
Pretty red roses.
White puppy noses.
Mammoth proper hoses.
It is more like it.
Oh!
The strange worshippers pull at their faces.
Despite himself, a strangled cry escapes Brent
as he sees the ghastly heritage of atomic radiation.
Hey, Tony, let's have some.
Get out of here.
I mean, hell, this turn, the other cheap thing can be carried a bit too far, you know.
Hey, neighbor, let me give you some advice.
The Russians are about to pulverize us if I sleep tonight.
That is if the crazy Arab social rights don't get us first
and the fire will rain down from the sky.
The fire will rain down from the sky.
People die.
I love you.
The flying saucers are my friends
because they're so nice.
I'm gonna see them again and again.
Is that before or after the bob pills?
The Bob Pills.
And we are back.
The Bob Pills are this stop-and-go game for all types of loveierenness or for the investigating
inなら huh Huh fuck Yeah more and more
not just used to teaching something
no
were just
216-687-
If not, if not, if not, if not.
Call any time if this
is on the air.
Well, hey, Dr. Sinister, how's everything
going? Well, it's
been how long since I talked to you,
so that's a long story. And don't be
a stranger, Ragnar.
I know. I'm a stranger.
Yeah.
We guessed it was you. That call
from Kentucky was Ragnar.
Yeah. 859
represent. Yeah.
Well, the good
news and the bad news is that
I'm not as
in kind of a bad financial
situation as I am with the house.
Oh, that is good.
But the bad news is I will have to sell it.
Oh.
And then what?
And then I
severely declutter and I take a
smaller life into a new
apartment somewhere. But I've
come to the conclusion that I'm just not
ready to own a house. And
it came to a realization
with three things. When
my dad died and basically left
me with nothing because senile dementia
basically destroyed any inheritance
that I would have gotten for keeping
the house in good condition.
Then
the house started falling into
disrepair. And then
things that are major repairs like
a new heating and air conditioning and a new hot
water heater, things like that
just start stacking one on top of the other.
And I don't have
barely enough income to just keep
utilities going in my house
anyway. And
keeping up with the property tax also
every year became an
issue when I had medical issues last year
and had a nervous breakdown from working
at my new call center job for
a major
smartphone company. Let's just call them that.
Oh, smart, eh?
I'm sorry to hear that.
And
then I just
came to the realization one day.
That I don't have any kind of slack in my life
anymore because this house just
is a slack vampire to me.
The house that fed on slack.
It's a slack trap.
Exactly. It
became a slack trap.
Just make sure that you have a slack pad
to land on or in
first before you do
anything. Honestly, I have no
idea how people can afford to own houses.
And even living in a place like Cleveland where
the cost of living is relatively low and property
values are relatively low compared to other parts of the
country.
I would need to make literally twice as much
money as I make now to be able to
comfortably afford a house.
You're paying for the financial errors in the banking
system. That's what it is. You're paying for all the
annals.
I'm talking about basic maintenance.
Just basic maintenance.
And all that. And property tax
and all that. It's like,
yeah, I don't think I'm ever going to own a house
in my entire life. Ever.
Here's the good part of it. I talked to a real estate
agent yesterday who also happens to
be, you know, a radio
host of a major radio
program here in Kentucky.
Now that is a coincidence.
Well, he actually showed me the true value of the
house and the land. It was even less than you
thought.
No, actually, you remember the $75,000
that my dad stole from the home
equity loan?
Well, he
managed to borrow
$75,000 behind my back
on property that he never owned in the
first place.
Goodness.
That's some heavy horse trading
there.
Yeah, he actually
got a major bank, and I'm not
going to name the name,
out of respect, because I don't want to get
sued necessarily. Well, that's a good thing.
Yeah, but he got
a major bank to sign off on a loan
on property that was never in his name
to begin with, and
left me holding the bag for the loan.
But here's the deal. When I
turn around and sell the house,
which is actually going to be more than
the amount of $75,000 that was
borrowed against it,
I'll hold that whole amount in
escrow to where I can't touch
it and the bank can't touch it.
And I'm going to say, you want that
$75,000? You show
a judge that that loan document
exists. Then I'll release it.
And you heard it here first.
All of Northern Ohio is
inspired by your story. Your
inspiring story, Ragnar.
We want to be like you.
You're giving away your plans there, man.
You're tipping your hand.
Be like Elvis. Give your house away.
But how many people are listening after all?
What if I gave it away as a
habitat for humanity restore?
Imagine the tax refund on that one.
Why don't you just incorporate
as a church?
Why don't you just incorporate as a church?
Well, here's the even better
part of it. Princess Wee,
do you remember me showing that beautiful
photo of that beautiful woman in Montreal, Canada?
Yes, I do.
I may just as well
cross the border and go live with her
if Trump gets elected. She's not really a woman,
Ragnar.
It's a thing! It's a thing!
Not man! Not beast!
Thing! No, that was a woman.
You're thinking of someone else.
It's always good to
explore personally and make
sure you have bought a
pig in a poker.
Real quick, who's been that?
Princess Wee knows. This is someone that
I'm going to build my own pleasure with
on July 5th.
On July 5th.
Yes.
On July 5th, 1998.
Mm-hmm.
Yes, July 5th, 1998.
It's only just around the corner, kids.
It all boils down to that. Yes, so rushing toward us
like an express train seen in the distance
which looms up suddenly at the last moment.
The wagon load exploded.
I heard that person before
and that was a radio voice.
Is that an actual person now calling
from the Clever area?
It's just part of our art and cleverness.
No one would actually...
do that in today's real estate market.
Oh, I'm...
Yeah, I mean, yesterday
I was the little dog that was moving around
the Monopoly board.
Today I'm Rich Uncle Pennybags.
Rich on what?
Rich Uncle Pennybags from the Monopoly game.
Oh, Rich Uncle Pennybags.
I'm sorry.
Did you get yourself a monocle and daddy warbucks?
Ah, Uncle Pennybags.
Also, I have LeBron James to thank
for giving me a little flat...
Peter J. Pennypacker.
For the free tacos.
Pennypacker fortune.
You got free tacos?
Free tacos?
Yeah.
Everybody got free tacos.
I'm moving to Kentucky!
Yeah!
Free tacos!
And reclusive billionaire
John Bearsquare Tipton.
I want a free taco.
Hey, have you had a chance to make a...
I was in a movie the other day
at a major taco company,
which I'm not going to say the name of.
Yes, it wouldn't be...
It would be proprietary information.
Exactly.
But it was all thanks to...
Hey, man, I think...
It was all thanks to LeBron James winning on the road.
You should...
Rockdoll, if you have not yet seen it already,
you should look at some of the...
I saw some pictures of downtown Cleveland
during the victory parade on Wednesday.
I don't think that...
That's exactly how Lexington looks
when we win an NCAA championship.
There were one...
There were 1.3 million people
in downtown Cleveland.
1.3 million,
which is like three or four times
the population of the city itself.
Yeah.
And only...
Were there any couch burnings?
No.
There were no couch burnings that I know of.
And only one guy got shot.
Only one guy got shot.
We're gathering that pay.
In the Ancule.
Right.
Yes.
But yeah,
Sportsland has officially annexed Ohio now.
What is Sportsland?
Well, he is Governor Rocknarr.
He is the governor of Sportsland.
Administered by Governor Rocknarr
after the econoclasm.
Governor Rocknarr will take over Sportsland.
Exactly.
As we know,
these things are set in...
Etched in brass.
It's a...
It's a wall around Sportsland
and they're changing paperwork.
A wall of sheer binding energy.
Tuxes out of America now.
Force that cannot be transcended.
You know,
enormous energies
are going to be brought into place.
This planet has only a small amount of energy
which we get parasitically
from our central star,
the heating system.
But this is by far
different from the universe's
most awesome energy.
Which our friends,
the X-ists,
manipulate.
Are we going to see a Tegxit?
Are we going to see a Tegxit
before X-Day?
No, not until after Hillary Clinton
gets elected.
We're going to practice Earth's tip.
Returns from the Antarctic Expedition.
She'll be back any day now.
Earth out of solar system.
Hey, let's...
Actually, we're getting another call right now.
I hope you guys will hang on here
because I think we're about to be joined
by the one and only
No Money Mark.
Hello, you're on the air.
Hi, how you been?
Everybody?
Well, we'd be okay.
Better than Ratnar, apparently.
He's engaging in some
high-finance, jittery poker.
I'm on top of the world right now.
Like James Cagney in White Heat?
Exactly.
I mean, I'm not afraid anymore
about what's going to happen to the house.
That's good.
It's good not to be afraid.
The markets hate uncertainty.
Have you ever drunk Moxie?
Do you live in a foreign country?
I have drunk Moxie
and I know where you can still get Moxie.
I think you can get it in New England, can't you?
You can get it at Galco's New World Grocery
in Los Angeles.
I have shipped of the Moxie.
But who wants to go to Los Angeles?
Well, you have to go there
because they have every kind of soda known to man.
That's not exactly making it sound any more appealing.
Yes, but with 20 bucks you can come back
Do they have Ale 8?
Wow.
They have Inca Cola.
There's a couple of specialty gas stations
in Texas that have that.
Well, then you have to go to every run-down
rag-tag gas station in Texas.
I'm going to do it.
Oh, no.
They're not rag-tag.
They're far from rag-tag.
They're a very nice little country store type place.
With coolers, with heavy glass doors,
filled with sweating cans of soda.
Made around the United States
and some Canada and some Mexico.
Well, I guess that covers that.
I'd love to be a Mexi-Coke right now.
Mexi-Cokes are awesome.
Mexican Cokes are pretty good.
The ones that use refined sugar.
They're in glass bottles.
Yes, indeed.
They sure will.
Yes, but then Mexico has its own
delicious soda.
Delicious flavors.
Not just Coca-Cola, but Squirt is made
on the old machines in Mexico.
And RC Cola.
They make Tab down there,
if you remember Tab.
I remember Tab.
Yes, they never stopped making it.
But that, too, is all available
at Galco's Old World Grocery in Los Angeles.
Plus all the Mexican sodas themselves
are quite delicious.
The Pina and so forth.
The Penafiel.
Yes, you must have very vigorous aisles
of lemon juice to consume this heavily sugared,
foaming, surging beverage.
I'm sure Hal remembers that Fanta was invented
by Nazi Germany.
Of course.
And Fanta.
The Fanta Menace.
Fanta was quite popular in the desert
when I grew up in Arizona.
Yes, there was a Fanta bottling company in the desert.
Exactly.
Few people ever ventured near it.
And those who did were not seen again.
It is a favorite bevy in Great Britain right now as well.
Fanta.
Mm-hmm.
And then in California,
we have Shasta beverages emanating from the Deros
under Mount Shasta.
You drink that stuff?
Do they have Werner?
They know what that is, right?
Yes, we have Werner's, Werner's Diet, and so forth.
Werner Heisenberg?
The Reeds Company makes the best ginger beer,
including the ultra-strong ginger beer.
If all these obscure soft drinks are still being made,
why can't you buy them nationally?
Because there's a conspiracy plan
Distribution.
They're not just about soft drinks
and the people who drink them.
They are now considered responsible for the epidemic
of obese children you see marching down the street.
Not exactly marching.
Well, they're sort of undulating.
Puffing and puffing.
Yes.
The worst for your teeth would be things like Coke or Pepsi
that have high quantities of phosphoric acid in them.
Yes, the wonderful phosphoric acid.
Ph of two.
Carbonation is not quite as bad as just adding phosphoric acid to something.
I mean, like, Pepsi has a Ph of two.
Well, here's the thing, you know,
if there's ever any kind of outbreak of some kind of, like,
Andromeda strain-type virus that turns everybody else's blood into, like, powder,
we would be the ones that would survive.
That's happened to me.
Because our blood would be at different acidity level.
Well, the thing is, these, uh...
I, I, I prefer taking different kinds of acid.
The human body itself contains powerful corrosive acids,
which are contained in their proper...
area.
Uh, and Coca-Cola...
Oh, up until then.
Oh, sorry.
It's a healthy, uh, belt.
But, but, uh, belches and burps occur in nature and in cosmic physics,
where they create planets, nebulae, and galaxies.
It depends on the, uh, the, the depth and the resonance.
That's always been my opinion of the difference between a, a belch and a burp.
Yes, we have learned how to make ever-bigger booms here on our planet,
but they are only baby burps,
compared to what the universe can do with its vast, explosive force.
Can I add, uh, that it has nothing to do with the subject currently,
but the South was, had many, many different varieties of soft drinks, and still does.
All available at Galco's Old World Preservation.
There's not quite as many as there used to be, but there were, there were, every town had its own soft drink.
A South out of America now.
But now they're trying to force Po folks to eat kale and health food.
Uh, they replaced all the candy bars and vending machines in San Francisco with kale chips and snacks.
So, if a diabetic is having a bad moment and tries desperately to get a candy bar,
sorry, buddy, we got health food.
It's for your own good that you can expire on the floor in front of the candy machine.
No, not all, San Francisco maybe, not...
There's a supervisor named Scott Weiner who's trying to, uh,
Oh, God.
He's trying to eliminate all, anything that isn't health food as long as poor folks, uh, consume it.
Oh, Scott, next thing you know, next thing you know, Scott Weiner is gonna have,
is gonna have vegetarian rules that you can't feed meat to cats.
You may laugh, but you'll see the name of Scott Weiner as he edges closer and closer toward the governor's position in the state of California.
Oh, Lordy. Is he one of Hillary's superdelegates?
He was a weiner.
He sounds like it.
He's on the Hillary side, but he's still in contention with James.
He's on the Sanders side, who got a surprising amount of votes, and there'll have to be a runoff election.
But so much for californicating politics.
You don't want that on this show where we're talking about cosmic things.
Like how the Exists power their interstellar space vehicle.
How do they power them, Dr. Howell?
Well, how are spaceships powered?
You know, that is one of the two problems.
One problem is too far, and the other problem is not enough power.
I thought they were fueled by mutilated cattle tongues.
They can be fueled by anything, because all you need to do is confront matter and antimatter to get the giant explosive force that will push your vehicle through the brain.
Hey, let's pause for a moment here. It sounds like nobody Mark has a comment he wants to make.
What do you guys think of the Brexit?
Of champions? Wheaties?
Mr. Brexit?
The solar system out of the galaxy now.
My personal take on it, I don't think the UK ever should have joined the EU in the first place.
I don't think they ever really had their hearts in it.
It was Napoleon's idea. The common market. United Europe.
There's two reasons why the EU rejected the UK's admission into it.
No, that's the other way around.
The plucky British decided they wanted their shillings, pence, and all that stuff back.
And the pound has been devalued.
It's lost a good deal.
It's going to get ugly. It's going to get ugly for a while. It's going to cause a lot of economic and political chaos for probably a decade.
It's probably going to take a decade before things get back to normal.
British clockwork toys are now affordable again.
I thought it was already ugly.
More people are going to come to my golf course. They'll be able to fly to England and spend their money here.
It's huge.
Because the economy is going to destroy thanks to Obama. I think it's a great idea. But it's all Obama's fault.
The beauty of me selling my house is I can actually move to Amsterdam now if I want.
And you can start that Chef Boyardee franchise once you get permission from the chef.
Oh, don't encourage him to do that.
At this point, I've got nothing holding me back from Lexington anymore. Why not?
But Lexington and Concord? What about the rude bridge that arched the flood?
Are you going to make America a cheese grater again?
Their flag to summer breeze unfurled.
Cheese grater?
I just got that. It took two and a half hours.
That's where the embattled farmers stood that fired the shot heard round the world.
You'll leave that for the double Dutch of Amsterdam?
No, in a heartbeat. Because there I'll just be a person and I'll be looking down upon.
Well, if you stick your thumb in the dike, perhaps you will be suitably...
Ouch!
Oh, you had to go there.
I can see you being a Dutch boy, Ragnarok. I can see that.
You can start by cultivating the haircut.
I wish I could do that lurch.
Well, I always use the term Dutch boy as...
They've had to go in a different direction than building dikes because the sea level has risen so high now that they're going more towards the little Venice routine.
Pardon my French, but you'll be in Dutch if you don't put some English on it at the finish.
See, I always use the word Dutch boy as an analogy...
Hey, Dutch boy!
As an analog of...
...of a fag hag, you know? I'm a straight male and once upon a time I realized that like half my friends were lesbians.
How many of them were Dutch?
None of them, but...
See, I know some Dutchies.
I know they might have had some Dutch ancestry, but they were all as American as apple pie.
They were a bit worse than a Dutch fag hag.
I remember...
Now we're casting insults around.
Let's have another Friendsgiving in Amsterdam with Xavier Hollander. Why not?
If she's up for it.
I think she would be.
She was nonplussed.
Nonplussed by this not-American holiday happening at her bed and breakfast, but willing to do it.
Well, she had that American manservant who knew how to cook a turkey.
They knew what a turkey was. They barely knew what a turkey was.
The whole world doesn't celebrate these American holidays.
It's like a chicken, only bigger and less flavorful.
Yeah, but they're only Chip Boyardee.
Oh, that would be...
Yeah, that's...
Thank Cleveland for that.
The Dutch are dying for Chef Boyardee pizza.
Thank Cleveland for Chef Boyardee.
Yeah, exactly.
They're $18.97.
But they have cod stands.
Chef Boyardee would be like one of those fancy type restaurants.
You can go to a cod stand and get a cod sand.
Which?
A noodle.
We could use pool noodles and cod pieces before we have our ritualistic armor fight.
It's all delicious.
I'll have a Coney Island whitefish sandwich, please.
With a couple of Yankee Doodles and devil dogs on the side.
You want the Marines to be on the side?
How about curly fries, Larry sandwiches, and...
And mohash.
I can't stop imagining the cod piece with pool noodle.
Well, see what you did?
You've contaminated Princess Wee's mind.
This is starting to sound like noodle implements.
Yes.
And like all fertile things, her mind is readily smelly.
A noodle ready to be fried.
Fertilized.
Speaking of, we should pay honor and respect to someone that...
I don't know if any of you remember that, you know, Crazy White Sean.
He passed away a couple of years ago.
Oh, yeah.
Unforgettable character.
His act made you literally pass out in horror.
What happened to him?
Did he take one shard in the face too many or something?
I think it was him eating the light bulb that kind of did it.
Damn.
Oh, that's nothing.
Uncle Fester ain't got nothing on him.
You can eat the light bulb as long as you chew the glass really well.
There's one bucket of bricks hanging from his...
I saw a guy like...
I saw a guy pound nails into his sinuses.
Yeah, my circus friends do that too.
And there's some on NXT that can be seen.
You must have met the Enigma at some point.
He has to pull them out with a pair of pliers.
And they always have like that little tiny bit of brain at the end of them.
Is the guy who has the full body blue jigsaw puzzle tattoo?
He's dead?
Oh, man.
I got to meet him about 15 years ago, actually.
It was weird.
He was just hanging out in Cleveland because he was doing a Halloween show
down at the amphitheater in the flats.
And he was just hanging out at a bar one night.
And we ran into him and had a good time.
And he was very unique.
And we hung out with him the night after his show.
Actually, the day after his show.
What was that?
Akhenaten coffee shop we were at, I think.
Named after the heliocentric pharaoh of ancient Egypt.
It was the one by the Cannabis Museum.
By the Hash Marijuana Museum.
Yeah.
I don't remember that place.
You weren't there.
If you did remember.
We were special guests there.
I remember that.
Yeah, we were the judges.
Yes, we had a grave responsibility.
Barney's in Amsterdam just hooked us up with all that stuff.
Yes, we had to march around from bar to bar, huffing it.
We were not allowed to rest in any particular place.
I remember it well.
Oh, it was awesome.
And it felt like being in a Grand Theft Auto type video game
where you have to go.
You know, make these little achievements
and collect all 27 coffee shop rewards.
Make a little achievement over there
and you have to clean it up.
And were you all given T-shirts and a beer?
Oh, absolutely.
Well, we were given samples,
which we were not allowed to bring back over the border.
So we had to give them to our eager hosts.
It was like a real cup d'or, right?
Yeah, really.
A gold cup of, you know, okay.
Yes, I didn't pray that this cup...
be passed from me.
But it was the Cannabis Cup, of course.
And we were there in time to see the bizarre Christmas preparation
that the Hollanders have with Black Michael and Father Christmas.
Black Peter.
Black Peter, yes.
We have to let our listeners know that this, you know,
Habsapropzipulops, or Frop, is not cannabis.
I already covered that in an earlier part of the show.
It is something far, far better.
Yes, it is.
Medical cannabis is now legal in Ohio.
It's the 25th state.
Yep, medical weed is coming to Ohio.
Well, that's good.
And, I don't know, I have really mixed feelings about it.
I think it's kind of...
You know, it's so obviously, like...
I don't know, that's a topic for another day.
Whatever.
But one thing I do have to say, though,
is that portions of the following broadcast
will be objectionable to some members of the audience.
Therefore, WCSB advises listener discretion.
The views and opinions expressed on this program
are not necessarily those of the audience.
Those of WCSB or Cleveland State University
or anybody with their head screwed on straight,
for that matter,
this is a special edition of Synesthesia.
I'm your host, Dr. Sinister.
We have us right now joining us by phone.
We have Governor Rocknar of Sportsland.
We have No Money Mark.
We have Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
We have Dr. Hal.
We have Princess Weardo.
We have the Reverend Ivan Stang.
The gang's all here.
We're getting the band back together.
There are people in most countries
who would like to live in the United States
or the Dominion of Canada
where that good auger coal is sold.
The citizens of our free world
are the envy of every other country in the world
because of the personal freedoms that we have enjoyed.
Why then doesn't every other country
enjoy such a level of personal freedom?
One answer is that although people might be
enjoying these personal freedoms,
they'll vote for whatever dumbass they choose.
Now, I'm going to be your dictator.
Exactly.
And that's how they sell their lie to the people.
Yep, it's orange in all two true stories.
It never changes.
It's been that way for a lot of people
since 1776's struggle that's continued ever since.
Ever since primordial humanoids
thrust their chests out
and dominated by brute force
in the council meeting
around the pounded Earth mound,
Earth's own politics have taken a familiar shape.
But we subgeniuses will move
into a completely different realm
and leave the country.
Quarreling humans adrift
on their own disintegrating world.
Yeah, well, now they're builder baggers
and all the rest of their...
Not baggers.
WCSB.
There is no way to move through space
without the annihilation of matter,
anti-matter,
because even the hydrogen-helium reaction
of the sun is inadequate.
Not only do you have to get up
to an unthinkable speed,
then you have to stop also,
which is an annihilation.
It's an entirely different suite of problems.
Well, just use the inertial dampers.
Well, the problem is that this anti-matter
cannot come into contact with matter
without creating the explosion.
But in our universe, in our galaxy...
Which is why you have the containment field
around the anti-matter core.
You have to have that plasma container bottle, yes.
But our own galaxy has fountains of anti-matter
erupting out at various places,
engaging active creation.
Two-bedroom jobs.
In the universe.
Perfect efficiency.
Who needs anti-matter?
The total control of matter to energy.
Gravitational wave drives.
So you could take a piece of tongue
or a piece of old shoe leather
and have enough to force a planet out of its orbit
with that particular...
The problem is when you jump the battery
on those spaceships,
you've got to be really careful.
Well, that's why Scotty was always worried
on Star Trek down there.
If I give out any Marshall Blue!
Exactly.
I cannot change the laws of physics!
Every time the Starship Enterprise's warp core
was about to lose its anti-matter...
Only the writers can change the laws of physics!
Scotty would eat another secret snack
out of the refrigerator down there.
Secret snack.
Indeed.
And who gave Anton Yelchin the red shirt?
The red shirts were worn by the engineering section.
It has nothing to do with people
who are left behind on planets to die.
That's popular mythology.
Gold shirts for...
Administration.
Red for engineering.
Blue for science.
I'm just going to come right out and say
that I do not care for the Star Trek reboot...
at all.
Yeah, they had to tear down the whole
previous Star Trek universe.
Anton Yelchin is not Chekhov.
He will never be Chekhov.
He's dead.
He died in a recent freak accident.
I'm aware of this.
His car crushed him.
His own car.
It was the first ever to have that happen
as a result of that recall.
Well, um...
The original Chekhov was put in Star Trek
because they thought he was like
Davy Jones of the Monkees
and would bring youth in to watch the program.
Boy, now that you mention it,
I do see the resemblance.
Yes.
Yeah, like Davy Jones' locker.
That's the same Harry suit
everybody has to wear when they're playing.
And pretty soon,
any time anybody was injured or captured,
it turned out to be Chekhov,
the chipmunk-faced Russian
who the entire script had to divert
to pull back.
A Russian was always wounded first.
You're right.
Remember?
Yes, it's true.
You know what?
I hated the Jar Jar Abrams version of Star Trek.
Aw.
I hate Jar Jar Abrams.
Well, I thought it was rather...
But Anton Yelchin was actually pretty good
in those movies.
Mm-hmm.
But now we've seen the last of him.
Definitely great casting
to bring Scotty in
as the hero of
Shaun of the Dead.
Right.
Especially now after the Brixton
of the British Empire.
The Brixton of the Union of...
You know, the UK and stuff.
When the Scotts break away,
then where's Scotty gonna go?
He's gonna be...
Yeah.
Well, he's already with the angels.
The beauty of Star Trek now is...
I think we need not worry about that.
...the original universes
that it existed in.
It becomes its own universe
for whoever wants to believe in it.
Vulcan is out of the Federation now.
Are you out of your Vulcan mind spot?
Well, the fact is that the universe...
You bloody nose picker.
It was...
Previously,
this universe was destroyed
only to create the current universe,
but that doesn't mean
in the give and take
of Benzedrine-laced script writing
that the old universe
can't later be determined
to exist somewhere.
So we have the contrived scene
of old Star Trekkers
fighting new Star Trekkers,
just the way Superman
tangles with Batman.
Something which actually happened
in more than one DC comic.
Like the one
that I took from the
Bulldog auction last year.
Lex Luthor teamed up
with the Joker
and Superman
fought Batman.
It seemed as if the world
was turned upside down,
like when the British
had to acknowledge
the American victory
at Yorktown.
We all remember the song.
We all play it.
It's a tune
when I'm in the bathtub.
It's a song of our own defeat.
Our own smelly...
People mistake Hal
for his current human form,
but right now,
he's the guardian of forever.
This isn't even his final form.
That's right.
I'm in transition.
See my gills?
He has his own beginning
and his own ending.
Sorry.
Well, look,
I was just trying to explain
how when anti-electrons,
which we call positrons,
meet electrons,
there's a whacking great explosion.
This is what our friends,
the Exists,
are using to come here now.
They are...
going to enter our solar system
in less than 24 hours.
And by July 5th,
they will be hovering
over the landing field
where the eager subgeniuses
are turning their anxious faces
upward at the spinning shadow.
And how those saucers get towered
is they actually harvest
the souls of the human pinks.
The matter is the soul itself
and the antimatter
is the hatred within that soul.
That's how the Exists
power their big ships.
And that's how they use
their own weapons
to destroy them
and save the world
for the rest of us.
Lovely, beautiful,
educated subgenius.
What a sad way to put it.
It's true, though.
You have to destroy the world
to rebuild it anyway.
The largest explosive power,
as I have described,
is from the confrontation
of matter and antimatter.
But science has also...
Actually, it's a matter-antimatter.
It's a matter-reaction
that causes the continuous burning
of Bob's pipe.
There's a recent theory
that there's something
even more horrible
and even more powerful,
which is called
zero-point energy.
The power of absolute vacuum.
Ask Dr. Howell, please.
Dr. Howell, tell us,
what is zero-point energy, please?
Zero-point energy,
according to some,
if you had a vacant pickle jar of it,
it could boil away
all our oceans
in three seconds.
A vacant pickle jar.
It is the power
of absolute negativity itself.
It's the nothing.
It's too much for humans
to have control of.
Fortunately, they're never going
to get anywhere near there now.
Catastrophe might indeed follow
if we could figure out
how to capture
and exploit vacuum energy.
So we don't even have to worry
about the matter-antimatter thing.
The only thing that can stop the nothing
is to give the Empress a new name.
Unless our son decides
to go haywire
in the next few days.
Called the Luck Dragon.
It could happen, too.
Sure.
It could just decide
that it had burned up
all its fuel
and then suddenly swell up
to a grotesque size,
immolating all the inner
rocky worlds,
including our own.
If it happened at night,
we would see the moon
get super bright
all of a sudden
and realize our life
was to be measured in hours.
Honey, what a bromantic...
What a bromantic...
Now, if you're on that side,
you're protected for a bit
by the rocky bulk
of the Earth itself
from the solar storm.
And that does take
eight and a half minutes
to get here anyway.
I love subgenius pornography.
And there'll be plenty of that
at X-Day.
Yes, we will be titillating senses
you didn't even know you had
as you reach your newly found
evolutionary potential.
Like pollywogs
in old Ziqua's pond,
at the last minute
we will find ourselves
developing unusual
new supernumerary structures
and organs of unknown purpose.
Now, you know,
there's another possible side
to all this.
Earlier, Dr. Sinister,
you were mentioning
the good shepherd
and what happens to his sheep.
My brother is a shepherd of goats
and I asked him last time...
Why a goat?
Because they're so tasty.
What happens to the goats
after you sell them?
And he said,
I choose not to think about that.
And, uh, friends,
isn't that how Bob regards us?
He just doesn't even want to...
He's going to get us
to those saucers,
but, you know, when you...
Well, wait a minute.
Now, what happens...
What happens next?
And, well...
He loves us so much.
I prefer not to think about that.
The lust and slackfulness of Bob
is not necessarily shared
by some geniuses.
He knows of the awfulness
and the hedonism
of the entire unifracture.
When everything goes to...
When the goats get eaten...
Or whatever.
Or milked.
Perhaps cheese is made
by the exes of a cow.
There's a lot of things
you can do with a goat,
especially if you've got
real big boots.
Yes.
That's right.
And you can use them
as a lawnmower.
Have some dirt custards on me.
You don't need to use
a gasoline-powered lawnmower
at that point anymore.
The lawnmower?
Goat?
Do goats?
Mr. Natural,
do goats eat cans?
Why, yes, my boy.
They certainly do.
They do eat a lot of things,
but not cans, right, Hal?
Well, yeah.
You put one down in front of one
and he might try it.
He might ruminate upon it.
Being a ruminant,
he might chew thoughtfully.
Eat a nice, thin Ale 8 can,
probably.
You know, it's just like
the circus bros
who do eat broken glass.
If you chew it up
into small enough parts,
it gets coated with mucus
and it just passes
right through you.
Similar does the goat
with his stereotypical can
and the other objects
which he eats.
Even humans are subject
to a condition
known as pica,
where for some cause,
rooted in an unknown
psychological aberration,
people have been known
to eat inedible things
and create boluses
or bezoars in their stomachs.
Eating string, fabric, dirt.
Stones.
Yes, yes.
Reverend Funny Night
made a whole bicycle.
He's supposed that's where
Crazy White Sean's soul came from
and he's supposed that's where
his soul's gone back to.
Is that of a goat?
Well, it may have gone
into another organism
of a higher or lower
category.
Yeah, it could be
like a real high goat.
Like, you know,
the meta-goat.
They all start out
as zygotes.
That's right.
Yeah.
And end up as perigotes.
Do you still play video games?
I'm sure you do.
A stangor, right?
Uh, yeah, yeah, of course.
Yeah, sure.
Yeah, yeah, right.
Do you have goat simulator?
Oh, yes, I certainly do.
I have goat simulator
in my phone.
On his phone.
All right, now let's not
commit a hate crime here.
Actually, goat simulator
is awesome
because it's just
the most random,
free-roam,
and bug-filled game
there is.
It's really bull-dodger.
And the bugs are what make
the games so much fun.
It's a very surreal experience.
Exactly.
We watched an expert
goat simulator player,
Reverend Bucky Argyle,
in Germany.
Hi, Bucky.
Hi, Tanya.
Yeah, I think
he really had,
he could do a lot of things
He could get the goat
to the top of the skyscraper
in no time at all.
Oh, it's easy.
And bug people off
of the top and so forth.
That was really,
really so...
Oh, the fun is
you can take the random pinks
that are at the barbecues
and just drag them
to the sacrifice pit.
Oh, really?
I didn't know that.
I really haven't played
it much myself
because there's a lot
of monsters
that need to get killed first.
But, uh...
You can get,
you can get a jetpack
for yourself
and just fly around everywhere.
Oh, the goat?
The goat gets a jetpack?
Yeah.
It makes better sense
for them than a human.
I can't even think of goats
right now
because there's a crushing weight
on my forehead.
It reminds me...
And I can hear these voices
from outer space
crying and yelling at me
and trying to get me
to do things.
And I just refuse.
But I still can't resist.
It's so much for you,
space bullies.
Yeah, I was on
the sub-site the other day
and I was back on the
uh,
uh, old Mac page
which for stuff
that you had
if you had system 7, 8
or maybe 9.
Faith and Begora.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Those, uh,
those ancient games
are really wonderful
on those emulators.
You can, uh...
Yeah.
They only take up
about 4 kilobytes, too.
A whole centipede
or the original Donkey Kong.
They're the size
of a text file.
You could fit them all on a...
You could fit every one
there ever was
on a floppy disk.
Yeah.
Yeah, Rocknard gave me
a floppy disk.
It had the emulator
and about 40 games on it.
It was long.
That was like 20 years ago.
You know, I probably have
some stuff on floppy disks
going around
that has been lost forever.
I don't know how
I would be able
to read them now.
I, I,
all of my
old computers
still work.
Oh, wow.
So try me.
They're all Macintosh,
so...
You know what?
My old,
my old Windows 95 computer
probably still works.
My 1984 classic Mac
still works.
I can look at...
I can...
You can put
all of your system
and MacPaint
and MacWrite
and all of your data
on one floppy disk.
Product placement.
And no RAM.
But then how do you
get it off that computer?
Oh, oh.
Another one.
Well, I think we're
starting to run out of time.
Well, that's when you have
to buy the $7,000
external floppy disk
so you can have
a second floppy disk.
I've got...
As far as I know,
I've still got stuff
that can read those old things.
I had to resurrect
the parts of the book
Revelation X,
which had been laid out
by Paul Mavridis
in Pagemaker 1.
And I was able to
force evolve
the whole book
up to InDesign.
No, no.
It was a move upwards.
The funny thing is
everything...
I had the right fonts.
I had everything in place.
And it worked completely
except the...
the kerning.
I had to figure out
what kerning adjustment
to make
so that the pages
were exact duplicates
of what they had been
20 years earlier
in 1994.
Hopefully you saved
everything in Adobe PDF format.
In a what?
Adobe PDF format.
Well, our last book
was actually delivered
to the printer
as a 250 megabyte PDF.
What'll I think of next?
And when I went into
OfficeMax today
to get the X-Day brochure printed,
the young lady there
could work with the PDF,
but they had evolved away
from the ability
to make a copy
from a Photoshop file.
Photoshop was just too old time
and she couldn't do it.
I had to lean over the counter
and go, no, no, scroll down,
scroll down.
I'm sure she was
appropriately grateful.
No, as a matter of fact,
she was surly.
And resentful
that I knew how to work
this machine at her office,
you know, at her workplace.
Have you ever heard of pride, dear?
I, a subgenius,
have never, ever,
I have heard of it,
but this is a feeling
I have never felt,
for I am the most humble
and egoless
of all prideful creatures.
I read on, read on, read on.
And as Brinwickle once said,
when it comes to humility,
I'm the greatest.
Right, exactly.
No, actually, actually.
Nobody's more humble than I am.
No, no, Dr. Howell,
truly you are the most humble.
I am more humble than you.
Great.
In this shell.
Well, of course,
one who claims humility
has automatically screwed the pooch
because you violated the rule.
And remember,
practice it all in your closet.
We're not going to do that.
Nobody can see you.
Not out in the street
where you can be thought to be
a whited sepulcher
containing all manner of uncleanliness
with a clearly whitewashed exterior.
Amen.
Do not...
Oh, by the way, Doc,
Reverend Stang,
I gotta say,
as someone who worked at OfficeMax
for almost a decade,
I'm sorry for the low level
of customer service you found there.
You're fired!
Oh, is this on?
You're fired.
No, you're fired.
Gentlemen, please, please.
No fighting in the war.
Push, push, push.
We're all fired right now.
At least we want to go home.
Well, there's no going home
for some of us.
We are on our final flight path,
our ultimate trajectory.
It's a one-way trip, baby.
Coming in for a landing.
But how many years can you say this?
I mean, it's just...
As many as it takes.
Come on.
Yeah, yeah.
What do we get with the program?
Be a sport.
I'll try.
I mean, are you going to ask
the Jehovah's Witnesses that?
Yes.
Is it Jehovah's One's Witnesses?
They won't even blush.
Jehovah's Witnesses,
as we know.
Jehovah's Witnesses
defense attorneys,
in this case.
No, Jehovah One
has lost his marbles
in the continuum long ago.
Is the evil...
Well, not evil.
No, not necessarily evil.
And not good either.
He's just a senile lord.
He's just kind of the insane space deity
that the laser project has to signal home
to Jehovah One's parents.
He still threatens this Earth,
but he knows no better.
Yeah, your son is actually kind of going crazy right now.
No, the sun is still on its same orbit
around the Milky Way that it's been on.
It shows no sign of deviating from that.
Well, he was a baby, and now he's all of a sudden...
I forgot.
Also, he was in an assisted living facility.
Well, now, don't confuse the different
Trinitarian parts.
They all fit together nice and neatly like this.
They snap into place, and then you have the Godhead.
Easily accessible.
It's a laser beam signal, a tachyon signal.
Coming from God knows where.
The fountain of creation.
No, God knows when, actually, because tachyon,
traveling faster than light, would come from...
Self-sufficient.
...a head in our future going backwards in time.
He's trying to explain to us about tachyon particles right now,
which goes over the tachy...
...going backwards in time.
Yes, it is, because, after all, they are entirely theoretical.
But let's say your tachyons do exist.
Let's say that.
Are we really to believe that there is retrograde movement
backward in time from these bodies?
Right now.
I think that's all...
...wishful thinking.
...that there has to be an anti-time that goes in counter-clockness
to our normal time.
Yeah, but if there is...
If there is tatter and anti-matter, then there is time and anti-time.
And that is staying?
How do you suppose time control is managed?
Exactly.
You know our galaxy is hungry, ready to gobble us all up.
And wherever you have gravitation and falling, you have time.
We have staying as well.
Wherever you have gravitation and falling, you've got the Reverend I.
In a minute there is time for decisions and revisions, which a minute can reverse.
What?
He's laying the blame for gravity on you, Grandpop Bob.
Just because I answer the mail at Bob's factory doesn't mean that I'm Bob, okay?
But primitive peoples make this confusion.
I'm like one of the elves that worked for Santa.
Yes, well, once again...
We're Bob.
Bob don't ever change.
Always will be Bob.
With Santa Claus, we have the same problem or condition that we see in the insect kingdom,
where one large organism is surrounded by many small ones furiously working and supporting
the central one.
These others are miniatures of the first but sexless drones, and only Santa Claus itself
produces innumerable progeny.
But in our world we have deceit.
And that means that one of these little tiny small elves could actually be Bob himself,
making the other elves look bad, very bad.
Not intentionally.
Not on purpose.
Well, he's unintentionally making Bob look bad.
It's an epiphenomenon.
And besides, we swore to stomp out Smurfs generations ago.
Well, if we're going to stomp out Smurfs, we've only got six minutes left to do it.
Well, Santa...
Reverend Stang?
I have a question for you.
Is there a Jehovah Two?
How many Jehovah's are there?
Yeah, right.
There's an infinite number of Jehovah's.
That's what Jehovah is.
He is an infinite number of deities that live in an infinite number of universes created
by the infinite number of choices that you make throughout your timeline.
He's on dope.
A really good one.
Remember, beauty is balance.
Old Kentucky prop.
Our galaxy already has started to pull in the large Magellanic cloud.
The Milky Way grows and evolves by the second.
By swallowing smaller galaxies.
And sometime fairly soon, in cosmic terms, the galaxy of Andromeda is going to collide
with ours.
Weeeee!
Yes, Santa.
I can hear it putting on the brakes now.
Ah, there are no brakes, unfortunately, for anyone.
God, don't give galaxies no brakes.
Don't give nobody no brakes.
They'll just turn into kind of a blob galaxy.
Well, they will reform.
They'll reform, of course, all according to the laws of gravitation.
Mm-hmm.
Just as there is a Big Bang, there is also a big collapse that comes into it and creates
another Big Bang again.
The universe has been reformed.
Yes, it's time we got off this treadmill of absurd...
I can't believe that you're accepting...
You always want to get off after a Big Bang.
Yes.
It comes with the territory.
So to speak.
I can't believe everybody's so accepting of all this.
Hey, I have another...
...because you were written smote and low.
I need to announce another joke.
I have a lot of dibs I have from X Day.
Here we go.
This is not a national park this time.
Is this McDibs or what?
Well, you know, when...
Giga dibs or giants...
Start that...
I know you're claiming the Rijksmuseum.
About...
Yes.
No, yeah.
Go ahead with the Rijksmuseum.
Yes.
I reserve for myself the original manuscript on which Sir Isaac Newton predicted the end
of the world from biblical evidence for, I believe, the year 2035.
Ooh, good one.
Yeah, I want that because it'll look funny someday.
Unless the world does end in 2035, in which case it turns out, I guess, that Isaac Newton's
smarty pants and the Bible was right.
That wouldn't be quite as surprised, now, wouldn't it?
Well, didn't he just drop apples out of trees or something like that?
And he tripped balls.
He knew more than most people have.
I have never forgotten.
Will you look at it with...
Especially when it comes to alchemy.
And yet he was still a nut.
He was quite a good people, Fig Newton.
He was the smartest guy in the world.
Well, actually, that's debatable because another guy invented the calculus at the same time.
I thought he was a little bit mad.
But...
What did he mean?
Yeah, well, he was crazy as a loon.
He was...
Absolutely.
...in charge of the coinage of...
Yeah, he was also in charge of the mint.
...English kingdom.
But...
He invented money.
Once he had a special...
...and fallen.
...device made from an artificer.
A clockwork maker made a beautiful model of the solar system.
By turning the handle, the little gears would move the orbiting bodies around the planets.
And a friend came over and said, oh, what a beautiful thing.
Who made it?
And Newton said, nobody.
I had not heard that one.
That's a good one.
Yes.
He's an atheist.
Hi.
I'm a scientist.
Is that the same as the joke about the agnostic...
It's not a joke.
...language...
No, it's...
It's a historical anecdote.
Oh, I know about the part about him being an atheist or an agn...
No, he was not an atheist.
He was not an atheist.
He was a religious nut by our standards.
...at all.
He was very, very devout.
He took the Bible literally, and that's where he made his calculations about the end of
the world from.
In those days, they all believed in Providence, which is just a town in Rhode Island.
Well, Providence is...
Well, it's really there.
The way that...
Good was able to be churned out of evil by the avenging angelic spirit.
Didn't he make eyeglass lenses out of gold and think that he could look at the sun through
those lenses and it wouldn't damage his eyes and he became blind?
Well, they had tiny little holes in them.
...of his thyroid gland.
Well, there was a...
No, there was a theory behind that, and gold is used in the insides of the helmet visors
to keep the...
...in his fracture.
...it is.
... Telescope, as it were.
It's called a Atlampia.
Yeah, it is.
... בcke tipos dw residency...
DOUBLİת gates master who drives a
greatecat here in
So, I'm just...
sent to Benjamin Franklin, who
apparently used them in his
visits to France.
But now their
whereabouts
are unknown.
I got me a gold
tooth that's made out of King Solomon's gold.
It's magic gold. Maybe it'll
sell me a gin and I don't need
London Dry.
All the gold in the world has come from outer space anyway.
It all came from asteroids.
All the gold in the world can't buy
me happiness, Dad.
Did you know we're all in a vast
cubicle of quartz
of Ontario quartz that made its way
under the lake or the lake
we're sitting on? Quartz and pints
and Heinz Schwartz and Gluck.
And boots and pence. Boots and
saddles to horse and away.
Yoiks, tally-ho. We're coming up
on the end of the hour. Yoiks.
Seven, six,
five. Yes, drink, puppy,
drink, and let every puppy drink.
Well, my conscience
is clear. I've done
what I could to bring the heathen
and the sheathen to subgenius
understanding. Oh, and puppies
drink their sweet, sweet, sweet.
Now I must get into my own escape
capsule and take my
chances in the rickety, rocketing
cosmos.
Yeah, I gotta get in my escape
capsule also.
Hey, rock...
Oh, shut up.
I took a powder.
The world is ending. Quit. Run.
Hide under the table.
My phones are going down.
Oh, my goodness. Oh, man, I hit all the wrong
buttons here. Anyway, this has been
Synesthesia on WCSB Cleveland.
Stay tuned for a very special
episode of Cramp Radio.
Until next time, keep it surreal.
...
This show,
The Hour of Slack.
If you need more
information,
please
...
measuringometers.llg.com
That's 1-814-17-Clavelin Heights, Ohio 44118.
Praise God.
I'm hoping now I can give out your phone number, your own phone number.
And now we'll copy the fire sign theater again for those of you on drugs.