Yeah, feel that bump on Bob's dome.
Let's see, Bob.
Oh, hey, that is a good one.
What happened?
The subgenius hour of slack.
Toward an inexplicable horror.
Something too ghastly to face.
So let's not.
Instead, let's walk down this shady lane.
Putting one foot after another.
The way to proceed.
The best way out of anything is straight through it.
And so we're going to go straight through another show for you.
In a series of prize-winning Bobcasts.
Familiar to college radio and dyspeptic late-night listeners.
So let's get started.
Well, make up your mind.
It's another hour of slack.
Slack.
Yes, recording here at Wisteria on July the 6th.
That's true, ladies and gentlemen.
Which was not really supposed to exist.
The post-X-Day day, if you believe that sort of thing.
That calendrical fake news.
There we go.
Since X-Day did not happen, it can't be after X-Day.
It must be, perforce, before that great day when the dreadful judge in middle air shall spread his throne.
And the quick and the dead shall be judged aboard the saucers.
Well, they've already been judged if they're on the saucers at all.
And they've been judged well and good.
It's just like the Christian great white throne ceremony.
Which is just for the sake of the ceremony.
Since everybody there is guilty and has to go through the smoking door on the right.
Does his name appear in the book of life?
No, Lord.
No name ever appears here.
Then depart from me into the eternal flames prepared for Satan and his fallen angel buddies.
And here's Saturday sketching.
And here's the last one.
If this is indeed Saturday.
Shatterday we call it.
And our hopes have been fractionated into a thousand shards.
Number one, recuperate from Friday.
Still working on that one.
Is that done?
There's a few. A few have recuperated.
We're recuperating.
Most of them are still...
De-be-cu-perating.
Yeah, they're still super-rating.
Yeah.
Baptism in Pond, 2 p.m.
At 2 p.m. we will baptize the faithful in the waters of old Sequaw's lair.
Those brave enough to brave those waters.
Or willing enough to receive the icy benediction of cool embrace of water on a ragingly hot day.
The problem is getting past the wall of ticks to the water.
Yes, well there are plenty of ticks.
There are plenty of ticks in the forest and you don't want to tick them off.
Seriously, there are quite a number of these arachnids and they're all snapping their jaws in anticipation of a blood meal from you, oh faithful listener.
The other thing today...
Oh, it says costume or not party.
I have a feeling...
That's your clothes optional...
Mostly not, no.
No, so you can...
Costume or dress like a slob...
If anybody bothered to wear a costume or isn't already wearing a costume...
All right.
All the time.
Okay, that's the...
Because some of them are.
That's what used to be called the ball.
Yes, there was a ball back then.
The costume, it was a ball.
And there was a feast, but that was already this morning.
The feast of St. Swithin's Day.
Well, we try to keep up.
And the important thing, the Bulldada auction.
Exactamente.
The Bulldada auction will come up in all its savagery and splendor.
After the baptism in the pond...
I guess so.
We will reassemble our afflicted powers and troop back here to Caffeinas, where we will start putting on display and on sale the treasures of time, subgeniuses donations for the Bulldada auction.
You can see just a few of the samples here on the desk.
Yeah, the exploding death robot should be really popular.
On the other hand, we still are taking donations.
If you have things which you would like to see auctioned off for the greater glory of Bob and his church, you may donate them up to and during the time of the Bulldada auction.
And the Bob burning late tonight.
Yes.
I have seen the effigy auction.
Bob himself will burn like a torch to illuminate the true path.
So, there. That's all. That's our future set out for us.
The subgenius, Otto Daffay.
Although, you know, it still could be X-Day.
Any second X-Day could happen. Any second. Are you ready?
We like to say that in our disappointment every July 6th.
One must be ready.
If only it would happen.
They're always telling us in San Francisco, oh, the big earthquake is coming any day now. Be ready. Have your earthquake preparedness kit.
I did get one yesterday. A 7.1.
Wasn't that in lower California?
Yeah, yeah, southern California.
In Los Angeles.
Right. So, it doesn't matter to you, the northern Californian.
Well, I am sure my dinosaur collection is safe.
But, at any moment, those two plates could let go.
And with an enormous crash, the vanity of man could come tumbling down and be swept away.
Especially one good earthquake under Silicon Valley. That's what we all hope for.
But, this still hasn't happened.
And the only reason I mentioned it is one is always told to prepare and be safe.
But, one may never prepare adequately and there is no safety.
Only a silly propagandistic illusion.
Wouldn't you agree, Reverend Stang?
So that the exists in their fire and fury could appear any nanosecond.
What's really fun is when somebody decides a city needs to be evacuated.
As if that were possible.
In the next 25 minutes.
Lower Manhattan must be thoroughly evacuated.
Right.
Well, the last time the mayor of Houston said,
Everybody get out! This hurricane's coming!
People were trapped on the freeway for days.
And he only meant Hurricane Carter.
Yeah, the hurricane never came, but a lot of people got injured on the traffic jam.
So, there you go, kids.
There's no escape.
You can't get away.
You can climb up onto your attic and then onto your rooftop.
And the helicopters will just fly by.
Sticking their, pilots sticking their tongues out at you, waving.
If you live on the edge of an active volcano, you can have a safety plan.
But you can't have safety.
Well, here we are.
And there they go.
Yes, once again.
The saucers flying away from us.
Back into the void.
Empty handed.
They didn't lift up any subgeniuses that we know of.
No.
Although I'm going to be really mad if I find out everybody else outside of this camp got ruptured.
Only the suckers that paid money get left behind.
That would be, that would be a pisser.
Thanks, Bob.
Thanks, Obama.
Now let's, uh.
Thanks, Philo.
Thank you.
Thank you, Bob.
Thanks.
It's okay.
So—
Yeah, go on.
Philo ran off.
He's already gone.
He tends to leave suddenly like the Lone Ranger.
Who was that masked man anyway?
Well, we got one new subgenius today, only he's a really old one.
Oh, really?
Reverend Sosodotta from years past.
Oh, he's—
He has returned to the fold.
Very good.
And is he going to be at the baptism?
I don't know.
Below the fold?
There'll be lots of folds visible at the baptism.
That's true.
Vertical wrinkles, the amazing lack of elasticity of the human frame after a certain number of years.
Quite spectacular to view.
And these epidermises contain the doctors of the church, the saints that you see all about you,
who have made all of this possible.
Saints, taints.
The taints of the church.
Irredeemable.
Taint Paul.
Taint Hal.
Taint Philo.
Taint Peter.
Taint here.
Philo taint here.
Philo's taken off.
For the wild fruit of Kentucky.
Of Kentucky.
Yeah, back where he is.
He's got to mow his graveyard.
Yes.
He actually has a graveyard.
The old family cemetery.
It's on his property.
He has a graveyard of humans.
I have a graveyard only of shellfish.
And many other creatures.
Millions of them.
All kinds of animalcules from the bottom of the ancient sea.
Well, we do have the robot skeleton and the alien skeleton and the devil skeleton.
Yeah, I thought you said the same thing.
You had a devil skeleton in there.
Yeah.
It's got a long tail with a little...
A barb at the end.
Yeah, a barb.
A biffid barb of hell.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Yep.
And, uh...
Are you interested...
Oh, it's old Mr. Scratch, all right.
Uh, Hal, you'll find it interesting the devil's jaws in two parts like a bug's mandible.
Yes, well, you see...
Sideways and up and down.
They have the ability to pull in one...
One...
The side of one jaw, uh...
Alternately with the side of the other jaw.
Just like the...
Crotolid snakes and like the Tyrannosaurus, uh...
Rex, whose jaw was in two pieces and had two separate sets of muscles to pull...
Them back...
Here we go.
Apart and in tandem.
Demonsaurus Rex.
Oh, also interestingly, the...
The fossilized Cretaceous devil has a heart.
A cold, hard heart bone.
I've never seen any other creature with a heart bone.
It's even shaped like a heart.
It does don't pull out that stake that's, uh...
Stuck through it.
Yeah, heart bone and it has a...
What do you call a penis bone?
A baculum.
Yeah, yeah.
Or a bacula.
Like a bear or a walrus.
Or a raccoon also has this penis bone.
Yeah, my dad has swizzle sticks made of all of those things.
He does?
Yeah, the walrus bone is big enough to...
Kill somebody with.
Ah.
And it's got scrimshaw on it.
What a murder weapon it would be for Inspector Poirot.
Yeah, yeah.
The scrimshaw walrus pizzle murder.
Yeah, the walrus pizzle murder.
Monsieur, I accuse you of an abominable crime.
Jack the...
Pizzler.
Mm-hmm.
Uh, well...
So, well, we'll display all of those next, next day.
In the Museum of Curiosities.
The Cabinet of Wonders.
At Subgenius Headquarters.
The impregnable fortress.
Yeah, but the fortress actually...
Bob actually did make the fortress pregnant.
So you could say that it was a pregnant fortress.
There were giants in the earth in those days.
Yeah.
And they moved these huge stones to build the lofty tower you see before you.
A couple of days, of X days ago, Bob actually had forcible sex with the back end of Potter Nostril's car.
TMI.
And he and Petal were in the car at the time, trying to get some privacy.
And suddenly Bob was at the back of it, just humping away like crazy.
And didn't it, like, a few months later, had a little Volkswagen or something?
It's a little small D4 broken car.
Yes, Bob's pipe strikes again.
Bob's tailpipe, that is.
It kind of wrecked your car in the process.
It's an old gypsy legend.
Yeah.
Give it back.
Bob's horrible little bastard bought her children.
That's how Bob tells your future.
He reads your palm, your tea leaves.
And writes your muffler.
Leaving it all split open.
Sopping.
Gross, huh?
Oh, is this the Wolfman dance music?
The victorious dance of Ilonka the Proud at the gypsy camp.
Oh.
You know, she runs off with Professor Lampini's Circus of Horrors.
Yeah, but she doesn't want to make it with the hunchback guy.
Not after she discovers his hunched condition.
It's a very sad scene.
Right.
Yeah, she's all, he's real cute.
And she likes him up until she sees the hump.
Yeah.
That's a surefire.
But then she falls in love with the Wolfman.
Which is exceptionally irritating to the hunchback.
To be turned down and then she goes for the Wolfman.
Right.
It's not like he's all that great of a catch.
Certainly self-absorbed.
Moaning and bitching about his werewolf destiny all the time.
24-7.
Yeah, he does really feel, Lawrence Talbot feels very sorry for himself.
I've said it before.
In his case, he's psychologically.
He's psychologically identifying with the oppressor.
He thinks he's one of the humans, but he's one of the monsters.
He thinks he's one of the humans that something happens to.
And he's on the side of the humans when the monsters have their conspiracy going.
I know a whole lot of subgeniuses that have that same problem.
They think they're human.
Or they think they can pass.
So they identify with these humans instead of with their monster brethren.
That's Stockholm Syndrome, you know.
Yes.
Fall in love with your captors.
Because what else can you do?
It's just a thing that happens when the humans surround you.
The thing next to exit.
No, honestly, I'm surprised.
If it's a mummy, I'm sure they must have been forced to get rid of it by the wave of...
I have a feeling...
... social judgment.
Probably when the gang of young American Indian movement guys shows up going,
You can't have this sacred relic here.
That's when the owner goes,
Look, let me show you something, guys.
He opens up the case and he goes,
It's paper mache, okay?
This never was.
We never had any of your ancestors in here.
This is a fake.
I'm surprised anybody ever falls for it.
I suspect that myself, actually.
It's hard to tell.
I mean, it's so far gone.
It might as well just be paper mache.
Yes, a mummy.
It's supposed to be well preserved.
The whole point of a mummy is you preserve...
Well, the baby really looks bad.
This rotted, crumbled thing.
Well, the baby mummy...
The mummies in Guanajuato...
... are in better condition.
Yeah.
Well, I don't get the impression that anyone really intended to mummify this person or paper mache model.
I don't know.
It's just a, what is it?
You know, from the...
But I do know this.
Make your own conclusions, ladies and gentlemen.
I know where the switch is for all the lights at Carlsbad Caverns.
Uh-huh.
It's one switch.
It can shut off all the lights.
All the lights down there.
A ranger foolishly showed us that.
We were the last people to leave.
And we said, hey, what does it look like when it's completely dark in here?
He goes, oh, let me switch it off for a second.
I saw where he reached behind a bench.
And there was the lights off.
So...
I saw where he reached last year.
Next time we go to Carlsbad Caverns, Hal...
Yes.
We...
We plunge everyone into Cimmerian blackness.
Well, first we smuggle some phosphorous or glow-in-the-dark ghost outfits in there.
Gotcha.
So that we can be dressed up as Indian, the spirits of angry Indian medicine men...
Yes.
...who are haunting the cave.
So, first we plunge the place into darkness.
Then we, in our cohorts, rise up...
...from behind stalactites or mites or whatever and go...
...going...
...and hope there's not a good guy with a gun.
Well, what if there's...
Because that's always the problem.
...panicking, running into the walls, falling into crevasses, impaling themselves on stalactites.
I asked the ranger, do kids ever hide out in here?
And he goes, oh yeah, oh yeah.
He goes, not long ago, these two boys hid in here when they didn't reckon on us turning the lights off.
And it stays 50 degrees all the time down there.
So, yeah, they were scared boys the next morning when the rangers came back.
When the rangers came back laughing.
Yeah.
Well, nobody knew they were there when...
Surely they have cameras and stuff.
Pioneers.
There's plenty of light in there when the lights are on.
Colored lights.
Oh no, they say they're not colored.
They go, these aren't...
Believe it or not, those rocks really are blue, pink, and so forth.
Down there.
That's gorgeous.
I've been in Carlsbad Caverns nine times.
And if anyone wants to see it after next X Day, you're welcome to come to my escape planet.
Where I will have Carlsbad Caverns in the Grand Canyon.
We'll just stick it in the Grand Canyon.
How's that?
I just thought of that.
But you know, it'll be easy.
You just ask Mom to do it.
You don't even have to ask.
It just happened.
It already knows.
And maybe that's why we haven't been ruptured.
Because it knows we still have to do it.
Dirty, dirty, dirty little minds.
We're not going to let these subgeniuses on our beautiful escape saucers.
As long as they're still stuck in the mud plain.
Their minds filled with lustful thoughts of desires and sex and coffee.
Speaking of which, I would...
No, I don't need another coffee.
You were thinking of it.
Thinking of coffee.
No.
Well, we need somebody else up here, don't we?
We could always use another voice here to throw more light on the subject.
And we do invite anyone who feels like coming up.
Like perhaps you, Lord Reverend Angry Larry, could take up microphone number three.
And make this duo a trio.
That was the curse.
The accursed...
Yeah, that's why I turned it down.
Oh, oh, oh.
It's not doing anything now.
Well, something's doing something somewhere.
Because we're managing to continue after the fact.
And I gather you brought that to quiet your microphone stand.
A wonderful maneuver which prevents those telltale sounds leaking through.
Which indicate equipment being moved.
And we even have the wonder of the headphones here.
Something which in other years was not an option.
Oh, no.
I was wearing the headphones yesterday.
But with Philo's Magna whatever he had up here, this giant whatever.
The Magna woofer.
Yes.
It was in the way.
It's the thing that keeps his heart going.
Or what do you...
It is his heart, basically.
It's the low frequency modulator.
He doesn't actually have a human heart, Philo doesn't.
He has some sort of overman thing.
One of the rewards he got for working for the phone company for so many years.
No, no.
He got that at Dobstown.
The phone company takes away your real heart.
And so, Philo was able to replace it with an overman heart.
With some kind of a bell heart.
Yeah.
Ooh, there's that breeze.
Yes.
A cool evening breeze on a warm flowery shore.
And while we're in this breezy breezeway here at the Church of the Subgenius broadcast,
we are approaching one hour before the baptism.
Remember, this vital ceremony will be held at the church of the subgenius broadcast.
And it will be performed at 2 p.m. at the Pond.
This is a sleepy X-Day.
Snorefest.
Sausage snorefest.
Beautiful...
Snorefest night.
Snorewood, Ohio.
But hey, what did you guys think about the clown show last night?
That was quite impressive.
The...
The erupting clown.
The wiener mobile jumping over two flaming cars.
Three flaming cars.
I did not think that I would ever see such a...
Such a marvel.
It was...
Well, they certainly built...
Took their time building up to it.
Well, yeah.
As always.
Well, they had to find three people that would donate their cars for them to jump the
wiener mobile over it.
Yeah.
While the cars were...
Of course, not the real wiener mobile, okay, please.
So...
It was a replica of the wiener mobile.
Yeah, we don't want to...
We don't want to get hung up by Oscar Mayer.
No, there is a life-size wiener mobile out somewhere on the nation's highway.
It's a replica.
There are several of them.
They actually just posted a thing where they're looking for drivers to where you can drive
one around.
It doesn't have to be a midget like the original little Oscar.
No.
Yeah, no.
There's one in Dallas and I think there's one in Cleveland.
There may be.
There's one in Detroit and at the Henry Ford Museum that's there.
Oh, right.
Right next to where you can buy Oscar Mayer hot dogs, which I don't recommend.
One of the worst hot dogs I've ever had.
Really?
It's like a big slab of bologna.
It's terrible.
Make mine Nathan's.
That's my personal favorite brand.
They're full of garlic.
Oh, yeah.
The actual Safeway house hot dogs are pretty good.
The best thing of their kind.
Hot dog.
Hort dog.
They're large and...
Well constructed.
What can I say?
What one wants in a hot dog is present in these, nor is the price excessive.
And the bulldada will happen after the baptism.
Yes, it will.
The bulldada will happen after the same.
We could do one now.
We could.
Well, there's...
Except there's no button.
You need to...
I don't want to go on.
Oh, please don't say this.
There's nobody here with money because I offended people yesterday.
The crowd to be here and refreshed from the immersion and the purgation.
Well, who wants to buy this robot?
Me.
Well, you can put in your bid early with your privileged position here, but the point
is we've got to do it when the...
Although, the clown said that they bought a bunch of stuff.
Emotional moment.
It's right.
I think.
The clowns want a big penis.
Oh, yeah.
It's here, too.
It's here.
If they're here, they can bid on it.
A big wiener head.
There it is.
It's just the head.
It really looks beat up.
It looks like it has been through hell.
It has been beat on so much.
And mostly by dames, actually.
I used to bring that to the subgenius conventions.
There got to be a regular tradition of female takeovers that often involved violence.
And I would sometimes put that thing on to be kind of the scapegoat.
The diffuser.
Well, just to lure them.
If they could beat on one dickhead, they'd feel better and they'd leave the rest of us alone.
Well, I must say that.
The padding on the inside is considerably.
Oh, wow.
But where the nose goes.
Yeah, no.
You don't have a whole lot there.
No.
There's tiny little slits for eyes on the underside.
Which makes it look like some kind of a Toho character.
Like this would have fought Godzilla.
Matango.
Or Gammon.
Well, it looks a bit more like.
Attack of the mushroom people.
It looks like it would fight big man Japan.
Right.
Like you pictured this.
Like, ho, ho, ho.
Yeah.
I'm not being racist.
I'm just.
Yes.
You must be familiar with the attack of the mushroom people.
Yeah.
A.K.A.
Matango.
So if any children go, what is that?
It's a mushroom man.
Oh, okay.
I have one of those.
I can say, I'm President Trump's crotch.
Oh, yeah.
No, not nearly this big.
No, but it supposedly is like a.
She described it as like the mushroom character in Mario Kart.
Mushroom.
But lives on.
On the island.
Yeah.
Mushroom headed and stumpy.
Strangely.
Stumpy the clown.
Right.
But be a little deformed.
A little asymmetrical fellow.
Whose water that is.
Stumping along on the campaign trail for 2020.
Well, yeah, it's a kind of a liability if you've got a.
He's.
A.
Special.
Recognizable.
Weenar.
Bill Clinton had that problem because he has vitiligo and it's spotted.
Just like Michael Jackson.
Yeah.
And others.
Oh, now we know.
I got a certain piebald condition.
Professor pressure.
How do you know about that?
The spotted leopard.
Well, that didn't mean you have it all over.
You know.
Yeah.
But you just kind of assumed.
And you know what happens when you assume.
Yeah.
You assume to the head of the class.
I tell you what we will ask him when he comes back.
Do you have a spotted pack?
Do you have a spotted packer?
If you pecker spotted like your hands.
I don't mean to be asked something too personal.
Because Princess we has this thing that she believes that your packer may be spotted.
Oh, really?
Well, I didn't realize.
We were going to get this.
We're having inspections at 5 o'clock.
At the baptism.
Say, all right, drop them.
Let's see if you're speckled.
This and other mysteries will be revealed at that time.
If you have the Michael Jackson disease.
Right.
The Michael Jackson Pollock 5 disease.
So it's coming up, folks.
Set your chronometer for a little more than an hour from now.
So we have this cool ray gun up here, too.
Yes, from the estate of the late president.
Yeah, for all I know, batteries should make noises and light up.
This doesn't explode.
I don't think this right here goes to the robot.
The robot.
Okay, bopper in there.
This is interchangeable technology, ladies and gentlemen.
This car is full of clowns.
It's been made by beings of an extraterrestrial origin.
Uh-oh.
Or Japanese.
Celestials.
I could probably put batteries in this and we'll see if the batteries want to blow up in this, too.
Yes, that might be a good idea.
Charge it up with power to spare.
We've got... I got the...
Here's some of those ones that... I think with these ones...
Here's some more-than-kind batteries.
Yes.
Oh, no, actually, those are the ones I took out of this recorder.
Right.
They're probably about half... half powered.
Oh, you don't want to put any half-hearted, half-spent batteries in.
Well, these ones are the ones that were on fire yesterday, so I'll try these.
Oh, well, they've all been traumatized.
You're putting in an array of the walking wounded of the battery kingdom.
Okay.
Those were violated that were put in the non-functional robot and began to heat up because they were ready to...
Oh, man.
Oh, shit.
There's some... there's some definite corrosion in here.
Oh, yes.
Just a little bit.
Acid has etched its way through the cover.
Did these come from... did you find these out when you were looking for fossils?
I found those in... yeah, basically in my basement.
Oh, right.
Just shake them out and we'll dispose of them properly.
Hey, don't be a wiener.
You may already be a wiener.
You may already...
Remember, marijuana is a match.
Maryland is the flame and LSD is the bomb.
LSD is the bomb.
Yeah, they used that tape on the WCSB PSA collection.
I hear that almost every week.
Wow, that was...
That was definitely terrible.
Reverend Agri Larry is planning to do the...
I'm not sure I want to see that.
I'm not going to be around to see how an alien does a ray gun.
We might as well.
These are inferior ray guns.
These are made with your non-space age polymers that you... that earthlings seem to tack onto
everything that...
Extruded plastic.
The kind of disintegrating gun that is slowly disintegrating.
Yes.
In the basement.
Yeah.
Let's see where the other end is supposed to go.
Oh, there it is.
Oh, not that one.
Well, we'll know in just a moment, ladies and gentlemen, whether this alien device can
be reactivated since it's going to be offered in the Bull Donna auction later in the afternoon.
You know, it's funny.
Now that Philo's not here irritating me with this little noise maker, I miss it.
Yes, of course.
He's nice.
We will all remember that next year.
That rascally...
That rascally Philo.
Yes.
He's left us with...
He's wistful for his presence.
Well, if you ask Reverend Lucy Van Pelt, I can be just as annoying if you wish.
Oh, that's a...
I believe you.
I...
Oh, oh, okay.
Here, let's see.
Why do these batteries...
Okay.
The battery chamber itself could have been fused and melted, but we'll now try to activate
the gun.
To...
Oh, okay.
I'm just not the same as I used to be these X days.
How so, Reverend Stang?
Well, this is like the next to the last day.
I still haven't hung up that big vinyl Dobbs head.
I was wondering where that was.
We have a projector, but I haven't bothered to plug it in and point it at a wall.
Oh, oh, look at that.
There's another storage, battery storage area here.
I see.
And those batteries also are long past their prime.
From an older era.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Maybe they all have to work in conjunction with one another.
So, you really have to load that thing up with battery sets, so...
For sure.
Yeah, that big vinyl Dobbs head is at the bottom of that blue case there behind us.
We never did...
But we got the big eyeball back there.
That's a good change.
The giant eyeball that eternally watches.
Yeah.
Okay.
Oculus Aspicidnos.
Tenebrarius in Tenebris.
Oh, wow.
They won't come out, eh?
It's like it's, it's attached in there.
Like something, maybe it was.
Almost as if there's something on the other end pulling in the other direction.
Yeah.
Give it a good yank.
Well.
rattling around in there. It's just not
letting go.
Where's the pair of pliers?
Pliers. Or a thousand tiny
fingers. Yeah, oh!
It appears to be loose in there, but there's something
When you pull it, there's something
pulling back.
Well, uh, who's
the master here? Give it a big
pull. Give it a yank.
Some little gremlin's gonna come out
hanging on to that. Oh yeah, there's somebody
there's someone on the other end.
Love some little arm holders.
There is a man out on the wing.
What the heck? She wants to get some
white underwear. It might be
best she get them in asbestos.
Alright? Might better get them in
asbestos. And I'm teasing now,
of course. Don't
wear asbestos.
It might get
be harmful to your breathing.
First I want to remind you that in the last days
there will be some scoffers who will do every wrong they can
think of. Scoffers,
mobsters,
mockers, and blasphemers.
An organization of
sneering
scoffers.
Scofflaws.
If you will.
Battery had swollen
up. An abnormality.
Oh yeah. All strapped in my
suit. Nonetheless,
we're going to charge it with a pure
battery and see if it can be
revived. These were all death
traps. Everything we're selling at
the Bulldog auction is
hazardous. Possibly.
They're still testing
this one example of
alien weaponry.
Revan
Stang, that woolen cap
seems like it might be warm on
this hot day.
I feel whole, though.
I see. He feels reunited
with his helm. I see.
Well, one must feel
reunited with one's
helm.
Yeah. Well, you
should know.
You often wear a crown.
Not often enough.
An easy-wise
head that wears
a crown.
Nope. This ray gun
is... Is defunct,
eh? It looks
good. Or it didn't come back.
But all it needs is sound
effects. Mounted on the wall of
your den. And that one plug
in that, you know, adds ray gun.
In fact, you draw a little line
from where the gun is in the
picture to where you want it to
appear to be shooting. Unless the batteries that were on fire
yesterday are default, are
bad now. It could be they were
thoroughly contaminated by
their momentary exposure
to the bad robot.
Oh, yeah. We're going to be auctioning that little zombie.
That bobblehead
zombie. He's kind of
bobble arm. It's a whole body.
It's not just a head. He's a bobble body.
Yes.
One bobble arm and a bobble.
He has a full body bobble going on.
A reanimated corpse. A revenant.
One of the walking dead.
What do we hear for this little
walking dead toy? Are you starting
the auction? Well, this is
just an example. One of the many things that we
will be... I just thought I'd
throw that and see if anyone noticed.
I'm asking because I have been
asked by so very many people
when it's starting. Yeah.
Well, after the baptism...
The baptism is in an hour
but we...
All in
good time. In the fullness of
time, as Hal would say.
Yeah, we've got lots of time since
the aliens didn't arrive yesterday
and Bob's prophecy
didn't ring true again.
Yes, the
time seems
all wrong where these
matters are concerned.
But, yeah, so now we've got
time to kill.
Time to murder
and create.
Yeah, where's that
clock stabbing dagger?
Well, then, it's right on the front of that pulpit there.
Well, that's just a model.
It's a great model!
Yeah, but we need
a bigger... we're going to need a bigger
clock killing dagger. We're going to need a bigger
clock killing dagger. Okay.
You're going to need a bigger boat.
We need to harpoon
Big Ben.
And that big bully.
In the pond, known as
Leviathan.
The giant behemoth.
The fire-spitting monster predicted
in the Bible.
His core, a seething
mass of lethal radiation.
Oh, Princess Wee,
since the world didn't end,
you understand what that means.
No, I don't understand
what that means. You're going to have to spell it out for me.
You still have to do Starwood.
Oh, damn!
Yes.
A whole lot of us still have to do Starwood.
That's the largest
unfairness that I've experienced.
Another week of slack.
That we're sentenced to.
Sentenced to
yet one more week of slack.
Darn it.
If only we could go back to that
comfortable anti-slack
we're used to.
Yeah. Chores.
Normal, ordinary chores. Yeah.
Laundry, dishwashing,
yard work. Getting the house sold.
Enough of all this partying
and orgying and
inebriating
and so forth.
Exactly.
Oh, that's auction stuff.
Oh, Reverend Watney
Falk's book,
The Blasphemera.
It's in the auction.
It is a great
book.
Yes.
Great?
Well, it's great to be...
I might as well kill myself now if I've achieved greatness.
Well, I meant great in size.
It is a great tome in size.
It should have saved me ten years ago.
It's a thick one.
Yes. So that's good.
We've got three things to auction
that don't have deadly
exploding batteries in them.
Some people pay extra
for the booby traps.
But these are...
Don't speak metaphorically.
There are.
Oh, yeah, but that's metaphorically.
Yeah, they probably won't...
They'll only explode metaphorically.
They are decorative objects.
They'll only blind you metaphorically.
They simply cannot be switched on.
And you go and get a metaphorical
tetanus shot afterwards.
They're decorative objects.
Do you think it's all right?
Oh, wait.
I have a new lyric.
To leave the boy...
To leave the dog when we go shopping.
No, when we go to X Day.
Oh.
Yeah.
To leave the dog here during X Day.
Yeah, I think it's all right.
Do you think it's all right?
I think it's all right.
But it wasn't.
He still got out.
She got out.
Our girl dog got out.
Yeah.
But they caught her.
But he slept through it.
Idiot.
He's not a rebel.
He's just an idiot.
That's us, friends.
Hal, would you hold that sign up?
It's right in front of you.
That cardboard sign.
Truer words were never spoken.
And you know, the person who spoke it
didn't recognize the truth when he said it.
He just...
He was Argus Fox.
He was sitting up here at a loss for words.
And he just suddenly goes,
I'm not really a rebel.
I'm just an idiot.
And he said it with such vehemence.
I thought, that's the subgenius condition.
Let's face it.
You know, let's get real.
As Bob said, but isn't it okay if we're only offending dumbasses?
Yeah, I think it's all right.
Yeah.
I think it's all right.
I think that's...
She thinks it's all right.
But it's okay if we're only defending dumbasses.
I think that was what he said.
That was...
There was some big...
No, offending dumbasses.
There was a big PC stink a few years ago.
And that was Bob's take on it.
It's okay if we're just offending dumbasses.
Of course, that's a very offensive thing to say.
That is.
But it's direct.
And he's got a point.
And yes.
It is okay.
Not only is it okay, it's our bound Bob given duty to offend dumbasses.
That just proves if they're offended, it proves they're the dumbasses that we've...
You know, that's the test.
It's an intelligence test.
When subgeniuses are applying the intelligence test, man, if you can't pass that, that means
you are lower than a subgenius.
Of course, some of our...
If you're below a subgenius...
Some of our numbers, such as Dr. Howell and good old Friday Jones, worked out that the
word subgenius actually can be taken as other than a genius.
Above or below or around.
You know, sideways or just a tunnel right through the middle.
Okay.
So...
And that's the exception by which we had both Friday and Dr. Howell.
Correct?
Well, yeah.
They managed to bamboozle us into convincing us they weren't geniuses.
Simple behavior observations will reveal that anyway.
Sub.
Beneath.
Eventually.
Other than.
Aside from.
Yeah.
But not mensa.
You can't be in mensa and Church of the Subgenius at the same time.
You can't.
Can't do it.
We do have a cure.
Yeah.
We have a cure.
You can either...
She wants the cure, Reverend Stein.
Yeah.
Well, there's two approaches.
Okay.
One is the ball-peen hammer.
One...
Well, it's kind of a laying on of hammers.
It's a...
You'll forget.
You won't remember it.
It'll hurt for a minute.
And the other one, of course, is just drugs.
Plain, ordinary liquor will do it.
Don't need anything fancy.
We've got proof all around us of geniuses who've now become saved subgeniuses, although
their livers are almost gone.
Their brains at least now qualify.
Geniuses don't need livers.
I didn't get that.
Or was it don't eat livers?
I thought it was eat livers.
Don't eat livers.
Well, subgeniuses don't need brains.
But they do eat brains.
Don't need no livers.
Or perhaps a six and a half dozen of the other, as my brother used to say.
Remind me not to have any more of that allergy.
No more allergen?
No, I can't.
The pollen is just not...
I can't handle it anymore.
I used to be able to.
I used to be able to handle everything.
The excess had been rupturing bits and pieces.
I don't know.
I don't know what else is.
My energy is I think what they took last year.
Well, actually they took...
I don't even want to go into what they took last year.
But now look at me.
A wisp.
A shadow.
A pathetic shard of a once man.
Now dear, you're not a wisp or a shadow.
No.
Look at me.
I've created my own bubble cell and my own body, individually suffering the pain of a
hundred billion pains, each pain being distinct and worse than the last, and every cell has
this pain of 100 billion pains multiplied by that number of cells.
It's probably a hundred billion cells in my body.
Maybe 6.
Internal intestinal flora and fauna aren't real happy either.
They all have indigestion.
So imagine that.
You're very bowel bugs having indigestion.
And insomnia.
Twitching all night long.
That's messed up.
Yeah.
Yeah, man.
So yeah, hurry up, X-Day.
Come on, Bob.
Where's the fountain of youth?
It wasn't any of those pills I thought it was.
Or exercise.
I've discovered the hard way that that which does not kill me makes me weaker and weaker and weaker.
Age is one of those things.
Just all by itself.
Just simply growing older.
Damn it.
You know, I was sitting here going, I don't have anything to talk about.
But then I realized, yeah, I do.
My health.
Problems.
I'm an old man.
That's all old people talk about.
Their ailments.
Damn it.
My dang pups are barking.
It's not interesting, dear.
My lumbago's acting up.
I know there's a storm coming in.
I can just feel it.
You can feel it in your bones.
And they talk to me through the fillings in my teeth.
Do you feel it in your lower spinal series?
Mm-hmm.
When the storm clouds are forming?
No, actually, I don't.
But my sister does.
She calls me up and says, storm's coming.
She's right.
However, she's in a women's prison in Texas.
Boy, I've learned a whole lot about the criminal law justice system that I never expected to.
As our public defender said, most families never have to deal with a murder trial.
Man, it's just, it is pretty serious.
He's right.
Well, you find out all kinds of things.
Insurance companies won't insure a house owned by a felon.
You can't get insurance.
My sister had to give her house to her son so that we could continue to insure it in case it burns down while she's gone.
Dang it.
Oh, I've got funny letters, too, that I left most of them at home.
But I got one I was going to read.
The things I don't want to smell anymore.
Things I don't want.
Things I don't want to hear anymore.
And things I don't want to see anymore.
When you're in the most boring and uncomfortable place in the world.
An interesting document.
You end up writing a lot of letters to your sarcastic loved ones in pencil.
And coloring in coloring books.
She reads about three novels a day.
Let's see.
Musings.
There is no one in this new dorm that I've met yet that I can converse with.
Nothing other than the usual.
What's for chow?
Have they called mail yet?
In case you didn't know, the world is full of terrible human beings.
I realize they aren't all terrible.
But I despise people more than ever now.
Oh, here's her.
Things I don't know.
Things I don't ever want to hear again.
The constant sound of fans.
I know how she feels.
That's off the chain.
That's what's up.
She wants to be with you.
She just doesn't know how.
It's got her feeling some kind of way.
Oh, another one.
I'm finned to go.
Things I don't know.
Things I don't want to see on a daily basis.
Number one, ass crack.
Pants under the ass cheeks.
Hence the ass crack.
Guards.
Yellow lines to walk in.
Razor wire.
And women.
Even ones that look like men.
Things I don't want to smell anymore.
A. The chow hall.
B. Twenty different kinds of commissary food all being, quote, cooked at the same time.
The farts of a hundred and two women.
Hey, boys.
Her bunkie wants to know if we know any men she can write.
Interested?
In answer to your question,
no, she is not in the least bit attractive or interesting.
No, she does not have money.
Yes, she will probably talk dirty.
Yes, she is looking for a savior,
although she claims to believe in Jesus.
So doesn't she have one already?
What else could she need?
It boggles my mind that people who claim to believe they have a savior
or an afterlife of eternal bliss
are the ones who are not.
They are the most afraid of death.
Death doesn't scare me.
Dying is a concern, but not death.
Well, she's been dead.
She has actually...
uh...
She's been...
She's already been there.
Yes.
Yeah. She's like the...
What's her name in Peaky Blinders?
The matriarch.
She was actually had her head in the noose
when the pardon came through.
And she...
She said, you know,
I've already been there.
There's nothing else you can do to me.
Huh?
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, my sister says that is her.
Nearly to die can be good medicine.
Yeah, my sister is like the professor
on Gilligan's Island.
And the people
are amazed that she...
She remembers the words
to all the songs
in her head.
She won't sing them, but she can
recite them and then the other girls
sing them.
She...
She knows...
They were flabbergasted when she described
where Israel is.
She had to explain
why Robin Hood
doesn't just go get a gun.
She had to explain
that this country,
the USA,
was not always English speaking
white people.
They did not know
that.
So,
this...
She has to
explain the Star Wars movies to them
constantly.
Why'd they do that?
Well,
you know,
it's...
It's...
I mean, she's been...
She had a regular job out in the world.
She'd been passing,
like we all do.
But they were regular,
ordinary,
ignorant Pobuckers that,
you know, could read something.
Regular pinks, not the extreme...
Right, regular pinks,
not the extreme...
The victim Pobucker...
God! And yeah, they do divide up into
gangs, and she ended up hanging out with
the Mexicans, mostly,
because they didn't seem to have as big of a hang-up.
It was like they didn't really care
that much.
And, uh...
But you don't get to be friends
with anybody for long, because everybody
gets moved around, and they're constantly
shuffling them.
In order to get a pillow,
she has to have a special
doctor's visit. To visit
the doctor, you have to sit on a crowded,
un-air-conditioned
bus to
Galveston. On a hard,
un-cushioned seat, the bus
bumps and bumps the whole way.
Yeah, it stops at all the other prisons in between,
so it takes all day long.
And that's just to talk to a
doctor, and say, I really
need a pillow.
That's the only way to do it. It's like the
system of control.
They remind you every
step of the way that
you are a bug.
Yes, little girl?
They also have to be subject to a humiliating
search, just when they leave
and when they return. Oh yeah, any time
you go out or come back, or even when
we go to visit her. You get a visit!
Yeah, she then has to
be, you know, get
a humiliating search. Strip searched, not just a search.
Strip searched. Yeah.
Yeah. Over and done.
They make it as humiliating as possible.
Yeah. It's just constant
reminders. Oh, we're gonna
have to head down to the pond.
That's right. Skip back. It's time.
Yeah, we have to go.
It's, it's, uh... In 15
minutes it will be a two-zone... It's time for the
trek to the pond. I predict there will be
four people standing on the bank
and two in the water. It may take a moment to get set up.
Don't we have room in our vehicle
to take people if people can't walk
that whole way? People, yeah, people, sure, but
this... Subgenii, I
meant subgenii. People, yeah,
people, sure, but this... Listen to me.
If there are subgenii that can't make
the walk but want to be in
the Bobtism, don't
you think we could bring a few? Yeah, it's a long way.
It's a long way. It's all the way down
at the swimming hole. It's a long
way to Tipperary. We have a vehicle there.
Uh, there are only three
seats being used out of
four,
and then you can probably... Okay, bye.
Okay, bye.