This is KNON 90.9 FM in Dallas, Texas.
Set my body on the radio, on the radio, radio control.
Can I just bring it back here, Jack Siegel?
The show is starting up.
Go ahead and hit number five ignition switch.
You want to turn it into a broadcast?
Oh, we're already broadcasting.
All right, let's hit.
All right.
You love it listening.
Whoa!
Oh, yeah.
Hey.
Yes!
It's the scream that knocks you out when you go down for the count.
It's the dream becoming reality and the battle cry of seduction.
Best of all, it's true!
Are we controlled by secret forces?
Do you ever get the feeling that free will is a joke?
Do people think you're strange?
Do you?
Then you may be on the right track.
This is Doug Smith, radio operator.
I'm going to bring you a piece of that green cheese for sure.
No trouble.
Just get set and get going.
Here we go.
Recording.
Everything's going fine.
No trouble.
Welcome potential initiates and remain with us for the next 30 minutes.
Bob?
The message is now part of and registered in your subconscious mind.
Every time you say, see, hear, or think.
What about Slack?
That's your key phrase.
It will trigger the entire message without your being aware of it.
Welcome to the subgenius radio industry.
Power of Slack.
Sponsored by Bob.
Sponsored by the church of the subgenius.
This is Reverend Ivan Stang, sacred scribe of the first orthodox mega fist temple lodge of the church of the subgenius.
The sexiest man on earth.
A young Adonis who's irresistible.
Wait a minute, I've got to have sex with you.
You shall have sex.
Bob is sex.
Bob?
Bob.
We are controlling transmission.
Sponsored by the church of the subgenius.
Three.
Two.
Two and one.
Now to continue with the tape recording.
Oh, and the barrage, the intro barrage, by the way, dear friends,
is by me and Puzzling Evidence and St. Byron Werner and Mark Mothersbaugh.
Walk forwards.
Walk backwards.
Radio control.
Walk hard.
Take a vacation.
Radio control.
Bob's getting down with you here tonight.
Bob's getting down to help you.
No part.
Wait a minute.
Okay.
Oh, Ben.
The Subgenius Foundation, the Reverend Ivan Stang and Dr. Philo Drummond,
and they are, as we mentioned before, the dual heads of the Subgenius Foundation,
which is the publishing and PR arm of the Church of the Subgenius.
You're in the...
Just for the bucks?
Do you have some?
No.
Don't you kick me in the gutter.
This one's for Puzzling Evidence again.
Oh.
Yuck.
Hello?
Hello.
This is the famous Subgenius radio program.
We're calling you from the left coast.
The United States.
Did you hear about that?
We're sorry.
You called the wrong show.
We'll have to reconnect and be part of your dialing process later.
Now let's go over that again.
Dial again.
And dial again.
We're sorry, too.
Because it's spooky.
And dial 823-7490.
And be on the show.
But, of course, a vast conspiracy...
The show.
You won't believe.
You heard the whole thing.
823-7490.
The show.
Oh my god!
Die Autobots!
First Prime.
Then Ultra Magnus.
And now you.
It's a pity you Autobots die so easily.
Or I'll kill you.
I might have a sense of satisfaction now.
You got the touch!
You got the...
Arise, Ragnus Prime.
Optimus.
Yeah!
Just you wait!
Let this mark the end of the Cybertronian Wars
as we march forward to a new era.
A new age of peace and happiness.
Till all are one!
Dear friends.
It's so true.
And this show.
My subgenius listeners marks a new age of the merging of all shows in friendship.
Ending the battle of the shows.
And joining together in masculine power against the conspiracy.
I'll kill you even if I have to.
You can call.
828-9500 or 823-7490.
If you're...
If you think you really want to know what's going on.
You can call.
I'll call and you'll get to tell me.
If you think you're really going to tell me.
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Stella!
Open the Padme doors please, help!
Open up, Podbean girls, please, now!
Is it safe? Is it safe?
Is it safe?
Here's Johnny!
Elliot! Elliot! Elliot!
Fall home! Fall home!
I am not an animal!
Badges! Badges!
We don't need no stinking badges!
My sister, my daughter, my sister, my daughter, my sister, my daughter!
It's hard work bringing you great movies.
Queen of Blood.
She's gorged herself of fresh blood.
She's a monster.
We have a good supply of blood plasma with us.
We'll use that to feed her.
And if we run out of plasma, Commander?
I have some good news.
May I share it with you?
Hi, I'm Reverend Doug.
Welcome to our singles group.
Oh, by the way, have you been born again?
I can acknowledge your need for your space.
The model carefully today.
No doctor will ever touch me.
Warriors of Allah feel no pain when they die.
Yes, Jesus loves me.
Sister Mary Elizabeth, hit me with a stick.
Man didn't come from no monkey.
He came from the breath of God.
Hare Krishna. Hare Rama.
Here's your flower where's my dolla.
Where's my dolla?
I'm not allowed to tell you what my mantra is.
When I hit yo-
When I hit your head you'll hear again
you'll hear again
When I hit your head.
when I hit your head you'll hear again
you'll hear again when i hit your head you'll hear again praise him praise him
the devil's in you boy
praise him i'm filled with the fire of the justice of the lord when i hit your head you'll hear again
man didn't cover no monkey he came from the breath of god hallelujah oh thank you thank you jesus
oh yes yes yes dear friends that would i i uh copped that little bit of tape there off of
cinnamon
max uh the other night from the dangerous film club show which is a quite a fun show and that
that bit and the monster movie or movie lines bit before it was by
uh chas and james chas dean and james sienna uh and you ought to see it on tape
so if you get cinemax check out dangerous film club got some nice bits
and here in the background we have spike jones the first practitioner of doctor music dear friends
doctor music the music of non-musicians with or without normal instruments sound effects sound
effect music friends that's what we're listening to it's advertent bulldada you might say as opposed
to inadvertent bulldada like jim and tammy or most tv spike jones
spike jones
and we're going to jump back into that but i have to tell you about jayner hyper cleats coming to
town dear friends jayner hyper cleats saint jayner hyper cleats december 6 at club dada um
a subject you can you why don't we just say it's a subgenius revival folks december 6 club dada
with jayner hyper cleats and uh you can see the subgenius video arise uh this friday night at 10
o'clock
uh thank you will the memory is still here this friday night the dallas fantasy fair friends at
marriott hotel six uh on at lbj and coit i-635 and coit marriott hotel dallas fantasy fair at
10 o'clock this friday night the subgenius video arise for free for subgeniuses you better bring
that picture of bob or they may not let you in
uh
uh uh
at the age of three.
Soon thereafter, he began to exhibit
strange powers of persuasion.
By age six, he had made his first million
almost by accident.
In college, he met and married his first
and still his primary wife, Connie,
who is now revered by female subgeni
as the blessed anti-virgin.
With Connie's encouragement,
the young Dobbs became a salesman of legendary
and almost frightening abilities,
known to his peers as the man who could sell anything.
He worked his way up to the very top
of the conspiracy ladder and might have saved it.
But late one night in 1953,
while working on an amateur television of his own design,
an event occurred which was to become a milestone
in man's mind path to slap.
He was suddenly seized up in the spirit
by the hand of the devil.
The hand of Jehovah One itself,
the cosmic puppeteer of the Old Testament,
the wrathful alien space god
from some corporate sin galaxy.
In this timeless moment,
which we call the divine immaculation of the Bob,
Dobbs received the first of countless
grain-curdling pronouncements
which form the sacred prescriptures of the church.
He was shown a vision,
a world where all humanity was equally wealthy,
rich beyond imagining,
but without working.
This experience, combined with his UFO-given sales magic,
led him inevitably into the religion field.
He quickly discovered the golden rule
embodied in his classic saying,
they'll pay to know what they really think.
Is this Bob?
You're cool.
Psychedelic Groover-Rock-a-trasmik.
I can dig it.
You wanna hear me rap?
The suspect was observed running down the street
with a ball-peen hammer.
The officer apprehended the suspect
and fired six warning shots into the back of her head.
The ball-peen hammer was recovered by the monster.
Oh, it's neat riding the shore out on the coast.
Hey, you know what?
School is where it's at, baby.
That's right.
And just say no to everything.
Even the show.
Be for bliss.
Ah, friends.
Before I continue, I'm gonna try the other deck.
See how the other...
The deck, freshly repaired.
So...
Not new.
Usually used when I'm getting the first post.
Yeah.
19lungs positivist.
We can't blame you
for this, baby.
But cigarettes aren't expensive,
which one ever is,
my lips are only insane.
It's just a buddy.
Some usually even unexpectedly 출출기라고
What?
Robbins, Robert Williams, the underground cartoonist, Gary Panner, and Mark Mothersbaugh
are all represented in these horrible news reports of different kinds. It's just a weird
coincidence, a wave, a flap, you might say, of subgenius vocal intrusion into normal airwave
reality. Ah, ah, nothing, I see. Oh, well, wait, wait, let's, let's, let's just, uh,
let's just flip the right switch, turn that zombie's nose around, and there. Okay, get your
cheap sunglasses on. It's time to admit to the bad influences we've enjoyed over the years,
and the bad influences we all were, and the bad art we've really loved. Stuff that issue
of Zap Comics into your back pocket, and let's trip back in time a few weeks to an art opening
at the Otis Parsons Gallery. It's called, what else, Bad Influences.
Here's Georgeanne Dean on the faculty of Otis Parsons Illustration and Commercial Design
Department. She's organized Bad Influences, and she's bad.
None of us have been able to do that.
Unaccepted, or even invited, or we couldn't even get any credence with these, um, galleries,
you know, with respectable galleries around town, and we'd all shown at all these underground
galleries. We like to keep our work within the popular culture. In other words, we like to,
we like our work to be mass distributed, so we work in comics, and magazines, and we do album
covers, and things like that as well. Vietnam veteran Doug Wellman. In an 1970,
we were challenging each other to see what kinds of pirate signals we could broadcast,
and my joke had to be taking a turntable up in this aircraft, and on the flight I did it,
we had a crew chief who got an air metal or some metal force shooting down
seven of 11 MiGs. He was playing Electric War Game next to me, and I'm broadcasting
Louie Louie and Aqualung 2.
To, uh, to these pilots at the same time.
The show includes five other artists whose work you may have seen, but not on a gallery wall,
maybe in your record collection, or in Playboy, or Pep House, or Hot Rod magazine,
and the show features memorabilia of the bad influences.
On these artists, a big hot rod in the middle of the floor, horror movie posters, a robot collection,
cheap toys. Here's George Ann again.
Barbie. Oh, there's a big Barbie dream house over there. Barbie, I just loved. I thought she was
like the most wonderful woman. She just had everything. She was the best body. She had a
gigantic cranium, so you knew she was brilliant. She just had it all, so she was kind of, you know,
subconsciously that became like the woman I wanted.
be I suppose.
Next to the hot rod is the many layered graphic comic book art of Robert Williams, along with some of his psychedelic paintings circa 1968. He was one of the
pioneers of underground comics in the 60s, starting as a cartoonist for Ed Big Daddy Roth's Hot Rod Magazine.
What you got here is you got influences that affected people young and more like poison. In my display over here, I got like early EC comic books that the
Kieffhofer committee outlawed in the 50s because they were so good. The draftsmanship was beautiful. The stories were fantastic.
That's cool.
They had sex and violence, gratuitous sex and violence. The stories were just a little heavy. They were saying that these comic books were like, you know, poisoning our children.
One of Williams' comments in the full color catalog is a key to the show. If it commands attention, it's culture. If it matches the couch, it's art.
Let's face it, you know, that's a fact. And that's not bad. That is not a bad thing.
It's a good thing.
If the people are happy and the painting matches their couch, that's all right. A painting like any of these would destroy anyone's living room.
The show also includes work by Byron Werner, psychedelic mandalas based on movie stars or other cultural icons.
There are wall-sized murals by Gary Panter, the creator of the Jimbo comic strip, and recently the Emmy-winning designer of Pee-Wee's Playhouse.
In other instances, the Northeastern comics are the only ones who have been able to make a living in the world.
For some, J.D. Rischer apparently intended to write a film about the
history of American culture.
J.D. Werner was very interested in each human being and came to the knowledge he had of walks by their ancestors, subjects they looked like warriors, and people we saw in the kingdom.
In principle, in terms of the fehltive tranquility, the Chinese heaven, it's indeed very wild.
J.D. For instance, variety of пов together's media outlets is written about one or two different kinds of lovers.
For instance, great writer James weighted one man and —
Dom reperio used
him as a prop image.
Post-C kits and aha, you expectwar and a lot of women.
naming each one of us, telling us what we're having in our box lunches,
maybe naming a couple of things on the aircraft like a book
or something that was there before flight time, a few hours before flight time,
and I would imagine was carefully scoped out by a Vietnamese compatriot on the ground.
And so within an hour or two after takeoff,
they'd have all this info that seemed like they were on the airplane with you,
like a spy was in your midst.
I have a feeling that thing's still alive.
A delicious Blooperton sundae.
It is.
Boy, is this thing ugly.
Wow, does it stink.
Smells bad.
Yes, Topo Jijo, I know.
We still must take it in.
Because it is hungry and has no place to go,
its fur is matched and it needs a place to sleep.
I don't know.
It only wants to be friends.
Friends, huh?
You think this thing has an intellect?
Next thing you'll be telling this thing can feel and think like us.
Smoke.
Good.
Here, take this torch.
Torch.
Good.
I think this thing is going to be a good show.
Yes, and so the show crawled toward its end.
I think he's accepted some basic information
and is now ready to go on to the second phase of his monstrous career.
Not a phase.
It didn't phase the show.
Yes, the show monster kept on and on.
It seemed like his brief life had been a long one
as he learned the mysteries of art and science.
Really?
Yes.
He learned to calculate the third and most mysterious ray,
the great ray that lies beyond the spectrum.
Come on, I just want the end of the show to come
before we get to fly back to some other city.
I think it's St. Louis now.
Stuart has served me raw eggs.
And then she gave me out-of-date chewing gum.
And then she wouldn't give me a date.
Then she wouldn't let me out of the bathroom.
She didn't say a thing about me.
Then she wouldn't let me off the plane.
And then she kept making me drink more of that coffee.
Treating me like a drug.
And then she gave me a three-day-old newspaper.
And she gave me these pills.
Did she give you any of those?
I was on the plane taking the pills.
That's all I remember.
Then...
Last but not least, there's the lead singer of Devo,
Mark Mothersbaugh, with his wall of hand-drawn postcards.
They're two chunks out of a diary that I've been keeping
for about 15 years.
You're in some radio station about to talk to a disc jockey
who's really into Aerosmith and could give you it
whether he talks to somebody from Devo or not.
Or, you know, you're waiting to show up in court
in a court battle between Virgin Records and Warner Brothers
and you're just like some stupid pawn that's been trapped in the thing.
You know, so I just sit there with postcards.
And I used to mail them off, and then after a while
I ran out of friends, so I started saving them
and they turned into my diary.
Just like I told Hitler that time,
back when we were just a couple of fronting buddies.
One man's bummer is another man's beautiful thang.
And he always believes in that.
I have sent for you, Dodgers, because we are facing a crisis.
The world's supply of Eludium Fosdex, the shaving cream atom,
is alarmingly low.
Now we have reason to believe that the only remaining source is on Planet X, somewhere
in this area.
And you want me to find Planet X, is that it?
Can you do it, Dodgers?
Oh, in doobly-doobly-doobly-doobly, sir.
I'm Sinbad the Sailor, so hardy and hale.
I live on an island on the back of a whale.
It's a whale of an island, that's not a bad joke.
Its lord and its master is this handsome bloke.
Oh, the most remarkable, extraordinary fellow.
Sinbad the Sailor.
I scare all creation on land or on sea, but talk about women, they all fall for me.
I take my adventures wherever they're found.
I go on the brag boat.
I've been around.
I'm the most, the most phenomenal, extra special kind of fellow.
I'm Sinbad the Sailor.
Oh, my.
Oh.
Unfalteringly and without ceasing and without pleasure, the long-hanged one proceeded past the little girl's underpants.
For was it not written in the time of Noninglianiox that he who shall be the one of the batteries shall endeavor ever forth and proceeding vastly superior to that which has never been known? And it was so.
Now we'll try this pair. Ah.
He's just trying to figure out whether his batteries are working.
I can see clearly into the future and backward dimly into the past.
Wherefore, I shall secrete not thine fluids from them, because I love the sound of the word them.
It is neither them nor they, and yet it is them.
Thame.
I was suddenly struck in the back with an armor-piercing needle, the kind which has never been known before in this realm or any other realm except for all others except this one.
And I said to them, I said,
Thame, am I not Peshi in front of your mother?
Mother?
Eh?
Thine gray-headed, olden, gelatinous, lithide, Grecian mount-beast.
Thine mater.
The one from whence thy came.
Pfft.
As she achieved Sitor Spasm, a large...
...voluminous material shot rapidly out of her.
...igniting thusly on the friction of the hairs of that self-same region.
Who killed Bambi?
Who killed...Bambi?
Who killed Bambi? Who killed Bambi?
For your story
Bambi is dead.
There may still be time.
We must believe there is time to change our lives.
We have much to overcome.
Our own superstitious or religious faith in power.
Our suicidal self-hatred, the product of millennia of patriarchal training.
And a need to be more than we are.
Consider.
We must approach the future positively.
Monsters like a dead man will be around me all night.
Until we need to look past the door which should be locked.
And back.
My silences will terrify me and bring me no element of balance.
For my spirit is locked away inside the quiet storm.
Which will make you suffer from suspense.
The Exists have landed.
Their machines are following our tracks.
Bob's vision.
Stands proven.
A world without slack.
Thank you, Bucknaked.
But what is the commodity with which Bob will bargain Earth's fate?
Some claim it is the souls of his followers.
The true subgenius does not question Bob's wisdom in such matters.
We have only our simple faith that Heaven will be ours.
If we only believe.
Ironically, his mission will not be to sell Earth, but to prevent Earth being sold and transformed into a kind of stuckies in space.
Don't forget that Bob has come to his prophecy at the end of the world, July 5th, 1998.
Okay?
When most Americans will have handovers, but it's not just for the Americans, it's for everyone in the world.
I didn't hear that.
Yeah.
Right.
That is why...
I'm gonna start smoking again.
Oh.
Yeah.
Start smoking, start drinking, and live it up.
Start fornicating as if your very life depended on it.
But this plan will succeed only if conditions are just right at the appointed time.
Otherwise, dark forces of antiquity will be awakened from their slumber of eons and rise again from Atlantis to rule our world in their sizeless nip.
These primordial elementals, the Elder Gods, have countless demonic and interplanetary minions carrying out their unholy schemes.
They even control Bob's own evil twin brother, Dick God, the Unclean.
Now, friends, I ought to mention that what we're hearing right now is actually the soundtrack from the subgenius video.
Which you can go see for free at the, uh, Marriott... at the Fantasy Fair, Dallas Fantasy Fair, this Friday night at 10 o'clock at the Marriott Hotel at Coit and LBJ.
Now, try to imagine, try to figure out what images did we put with this soundtrack?
Go ahead.
Could God really be defeated by these beings?
Ah, but you must not underestimate the conspiracy.
Its weapons are so insidious, even the human conspiracy leaders are unaware of them.
The fact that the conspiracy itself is ignorant that it is a conspiracy gives it such control over our minds that the very thought becomes unthinkable.
You cannot think about your own minds! That's part of the problem. You cannot think about your own mind.
You cannot wash so if you cannot see your own mind.
You cannot run from your own legs. You cannot hide from the guy who's stupid as you are. You cannot hide from the guy who's buried you.
He's buried you in all reality!
That was my shit, I got my legs pulled away, you got it? My legs are on fire!
The bovinity and temerity of the human mind itself does all the work.
The evil ones may just lean back and watch the little humans march gladly, even proudly, to their doom.
But we, too, must be vigilant.
For, thanks to the false slack bombarding us daily, it is terrifyingly easy for even a subgenius to slip back into normality.
Why is it that the Doctors for Bob on one hand attack capitalism and all it stands for,
on the other hand you seem to be constantly asking for donations, like for KBF or for the Doctors.
Or KANON.
You're always asking for a million dollars up here.
For KANON.
Well Gary, if we want to destroy the concept...
Who needs it?
If we want to destroy the concept of money, it's gonna take money. And lots of it.
We are in danger of losing the entire ministry. I hate to say it.
I'm not just talking about the radio ministry, I'm not talking about just the TV ministry,
I'm not talking about just my personal jet, I'm talking about the home for slackless children,
I'm talking about the research center for the causes and cures of normalcy in Dobstown, Malaysia.
I'm not asking for this money for myself. I want people to think about the babies, the children that are starving.
You can't grow a fruit tree by planting babies. There's 10 million babies that are dropped into the ground every day.
And we're asking the people of Little Rock tonight to come in and pledge donations of one million dollars to Doctors for Bob.
We are five million dollars in debt.
If we could only get five people to call in with pledges of one million dollars...
So it's 823-7490. Or 828-9500.
...be so hardened that he wouldn't want to give a million dollars to Doctors for Bob.
But a man knows, you know, you come up here and ask a million dollars, you know...
Is there any truth to the insidious charges that you actively encourage people to do?
...to hate one another and consider this to be a positive thing?
I mean, someone's considering to give a million dollars to the Doctors or the KABF.
K-A-N-O-N.
You know, surely something to think about. It really is.
Think about it, friends. Send those pledges in.
Oh, there's another one. Praise Bob!
If you really want a first class seat on those escape crafts that are gonna take off in 1998,
pledge in your million dollars to Doctors for Bob.
Escape crafts, huh?
That's right.
Kind of like the shuttle, right?
Yeah, in 1998, when the X's invade, only people who have sent money in to Doctors for Bob...
And K-N-O-N.
...will be able to escape on the X's sausage.
And we don't want the money. We take the money and we put it in big piles and burn it.
But the smoke, the part of your soul which is attached to it, it's not gonna be burned.
The price to the dollar goes up with the smoke.
Your soul will be received by our interplanetary space guardian and lobe.
Ye shall be saved.
Yeah, yeah, praise Bob.
Oh, yes, yes, yes, dear friends.
And that was Jaynor Hypercletes on Sister Station KABF.
It's a show attack here.
And remember, December 6, Jaynor is coming to town.
That's right, Jaynor Hypercletes in a rare, rare public rap.
The Jaynor Hypercletes Comedy Show and Subgenius Revival at Club Dada.
Club Dada.
On December 6.
So, you folks, don't you be missing out on the incredible Dr. Hypercletes, the beat poet of the 80s.
Dear friends, you don't have to know anything about Subgenius to enjoy a show like this.
It's a Jaynor Hypercletes show.
He does, aside from the preaching, he also does...
Oh, the...
I...
My son Andy, Andy Kerr.
By the way, my name's Graham Kerr.
And this is Negative Land.
Negative Land, dear friends, from Famous Potatoes.
When my son was just 10, he made his first attempt to follow in my footsteps.
And I think he was jolly successful.
You know what he cooked?
His favorite dish, scrambled eggs.
They were soft and creamy, and I really couldn't have done better myself.
I'd like to share our secret for perfect scrambled eggs.
Just whip four eggs together without liquid.
And season them.
And then pop them into melted butter.
You know, when the butter is just at the point of browning and smells like hazelnuts,
that's the time to add the eggs.
Add the eggs.
Stir them rapidly.
And when they look just right, add a quarter cup of cold milk.
This little trick halts the cooking process that so often makes eggs dry.
Fresh eggs are one of the world's great delicacies.
They deserve to be treated with respect.
Right.
That was negative land.
Negative land on Ralph Records' famous potatoes compilation.
Mwurgh!
Once again, Dr. Philodrumon.
The Philodrumon German Hour.
I love the German stations.
They make you always feel like...
drinking beer.
You know, you listen to them and five minutes later
you're ready to chuck down about a quart of beer, man.
Your favorite beer.
It's a fine, manly thing to do.
To be proud of, so don't fear it.
That's right.
Stifle not thine fears of beer drinking.
Even if it's the non-alcoholic kind.
Now, the sweet strains of...
Erich Weinsteinfanker.
I'm going to translate this while they're singing it, Doug,
just for your benefit.
When I fly on Lufthansa,
I'm inspecting your navel.
Delving deep into the crevices in your...
I find nothing special.
The marbles of your eyes
roll themselves in quivering, quaint clusters of simian glee.
While foisting upon my fellow man,
near Valmaria.
Pain and suffering known not to none before now.
I sound my such dead lady.
I kill with wanton pleasure.
Delving deep into the sexual dimensions of...
I'm glad that...
So deep, my dead sinar.
I kill...
My empty one.
Ah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Ah, yeah, that's good.
Yeah, that's good.
Yeah, that's...
That's...
That's good.
My...
Yeah.
I'm glad that...
Oh, that was a breather.
And here's our goodbye, because it's time to go.
And so, arrivederci.
Would you mind telling me what there is left in that form?
Nothing.
Not a thing.
And goodbye, all of you, too.
Good...
Goodbye.
Well, it's not time to go yet, but it is.
But...
Hello.
Goodbye.
Elliot's heart almost stopped.
But he had to hang in there.
Oh, God.
After all...
Keep the show going.
He had to eat.
We've got to eat.
Keep the show...
Oh.
He saw blew his mind.
But he saw blew his mind.
We are here.
Where are you from?
I don't like his feet.
Let me feed you a little twerp.
Hey!
You can read along with me in your book.
You will know it is time to turn the page when you hear R2-D2 beep like this.
Get ready to turn over that cassette now.
Kids.
Oh.
Praise Bob.
You're listening to the...
You're listening to the Hour of Slack radio ministry here on K&ON 90.9 FM in Dallas, Texas.
And it will happen again.
It will happen again every Sunday night.
You can never, ever escape the show.
Totally.
I'll be right here.
All right.
Okay.
I've got it.
All right.
I'll be right here.
Oh, no!
Oh!
Oh, no.
Oh, my God.
Ha ha.
I have to go to the bathroom.
Oh, I don't know.
I've got to get to the bathroom.
Dream.
End of the tape.
Beginning in...
Oh, my gosh.
This is Doctors for Wotan here in the background.
The first reunion of Doctors for Wotan in about five years.
That's right.
This was actually after last week's show.
Dr. Drummond and I went home and did this horrible, horrible noise that you hear behind me.
But I think for the next ten minutes, we're going to begin our new Negative Land album series.
The new album from Negative Land, called A New Album from Negative Land on SST Records, has come into our possession.
And it's cool.
I've played some of these pieces before, but it's got new ones and they've been remixed.
I'm even on this record.
It's the only record.
The world that my voice is on.
Going.
We'll briefly here go to...
What song?
Backstage Pass by Negative Land.
On SST Records, dear friends.
I ask you to pick up a good time for the audition if possible tonight at Newton Hill,
cost 6.65 million İnteresca City Hall.
No Director RF drama.
For more requests, contact Sharp跟大家 I of 6antfs25.org an E예요x 6pls77124 4%
Do it at 525-936-5 ciento!
First go, man.
Ellie, like the shit.
Whoops.
Give up.
Friends, did you hear that?
I'm going to have to give up.
Give up.
I give up.
I'm sorry.
Subgenius is stupid.
Technology is good.
subgenius is stupid.
Pan-ON is good.
Till 10 o'clock at night
Communism is good
Christianity is stupid
Give up
Give it
From 5 o'clock in the morning
Till 10 o'clock at night
Communism is good
Christianity is stupid
Give up
Give it
spreads up to the Arctic part of the Ural Mountains.
It's crossed by nine northern parallels.
Ten fair-sized European states could be placed on its territory.
Besides indigenous residents, that is the Komi people,
there are also Russians, Ukrainians, Nenetses, Chuvashis, and Tartars.
And now let's go back into history a little bit.
A boy lying on skins behind our backs was turning the knobs of a small transistor radio.
And the tent was suddenly filled with an announcer's voice speaking Komi.
Then with music from Moscow, followed by English and French speech.
The recording was made at the Moscow Theater of Musical Media.
Now back to modern times.
Your attention please.
At the recommendation of the International Time Bureau,
commencing at 23 hours, 59 minutes, 60 seconds UTC,
an extra second will be inserted into the NBS time scale.
This adjustment is required to maintain internationally coordinated universal time
as broadcast from these stations in close agreement with UT1 or astronomical time.
SECURITY AGlaw you see no
reaction by today's Madison University.
Stewart Eskalender.
großen der Kompะ I evidently need to—
Choose our company repair.
In the U Müller Museum, Han적shêtre, 399 те
Z storeky
превыш rover
additional incommunistive
ulp
We got so much power, that's ridiculous.
We have...
Power, power, power, power, power, power now.
It's ridiculous.
We got so much power now.
Do you know how many time zones there are in the Soviet Union?
It's not even funny.
Do you meant...
That's ridiculous.
Do you know how many...
It's not even funny.
Do you meant...
That's ridiculous.
Do you know how many...
Do you know how many times...
That's ridiculous.
It's not even funny.
Do you meant...
Do you know how many time zones there are in the Soviet Union?
It's not even funny.
How many time zones?
Yeah.
We have four in this country, right?
How many time zones?
Yeah.
One, two, three.
Four in this country, right?
Behold, the bowels of the heavens shall be opened to smite and pump the earth with strangeness.
Ew, look.
It's the colon of the earth.
Let's pretend like we have a contest going.
We'll just call people in the phone book and say, you won.
A little bit farther up the colon.
Yes, there it is.
Lips flapping in the wind.
It doesn't have to be true.
Like hideous.
It takes a little more time.
Putting a little bit more of a wry thing on correct.
Make a living for the artists by your corporation.
Just a minute.
Just a minute!
I can't hear a thing!
Quiet, please!
Is there any escape?
Oh, there's so much noise!
I can't hear the music!
Is there any escape?
What orchestra is this?
The noise?
Hey, that's, uh...
Negative land, dear friends,
and this is KNON 90.9 FM
in Dallas, Texas.
Thank you.
I hear a lot of noise,
um, because, uh...
Well, you know, the big city isn't around here,
and once we do hear somebody shoot off
a couple of guns in the distance,
and...
uh, somebody grabs some tin cans or something,
that's about all.
So it's very quiet here in the neighborhood.
Wahoo! Look out! Here I come!
Michael Jackson!
Look what you've done!
Michael Jackson?
Better than my doll!
Open my dress with your old bicycle!
Paul McCartney and Michael Jackson?
Gee, Carol, those mud saints will never wash out.
Bruce Springsteen?
Oh, gee, what am I going to do?
Dan Healan?
Oh, I'm sorry, Carol. You were too close.
Tina Turner?
Marv! What good does that do?
David Bowie?
You know you aren't supposed to be riding your bike to your lunch hour.
Clash?
With Madonna?
QE West is the news?
With the cars?
Kirby Hancock?