And that's where it happened.
When I woke up, it was still raining, and I was lying on top of the mud like a man trying to find the sugar bowl at a restaurant under a grandstand.
The door to my apartment opened, and she sauntered in, moving slowly from side to side like a piece of bubble gum in a set of false teeth.
Her voice was all right, too. It reminded you of a furnace in a basement full of cats.
Good evening.
I stood up like a dirty, wet baby on a floor full of marbles.
Well, well. Talk.
No.
No? No.
Good. See?
Yeah.
He admits it.
I don't understand.
The rain had washed the makeup off her face, and she looked sharp and quick, like a piece of candy in a bad tooth.
Yes?
She looked like a stubborn seed in a deep freeze.
She looked like a guy who didn't figure on a leaf in a pool of water.
Yes?
She looked like a false baby on a furnace in a basement full of tea.
Oh, you take your work too seriously.
I don't understand it.
Be sure to join us next Sunday evening and every Sunday, same time, same station, for radio's newest show,
The Subconious Hour of Slack.
There's something about them you'll like.
Grigger, Dieblock, and Hardip, an old-running Tunican's best watch comedy.
I'm not talking about purity, I'm just talking about purity.
And that's from PR News.
I'm Bob.
I'm Paper Pat.
We're just gonna be.
And the Lost Fire.
I nearly saw it.
So, a stu-by-siveling.
And Celebrating Elvis.
And I was just staring at God.
First in news.
From PR News in Washington, I'm funded by Western governments, without the congressionally approved murderous criminals.
Speaking is over.
Sweet cozy bubble cozy.
Not that seven do looks too much.
At the boo.
At the time.
At the boo time.
First sweeping cut.
And PR News.
The Obama administration is detached from reality and another attempt to cling to pure power.
The White House says this is PR News.
Indian law generally seeks savage gang rape and murder of the victim.
But that does not comport with the wishes of the family.
Prosecutors, meanwhile, say they have matched DNA to pure news found on the clothes of five accused men.
The U.S. Coast Guard is grounded in Alaska.
Crews are trying to connect a tow line after PR News hampered their efforts.
In Washington.
Ladies and gentlemen, once again, the Ask Dr. Hal show is here.
This is radio.
Hello, dear friends.
This is your annoying horror host, Dr. Harlan Dowell.
Hello.
Here in the great Sonoran desert.
Tonight, we expect a turbo-philosophy forum.
A crowd of sages to make the air redolent of their special aura with their discourse.
You will hear it.
And you will be, no doubt, amazed.
Dumbfounded, even.
And now, prepare to gird your loins for a journey that lies ahead through realms of endless night and sorrow.
But that's just to get to the good stuff.
Heya Tom, it's Bob from the office down the hall.
It's good to see you, buddy.
How are you?
How have you been?
Things have been okay for me, except that I'm a zombie now.
I really wish you'd let us in.
I think I speak for all of us when I say I understand
why you folks might hesitate to submit to our demand.
But here's an FYI.
You're all gonna die screaming,
All we wanna do is eat your brains.
We're not unreasonable.
I mean, no one's gonna eat your eyes.
All we wanna do is eat your brains.
We're at an impasse here.
Maybe we should compromise.
If you open up the door.
We'll all come inside and eat your brains.
I don't wanna nitpick, Tom, but is this really your plan?
Spend your whole life locked inside a mall.
Maybe that's okay for now, but someday you'll be out of food and guns.
And you'll have to make the call.
I'm not surprised to see you haven't thought it through enough.
You never had the head for all that bigger picture stuff.
But Tom, that's what I do.
And I plan on eating you slowly.
All we wanna do is eat your brains.
We're not unreasonable.
I mean, no one's gonna eat your eyes.
All we wanna do is eat your brains.
We're at an impasse here.
Maybe we should compromise.
If you open up the door.
We'll all come inside and eat your brains.
I'd like to help you, Tom, in any way I can.
I sure appreciate the way you're working.
You're not alone with me.
I'm not a monster, Tom.
Well, technically I am.
I guess I am.
I ain't no Impermanence.
I don't know who this Impossible Man is.
Tell me.
Everything's gonna turn into pure waste.
Talk to me about it, too.
Go.
Talk to me about this Impossible Man.
I've got another meeting, Tom.
Maybe we could wrap it up.
Yeah.
I know we'll get to common ground somehow
Meanwhile I'll report back to my colleagues
Who were chewing on the doors
I guess we'll table this for now
I'm glad to see you take constructive criticism well
Thank you for your time
I know we're all busy as hell
And we'll put this thing to bed
When I bash your head open
All we wanna do is eat your brains
We're not unreasonable
I mean no one's gonna eat your eyes
All we wanna do is eat your brains
We're at an impasse here
Maybe we should compromise
Open up the doors
We'll all come inside and eat your brains
Barnyard fowl.
Yes, they drop pellets and pellets.
They drop pellets in the barnyard.
And they're loaded on pellets.
They're loaded on whatever they can scoop up in omnivorous fashion with their reeking beaks.
Yes.
Now, if we were a pilot of a...
They'll eat a grasshopper or a caterpillar.
Excuse me.
But if you throw a fried chicken leg in there, they'll eat it too.
Yes.
Well, if you are a pilot of pellets of pullets, you certainly should win a pulleter prize.
If only to prize the premium...
Out of my dead gold fingers, yes.
Out of your...
I mean...
I hesitate to use the word...
Three cameras.
Seven diapers.
Three darts.
Four hours driving.
One new PA.
350 feet water.
80 miles of cake.
Two hosts in need of words.
And my left arm is not working.
I fear nothing anymore.
See you all in hell.
Well, you see...
We were speaking of the devil in a pejorative way...
Yes.
And I would like to get beyond that...
...into a more fair and equitable realm of discussion...
Yes.
Well...
...since we are churchmen and in charge...
Yes.
...of our own doctrine...
here in the Church of the Subgenius.
Yes.
Especially when the head of our order is here in the studio.
One must not commit a theological solacism.
A blasphemy.
Or trip over the skirts of doctrine.
Oh, my God.
I'm in terror whenever I speak before Stang
that I may emit a blasphemy.
We must all speak before Stang sooner or later.
Yes.
So many have died and have been tortured.
Oh, sorry.
Suffer not the fashionable fools
for the prices they pretend to give for contemptible works.
Yes.
I won't speak any more of that time in the Church when...
Well, we've all had to make deals, haven't we?
Yes.
We've all had to sign that watchful bottom line.
And one hesitates to use the word purge or, you know, genocide.
Mm-hmm.
But...
Yes, I heard genocide the other night.
Yes.
Less...
The...
The less said, the better.
Of course, we commit genocide on certain insects,
but we fail.
That's the problem.
Plenty more where they come from.
Exactly.
You see their dying generations at their song.
Fish, flesh, or fowl commend all summer long
whatever is begotten, born, and dies.
Caught in that sensuous music,
all neglect monuments of subgenius intellect.
Ah.
Was that Tennyson speaking prophetically of the Church?
No, it was Yeats.
But the...
Ah.
But the idea is true.
An early subgenius.
What involved in the business of reproduction and passing along the DNA
will isolate you from all other concerns.
Ah, yes.
Right.
Well, survival.
You must incubate your clutch of eggs so that...
Yes, that is the only important thing.
The right-hand path will be not wroth with you.
Yes.
But the left-hand path does deserve to be given some consideration.
Well, so...
Certainly it needs to balance the right-hand path and the sinister...
Demonology, or actually demon worship,
simply balances the right-hand path.
Well, yes.
And, of course, all such so-called devil worship is antinomian,
but so is the Church of the Subgenius.
Although we are pretending to be a part of the conspiracy,
we are, of course, completely opposed to it
and only using its special luster and hallmarks for our own purposes.
Yes, feeding on it...
Something which can't be stressed too often.
Yes, feeding on it and killing it from within
in the same way that a virus kills a host...
Like Larry the lovable lamprey...
...uses its own...
Sinking his lance-like teeth into the quivering flesh of the bulbous host.
Yes, fast and bulbous, as Captain Beefheart used to say.
Speaking of which, have you seen this wild Indonesia?
Some of the most beautiful animals in the world.
What are you?
Crawling them out.
Really?
You mean this is like a...
Creatures I've never seen before in a film so rare
that you're not allowed to Facebook it.
Things like the orus and the slug bear and the squealer monkey?
Well, various rays, stingrays, of course, the great cuttlefish are well-known,
but a lot of these are much more...
They're well-known, but not until recently documented.
And, but there's creatures, many, many,
that have not been known until the last year or two,
or three, and they're unbelievable.
They're like the cuttlefish.
They're spectacular, very hallucinogenic creatures,
some of which...
There's one...
This may be a ray, a manta ray,
but some kind of a ray which actually walks on the ocean floor,
on little legs,
and, you know, disguises itself as the ocean floor.
I don't know.
I just...
PBS...
Stoned.
And I always want to talk to the great Douglas Long
and ask him questions.
I wish we had a veteran zoological PhD that...
You know, Pete Goldie's pretty good for that stuff, too,
but he's decided that a night at the opera with the Marx Brothers
is preferable to being here and the Ask Dr. Howe Murray crew.
How could that be?
A film he's probably seen how many times?
One cannot...
Fathom the tile setter's mind.
Well, this is the incredible coincidence of the two asteroids,
and, you know...
Well, it's not that incredible.
Where there's one, there's likely to be another.
Well, but here's another coincidence,
is that he doesn't show up on the show,
and I'm wondering if he isn't using his astronomical power
to actually bring the satellite towards the Earth
and crash it in some way.
To fulfill some grudge of its...
Like the mad inventor of the magnetic telescope
in the Superman, Max Fleischer cartoon?
Exactly.
An evil telescope that somehow causes planets to come to Earth.
That's right.
That was probably issue 187.
You know, ladies and gentlemen,
I think all our problems are soon to evaporate
like snow upon the water because K-Rob is in the building.
He'll slice his way through these technical issues.
K-Rob!
And this...
Oh, yeah.
Yes, yes.
As soon as he...
K-Rob!
May be here.
He may be here.
He is here.
But don't you forget it.
Now he's going to the bathroom, of course.
I hope that's what he's doing.
Well...
He's a music critic.
I hope he goes to the restroom before he does.
Well, I hope he goes when he does.
Yes, and when he wants, and not...
Will I, nill I.
Well, I don't know about you,
but I'm going to move some things out of the way
so he can settle in and...
Okay.
Work his magic.
Yes, it is magic.
Let us not beat around the bush.
That's right, folks.
What he does cannot really be explained
by that thin book we call science.
It's an act of reality imitation
on the spur of the moment
with a sensitivity...
A sensitivity that can't be matched
by the hummingbird hovering in front of the piston
or stamen or whatever the...
The caterpillar on the leaf
repeats to thee thy mother's grief.
Yes.
Kill not the moth nor the butterfly
for the lost last judgment draweth nigh.
That's right, folks.
So, repent.
Slack off.
Send in your money.
Quit your job for Bob.
Go down your subgenius checklist.
Don't forget, even though we're being very reflective,
contemplative here,
we do have subgenius royalty,
subgenius founders in the room.
That is true.
By the bucket load.
Let all know,
and let all who hear us now know
that this room contains the cream,
the core of subgenius,
and...
And if anything, may Allah forfend,
occur to those in this room,
the church would flicker and die
like the fitful flame of a candle.
And that's exactly why it's kept a secret from all.
In the name of Allah, the All-Merciful, the Compassionate.
Cut into a mountain,
the side of a mountain with a rock in front of the hole,
we conduct our radio transmissions.
Yes, it is necessary to be hidden
for the...
For the sake of this time in our cave redoubt.
Yes, we don't know who will be after us,
but there are many, many who would like to destroy us.
I went out last time.
You go out this time.
Well, I've got to get some pretzels.
Yes, of course.
We must feed the inner mass.
I think I need some...
And so it was written long ago,
even unto these sacred scrolls,
that a deliverer would appear,
riding above the multitudes,
on a special chariot.
And the people said,
but how could...
Could this be?
Who is this man who is to come?
And how is it that a chariot might fly?
What are you doing over there?
The horse was thirsty.
Oh, you see, the special chariot
doesn't actually involve a horse.
I was trying to get to that.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Yes, there's no horse involved.
A horse of another color, I guess.
Yes.
Maybe the Tartar horse,
the horse of brass on which the Tartar king did ride.
And if all else...
I don't know.
I love a Tartar horse.
We used to have those in a cafeteria in third grade.
You may have your Tartar sauce if you want.
Go ahead.
Why did they make that call?
Enjoy your Tartar sauce.
I mean, is it really...
Because it came from the plains of Tartary.
Oh, my God.
Turks used to keep it warm between their thighs and the saddle.
So it's jism from Turks?
I never said so.
You have this...
No, no, no.
No, it's not.
It's a salty sauce.
It's a salty sauce of the Black Sea.
Why is it green?
It could be...
It's not supposed to be green.
Don't you see?
It says refrigerate after opening.
Oh, I see.
I see.
Well, there was nothing like fish...
Don't judge all Tartar sauce by your science project.
Well, in Massachusetts, I remember, we used to call it Tartar sauce.
You talk about the same thing.
Tartar sauce, right?
Yeah.
All right.
Be that way.
Tartar sauce.
Okay.
Tossed salad?
Sure.
Yeah.
That's what we had.
Every Friday, I think.
Fish sticks with Tartar sauce.
And you loved it.
And you crawled 20 miles to get there.
20 miles?
That's right.
Through the snow and the wind at age five after working and milking the cows.
And you liked it.
But then you started to take drugs and you didn't like it.
You learned to take it and like it.
Yeah, you learned you didn't like it anymore.
Well, you weren't taking it in the right way.
Well, I suppose, yes.
You got to...
You got to take...
I'll bet you didn't know that tartar sauce, when taken in mass quantities, can be a hallucinogenic substance.
Really?
Oh, my God.
Well...
You just have to eat so much of it that you become physically ill.
Yes.
From PR News in Washington, I'm being charged as an adult.
Facing up to a million years in prison and $35 in fines.
Saying, quote, now is a time for PR News.
The suspect faces several counts, including attempted PR.
President...
President Obama says not.
Not.
The president said...
On Wall Street, 181357.
Despite several days of French airstrikes, Germany does plan to combat Canada, Britain, and the U.S.
as it tries to keep Mali's capital.
According to the Chinese embassy in Sudan, this is PR News from Washington.
Also in the news, large, unexplained glowing light in skies frightens Russians.
In other news, explosive bowel syndrome hits the city in a massive wave.
And to what do you attribute this, Dr. Drummond?
Bad.
People need to wash their hands more often.
Yes, there are those rules in restaurants.
And we can put the cute girl right on that one.
Bad hygiene.
The great spy.
It's funny, I have...
Oh, now we have a run on...
Where are those ladies?
Those ladies at the night.
Pest.
Hey.
Only because it's nighttime.
All the microphones are working.
Yes.
Hey, Rob, fix them all.
In an instant.
As I predicted.
Shot into space with the speed of a bullet.
I heard several predictions about that.
Shot into space.
And you have your headphones on now?
Yes.
So we're all comfortable?
We are all comfy.
Comfy?
I heard that prediction.
Prediction.
I don't know.
Maybe we could get other guests to come.
We've got another mic.
Yes.
One more mic.
Still, we could get that girl.
I think you could persuade...
We could get that girl.
Get that girl.
That's right.
Hey, you want to...
Bet your bippy?
What do they used to say?
You bet your bippy.
Can I pick on you?
Man, not...
Don't talk about laughing.
I know.
It gives me...
It causes acid flashbacks.
Yeah, I know.
It gives me bummers.
It's bad.
It makes me remember everything that ever happened to me in the past.
It makes me hate nature.
It makes me want to hate...
Because you watched it on acid probably.
It makes me want to hate nature.
It crushed your brain.
Because nature is so mean to humans.
I hate nature.
And I lived it over and over and over again.
It's mean to us.
Yeah.
And then I had to listen to the recordings of it.
Asteroid.
I know.
And then I had to relive listening to the recordings.
I had to be...
You can't count asteroids as nature.
Let me tell you.
Nature was mean to the Russians today.
I had to be in the eighth grade class that put on a laugh in.
Really?
Assembly class.
Eighth grade assembly class.
Dreary.
We put on laughing.
Rowan and Martin laughing.
Did the girls wear bikinis?
Nobody laughed.
No, it wasn't sexy.
Smiley face.
Yeah, no.
And people didn't laugh, did they?
People weren't sexy then.
Yeah.
There was no goldie on there.
Ten-year-old or 12-year-old girls were not considered sex bombs.
This is like 68.
Maybe by you.
68.
Yeah.
When you're there...
Well, by me, actually, yes.
I thought...
Yeah, me too.
I can see...
I was back then.
Then, at the time...
Yeah.
They don't have the same effect on me now.
I have more of a fatherly approach to all those children.
I should be a Catholic father.
Once again.
I should become a priest since I like children.
I know.
I should be a monk for the amount of, like, restraint that I...
Or you could be a monkey artist or a monkey god.
A monkey.
A monkey monk.
A monkey god?
Yeah, well, monkeys get some, you know, like the bonobo.
But monkeys are also famously frustrated.
Frustrated.
Bonobos are not monkeys.
Bonobos.
They are apes.
Thank you, Sting.
Apes.
I take that pretty personally when people get that mixed up.
Me too.
Because you don't want to be part of their group.
I will not tolerate it.
I see.
Monkeys are horrible.
As you were saying, apes are noble by comparison.
Yes.
Well, perhaps.
King Kong died for your sins.
Many monkeys, however, like spider monkeys and rhesus monkeys, are cute.
Only if one is a...
A sickening sentimentalist drenched in the pathetic fallacy.
I'm no kin to the monkey.
The monkey's no kin to me.
No, you're saying they're not cute.
I put a monkey in your pants.
What about a tarsier's?
Tarsiers are incredibly cute.
The finger monkey.
The squirrel and spider monkey.
The squirrel.
They're cute.
They're tiny and cute.
The bong monkey.
They're still...
Don't forget the bong monkey.
Yes, but they are still cute.
The master bathing monkey of Java is so cute.
Until they do something, and then they're not so cute.
The butt-picking monkey of...
Well...
South Africa.
But picking monkeys is...
That's Pithica.
The pee-drinking monkey of Borneo.
Of YouTube.
Well, then there's the...
Raving the farmer's field for the peas.
Of YouTube.
And then there's the lung-spitting llama.
Yes, that...
They're terribly cute.
That lung-sang rampa.
Especially if you get that green hanging...
The pee-drinking butt-picking monkey of YouTube.
The gigantopithecus is an ape of the...
But, you know, he needs to clean that well.
...high steps.
It's called the abominable snowman.
But, you know, there are also other primates living in that area.
Yes.
Snow monkeys, we call them.
We get snow monkeys.
Go home, snow monkey.
Oh, no, that's what the Russians call the fins.
There's no monkeys like snow monkeys.
No, I don't know.
And they don't have fins.
I don't know.
I've never heard of racism in the North Pole.
I've never heard of that.
Well, that's because you have to...
Snow monkeys.
...take off your parka before people can see how you are complected.
Exactly.
It's just nylon up there.
Everybody is just nylon and, you know, polyethylene or whatever you put it.
Polyethylene dances.
Parka.
Borodino.
I would never go.
Reb Stang, would you go to the North Pole or the South Pole?
No.
I have no interest in going anywhere but solid ground.
I don't want to go deep.
I don't even want to go deep under solid ground.
No.
I don't want to go out in the ocean.
Forget about it.
It's too cold.
It's cold.
Do you want to go on solid ground?
On solid ground.
No dirigible rise?
And not too high above.
Yeah.
It's not falling that I fear, but hitting the ground.
The through.
Do you want to go through?
Falling is probably fun.
Would you go in a canyon?
What about the dirigible?
Back in the day, I probably would have tried anything, but I was so surprised to reach
the age of 45 that I became careful.
Oh, yeah.
One time.
I'm cautious.
It shocks you.
Especially at 50.
You're just not ready for it because you haven't really planned to live.
Oh, yeah.
Over 40 years.
That would have, that seemed ridiculous.
Yeah.
Insane.
Seems ridiculously insane to me.
Control yourself.
But then you get greedy.
After you hit 45, you go, wait, maybe I could make another 45 years.
Yeah, sure.
I want to live to be.
Why did I smoke all the time?
I want to live to be 90.
Oh, yeah.
That's me too.
We can, we can hit.
Go for 99.
Hit the cusp.
You know, you're supposed to be able to live to be four or 500 if you hit the cusp of when
technology catches up with you.
Oh, yeah.
You know what I mean?
The hippie from England guy with the long hair.
Right.
The singularity.
But he doesn't, he's not thinking about the ideogularity, which is neck and neck race with
the singularity and maybe drawing ahead.
Oh, I know.
So you got your, you know, sure.
We might have a computer smart enough to save us from ourselves.
Yeah.
Or maybe they'll.
Or maybe not.
Maybe they're smart enough to kill us.
That's right.
Maybe, maybe they saw Terminator and they'll shut that thing down before.
I'm sure they'll have the singularity.
They'll save us from ourselves by killing us instead of killing us.
Instead of us killing ourselves.
Now, Dr. Drummond, you told me earlier today that you want to live to be a very old age,
but not because you love life, only because you want to live longer than everyone else.
Right, right.
It was simply one upmanship.
I don't really care about being immortal.
It was one upmanship.
I don't care about living forever.
I only want to live 500 years longer than the last human.
That's right.
So that you win.
You know what?
I would like.
I win.
I would just like.
The biggest toys, all the toys are mine.
You don't win.
Because you have to endure everybody's death and be alienated.
Well, but you're happy.
See, everything passes away.
Okay, but that'll take me like maybe 20 years to get over.
This is Dr. Drummond we're talking about.
You think he's going to feel all that sad?
I will.
No, he's going to go, hey, at least it wasn't me.
It wasn't me.
I will be sad.
Better him than me.
But remember, I've got 500 years to endure it.
So it's only going to be like the first two or three years that I'm going to be sad.
And after that, I'll be going.
All right.
Now, I can't be just sad forever.
I got to start picking myself up by my own bootstraps and getting back to doing something.
I like those bootstraps, by the way.
Those are great new boots.
My bootstraps.
Which you can't do.
I'm hoisting myself up by my own bootstraps.
And no one's worn any straps in their boots for about, what, 150 years?
I've got bootstraps in my boots.
No, that's not good.
I'm hoisting myself with my bootstraps.
You know, you shouldn't have mentally disabled people in your shoe closet.
That's what the names of bootstraps are, you know.
That's how Sam calls them.
Bootstraps?
Bootstraps.
Potards.
Oh, like being hoist on your own potards?
Right.
Oh, but what?
That's what those little things in your boots are called is potards.
Yeah, but then they changed it to being blown up by your own grenade.
Or blown up by your own little poot.
Or, yeah.
That's what potard means.
You mean when you try to go to the bathroom a lot and you only go a little?
No, when you...
Like a poot?
Is that what you...
A poot, yeah.
Like a poor.
I just love where this conversation is going.
Yeah, I don't know.
He starts using words like poo.
Yeah.
You know, I don't...
Poot.
I turned into the trailer trash show.
Yes.
A poot.
A poot, indeed.
I'm a poot to get off of this microphone if you boys keep talking that way.
P for free, a penny a poot.
Okay, well, let's cut that part out in the next slide.
We'll take it out because it is a besmirch on our reputation.
Yeah, the besmirch is my honor and my dignity, my integrity.
I never used to watch the smirches anyway.
Those are endangered creatures.
Yeah, they were endangered.
Dr. Trump.
You know, we'll have to have a do.
Dignity, honor, integrity.
Yours, yeah.
It's a...
I'm the only one with any one laugh.
Everyone's duty is to stomp on every squealing smurf that is possibly...
I didn't want to be the last guy with integrity, but...
Well, you know, I don't want to live...
We've sort out that way.
I don't want to live longer than everyone else.
I just want everyone else to die earlier than I do.
And then I will have...
I think that explains Filo's approach.
Even that.
Fooly.
Yeah.
It's not that he wants to live longer.
He wants to see everyone die earlier.
And think how strong he is and how weak those may are.
I'll be sad for about 10, maybe like two or three years.
So sad.
And then the other 497 years, I'll be just like...
Party!
Party down.
I'm doing it for all of you guys that died.
I'm going to party like hell for you.
Party down, man.
For my old...
You know, I might live...
For like two or three hundred years and be sad that they're all gone.
But by then I'll have like plenty of robot friends and things.
And blow up dolls and stuff to keep me company.
I could do like that guy on the island and have like handprints for faces on blow up...
On a deflated soccer ball.
And you'd be happy with that.
Yeah, happy with that.
Or as a sex mate, the deflated soccer ball.
Yeah, but remember all the animals by then will be...
You'll be the sex mate then, though.
All the animals, though, will be conscious.
And so you'll be able to have sex with animals.
I'll be talking with the animals, though.
They'll be talking and having relationships.
You'll be chattering with the chimpanzees.
Having families.
You'll be having families with dolphins and some of the higher apes.
Now, that's just not likely.
I...
You know, let's not be...
Well...
Fantasistic.
Well, I have 500 years to evolve, too, you know.
So who knows?
My DNA might be up by then.
I'm thinking bioengineering.
You know, bioengineering.
We'll be able to create any kind of creature we want.
You know, human half, human half, whatever.
So sad.
Maybe they're diseased.
You know...
Diseased?
They'll have diseases, yeah.
But they won't care.
They'll just be...
You know, I've got to get some air.
It will be a world of no disease.
Get some arms.
No poverty.
Yes.
No sickness.
No war.
You'll be able to make love to any animal you want.
And it will be mutual.
It will be consensual.
They're all made out of rubber.
Love you.
That's right.
And never...
You won't need to sleep, work, eat.
You'll just lay around.
It will be a perfect...
A perfect paradise of sloth.
And sloth.
And indolence.
And...
Every temptation fulfilled to your wildest dreams.
You'll be taking in the absence of a Baudelaire.
You will be able to indulge every base pleasure.
Every taste pleasure.
You'll be able to bloom great flowers of evil that are incredibly sophisticated.
This is the only path.
To truth.
We will teach you how you can't dig up the dead and bring them back to life.
Now that is against the rules.
No!
They can be dug up.
The blackest sorcery.
The worst.
Reanimated.
Excesses of black magic.
The one thing you don't want to do is be a necromancer.
Well, they say that the first zombies that we got the word from were real and that these
creatures did till the fields at night in haste.
Yes, they did.
They're completely different from the George Romero movie monsters, though.
Because they're real, for one thing.
They're unfortunate souls who've given up their will and their individuality to the practice
of the nativistic shamanism.
Yes.
Speaking of real zombies, do you guys have any of that puffer fish?
Yeah.
Just a little...
Oh, yeah.
I do.
I have some of the talk.
I have some of the toxin right in my soxin.
The puffer fish is incredibly poisonous, but in just the right amount.
You cannot be injected with it, but you can smoke the...
Yes.
And you can become a zombie.
Now, is this different from the puff adder?
Someday there will be zombie bars where you can go and do puffer fish and be zombified.
Then you'll enjoy your job for the next three or four days.
Right.
Because you'll be high.
You'll be a zombie.
You'll go to your cube.
And you'll be fine.
Exactly.
You won't be bored.
You won't be looking at your watch all the time.
Right.
You'll be thinking about your next hit of puffer fish.
Yeah.
Exactly.
Well, you would.
But you know it's coming.
You're getting paid.
That's why you're working.
Be not puffed up.
I know.
So you can get the puffer fish that allows you to work.
Sure.
That's why the zombies do it.
That's why I do it.
It's like steroids for Armstrong or for a biker.
You know, you've got to have something to get you going.
Yeah.
Winners...
Some losers do drugs and some winners.
I think the...
Yeah.
No.
Video arcades have to say that.
I think many winners and many losers.
Almost equally.
Losers do drugs and some winners.
What a lot of build.
And medium people.
Malarkey, sir, if I may say so.
About the people in the medium.
Pure malarkey.
Comedians do drugs.
Well, they must inspire themselves.
They must need to depart from the...
Only anti-drug message producers do drugs.
That would be very good.
Yeah, that's right.
Because deep down inside...
Inside the crack.
What are they compensating for?
Yes, they protest too much.
Get them.
They're the...
Get thee away from me.
Oh, damn spot.
Get thee behind me.
Get thee behind me, coffee enema deliverer.
Oh, damn coach.
That's telling him.
Get thee behind me, doctor proctologist.
Doctor proctologist.
I saw that movie.
Get thee cord from behind my behind thee.
Jerry Lewis is...
The playful proctologist.
Get thee from behind me, Father McMurphy.
How many times, my son?
Yes, uh...
2,975 times.
Say 100 Hail Marys and then don't do it again.
Go and sin no more, you little malfeasance.
I've sinned so much I can't...
You're no longer a sin.
I have absolved thee.
I'm a 60-year-old priest.
I've been committing sins for 40 years.
The Lord will forgive.
Though your sins make your heart as black as a crumbling anthracite coal,
be ye washed in the blood of the Lamb and it will gleam like Mr. Clean's T-shirt.
Got a quarter for an old choir boy, Father?
A penny for the old guy.
No and no.
I'm sorry.
I'd only be encouraging you.
You need to work.
By the sweat of your brow.
Yes.
Dig post holes in the hot sun.
Learn the meaning of the dog.
That's the life of a zombie.
Can I have some more of that puffer fish so I can go back to work again?
Well, the life...
Of course you can, my boy.
The life of a...
I keep it right here in the chalice in the palace.
The life of a zombie is hard and he has to constantly be on the lookout for puffer fish.
On the other hand, the hours are great.
You get to work at night.
Be ye not puffed up.
And they are known as the only farmers in the world.
Who work at night, I believe.
Well, a lot of companies don't even bother to provide coffee, which would work almost as well as puffer fish.
They don't need to be...
You're keeping your zombies motivated to stick...
Keeping their nose on that grindstone.
Crossroads.
Wearing it away.
Maybe crossroads or something.
Since they're zombies, there's not much...
Poor zombies don't get any coffee, just like chain gang workers in Joe Arpaio's prison.
Who's he?
Oh, zombie, where are you?
He's America's toughest sheriff who...
Oh, right.
Brought back the chain gang.
Really?
The Arizona guy?
And racial profiling.
He's a horrible bastard and I hope he gets his.
And I'm on record as saying something.
Working on a chain gang.
You better not let the sun set on you in Arizona, Dr. Howe.
How did that go?
I know my way around Arizona, I think.
How did that song go?
I've been working on a chain...
Chain gang.
So we're gonna call mine.
Oh, there was one about a chain gang.
Oh.
Well, then it was...
Oh, that's one about...
We're gonna chain gang for Bob.
All the live long day.
Working on a chain...
That's, that's call mine.
Oh, no, that's call mine, right.
Yeah.
No, there's a...
The chain gang song is about Bob.
The chain gang might...
We're gonna chain gang for Bob.
Shuffle and clank into the call of mine.
Clink, clink, clink.
Yes, Colonel Clink.
We'll oversee the chain gang and all of its manifestations.
Oh, give me Bob.
Clank.
Let's just have a party.
I'm fusing my face.
Relax.
Clank.
It's...
It's fun.
Don't remember who I am.
It's time for...
Kicking up our heels.
Don't remember my face.
And making whoopee.
Whoopee.
There's a lot of old subgenius chain gang.
Here's a...
Here's one now.
Oh, thank you.
Subgenius chain gang song.
Oh, really good.
They had a different style.
They didn't...
They didn't sing in tune.
A little bit more swank.
Hit in the...
The rails.
Subgeni were more swank in the 50s than the chain gang.
They had Bob to inspire them.
This is a chain gang.
Yeah.
Subgenius chain gang.
This is what they sing while they were working out in the fields.
It's more quiet.
It's a goodbye with a high blow.
It's a little bit more easy going.
And I got as high as a steeple.
It's not the high energy, you know.
But we were intelligent people.
Steeple people, we call them.
Oh, the steeple people.
That's life, I guess.
Religious nuts.
I love the people.
Subgenius.
Steeple people.
Actually, my sister coined that term.
Really?
Well, this was Bob Hope's theme song.
You mean, you know, they go like, this is the hands.
This is the...
Right.
Tits.
These are the...
This is the house.
Here's the steeple.
Open the door.
Or this is the church.
Here's the steeple.
Open the door.
Where's all the people?
The rupture happened.
Next day, I'm left behind.
I didn't send my $35 to Jesus.
Oh, my God.
There's no people left.
They've been burned to death.
And the subgenius got away.
Life without people.
But that was a great part of the show.
This is a worst case scenario, ladies and gentlemen.
That's right.
That's my mom.
So genius pornography.
Life without people.
That's right.
Just blow them all up.
And then you can, like, get anything you want at the store.
And you can, you know, watch all the movies and not have to pay.
You know, the reason that asteroid missed us was because donations weren't up enough.
We didn't have the numbers.
Right.
The collection plate was far from full this day.
And so the asteroid passed us by.
Once again, ignored by Bob's judgment.
Yeah.
Who cares?
Well, why should he care if the collection plate ain't...
It's not full.
Are you telling me...
He's a jealous God.
An angry God.
Yeah.
Why, you're saying just because of our cheapness that he has not...
The hit was on and then it was called off?
He's a God with a full bladder and it's irritating him.
He's packing a mean load.
And he wants to get a move on.
It was prostate problems of later middle age.
Now we've got to wait to, what, 2047?
For the next...
Good to the last...
No, no.
Only until July 5th.
Oh.
1998.
Yeah.
We don't know...
You mean like...
We have no idea what today's date is.
Not really.
We don't know what planet this is for sure.
Well, it could be a Mayan calendar.
But we know by these stripes, we know that on July 5th, 1998, the world as we know will end for the pinks.
Yeah.
And we will be reborn.
We've saved.
It's as simple as that.
You know, it's funny.
I heard that about...
I'm afraid I may have to say it again someday without pay.
It's funny.
I heard that about last year where...
We were supposed to go from out of the planet of the clocks and...
It's just a test.
It's a yearly test.
And go to that terrible...
We know not which day.
Planet of the ape.
...is going to be the real thing.
But you just keep doing the drill and that way you'll know you'll be ready.
This is the planet of the ape.
Well, we'll always be at the assembly point.
And they did blow it all to hell.
Yes.
Yes, we know.
God damn them.
They did.
Well, but...
Yeah.
But this is the planet.
This is our second chance.
Yeah.
And it is just as bad as...
...as the first time.
Which we don't know anything about.
Right.
Well, according to our lawgiver, there was a terrible conflagration.
Caused by the humans.
Yes.
Per usual.
The filthy creatures.
Right.
Our...
Yes.
Compulsive masturbators.
Our cousins.
Yes.
Not good apes.
Not...
Proper, fragile...
Bad apes.
Monsters.
Well, they're bad apes.
But, you know, a creature has to have a certain status to be bad.
Whoever heard of a bad caterpillar?
But apes...
Right.
Have enough status to commit sins and be evil.
Bless them.
Well, baboons do commit murder.
That's been documented.
Yes.
And drive tractors in South Africa.
Even simple monkeys practice deceit.
Yes.
They lie through their teeth and smile at their friends.
Simple monkeys do.
And more subtle monkeys...
Yeah.
...don't get caught.
That's right.
So, oh, these little liars and razzle.
Speak for yourself, Dr. Half.
Well, it might only be a matter of time.
But, actually, once again, let's not have that invidious distinction.
We are apes, not monkeys.
Yes, well...
Great apes, though.
Yeah.
Truly great apes.
Well, really spectacular.
Not as great as grape apes.
Gigant, perhaps.
But great nonetheless.
Superb.
Stupendous.
Great in size.
More graced.
Very, very large apes.
John Clayton, Tarzan.
How can we praise ourselves more?
Somehow.
We have to think of ways.
Yes, the...
We must demand more bananas.
That's it.
The Titanic apes.
The banana...
No, that brings us back.
All right, more bananas.
Yes, we'll put that in.
I love bananas.
So, I...
And no more terrycloth on wireframe mothers.
No.
Well, what about...
I hated that.
Assured mutual grooming.
Some of the worst years of my life.
When I finally found out at the age of five,
and I looked in,
there's this coat hanger wire face,
just with little crumbling bits of foam,
just like falling off.
And that was your mom.
And that's mom.
Harsh, man.
It's a cold, cold world.
For us experimental apes.
You said you'd stay alive for me.
And, you know, her arm kind of fell off.
Well, you know, you can't expect perfection.
I just cried and cried.
All things must pass.
Your hopes can now be resurrected.
Everything worth having will be retrieved
after X-Day
to those who have paid their dues to the church.
They're tied.
It's so simple, so cheap,
and yet people go,
well, that's just what they want me to do,
so I won't do it.
Because they're contrary.
We understand.
It's natural.
Right.
It sounds like a con man.
It sounds like a con man talking to you.
Sure.
But, see, if we tell you...
It's too good to be true.
That's what they always say about a problem.
It's a profit.
But we know it's good, and it's true.
That's...
The thing is, if we tell you that we're not con mans,
that's the first sign that we're not con mans.
Right.
Well, a really good con man
would not go anywhere near the subject
and start talking about con men.
That's how you know we're not good con men.
Then you know...
We're the worst con men.
It doesn't mean you're honest.
It means you're an inept crook
wasting their time.
So they can trust us.
They can trust you as far as to the front door
when they're hobnail boots.
Let's kick your bombosity down the concrete steps.
Now, subgeniuses, you know,
con man doesn't mean conspiracy man.
He's confidence man.
Confidence man.
That's quite right.
He commits his crime by getting your confidence.
And by causing you to try to cheat somebody.
Yes.
And he's so friendly.
That's why you like him so much.
He's friendly, and you think you're getting the drop on him.
The friendliest guy around is the con man.
The friendly part isn't bad.
The twisting of...
Forcing one into a greedy attitude is bad.
And, of course, one pays horribly
by the complete success of the con.
But the con man, you know,
he tells you that it's all a con
and that so many other people are conning you.
No, he is the soul of probity.
Our kind of con.
They're always trying to sell you a pyramid scheme.
We're trying to sell you an eternity symbol
show.
We're trying to con you into the truth.
A dream.
That's what we're...
Yeah, we're trying to con you into believing in yourself for once.
They're conning you into thinking you're okay.
Believing in yourself.
It's all bluff.
As the Fireside Theater pointed out, it's all bluff.
You're born, and you start bluffing your way to a nipple.
Then you bluff your way through school, and you bluff your way through a marriage.
And you scream a little louder than you really should.
Your way through the radio show, and then the bluff is over.
And you reveal the bluff.
You bluff, but it's still a bluff, but you still reveal it, and it goes on forever.
But if you bluff, you bluff others into happiness.
That's right.
It's a lie, but it makes them happy.
That's right, and they want it.
It's like a pop song or a heater.
A heater or a piece of food.
Yeah.
A piece of music or, you know...
Or a hit movie.
A religion's just like a hit movie.
Anything that covers your eyes with illusion.
A playboy.
Fold out.
And deceit.
And...
It makes you feel better.
A fantasy.
It's okay to lie to yourself.
It makes you feel better.
Yeah.
Whatever gets you through the day.
That's right.
As the serial killers say.
Exactly.
And maybe in about 20 years, then you'll realize it, that you've been lying to yourself,
and you'll know the truth for about three days, and then that'll be good too.
Then you develop the most convincing lies of your whole lifetime.
Right.
Rock solid lies.
That cannot be shaken by doubters.
Exactly.
And that's why you have to...
Or bullies.
...believe in them even all the more passionately.
You believe it in yourself.
Of course.
You're just a pyramid of lies, but that's the way it goes.
There's nothing wrong with that.
That's the way nature intended it.
You have to be fanatical.
In fact, in this society...
That's how primates develop to this point.
Yes.
In this society, you really have to be kind of like a little tank sometimes.
A signifying monkey.
A signifying tank or monkey.
Well, yeah, but monkeys have a lot of...
They have teeth, as you pointed out.
They can be quite effective in their barbaric violence, but of course, so can apes.
And yet, they can produce the most beautiful music as heard in the background.
There you are.
Yeah.
A little monkey quartet played with George Shearing.
I guess you've noticed that my arms don't fit in my old suits
I guess you've noticed that I'm eating lots of jungle fruits
Anyway, more than I used to
I used to be so tall and thin
Now I'm not exactly sure which file I'm in
And I know there's a monkey in the future for you
And there's nothing modern science can do
I'm keeping the thumb
But I'm getting old
I'm devolving
I am devolving
I guess you've noticed that I can't sit still at dinner time
I guess you've noticed that I quit my job
And I learned to sign
Anyway, more than I used to
I used to have a little body hair
Now I have to use a razor everywhere
And I know there's a monkey in the future for you
Now I'm not exactly sure which file I'm in
I'm getting old
And there's nothing modern science can do
I'm keeping the thumb
But I'm getting dumb
I'm devolving
I am devolving
Why don't you agree with me?
I don't understand
How you expect me to defend my actions
Knowing what you now know
I'm devolving
I guess you've noticed that I can't sit still at dinner time
Heat the$ &&
Chill out
I'm d naive
But you feel regularly
Mine
All coming
Saying BBC
But are you so happy that you want to stay the night long?
What's in the gay black box?
I was just five years older than you
I guess you've noticed that I drag my knuckles
When I dance
I guess you've noticed that I stuff a tail
Inside my pants
Anyway, more than I used to
I used to see a movie now and then
Now I'm never gonna watch King Kong again
Cause I know there's a monkey in the future for you
And there's nothing modern science can do
Okay, okay
I'm keeping the thumb but I'm getting down
I'm devolving, I'm devolving
I am de-evolving
I'm devolving
De-evolving
I'm a coal miner's duster
From PR News in Washington, I'm accused of opening fire despite the objection of prosecutors and others.
Vice President Joe Biden said
Uh, uh, uh
Biden said
Uh, we could, uh, would, uh
Biden stressed that he's saying
I come to this meeting with a
With no mind
I come to this meeting with PR News
West Virginia Democrat Jay Rockefeller said Biden should rot in hell
Republican Congresswoman Shelley Moore Capito had already said
It's not yet clear which seat
For Wall Street, 17-13-348
Nation's trade gap expanded to just under 49 billion percent from the previous month
Proceedings were briefly interrupted when Joe Biden yelled out the quote
You're listening to PR
You've been listening to PR News
You've been listening to the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack
For free information, write to
P.O. Box 181-417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118
Or see www.subgenius.com
Praise God
Thanks, Bob
Now let's see what you got around here we can tax
Mmm, let's see
What's going on here?
Say, what kind of a joint is this anyway?
Why, I rep octopus him
Two deep breaths
He just lost a leg
I bet's what worked
YOU PURpole
Keep credit, Punch
What is your secret code?
You sell me down
Coming right up
Good job
Phop
Friends, we're glad you listened to this show,
and we're even more glad that some listeners have donated enough
to help us keep on going for another couple of months.
Not just this show, but subgenius.com and all the other archive sites.
But if you truly love Bob and want some of that slack back to rebound to you,
you should go to subgenius.com front page, or especially the radio page,
or the catalog store pages, and help out financially as best you can.
Now, we know what it's like to be on the brink of total poverty,
and we don't want any subgeniuses to make their own situations worse.
But some of you still have jobs.
Even five bucks makes a big difference, even if it's only once a month from enough of you.
Fifty bucks.
Makes an even bigger difference.
All we're saying is that blowjobs could go the way of Steve Jobs if you don't pay Dobbs.
We also take checks and money orders to Subgenius Foundation.
P.O. Box 181417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
Thanks for anything.
You can do to help let there be slack.
Subgenius.com