Remain seated and come to order. The court is again in session.
Your behavior, to say the least, has been most strange.
I want to warn all who are here that the police have orders to arrest anyone creating...
The self-genius power of...
What?
Your honor, this is preposterous.
Yes!
I'm rational.
Who else is pixelated?
Why, everybody is pixelated, except...
The self-genius power of...
What?
Your honor, this is absurd.
It was twisted around to sound imbecilic.
No objection.
There's a theory that our universe is the creation of another universe...
Only one more hour to go.
...that is a gigantic experiment in some kind of computer program.
There is a...
Perfect.
...exactly reputable theory for that.
Not even a crank.
That cuts it, hardware boy.
It's a business.
So that guy, you know, he may have been...
No skinny pink boy is going to tell me how to say things on my show.
What is that?
What sort of sound is that?
I should say in a video game, fanaticism consists in thinking some one matter so overwhelmingly important...
That it outweighs everything else.
...that's what I feel.
I have the pain of 10,000 or three old men all the time.
Really?
Yeah.
I have nothing against Canadians.
Well, it's a different pain for men and Canadians.
I'm playing Bob and Doug right now, as a matter of fact, to show my love for Canada.
What about us?
Get out.
You have what?
The wives of 10,000 or three old men.
10,000?
You're blowing the floor.
I'm blowing the floor.
Philo has the flatulation of them.
So, Hoser, what are you talking about?
We should probably put our clothes back on, huh?
Way to go.
Take a seat.
Okay.
No, that's optional.
Hoser, the flatulation of 10,000 arthritic old men.
Okay.
And they're wild.
And then...
Go pick your nose.
The acetic amino acids will be here tomorrow night!
Ah, yes, dear friends.
But tonight, you're listening to Hour of Slack number 1080, of which I am your host and prayer
partner, Reverend Ivan Stang.
And we're going to continue with the part two of the show.
The amino acids are already inside of you now.
Yes, the amino acids are already inside of you now.
But this background music is, in fact, from their new album due out in June, Humanity
Will Fall Like Hens.
But tonight's Hour of Slack show is a real Hour of Slack show.
It's got all the normal Hour of Slack, but it's from the abnormal station of KPFA from
January 10th, when we did a five-hour epic.
And it's from the abnormal station of KPFA from January 10th, when we did a five-hour
epic.
And that epic is part two, starring host Izzy Isn't and host Puzzling Evidence, both whose
shows we used up, with Dr. Howell, who actually arrived later in the evening, Philo Drummond,
yours truly reverend Ivan Stang, reverend John Shirley, Gary De Brogfran, Michael Pepe,
Princess Oui Ardoh, K Ausmic Bobcat Drummond, that's the new Mrs. Drummond, Phineas Narco
of NationalSynical.com, K Rod, Katie Koukos, it's gonna be a great show.
Somebody named Walter and the uber-goober booby baby on keyboards, plus Bishop Joey from the First Church of the Last Laugh.
And so, let us go into that very world.
Reverend Sting, I have to return to my apocalyptic theme because I am the purveyor of the signsofwitness.com website.
You know, I'm reporting for it. I've got to ask you this. What will the apocalypse be like?
You know what the party is going to be like a little bit before, but when the actual end comes, could you describe a little bit what it would be like?
Well, it will depend on how...
Besides a blessed relief, I mean.
Well, individuals who never irritated any subgeniuses in any way during their lives will have it much easier than those who...
Are we going to go back to the end of all these horses?
No, because they're...
They'll die instantly, practically.
The ones that at some point in their lives irritated a subgenius or inconvenienced one, however inadvertently, will see the pains associated with hell.
The Dante-style hell, as well as modernized versions of subgenius history.
This could be a widespread belief. Just think how quickly you'd go through the airport, through security.
Oh, it's Reverend Sting.
Going right through.
You know, oh, you'd have to be...
Wouldn't you like to sit in first class, Reverend Sting?
Oh, well, there won't be airports after the end.
Well, there may be airports, but there'll be the kind of airports where you're waiting in line with 5,000 other people for...
And there will be radio like this one.
You'll have to do this show 24 hours a day because there's nothing else to listen to.
We'll hate it.
Gotta throw it up for the Barcelona.
Nightmare.
Just like us.
That was the way it used to be.
There was nothing but this show for 24 hours a day.
And how far we have fallen.
It's only eight or five hours a day now.
People will pay for the show.
I only do this show about an hour and a half a day.
You can only abuse your body most of the time.
Michael Jackson.
Michael Pepe.
Michael Mann.
Michael Jackson.
I know, I am Michael Jackson.
Yeah.
He does what the hell he does.
I don't care.
I Tomato loved that short movie.
And I'm hard off.
I like the album.
I S reward that.
I don't a Muse.
I don't act like an iron.
I listen to it.
My leg.
I don't like it.
My Grandpa.
It's just not you, Gary.
You know, Gary, that hair, it's just not you.
It's just not me.
It has a life of its own.
Those shoes, those just aren't you, Gary.
Not you.
They're not you, Gary.
You know, it's getting so the teenage girls only grab the bottom half of my hair now,
and they leave the top half alone.
What do you think that means?
It's growing farther down toward your crotch.
That's a little hint.
The rest of you are all cots.
Just a subtle hint.
Faces in the crowd.
Just a scruttle hint.
Nine to five, no button.
It's their way of saying, not you, Gary.
Are you here?
You're the guys that read shirts on Star Trek.
Get out!
You haven't seen Idiocracy yet?
No, I have not seen Idiocracy, although you're the third person in about two days to mention it.
I just, as soon as it's downloadable, I'm sure I'll have a copy.
It is downloadable.
Oh, well.
Well, as soon as I'm home, I'll download it.
Let's just watch it now.
From my favorite channel.
Which channel is it on?
Don't play it with your brother.
I don't know, but they have the Fox News channel on it.
It's 500 years in the future.
Oh, cool.
Hello, baby.
Well, my favorite channel is alt.binaries.movies.givics.
Yes, it's on there.
That's one of those non-pay channels.
Hello, baby.
That's the Drummond family in the background.
That's all they do is they spoil, they talk to their baby.
Hello, baby.
That's Philo's rant now.
The baby has a very powerful mind and it has taken them over completely.
It has, actually.
That baby might as well be running there.
They'll drop everything they're doing just for that baby.
Baby!
Why do they say sleep like a baby when babies wake up every two hours?
Tall.
To take an example.
One of the misfits.
I suppose there will be some people who dislike it when they attribute it to babies and not the cats.
It means that stuff runs out of your mouth and you're both ends while you're sleeping.
But if you fall.
That's what sleep like a baby really means.
It means you have to be cleaned up after the sleep.
It was so atrocious.
Princess Gwee has just walked in but seems not to have her own microphone.
Or even a chair.
Lady just entered the room, boys.
I'm shortly about to take the next rocket out, in fact.
I've been holding the fort.
There's a chair in there.
You can go sit if you dare to sit next to Phineas and Arko.
I'm not going.
Yes, Princess Wee Ar Do.
Please.
I'm the queen of all the UFOs.
But only the unidentified O's.
Could she intercede for us when the UFOs come in the next day?
Could we fall to our knees in front of her and beg her to intercede so that they don't turn us in?
No, because when they come then they're no longer unidentified.
You know what I'm saying?
What is her relationship with known objects?
That's the drawback to being that particular kind of queen.
Identified flying objects then.
Yeah, what about known flying objects?
She's got no... those are out of her jurisdiction.
Really?
Those aren't her responsibility.
Wanna play with me?
Uh huh.
It's the 60's.
Have I done something wrong?
Bob's still in college.
Where's Glass Madness to sing a little Bob song?
I'm Bob better than you're Bob cause you're Bob sucks.
He sucks so bad.
We all slack Bob.
He can kiss my wallet goodbye.
La la la la la la la la la la la la la.
That sucky little Bob.
So bad, sorry.
Hey, we both can.
All praise the moon.
You'll have to buy the price.
Did I hear a little tiny collar?
A teeny teeny tiny collar.
Where will we be a more?
Boy, boy, boy.
Can I help you?
Hi, how are you?
I'm good.
Oh, Brad Smith.
This guitar will do anything.
Watch it play me.
Watch the mini-chopper.
Not you, Gary is playing the guitar by rubbing it just against the Harrison's face.
Which are like guitar picks.
Oh, I get it.
Yeah.
Well, okay.
Never mind, not all with us.
Wa- الذي army Brister-
F comunque.
Whom everyoneねr bewusst?
Century pub!
Man.
creams.
Tea break.
Never mind, go smoke.
You gonna throw that hop out loud?
Lucky for you, a gas, hot summarize.
It still ashes, each for a pint.
Oh,okay thank you.
We'll see you at the pub for the coffee, at a bar.
I hear the ocean
and I hear my
tinnitus
hey guess what you guys I've learned that I'm losing
my hearing
they always do that
they cannot help themselves
well should we yell louder or what
yeah that actually helps
quite a bit
you have headphones volume controls under the desk
there the little knobs
they don't turn it up
they don't nearly
turn it up high enough but it's better than nothing
well it's
it's not the jacks
or the headphones or even
the show it's unfortunately
my
ears you know I'm really
really really old
well you're mighty close to an electric guitar
right now I'd watch out
yeah that's part of the
problem too many years spent filming
my friends bands
standing in front of the speakers
and now I hear these
these crickets all the time
I used to think they were real crickets
I moved to Ohio in the dead of winter
princess we would say listen hear that
I go yeah I hear the crickets
what kind of vehicle did you use to move to Ohio
is there a history of this
we used
we used slaves actually to haul
bobbies
the church building itself
you must have got out just in time
brick by brick and that's what we used to do
this was Texas under George Bush
before
so it wasn't that expensive
you know it wasn't
the unions were still
out of
they weren't there yet
we were able to move the church
stone by stone
so to speak as it were
brick by brick
floppy
disc by floppy disc
did you move your frock brick by brick
or did you weave it
it was sort of like Easter Island
we moved the frock
which bathtub full by bathtub
when they moved the building
they found something horrible underneath it
over there
and I named my frock
festering
a festering expressence
and Spomam pachal all those years
Dr. Drummond finally arrived
I heard he's just wheezed tackle
actually I've been here just now for a while
lurking about listening and calculating
as it were
I've been repositioning my monitors
been recalibrating my whistle
we're swinging as we pucker
we're pinging and swuckering here
you're swucker and pingerin
yeah that's how you feel
the world's
alright well in that case
I gotta get my
wall wart
here you go
I have a wall wart
and I didn't say Walmart
but I said wall wart
welcome to Walmart
I love you
so I'm just gonna say
you know
look a price fell
how long will it be before all of us are working as greeters at Walmart
I'm gonna get a job there real soon
Walmart world
I already am
I know I can get a job there
cause that will meet my standard of brain power
well they don't P test you there
at Walmart
that's one thing about it
I mean they may not pay you well
or give you any benefits
but they don't P test
they don't welcome to Walmart
they do
yes and after 20 years they give you a shirt
what if they give you a shirt and don't pee
want a cart
no
you can live in that place and they'd never know
people do
I do
but do they give you a sincerity test
there's plenty of food
what fluid did they take out for a sincerity test
there's a mattress department
I don't know but it comes out of the base of your skull
toilets open all night
snack food galore
TV's
his sincerity fluid is slightly too viscous
TV's DVD's CD's
Dr. Drummond would have to use somebody else's
I'm totally depleted on the sincerity solution
clothing you never run out of clothing in Walmart
in fact I was going to try to get a depletion allowance for my lack of sincerity
if you were living in Walmart you'd be home now
I've got some synthetic
the Reverend John Shirley
I think it should be worth some kind of government subsidy
the Piss Baptist must go on about his Piss Baptist duties
you know there are 10,000 people lined up in the Grand Canyon waiting for me
and I'm a sincerian
there's an enormous vat next to the Grand Canyon that I use to keep my fluids and the other fluids replenished and flowing
and everybody is very grateful
let John Shirley's mercy rain down
you know the Forest Service is not allowed to say how old the Grand Canyon is
that's what I've heard yeah
they're not allowed to say this
they said they were going to change that policy
they were going to stop selling that book about how the Grand Canyon is only 4,000 years old
they haven't done it
because that would infringe on the rights of creationists
to state theories of ancient science
well I'm really hungry my stomach is rumbling
I read in the newspaper that 29% of Americans find this hard to believe
but some new survey 29% of Americans believe that the sun revolves around the earth
it doesn't?
are you saying it doesn't?
okay 29.01 I guess
it sounds believable to me
I mean I can believe in a supernatural being that's been around since the beginning of time
with no evidence at all
why can't I believe in something as equally believable as this?
I mean what do you think?
I mean that's what I'm saying
you can believe anything you want to believe
you can be what you won't
you can believe what you want too
anything you want because when you grow up you can do anything you want
I'm very proud of you young man
my stomach is really rumbling
I know it's playing a rumba
do what thou won't
do what he won't
you've heard do what thou wilt shall be the whole of history
the whole of the law
but for the subjeetists it's do what they won't shall be the whole of the law
do what Jesus won't
do what they won't
the engine of the train
you will
weighs something like 80,000 tons
they won't but you will
what would Jesus not do?
who would Jesus do?
I forget the actual weight but it's
Magdalene this year
WWNJ
NDJ
I've been drinking now and it's dead
GWBBQ
they won't
surely not
I'm just making a great fan of myself
Princess Weah
and her throne is ready
if somebody wants to get in
her throne and her sacred microphone is ready
you know it turned out Princess Weah was actually the daughter of Darth Hater
the Doctor Doom
the Doctor Singer from outer space?
no, Doctor Doom was one of those guys
one of those ass guys
amino acids
you're right
I'm going to escort the fist Baptist to his limousine helicopter
doing the show is sort of like trying to jump on a big man's plane
dear friend
I'm going to escort the fist Baptist to his limousine helicopter
just before I go to bed
I know that you think that sounds funny
security 5 report
ok now I've got some catalogs here I want to read from
do you have my catalogs ready?
I'm ready to recite my catalog copy now
this is Charles Collins an accountant from the British Columbia
a testing laboratory in Houston Texas
this is the sound of the future
the switches have just been turned
there was already so much money in it
and a human being is about to receive an outer signal
that many fingers with lots of neurons
that will never wrinkle or decay
have you ever asked yourself how much money you have?
how much are major companies willing to pay you
to create a show like this one?
it's true
from health supplements to credit cards
they do it because it's good
and it can bring in millions
this is like a dream come true
I have a retired lifestyle and 39 bucks to spend
I'm going to go to bed
but I didn't care
remember there's no risk
no risk
after a while
I'm going to go to bed
but I'm not going to sleep
I'm just going to let go of my hair
I let go of my hair a long time ago
I see it like ever increasingly disharmonious
push even more
ever. So I
decided along with my $10,000
to check
in to the local
I was reading Bob's
note and there
I found out that he was a great guy
and a very successful
copywriter.
You'll be hearing a lot about him once you
start our new program.
Oh yes, I
almost forgot.
How can you
swiftly can you change your career?
Fuck a bitch.
What's she doing?
Oh my god, this is
still going on.
Okay, alright, alright.
We arranged the
show now.
We just, the show
can start now because we are rearranging.
We arranged the studio
into three
sectors. There's two sectors
for married
people and their children
and then there's the main room which is for
the lonely
geeks.
Phineas,
Don Joyce,
Puzzle
and Sad, Old Bachelors.
Weeping.
You can hear them
weeping.
I'm hollering.
This is turn time.
Three hundreds of years ago.
You should do these
high good reputation
for your
requiring nut.
You know,
you got your
five cameras
till here.
You have got new
where you generally
till seal with
Yeah,
with all
all
trigger
tick sleeø
have to
happen
to
program
robot.
He said
more
text
operator
with
site
and
on
bedroom là
ok, wait.
I suppose,
Pills! Leave my pills alone!
He's just like Philo.
Bishop Joey is just like Philo.
He reached in, he just transgressed my personal space.
Violated!
He violated me. I feel raped.
And it was good, too. I loved violating your personal spaces.
I feel raped.
I feel used.
Yeah, because we here at the one pretty true church,
the first church of the last life, kicks the subgenie's ass every time.
Listen to that fake Texas accent.
Every time.
That is the fakest southern accent.
That's so fake. Oh, you look at these boots. Smell the bottom of my boots.
That's the fakest smelling cow hockey I ever smelt.
Well, just look at my...
Is that my tinnitus or is that the show?
It's the show, dear. It's just the show.
It's gotten to where my hearing, really, it's true, my hearing's gotten so bad
that Princess Wee has to translate for me.
And she plays tricks on me by mistranslating things.
The waitress says, that'll be $30.
And Princess Wee says, she says she wants to have a three-way.
And then I end up humiliated and embarrassed.
And they all think it's funny.
People make fun of old days.
F-persons like myself.
Now, I don't want to forget my students
and the subgenius how to make your own cult,
do's and don'ts.
Ah, K-Rob has arrived.
The mighty K-Rob.
That means that sound quality may improve.
Uh-huh.
Listeners, there is hope.
Undoubtedly.
What is that?
Oh, no, Michael Pepe.
As I suspected.
Michael Pepe.
Michael Pepe even arrived.
That means the station will be on the air for another half an hour or so
before the Pepe effect works in.
Before we're publicized.
Pepe kind of looks like Philo's new daughter.
Michael Pepe has a new...
This is Philo's daughter.
No, that's Philo, not his daughter.
Philo's daughter.
Philo's daughter is the...
One with the mutton chops in the other room.
Yes, Dr. Drummond and Mrs. Chaos McBobcat
have brought their baby,
their new infant child, Michael Pepe.
You can hear it crying now.
Pardon me, Michael.
I'm in headphones and you're not on a mic,
so I can't...
Nothing makes any...
He said something about how many eyes does it have.
I want you to take it out.
Only three.
Let me...
Actually, my nephew, Alex, today, asked a question.
He seriously asked me,
hey, if you had three eyes, would you be able to see the fourth dimension?
And I said no, because the fourth dimension isn't something that you see.
So eyes are not the sense organ you need.
Your time sense would be able to...
Except you smell in the future.
Somehow.
Isn't the future a sense of smell?
Well, you see the fifth dimension...
Well, they broke up.
The fifth dimension, I think, broke up.
The fourth dimension broke up.
What is that noise in the background?
Is that the show?
Yeah, it's puzzling evidence.
He puts on weird things and he leaves.
Michael Pepe, you have to get on a microphone for anyone to hear you.
Including me.
I'm deaf now.
So I've been reading your lips so far, but the radio audience can't hear that.
He thinks I'm joking.
These kids these days, they just walk around like zombies.
We just cussed each other out in sign language.
Hey, I learned sign language the other day.
The sign...
Okay, radio listeners, the sign for sex is this.
And the sign for...
Bunghole.
Cactus is this.
Spiky, spiky.
So when you see somebody, you want to have kinky sex with them.
You go like that and then spiky, spiky.
The sex symbol, of course, is the old temple of Devo with the finger.
That's the formal, polite way of saying sex.
Now, if you turn your fingers around like this, that's butt sex.
Or in 69, it's like that.
The sex symbol, friends, is actually two...
Two fingers of each hand tapping together on the end.
Like if you made two little figures that could walk along the tabletop using your fingers.
You put those two figures together and tap them together.
Yeah, but Uranus is not a planet.
Uranus is not a planet.
My anus is.
You have to get on a microphone, Michael, or it doesn't really...
Nothing you say really exists.
Is that Michael Poupe?
No, Michael.
My student...
My student that's listening...
Is that Michael Poupe?
Give me the hook.
Get the hook.
Maybe logic.org class, online class in the Church of the Subgenius,
should know that this is the subgenius business meeting.
Michael Pepe's here, so I have to hook myself up.
Business meeting.
Well, what is the business?
The business is...
We're trying to untangle the truth.
The true history of the Church.
Bob assigned us to do a commission to study the...
What went wrong during the previous Church administration.
The previous administration of the Church made many mistakes,
and we're trying to delineate what happened decade by decade since...
Well, for the last hundred years.
Yeah.
And then what happened?
The bad karma having to do with the elimination of the Gary Factor.
Once Gary was eliminated...
Well, it's not you Gary to finally add it up to where the Church is going to suffer badly.
And right now...
Actually, that started several years ago on July 7th, 1987,
when Gary stormed out of the studio saying,
I've had it with you guys.
Manic. Manic.
Don't call me that.
Don't call me.
I'll call in the shot.
I remember that.
That was the funniest thing he ever did.
That was.
I hated to say that, but I'm glad you just put that out on the table,
because I wanted to comment on that, but I really didn't want to be the one to bring the subject up.
I thought it was a great pitch.
Now, one point of contention is when exactly was J.R. Bob Dobbs born?
Some say that it was in the early 20s, but we're looking now at 1927 or 1929.
It was a midnight clear.
We know that.
Bob was born in the late 20s.
Yeah.
We know it was on a midnight clear, and we know that it was in a cheap motel.
How else could they land?
We know that in 1945, Bob killed Hitler again.
And he met Philo in 1927.
He met Philo in 1950 in college.
Well, you know that means I'm old.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, Gramps.
Now, in 1953, Bob was immaculated, and the countdown to X-Day began.
Unfortunately, it ended prematurely.
Lunch.
And had to start again.
But we don't know where to start exactly, because we don't know where to start.
We don't know where it ends.
Welcome to school.
I'm Principal Bob McKenzie.
In 1955, Bob had his second pre-vision.
My Vice Principal Doug.
And in 1956, Princess Wea was born.
When did Bob get sterno, Craig?
1955.
1955, sterno was pregnant?
Oh, wow.
And then eight years later, Jane was born.
Oh, that's right.
That's right.
It says so here.
In 1957, some bad boys got me to sit on a cactus by telling me it was the king's throne.
Those evil, evil bastards.
And my parents spent the afternoon pulling tiny cactus spines out of my, out of my, out
of my house behind.
You're lucky you didn't have my parents.
They pounded the X spice into my body.
Well, I was, I was spoiled.
I'll admit it.
I was a spoiled child.
Okay.
In 1959, Bob started producing movies like...
Is this KPFA or is it DC?
Attack of the Giant Shrew People.
It's K-P-O-M-A-N-C-Y.
mama.
I didn't get that criticism.
KPFU, man.
It was undoubtedly
a criticism, but I couldn't make it out.
If you could call back and criticize us again,
we would very much appreciate it.
We'll all be quiet and listen to your criticisms.
Your constructive
criticisms. He said something like,
is this KPFA or is this...
And then I missed it. So I don't know what we were
being compared with.
The mad god, communist,
insane, you know...
Pardon me.
Language.
Now, in 1960,
Bob discovered that
males, as they
gradually emerged step by
step out of boards,
caused hammers to fly up
and down with human hands
gripping them on one hand.
That was Bob's great discovery
about cause and effect.
Anything is possible today.
You don't hammer a nail. The nail
causes the hammer to go up
with the human gripping.
And how do you feel about that?
I feel satisfied that the church
has progressed
as predicted.
If this was the...
Year 1963.
Oh!
And man are still alive.
We are still alive.
Is this Claire here?
This is the noisiest show.
Yeah, it's got so many
Princess, we think how pleasant
our show hour of slack is.
I'm trying to control it,
but it's out of hand.
It's like chaos.
It's got a mind of its own.
It's got a Don Joyce of its own.
It's a Santa.
This is Walter Bloom at Times Square
in New York City, returning you to
Charles Collins in Texas.
Now that was pretty professional.
Charles Collins again.
As I look at the strange devices
before me, I find it difficult
to understand or even believe.
I believe it.
I believe that this show sounds better
when they play tapes of other shows on it.
Good work, everyone.
But I knew what to expect
when I was born.
I was born.
They told me.
They gave me instructions for life
when I was born.
And told me what to expect.
Unlike other people.
Who just have to blunder and bluff
their way through.
Unfortunately, I lost the instruction book
when I was about five.
I had to be toilet trained all over again.
We have a long day ahead of us,
so we should begin with a two hour
break.
I kept having to call tech support for life.
Get up and go out.
Go outside.
Good day.
Okay, there'll be smoke.
Send it out outside.
Operation.
Security.
This show reminds me of my hearing test,
which I flunked.
My voice.
Now to wait till someone phones in
where the pieces fell.
I'm not listening.
Gary Gbrodfred here has a special electronic guitar
that every time he touches one of the strings,
it creates a whole new show.
It's like a sampler.
And each note of each string
has a separate show that plays back.
I will play our game.
Princess Wee is playing her messages over the microphone.
Outward.
Then maybe we'll be finally knowing what the flying saucers are.
Who are the masters of the UFO?
Wee!
Standing next to me is a technical expert.
A fanatical group all together
have a comfortable feeling
that they're in the same boat.
They're all friends of each other.
The people who are not on a microphone
in the other studio are all laughing
because they're having fun.
But the people who are on microphones
and listening to the show
all look grim.
Maybe we should get off the microphones
and join the party.
Just go jam.
Just go jam out.
No, the jamming is happening right here.
Gary is doing all the jamming.
I've been waiting until you jam this thing.
It says fire drill.
He's been jamming it into the edge of the table
and onto the equipment.
Jammed it into the microphone.
Jammed it into his mouth.
Okay, light up.
Flambering cacophony
of symphonic proportion.
They're all very much excited.
Something is cool.
You can see it in any political party.
There's always a fringe of fanatics.
In any political party.
So a lot of people think the world's gonna end in 2012.
Yeah.
But the reason they think that is because of the Mayan calendar
running out of numbers, right?
Right.
That's Frank Zappa's birthday.
But that's just another bunch of arbitrary numbers
made by the media.
By humans.
Why should nature and the axis and the world ending
depend on silly, arbitrary human numbering traditions?
Well, it's just a coincidence.
That's silly.
It's just a coincidence.
Oh, just a coincidence.
Yeah, that's what they all say.
Except for the scientists who say that nothing is a coincidence,
and it's all a meaningful, mystical message from Bob.
Well, some...
They're talking about...
Real good scientists.
This is the mystical message music now.
Let's get on with the mystical message.
Come on.
Perhaps an author...
I thought the music and the sound was itself the mystical message.
The answer, Mr. Collins, lies in a system called prepared curing.
I thought the bared curing was the mystical message.
Mm-hmm.
A surface each person lives within is treated with a chemical reaction.
That's a mystical message.
It is then dried at low temperatures so as not to set the cat.
When we have the shape of each human being in question,
we heat it with this device.
The educational film in the background is describing where babies come from.
What's Chicago?
Well, that's pretty much where my...
Yeah, Chicago...
Yeah.
That's where my dad explained it that way.
Really?
They said babies are poured into a little mold.
They have a mold...
Person mold.
and they pour the baby juice in there and the baby comes out.
That's what they mean by breaking the mold.
Babies came from friendly 13-year-old girls.
Really?
Yeah.
I'm glad you think that's right.
Babies come from friendly 13-year-old girls, he said.
That's what he said.
In some countries, that is correct.
Yes.
In many countries, that's correct.
As I keep reminding Princess Wee whenever we're watching a movie like Peter Pan or Lemony Snicket or Harry Potter,
I go, look, you know, in many countries, those girls would be married by now.
They'd be grandmothers.
Not quite grandmothers, dear.
There's nothing wrong with that.
There's nothing wrong with it, is there?
I mean, not that there's anything wrong with it.
That's what they always say when there really is something wrong with it.
Are you having some kind of attention deficit disorder?
They do.
Is that what's wrong with you?
And they feel a bit cozy with each other.
Hey, Reverend Stang, I got a couple of extra catalogs over here.
Oh, is it time to read catalogs, Dr. Drummond?
Yeah.
You know, that's my favorite part of this show.
When you read the catalogs at random.
Hold on a minute.
I'm going to bring one over to you.
If it wasn't for that, I'd have nothing to edit out of your shows when I replay them on Hour of Slime.
Yeah, I edit the best catalog readings out.
Oh, he really does have a catalog.
He just handed one to me.
Now I can say, Dynamite Discount Deals Authentic,
extremely free-flying, real leather,
I can't do it as well as Dr. Drummond.
Nobody can read a catalog like Philo.
No.
It's easier than ever to stay connected with friends, family, and colleagues around the world.
Philo, I notice that you're better at reading those catalogs
right when Dr. Howell is coming to a dramatic crescendo.
Sleek, powerful, and completely portable.
On the go, in the car.
I've studied the dynamics of this show.
The perfect self-contained system.
I've studied everything.
Eliminate the hassles.
But Dr. Drummond, what does that have to do with our topic?
Always make clear.
Hey, is Bishop Joey running away?
You lucky son of a bitch.
Don't you remember?
Every third word, the listeners are supposed to take the whole show,
cut it up into pieces, extract every third word, compile it,
then recite it backwards for the audience.
Secret messages hidden within.
We can't do it where it's too easy.
We have to, you know, perform some kind of upgrade, memory transfer, hard drive,
refragmentation.
Not a defrag this time, but a refrag.
We're going to refrag the hard drive.
We don't know why we have to do it.
We're possessed to do it.
But in the meantime...
Are we going to get to the business portion of the show?
What are we supposed to do the business meeting?
What is the business?
I've got a budget I've got to tell you guys about.
How I legally robbed a bank last month for over $87,978 and got away with it.
Well, let's split.
Let's split.
I don't mind because I'll easily make that much this month.
Brain pan!
Okay, now I want to know how does the listener digest the show in such a way that it enters the brain pan according to the prescribed pathways?
Hey, I drained my brain pan last night.
What's your excuse?
Okay just another show, and what's the no table?
What did we say?
Dis nan, he's not giving you an answer.
Now is the last time you've talked to me, Edward!
You do have to go play with your mental story novel while he's gone.
Well, think about it, I know he's at playing Pokemon.
We've had one.
And he's going for some kind of candies again.
Those are them.
And Will Fitzphil has some of hers.
Well she's here, but there is this牌 on him.
Is that forte yours?
Mr. Collins, we have proven beyond a shadow of a doubt
that we can give to every man, woman, and child
a perfect and lasting shape.
Is that sex education tape still on?
About how they give you a shape?
I got my shape from my dad.
Yes, it's not a sex education tape, though.
Far from it.
Thank you, too, unfortunately.
This is Charles Collins reporting on one of the miracles of our time.
Sex disinformation tape.
It's actually a commercial.
We are ready to switch you over to a home in Cleveland, Ohio,
where a family prepares for this experience.
Now, how coincidental is that?
That's my house.
Hey, they're showing our house.
Talk about your coincidences.
How?
You can't be.
Stand by, please.
What's happening?
There's somebody standing next to our house.
Don't be anxious.
Stand by, please.
Wait a second.
No, no, stand by.
Can you just hop from one foot to the other?
Please stand by.
I'm hopping, I'm hopping.
People, people, please stand by.
You say hurry up.
Hello?
Don't all rush around in a little gaggle of peace.
I gotta go.
What's going on here?
Where's the bathroom?
The bathroom.
Keep your hands at your sides and stand by.
Don't touch anything.
It's all hot.
Stolen by Ivan Stang.
It's starting to trickle down my leg.
When he escaped from Texas in a 1953 Chevrolet.
Two times.
No, Philo has the, has the prop, not me.
Everybody accuses me of being the one with all the prop.
It was Philo.
That's what we're hoping, Pope.
We want, that's what we want from a Pope.
As a Pope.
As, you know, as a Pope myself.
I did bring some of course.
You're a Pope?
I'm a Pope.
I'm a Pope, yeah.
We're all Popes.
That's right.
They call me Michael Popey.
I'm a Pope, with my old bathroom.
They're just kidding.
I'm a Pope.
They're just P-Dogs.
I thought you were like a favorite.
I'm a Pope, with my old bathroom.
I know a P-Dog is here.
And Pope Pep and all that.
Yeah, that'd be the second was the first King to known to have ordered pygmies to dance.
This is all-
Ladies and gentlemen.
Are you director?
A new subgenius has entered the world.
And he smiles immediately.
He was as soon as I said that.
He's a uber subgenian mutant.
So named for her diet.
And her, excuse me, a genie.
She's now picking her nose on the air.
This is, of course, a natural subgenius reaction to being on the air.
Actually, if you'll notice, the uber booby baby is wearing the latest Bob bib.
That's right.
There is also a bib with Bub on it available.
Bub the faceless.
Yeah, birth defect.
Bub bib.
I'm not kidding.
You can actually go to CafePress.com, subgenius shop, and there's a Bub bib.
As well as the Bob bib.
I got your mail.
This is a Christine Bob bib.
It hasn't been drooled or vomited on in hours.
She loves Bob.
That's very clear.
She has pretty blue eyes.
Your butts look big in those pants.
What's her name?
What's your daughter's name?
Can you hear me?
My daughter?
Uber booby baby.
That's on her first certificate.
Uber booby baby...
Uh, drummond?
You mean Lily Cat?
Or... will you say her last name on the air?
No.
Drummond?
You say Drummond on the air?
Oh.
Yeah.
I see.
Lily Cat Drummond?
Bobcat!
Yeah, Bobcat's her last name.
Oh, okay.
Bubba Bob Bobcat with a Bubba Bob bib.
She's Lily Cat Drummond.
Lily Cat Drummond.
Bo-bo-bo-bo-bo-bo-bo-bo-bo-bo.
2006.
Actually, she wasn't born quite on that.
No, it was, wasn't it August, it was late July, I think.
Yeah, because I remember because Chaos McKinney wanted to make sure she wasn't a cancer.
Yeah.
And because she didn't want, you know, which is my sign.
Someone did?
Wanted to make sure that she wasn't like Michael Pepe.
Hey, Michael Pepe, did you know that Marion Kester's daughter was born on my birthday?
Your illegitimate child.
Really?
Yeah.
My illegitimate child?
Oh, my God.
Yeah, he doesn't even remember Marion Kester.
No, I remember her as one of the many, many girls.
She was his Republican girlfriend.
Oh, my God.
She was, she was at least almost as much of a Nazi as I am.
Oh, didn't she?
Which is pretty extreme.
Didn't she become like a conservative writer?
She became a Republican.
And changed her name to Coulter or something like that?
Yeah, Kester Coombs.
And she had two daughters and moved to Maryland.
You know Maryland.
And Virginia and all that.
Yeah.
He worked for the Washington Post, her husband.
Well, her daughter was born on my birthday.
And then after that, all the subgenius daughters were born on my birthday.
Now, that's funny.
Now, three months.
Three months after your birthday, then, you have a big, like, fertilization ritual with
the whole females in the church?
Yeah, we organize the fertility nights for them.
Yeah, three months after my birthday.
Now, that must be intense for you because you just happen to service all these many
women.
Oh, I just fell.
Oh.
Who provides the stud?
So, I match the males with the females.
Oh, yes.
Of course.
And they, yeah, it's a genetic.
Yeah.
It's very carefully scientifically done.
You're like, yeah, you're like the Mendel of the human race.
Right.
Selecting biological.
Really?
You're like the Gregor Mendel?
Yes.
I'm the Gregor Mendel.
You're a great geneticist.
Yeah.
He's a great geneticist.
Subgenius breeding.
And he breeds humans.
So, really, I don't see you as a subgenius.
Well, subgenius.
This is why he hooked up Philo and the...
Actually, we're trying not to breed.
You know, that's what we all do if you think about it.
That's what, if we're successful, we all do that.
We breed humans.
That's our job.
Yeah.
Is it really?
We have to move our DNA into the next generation.
I've done so.
You've done so.
But my DNA is so twisted and snarled.
You have to keep...
Your job is different, Michael.
Yeah.
You have to keep your DNA in this generation.
Out of the...
You don't want to put it into the next one.
Yeah, no.
You want to keep it in this one as much as possible.
That's right.
Stop it right where it is.
Yeah.
I know.
Some of us have to put it into the next generation.
Yeah.
I know.
I've been required to do that.
I actually...
You recall...
You're working on a cycle of every 12 years.
That's right.
We discovered that there was a 12-year drum and uber baby cycle.
Yeah.
Like there's cycles of locusts and ladybugs.
And they go into hiding.
There's cycles of drum and uber babies.
Yeah.
They can't be...
They're always females.
Well, don't...
And they're well over spawned.
That'd be 12th year.
They're actually in webs, in trees for those 12 years, right?
That is true.
Do they hang in the...
Did you mention that she was born at 6.06 a.m.?
Oh, my God.
Yeah.
6.06, of course.
6.06.
Yeah, we did mention that last...
Spells B-O-B in lowercase.
That's right.
6.06 is lowercase B-O-B.
Yeah.
It's not funny.
Quit laughing.
No.
I know.
It's a...
That's the type laughing.
It's a hell child.
Oh.
But that's good.
That's a good thing.
That's the type laughing?
She puts the friendly, sweet face on hell.
I thought that was laugher caller for a minute.
I know.
I love that.
Laugher caller.
The one that just calls and then just laughs the whole time.
I'm so funny.
In Cleveland, we have a master...
I didn't do it.
...that calls and master bites.
That's where we got...
I had somebody that laughed at that.
He would...
Are you laughing?
He would listen to our show and master bite and say, oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
I want to show you the map of the internet callers.
Do you want me to show you that?
It's really cool.
The map?
Yeah.
The map of the internet callers.
Here, hold down the fork for a minute and I'll show you the map.
Just like a sci-fi movie?
Oh, is it just on the...
Oh, I know what you mean.
I'm going to show it over the air.
It's the web that shows what addresses are taken.
Oh, really?
I hope my students in the Maybe Logic University course are learning a lot about subjunius history
from this educational show.
Well, of course, they've got to be soft.
I apologize to the regular over-the-edge listeners who expected quality and got this.
So do I.
Well, that just happened.
Sometimes the regular show is out.
The summer substitute comes in.
Friends, you have been listening to the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack number 1081 in
this case, which was a reprint of the 10 Puzzling and 10 Puzzling Evidences shows combined on
KPFA on January 10th, which included a bunch of the subgenius old-timers.
And that's what that was.
And if you want more information about the Church of the Subgenius, please to check out
Subgenius.com.
If you look at the radio section of that, you'll find links to all of the many subgenius
shows, including Suzy Dufluzzi's fabulous one on WREK Atlanta, which is also joined
by the Lymph Node Institute's fabulous one on WREK Atlanta, and the Puzzling Evidence
show on KPFA, Berkeley, Price Bob, Subgenius.com.
Yes.
Oh, and praise the amino acids heard here in the background in their new album, Humanity.
Will fall like pins.
And will they not?
Ah, yes, yes, yes.
Dollar sign.
B.
O.
Space.
Space.
Y.
O.
U.
Colon.
B.
U.
T.
Space.
H.
E.
Space.
Space.
Space.
E.
V.
N.
Space.
M.
O.
R.
E.
Period.
Dollars in a sense.
There is a fifth Bob beyond that which is known to Bob.
It is a Bob as vast as Bob and as timeless as Bob.
It is the middle Bob between Bob and Bob between Bob and Bob.
And it lies between the Bob of man's fobs and the Bob of his Bob.
This is the Bob of a Bob.
It is an area which we call
the
Self Genius
Power
of
Squatting.
How about some Bob?
Pfft.
Bob.
How about some Bob?
Maybe you're finished mister.