From PR News in Washington, I'm allowed to remain in contact with children, despite PR News.
On Wall Street 3 1⁄2, President Bush says,
PR's bad.
The Energy Department is warning that suicide bombers will be up to 50% higher.
Some Republicans had argued that they could not support PR News in Washington.
Get your things out of this house right now before I throw them into the street and you wet them.
Bye, June.
Get out before I...
Yeah!
Close the door, Cratchit! Shut out that infernal noise!
So I'm down in the basement
Racking up all the points
Killing binary soldiers
And trashing all the joints
I'm the dungeon master
Master of all I see
Scoffing up for pizza
Playing a little D&D
Mom peeps into Crash the Show
She scowls and frowns and says,
What do you know?
She says, you gotta do something someday
What you gonna do?
What you gonna do, Junior?
Good day, Bob.
I say you think you know me
And what I do?
I'm gonna do what I can do
I live in such a world of fools
I'm a musician
And I'll tell you what I'm gonna do
I'm gonna picket my guitar
I'm gonna strum me some chords
I'm gonna get with my fellas
I'm gonna put it all together
I'm gonna make a smash hit!
Just like Molly Hadgett
Just like Dashiell Hammett
Ain't no one gonna match it
Ma says that nothing in life is free
You ain't going nowhere
Playing D&D
Whatcha gonna do, whatcha gonna do, whatcha gonna do
Here's what I'm gonna do
I'm gonna put it all together
I'm gonna make her smash it
Just like Molly Hatchet
Just like Dashiell Hammett
Ain't no one gonna match it
I'm gonna make her smash it
Not convenient and it's not fair
Hey boy, hey boy
I got a message for you
About a thing called love and the stars above
And a little white dove since pushed her to shove
To fists and cuffs
Things really got rough but it does enough
Hey boy, hey boy
I heard it from a friend about you
About your hatred
When you're lying in your bed
And your face turns red
With your hatred fed
From the things you said
And you wish you were dead
Because you're separated
From a thing called love and the stars above
And a little white dove since pushed her to shove
To fists and cuffs
Things really got rough but it does enough
To smash it
Hey boy, hey boy
I heard it from a friend about you
That your heart is broken
And your anger's smoking
And you're lying there poking at a lid
Talking of days gone by
You laid outside
To fill your eyes
And you just started to cry
And say oh God why
And you wish you could die
And your eyes are dry
And time don't fly
On you's a hellish night
I'm gonna make her smash it
I'm gonna make her cry
And your eyes open wide
Oh that's a hellish right
As you go swishing from side to side
Because you feel hatred
When you're lying in your bed
And your face turns red
With your hatred fed
From the things you said
And you wish you were dead
Because you're separated
From a thing called love and the stars above
And a little white dove since pushed her to shove
To fists and cuffs
Things really got rough
But it does enough
Hey boy, hey boy
Hey!
I heard it from a friend about you
From the American Astronaut, dear friends
The great film, The American Astronaut
The music, I think, is performed by
The Billy Nayer Show
And you should learn more about that
From theamericanastronaut.com
Or the Billy Nayer Show
Or thebillynayershow.com
And before that smash hit
Is by our own
Reverend Norrell Preff
And you can get a lot more
Of his at
Norrellpreff.com
N-O-R-E-L-P-E-F
Dot com
And Lee Murr opened for us
And this is Hour of Slack number
The Billy Nayer Show, by the way
Will be at 9X Day
Yes, the subgenius
Fantabulous
Love Fest
Called X Day
This will be our ninth one, yeah?
Yeah, we say
We say yeah to X Day 9
Now we're gonna have some fun
They kill for one reason
They kill for food
They eat their victims
You understand that, Mr. Berman?
That's what keeps them going
The more you run over a dead cat
The flatter it gets
Give me the girl or die
Well
If I have a choice
I'll take death
So be it
Or pursue your present course
And face obliteration
You can just go to hell
You go to hell and you die
I'd like to repeat that
Because it sounds vaguely important
You are fined one credit
For a violation of the verbal morality
Maniac is imminent
Request advice
Hey, I'm tired of talking
When you gonna do me, huh?
It's a very difficult job
And the only way to get through it
Is we all work together
As a team
Jeff, don't do that
We haven't
I've got business baking
And don't tell
Lambre Systems did that
And you can get free videos
From Lambre Systems
At lambre-systems.com
And now from the album
Pairs in Bob's Ears
The great Dr. Ahmed Fishmonger
Jehovah
One is sent a new Messiah
He's the one who grins
And smokes the pipe
For in a world of darkness
Danger and despair
We can go on smiling
Cause we know that Bob Dobbs
Is always there
And I know that Bob's on my side
I know it as sure as I'm born
He will make the proper deal
With the exes
And the most racist whore
Then we'll come to meet him
Then we'll greet him
And rule forevermore
Bob is my one true savior
You can't keep all of the rest
Looking at his smiling face
Helps me when I'm depressed
For the pinks I sure feel sorry
For tomorrow they'll fry
With all the rest
Bob has got no real brain
To speak of
Though his luck has seen him
Through the last year
And the last year
For all the geniuses
Led us on the wrong track
At least we know a subgenius
Won't turn around
And stab us in the back
The con thinks they have us suckered
But I know that that is a lie
They're due for a big surprise
From demons from the sky
Makes me so glad I'm wised up
Got it sized up
Hell I'm a lucky guy
Bob brought me slack
And that's lots more
To do
More than I ever got from the con
Though I know it's only
Cause of all those pills he's on
Heck I know he ain't too clever
But whatever he says I'll do or die
A new breed of rasta youth is currently dominating the reggae scene in Jamaica and around the world
Dressed in turbans and robes and preaching militant lyrics
With religious and social messages
The Bobber Dreads or Bobber Ashanti
Are some of the most imposing figures on the island
Now I've been playing tunes from Bobber artists for years
And there's all kind of rumours about members of the Bobber order
That they believe in racial segregation
Repress their women
And basically known as Jamaica's homegrown fundamentalists
Dancehall star Capleton
Whose lyrics include slackness
Reference to guns, sex and violence
Quote him
Calling himself the prophet
His lyrics became conscious and increasingly militant
Preaching reparturation of black people to Africa
Human rights, religious purity and the burning of the wicked
More and more artists started to throw their weight behind the Bobber movement
This new wave reggae had very strong lyrics
With reference to burning the government
And other parts of what the Bobbers called Babylon
The spiritual home of the Bobber Ashanti is in Bull Bay, Jamaica
Bobo Hill
Which was founded by leader Priest Emmanuel
Holy Manuela is last year I Jah Rastafari
What is very clear
I mean everybody here is dressed very traditionally
In turbans and robin
You get this feeling that you're a hundred years back
But when we do actually get inside
In their rooms, their computers, mobile phones
They're in 2004 definitely
Holy Manuela is last year I Jah Rastafari
Rastafari
The priest dressed in turban and long African robes
Invited me to join in prayers
Anytime you hear we talk about God
Christ, Father, Moses
This man we are talk upon
When we pray
When you see we come in and pray
This man we are pray to
Prophet, priest and king you see
Mostai
Slasya I Jah Rastafari
Priest Bob
Man, you should have seen the Bobo Dread last in the room
Man you should have seen the Bobo Dread last in the room
You see the Bobo Dread is a man we're well humble
Walk from dream and go straight to jungle
Hop on them shoulders is a big bundle
Priest Bob
Man they say we bring forward a purification
And a world peace
You know we wish everyone to them own vine and fig tree
This music, as I say, is a heart ball music. It walks under the earth like a living man.
It can make the hills and the mountains dance. The trees dance, the animals dance too.
It rises up earth, creates lightning and thunder in diverse places.
It's a comfort to the heart of the righteous and discomfort to the heart of the wicked.
It's cutting and clearing, renting and tearing, bringing down the pillars of Rome.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, so long, so long, so long, so long, so long, so long, so long, so long, so long.
I'm coming from the land of the devil, the land of the dead.
They say that I'm the one who's dead. I'm a prince of peace.
I'm a prince of peace.
Bobo artists have to come to terms with spreading the good word through an unholy music.
We don't learn much at school, but we learn from the music.
So they see Bobo more and more, and they see them on stage.
Now they see them on the TV, music videos.
They start DJing and they say, yo, go buy Bobo and learn what's what.
Some Bobos become very rich and famous and change their lifestyles.
Whatever the case, artists calling themselves Bobo have been consistently topping the reggae charts worldwide.
Whatever gets you rich and famous, you're going to do a lot more of it to get more rich and more famous.
You better believe it's commerce.
Or is the Bobo artist popularity part of a global backlash against the dominant forces in the world?
For now, though, the Bobo movement is one of many faiths in a very religious country.
Although appearing extreme in some of their beliefs, Bobo is currently inspiring more lyrics than revolution.
He is known for singing some of the shyn breeze in thesey music.
There you go.
I won an English contest.
You watch the dance with the man I choose as gameplay.
Thank you.
Bye-bye.
Set tape recording made at a C in 1973.
I picked the gall darned terror of the frigging gods out of my nose.
Pardon my language.
But yee-haw, let the sons of God and man bear witness.
Even in the belly of the thunderbird I've been casting out the false prophets,
I'm busting a dud and blowing my o-ring, and right to throw a lobe.
For I speak only the frigging truth, and never in my days have I spoken other than.
For my every utterance is a lie, including this very one you hear.
I say, have sex with, em, if they can't take a joke.
My God, anything for a laugh, I say.
I am the last remaining homo correctus, I am the gall darned man of the future.
I'll drive a mile so, as not to walk a foot.
I drank the devil under seven tables, I am too intense to bite.
I cannot be tracked on radar.
I wear nothing uniform, I wear no gall darned uniform.
Yes baby, I'm twenty-three feet tall and have thirteen roseau breasts.
I was.
Suckled by a triceratops, I gave the ante's verge in a high protein tonsil wash.
I'm a bacteriological weapon, I'm armed and loaded.
I'm a fission reactor, I fork plutonium.
Power plants are fueled by the sweat from my brow.
You make me happy when I am blue.
Too low.
1-800-1961.
I'm acting just like an animal.
Is all the time I need and all the time I want.
Ample.
Antithesis.
Are you hungry?
Are you in good hands?
Ashes of a dead world.
And he moved an entire community back into the dark ages.
Uh-huh.
Better blood?
Bob called me.
I sing the body electric.
I burn up.
But I made love.
I can't even play Perry Como.
Chip off the old block.
Come on Alice
A dimension of wind.
Don't make any noise when the music's playin.
Don't paint the sun anymore.
Don't touch, don't touch my tool.
T-Zone, cut up by Reverend Norrell Preff, and more of that to come later.
And for this next cover tune, I'm not sure who performed it.
Possibly Prozac for lovers.
Sitting on a park bench
Eyeing little girls with bad intent
Snot running down his nose
Greasy fingers smearing shabby clothes
Hey, Aqualung
Drying in the cold sun
Watching as the frilly panties run
Feeding like a dead duck
Spitting out pieces of his broken lung
Hey, Aqualung
Sun streaking cold
An old man wandering lonely
Taking time the only way he knows
Leg hurting bad
As he bends to pick a dog
And he goes down to the bar
And warms his feet
Feeling alone
The arm is up the road
Salvation, all the motive
And a cup of tea
Aqualung, my friend
Don't stop, don't stop me now
I'm not afraid of the way I need to see
Your poor old soul, you see
It's only me
From PR News in Washington, I'm hampered by a lack of city officials.
Massachusetts Governor Mitt Romney has declared a state of PR news.
This is me.
And I don't get it.
You know this.
PR is a violation of obligations, nations.
Secretary of State Condoleezza Rice exploded today in Texarkana, Arkansas,
aggravating several people by exposure to PR News in Washington.
Could you tell me a story before I go to bed?
Yes, I can, dear.
I'll tell you a story about the shrinking intellect.
It's about a whole town full of people whose brains got smaller at one time.
Well, it actually took about five years.
I don't know what started this.
I don't know.
Where it began.
But it reached such a sorry state that people would walk up and down
from one edge of the town to the other,
burbling inanities to each other
and sniveling off people they didn't quite dig.
And then, pretty soon, big hunks of their teeth fell out
because the decay had seeped down from their brain area all the way into their mouths.
And next thing you know, the tongues was a-wiggling,
and they were in pain.
That's right.
They were in some heavy, dark pain.
But the tongues kept a-wagging.
The brain was dead.
The brain had actually atrophied into a piece of lump.
A lumpage.
Say what?
Another prophetic vision.
You'll thank us for it later.
And he said, well, that may be, but I doubt it.
A lonesome cowboy Dave did that.
And now for some live clips from Radio Synesthesia from WCSB Cleveland
with host Dr. Sinister and callers,
Governor Rocknar, Big Johnson, and yours truly.
Yep.
There you go.
Yeah.
Hey, I was going to say something, Rocknar.
How's your LCD projection TV doing?
Oh, it's doing great.
Hey, I was talking to a technician.
He says that in a couple of years from now,
you'll be putting a new bulb in that LCD projection TV.
Yeah, that's what they said.
Yeah.
Huh?
That's what they said at the store.
They said they'd help.
But the bulbs are actually cheaper.
Yeah, it's cheaper to get a bulb fixed.
Oh, a couple of years from now, after the X's come,
if you don't have that subgenius minister's card in your pocket,
you're going to be running that.
That projector with candlelight.
You're going to have a candle inside that video projector.
The X-Day prophecies are as relevant today as they ever have been.
You'll be reduced to 16 millimeter projectors after X-Day.
Yeah, I'll tell you one thing.
You're so lucky.
I'll tell you one thing, Stang.
You know, I mean, I understand that prophecy is prophecy,
but PR is PR.
And when you set a date like that,
I think a lot of people lost interest after the conspiracy in 1998.
That's what you think.
Well, we thought, yes, our business fell by half.
That's really...
We lost our mansions.
We lost several of our limousines.
Not to mention that, God almighty,
I can't even count how many employees and...
Quit?
Interns, as we call them.
Yeah.
That's...
So, yeah.
You know, obviously, a lot more people had faith in precisely that date
than I would have thought.
You know, it really boggles the mind,
because when you think of the subgenius type,
you don't think of them as being terribly punctual.
You don't think of them as being...
You think of them as the kind of people who have to constantly
check the calendar to see what month it is.
They probably didn't pay their taxes on time, either.
I didn't.
You know, I mean...
And that's not even the real...
calendar, anyway.
You know, we all know that that's the bogus conspiracy calendar.
We don't really know what date it is.
Well, the lesson of it all is that we don't know nothing.
Exactly.
And Bob Dobbs could come any second.
He could be knocking at your door
with a giant spaceship hovering outside,
and you're either going to have that ticket to ride,
or else you're going to be target practice.
Yep, yep.
We were sitting in the park.
It was a bright...
some shiny day.
We went on all the rides.
And then we died.
We went in the funhouse.
Charles Manson was there.
He was our guide.
And then we died.
It was a beautiful day
in the amusement park.
Not a cloud in the sky.
And then we died.
We went on the dive of cars.
They were going 87.
And the eights they declined.
And then we died.
We went on the sky ride.
We thought we could fly.
Gave it a try.
And then we died.
It was a beautiful day
in the amusement park.
Not a cloud in the sky.
And then we died.
We went to the Jeffrey Dahmer Lake in Intakistan.
Asked them what you got for dinner.
He said he just arrived.
And then we died.
We went on the rollercoaster.
It got off track.
We flew through the sky.
And then we died.
Duh, duh, duh, duh.
If I can't hop it, I'll go down.
Everybody's dead except me.
I do it every day.
It's the family friendly SUV.
It's big fat.
Feminine Itchено.
and odor there are forces from beyond our world respectfully submitted for your perusal we have
four big lovely turbines and they're getting hungry free sample friendly mobility specialists
are standing by listen the bean dip's starting to get a little funky get more out of now greed
avarice cruelty look i know you've got your hands full but somebody get on the pipe
i really love the hands-on environment happy
or the world may be turned upside down but i know that i've been put here for a reason
he shouldn't have thought those bad thoughts hey what's the idea of running around the street with
no pants on hit the horn button some people aren't built for competition janie or big
pretentious houses they can't afford or rich communities they don't feel comfortable in
hungry the army's in hooray for the army
you
I just can't take this another day not another hour
I celebrate myself and sing myself idiotic
I don't like any noise in the music's playing if you're a homo
I'm all right why am I all right I think you're out of your mind it hurts me
I've sent to the authorities joe's diner I'm just off my rock leave let's start over people
I mean yeah people you know but not
not this is this is the most thing I've ever heard of hello there I'm torturing evil
I'd like to begin with an illustrated detailed course in perversion
we have a constitutional guarantee of crime and violence
no matter who buys this material 75 to 90 percent of it ends up in jail
In one where they're getting lives Waar song
will the truth someone else hope thedle
that only forked cookingAP香港才、 débθε公席 published here to look at these new things morning empty if you want
The teachers of unnatural sex acts
Their trust is gone
Military Kaplan's Association of the United States
That's living big
I spend a lot of time thinking
Form a citizen
Or pervert
That's living big
My brain here is a lot of games, guys
By Saint Foo
And before that, Norrell Preff's T-Zone
And that song, And Then We Died
Was by Wally Pleasant
Actually, you know, it's funny
I'm looking at this
You know, I'm looking at this
UAIOE CD here again
And the guy on the cover
In the artwork
Kind of looks like Bob's evil twin
That had never occurred to me
Until just now
Well, this guy
This guy really does
He's got
Well, this is
This is from 1989
The artwork of Brute
No, this guy's got the hair
He's got the grin
He's got the
Like a lot of the so-called Bob clones
I've seen people just say
Oh, his smile kind of looks like Bob
Or oh, his pipe kind of looks like Bob's pipe
Or his hair kind of looks like Bob's hair
But like you never see
Like every Bob's pipe is like Bob's pipe
Or any Bob clone picture I've ever seen
You don't have all those qualities going together
Every now and then we find one
That is obviously really him
But they're quite rare, really
Actually, one I saw was
A Mr. Pipe character from Ren and Stimpy
I saw one
Now, that was Bob
That guy, you never saw his face, though
Right
That's how you know it was Bob
Yep, yep
Hey, I was gonna say something
You know, there's an easy way
Of getting around the whole UFO thing
Floating near your house
And you're gonna get attacked
When Bob comes to your door
Kill him
Exactly
He'll be back in two minutes
Kill him
He'll be back
Keep killing him
He'll run out of ammo
The factories cannot pump out ammunition fast enough
Think how many times Elmer Fudd said that about Bugs Bunny
See what happened to Bugs Bunny
He just keeps coming back and back
Wile E. Coyote keeps coming back over and over again
I think Bob's like a vampire
He just put a stake through his heart
Nope
I mean Bob's like a exhausted burned animal
Get rid of anything
In the looseness of the web
The puzzle is just a game
I know nothing
what i thought
human was
human
Marley Needs.
So it's a gag.
It's a prank.
Humanity, why do you bug us?
Oh, massive bring down.
The world is a bongo drum.
And we are merely the ubleo de suido de suido.
Hello, hello.
How are you?
From Smith.
Hello, hello.
My name is Juan Juan.
Hello.
Thank you.
He's lost his faculties.
Music mix by yours truly, I, Vin Stang.
This music that you've been hearing in the background, by the way,
is by the Flying Ryan Brothers from their new album, Blue Marble, a CD.
You can learn more about this incredible instrumental album,
the Grammy-winning subgeniuses, the Flying Ryan Brothers,
from...
Ryanetics.com.
That's R-Y-A-N.
I pay no taxes.
The devil's hands are my ideal playground.
I hold the seven-bladed windbreaker.
The wheels that turn are behind me.
I think backwards.
I do it for fun.
My imagination is a frigging cancer,
and I'll pork it before it porks me.
The say a godzillion is the highest number there is,
well, my god.
I count to a godzillion and one.
Yes, I'm the purple flower of Hell County.
Give me wide hearth when I drop my drawers,
mother nature's moods.
I use a python for a prophylactic.
I'm thicker, harder, and meaner than the Alaskan pipeline,
and carry more spew.
I'll freeze your seed before it gets the bathroom tile.
Yee.
From NPR News in Washington,
I'm severely disrupted because of the very positive day.
Forecasters could become Tropical Storm Wilma today,
with top winds of 1935 miles per hour.
Getting relief aid to remote areas has been severely disrupted because of PR's radio reports.
Investigators were killed.
PR's bad.
Meanwhile, the US military says ministers and central bankers said in a statement
they were concerned that finance ministers from wealthy and developing nations say,
this is PR news.
Washington.
They said they don't call it PR enough.
naive AI
They think proper沒有
Golden Age
Thank god, we came through.
FOR
MONTH
I
WANT
BUY
THE
Da Vinci.
And now, Norel Press.
Welcome, sir. Nice to have you on the program.
All Russia, all juicy, juicy, all Russia, juicy, juicy, juicy, juicy.
Let this be short.
You know, I'm lightning, but...
And I am deeply, deeply messed up mentally, emotionally
because of the propaganda.
Plantation.
Propaganda.
Got this mental illness.
Form of mental illness, Rush.
Mental illness, Rush.
Abortion, homosexuality, promiscuity, prostitution, racism.
I hate, I hate, I hate, I hate, I hate, I hate, I hate, I hate to stop you, but...
I have to. I have to.
So if you just hold your...
Propaganda.
Institute.
I'm just darker skin, Rush.
Amen.
You look evil.
All right, all right, all right, all right.
Mental, mental illness.
Mental illness.
Well, Rush, that's...
But, but, but, but, Rush, thanks to you, I have...
I can smell you ten miles away.
Fontaneous.
Man came from pornography.
Slave.
Slave master.
Keep them on the plantation.
Man came from race.
Man came from slime.
That's me.
Stutter around.
This is one of the greatest oral-foral final exam at the Limbaugh Propaganda Plantation.
Me?
I'm just...
I'm just working on the job and lucky to be doing that, friends.
Because since they've had this crackdown on crack, they have succeeded in true conspiracy fashion
in making it so you can't get anything but crack.
I wonder why that is.
Actually, you can't even get crack in Dallas.
You can get plenty of cocaine.
Oh, yeah.
Cheaper than ever.
Because coke, like most of these other drugs, lights up that little spot in your brain.
That would normally be lit up by sex.
Or a real kick-ass riff off your favorite song at just the right time.
Or the right incredible climactic passage from a great book might light it up on rare occasions.
Or Jesus or Jim Jones or whatever.
Or a subgenius tape or a subgenius show like this every two minutes will light it up.
Or the merest glimpse of one of Bob's hundred-year-old footprints might light up that spot.
That mighty undiluted, unneagified squirt will flood that spot with just the right juices from just the right glands.
But since to read that good book takes days,
and you've got to be in the right place at the right time for that song to have the effect,
if you're going to get it through sex, well, that takes at least five minutes.
And often, you have to take them out to dinner.
But my God!
You can just go out.
Spend some money.
And in no time at all, you can light up that little spot.
Just as soon as you can get back in your car, baby.
Just as soon as you can get you a sample.
Fire that booger up.
What else do you need?
Why would there be any need for noble feelings for all mankind?
Or even any sense of human decency whatsoever?
Why would there be any need for anything but to light up that spot in that brain?
And when you get those headsets, where you just tape a little pad to either side of your temple,
one in the front and one in the back on a shaved place on your head,
and you have that little control in your pocket with a battery in it,
as long as you've got you a $1.98 9-volt battery in that thing,
you can crank it up to 5, to the 5 marker on the dial, and feel mighty damn good.
Or turn it up to 10, and you'll never turn it off.
There better be somebody standing by.
Anywhere past 6 on the infinite control with knob, and you're not going to turn it off.
You're not going to, friend.
You might turn it off for a second, but it would hurt.
Oh, it would hurt to turn it down.
Even to turn it down.
And once you've felt that 10 setting, you're not going to want to live with anything else.
You're going to be crying a year later for the 11 setting.
You're going to be begging.
Oh, you'll be reading all the catalogs, waiting for that breakthrough that'll give you an 11 on the dial.
And you'll be feeling that control.
Oh, yes siree.
You think they got a drug problem now?
You think there's a drug problem in the United States?
In the whole world now?
Oh, mark my words, ye sinners.
Wait until you get some electronics involved, baby.
You think those computer whizzes got rich quick?
Well, wait until they invent the head zapper.
Oh, it's my head, you'll say.
It's my head.
That's all you'll be able to say.
Every song will be the song.
It's my head.
That'll be the only awareness you need.
It's just between you, your head, and your control.
Your pleasure center stimulator control.
Oh, yeah.
You'll be like a monkey in a cage sitting in a pool of his own saliva.
That's right.
Because once you feel number 10, you ain't going to...
You can kiss what you now know as reality.
Goodbye, baby.
Yes.
And after a while, even the 10 starts to feel like pain.
But you can't go looking for the 11 button because you can't get up.
You've been there too long because you're dead.
You're a ghost that died while it was high.
Yep.
If you die when you're high, my friend, your spirit becomes a wandering shade.
Wandering, trying to score for eternity.
Or at least until a subgenius priest comes along and sends it spanking back to where it originally came from.
My God, and here I am running out of gas.
You're always going to run out sooner or later.
That's what you got to remember.
Too much.
Oh, yeah.
Too much is always better than not enough.
Till you run out.
And you will, friend.
You'll run out of that church air right when you least expect it.
Right when you thought you had all the church air in the world.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, I had all the church air in the world.
But, but, but, Negi has it now.
Oh, you'll scream.
You'll cry.
You'll wail and gnash your teeth.
And you'll wish you could die.
You'll wish you could die.
But you can't.
You can't die.
Because your terror keeps you alive and manufactures just enough church air for you not to die but just to keep needing more.
You're going to be ready for the finals in 1998, my friend.
It's a beautiful world we live in.
A sweet romantic place.
Beautiful people everywhere.
The way they call their hair.
Makes me want to say it's a beautiful world.
It's a beautiful world.
Now believe me.
It's a wonderful time to be here.
Beautiful times.
It's nice to be alive
Wonderful people everywhere
The way they show they care
Makes me wanna say
It's a wonderful place
For me
My place
And all that blue
That blue
It's a beautiful world we live in
A sweet romantic place
Beautiful people everywhere
The way they comb their hair
All makes me wanna say
It's a beautiful world
For you
How are you doing today?
For me, that is a really difficult question, Dr. Lawrenson,
because the world around me is shrinking,
and the Four Horsemen of the Apocalypse are coming to see me today,
and they're not bringing flowers,
which just makes it really difficult to get organized.
I'm in here because they say I have a nervous condition.
Well, well, here's my question.
Who wouldn't be nervous if they really, really looked at their lives?
I mean, whose life is that good?
Um, we're talking about our ability to go forward in time, to go into the future.
It's a trip. You know, it's like a serious vacation.
See, stay calm. They're always ordering us.
Be calm, be calm, be calm, be calm.
Then what are you going to order me to be calm?
Well, I've been approached by the Federal Trade Organization.
And what have they approached you about, Mr. McKenzie?
About me?
And this is nuts. But they have asked me to head up the organization for the organized.
I don't believe in disposable language either. You know, small talk, little talk, chit chat. Useless.
The organization for the organized.
When I was in the Gulf, the organization was recruiting the organized.
I knew it. I knew it!
Long live the organization for the organized!
TV, you know, helps soothe an active mind.
Sister, can I mention about the double entendre from Bugs Bunny?
The what?
There's a double entendre in one of Bugs Bunny's cartoons.
Well, why don't you try it?
Bugs Bunny and Aladdin's lamp.
Try it.
Okay, there's a big, mean-looking guy, big-looking Arab with a scimitar, right?
And he's got a full mustache and a beard.
Bugs looks at this guy square in the face and says,
What's shaking, beaver puss?
Well, interesting.
Yes.
Interesting.
I saw a Porky Pig in which someone tried to insult Porky by saying,
Ah, your mother smokes tennis shoes or something.
And Porky kind of looked at the camera and goes,
No, it was his sister.
Your sister smokes tennis shoes.
He goes, No, my sister doesn't smoke tennis shoes.
My sister works in a butcher shop and smokes ham.
Cannibalism jokes abound.
Actually, you know, when Looney Tunes originally came out, they weren't intended as kids entertainment, really.
No, they weren't.
They were marketing to a...
I might curse like a real sailor.
I didn't understand most of those cartoons until I saw them years later after I'd grown up.
Yeah.
It's like I caught that beaver puss reference on Nickelodeon one day.
I was just shocked that Nickelodeon let it go through.
Well, you know, you see funny stuff.
Yeah, they obviously thought, Well, it's Bugs Bunny.
It's harmless.
No, it isn't.
Well, you know, little kids...
That's what I've always had to say about, you know, sexual references.
It seems that, you know, sexual references really bother Americans more, you know, and violence doesn't.
And violence really bothers Europeans, but sex doesn't so much.
You know, I just wonder what kind of culture we'd have if things were any different, you know, if we flip that around.
You know, it's okay to show somebody's head getting blown off, but it's not okay to, you know, to show some...
Well, this country was settled by religious nuts.
It was.
That were, you know, kind of been hinted at, kind of politely asked to leave from their respective...
Pretty much.
...original countries.
And, you know, but here's what I've always had to say about...
About sex references and sex jokes on TV.
If a kid is young enough that they shouldn't be hearing it, then they're young enough that they're not going to understand it at all.
And it will be totally lost on them, and they probably won't think anything of it.
Right.
It's a joke that kids aren't going to get, but all the audience in all their...
Suitable for children up to age four, but...
You know, some of them might...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Some of them might...
And over age 18.
...might get a little confused.
At which point, you know, they should ask their parents and maybe...
Maybe their parents will explain it to them.
And, you know, if not, there's always the internet.
But, you know...
That's...
Likely all they're gonna find is porn.
The internet's gonna be the last place you're gonna be able to go for real cartoons.
Oh, yeah.
Everything I know about sex...
Information.
...I've heard from my dad's detective paperback cover.
There you go.
Yeah.
See you next time.
Bye.
Bye-bye.
Thank you.
Friends, that was Artemia Salina, and you're listening to the Hour of Slack.
If you want more information about the Church of the Subgenius, check out www.subgenius.com.
Praise Bob, and praise Princess We.
We.
Life or death.
Mother!
Charlie!
Master Blasters.
Maybe we're all insane.
More and more people are discovering.
Blood!
Much too hot.
We will demonstrate to all interested parties a new and extremely interesting power source.
Next time I'm going to get off.
The other day at our office, a lady mentioned the nice balls that she saw.
No comment here.
No comment at all.
No logic.
No reason.
No explanation.
Just a prolonged nightmare.
It means he has no mental facilities.
Facilities, yes.
Who said that?
There are no more boundaries, governments, or noble causes.
No?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
I'm not a housebreaker.
Oh.
Oh, yes, I did forget something, didn't I?
Oh, yes, it's good.
It's very good.
I say we sit on it the rest of the day and see what some 105s can do.
It's one long heart.
You'll find that our balls are attached to some very nice and knowledgeable people.
Out of the frying pan.
Into the fire.
Over.
Overactive bladder.
Over and over.
What are we gonna do now?
Know ye by these present that I do hereby declare peace upon the entire world!
Pick up the phone and call now.
.
This is the first message.
From the PLF.
You judge of the so-called subgenius.
You have disgusted a race of the pinks.
You have spread lies and deceits against us.
You shall not succeed until we are avenged.
We demand vengeance from the lies and deceits which you spread about us.
There on your hour of slack radio ministry.
Your sick heart.
This is disgusting.
The pink race shall succeed.
We will stop at nothing to destroy you.
This is the first of many messages.
This is a warning against you, the church of the subgenius.
The church of the poo genius, more like it.
Yes, poo genius.
Church of the poo genius.
You have nothing to do with Bob.
We own Bob.
You don't own Bob.
We are Bob.
Chaka-ba-ka-lay-kee, chaka-ba-sa-ka-la, ka-da-da-ba-ta, da-so-ma.
Chain smirker.
Mm-hmm.
Do you remember December's foggy freeze?
When the ice that clings onto your beard was screaming agony?
And you snatched your rattling last breath with deep sea diver sounds.
And the flowers bloom like madness in the spring.
Chaka-ba-kyo-ka-kaa, Chaka-ba-kyo-ka-koo.
Chaka-ba-kyo-ka-ka-kaa, frustxes your mind's positions.
When I Mama can say duskани gaya, you remain calm your definitely and have filiality.
At Entonces as much as you pay the need that you return home, the next is dói- Чтобы.
Yú éca par.
Goido goido goido-
Guido cana Guido comments.
Sha la la la la la
Sitting on a park bench
Eyeing little girls with bad intent
Snot running down his nose
Greasy fingers smearing shabby clothes
Hey aqualung
Drying in the cold sun
Watching as a frilly panties run
I kidnapped the future and ransomed it for the past
I made time wait up for me to bleed my liver
My infernal breath wilts the tree of life
I left my s'more on the rock of ages
Who'll tear flesh with me?
Who'll spill their juice?
Who'll gouge with me?
Whose candle will I fart out?
Who?
I'm ready
So step aside
All you but loot
Neurotic
Insecure
The spectacle slaps all limp meat
I'm a crime-fighting master criminal
I am not a criminal
I'm insane
I'm a screamer and a laugher
I make a spectacle of myself
I am a sight
My physical type cannot be classified by science
My familiar is a pterodactyl
From PR News in Washington
Unformed in the Caribbean
Japan's Prime Minister has triggered hostile reactions across Asia by visiting Tokyo
The U.S. military says it has carried out aerial bombings of PR News in Washington