you are about to participate in a great adventure you are about to experience the awe and mystery
which reaches from the inner mind to the subgenius
all right all right well we're good we're not going to waste any time dear friends tonight
we're going to get right into it that's got to be the quickest title comeuppance ever on a hour of slack show
but it's because we have a lot of ground to cover tonight we're going to present to you an entire play
from brain rot radio theater in cleveland originally broadcast on wcsb cleveland
this amazing
uh
well why not just call it what it is it's a parody i suppose you might say called a clockwork
orangutan uh starring lonesome cowboy dave psycho pathfinder and scabby days those uh three
that that that anything for a laugh duo
and uh yeah we don't we don't normally just give a whole show
to a show that's not a show that's not a show that's not a show that's not a show that's not a show
to one tape but that's mostly what we are doing tonight partly because we're not really here right
now we don't have time to monkey with yet uh uh a uh a fourth show all done in one day yeah we're
having to do the hour of slack now like a game show where you do uh uh all weeks episodes in only
uh
One day.
Saves time and money.
Well, those things are.
They're as real as Bob.
As real as Bob.
So anyway, let's get right on down into this alternate universe created by Brain Rot Radio Theater.
I think that pretty much all subgenius listeners will get it sentence by sentence.
Although there may be some just so young or so queasy that they never saw the original Stanley Kubrick movie that this is a...
Well, yeah, I'll admit it's a takeoff.
You know, on the hour of slack, we don't normally do comedy.
I mean, this is a religious radio broadcast.
But, well, in this case, we have to make an exception.
And here it is.
Good evening, and welcome to Brain Rot Radio Theater and the adventures of Lonesome Cowboy Dave, Psychopath Finder, and Scabby Dave's.
Imagine, if you will, a world in the not-too-distant future.
A world infested with wilding youth gangs and rampant social decay.
Imagine a world of harsh drugs that send young minds into fits of ultra-voyance.
A world where subliminal cold warfare has created an underworld language of Anglo-Russian gibberish.
Good evening.
And welcome to...
A Clockwork Orangutan.
A Clockwork Oracle Oracle Atari bankingtime
Starring...
There was me, that is to say,
Lodestone Cow Pie Dave,
and my three droogs,
that is to say, Psychopath Finder Boy Georgie,
and Scabby Tim Days, who is Days,
and the Invisible Spotty.
And we all sat down in the Corova Milk Bar
one Saturday, Notchie,
wondering what to do with our Krabby Raw soups.
The bar served Milk Plus,
that is, Milk Plus, Synthamask, and Veleslog,
the two vital ingridies,
and before any night of any soggy Notchie of ultraviolence,
they stuffed a Pete Knives in,
Pete Knives in your soggy violence.
Okay, okay.
This is the announcer for...
They get the picture.
You guys are...
You're in a futuristic-looking youth gang,
and you talk funny,
and you drink synthetic drugs which make you violent.
Yeah, yeah, but you forgot to lay in more establishing stuff
like our cool outfits and all.
Yeah, but me pay 65 bucks
for this unseen bit of hot fashion.
Okay, okay, you guys are in the Milk Bar,
where statues of naked women
dispense drugs from their breasts,
and you guys are all wearing white coveralls
and big, kicking Dr. Martin's boots and bowler hats,
except Spotty, who's wearing a beret.
Hey!