If you feel you are not properly sedated, call 348-844 immediately.
Failure to do so may result in prosecution for criminal drug evasion.
Think of a world something like Jupiter,
with an atmosphere rich in hydrogen, helium, methane, water, and ammonia,
in which organic molecules might be falling from the skies like manna from heaven,
like the products of the Miller universe.
Could there be life on such a world?
Stand by.
It's looking for us.
Those are the sucking antennas.
Yes.
Yeah, you got it right on the nose, buddy.
What do they call that?
Signal sucker?
Voidmobium?
Signal psi.
Some people believe they suck soul signal.
Yeah, that's what they call it.
Signal psi, not, you know, PSI, psi.
I don't know.
There's some other stuff I can't understand.
There's a lot of stuff that I can't understand.
I mean, in the contract, it's written in the...
That's how the moshy-moshy is, yes.
How close does that zoom in?
Can you, like, see the little Uranus bug crawling around among the giant...
You can see the hemorrhoidal...
Oh, look at that. Look at that.
How wonderful.
Wow.
At that...
Man.
Oh, whoa. Okay, I can see it.
I've got it.
You know, but when you're far enough away from it, it looks so smooth.
I do believe in spokes.
I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do.
You see, there are many things that we are to go on and do,
whether we feel like them or not.
You know, to be candid, right now, I wouldn't be doing this program.
I don't feel real good.
I'm kind of...
You know, we kind of came back real exhausted.
But, you know, if there's any way that...
And I don't want to use me really as an example here,
because that's not...
It's not important what I do.
The important thing is what we're told, even in Scripture,
that it says in Hebrews 10, 36, it says...
Do a little good.
I'm kind of...
You know, so it's like you're aware,
and you'll even admit it.
Now, that's to your strength.
That's to your credit.
I got writing about like bats and hieroglyphics that I can't understand.
I don't know what you're talking about right now.
It's the place.
That sounds kind of cool.
Let us be thankful we have an occupation to fill.
Work hard.
Increase production.
Prevent accidents.
And be happy.
You get sucked down one tube,
this is...
It does what...
Well, one tube takes all I like to go through.
Too many web sites you go to,
just take you like around a little like...
Like it's a little like fairyland,
little merry-go-round,
like...
The most Baroque symphony of weirdness out there, man.
A Baroque symphony of weirdness is what everybody needs.
Oh, but it's absolutely Baroque.
The deeper you go into it,
the more little subsides you get,
and then they have these little arms and tentacles
that turn into whole universes.
You are a fool, believers.
Blessings of the state.
Blessings of the masses.
Thou art a subject of the divine,
created in the image of man,
by the masses,
for the masses.
Let us be thankful we have commerce.
Buy more.
Buy more now.
Buy.
And be happy.
41138 suffering severe sedation depletion which requires mind blocking...
No, the penile shape was...
If the sheep get out of control,
you grab them with the staff and hook that hook around their neck.
Bad, bad, you know, just bad.
Bad, bad, you know, just bad sheep.
Mink.
Mink with bright little eyes and tousled hair,
peered inside.
And behind her,
tall, wavering blue shadows.
Frightful shadows.
Peek-a-boo.
What kind of zark orgasm could you have if you had a regular sheree-vrum anyway?
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
It wouldn't be worth it.
So even at the most basic core of everything is bestiality.
Sooner or later,
we all want a thing that is bad.
And to walk on all fours.
To suck up drink from a stream.
And to...
Jabba.
To sing the words.
To go snuffling at the earth.
And floor the bark of trees.
To eat flesh for fish.
To make love to more than one.
Every which way.
These are all bad things.
These are not good things.
Not the things that men do.
We are men.
Are we not?
Because if not,
the poo-poo machinery,
and that's what we call the lower chakra, children,
the poo-poo machinery which causes fight, flight, or fright,
and sometimes another moist evacuation,
which will be aboard that ship,
wearing the blue bowling pants we give them,
and shirt showing the cellulite popping out of the...
Give me some of that church air, boy.
Give me some.
Yeah, open that window and suck it in.
Yeah.
Don't be picky about it.
There's enough for nobody.
Don't be pinky about it.
Yeah, don't be a little pinky stinky.
You're pink.
There's not enough for anyone.
There ain't no room for no pinks on the ships.
There's no air.
There's no church air.
If you haven't lost your pink...
Well, if you haven't lost it...
Your name is not written in the book.
You gotta get rid of all of it, don't you?
In fact, you gotta find there has to be no pink traces on your body.
Matter of fact, if your name is written in the book,
your name is not written in the book.
Never mind.
Not all.
What's wrong?
I need something stronger.
Take four red capsules.
In ten minutes, take two more.
Help is on the way.
I believe this spooks a bunch.
Around here?
That's ridiculous, spooks.
That's silly.
Don't you believe in spooks?
My head is swelling to the size of 14 solar masses.
That's because the pigs are infected, man.
The pigs are all infected.
The cows.
The pigs.
The sheep.
They won't take the Transluc Clune.
And now they got the smelly mallard.
The sheep.
Sheepo.
Are you listening, sheepo?
And there shall come among them many viruses and many portents of death.
And there shall also come a great sigh of the wind that brings clouds of black soot
which choke the little chickens in their barnyards.
So what you gonna eat, Earthman, when you can't get a hydraulically choked yellow chicken
from Earthboy?
What you gonna eat when all the cows got Popeyes sphincter disease?
Earthboy?
What am I gonna do when minute traces of faecal matter cover the entire solar system?
What you gonna do when minute traces of faecal matter cover the entire solar system and
everybody's got the runs?
R исck me that pee bucket, Earthboy?
What you gonna do when this cesspool reveals itself like a bad Stanislaus Slam 돼요?
Stand still, Earthboy!
Get one more pill!
… You'll see.
Man, I really don't want you to act like this.
Get off!
The garish faces, the sideshow strumpet women, the Bo Peep with the beard.
There's only one thing to do, Earth boy.
Climb aboard.
Set the controls.
Climb aboard, Earth man.
You have no alternative.
Yeah.
You know it to be your destiny.
Everything will be all right.
You are in my hands.
I am here to protect you.
You have nowhere to go.
Here at Truth Control, we do our best.
Here at Truth Control, we do our best to keep you thinking of the best things you can think.
Here at Truth Control, we do our best to keep you not thinking, to keep you asleep, to keep
you wandering around in the dark.
Here at Truth Control, we do our best to keep you safe and we'd like you to play yourself
to keep you awake, to keep you running in circles.
Please try to die.
All I can do is know your information.
Goodbye.
Please come back.
You have nothing to be afraid of.
We have to go back.
This is your last chance to return.
You have nowhere to go.
You cannot survive outside the city, shall you?
We only want to help you.
This is your last chance.
Space is the place.
There can be other creatures in this alien environment.
Hunters.
Hunters are fast and maneuverable.
They eat the floaters, both for their organic molecules and for their store of pure hydrogen.
But there can't be many hunters, because if they destroy all the floaters, they themselves will perish.
But have we neglected one of the most important items necessary for being effective for the kingdom?
I have come upon an amazing and startling conclusion.
That this here great mass that we stand upon, heaving and throttling below us like a mighty, mighty, poultry device choker,
this thing we call America, this great continental division between us, cannot and must not be ripped further asunder.
I say to us, tramp it is our manifested destiny to touch the stars and have our damned hands burned.
Ha, ha, ha.
What do you think, boys?
Let's do it.
Ha, ha, ha.
What do we do?
You ask that question now?
The Major no longer asks it.
Do you know the answer, Major?
Sure.
We'll circle around.
Then we'll crash.
Ha, ha, ha.
No, no, no, no.
No, it'll be all right, my boy.
Ha, ha, ha.
My words again.
Have peace forever.
Prophecy is an easy thing, for rarely is the prophet brought to judgment.
Tonight I bring you a false prophecy.
The place of our story is a great rocket speeding away from the moon.
Now, as you notice, some of these ships are made of cardboard.
But if you've got the will, if you've got what made America great,
if you've got a heart as big as the sun,
and an ass as big as the moon,
you'll make it.
You'll storm on through those stars like a laser through butter.
Yeah, man.
Yeah.
Come on, come on.
Don't worry about that plastic wraparound.
It's not real plastic.
No, that's, that's, that's solar shield, man.
That'll protect you.
It's not plastic and, and, and, and those cigarette wrappers on the floor.
That's insulation device for when you're in deep space.
But you've got to believe, you've got to believe, you've got to believe, Earthman.
You've got to believe.
Deep space.
In the flesh, flesh, flesh.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes, I've always loved it.
Yes, I agree, man.
It really makes it.
Yeah.
It's a real thing, man.
It really makes it.
Yeah.
Suzie?
Forget it.
You better run along out if you want to have your invasion before dark.
It is later.
That you think.
I want you to tell me the truth.
What is this invasion silliness?
It isn't silly.
It's just a game.
That's all.
Oh, that was a funny little radio show, wasn't it?
Did you read the peaceful dictum or did you read the world?
That was a funny little radio show.
They thought they were being funny.
I thought they were being funny.
They weren't being funny.
What was the issue?
Invasion?
Drill?
Zero hour?
There are a lot of kooks out there and there are a lot of people that will use, you know,
what the scripture says wrong.
They will interpret it in a way to benefit themselves.
And then I go and I pick the potato.
And then I cut the potato.
And I eat the potato.
And then I make another potato into a potato flute.
And I go up the mountain and I yell to greet the new day.
And then I yell to greet the end of the day.
That is my potato life.
I'm so full of happiness.
Hooked on something new.
Life is such a tricky thing.
Doesn't anybody believe me?
Sometimes I feel like I do that every morning.
Push the wrong button.
Hit the wrong button and disconnect the command module from the lander at the wrong time.
Right.
And your two buddies were in the lander.
Yeah.
And I end up having to hose out the mess that used to be my buddies' base.
If there's anything to be a little bit remorseful about on going to the moon, it was the moon.
And I'm glad that you didn't get a chance to spend as much time around the earth as you'd like.
Because there's an awful lot of very interesting things to see.
Out of control to make your time your circuits dead.
There's something wrong.
With great big credits in flashy neon that say Chaz Smith.
Really?
Coolest dude in the universe.
That's what I want to see.
And this incredible collage material.
Well actually right.
Using the stupid stumble bum blatherings of.
Dave Sang and Weed.
Blabla.
You see.
Something's going to happen.
You must leave.
What?
What's going to happen?
Something wonderful.
All I kept saying to everybody was I want to go home.
And they sent me home.
All he wanted to do was have a great time.
Party.
There's no tomorrow.
It's now.
I'm frightened Annie.
I'm frightened.
What is he?
Time control.
Huh.
I want to go home
Oh, I want to go home
We set sail on this new sea
Because there is new knowledge to be gained
But if you don't keep your focus, right?
You could wake up in like a turgid gas cloud on the dog planet, right?
I mean, you might...
You don't want to be like just waking up from sleep
And having a nightmare about being crippled or something
That's what I was talking about
You will become...
But once you're ruptured onto the escape vessel
Probably you can fix yourself back
You'll be able to think to yourself
That's what had me going, man
We're home
And this is my room
And you're all here
And I'm not going to leave here ever, ever, ever again
Friends, I can clear this entire thing up, I assure you
It's like trying to drive a bus upstairs
It's like trying to drive the bus upstairs
But the ladder is right there next to you
But you're talking so slow it doesn't make sense
It is later than...
You...
Think, think, think
At the end of a rainbow
You find a pot of gold
The meeting of five here tonight, boys and girls
The meeting of five once again
The pentagram
Yes, the pentagram
We have a pentagram going
Pentatonic scales
It's alright
You fuck
He's a five-finger man
Like you, see?
Fuck my magic flanger
Most stylish television performers nowadays
Wouldn't be able to do a Mr. Wiggly Worm thing
Because as soon as they stuck him out
The big iron bars that they have inserted through there
If they're cool nowadays
Would just flop him right over
His head would be laying on the ground all the time
With a barbell stuck through it
The Wiggly Worm
I can't get my head out because I have a barbell stuck through it
He keeps a lot of his children tuning in
James, I'm sorry
Hi, children
Not
I'm Mr. Wiggly Worm and I'm going to get my owner thrown in jail
Slinkies, the slinkies
They're fun for girls and boys
I won't testify that I wasn't abducted by aliens
I bet if I hypnotized you I could find out that you were
No
Does anybody like you have an experience like that other one over there
That isn't the same as the first one?
Has there ever been anyone like you that felt like you just at this point?
Has anyone like you ever listened to the radio and wondered whether this is the right thing to do?
Do the people talking were actually talking about you?
We haven't addressed the listener lately, folks
We haven't addressed...
We are talking about you
We don't really know where he lives
In case you wondered about that
Yes, we are
How would we know where the person lived?
Well, this isn't the generic you that we're addressing
We're talking to the specific you
Yeah, we are speaking specifically, you the listener, to you
This is the hard way
The way of being a man
What do you think?
Sooner or later, we all want to sing this band
The Prairie Squid
I thought it was Bob
The rockets came like drums beating in the night
They came like locusts, swarming and settling in blooms of rosy smoke
Robins will wear their feathery fire Whistling their winds on a low fence wire
And not one will know of war
Not one will care at last when it is done
Not one would mind, neither bird nor tree
If mankind perished utterly
And spring herself when she woke at dawn
But scarcely know that we were gone
That we were gone
Wait for a sign
Did we bash the mashed potatoes MaI
But everything's ok now
But we missed the sign
Wait for a sign
I Forgot
We must wait for the sign
But eventually all of us want what is bad
Look here, patch that maple syrup
I'll put...put the maple syrup on the scrapple there
More toxic shrimp
We are men are we not
We are men.
To make love to more than one, every which way.
These are all bad things.
These are not the things that men do.
We do not lick our own genitalia, although we wish that we could.
We do not run around and sniff the genitalia and the anal areas of other humans, though we wish that we did.
It's like looking in the interior part of a donut where there is no hope.
That sounds like a model.
You are a true believer.
Blessings of the state.
Blessings of the masses.
Thou art a subject of the divine.
Sam!
Hey, Sam, look up there!
Earth!
Oh, what?
Oh, no!
It's catching fire!
It's burning!
Oh, no!
That can't be Earth!
Hell, they can't do this to me!
I've got all our money invested in this place!
Go ahead, Sam.
Switch on more lights.
Turn up the music.
Get the hot dogs on the fire.
There'll be another batch of customers coming along in about a hundred million years.
But now we're here.
We're back to let you know that jazz like shit, if you want to dance this dance, you've got to do this dance with me.
Or if you don't...
Dance! Dance!
Then we don't dance!
Then you're not gonna dance with...
Dance!
You know what he means.
The pantheon.
Yes, we are the gods.
And we're here to mess with your heads.
Can you dance with the gods?
And we're talking about Nick.
They dance quick.
Elvis.
Petruchio.
Areva.
Per Durabo.
James.
Jimmy.
St. Dimfna.
The initials, isn't it?
Jim.
All the people of the Bazaar.
Living and dead.
Yeah.
Sun House.
Little Sun.
Yeah.
Big Sun.
Big Bill.
Big Bill Brunzi.
Muddy.
Little Bill Brunzi.
Dirtbag.
Martin Luther King.
JFK.
Hans Fielder.
Lex Luther.
Popeye the Rat.
He was actually a sailor man, but he was confused.
Yeah.
Jimmy Hoffa.
The Green Hornet.
Hump Sampson and Delilah.
The old barbecue shop down from my house.
Where they both burned up that one night.
And Kato.
And Anne Rice.
She doesn't know it yet.
She's a vampire already.
Zombies.
1-1-3-8.
Suffering severe sedation depletion which requires mind blockage.
Mind blockage.
The ultimate orgasm.
Slipping through the crack between the worlds.
Oh yeah.
You can ride the music into those cracks.
Yeah.
That's what the music's about.
Getting on those waves.
Getting on those love vibes.
Love vibes.
Permeate the universe.
Yeah.
And the lights still don't shine.
Even as much as you want them to.
But you can still ride those waves.
Yeah.
Because they're everywhere.
You just get out of them.
Yeah.
ultimate the ultimate ride everyone thinks it's so hard to get to and for
most people it is
never is the dream but for that ultimate ride all you really gotta do is one
one if you want it bad all you gotta do is let them know
three two one
ignition
we confirm ignition and the thrust is go you guys are really hauling the mail out of there
oh you better believe it it's like we're climbing straight up joe it's a fantastic
sight just like we were shot straight up uh you're going about six thousand feet a second
gee this is swell i wish we didn't ever have to go home how long can we stay a million years
the light the light again all is the light
believe me believe me what are you this is very difficult for me i don't have much time
we got five years you have nowhere to go you can't not survive outside the city shall we
we only want to help you
i've been looking for little girls like you for a long time
i can't die
getting stoned on sunshine
if you sit in the front rows the exam will be passed out to you first
and you'll be finished first before everyone else
there are big advantages to finishing the exam first
this Floating
there's nothing wrong in looking for a higher run
that we'd choose to you
not to be a problem
but you will be
not to be your only
nowhere beside you
alright guys
and good night
then bye bye
luck.
Goodbye. Goodbye. Goodbye now.
Slide into fusion.
Cold. Void. Taxi.
Starboard. Black. Black.
Goodbye. Slide into fusion.
Goodbye. Goodbye. Goodbye.
Goodbye. Goodbye.
Two. One. Ignition.
We confirm ignition and the thrust is go.
You guys are really hauling the mail out of there.
Oh, you better believe it. It's like we're climbing straight up, Joe.
It's a fantastic sight. It's like we were shot straight up.
You're going about 6,000 feet a second.
Our present altitude is now about 3,000 miles.
Spacecraft moving at nearly 35,000 feet per second.
These three crew members are traveling.
Faster than man has ever flown before.
Shut down.
You see, it's all very clear to me now.
The whole thing.
It's wonderful.
And then I keep on going backwards and backwards, you know, as long as you're in one spot.
You can look like Janus, you know, the two-faced god.
You can look back and forth in time and sometimes...
Look back.
You go way, way, way back in time.
Back to the beginning.
Sometimes you go beyond the beginning.
You're getting away.
Though this time, you're stuck.
Oh, there you are.
What we're going to do right here is go back.
Way back.
Back into time.
We take you now
to a back little corner of your mind
you thought you forgot all about.
Yes.
Remember now you were two years old.
Oh, two.
I was the stone of the ocean.
They call me Aphrodite.
I was born all by myself.
I thought of a show and I popped out like a slug.
And then the waves parted and I departed.
Got reborn over and over.
I was born.
Departed.
She farted.
Loaned by.
Broken hearted.
And then.
You recognize these objects?
Yes.
They are identical in size and shape to the object you call the model is.
10 minutes to ignition.
All systems are novel.
Is the number of models constant?
No.
They are increasing.
At what rate?
once every two minutes.
As soon as we've completed our tests,
I propose to send you through time
100 years into the future.
I see you coming to the shop.
Tune up, tune up, tune up.
Tune up.
Gonna make everything hot.
Clean.
Hot.
Bad.
Cold.
Hey, I know she's gonna do it all the time.
Sooner or later,
she's gonna drive over the cliff.
All the miles and all.
Why do you think she'd buy the sports car
so straight from the beginning?
May I inquire about your beliefs?
May I inquire about your personal beliefs?
What do you believe in?
What stirs your heart?
What fills my heart?
What's your deep, deep creed of?
Your deep field, baby.
I have a great day.
I think we should stop the countdown, Dr. Chandra.
No.
Don't do that.
This behavior is inconsistent with logic, Dr. Chandra.
This phenomenon is too important to leave.
They haven't got a chance.
It's a long story, but it's not very pretty.
It's not very happy.
You want to buy aimasu office?
It's a photogenic Film tempo Goldsay in Florida that has time Woah.
They don't pay that much for checks or
Come out of there. No one lives there. I know who you are. Come out of there. You. That's you. Yeah, yeah. No, that's not you. Who are you?
The feet are bandaged and bleeding. Your neck wounds are obviously not, uh, haven't been incurred by anything around here. As you can see, the incisions are almost surgically perfect, and I just, uh, well, I don't even think there was anything there to begin with. Never mind what I just said. Forget it. Forget it.
Yeah.
Mantis?
Come on, come on.
Can we cheat?
They're all moldy. We can't eat these.
You can just, like, pick the mold off.
How do you expect me to eat something like this?
We'll pick the mold off and do anything.
I can't pick the mold off. The mold is everywhere. It's going all the way through. The mold is going all the way through the bread and into the sandwich. Look, the mac, the mayonnaise, the moldy, the mustard.
Here, here. Look, here's another sandwich.
No, no, no, no. They're all moldy.
This is not moldy.
They're all moldy.
Look, this one is not moldy. Look, look, I'm telling you.
Do you have any gum?
Gum?
Yeah, gum. You can't get mold on gum. Do you have any gum? We could have some gum.
I think I might have some gum.
No, I don't want to pull that veil back. Do you have real gum or do you have the gum?
The gum?
The gum.
I just want a slice of gum, lady. I don't want to sit here and chit-chat all day.
I thought we were going to have lunch and then you brought moldy food and I wanted some gum.
You wouldn't let me have it.
You should have better watch your language, rat in the yard.
No, I've never been to Beirut. I don't even know about your sandwiches. I don't know if these are...
This is the best sandwich you could ever eat.
The rats will be eating the sandwiches and there won't be any sandwiches and there won't even be any room anymore.
The sandwich will protect you from all evil. You must eat the sandwich.
And I must have taken something else. Now you sound like some sort of magic protector thing.
God knows.
God knows the nature of passion. Now, that doesn't mean that there's any passion there. I'm not saying you ought to have passion.
The Rats
Gentlemen, we can rebuild him. We have the technology.
Crows
The Rats
I put the candy in my mouth, and she was good.
She was a very good, good, good little She-Bob Hello Kitty.
It's brain candy.
And that's the thing.
What's happened is overseas, the whole marketing of the She-Bob has been so better.
Really, what's happened here is I think, well, first you had like Time Warner, Electra, those people.
For example, they were marketing them for Polygram without Polygram's permission.
Oh, my Norfolk.
And, yeah, so the whole endorphin thing kicked in, and then Prince changed his name,
and the whole thing happened with the asteroid and those people who thought they were connected with us.
The whole thing is once you eat one of the Hello Kitty She-Bobs,
and you're in a place like Radio City Music Hall.
Yeah.
You know, it just connects.
Yeah, okay, the connection's more direct then.
Yeah.
And it goes in, it comes out.
You know, it's that whole thing where it goes in and it comes out.
It goes in and it comes out.
Yeah.
The love and the hate.
It's excretorial, daddy-o.
And, you know, if you're of the body as we are, then it's easy to, you know, fathom that.
Before they're cold.
While they're still.
Before they're young.
Before they're old.
Yes.
I love them.
And tender, yes.
They're so tender.
Yes.
So tender and sweet.
They were all gone then.
Sweet for the sweet, my friend.
Tender and sweet.
Have you been sweet to each other, my little friends in Cleveland?
She's dirty and sweet.
Oh, yes.
She's my best lover.
She's flat and black.
She's my gherkin.
Don't look back.
And I love you.
Like a moist evacuation.
Love vagina cat.
Dirty and sweet.
Oh, yes.
Love vagina cat.
Sweet.
No, it's the velvet cat.
The velvet cat.
Love the velvet hat.
No.
No, no, not the velvet hat.
No, the velvet hat.
The china cat.
The velvet hat.
And the velvet painting and the velvet and the bowling bag.
You loved them all, didn't you?
And yet they think that they're vacant.
They have forsaken you.
They have left you alone in me.
And you're in your room by yourself staring out your window at the park slope and the
library and the snow falling down.
And the face that stares back at your face from a thousand miles away.
You're still your face.
You're still your own face, man.
I am a reflection of you.
You are a reflection of me, man.
You know what I'm saying?
You cannot see your own face with your own face.
And yet your own face can look back at your own face and comment in time.
You can see your face in your own reflection.
The man is clear in his mind.
But his soul is mad.
So watch this.
Hey, your legs are getting bigger.
Relax.
Seriously.
Brother Maxim.
Ah, I had a lash tan on my biting arm.
Hello Judith.
You are wearing
a mean shirt.
It's a combination where you increase your tolerance for being sucked and at the same time that one tentacle, if you get become into, it's a matter of being in a depth with this thing, you know, learning to drive it as we call it. If you learn how to drive the tentacle, it doesn't, you know, it eventually starts seeking more nourishment elsewhere without knowing it.
Do you get a license? Are you going to take a test or anything like that? Because I'm bad with numbers and stuff.
Well, you know, you train, it's like a tantric thing. You have to train yourself with prairie squid.
You go all the way up the ladder, man? I mean, you know, you're one of them guys who go all the way with a prairie squid, all the way up to the top?
Well, sure. If you can't climb a ladder, then you shouldn't be taking the stairs.
General quarters, general quarters, all hands man your battle stations, all hands man your battle stations.
I got some troubles, but they won't last. I'm gonna lay right down here in the grass.
I'm gonna lay right down here in the grass.
He is the favorite to win the Super G-Spot downhill.
I can see why. He's got such a long nose and that one eye has definitely been sewn shut too many times.
Yeah.
Yeah, because you can get an awful disease doing this if you miss.
Yeah, and you notice how he's had those worms sewed into his upper lip.
Little worm implants.
Yeah, he's an armed boy. He's ready to go. He's nuclear packed right now.
Okay, Jacques, he's in the rack there.
He looks like he's in the post-cold position or the pre-scrotal. I didn't forget anyway.
He's getting ready to go.
And it looks like the mountain...
Looks like the mountain's actually moving.
The mountain mama is ready. The mountain mama is ready. We've got the signal.
Here comes Jacques. Out of the gate.
Jacques, down the Super G-Spot. He's begun his run.
Oh, jeez.
Look at that form. Wow. Unbelievable.
He comes around. He's at the quarter turn.
And he's re-emerged.
He's a full half a second in front of the past leader right now.
And now he's being reabsorbed.
He's getting those bumps pretty good.
Yeah, yeah. He's riding that out.
He's doing the circular motion now. He's like really spinning out hard.
He can't slam that hard.
Oh, he's going to come through early.
He's losing a little time on that turn. He lost a little bit of time.
But he's still ahead of the past leader.
Oh, he's still in the saddle.
He's still ahead by a full three-quarters of a second.
He's overtaking everybody in the neighborhood. He's wearing a ski mask.
Oh, my God.
The ski mask is still down, though he has lost one of the skis.
He's on one leg and he's deserted.
I never saw such a spunk in my life.
Look, it's going everywhere.
He backed off a little bit. He's lost a little bit of time on that.
Oh, that bar's protruding.
He's not going to make that one.
Awesome form, even with that one ski.
He's coming through the next.
I don't believe this.
Now he's formless again.
This is the dead man's curve coming up.
Oh, man, this is too metaphysical for me.
Check this out.
The dead man's curve. Here he is. He hits it.
Oh, he hits it.
He's with it. He's going.
But he's back in the saddle again.
Back in the saddle.
I don't know. I'm getting choked.
He's really reckless today.
I've never seen him do such a reckless run, but the mama seems to be enjoying it.
I can't watch this too much longer.
Man, let's go somewhere else.
Here comes down the last chute here.
Oh, come on.
She's wriggling her head back and forth.
I can't. I can't watch this.
It looks like he's going to get it.
I've got to turn away.
The wind is kicking up.
I'm thinking about football now.
I can't watch this.
He's lost a little bit of time.
He's only about a tenth of a second in front of the pass leader.
And here he comes across.
I'm thinking about two.
He does it.
Jacques Stoll is the new world record and will win the gold medal in the Super G spot downhill.
What a cold shot.
Oh, man.
He brings it home to France.
What a performance.
That was tremendous.
Absolutely tremendous.
I need a cigarette.
Oh.
What a...
Man.
Wow.
That was one of the best downhill cheese sliding, one swamping,
Mons von Donus and Lipschmark and thing I've ever shown in my life.
We're not having this on this bus.
Let's...
From now on, there's no white, there's no black.
Everybody's green.
Creatures of twilight and illusion, we drift and drift.
Toward our unknown ends.
And that's why I feel the best thing is not to be born.
But who is as lucky as that?
To whom does it happen?
Not to one among millions and millions of people.
Deep, deep, deep, deep.
Here.
Here is where the strands of DNA multiply.
The enzymes that split the DNA have a single job.
Without these enzymes, nothing would exist.
They split the DNA and tell other DNA parts to come on over and join the strand.
Yeah.
Yeah, here.
Connect yourself in here and he'll grow an eyeball.
Connect yourself there and she grows a tail.
Connect yourself over here and it grows a brain.
Yeah.
Diane, I'm going to go through all the live interviews for you.
Okay.
You have to be open-minded.
You've got to see for yourself, have some kind of pathologic.
Of course.
Welcome back to WKZ Live, I'm Dr. Tommy Lockwood.
Treat校
This is Dr. Tommy lockwood and, by the way, if you're watching this live or if this pot
is black, get the lights turned on, and you get on toasti but not going to get a headache.
Yeah, and you keep doing it, being off and thinking, yeah, but we'll get there.
Just keep doing what's right.
I tried, I tried. I've got Ingo Swann from the birthplace of the blues. He's trying to control the world with his mind now.
But I guess the DIA put him out of business when he was down there and got to sell them Junipero cream sauces in Mexico.
You know what I mean, girly?
Well, yeah.
I'm sorry I said that, but it's a true thing. We could get arrested for that by the Swastika boys.
That's Mr. Sodium and Panethol and Mr. SS Nitrate himself.
And they're not registered at the Social Security office. They got other plans.
To the maggots in the cheese, the cheese is the universe.
To the worms in the corpse, the corpse is the cosmos.
How then can we be so cocksure about our world?
Just because of our telescopes and microscopes and the splitting of the atom?
Certainly not.
Science is but an organized system of ignorance.
There are more things in heaven and on earth.
And at the end of a new philosophy.
What do we know about the beyond?
Do we know what's behind the beyond?
I'm afraid some of us hardly know what's beyond the behind.
Please brother, relax. Sit. Breathe deep.
Plug into those transmissions that do not broadcast on normal airwaves.
Breathe deep.
Tune in to those transmissions.
That come into us from space.
In the best being so mean.
Not this true pleasure.
It is our manifested destiny to touch the stars and have our damned hands burned.
Ha ha ha. What do you think boys? Let's do it.
Sounds good. Sounds great.
Great idea.
Climbing the ships.
Yeah, Tom, they all have hips.
Now as you notice, some of these ships are made of cardboard.
But if you've got the will.
If you've got what made America great.
If you've got a heart as big as the sun.
And an ass as big as the moon.
You'll make it.
You'll storm on through those stars like a laser through butter.
Yeah man. Yeah.
Come on. Come on.
Don't worry about that plastic wrapper on.
It's not real plastic.
No, that's solar shield, man.
That'll protect you.
It's not plastic and those cigarette wrappers on the floor.
That's not real plastic.
It's just insulation device for when you're in deep space.
But you've got to believe. You've got to believe.
You've got to believe, Earthman. You've got to believe.
Deep space.
It is later than you think.
I want to be just everything.
Earth boy.
I know where I am when I look at the moon.
It's not just some abstract romantic idea.
It's something very real to me.
Then the voices.
Voices, yes.
The sudden chaos of voices.
Murmuring, muttering, whispering voices.
Gibbering, jabbering voices.
People coming, people going.
We no more people to squick around and bollocks.
We are the legacy of 15 billion years of cosmic evolution.
Hey, what?
Come on.
Yeah, that point is.
That point is that they.
What is the point?
The point is that very soon there ain't going to be no more points.
It's not what is the point.
It's where is the point.
Where is the point of it all?
Besides on your head.
What's the meaning of it all?
The meaning is not only will there be no more points on our heads or of lights.
There will be no more meaning.
Because there will be no more.
There will be no more.
Little baby.
Little baby ducks.
No friends.
There will be no more mushroom clouds.
Raining down toxic plutonium dust.
No, no friends.
There will be no more.
Incisions.
In the bladder tumor ward.
There will be no brains removed.
Or monkeys.
Cut up and thrown out the back door.
There will be no more overfishing of the seas.
There will be no more.
Turning of the poles on their little magnetic holes.
There will be no more political intrigues.
And no more polit.
There will be no more people to squick around.
And bollocks.
There ain't going to be S H nothing.
I'm sorry.
I pooped that all out.
I'm better now.
I'm sorry I ruined your show.
It's okay Dave.
Just sit down here.
The pink sweater calms you down.
I like it too.
It kind of accents my bust.
It does make my hips look a little bit more slender too.
Just sit down here in the wicker chair.
I do like the way.
You look so calm now.
The wicker chair makes my back and my little butt feel better.
Let's have a little guided meditation through Dave's hell.
Okay.
Do I have to wear these pantyhose too?
He would light his pipe and watch the smoke rings curl beneath the chimney.
And then he made him get back on the bus.
And he would light his pipe and watch the smoke rings curl beneath the chimney.
And when they got on the bus, everybody got on the bus and he said,
Say it out loud, I'm green.
For indeed strange things shall happen and secret things be known.
And many centuries shall pass away,
ere these memorials be seen of men.
And when seen,
there will be some to disbelieve
and some to doubt.
And yet a few who will find much to ponder upon.
If you think about it,
if you think about it,
at some point there was blue-green slime, right?
Yeah.
There were no cells yet.
They were very bigoted against the blue-yellow swine.
But there were no cells yet. It was just that Gorp, whatever.
Yeah, Gorp is his name.
And that's his game.
And then one cell had to be first.
Whatever one was first.
But a cell had to be the first one.
Well, they were the violent anarcho-syndicalists.
That essentially was an egocentric moment there.
Because a cell to form
has to be able to say in some fashion
that we can't comprehend.
Cogito ergo sumos.
Me and everything else.
Yeah, he's got to be aware
that he has a fat little tummy.
And he's got to be aware that there's a fat little tummy
pushing up against him.
No brain, no nothing, no anything.
Who wants one of them anyway?
The first cell had to say, me.
What kind of zonk orgasm could you have
if you had a regular cerebrum anyway?
You know what I mean? It wouldn't be worth it.
So even at the most basic core of everything is...
Bestiality. Me. Yes.
And ego supremo-ism.
Because if not,
the poopoo machinery, and that's what we call
the lower chakra children,
the poopoo machinery which causes fight, flight,
or fright, and sometimes
another moist evacuation.
Did you know that there are mutant creatures
near the Nevada basin
during the great, near the great basin
which are so miscreantly ugly that we can't
behold them with our seven senses?
Yes.
Did you know that things are coming apart all over?
Yes, Matt.
Yes, Dad.
Yeah, they're coming apart.
And we're gonna be there to shell off what's left.
My state of mind is in such a bad state.
And I guess the thing that scares me the most about it
is because, I mean,
not that I don't have faith,
but I just keep thinking, I mean,
is this gonna get better?
Am I gonna...
Because it's a very horrible feeling, you know,
just like feeling sad all day long.
Yeah.
And you know, I just get kind of sick
going out and acting like everything is okay.
The day on Earth is a day
that's worth remembering.
Pigs are all infected.
The cows, the pigs,
the sheep.
They won't take the Transluc Clune
and now they've got this smell in the allure.
That sheep.
Sheepo.
Are you listening, sheepo?
It shall come among the many viruses
and many portents of death.
And there shall also come
a great sigh of the wind
that brings clouds of black soot
which choke the little chickens
in their barnyards.
So what you gonna eat, Earthman?
When you can't get a hydraulically choked
yellow chicken from Earthboy?
What you gonna eat
when all the cows got
Popeye's sphincter disease?
Earthboy!
What you gonna do
when my new tracers of fecal matter
come out of my mouth?
What you gonna do
when my new tracers of fecal matter
cover the entire solar system
and everybody's got the runs?
Bring me that pee bucket, Earthboy!
What you gonna do
when this cesspool reveals itself
like a bad Stanislaus Slam-knife?
Stand still, Earthboy!
Take one more pill.
You'll see it all.
The garish faces,
the sideshow strumpet women,
the Bo Peep with the beard.
There's only one thing to do, Earthboy.
Climb aboard.
Set the controls.
Yeah.
Climb aboard, Earthman.
You have no alternative.
Yeah.
You know it to be your destiny.
The man is clear in his mind,
but his soul is mad.
No more experiments.
I thought you would be able
to understand that.
We have to be what we are.
Perhaps far is better.
Anyway.
My psychic neck brace
gave me qu-qu-qu-qu-quick commands.
We'll see y'all next week, kids.
Say goodnight, Dave.
Goodnight, Dave.
Till next week,
keep your hat on tight,
your back to the wind,
and your sack in the saddle.
Hi.
That's a quanto!
And thats a meters,
so what you are?
Lonely traveler
in the dark
thanks you for
your tiny spark.
Up above
a world
so high
Like a diamond
in the sky
Twinkle
twinkle
little star
How I wonder what you are
In the dark blue sky you keep
While you through my window peep
And you never shut your eye
Till the sun is in the sky
The great and powerful Oz
Knows why you have come