No, no, no. How does that start? I can't remember.
I, uh, yes, friends. No, I, yes, dear friends.
You're listening, no, uh, radio ministry.
It's the subgenius radio ministry hour of slack.
Brought to you by the Church of the Subgenius.
Produced here at the beautiful studios of WCSB, Cleveland, the home.
I love that show. It's so iconoclastic.
And, you know, everything is worthy of poking at and making fun.
And sometimes throwing dirt on the shoes and pulling a knife at it.
Yeah, they're just a mirror that reflects the illness in society.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
We may go on. We're going to go on for a long time tonight.
We're going to take over the station.
We might have to share boats all night.
We're going to, uh, disregard any, uh, any attempts to take over the station by...
Stand back. They are killing me.
The next... Oh, no, we won't go. I won't go there.
We're really, we are going to give it over to the next DJ if you're listening.
We were just teasing.
Yeah.
We're just kidding.
That's us. We've got our little cot set up here.
We've got a...
We're going to have a...
Hot chockeys here.
Getting ready for our slumber party.
And Philo and me each have a little candle here.
I didn't tell you to give them my hand.
And you got your little nightcap?
Yeah, I do.
Chestnuts are roasting.
Sexy guy show.
The sugar plums are dancing.
Yeah, this is the guy show because this is the last show of the millennium and we're covering the history of the subgenius church, which is basically a guy church.
We would have a girl on the show, but she didn't show up.
That's the next show.
Next to the last show.
This is the last show.
We paid her.
When was the first...
We paid her and she still didn't show up.
I told you you should have given her that money in advance.
That was back in Jane Eyre's childhood because he had the little...
The little...
I said half now and half when you show up.
He had the original little head and he would watch that thing as a child and make little songs and say little things and do little stuff.
Oh, you should always do the other half.
Always do the other half.
I have to do the other half now?
Amen.
I did not.
Okay.
I honor you, Stangford.
Give me the money.
You know that...
Hey, Reverend Stangford, you remember back there in Fort Worth and that boy named Patches?
Patches.
He was a poor boy, but he was a great tap dancer.
All his britches were made out of patches.
You know, they wouldn't let him into the church, the regular church.
They said, get out of here with them Patches britches on.
Patches.
You're a patch bitch, boy.
But the bitches in the subgenius church...
That's what they said.
They liked the way he dangled in them patches.
Patches, get out of here with them Patches britches or I'm going to make you my prison bitch.
And so Patches...
They said that at church, too.
Oh, they did?
And so Philo scratched Patches' itches.
In churches.
And quit his bitching.
He did a batch of bitching that one night, though.
It is a new...
Not only a new year...
Some batching scratching.
Millennium.
It is a whole new millennium coming forth.
Wow.
As we, together...
Look at that, a new millennium.
The subgenii of the Bay Area and the Midwest,
Mestern Western,
come together in our...
You understand the Mestern Western show?
...ascendancy as we go forward into what is now
the only millennium...
...that truly exists.
So are the subgeniuses going to be at Burning Man next year?
We're at Burning Man every year.
Every single...
We were at Burning Man before it was Burning Man.
That's true.
In fact, you know, it's a little known fact that...
...Warm Boy.
...that the subgenius church is part of why Burning Man exists.
It really is.
And it's just why I partly believe that Warm Boy should be there.
Did it start with Janer talking about that Burning Monk?
I'm sorry, yes.
No, that was... It did start with...
Actually, 1988 or so.
That was when Trelloid still walked among us.
Wow.
It was still throwing matches up at Kathleen.
Yeah, yeah.
We're going over the subgenius history here on KPFA.
Let's rewind now back to 1982.
We're taking 1982 into 2001.
Doug Wellman used the sound effect on the air
to represent a tape rewinding.
But when was the baby...
But since 1980, you'd been getting tapes of me doing...
And then, of course, we took the...
...and made it into...
...the West Coast...
...which then degenerated into...
...and what about...
...where did mama fit into it?
That was my mama.
I thought that was Sterno.
That was Sterno going...
That was your mama.
...and Mickey.
I would have guessed it was I who was...
...honored Sterno.
...and Mickey.
Oh, I see.
As long as you honor somebody, you can then claim it as yours.
Sure, yeah, yeah.
I always do.
I honor you, Stang, for...
Give me the money.
You're listening to the subgenius radio ministry,
Hour of Slack.
Now I really do have to flip it.
Oh, please don't look in the mirror.
You're not going to like what you see there.
What is that?
It's a priest bob.
Priest bob?
Oh, yes, dear friends.
This is Li Jing, the Chinese subgenius,
and you are listening to the Hour of Slack.
Oh, yes, it is so true.
Thank you, Li Jing.
I got a call from China just this morning,
the high priestess of all Asia.
You know, friends, if you had joined up,
if you'd been the first person on your continent to join up with the church,
you'd be the pope of this continent.
I know.
Dr. G. Gordon Gordon here.
I am the pope of South America.
The entire continent of South America.
It's mine.
When those souls...
Ah, the harvest, friends.
When we start collecting those souls,
you know who's going to get to skim,
to skim that fine, fine layer off the top out of the soul-rendering vat,
don't you, friends?
Oh, and they're trying to keep them from selling any kind of soul down there nowadays.
Oh, yeah.
They don't.
Used to be in the old days, you couldn't give it away,
and now it's against the law to sell it, so what are you going to do?
And all the religions want to have your soul, friends.
Bob wants your soul, but just temporarily.
He'll give it back after he's...
And he only uses it a little bit while he's got it, friends.
That's something to think about.
He doesn't dry you out.
That's right.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Appreciate it.
Just like...
it'd be
and normally it's just I trying to Ram LETS,
if, if, you are,
and walking out
One day a shiny
silver psychedelic
spaceship
took a long trip
from the outskirts of heaven
to the 7-Eleven
They had a funeral
going in the parking lot
for the second going of Jesus
And if he ever
comes around again
I'll be the first
to stick the spike in
Let's go, let's go now
Let's go now
Last Christmas
Christmas, or just before New Year's with Dr. Philodrum and guesting on Puzzling Evidences.
Oh, and of course, Einstein's Secret Orchestra Swamp Radio hosted by Dr. Chaz Smith and starring
Lonesome Cowboy Dave broadcast from WCSB in Cleveland and also with yours truly as a guest.
Yes, and friends, at least it ain't reruns of Hour of Slack. I've had to trip through four hours
of Slack in the last couple of days because to get things done ahead of time because of our
upcoming subgenius church field trip to Amsterdam. And the main reason we go to Amsterdam in a group
is so that we can come back and irritate our friends by regaling them with tales of our
ripping and...
Tripping times.
I get tired of people telling me that they're tripping all the time when it's so obvious.
Their faces have changed, like blue and red things are coming out, you know, wearing green.
Yeah, and one eye is dribbling down the side of their face.
And they've got this kind of ripping.
I can't stop ripping.
My clothing is all...
And they're giggling. It's cute.
You can tell they're high on something.
You know, the wall behind them is kind of like melting.
Yeah, and they...
All those blacklight posters around them are fountaining and...
Yeah, it's...
I find them very disturbing to the environment.
Try and get them in your car and have the windshield start melting and have the radio playing.
It looks like toothpaste is coming out of the radio.
Man, you want to throw them right out of your car and they still laugh as they roll down the freeway.
It seemed like everybody I looked at was tripping because they were all just melting.
And they're...
You know, they put on this music that tasted like ice cream.
The air was tripping.
Hey, man.
Um...
Why not crackers?
Is that what you called them?
I thought it was...
Okay.
Hey, man.
Am I still sweating?
Hey, hey, I heard...
No, you're in New York, man.
You're in Greenwich Village.
I heard that you had shrooms.
They wanted a pound of flesh.
They wanted that which makes you alive.
They wanted your soul.
That's what they do want.
They want a...
Peace.
Could you make some coffee for us, man?
We've been walking out in the rain.
It's cold, I think.
Yeah, yeah.
Sit down.
Sure.
How did you get up?
Um...
I don't know.
It was like...
I think it was yesterday, but...
This one kid died.
I think he died.
They found him in the woods.
Well, yeah.
That's where we found him first.
Down by the lake.
Oh, man.
Yeah, man.
He was, uh...
Checking out...
He almost got...
He almost got ran over by a pontoon boat.
He came to study consciousness.
But he ended up with his pants around his ankles down by the lake.
Freezing at dawn.
I had...
Wondering what had happened.
Marijuana, where?
Where?
My name is St. Andrew KSC of Chicago, Illinois.
And I'm here to tell all of you about the wonders and the truth that is behind J.R. Bob Dobbs.
Can I hear it, man, man, brothers and sisters?
That is right.
Let me tell you.
You're right off the bat.
I was here earlier today.
I saw three fine young women here who have not been ordained in the Church of the Subgenius
because they didn't have the money.
$30 for salvation.
The only $30.
You can't even get a good hand job in Chicago for $30.
Right in this church, if you pay your $30 from the body, you will have more sex, more
slack, more fuck, more booze, more anything that you want, anything that you could ever
dream about.
And it all comes with a money-back guarantee.
You can keep you five years out.
You're dead.
And in the pits of hell, with the flames of Satan blinking your ass, you will get a signed
$90 check from J.R. Bob Dobbs.
Can I hear another amen?
Amen!
You people are not stoked up enough for this shit.
You are not in the mood in order to be saved.
You need to get down on your stuff, get jiggy with it even if you have to.
Because you know, Will Smith is getting more pussy than you because you haven't saved $30
to Bob.
No!
Oh, sire, there is no more money.
We gotta get some money.
That's right.
We need Turkish harkaback, black and rotten, Philip Duncan Burton, Perkaluma Burton, Burton
Bushman.
I have friends.
I am Florida Beck, Florida Beck, Colorado Beck, Colorado Beck.
Ah, yes, dear friends.
St. Andrew at the Tampa Defival.
And now, friends, let's go back to Dr. Philo Drummond and puzzling evidence with some more
subgenius history to be followed by some new non-music by New Monet.
I'm gonna be at an old person's convention that day.
Because the show will have been retired.
I'll be at a place where there's a lot of old people.
Oh, work?
They'll be having fun.
So is there gonna be the 20th anniversary?
I'll be whacking them on the head with this big long board.
20th anniversary of what?
It's got floppy appendages hanging out.
This show started in June of 1982.
Was it that long ago?
Yeah, it's been way too long.
Rob Nelson.
June of 1982.
Yeah.
I'll remember that for sure.
Rob Nelson.
Because it was Ivan Stang and Lies and myself.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Get your sticking paws off me, you damn dirty ape.
Do you want to touch my monkey?
Monkey?
I don't make monkeys.
I just train them.
No more monkey business.
No.
Birds and the bees and the monkey babies.
Ah.
But what is...
What does this have to do with Bob Slack and the conspiracy, the great themes which has driven the church...
Well, I'll ask a question.
Should we be concerned with George Bush being in the White House a fundamentalist Christian?
Or is this all part of Bob's plan?
All I know is that...
What language did Jesus speak on the cross?
Uh...
Mayan.
Yeah.
It wasn't Aramaic.
It was Mayan.
Eli, Eli, lei, sabahana.
Yeah.
Well, you can just...
You can just ask him.
He's probably not awake right now, but...
Everybody knows it's classic Mayan.
It means,
Moo, sad-eyed and bearded.
Come down with your fierce temper.
Wow.
That's what it means.
Because he was actually asking for revenge on all those people.
He's been misquoted all this time, dude.
He's been misquoted because they thought he was speaking Aramaic.
Hey, dude, where's my car?
In Aramaic, it means something like, you know, father, father.
Why has thou forsaken me?
But in Mayan, it means, moo.
And in English, it means, come down and release your fierce temper.
Thank you, thank you.
In English, it means, please pass the gefilte fish.
Oh.
It's luminous blue.
What is the next great frontier, lonesome cowboy Dave?
The next great frontier is the frontier of the human mind.
Delineated and demarcated, sans frontiers,
by only its only limited imagination.
We've been there, done that.
Imagination.
And, okay, all right, then I'll just forget about it.
Can I get...
The mind has been completely mapped and explored.
The mind is still a vast frontier where very few have ever truly tried.
Your mind, maybe.
The mind is still a place filled with cavernous muscles and tiny little tissues,
which no one has ever tried.
No one can reach except for their own cerebellum.
The human or normal mind has been completely worked out by marketing companies
and conspiracy medical science.
For the last hundred years, they've had it down, down, down.
Don't you believe what the ancient Rishis have told us?
That by properly using our minds, we can even fly as if gossamer on wings of felt?
Is that what the ancient Rishis told you?
Not the Rishis, Monk.
It's the Rishis of ancient India.
You've got to lose your shit in order to fly.
It's what Sundiata said.
Anyone who finds himself that far off the ground without knowing why
loses their shit, and that's a truism and a falsehood.
Tish, tish, tish, boys.
Fish, fish, fish.
That's a lie.
And it's nice to hear your show return to a slower, more deliberate pacing.
Of course, that's the edited version.
Over here, we're doing the edited version of the last show.
Yes, yes.
But don't let it be forgot that air there was a spot for one brief shining moment
known as...
Brigadier.
Camelot.
Oh.
In short, there's simply not a more congenial spot than happy ever after.
Brigadier.
Here.
Eight.
And Camelot.
Okay, I got it.
I think that now that the bushes are back in, I think it's going to be like Camelot.
It is a lot like Camelot.
Oh, it's certainly dad bush.
I like the bushes.
Now, see, this is kind of like, this is really George Bush's second term.
Exactly.
Oh, no lie.
It's like...
It's like the...
We're rolling now, folks.
Line.
You know, it's like the emperor of...
Bush dynasty.
We'll be rolling our way into the 2000s.
I meant to bring my new mixotology tape.
That's a no, I know.
I didn't get the new mixotology of...
Actually, I have it on a CD in the car, but I'd have to go out there in the cold and rain.
We should get it so we can play the...
See, there is your car driving away because you said that.
Hey, come back in!
So, do you think that the news will be more entertaining now in the next four years?
No, I think so.
Because, at least for those of us on the left, or where we call ourselves the left,
you know, you've got to have a target.
I feel now like those right-wingers did when Clinton was president.
I always believed that a vote against your conscience is a vote against boredom.
I just wish Jesse Ventura had won.
Me too.
I really wanted to have a wrestling president.
That made me so happy when he was governor, and I thought that he should be president
because he's stronger than those other guys.
I think he should...
No kidding.
He kicked...
But, you know...
He's going to be in the XFL now.
He's got a new job in the XFL working for Vince McMahon.
Really?
Yeah.
When you lose it out there, you're in a world of hurt.
Oh, you're doing Dennis Miller now?
I feel like I'm screaming at him.
I got a job!
Gun or a job. Copyright 1983 by the band that dare not speak its name.
Palmer Reedy's on vocals. Thank you.
Good evening, my fellow Americans.
Hey, how you doing?
I appreciate you very much for the opportunity to speak with you tonight.
Oh, you know, it's our president, too.
And we are rolling, folks.
Getting ready for the second Bush dynasty.
Rolling, rolling. Keep them take dicks rolling.
Little something you show.
Oh, hi.
We'll be in the picture and then you'll see it on the way.
And then there'll be the outcome of the presidential.
I'm rolling, I'm rolling.
I'm rolling, I'm rolling, I'm rolling.
Why is that so funny? It's just some guy saying I'm rolling.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Rollin', rollin', I'm rollin'.
I'm rolling Democrats up in rugs and burning them.
Rolling a Democrat down the hill.
Yeah.
Someone got me running
I'm running out of time
Including the old one, if there were some subgeniuses on our news group
who were seriously trying to convince us that the Jews run America.
Well, you know, that may be so.
I grew up in the film business in Dallas
and I knew an awful lot of good old boys that kind of were running the shows
and they didn't seem to be in any terrible fear of Jewish, black, or Hispanic, or subgenius.
Conspiracies taking them over
because we're all too busy fighting amongst ourselves.
You know, all the little minority groups and weirdos are all too busy fighting themselves
while the man laughs and the burning man burns.
And my main man, Bob Dobbs,
while his stocks are rising from sheer unthinking slack power, friends.
And that's why we must, like Bob's stocks, rise above the little conspiracy.
That are dangled in front of frustrated crackpots
like easy answers to our blinder tubes, oh my droogies.
And, you know, the complex is not simple.
You can't, and Rush Limbaugh is always talking about, oh, I make the complex simple.
Well, great. That's great for simpletons.
But the complex is complex.
Some of us like it that way.
A does not equal B.
And A to the square root times X certainly does not equal B.
Friends, there is only one conspiracy.
And that is the conspiracy of the normals.
The one that doesn't even know it's a conspiracy.
But it only takes one such conspiracy to bring every one of our little individual conspiracies down.
That's the sad, sad part.
Especially when a subgenius falls for conspiracy.
And the conspiracy is a conspiracy bullshit.
Such as the idea that the Jews control America, so forth and so forth.
The big conspiracy always gives you a bunch of your own special little conspiracy enemy to hate.
They want to get you really hating one of those little conspiracies.
Because that way there's always one for you to join.
There's always one that's your friend.
That's also against that other little conspiracy.
And most of us on this last November 7th went out and voted for whichever conspiracy was the least of our enemies.
Or else we didn't vote at all.
Which meant you voted for whoever really won.
Well, we know who won.
Because like I say, they just shoot you in the back.
That's how they get there.
But, friends, I don't know.
It might be true that mere human Jews or commies or queers or Nazis or negroes or Mexicans.
Or Scientologists or good old boys or white supremacists or subgenius idiots run the entire world.
I don't know.
But I do know this.
They all know how to throw a damn good party.
But the party we will throw will make their parties look uncannily like, almost like little concentration camps.
A funny coincidence.
We talk a lot about coincidence.
Not many people like to admit that if alien science would seem like magic to us.
Then really, it would be magic.
Any good alien science would just seem like coincidence.
Notice any good coincidences lately?
Maybe that's just alien science.
Who is to judge, friends, but Bob?
And so let none be a bigot except for Bob.
Only Bob has the ability to judge a book by its cover and look a gift horse in the mouth and see.
And then get paid extra just to take that horse.
Friends, I myself have had to start being a bigot.
I have to be careful not to say mean and bigoted things about Christians and Republicans and commies.
And I was actually patting myself on the back one day thinking, wow, I'm so cool.
At least I'm not anti-Semitic for a, you know, Texas boy.
I forgive the Jews for inventing the thing that fucked them up and us.
I forgive them for inventing Christianity.
But I can never forgive our yeti ancestors for the foolishness of creating humans and then letting them out of their cages.
And now somebody said to me, Reverend Stang, did I hear you correctly?
You said that you shouldn't be mean and bigoted to Republicans, Christians, and communists?
Are you feeling okay, Reverend Stang?
Friends, what I meant was it is wrong to be mean and bigoted only.
For that is what we must say for the icing on the cake.
In our hating, we must use accuracy, clarity, and objective reasoning.
Because that blanket hating of abstract concepts is exactly the main conspiracy construct.
We must hate individual Christians and Republicans and Democrats.
Individual Christians.
You know, people.
Because the group, the them that you start hating, that's just a conspiracy-defined sub-conspiracy.
I don't mean sub-conspiracy.
It's there to lull and lure certain especially frustrated subgeniuses into thinking that there's a simple answer to everything.
And this us versus them crap is in fact the very sort of mass fuzzy thinking that the conspiracy invented.
Not Bob.
There's no us and there's no them.
There's just you, me, and everybody else.
But then you go, but what if the alternative conspiracies, can't I believe in any of those?
Can't, you know, aren't some of them at least cool?
The, you know, the jokers, the deformed people, the outcasts, the trans-ensexuals, you know, the mutants, the retards, and the hideous supergeniuses in wheelchairs.
You know, what if, what if...
What if them?
What if the bonobos, onobos, and monobos?
What if these once beloved minorities?
Must we distrust and hate them too and slay them instead of worshipping them as we subgenii always used to worship those weirdos and geeks?
In other words, can't we just kill without hating?
You know, it's enough.
That we're slowly, that on X-Day we're going to slowly dismember entire cities full of ignorant, disbelieving normals.
Do we have to drag hate into it?
Do we have to dirty up our clean killing with hate?
Friends, I don't, I don't feel that that's necessary.
I don't feel we need to lower ourselves to that kind of behavior.
Hating while killing.
We'll kill them!
Let's have the internet shut down.
I want them off the internet tomorrow.
If the Scientologists can do it, we can do it.
Stop the bandwidth.
I'm calling, I'm calling Ma Bell tomorrow.
And he can do it too. He knows the bells.
I know Mrs. Bell. I'm going to give her a call and I'm going to ream her out.
And the crowd goes crazy.
Not much of a crowd.
Well, it's early in the morning.
It's early out here.
We have a Last of Genius show.
Yeah.
There's probably a lot of people out there.
There's probably 20, 30 people there.
How many people came to the Last of Genius show?
And how many people will come to the one on Flash's property?
Are we going to be able to do that on Flash's property?
It's the scariest thing in the world.
Why would we do anything on Flash's property if he doesn't have a hot tub?
Oh yeah, you're right.
Because he's got two big legs.
Well, legs, great.
To throw Ivan Stang into, get it?
Yeah, it's like shooting Bob.
I know, exactly.
They did produce some amazing photographs though, just like shooting Bob.
Yeah, just like shooting Bob.
Done there, been that.
Yeah.
Hey, if either one of you guys ended up at X Day, you know, you'd be the next ones in line to get roasted.
I'll be there.
I can't wait to get roasted.
Bob would love to get his revenge on puzzling evidence.
I know that for a fact.
Bob just wants to pay me back the money he owes me.
Yeah, oh, Byron has that money, Philo.
A guy gave it to Byron.
Along with your prop.
What's the matter, haven't you ever seen a man with throat cancer before?
I understand Byron still has your prop, is that right?
Thank you, yeah, thank you.
No, you have Byron's prop and you need to give that back to him.
I couldn't remember who had it, but I knew one of us had it.
You have it and you need to give it back to him.
I don't have it anymore, I'm sorry.
You may have left it at some girl's house, but...
Something happened to it.
It was in my possession for a long time, but little by little it's just kind of flickered away somehow.
I don't know how it disappeared on its own like that.
It started out about a pound and then little by little over the years...
It was a pound of really good prop.
It dwindled down to nothing on its own.
It's sort of like it just, like the will of the wisp or like the...
It was so beautiful.
The, um, the...
It was Haber prop Zip-U-Lot.
The legendary manna from heaven.
It sort of just dwindled away in the sunlight over the years.
The very manner of it, nanners of heaven.
And this was the gift of the subgeniuses.
If you go out in the street right now, you'll see the streets covered with Haber prop Zip-U-Lot.
They were talking about banana.
Brought to you by the subgenius church.
I got a banana from heaven.
I remember that.
I remember when I was eight years old, I saw Bob on Night Flight.
It changed my life.
And you let me down, man.
You let me down.
Come on, caller.
Be brave.
Poor Bob.
Light your own flame.
He's gotten the brunt of all of our jokes.
Brody Culpepper just came back on Christmas Day from Laos and he said the entire population near Dobstown, Malaysia, walks around with little bob pipes.
Everybody.
Well, they were doing that back in the 60s.
Yeah, but no people were going there to look at it, so it wasn't really happening.
Uh-oh.
Yeah.
I'll see you again, old scratch.
What are those funny things sticking out of your head?
Those are our antennae.
Are you a television set?
What in the ding-dong-heck-a-ma-doodle-hell is that?
Let's see if you bleed chlorophyll.
Plants are the most cunning and savage of all life forms.
I was following up on a lead to what some might consider just another New York City massacre.
A pretty woman thrown out of a high-rise window.
Her Japanese husband disemboweled.
And their two kids turned into shredded wheat.
Do you know what it's like to be violated by a 300-pound Filipino skinhead named Gunther?
It ain't no picnic!
Stop living in dreams.
No woman can travel the world without a man to defend her.
Please allow me to introduce myself.
I'm a woman of wealth and taste.
I've been around for long, long years, seen many men gone to waste.
I was round when Jesus Christ had his moments of doubt and pain.
Made damn sure the pilot washed his hands.
And sealed his fate.
Pleased to meet you.
Hope you guessed my name.
That thing that's troubling you?
It's the nature of my game.
I hung around St. Petersburg.
Till I saw it was time for a change.
I killed the Tsar.
And the ministers.
Anastasia screamed in vain.
I joined the ranks in the General's tent.
As the blitzkrieg raged and the bodies stank.
And I shouted,
Who killed the Kennedys?
Well, after all,
It was you and me.
Pleased to meet you.
Hope you guessed my name.
That thing that's troubling you?
It's the nature of my game.
Now, just as every cop is a criminal.
And every sinner a saint.
Heads or tails just call me Lucifer.
Cause I need some respect.
If you need me, have some courtesy.
Have some sympathy and some taste.
Accept your well-earned apologies.
Or I'll lay your soul to waste.
Hope you guessed my name.
Ooh.
Fuck your life, Sht.
I'll lay my soul to waste.
Hope you guessed my name.
People won't tell.
And the horrors of losing their past.
Not only because of this me-
a thought or several.
Consider these alternate titles.
Earth Needs Women.
Angry Blue Planet.
Robinson Crusoe on Earth.
Mission to Earth.
Abbott and Costello Go to Earth.
Earth Attacks.
The Earth Chronicles.
Or even Reproduction Cycle Among Lower Lifeforms Under the Rocks of Earth.
Now think of these alternate titles.
The Day Mars Stood Still.
20 Million Miles to Mars.
Mars Versus the Flying Saucers.
Now, why do those somehow ring true?
Maybe some of you, they didn't ring true.
You said, what?
What the hell is he talking about?
Well, friends.
Some of us, and I think, I think you,
some of us have felt for a long time that we're on the wrong planet.
As Susie the Floozy put it, right hemisphere, wrong planet.
Well, you know, we always assumed,
well, that's because we're subgenius descendants of the Yeti.
We don't have pure blood human genes, you know.
Of course we feel a little left out.
But, you know, we've begun to suspect because of certain,
clues Bob left mostly in cheesy B-grade science fiction movies.
That, now, this sounds, again, this sounds ridiculous.
Ludicrous to the polished ears of the modernist, perhaps.
But, you know, it's theoretically possible to bump a planet out of its orbit.
Totally out of its orbit, put it into a new orbit.
It might even be possible to switch the orbit of one planet with another one
that was a similar size.
Could it be that the reason some of us do not feel at home
is because we were native to the planet now called by us Mars,
but which was originally the one true Earth,
and in which, in fact, we, the Martians, are in fact the only true Earth people,
and the conspiracy of the normals,
in fact, the ones who, oddly enough, seem to be trying to turn this planet into a,
a, a place with a poisonous,
poisonous atmosphere,
a dry desert covered with just rock and concrete.
Maybe somebody's pulled a trick on us somewhere.
Well, of course, now, at this point you're thinking,
yes, that all makes perfect sense.
Earth was switched with Mars.
The true Martians are us,
and no wonder we feel out of place.
And the true, the false Martians are trying to turn this planet into a false Mars
with, you know, carbon dioxide atmosphere,
and so forth.
Now, of course, and you all agree with that, right?
That makes sense.
Here's the tricky part.
It happened in 1953, and no one noticed.
I'm going to leave you, I'm going to charge you with thinking about that.
How did they switch planets in 1953 without any of us ever noticing?
Could we be that totally out of it?
Could perhaps the reason that X day
hasn't happened yet be that 1998 hasn't happened yet,
and that they kept it 1943 for 10 years or something like that,
and no one even knew the difference.
Everybody cuff now.
It's time to be carnivorous with your friends and family.
Everybody cuff down and pull out a paring knife,
because we're going to remove the sockets around Grandma and Grandpa's eyes.
They made a delectable treat for afternoons, summer pickled,
sitting by the old patio, or maybe talking to the fire.
It's time to go back.
You must keep talking to the fire.
It is time to return.
Shut up, Pink Bob.
You can feel it for miles and miles.
Earth back to Mars.
And now the aroma is in the air.
You can sniff the aroma.
You can feel it.
Seize all.
All atomic pesticides.
It is talking to you.
The womb is talking to you now.
Get me out of here.
It is later than you think.
As we descend upon the minds of the members of the Cabinet,
the United States government, and the Senate, the Congress,
and the other representatives,
the representatives of the Congress,
the governments of the world,
we shall find in each one of them the chip is completely unaltered.
The plan is now in stage go.
The green light is lit and everyone is smoking.
The lamp is at your feet, old Buddha.
Please, please, put that back on.
I can't stand the sight of it.
It's...
The Exhibitionist Buddha.
Little mentioned in ancient texts.
Slathering Siddhartha, he was called,
for his bow-legged appurtenance,
and the strange way he made the women in Gopis cry
as they ran from the villages in fright.
For this is a matter of life or death.
Who is he?
Your lives.
The lives of everyone on Earth.
At one o'clock on July 24th,
Zyra, a new planet, will pass so close to the Earth,
it will cause vast destruction.
The Z-ists.
Never before in the history of the world
has humanity felt so close to God.
As Zyra inexorably rushes toward us,
perhaps to destroy the Earth,
men and women of all races and streams
pause to think, to pray, and to atone.
As the evacuation of coastal cities progressed,
tales of individual acts of heroism and sacrifice
poured into newspaper offices.
So that's what's happening.
How can we get out of here on a broken planet?
The planet Zyra is heading towards Earth.
We must not tell the people
As inexplicably as life itself,
the planet Zyra hurtles closer and closer to Stang's head.
You know, Stang's head equipped with a special antenna.
Nineteen-year-olds today are so stupid,
you could probably play that on the radio and they'd believe it.
No, no, they would not believe that the planet Zyra is actually approaching.
That's exactly why they let us play it on the radio.
Just think if you were one of the skanks-wanks who had enough dough.
Only those teenagers would believe it.
Only the sub- and the subgeniuses would believe in anything.
Praise Bob.
And, uh, friends, you're listening to the subgenius radio ministry Hour of Slack.
As, uh, recently, a combination and a collision of shows from KPSA,
WCFN, Berkeley, WCSB, here in Cleveland,
and, uh, elsewhere around the divivals around the world,
and the artists of alt-binary slack.
And, friends, if you want to know more about the word Bob Church's subgenius books,
tapes, and videos, and geegahs, t-shirts, and blah, blah, blah,
and, uh, friends, you can always check our website at www.subgenius.com.
Subgenius is spelled without an O.
Although we do have a decoy one there,
for the real subgeniuses, so they won't get lost.
And, uh, you can write for free information,
or more at, uh,
Hour of Slack at Post Office Box 181-417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
Now, if you want to send your tapes, or CDs, or videos to me, Reverend Ivan Stang,
uh, my actual production studio is here at the Cleveland branch,
and you can send that to me at Post Office Box 181-417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
And if that's too confusing, I'm stang at subgenius.com.
Friends, you can also, uh, you might want to get in touch with Einstein's Secret Orchestra,
who's doing this music in the background,
and who has the show on WCSB on Thursday nights,
from which this show is scavenged,
like a Frankenstein's monster from the parts of dead shows.
That's Einstein's Secret Orchestra, ESO, at Post Office Box.
Blah, blah, blah, no, yeah, yes, friends,
the church of the subgenius was born out of Bob in Dallas in the 19,
in, actually, January 1st, 19...
1980, the pamphlet number one was first released.
But, my friends, it was never limited to Dallas.
Dallas, we, it was a good place to begin the operations,
because it is a sterile town, a sterile city, full of sterile pinks,
most of whom don't even come from Texas.
And, uh, friends, I, uh, have, uh, have gotten out,
and, of course, uh, the church is in the hearts and minds of every subgenius,
everywhere.
Uh, some find it on the internet, some find it in the bookstore,
some find it in the junkyard,
uh, but the luckiest ones find it in the gutter,
at the bottom of a bottle of muscatel.
Because, friends, those are the ones that have reached the bottom,
that have yet achieved total slack through slacklessness,
and now can reverse their evolution, as under Bob,
to become slackless millionaires,
who give all their money to Bob.
Praise Bob, Hail Connie, and, uh, ah, yes, let there be slack.
Listen.
Friendly persuasion.
Hahahaha.
They're sackin' ke opportunity if not more.
Uh, keep your eyes open.
don't even try stin' cladNOsunisire
kwa-chackinko
wellh Axy  vibrating
Woy-whAM!
Phat-machist!
Ha ha, smigy mu MODO.
Vice ses.
Runway persuasion
Friendly persuasion
And that was the Bran Flakes new album, dear friends.
Friendly Persuasion from the Bran Flakes new album.
And you can contact...
They are at thebranflakes.com
And Bran Flakes is spelled like you would expect.
But it's thebranflakes...
One word.
Dot com.
And now, back to Burning Man with Philo and Puzzling.
And Burning Bush with Phineas.
Ah, yes.
It's so exciting.
We're out here on the playa.
And it's raining.
And we're going to get money.
And we're going to get the badge of our new president.
We won't be able to walk out of here.
No.
We'll just have to stay here for days.
But we've got George W. to study the words, the wisdom.
The optimisticist can happen.
Yeah.
The optimisticist can happen, scum.
I asked you to pray for...
I asked you...
I voted for...
I asked you to pray for Gore.
I asked you...
Our future demands it.
You were supposed to vote for Larry.
You're supposed to pray to God on your knees.
That he dies.
Together we will create an America...
Is he like the Jesus guy?
Yeah.
And an America that is...
An America...
In our diversity...
Diverse...
Excellent school...
Yes, all Americans will get diversity...
Excellent...
In the new America.
Shared American values...
In America...
American values...
The charge...
No, I don't think so.
Fight the Bush crackdown.
Not over National Radio.
By now, in Bogota, Colombia,
is the editor of...
The newspaper...
Juan Carlos Pastrana.
Pastrana.
Pastrami.
Yeah, I can have some pastrami on my Bushdown crack.
Okay, fine.
Fine, fine, fine, fine.
Man, I'm tired.
End of message.
Hello, Radio Shack.
This is Bob.
How may I help you?
This is Radio Shack.
This is Graham.
Can I help you?
No, it's Bob.
You're calling me?
Uh-huh.
Oh, somebody's played an evil joke on us.
Ah.
What people will do is...
People who have conference call capability on their phones...
Sad little...
It's a sick world.
Okay.
They're the only puppies sick enough to do that.
Oh, I gotta run.
Okay, bye.
Hello?
Pardon?
Goat?
Uh, no, Goat is not here yet.
You're talking to Mr. Miracle Man.
Would you like to pump the obscenities,
or would you just like to have your feet shaven?
Well, I'm sorry you're gonna have to wait,
because we're on wait mode, as you know, right now,
as Scott and Lona have told us,
we've been waiting here for the last 45 days,
and still there's no sign of it.
Uh, we're calling it now, uh, Day 45.
Can you tell us a little bit of, uh,
about, uh, where we stand right now, Reverend?
Well, yeah, that's exactly right.
Day 45 and counting.
45 days until it is released.
And it appears...
It will finally happen.
And if, uh, tomorrow, things, uh, go as the way they have been going,
and it's not likely to get much better,
it'll probably be Day 46.
It will be Day 46.
It will still be waiting.
It will be.
Forever after Day 45.
I'm gonna say the...
It will be it.
For me and my family...
It will be the world.
...has been excruciating.
Uh, my little dog, Norice, left me, uh, something in the mail,
and, uh, the rest of my family just broke up, as it were.
They didn't even, uh, bother to call me.
They just, uh, in a thousand little splintered pieces...
I saw those horrible little melting pieces.
We've had calls like this from, uh, everyone in town.
In fact, everybody called at one time to tell us that, like, everything is collapsing.
It is.
And it's time to go.
Back into our...
Till next week.
...original component parts.
Keep your hat on tight.
You're back to the winter sack in the saddle.
Try to keep from bleeding.
This is the S.O. Radio, kids.
Try to continue...
We'll be back next Thursday night.
...taking air.
After we go and sweep the Freetown Music Awards.
...and the big nasty from croaking up your throat and going into your head.
I think it's awesome.
...me home.
You said...
Silly boy.
Put your arms around me.
Take me home.
You silly boy.
All the world is not right.
Silly boy.
Hurry up and go.
You can't hear me, can you?
I don't even know what you're talking about.
I'll burn his head, doctor.
We can't even say it's a garbage truck.
Bagpipes on top of that are bubble gums...
That happens many times.
Dig it up, good night.
... Rubbia!
And this is a rerun of Hour of Slack number 777.
Hour of Slack number 777.