Ich geh auch schon raus mit.
Es ist ja offen an die Betten.
und hat den Traum wahrgenommen.
Machen Sie euren siebten Toiletten so gut,
dass er die anderen sechs übernimmt.
Körle in einen Ball und schließe deinen Kopf mit
THE SOGENIUS POWERHOUSE.
Ich habe meine Westenböcke nicht gemacht.
Schließt nur eure Augen einen Moment
und erinnert euch, dass ihr alle Bob-Buttonen habt,
die ihr vielleicht wollen könnt.
Brillant vier-farbene Bob-Buttonen.
Würde das nicht eure Augen poppen?
Ja, Gang, das ist wirklich was.
Weißt du, Kinder überall schreiben mir,
was für einen tollen Kick sie aus diesen Bob-Buttonen bekommen.
Sie mögen den Weg, wie die rot, schwarz, blau und gelbe Farben
gegen die puren, weißen, enamelten Kappen,
Schuhe oder Jacketten stehen.
Es gibt keine Frage, Gang,
diese Buttons werden täglich mehr populär.
Aber wie ich schon gesagt habe,
kann man diese schmutzigen Bob-Buttonen nirgendwo kaufen.
Nein, all you do is to see to it,
that mom puts in a good supply of Bob-Buttons for your house.
Then you'll find the button,
in the inner wax bag.
It's a prize for you.
It's doubtful you like Bob anymore.
Bob's broke.
Bob goes haywire.
And Bob's desperate.
And Bob's almond-shaped.
And Bob's never gonna find out.
And Bob's drunk.
News at 11.
Aliens have landed in front of the White House.
More details after
the subgenious
Hour of Slag.
I am unable to continue
blindly working on a project
of such phenomenal destructive potential.
Accordingly, there is only one
course of action open to me.
Zach Hobson, July 5th.
One.
There has been a malfunction in Project Flashlight
with devastating results.
Two.
It seems
I am the only person left on earth.
Is this really so?
Oh, man!
Oh God!
Dave!
That idiot blew up the station again!
I can't believe he would destroy the station again.
As if in some Mobius movie.
Every week he must do the same thing.
He's crying.
He's silly, silly.
We're gonna need more donations, friends.
Gonna need a lot more donations.
You're gonna need a lot of backbone muscles.
A lot of free...
Put out that fire!
...any sort of gland.
...
Oh yeah, right, whatever.
Was he talking about terrising his lawn or something?
Building burgers. I hate those building burgers.
I thought he was talking about terra.
Oh, terraforming.
No, terracing.
So he's going to start a garden or he's going to start the earth over again.
Which is a very old story.
It didn't originate with the church of the subgenius.
It goes way, way back to 912.
Nebuchadnezzar in the days of ancient Sumeria.
What? The creation
of the world? Stories?
The garden?
The Adnoi people?
I can't say it.
The Adnoi people
were a kin to the Exes.
Although Exes were easier to pronounce.
Yeah, and it rhymes with sexist.
Yeah.
So you're saying that your own creation or the creation of those
who have fondled you for so long
is a sexist creation?
No, it's the other way around.
We were created by them in a test tube.
Millions and millions
of years ago.
In the deep past.
And friends, that's where I
have returned from.
Follow the pirate flag.
Dave, I don't know if you knew this, but I,
Reverend Stang, have been
lost in time.
Mostly the
deep past. Mostly the
1980s.
Are you serious?
Yes, I inserted the lever
into the machine.
I pulled the crank.
You pulled your crank?
I ignited the platenorite,
which is the active ingredient in the time machine.
That's really dangerous.
And I traveled through
time itself.
The other dimension besides space.
I thought it was a pair of fishnet stockings, and now you're
saying you traveled through very time and space?
Relativistically speaking?
Yes, and I went back, back, back
to a greater day.
A more glorious age.
The early ages
of the subgenius.
The peas and the cheese nut and the children
laughing at each other.
When the subgeniuses still loved Bob.
And when Bob still loved
his children.
Bob Dobbs is crippled.
Yes, friends, it's because
of that job
I got myself into.
Teaching.
I'm Professor Stang now, and I've been teaching
an online course in
the history of the Church of the Subgenius.
The first 100 years.
Is that why you have the bleeding ear dog
with you now?
I've been kind of filled
with the spirit of the bleeding head of Arnold Palmer.
Yes, I dare say it.
The launching of said bleeding head
has, and I've been
recalling those wonderful rituals.
He's got the suede patches on his plaid shirt.
And I've been in terrible pain.
Because of all the hard work
late into the night.
Scanning and, you know,
documenting this trip
into the past.
Which is so much more fun than the future.
Because the future is
scary and grim.
What could be more fun than the past?
A jolly trip down memory lane.
Yes, back when I was
tortured and abused by
joblessness and jobs.
I can't breathe.
Actually, what I
discovered in my trip to the past,
I met my younger self.
Who was actually
never that young. And I'm pretty well convinced
that the conspiracy has
their own time machine and has gone
back in time and swapped us
for
imposters. With imposters.
Meaning your cyborgic, cymorgic body
is ensconced in some
CIA wagon, nut wagon out there
in the middle of the cosmos.
Why you, the elder
Zionist. Well, I don't know.
I don't really know.
All I know, I looked at these videos
from 1980 and I was never
that young and my friends were never that
young. They were never that cute.
That didn't happen.
I supposedly shot those videos, but somebody
has crept into my home,
dug through these ancient archives
and replaced them, doctored
them. They took the doctor tapes,
the tapes of doctors at the
subcons and the world conclaves
and had restaged
with actors. Well, did you notice
in the one picture that Hal
has a bouffant hairdo?
Right, exactly. I mean, there's
none of us ever had that much hair.
You vaguely remember that time, but if someone
were to say, well, did you walk down, were you in
Lower Haight and you walked down the street to Leggies or something
like that and had a pizza pie? It's like,
no, the memory is so fragmented
and disconnected. I can
barely remember him wearing the bouffant
hairdo. It's
strange. I had many
false memories.
And I
discovered that I had split
into two persons. There was the
elderly, the subgenius
sacred scribe
who was having a great time and a new
career. And then there was
worker Smith,
a worker Smith,
citizen Smith,
who lived in the year of 1984,
much like Winston Smith.
I'd say very much. Who, by the way,
joined the church in 1984, the
artist named Winston Smith.
And also the minister of information guy, too.
Ministry of... Well, that's in the future.
He is a minister of information
now, but... Yeah. But we gotta
go to the next 1984
for that to happen.
But first we must go to the next
1998. Well, wasn't
there a collision day?
The time collision. That's
in the future, but it could have repercussions
that echo back to our
time. And maybe these are just ripples
from that time intersection
that we're starting to see.
It's just like a loose fart sprung in a hallway
when there's too many people. You can never tell where
the rebounds are going to go or even some
of the sockets are going to start frying.
Here, come with me. Let's try
this. I'll crank the
lever forward. Here, I'll turn up this little knob.
And look, you can see
the calendar pages are flying
away.
The candles are all just
dripping down. That mannequin
across the street keeps changing clothes.
You could change everything.
My wife keeps changing her mind.
But
we are going this time, not into the past.
But deep into the future.
Deformation's a little...
The human race has split into two
species.
Well, actually, that all happened a long
time ago when it split into the subgeniuses
and the humans.
But you meant the sexual change...
But what of the Morlocks?
And this is what I learned
in my travels.
The Morlocks, which the pinks like to
regard as some kind of monsters,
are just because
they live underground and come out at night to steal
humans and eat them, like cattle.
The Morlocks are the ones
that are in charge. They're the ones that know
how everything works. And they're pretty, too.
Well, if you're a Morlock...
Well, they're pretty to others.
It's too late when they encounter
them and stuff, but Morlocks are pretty.
Their skin
is very, very shiny and soft.
Their teeth are very, very, very long
and yellow. And it's just
a matter of moments before they snap
the back of your head and eat the
intestines.
Well, they're not that crude about it.
They have little forks and knives and things.
That's what they call it.
They flay you and cook you and so forth.
That's what our descendants will be doing, Dave.
Because we are the
grandsires of the Morlocks,
not of the Eloi.
The Eloi are the cattle. They're the sheeple
that are literally raised.
It's because of class division
today that all of this will happen.
In the continuing class division?
Yes, and in the continuing sequel to
H.G. Wells' Time Machine called
The Time Ships by Stephen
Baxter, which I've been re-reading.
Who is not H.G. Wells?
No, Stephen Baxter.
Yeah, but he's British.
That counts for something.
I have no idea what it might be.
Anyway,
I've had this time
paradox.
Here's another thing. I look at these old
videos of the olden
days of the subgeniuses.
And I find myself identifying
not with the me that I see,
but with this guy, Doug Smith.
Did you ever hear of him?
He was like the office boy.
He's a character.
Well, okay, yeah, right.
He was a real guy.
But every time I see him on the film, I go,
oh, that's me. But no, that's not me.
That's this loser.
I remember that guy, but why do I keep
identifying with him?
It's not because he was a character in your film,
but what I was saying was he was an actual
kind of a character in Dallas.
He was a known Lee Harvey.
And a crackpot and stuff.
And that's why you're fixated.
When you see him, it's not recognition
of your own cellular self.
It's recognition that you've rubbed elbows
or perhaps pubis with this inordinate
meaning and want to continue
some way.
I believe that's right.
It's a good theory.
It holds all kinds of water.
I don't take no truck
with this modern day
psychotherapeutic jive talk.
That's a bunch of
fruit.
It's a bunch of fruit for all.
It's a bunch of hoo-ha.
If you asked me.
You guys with your malleable memories.
You got a smoke sugar?
Hey, here comes another malleable memory again.
I didn't really say something so stupid
that it caused that person to have a nervous breakdown.
That wasn't my fault.
No.
That's funny. That memory is so much more comfortable now.
I didn't do that off.
I didn't snap at that innocent child
that time like I remember.
This memory is completely
different now.
And now the hypothalamus comes out.
They say time heals all wounds.
And there's jokes about
what it does to heals.
You should see them in the old days
they had shoe stores.
You would go there and you would argue with shoes.
Perhaps like one of the reptilians would come in
and maybe start a credit thing with you.
Yeah, but it's all been replaced by mall warts now.
Mall warts.
I hate that phrase.
Oh, I hate the one on Mars.
Oh, it's the worst.
Mars marts.
Those are the worst.
The wall of Mars mart.
Yeah, flaying your feet is what it should be called.
The flaying of the vesicles in feet.
You know, they suspect that they've found
evidence of underground water on Mars
squirting out.
But I don't think what squirted was water.
The scientists said
we suspect that the fluidizing agent
is water.
But I don't suspect that myself at all.
Well, see, when you get to be my age,
any fluidizing agent,
you suspect to be water.
Why do they use fluidizing?
Earlier you suspected
it's a schermatopoferenema
or the other spermatic devices
that they use to impregnate universes.
Sometimes, anyway.
I hope I never get old like you, Dave.
Well, you'll probably be cursed
with getting old like yourself.
How long will it be before I get old like Dave?
Five years?
But Dave's about five years further in the time stream.
No, you've already gotten older like yourself.
I know, man.
Once again, you've got to stop obsessing
with these characters that are not real people,
but just characters.
I remember...
I'm going back.
I'm going back again.
And I remember the first time I met
Dr. G. Gordon Gordon, Bob's bodyguard.
I remember thinking,
I can't believe that there's a subgenius
who's that old.
I think at the time he was 39.
Well, that's an old subgenius.
Well, when you're 26,
when you're 27, sure.
Yeah, 39's real old.
What's the expected lifespan?
Everybody knows a subgenius doesn't have long on this plane.
Philo just married a 37-year-old
and I thought he was being a crib fisherman.
A crib fisherman?
Cradle robber.
And she's robbing the grave, of course.
She's leaving the analogy of a fish out of it.
Because aren't you?
We're going to go to San Francisco
and see Philo and Puzzlin
and Dr. Howell and...
Lies.
And not you, Gary.
And lies.
Yeah, there'll be a lot of lies.
Will you be having San Francisco treats
or just taking the telegraph or the...
Actually, I think we're going to have...
Carmel car, whatever it's called.
We're going to have our annual
anal subgenius business meeting
at the Crosley Bendix studio
in Berkeley.
Where over the edge...
It starts over the edge
and then we fall all the way into the puzzling evidence
and it's five hours long.
Oh, and Phineas Narco.
Maybe we can dig up...
We've got to remember not you, Phineas, this time.
Five weird hours.
There are a lot in the Bay Arians.
Yeah.
The Bay Arians are a masterful race of po-buckers.
Of all different hue,
but still some sort of...
Yeah.
Of some kind.
They call it Baghed by the Bay,
yet there's no people wearing furniture on their backs.
Yeah, there are now.
There are?
Yeah.
There is?
Okay.
And...
Are there any Bay Arians, Breath Arians?
Do you think?
Oh, surely.
I heard that they died out.
They have...
I heard that, yeah, the Breath Arians just...
They all just sort of dried up and blew away.
Well, they still have Sufi frog divers.
I mean, they've had those since the late 60s.
Is that what's crawling up out of the water right now?
No, I think that might be one of the Pummelards.
They've got the long back.
Oh, that's not one of the Morlocks.
It's one of the Lesslocks.
One of the...
They don't have it.
They're not as hairy.
It's a very hairy one underneath.
Just don't get too close to the stone.
Uh-uh.
It's a face only a mommy Morlock could...
This music in the background is from the...
The face is in the coin area.
The George Powell...
And it's where the buttocks should be.
Time Machine.
Which is the only movie that's ever been made of the novel The Time Machine.
There have been some crapolas, including one directed by H.G. Wells' grandson in 2001 that just...
Oh, God.
I hear crickets.
Is that coming from your head?
I just...
I get upset when the holy texts are trifled with.
Hollywood does that.
Hollywood will take a great piece of literature that's an earnest warning that we should all heed
and change it into a guy flying through the air in front of a fireball.
But you should not...
Who saves the world by using his brute strength and going...
To push the lever at the last minute.
Just relax.
And it blows up every Morlocks hole in the whole world.
Everything's fine.
And the only reason the Morlocks came was because there was an industrial accident.
It wasn't because of the have-nots and the haves.
Here come some of those haves right now.
Oh, the cricket sound coming out of his left ear, you mean?
It looks like the maneuver horns went like one side of the...
They're coming after us, have-nots.
What do they call that part of...
Those horny haves are coming after us, little hornless have-nots.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Are you ready for the next course?
We've finished the long pig and coming up next we'll be having short pig.
Short pig.
And we'll be doodling in the ice cream, so please don't disturb this table.
It's a table of science and a table of reason.
So if you could just get your fat equipment back into the December zone where you don't belong.
It's dream time for you, baby.
Just get...
Yeah, never mind the fug fish and the Ernestines and the chocolate soup.
And any of the other...
And that's another thing.
I haven't had a dream in years now.
Did my dreams go to another time stream?
Is someone else dreaming my dreams?
Someone has stolen his dreams.
They're kept on dusk.
They stole my dreams.
They're keeping your dreams on dusk.
You stole my dreams, man.
Bob, I believed in you, dude.
I saw you on night flight and I believed in you.
I was only...
Eight years old.
And you let me down, man.
You let me down.
Stang.
This is the voice of someone who doesn't sound like Bob, but really is.
Fall upon your knee, all three.
Look.
Out the window.
Yeah.
Look, it is Santa Claus with a pipe.
It's stolen.
Your dreams have been ransomed.
Santa's real.
Your ransom has been neglected.
I knew it.
Go and look under the Christmas tree.
The baby Jesus is lying there.
Christ Jesus.
For you.
Oh, he's probably...
Look at that crucified baby.
He's so cute.
I told you if you had faith.
I told you.
So heartwarming.
Oh, this manger is so warm and comfy with that crucified infant there.
And who is that horned man sitting in that rocking chair over there knitting?
That's not Santa.
That's not Santa, is it?
No, that's...
We call him Uncle Scratchspunkle.
It's kind of a long name, but it serves his purposes.
Come on over and meet him.
He's a hell of a guy.
I've always wanted to meet Mr...
What's his name?
Scratchspunkle.
Oh, right.
Oh, sure.
That must be old Splitfoot that they're always...
Hey, hey, kids over here.
What's your name?
You with the long hair and the pull out.
I'm Reverend Ivan Stang and I want to be a famous filmmaker when I grow up.
I want to be just like that.
I want to be just like Ray Harryhausen.
Bend over and pull down your pants.
What?
I want to see what you're really made of, Stang.
To get in this club, you've got to be made of plenty of things.
My mama told me not to talk to people like you, Mr. Scratch.
Never mind.
I've got a check.
Okay.
Ow!
That thing's cold.
No, that's the device that was implanted in you long, long, long, long, long ago.
Do that again.
I say.
He doesn't even know how long he's been out there, does he?
He's snobbish.
He smiles, he laughs, he's living his own life.
He thinks there's nothing.
He's sold his dreams.
He has no dreams.
I'm laughing.
I don't laugh.
Stop breathing.
All right.
You, Philoderman.
You, the third Duranio.
You, you.
Step to the...
He's already...
Okay, he's sleeping.
You, we are done.
Step up to the front.
Step up.
Closer.
Up front.
Do you know how to do the little girly pirouette?
Do you now how to put one finger on top of your head and make a ballerina like me?
I'm too nervous.
You've practiced.
You've practiced for aeons.
Ooh.
Yes.
I can't, I can't.
I have stage fright.
You've been motionutos.
Don't you want to be Little Miss Sunshine?
Don't you want to be like him?
Her?
It?
Any of those things?
You can't give up now after we've come all this way.
Don't you want to assemble other things in the room?
For instance, the turn table.
Don't you want to be like everybody else?
Das ist die große Chance, normal zu sein.
Sie sah die Lichter in ihr Kopf kommen.
Am Topf ihres Kopfes, wo ein Baby ein kleines Donut-Farm gemacht hat.
Es war ein leiser Ort, aber sicher genug,
wurde das Gehirn gequetscht und vibriert.
Ein Donut-Farm, ist das was, was auf dem Kopf war?
Nun, einige Leute haben es allgemein umgekehrt.
Einfach... seltsam.
Ein paar.
Santa Claus.
Einfach... seltsam.
Nicht schreien, Kind.
Ich werde dich nicht schreien.
Ich weiß, du bist ein Bob.
Schleim, dunkle Haare, schön aussehend.
Dann...
Dann musst du...
Vielleicht.
Nicht wahr?
Was machst du?
Du wirst es finden.
Schleim.
Aber, je, ich...
Schleimhaare.
Schau, Bob.
Komm.
Schön aussehend.
Oh, je.
Ich weiß nicht, was ich tun soll.
Halt deine Mund schief.
So lang, Bob.
Ich verspreche, dass ich komme, aber er versucht, es auszuheben.
Ich sagte ihm, ob er kommen muss, ob er es will oder nicht.
Er hat es richtig gemacht, Bob?
Ja, sicher.
Oh, na gut.
Ich glaube, ich muss, wie er sagte, sie alle zusammenheben.
Und dann komme ich.
Nachher, ein entspannter junger Bob.
Das ist alles klar, Bob.
Echt?
Ist das einer von ihnen?
Das ist Bob.
Oh, so ist es.
Wie geht es, Sir?
Bob hier ist eingeschaltet und wartet...
Wenn wir da rauskommen?
Ja.
Es gab zwei große Jungs und eine Mädchen.
Sie versuchten, Bob zu sagen, er sei einer von ihnen.
Und er hat gemerkt, er hätte...
Oh, Robert.
Was ist passiert?
Sieh, Mama.
Ich weiß nicht, wie ich es dir sagen soll, aber...
Sei nicht so dumm, Bob.
Du hast einen guten Job gemacht.
Oh, Robert.
Aber Mama, es war wirklich nicht so, wie er sagte.
Bis morgen, Bob.
Ja, Frau.
Ich...
Ich verstehe diese Dinge nicht.
Ich weiß nur, dass er ein Mann ist, der mit Haar auf den Händen hat
und kein Blut in seinem Gesicht.
Er isst kein Essen und ist mordlich Angst vor...
...die Prussikus.
Die...
...so geniöse...
...Power...
...of...
...Wand...
...Ich bin ein Sturm...
...einer von allen...
...und...
...ich...
...helf...
Das ist PR-Mobio.
Siehst du, Bob, mit...
...especially mit...
...und...
...er macht Dinge...
...was...
Siehst du...
...das...
...Bee...
...Bob...
...da ist keine Frage darüber.
PR kommt aus PR-Stationen.
Hey.
Ja?
Ja.
Nein?
Wie?
Hey, du, B.
Ich wette, du könntest ein paar der Trick-Stücke, die sie haben,
wie das Plastik-Eis-Cube.
Das kannst du in den Rubber-Cheese geben,
das kannst du in den Kaffee mit Soap in den Mitteln geben,
um es mit Rubber-Snaken zu vermischen, mit dem Bug in es.
Geil.
Hat es funktioniert?
Oh, er hat es gemacht.
Meine Mutter weint und trinkt,
aber du bist aus dem Fenster.
Ja, warum nicht?
Na, Hank?
Das ist gut, tschüss.
Beavitt to Lemur.
There's no doubt.
That was all Lemurian stuff just then, by the way.
You must disclaim that through pure coincidence...
There's Lemur in the back...
And look, they're over in the background of the scene.
You can see him fighting.
What were you saying, Dave?
I was just saying that through pure coincidence...
Through pure coincidence of improvised girdle wear
and by that Lemurian rantade
that we were thrust into a position,
a carnal, somewhat abstruse position,
where we're forced, and forcing small children
to think that they must have sex with Santa Claus,
especially if they're a male,
a little, good little boy
who deserves more than a trick or treat on Holy Night
and more than one of those peppermint cakes
that you can eat at the end of the day.
And I'm not saying that's a good thing,
but I'm saying that there's a change in the wrong spot.
And I just wanted to disclaim from the bottom of my...
Yeah, that we're not into that.
No, we're a mirror reflecting the ills of society around us.
That's a satirical take-off on putting down that sort of thing, you see.
We're against young boys.
Man, how could I not have gotten that?
I'm sorry, I took three...
What are... Equinox?
We try to always be against the...
The young boys in our church.
Firmly against them?
Well...
You try to direct their...
Let's not go there.
We've gone there so many times before.
Yeah, but let's not...
Can we please...
Go there right now.
Particularly at this juncture.
Not... Later, Dave, later.
What are you foul-faced, smelly boys doing down there?
I can hell and smell and hear all of you up here.
You, Stang.
Get your hand away from that woman's...
Get out of there.
Can I put it on mine?
No, no.
Move up here by the stairs.
I wanna see your face in the...
In the light.
So you wanted to see me.
You wanna know who I am and what I am.
Well, then I'll show you I will.
Mwahahahaha!
Look, look, I didn't mean nothing by it.
See, you go on, do what you want.
What's happened to her?
She's scary looking now.
Friends, life is tough and it does things to you.
And makes you old and ugly and wrinkled.
Why, just the other day Susie the floozy was saying,
Yeah, Stang used to be pretty ugly, but you're cute now.
Isn't that weird how that happens?
I actually think it was the other way around.
Like I say, I was looking at old videos and I was like, oh no, I was cute.
If I didn't have any idea how cute I was, I would have cheated, started cheating on my wife.
No, you were looking...
...big time.
Well, you already cheated on your wife.
I blew it, man!
Before you cheated.
I totally blew it!
That's what everybody says, you know.
Now it's too late.
It's a waste.
Might as well just throw it all away now.
Calm down there, calm down.
Just a loser, man.
There are greater things at hand.
Greater gains, greater loss.
Bub, let me down, man.
Life is a bowl of pickles surrounded rich, rich,
He never gave me the bowl of pickles.
He gave me three slices.
Three slices.
And they weren't the kind I liked. They were sweet pickles.
Yes, that's the church of the subgenius.
You've been listening to the drama entitled WCSB I.D. Oye.
We'll be back to our normal programming after this word.
Okay.
That was it.
That was the word was okay?
Yeah.
Go ahead.
So are we back yet, so to speak?
Yeah.
Okay.
We're back.
Well, I remember what we were talking before.
We was trying to put out some of the small fires who are still in the studio here.
We had some problems with the EMS and we were trying to do a disclaimer, but you said
it was just satire about, well, I can't really remember the flow of anything.
Why am I even on the radio?
I'm going home.
Goodbye.
That was the way I felt for so long.
That's because you were in pain.
See, pain does that to you, Stan.
There's nothing wrong with you, really.
It's not in your mind, like you might think.
You think you're going mad, don't you?
See?
Sometimes.
No.
You look out the window and you wish you could fly by like a witch, don't you?
Maybe jump in the dumpster and have some little snack.
Sure you do.
Come on.
I saw a guy one time I was parked outside of a bar, stuck, waiting for Jesus actually
to finish up inside the bar, getting the money.
It was seven in the morning or something.
And there was an old man, he looked kind of like you, Dave, rooting through the dumpster
by the bar.
And he would pull out paper cups and look at them and there'd be a little bit of beer
in there and he'd drink the beer and then...
That's risky business.
Uncarbonated beer.
You know what uncarbonated beer looks like, don't you?
It looks like diamonds.
No, it looks like human urine.
And so, therefore, I would say that was risky business.
Well, I mean, he was giving them a little look, you know, and I mean, hey, look, if you
need it, you know how it is.
He just really needed a drink and that was the only way he could get them.
Well, Mr. Know-it-all, the part you don't realize is shortly after you looked away and
thought of inhumanities, inhumanities to itself...
Yeah, it wasn't like I went over there and gave him a buck or anything.
Right.
I could have gone over and said, here, man, take two bucks and buy yourself a quart of
beer.
I could have said, you know, you're going to be dead in two weeks anyway.
You prefer to anecdotally comment on it later rather than notice as he walked in the shadows
ostensibly to be looking for more of those things.
And the thing is, obviously, with Jesus...
He popped out.
Jesus could have filled every one of those dirty old cups with fresh new beer.
But he wasn't looking for fresh or old beer.
He was waiting to pop that third thyroid eye out.
No, he was trying to get money out of the club owner.
Well, I was trying to do a shtick where he turned out to be an alien and he just like,
you know, just...
Jesus?
He's not.
No, the old drunken fellow.
Oh.
So the old drunken fellow goes, ah, never mind.
Okay.
But you did know this person?
That wasn't you, was it?
No.
It was in Columbus.
I think.
Just because Columbus is in the same temporal plane as Ohio.
He really looked like he was really old.
And, you know, kind of had that...
Old look.
That lonesome cowboyish look.
Yeah.
I don't think those things combine very well.
But here's the...
Oh, I know what my point was.
I know, here was my point.
But the whole thing, while I was looking at that man, I was thinking, I wish I was him.
Because he...
It looks to me like he's got a slightly better deal than I do.
So I was working too hard then.
And I got the impression this guy wasn't really working very hard.
You know how hard it is to find a good hearty ale amongst all the urine?
Man, that guy works hours and hours and it's not for 10.95s, dang.
But he could drink on the job.
That's the difference.
Yeah, of course.
Look, my back hurts.
Drink it is part of the job.
I really wanted a beer, a medicinal beer all day today.
And there were two crappy tasting beers in the fridge.
But I didn't touch them because I knew I had to do a radio show tonight.
And that's how much I care about...
What am I saying?
Yeah, really.
I'm going home.
I'm gonna go have a beer right now.
He's gonna go and have seven medicinal beers and then try and find the keys so he can
go and get them.
And he's gonna get an additional six medicinal beers.
Hey, Bob!
You better not talk about Bob!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
It's real important.
Bob, shall we just talk about Bob?
If you get tired, just push one of the buttons on that and some stuff will apply.
Any button?
Yeah, pretty much.
Can we go like, you know, move one up, down and like...
That's what I like.
I like that.
It's like a show normally.
Okay.
That's what I do.
You're gonna drink them all?
You're not gonna save even like one or two?
Damn, I can't get into the car.
Yeah.
No.
See, Princess Wee has no...
Princess Wee's had to deal with me when I get carried away.
He can't get away.
You have the handcuffs as well?
Well, we don't talk about those on the air.
Look, this...
We're given an hour of public air space and we should use it for something edifying.
Yes, edification.
But aren't we supposed to like bitch about the president or decroceate?
decry the war
or something
I don't know, you know,
cool or whatever.
That shows our outrage with the fluxes
that we're in vagary with.
Yeah. Well,
well, everybody knows where we stand.
We're not very fond of wars.
This one guy on alt-slack
who does a radio show
of his own out of Houston.
He was going,
I need some Christmas stuff to do Christmas.
I was going to do a new show and maybe
use some Bush cut-ups.
And at the phrase Bush cut-ups
another subgenius
kind of cut in and went,
oh,
spare me.
And I've got to admit, when I
put in this week's Bush cut-up
I was thinking, wait a minute, man.
Haven't we had
enough Bush cut-ups on
all the college radio shows?
I mean, I got tired
of Clinton cut-ups before that.
Before that was the other Bush.
Before that it was
that other guy.
And then before that was that other Bush.
And then it was that other guy.
Before that it was that other Bush.
So it's been Bushes every time for 50 years.
People don't remember that.
They don't know their actual names.
They're given stage names.
After they leave Andover, Mass,
prep school, they're all given stage names.
They don't remember Fred Bush,
who was the president after Johnson.
The original one.
And John Bush, who was the president
just before Eisenhower.
In between Truman and Eisenhower.
What about Weisenheimer?
K. Bush.
The actual man behind the Civil War.
He thought Seward was pushing Lincoln's buttons.
My parents saw him get assassinated on Telegraph.
Yeah, with ice skates.
I guess they just cut him to ribbons
in front of a couple thousand people at least.
Man, those were the days.
Those were the days.
You guys are totally forgetting
the assassinated Samuel Bush.
Oh yeah, of course.
Sam Bush.
That was a sad day when Sam Bush went down
near the Depositorium.
And there were at least three extra
wounded gunmen.
They were called the Bush League, weren't they?
At a very serious time.
League of Bush or something like that.
That's like the Hanseatic League.
I think you're thinking of the Bilderbergers,
which is, although interrelated.
I like Wendy's. I prefer Wendy's, really.
And I like Limburger myself best.
Do you?
Is that what that is?
I wondered what that is.
It smells like either a chemical or like one of those...
Have you been rolling in cheese, dear?
Again.
Cheese is what I've been rolling in.
I let it fall.
We've all been rolling in something, friends.
And what have you been rolling in?
You know how dogs like to roll in
smelly dead things and then suddenly
show up at your doorstep wagging their tail
thinking, oh, they're gonna love me now.
Jesus loves me.
City dogs don't get to do that.
You get to roll in dead
like rats and stuff that are near the sewers.
No, they're not allowed out.
Dogs in the city can't go out.
They get snatched up and taken to the laboratories.
They must be on a limb.
Leash, don't you know.
Yeah.
Now, in the country, your dog will...
Dogs has always been my friend.
Except when they roll in the dead things.
And then...
Sometimes they will chase a silly skunk
out in the wilderness
and learn a lesson afterwards.
And sometimes they'll chase shadowy figures
that look like they're wearing those
Burger King crowns.
Have you ever seen those guys?
I thought it was drug users that chased them.
They chased the shadowy...
Oh, no, they flee shadowy figures.
Well, some drug addicts and dogs
are one and the same.
Well, and then you had that dog
that chased invisible things.
Yeah, yeah.
I lived on the Lakota reservation then
and this old medicine man gentleman
informed me that my dog could see spirits
because it had been injured in a car accident
and was different than other dogs.
That it could see spirits and chase...
Well, I believe it.
I don't.
You don't?
No.
Was the medicine man a known liar?
No, no.
No, he wasn't anything like Bob.
Well, see, there you go.
You know, Bob is a convincing
but still a lying...
Well, actually, I shouldn't say that.
Actually, these particular bunch of medicine men
were, in fact, charlatans
who put on fake seances.
But they didn't do it for money.
They really did heal people
because, you know,
the placebo effect.
And it really works.
I later, I went to several of their ceremonies
and I believed completely
that the spirits of dead holy manhood
Indian guys had entered the room
because you could smell the buffalo leather.
You could, you know,
they even made little sparkies
and flashies in the dark.
And later, sitting in the extra meditation
one year, I suddenly went,
that was nothing but masking tape
being stripped real fast in the dark.
And those were just old brattles they had.
And they just had a box full of smells.
Smelly old stuff.
And, oh my God,
that guy was faking that whole thing.
And he even told us,
he said, after you leave,
you may start to think about
what has happened here.
But you have to remember,
what's important is your feeling.
Think how you felt.
And he was as much as saying,
look, I know you wash your shoes,
you're probably not going to believe
this is real.
Sooner or later,
you're going to wise up and come down.
But I'm not doing this for money
and it really does help people.
And maybe you'll get some kicks out of it too.
That's beautiful.
And there were cases,
at least I heard of,
like a person that had been told
by the Bureau of Indian Affairs Hospital
that their cancer was incurable.
But they go to the medicine man
and lo and behold,
their cancer is miraculously cured.
Because they believed.
They believed, sure, Bob was a liar.
And sure, Mr. Steed,
the medicine man, was a charlatan.
But,
he wasn't the kind of charlatan
that's only in it for the money.
He was brought groceries.
You know, after you went to one of his things,
it was expected that you'd sort of
drop off a load of groceries next week.
So he was eating off your lack of suffering
because he was a true Hippocratic charlatan.
He wasn't like,
he wasn't a duck
or one of those people
that argue with french fries.
He was a serious, serious charlatan.
He was a helpful.
He's still a charlatan.
He was using his charlatanic powers
for good.
For good instead of good.
Just greediness.
Which is pretty good too, actually.
I mean, if somebody's gonna give money
to a charlatan, like say Bob Tilton,
that preacher on TV.
Who's gonna spend it right?
Who's gonna spend it more wisely?
Obviously the preacher.
Because he's not gonna give it to some charlatan preacher.
He knows better.
He's gonna buy something of value, a yacht.
You know, or a hooker.
A Mercedes.
He's sure not gonna give it
to some guy who goes,
God needs your money.
Don't you need to help God?
He can't do it all himself.
You've gotta smite the subgeniuses for him.
I know that always brought a fond,
I don't know,
sparked a little tumor
in the middle of my Lemurian region itself
when I think about
how many of those
of the professorial class
of the intelligentsia
while they're deriding the proletariat
for not catching up quickly enough
going backwards and forwards like that
at the same time
There's that word again.
Time.
The same time.
They do not see the slickness
of their own slack.
And that's why I hate them.
I hate them.
God will not survive
if you do not give me another sandwich.
That bothers me.
Well,
actually the gods won't survive
if no one believes in them.
They're exactly as powerful
as the belief
that people have in them.
So what do we call the world?
Is it Weltbekommt
or the world belief?
What is the great dragon?
The horns of Mazar?
I don't know, professor.
Why don't you tell us?
Well, no, I mean,
isn't there a word for that?
Probably a German three-part word
which is like how everybody thinks
and feels
at the same time
and then has the
composite right amount of stuff
to make something happen.
You know,
they're not worldview,
but it would be.
I know, Weltenschlang.
Weltenschlang.
Yes, I have quite a Weltenschlang.
Would you like to come up and see it?
Mine is as big as the world.
Yes, it's very wooden.
My wooden Weltenschlang.
Oh, you wooden.
That's Weltenschlang.
That was made in the late 1840s.
Yeah, I had to learn
that word in prep school.
Weltenschlang?
Yeah.
At least you weren't struck
with one forcibly around the head
and the shoulders
like when they run the gauntlet
at that other school you went to.
The other school I dropped out of,
actually, is what it's a long...
They dropped you out.
No, no, no, I quit.
Well, your prep school
was better than my prep school
because I didn't learn that word.
No, your prep school
was tons better than mine
because your prep school
was all girls.
Mine was all boys.
I'd have much rather been
going to your prep school.
I would have much rather been going to your prep school.
Well, with this time machine,
we can trade.
And Senor will wish you
have gone to co-ed public schools.
Yeah, she went to one of those schools
that was run by nuns.
Nuns.
The blue nuns.
Yeah, the blue...
They were the leap for milk ladies?
The leap for milk nuns.
Oh, cool, man.
Yeah, she was raised by nuns.
They drink like schweinhunds.
They're all nuns.
Oh, they can drink.
They can't have sex,
but they can do drugs.
Okay.
Oh, that's good.
That's the way they can give
real worldly advice to people.
Well, yeah, they should be on the bottom
where the rest rest
and know what's going on with them.
And, you know,
if you're going to
explanderate the feelings
and the apostasy of the Lord
or any of his minions,
you've at least got to know
where he's coming from or been.
Dig it.
You know.
Who's drinking his stuff?
Did you just say a dirty word, Princess Wee?
Oh, dig it.
I get it.
Okay.
Dig it.
But, you know, like, you know, like.
I misunderstood.
Did you think I said bugger it or something?
We didn't want to have to bugger the lad again,
but he was insolent and so.
Bugger it.
Lay your hand and shrimp.
Hey.
Um, um, well, we both seem, um, uh.
Somehow hurled right back into that bad stuff again.
I just don't know about you two.
Well, you know, embrace Bob, uh, with, with our hands.
Our feet.
If we were to give him the love he needs, wants from us.
Embrace him with our minds.
I don't think he actually wants love.
What does he want?
Our, um.
Money.
Well, Reverend.
Okay.
He wants our money.
Yeah.
We give him our checks.
We give him our actual paper money.
No, actually you give them to me and then that helps Bob.
Okay.
I'm actually, I mean, not me, but Subgenius Foundation Incorporated.
Which I happen to be the president of right now.
Okay.
I think she's the, uh, treasurer.
So, all right.
Well, we're here with the, uh.
Philo's the vice president.
The president of the church of the slave.
No, no, no.
I'm president of the Subgenius Foundation, which is a, uh, limited partnership, uh, in Texas.
Okay.
It also says here you're the high epoch.
No, no, that's Bob.
Bob is the high epoch.
Bob is.
She is a princess.
And she is a princess.
But I'm not an epoch.
And do you, are you also a princess or do you, uh.
No, I'm the, um.
The, the, the CEO perhaps.
Maybe the word might be, uh, the phrase.
No, actually I'm the, her consort is technically my title.
The princess's consort.
Okay.
Now, once we give our checks.
I was the palace janitor originally.
Our plastic money, uh, our sofas and couches are a different part.
The furniture that we don't need or anything, I suppose.
We give this to Bob.
Right.
But through the Subgenius, because you can't just write a check to J.R. Bob Dobbs.
He, where's, where, where are you going to send it?
Well, you send it to Subgenius Foundation.
The publishing and PR firm of the church, of the Subgenius.
But Bob will answer our, um, not prayers.
What would be the, the correct word?
He will answer.
Orders.
He will answer your orders with goods.
And we place.
Actual goods.
Yes.
Orders by a holy calendar perhaps or more like a, uh, catalog.
A bucket of pills.
An old fashioned bathtub full of pills perhaps.
Oh, right.
A claw-footed bathtub full of.
That's explaining.
That's explaining something here.
Um.
Whatever you want to buy, I'm sure that, uh, the man of Bob and Bob can provide that.
Just about anything.
So he will to those, um, who have decided.
To those who have enough, who have enough faith and are able to invest enough faith
and money in Bob.
All miracles can come.
Yes.
They are, is there a guarantee or is there anything that, um, a potential Subgenius could
do?
Something bad.
Well, as we, as we discussed earlier into every life from every life, some poo must
fall.
Poo?
Yes.
And Bob is no, he is a life form.
And so some poo falls from Bob and rains down upon us.
So.
And there are, so there are drawbacks.
Yes.
I can see why some people want to call the church of the subgenius a cult or, uh, an
ism.
Uh.
An ism.
And, uh, I mean, uh, when really, uh, obviously it's just exactly what we want.
It's exactly what it says it is.
It's a, a, uh, Sato futuristic, uh, mega futuristic, uh, religion, religion, philosophical, anarcho
materialist outreach.
Uh, and the outreach is, uh, well said there are thousands, it says here in this release
that's been just been released here in front of hundreds of thousands of guests and cabin
freaks.
Uh, all enlisted in the service of.
Of the church of the subgenius.
Right.
These are soldiers for Bob, nun snakes, uh, altered boys.
Says here even port caricature artists and portraiture artists are, uh, needed sometimes.
Right.
Um, there's.
Well, the, there's never a, an end to the, the need for, uh, paintings and drawings of
the subgenius hierarchites.
I suppose there's a lot of.
The sacred scribes for instance.
Oh, of course.
The, and different saints or what are religious characters?
Yeah.
Well, the saints that we still talk to.
We had to take down paintings of quite a few saints who lost their minds.
Well, it also says here at Ablator.
And took their pants off in the wrong place at the wrong time.
You know how some of those soldiers for Bob are rambunctious.
Bunch home from the front, I guess, looking for some act in, um, but not always, at least
here in the church of the subgenius, you also have a resume, a corrector.
What does that, uh, have to do with this?
A resume, correct?
Well, basically we just show people how to lie realistically on resumes.
Now this is also lie and resume.
That's related to the sacred doctrine of erasability.
Right.
So nobody ever checks.
That's the main thing.
So it's fair to lie on your resume because everybody else is doing it.
That's the reason.
That's why it's okay to steal.
I don't know if you knew that, but it's okay to steal because everybody else is doing it.
Ah.
But if you think about it, everybody pilfers a little bit somewhere along the line.
So that makes sense.
Okay.
As Bob Nelson once said, if, uh, if one or more, if more than one subgenius businessmen
do something, then it is therefore legal.
That makes it legal.
I see.
So it's not just memory that's malleable, but it's also morals that are malleable.
Oh yeah.
Well, absolutely.
That's what religion is all about.
Bob's religion is built on a shifting sandy beach of hypocrisy, as we've said so many
times.
And, uh, and yes, you are, you're in, the truth is, is to be wielded as a weapon.
You see, you just say, it's basically it, it becomes, it's okay to lie as long as you
don't get caught.
Same with stealing.
Those are codified into the religion.
Kind of intramural, like intramural.
Right.
And Bob said, as I've said so many times, uh, I don't practice what I preach because
I'm not the man I'm preaching to.
And he wouldn't want to be either.
We'd, we'd noticed that.
I was trying to make a joke.
I'm sorry.
You said that so smarmily.
Oh, well, no, I, I thought maybe that fit with the flow of what you were saying.
I didn't really know.
Well, it's beautiful smarm, Dave.
That's all I'm saying.
It's smarmalicious.
Well, thank you.
Um, I've never heard such a smarmy triacly.
I'm sorry.
I was wondering about your students.
Do you have many students now in the, um, well, what's the name of the post that you're
offering?
Oh, yeah.
The How to run your own cult.
How to run your own mind control cult.
Do's and don'ts.
The first do is don't.
Uh, and some of them aren't.
Some of them said, okay, I'm not gonna do the class assignment and create my own cult
weil ich ihnen gesagt habe, dass sie nicht.
Aber viele von ihnen sind Kulteure.
Es gibt 45 Schüler.
Und es gibt noch keinen Grund,
nicht zu signen.
Alle Materialien werden bis Januar sein.
Es gibt viele Materialien,
etwa drei Gigabyte bis jetzt.
Das ist viel.
Und das ist alles, was wir...
...nein-ein-mal-vor-geesehenes-Stuff.
Nicht nie vorher,
aber nicht seit dem vorigen Jahr.
Nicht mal gesehen.
Und nicht wertvoll gesehen.
Ich glaube, viele würden das auch.
Hat das ein Problem gewesen?
Muss ich wirklich alle Rezepte
von 1980 für Audio-Tapes sehen?
Wenn du das Mädchen-Band
Falsche Beweise sehen willst...
Was du auch sehen kannst,
sind die Läufer
von den verrückten
Weirdo-Artisten
und seltsamen Leuten.
Ich habe alle Läufer von Ken Kesey
von den Merry Pranksters gefunden,
die
eigentlich verraten haben,
dass der starke Fist so groß und dick geworden ist.
Das war unser Kirchenmagazin.
Er wurde so groß,
dass er es in einer Session
von Exkremeditation nicht mehr lesen konnte.
Das ist nicht necessarily eine schlechte Sache.
Für ihn war es schlecht.
Wir haben uns viel zu ernst genommen.
Er denkt, es ist eine Exkremeditation.
Du lachtest.
Aber er...
Er ist noch einer, der gestorben ist.
Es gibt so viele, die gestorben sind.
Sie waren alle meine.
Ich habe eine Menge Läufer von Robert Crumb gefunden,
die ich als lebender Gott gedacht habe.
Er war wie mein Hero.
Und hier war er,
mir Fan-Läufer zu senden.
Das war es.
Sie waren und sie waren nicht.
Er ist so ein zynischer Bastard,
dass er basically sagt,
du handelst diese kleine Celebrität
ziemlich gut.
Nächstes Mal wirst du sehen,
dass sie alle
die letzten Jahre sind.
Es ist alle alt.
Dann beginnen sie,
und sie fangen an,
dich über deinen Sexismus und Rassismus
und jede andere kleine Sache zu verbreiten,
die sie in deinen alten Comics finden.
Oder was auch immer.
Und dann bist du nur ein Niemand
und du bist depressiv.
Also hast du all das noch vor dir.
Es war eigentlich sehr gute Hinweise.
Es kam alles in Ordnung.
Was für eine krummige Art,
um seinen Punkt zu überwinden.
Krummig?
Ah, schau mal,
das ist alles, was es geht.
Es ist schrecklich.
Er ist eigentlich,
wie er sich in den Comic-Strips depiziert,
was ziemlich krank ist.
Er hat mich informiert,
dass es noch keine gute Musik gab,
die seit den 30er und 40er Jahren
Es gibt viele solche Leute
in den Lucid Island-Mitglieden.
Von ihnen.
Von diesen vier oder fünf.
Wir denken an Harvey Pekar
und seine Liebe für den alten Wax.
Krumm ist Teil eines Kultes.
Es ist ein Kult.
Sie haben einen Kult von Leuten,
die franke,
die auf Greyhound-Busse mit Karten
und so weiter.
Und es gibt nur drei Rekorde in dieser Karte.
Und...
Das ist...
Na, sie machen das immer noch.
Der große Subgenius Nenslo
ist immer noch da,
zu hassen und zu kranken und zu gräben.
Und...
zu verbreiten.
Und zu verbreiten.
Es gab so viel Sachen damals.
Und es gibt so viel Sachen jetzt.
Und es macht mich wundern,
wo all das Ganze geht,
wenn es so viel ist.
Ich habe gesehen, wo es geht.
Du stirbst,
und es wird geschlagen,
die meisten davon.
Es wird ausgestattet.
Die normalen Dinge,
wie Künstler,
werden ausgestattet.
Aber all deine wirklich guten Bücher
und Comic-Bücher
und die Rekorde,
die dir am meisten wert sind,
und all deine Snapshots,
werden in den Regen verbracht.
Das ist nur,
wenn du von deiner Familie
ausgestrahlt wirst.
Oh, gib mir einen Break.
Guck dir an,
was meine armen Kinder
durchgehen werden,
wenn sie mein Gebiet
aussteigen.
Sie werden nicht
all deine kulturellen Sachen
in den Regen verlassen.
Ich kann dir das sagen.
Ich hoffe,
dass ein Penalty...
Tisch, tisch, tisch.
Ein Penalty...
Habe ich das gesagt?
Das ist kein echter Wort.
Das ist eine Art Phrase.
Ich hoffe,
dass ein Penalty...
Ich bin wirklich sorry.
...einem Zeitpunkt in der Geschichte,
wo die 1930er,
40er,
50er,
60er,
70er,
80er,
90er,
2000er und so weiter,
und all das
Kutting-Edge-Stuff
alle auf einmal da ist.
Also hörst du
King Oliver
oder jemanden,
und am gleichen Zeit
hörst du etwas anderes.
Und es ist
beide neu
am gleichen Zeitpunkt.
Ich bin sorry,
dass ich das gesagt habe.
Was auch immer.
Nun.
Nun...
Wünsche,
Träume,
wenn Wünsche
Fisch waren.
Oh,
wenn ich nur
Zeit zurücknehmen könnte
und das Wort
wegnehmen würde,
würde ich...
Du kannst nicht
das eine sagen,
aber du könntest sagen,
Zeit ist wie
ein Wart in einem Bottle.
Das ist anders.
Ich weiß.
Ich habe eine
viel schlechteren Sache gesagt.
Zeit...
Ich bin so entschuldigt.
Prinzessin Wade
hat sich
abschließend
besessen.
Du machst es
immer schlimmer
und schlimmer
und schlimmer.
Jetzt werden alle
sagen,
oh Gott,
ich muss die Tape
zurück spielen
und sehen,
was für
schreckliche,
schreckliche Dinge
sie gesagt hat.
Tisch,
tisch,
tisch.
Wir könnten
einen Anruf
für
WCSB
Zukunftsärzte
stellen,
die
kommen,
um sich
zu übernehmen.
Denn wenn sie
nicht kommen,
werden wir
einfach
wegschlagen,
Freunde.
Ich glaube,
wir sollten
ein Ending
machen.
Wann ist das Zeit?
Ja, es ist das Zeit.
Es ist Zeit
für Dr. Sinister's Show.
Es ist das Zeit.
Das Zeit-Maschine.
Zeit.
Und wir werden
unsere rickete
kleine Zeitmaschine
anbinden,
mit Platinorite
über die Främe
und
wieder einmal
drücken
den Lever
und
flicken
durch
das Zeit
selbst.
Jetzt geht
das Joystick
da.
Ja, das stimmt.
Jetzt drücken wir es
zurück in die Linke.
Nein, nein, nein.
Wir gehen
in die falsche Richtung.
Wir sind in der
anderen Zeitreise.
Er kommt
in die Zukunft.
Oh, nein.
Das ist der
gefährliche Wast.
Ja, du wirst
aus diesem Welt.
Du wirst leben.
Topsy-Turvy-Leib.
Kein anderer Mann
hat jemals gelebt.
Nicht morgen,
nicht nächstes Jahr,
aber manchmal
bevor das Jahr 2000.
Bis zum Jahr 2000.
wird dieses
unglaubliche Event
stattfinden.
Und jetzt
wirst du Teil davon sein.
Wir werden
über den Horizont
unserer Zeit
fliegen, um die
größte menschliche
Erfahrung aller Zeiten zu sein.
Chef, glaub mir.
Du bist in der
Zeit, als Jimmy
zurückkommt.
Was hält er auf?
Du weißt, dass ich
nicht arbeiten kann
ohne Smack.
Chef.
Verrückt.
Dieser Junge
weiß, dass ich
Smack mag.
Und er weiß, dass ich
auch.
Besser niemals.
Und Candy Sweep.
Hier bin ich.
Junge Mann,
du bist verletzt.
Aber,
ich glaube,
wir alle
auf Smack
stimmen.
Richtig.
Leute,
nicht Smack
kriegen.
3.15 Uhr
und Frank und ich
sind zurück auf Stage 2.
Wir haben mit Bob gesprochen
und haben die gleiche
Geschichte von ihm bekommen.
Bobs Finger wurden
genommen und sie
haben die, die
auf dem Lampen
gefunden wurden, gematcht.
An diesem Punkt
gab es die Möglichkeit,
dass Bob nicht
ein Unfall war.
Ja.
Nein, nein.
Würdest du
freie Geld,
Geld,
gut.
Geld.
Freie Geld.
Du brauchst keine Bildung.
Du kannst Geld machen.
Geld.
Freie Geld.
Geh.
Geld.
Nicht schnell.
Also,
Verlangen.
Nicht kümmern.
Jetzt.
Es gibt Menschen,
dass etwas Mysteries
in der Südengland lebt.
Wo immer es
Lake Monsters gibt,
gibt es Leute
wie dieses.
Lokale,
Besucher,
Wissenschaftler und
Befragte, die sich
für Lake Monsters
bewegen.
Es gibt einen Mann,
der einen Lake Monster
unterstützt.
Ich fühle mich
geblasen.
So
lange.
Die neue Serie
von Broadcasts
mit dem weltweit
berühmten
Detektiv
Sean Markle.
Ich habe
Christoph
Wiener von
Stardust
gegeben,
dass er
in den
Kontrauten
geblieben ist.
Geheimlich
habe ich
gelacht, dass er
in der
und in der
Runde
und dass er
das
so
geliebt hat.
Schiff,
Schiff.