Dr. Howell is here in the studio with me.
I am with you.
He is with us all.
Hopefully, Dave will be calling in.
I'm going to play a little bit.
This will be a bit of a mystery.
Mystery?
First off...
Music?
Let's see.
Let's do a proper monster movie background.
I am seeking information about Bob.
Bob, let us see what is on the radio.
You're listening to PR News.
No, I don't think I can accept that program.
Nor that one.
Yes, she is.
Powerful.
Smart.
So, uh, come on, come on.
You won't believe your eyes.
You've never seen anything like this outside of a circus freak sideshow.
Except at other X-Days and the devotional.
And other performance venues that have featured the Mutant Mountain Boys.
Or other subgenies.
Or other dance systems.
This is a good dance number, so, come on up.
You get enough of that frop and it becomes plaid grass after a while.
Let me tell you.
You should try frop salts.
Gives you human munchies.
That makes good head cheese.
That makes good ass taffy.
And wanted me to raise you up to Sparrow.
Yeah, I know we love that.
laughing, having fun, everyone's going to parties, laughing, having fun, everything's
fucked up and it's all coming down.
It takes a worried man to sing a worried song, it takes a worried man to sing a worried song,
I'm worried now but I won't be worried long.
I don't know what's going on in the world these days, I don't know what's going on in
the world these days, everything's fucked up and it's all coming down.
Seems like everyone's got everything turned around, seems like everyone's got everything
turned around.
They're all going to parties, laughing, having fun, everything's fucked up and it's all coming down.
They just don't care about their fellow man.
It takes a worried man to sing a worried song, it takes a worried man to sing a worried song,
I'm worried now but I won't be worried long.
Like an ostrich eating pizza with his head stuck in the sand.
Don't you know it takes a worried man, it takes a worried man to sing a worried song,
it takes a worried man to sing a worried song, I'm worried now but I won't be worried long.
I'm worried now but I won't be worried long.
Always sugar Możicek kelling man.
When you're worried, he may have a organizing heed to your worries.
It makes us sound Straßen dell.
Disclaimer.
The mutant mountain boys, and their during Neghatma on this background.
But the mutant mountain boys do not represent the opinions of this station, or any other
station.
But they do of The subgenius foundation, which is okay.
that doesn't give a shit.
And with that, friends,
the Hour of Slack is now giving way
to the following show.
Insert show name here.
Dr. Sinister's Radio Synesthesia.
And the biggest change that's going to happen
is we'll change seats and headphones.
We might change seatings to...
By the way, this next day was marked by my headphones.
Finally, right?
I've had these headphones.
Oh, nigh on to 100 million years.
And finally, this very afternoon.
Oh, that is sad that Reverend Stang's
mighty headphones broke.
Well, they sort of work with the cushioning.
The cushioning part now falls out of both sides.
You're not supposed to put on them.
The cushiony part is held onto my head just by spring.
You shouldn't have been making whoopee with those cushions.
You might want to pause to change discs.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
We're going to change some discs.
We'll be back in just a few minutes.
No, not my discs. Stop.
I ruptured one.
At least something got ruptured this next day.
Well, there's always next year.
From PR News in Washington,
I'm Karen Thria,
astronauts to the International Space Station,
including Egypt's army chief.
Secretary of State Hillary Clinton
has left about two weeks ago
and died this morning.
Yesterday, she met with PR News in Washington.
PR's PR News.
PR News.
Gross.
And disgust.
President Obama says he's frustrated
that this is PR News from Washington.
Now, I make all such stories.
You know, now that the world is ending
and starvation will be rampant among the survivors,
I think it's important to let people know
that both cats and dogs have scent glands near the anus.
And when you're skinning and gutting a cat or a dog for dinner,
make sure and remove that scent gland
because that will spoil the meat.
And, of course, you don't want to penetrate the intestines either.
Right.
You can keep the mud bug vein in there if you want.
I mean, that's up to your own particular taste.
That's different from mammals.
There's a lot of things you have to do right
when you're gutting a deer or a rabbit.
There is more than one way to skin a cat.
Right.
And what are they?
There's a wrong way and a right way.
And the wrong way involves spewing all that scent gland
all over the meat.
I'm going to be one of the vegans now.
Or the gallbladder.
The gallbladder.
You must be careful not to punch at the gallbladder.
I would never do that.
Poison the meat.
The gallbladder or the branches.
Yes, the ureters.
Then there are those urethra-fractic records
which we were playing so recently.
To understand death,
you must make love to life in the gallbladder.
Yes, some say.
I'm very confused now.
I was hearing about gallbladders
at the same time airplanes were flying
and I knew that that had something to do with X-Day.
All planes are flying.
The planes are in the air.
The missiles are in the air.
Hallelujah.
The fighter jets have scrambled.
The balloon has gone up.
But soon they will be scrambled like eggs.
Yes.
You mean like us?
Good eggs.
The death rays shall be like whisks.
Mm-hmm.
Hello, you're on the air.
All shall be scrambled.
This was the theory of the egg-worshipping albuminites.
They are the egg men.
Cuckoo-cuckoo-choo.
We got another caller here.
All right, let's have it.
Oh, man.
Hello, you're on the air.
Is it a Google phone or a real phone?
How you guys doing?
Welcome on the show.
Are you there?
Yes, we are here.
We are here in more ways than one.
Oh, um...
This is Zane calling from Leviathan.
State short question.
I'm sorry, this is who?
Leviathan?
Zane, if you'm calling from Leviathan.
Leviathan.
That sea beast, Leviathan,
which god of all his works created hugest,
Leviathan.
Swim the ocean stream.
So he says he is?
Or out.
You believe you are sane.
It is.
But how do you really know?
On the Norway foam.
If you were not sane, would you know?
The pilot of some small night-shandled skiff
dealing some island.
Do not adjust your headset.
As seaman tells.
This is how it's supposed to sound.
With fixed anchor in his scaly rind,
moors by his side,
under the wind,
while night invests the sea.
And wish it more delays.
If I have something super, super big
that might change our realities,
as we know it.
My doctrine, I'd have no hell.
Would, uh...
I've decided to sit back and...
It's all passive.
It's all...
Not all.
A message.
Almost all.
I can prove that they're almost common.
But not quite.
If not commonest, probably homosexual.
Almost all?
No, all.
Right here in my hand, I have a paper with the names of those individuals.
Now here's the thing.
Some of them are not common.
Some of them have been together.
Some of them have been living together.
Is there any way you can get a free will?
Some are born to sweet delight.
Hey, let's all talk at once.
It's the man with two voice boxes.
Some are born...
Can you believe this freakish monster?
...to endless night.
The rudest thing on earth.
Hi folks, I'm Garly.
Millpup has reached, researching a guy named Charlie Five Tongues today.
Oh my gosh, is this Bob Bob?
Charlie Pryde, he was a country and western star.
He was a poet...
Bob will be here soon.
Bob is coming.
Again and again.
Oh my gosh.
Look in the dictionary, under coming, it says C, Bob Dobbs.
J-R Bob Dobbs.
Uh oh.
Uh oh indeed.
Uh oh, SpaghettiOs.
We've got another call here.
Everybody talk at once.
You're out of the air.
There's a dead armadillo under me.
All right, Big Johnson.
On Bob's bumper, he hid it far and square.
Where's the dog?
We're here.
Big Johnson.
I do not care if he drives by, cause me and old Bob Dobbs, he just don't care.
Whoa, hold on, hold on, hold up, hold up, hold up, hold up, hold up.
Everybody hold up.
I believe Big Johnson had something to say about...
Okay, okay.
She was born with...
She was a woman...
I think she's from England or the UK.
No, I haven't.
She's pretty good looking, you know?
It's pretty tragic that she was born with two vaginas.
You said she was born with two vaginas?
Okay, not only was Charlie Five Tongues...
That is a story I've heard.
Charlie Five vaginas or Charlie Four vaginas?
No, just two.
But the odd part is that they were working vaginas.
They had all the reproductive organs to have babies.
So she had two wombs as well and four ovaries.
Two sets of ovaries, all that stuff, two cervix.
Peggy's mother has two wombs.
Sounds like a good breeding stock.
Oh, God!
I've got three penises!
A womb with a view.
I thought I had a chance!
Finally!
Oh, my God!
How would a person have two ovaries if that's twice as many as you'd have to have four?
She actually had to lose her virginity twice.
One in each, you know why.
Speaking of which, portions of the following...
Portions?
Yeah, portions of the following broadcast will be objectionable to some members of the
audience, which is why we advise listener discretion.
The views and opinions expressed on this program are not necessarily those of WCSB or Cleveland
State University.
Take no portions here.
This is Synesthesia on WCSB Cleveland.
We've got our guests here.
Dr. Howell, Princess Wee Ardo, and Reverend Ivan Stang.
We've got Lonesome Cowboy Dave on the line.
We've got Dr. Zeronius.
We've got Big Johnson, the notorious PNG.
It's a natural story.
I'm not making it up.
She refused $1 million to do a porn.
She was offered $1 million to do a...
She should have offered many vaginas.
If I got one of my peni amputated, maybe I'd have a chance with her.
No, Terry, you're already married.
Sorry.
You're claiming credit for multiple peni now.
Yeah, but I think...
Welcome to the PNG.
You're a party dove.
You've got three, but your wife owns two of them.
I think Princess Wee Ardo is in trouble because this woman has two vaginas.
No, I'm not in trouble.
I think Reverend Ivan Stang will be leaving you for that woman with two vaginas.
It'll be headlines.
Dr. Reverend Ivan Stang marries woman with two vaginas from the UK.
Well, Ivan Stang, man with three peni, marries woman with two vaginas.
Still leaving her quite satisfied with her friends.
Actually.
She'll have a wife for each penis.
Then a husband for each penis.
For each vagina, for that matter.
There's actually, there's three in the center.
Of what?
Of several rings of them, but I don't know that we're supposed to go into that kind of detail.
With this ring, I thee worship.
Don't be divulging secrets like that.
Come on.
With my body, I thee worship.
And with all my worldly goods, I thee endow.
And by the science of Heaton, I pleasure my wife.
And by the science of Heaton, I pleasure myself daily.
Now, lizards have dual, or hemi-peni, don't they?
They do, but it is essentially one that is divided into two.
And this was also common among the dinosaurids.
Then there is the phallic Ouroboros.
The phallic Ouroboros.
The worm-eating itself.
The pair of phalli that appear to be eating themselves.
More interesting was the necessary sexual differentiation between the two types of the largest sauropods.
How likely is that to happen?
Somebody born with two sets of sexual organs that are the same?
Well, they might be happier than some of us.
Well, I don't know how many times has it happened.
Actually, it never happens that they're born with sets of sexual organs from both sexes at once.
Never, ever, ever.
Which bathroom did they use?
Huh?
The headgear is ours.
The girl screamed when they saw it.
The hermaphrodite used the boys' room.
Yeah.
See, that's male privilege right there.
I didn't lie. I laughed.
But every privilege carries with it a responsibility.
A responsibility.
I was like, what the heck is a girl doing in a guy in an immense locker room?
And then somebody whispered to me, she's a hermaphrodite.
And I'm leaving.
I said, I only thought I heard about that.
You had to run in terror.
I thought I only heard about that stuff in fairy tales.
Are you afraid of hermaphrodites?
Hermaphrodite.
With great genitals comes great responsibility.
I'm acting as if he never read the satirical Gaius Petronius Arbiter.
You know, we are, the world is enriched by all things bizarre.
That's true.
But did you know that the human fetus is actually born a female?
Yes.
And then it becomes a male.
Did you know that, Sinister?
I did know that.
But it's not born a female again if it's not.
What's funny is the Y chromosome is shorter than the X chromosome.
It's got less interweaving.
Yeah, but it's like three months older than the person becomes a male at three months.
Likes long walks in the moonlight.
If they're a male, they turn into a male at three months.
As each of the genes express themselves, eventually it runs out of options.
You didn't know that they become a male at three months?
Otherwise, your X chromosome is going to be a female.
I learned that in kindergarten, but go on.
I think embryos look tasty.
They kind of look like shrimp.
So if you have three X's, that means you're going to be a serial killer.
I think that's what they were born to do.
If you're four and you get some ziet
theyev
They held her down and they gave her some drug and the baby came out in like five minutes and was dead.
Wait, what?
They forced an abortion on a woman in China.
They forced it.
They held her down and they shot her up with a needle and the baby came out in five minutes and was dead.
They tried to do that with J.R. Bob Dobbs when he was in the womb, but it backfired.
They couldn't kill him.
They held his mother down in a Kansas cornfield and waited for a tornado to come along.
That was the only thing powerful enough to yank that infant fetus Dobbs out.
Bob's out.
And yet he survived.
Isn't that amazing?
Bob is an abortion survivor and that is why abortion is legal in the Church of the Subgenius up until the 15th year.
Because they've got more than a fighting chance.
Because any fetus that gets aborted doesn't deserve to live if it doesn't survive.
Right.
Bob was only a cluster of cells when this happened.
And yet when his mother saw the aborted tiny baby.
She loved him so much that she decided to keep him.
Well, it just gets crazy up in here all over the place.
And Wisteria campgrounds getting hit by tornadoes and firestorms and all sorts of earthquakes.
No.
No, just the opposite.
Everything around Wisteria is getting hit.
Honest.
It's the veritable bunker of the situation.
Yes, Zeronius.
In fact, I've been having...
Of course, I'm going to be driving into this disaster area tomorrow.
And the fact is, while Pomeroy and Athens are without power and all the pink cities around there, Cincinnati and Columbus, everything's shut down.
Wisteria still has power and water.
It is as if X-Day...
It's a preview.
It is an X-Day preview to show the rest of the unbelieving world.
It's a preview, Ben.
One final...
One final chance offered to them.
It had to stay for the wedding.
Otherwise, it couldn't have had the wedding.
The marriage of Cadmus and Harmony.
Yes.
This holy matrimony between these two fine mutants shall not be aborted.
Certainly not.
Not on our watch.
Why abort acrimony?
If you have multiple organs, you should have multiple organs.
It's an auspicious omen for this day.
For us, gentlemen.
It's an oasis of wellness.
That's funny.
I'm used to suspicious omens.
Just can't bust an argumentative animal.
Oh, man.
You're on the air.
I was wondering, that woman with the two vaginas, if she had a theme song, would it be God Save the Queef?
Oh, good God.
That would be fascinating.
Nanny Mae Derendinger.
Isn't that the woman that we're talking about?
Nanny Mae Derendinger?
Yes, she was...
Well, now, this woman really exists or didn't, though.
More than...
I mean, I haven't.
Did this woman really exist?
And this is a true story.
It's not just a thing going on.
Nanny Mae Derendinger.
Dreams can come true, my friend.
Write the Google words in and read her tale.
The sad story.
Oh, I saw it.
I did see it.
I'm sorry.
And so you see, nothing human is alien to me.
Ni hil humanum alienum me puto.
I embrace all mutants.
And weirdos.
Fervently and enthusiastically.
They may shave my...
What?
Are you complaining?
There's going to be a lot more.
That was a pardon.
Bracing, sir.
That was not at all invasive.
That was a loving act of spirituality.
And great significance.
Much like licking on that frog stuff.
One doesn't lick it.
Well, you still...
I know.
How many times do I have to say?
It must be squirted, dried, and smoked, all right?
Right.
And then smoked with great...
Poison yourself.
It's not my fault.
I'm not giving that information out.
I'm taking pains to explain that one does not lick a Colorado river tome.
That's actually the only way I've ever had that.
And, uh...
But I didn't do the harvesting myself.
How many licks does it take to get to the psychedelic center...
...of a Colorado river?
The psychedelic experience of cardiac arrest.
How many licks does it take you to get to the psychedelic center?
The psychedelic center, that's about two blocks down and on the left.
Hey, your Colorado river toad fell into my Australian cane toad.
Boy, this is good.
And that's how it gets there.
United again at once.
Let's cooperate.
Where do you go when you're toad away?
Let's learn the five C's of cooperation.
Castration.
Conviviality.
Candiru fish.
Your candiru fish fell into my California condor.
Ouch!
Speaking of the candiru fish...
The candiru condor on the line.
We might as well, since you introduced the subject.
I was told by...
...a little bit more authority than Dr. Pete Goldie...
...that that whole story of the candiru was simply...
...a bull and didn't really exist and there was no such fish...
...and it didn't swim up the human...
I was told that.
And then I found out, no, the story is not only true, not only absolutely true...
...but they had a guy and they made a video, which I watched, of the extraction of this thing...
...and they put a special camera on the end of a...
...flexible catheter-like tube.
I don't even have one!
They showed, you know, they had to cut the little fish to pieces to extract it...
...because it's backward-pointing gills.
And these things swim in the pond at Wisteria.
They shouldn't be here in the upper...
Supposedly they can't exist except in tropical waters.
But remember, invasive species are moving all over the place as a result of climate change.
Not to mention invasive feces.
In the Amazon, the natives go into the water...
...completely naked except for a special sheath on their peenies.
This sheath is to keep the candiru from worming its way in.
It is the only vertebrated animal that parasitizes on man.
Look it up with the search words...
...vandelia cirrhosa.
The word candiru is of native...
Is cirrhosa spelled like cirrhosis?
Uh, C-I-R-R-H.
The result of a cut-up...
R-O-S-A, I believe.
So there's...
Even if you misspelled it, it would still come up.
It would say, do you mean...
The intertubes are so smart these days.
So I could type in candiru cam.
So Pete Goldie's rational-sounding thing that it was all bullshit...
...was, in fact, proven wrong by this damn video.
The hook was the hook.
And it was a guy who survived the operation.
And he was the one who was peeing and who was invaded by a candiru.
So is it related to the salmon?
Because it swims upstream?
It swims...
It is a vampire.
And it looks for fish also to parasitize anything.
It follows the current.
The current flowing through the gills of a fish...
...and out from the operculum, the gill cover.
It swims up that stream.
It fastens its little teeth under the gill cover...
...and it drains the fish dry.
But it also swims up the stream from a human urethra...
...which its little sensor detects as being the same thing.
If you pee underwater, it cannot, as others have reported...
...swim upstream.
If you swim up a pee stream...
...if you're standing at the edge of the water...
...that is pure invention.
Ah, well, you know.
Candiru.
It's all part of nature's plan.
Well, with that cover, it makes you wonder why Noah put him on the ark.
But...
Hey, why'd God make a fish so small you can't eat it?
Yeah, how about that?
Why'd he make a lamprey-like creature...
...that could crawl right up your...
...urethra like that?
Because you've been sinful, kids.
God is a sick, twisted monster.
Well, we know he's somewhat senile after all his eons of...
The mind of God was damaged during the Big Bang.
He's sort of been resting on his laurels for some time.
He no longer directly interferes.
It doesn't matter why.
It matters what next, now that you've got a spiny thing...
...floating in your...
All right.
Here's something more about that.
It is actually being digested by the prairie squid.
Since you are asking.
When the candiru was originally reported, it was thought to be a hoax.
And in 1913, German missionaries in the area found that it did happen.
And they treated the candiru going up the penis by immediate amputation...
...in the missionary hospitals there.
And only later did it determine that the natives know of something...
...which, if they chew...
...will cause the candiru just to drop out.
But, unfortunately, that wasn't the German missionary way of doing things.
This was in some book that I read years and years ago by...
The missionary position.
...Villy Lay or somebody like that.
Made the missionary position impossible.
Author of Exotic Zoology.
Although he was a German rocketry expert, he also wrote these other books.
He debunked many legends of many fabulous creatures...
...which it would be nice to believe in.
Like the cannibal tree.
That consumes human victims and so forth.
Oh, wow.
Yeah, that one.
I hated to lose the cannibal tree.
How can that be?
I've seen that in that movie, The Lost World.
It just about ate that Indian girl up.
Oh, it's vividly described in the hoaxy accounts.
But weren't gorillas considered to be fabulous creatures?
They were.
They were thought not to be real.
But surely they have been known before.
The word orangutan.
Comes from the Malay term meaning, you know, forest person.
Forest man.
Orangutan.
Yes, forest man.
Now, Dr. Howell, do you happen to know when...
Which is also where the 20 o'clock recording came from.
...the gorilla was positively identified as existing?
No, I don't.
Because I think it was...
You say 1873?
No, I was just kidding.
Well, that would be amusing because it would be so late.
Man, there's some loud...
Somebody's really mad.
...singling a microphone, and it isn't me.
That's erroneous.
I can tell.
He's handling a microphone heavy-handed.
You can tell by the smell.
With sweaty hands.
The reason I ask is...
Sorry, I fell asleep.
That Zane Grave novel I was reading,
one of the villains was constantly being referred to as gorilla-like.
The heroine kept thinking...
By the characters in the novel?
He's like a gorilla.
And I thought, well, now, wait a minute.
This novel takes...
This novel takes place in the 1870s.
Did they even know what a gorilla was?
I think they'd heard of them.
They hadn't seen them, yeah.
So what expedition, if any, said, hey, that's a gorilla.
That's...
There's one for sure.
The Greystoke expedition.
The ill-fated Greystoke family expedition.
Well, those...
First of all, those weren't gorillas.
And secondly...
That's not true.
I actually think the expedition to find Dr. Livingstone.
Didn't they make...
I presume.
Uh, identifications of gorillas?
A gorilla, I presume?
That had never been seen before.
Now, the great apes that reared Lord Greystoke are not gorillas.
They are a type of apes called...
I knew that.
I'm not ignorant.
Yes, I know.
But just to point this out...
Did you hear about the chimps in the zoo who...
They are apes, but not gorillas.
This one chimpanzee in a zoo actually killed one of the babies in the...
Yes, I read that.
While a crowd watched.
Well, first of all...
Well, anybody in a cage is a prisoner and will exhibit pathological behavior we shouldn't blame him or his species for.
Secondly, even in the wild, sometimes the males do kill the infants.
It has been observed in the wild.
In fact, this almost happened to Tarzan when he was adopted by his adoptive ape mother, Kala.
She defended him from a male who wanted to kill him.
And her own baby had been destroyed by such a male.
Well, creed on the case of the...
Creed on the...
No to him.
Absolutely.
Tarzan.
Yes.
But in the case of the one in the zoo, it was obvious it was making a statement.
They returned the dead baby to the mother.
This is not going to be much of a life for you, son, so...
They kill the offspring of another male.
Right.
Unfortunately, it's part of their genetic strategy.
So their line will continue.
Right.
So their own genes will get the...
I agree.
It seems very selfish.
Maybe there was something personal going on.
I do the same thing.
If it turned out there's a dead cat on the line, I'd probably drown that baby in the well.
Still do it in China.
That's right.
Well, now they have the ultrasound.
They can really be selective.
And they can tell if it's been somebody with extra organs, too.
And that's next on the list.
So the apes that raised Tarzan have gone extinct, right?
Unless they still exist somewhere in Central Africa.
It would have to be in the Congo Basin because they couldn't possibly exist.
They're not existing anywhere else.
Most of the bush animals are now gone.
That used to be...
Well, you can still get them in restaurants in Paris.
Bush meat.
They are not...
You can get your spiny echidna in finer places in Paris.
Oh, yes.
Well, if you're rich enough, you can order a whooping crane with a side of century plant salad.
But for most of us, it grows more and more difficult to find these exotic animals.
And that's why we're here today.
We're here to talk about the
We're here to talk about the most interesting and most interesting things in the world.
I stepped out for a bottle of milk and it turned out to be tacos and beer.
After all, I'm sorry.
I missed out on most of what you guys said for the last two minutes.
Did I make a sound?
We were simply discussing.
You said you were making a sound.
Certain native customs.
Every time you unzip your pants and do that thing, it makes a really loud noise for those of us listening on the phone.
I'm sorry about that.
It's the effect your voices have on me.
Though I may not register the words, I certainly get a certain feeling.
You need to unclip the lavalier from your zipper area and put it up by your collar or something that's not being used so much.
I've been donning...
I've been donning a Dremel tool in the place of a zipper handle.
Life is but a Dremel.
That's not what you're hearing.
All you listeners who haven't called it yet, get your hands out of your pants and call us at 215-9-0-4-5-6-6-6.
This is a once-a-year opportunity.
Actually, we'll get to this next week, too.
Get your hands out of your pants and call us at 215-9-0-4-5-6-6-6.
We'll return to the zoo story in a moment.
Some of you may know that Reverend Lucy Van Pelt and I couldn't be here last year because we had a shop.
We have a store now called Used On Due in Weirdsville, and we sell books and records.
I had a girl come into the store the other day, and I got a great big bob in the window of my store.
And this girl comes in, and she goes,
Hey, mister, do you sell those displays that you have in your window?
And I said, What's the display?
I don't have display in the window.
And I'm thinking, Oh, that's right.
I've got Bob on my window.
And I said, Do you know who Bob is?
She goes, No, I don't know who Bob is.
And I said, Well, you know what?
You don't have $10,000 to buy this bob head that's in my window.
So buy something else out of my store, and that will help Bob out.
And she said, Well, I don't have $10,000.
And she left, and I was really kind of pissed.
It's like, well, we told her to go to subgenius.com, so she may be one of those pinks that go on there and look and not understand what the fuck is going on.
The pinks who are unwilling to pay the price of slack.
The price of slack.
The price.
Of Bob.
The price of slack.
The price.
Of Bob.
Of slack.
Oh, I want to let everybody know that there will be probably more.
Let me see what we got.
One, two, three, four, five.
This is the five fisted tails of Connie.
The only way you can get our music is through subgenius.com, and you've got to get a hold of Reverend Ivan Stang to do such.
And I know you want our stuff.
The price of slack.
Because it's really fucking good.
Or bad, if you will.
The price of slack.
You're going to go to sleep tonight thinking the price of slack.
You'll wake up in the morning and go, I need more slack.
I need your money, the money, the money of myoi.
I just want to make wine.
I don't have any.
You're more than making founder's money.
I mean, there would be some geek out there.
You just failed, vermong feeling like aorund belle
If, if you were still here, I would say that.
You know you're part of the law
worry vídeos
We're just talking about the people that are Shaft over you.
So, proud.
I'm out.
You tripped over your bass.
Yeah, well, it's not mine.
It's Styx, so.
You tripped over Styx bass.
Normally I loop it around because, you know, I know those Amino guys,
and I try not to, you know, they'll end up stepping on something.
Hey, does anybody want to play drums?
I mean, you have to kind of know a little bit about them to get up here and play.
Not like, oh, my God, I wanted to play drums since I was seven.
Actually, we're Styx.
Nobody would buy me a set of drums.
Styx.
We're playing musical fucking chairs is what we're doing.
Thank you for the inspiration for the new song.
The deck chairs of the Titanic.
That's the next song.
That was so last year.
So pull your wallet out of your pants in the Praise Bob Dance.
Yeah.
An epic tale of love and fun.
Fear.
The zoo story.
Hi, I'm Dorothy Baxter from the New Education Foundation.
Hi, Dorothy.
And what you've just been listening to is an example of alternative radio
and what it can mean to you and your students.
Today, now more than ever, children need to learn the right things.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Barbara became Barbara.
Oh, Dorothy.
It's been so long.
Yeah, yeah.
Some things happen along the way, honey.
What have you learned, Dorothy?
Well, I learned that a sex change operation can affect more than your mammary glands.
It can actually deepen your voice.
It can deepen your perception in many situations.
I happen to have extrasensory perception now.
All that from a little nip and tuck.
What part of his real name was Dorothy?
Tuck and roll job, we call it.
A tuck and roll job.
But it lasted for longer than a week.
Believe me, it was horrible.
It was horrible.
Well, it's the opposite.
We're going to start showing the tuck and roll show on cable.
You're on the air.
Hi, I'm Tuck and I'm roll.
No, you're on the air.
That's wrong.
Hold on, rookies.
You are on the air.
No, you are on the air.
We are all on the air.
Hello.
And the rest of you people are.
I was saying you're there too, aren't you?
Please.
He's there.
He's right over there, officer.
I'm so happy to hear from you.
You're there.
The one that Margaret gave him.
Whoever that was.
Why did I call him that?
Why not?
I don't remember her that well.
Did she?
Very good show tonight.
Yeah.
Well, we're thanking you for that.
We're trying to be entertaining.
That's the biggest lie.
That is a big old lie.
All right, all right.
Let's keep it in the family.
Dr. Howe's been doing a portrait of Dr. Sinister this whole time.
Yeah, just a nervous affliction that comes over me.
Ever since the hand transplant after that terrible railroad accident.
Is that why you draw all the time?
Uh-oh.
Well, there's something in me that insists that I make these images.
Wouldn't it be cool or really great if a lot of times some of the collars,
the hat, the one they hung.
And they made that sound.
They hung up.
Neat, neat, neat.
But that was actually like happening to them somehow.
Or the room they were in just like starts.
They were actually turning into an electronic pulse.
How do we know that's not happening?
Every beep that they subjected us to, they felt profoundly.
In the abdomen.
In the groins.
In the eyes.
In the labanza.
In the great labanza.
Yep.
I'm telling you that is a vengeful fantasy.
I need a cause.
We need not be so hostile to those misguided souls.
Zeronis sounded like.
He sounded like he had one of those little lavalier mics clipped to one of his teeth.
So that every time he closed and opened his mouth, that mic would bang against a tooth.
It sounded to me, as I said, it sounded like he was doing break dancing on his chair.
On his microphone.
Talented fella.
But I wonder if this isn't.
And all beside the point since that particular color is no longer on the air with us.
But of course it's beyond the point.
And who gives?
One of them was making disjointed noises.
Another one slobbered all over the microphone.
And the best description of that was actually the tooth of the zipper sound.
Baron Von Zipper.
I remember those movies.
But, you know, when we're old.
You know.
We're probably going to give away these childish superstitions about supernatural beings that
comes and pays us for our teeth.
What?
Or even cancer.
No no.
Not even the tooth fairy.
Oh, next, you're going to tell me Bob's just beats clip art.
Well, more than clip art.
Next you're going to tell me Jesus is just some made up, composite character.
I wonder if I should spill the beans since we're so close to x day anyway.
See this bean.
He has beans.
the actual model
for the so-called made-up
clip art. You're on the radio.
A living, breathing being.
Yeah, that's right.
There's a photograph of the
Dobbs head, the original Dobbs head.
It has come to life.
Yeah, it's...
Oh, right, oh, right, oh, right.
I know they don't believe it.
They don't believe it.
Too esoteric.
Too in with the in crowd.
guitar solo
From PR News in Washington,
I'm still the slow, stifling,
powerful turkey in the largest
single explosion in South Dakota.
The state is uncertain.
PR's bad.
PR's turkey.
On Wall Street, 5722-863-1233,
Bob tells us
this is PR News.
Yes?
Mr. Dobbs purchased
another radio station.
Assuming that radio
would be in his future,
Dobbs adds yet another laurel to his long list
of achievements.
You do take medicine for schizophrenia.
Hopefully.
I hadn't heard this country before.
In the last 20 years of his life,
the most dynamic
industrial individual
with 41 hours
of tape, as much as
41 hours of tape,
secret conversations recorded.
Therefore, simple mathematics dictated
that in less than one minute
of each hour, actually, the show could
penetrate the record
population with little effort.
And so, there were
the first 20 years.
Hey, calm down, Jack.
My head's too big. Wait.
I've been piping.
Here, let me close.
I'll show you back here.
Oh, here we go.
The distant future.
Ah, yes.
The year 2000.
The distant future.
Oh, that's better.
That was a long way back, Jack.
Smaller now.
There's no show in there.
Oh, yeah, I didn't think so.
Show's over here, Doug.
Y2K.
Right here I am.
We are robots.
Okay, good.
Yeah, well, we're the robot versions of ourselves.
That's the really cool thing I was trying to tell you earlier.
There is no more.
Yeah, we don't.
We're the automatons that just keep going, even though we're robots.
Even still, we're the automaton.
Our bodies have already left for X.
Yes, for automaton.
For the other world.
Yeah.
For the outer world.
We already left a long time ago.
We keep going about this myth of X day.
But still, it's good.
Everything is so automated now.
We actually did leave.
Still, it's good, right, X day?
Yeah, we actually, our real, our earthly selves actually did leave in 1998.
It's just our robot selves that continue on this illusion.
And here we are.
And this planet is Mars.
The humans are dead.
And we're still here.
But we're just robots.
Except for a person.
Michael Jackson was a human.
It's too soon.
Sorry.
Yeah, they talked about Ali, about Michael Jackson.
But what about Ali Akbar Khan?
They look like they're dead.
They're a boss and girl.
It has to be done.
I'll just confirm that they're dead.
Okay.
So that we can have fun.
Bubbles is not dead.
I told you it was dead.
Dead.
My, but wasn't that a peculiar little excerpt from the puzzling evidence show, KPSA?
Yes, KPSA.
Stops talking.
If you go to the podcast of the nào, keep nice bro.
The other little episodes of the show BLPP came out.
They're放Queen cuatro mil things.
They're top regularúrition.
And that's what we're going to talk about on Facebook.
NYX is not doing just that.
It's something Gzb replacing.
I forgot to tell Coleman, but I know how much his Newton's
niez can do.
He's got his novo province program coming up.
It's going to be a day of his life, his lingκ LGU
house, 9 canal, yeah es po tah, and his chance to get a female mayor and a woman mayor
태
Princess Wee and I left for the big drill.
Yeah, yay drill.
And the rest was recorded there at Wisteria Campground on July 4th,
the day before the world ended.
The jam band was Several Fisted Tales of Connie with Pisces
and Reverend Angry Larry singing on the price of slack,
and I think Reverend Robin Mountain Boy on drums,
and the instrumental had Dr. Sinister on drums and other things.
And Reverend Sud Shaw played guitar, and Bishop Stick played bass, I think.
I'd have to look at the pictures, which I could do on subgenius.com
by following the events link to the 15X Day photos.
The music behind me is by Reverend DJ Two Beans,
and this show, The Hour of Slack, is from the Church of the Subgenius
at subgenius.com and many other places.
Subgenius.com.
Which, by the way, holds the uncensored versions of about a thousand episodes
of Hour of Slack in MP3 form, as well as text logs of all the tracks we play.
But now let's play a nifty instrumental not recorded at X Day,
a ditty called Mass Produced, made by the Psychoskeletons.
So, here we go.
mashup
prepare
to
die
THRONE
than
Maurice
Dia
of Thanks for watching!
Let's let Jack get a word in here.
Do you ever wonder if the cowboys from Brookback Mountain ever marched in a Charlie Pride parade?
Well, you know what pride parade?
And with that, friends, we'll sign them.
Beloved country and western entertainer, Charlie Pride.
Pride. See, there's like the Pride Parade.
And that's where all the country western singers wear all the, you know, the crazy get-up.
The more march down the street with big, large haircuts and stuff.
Nine. Conflation of two non-related things.
Everyone marched down the street, not a cowboy or country western.
Artistic synthesis, but not historically valid.
Rejected.
You are obsolete.
I agree.
Obsolete.
Bobsolete.
Call your radio.
That too.
Bobsolete.
You're obviously asleep.
A glim-glam.
Some little glimpses.
Well.
Well, don't let it get you.
Get the whim-whims.
Do you have a question for the panel tonight?
Yes, I do.
All right.
Snow Toilet, let's hear it.
How come you picked up so fast?
Because I'm just a fast kind of guy.
Oh, man.
I was expecting like 20 minutes to take.
Oh, no.
Uh-huh.
Is that the question?
We'll pick up the line, but you might not be able to get a word in.
Well, the question for the panel, then, I guess, is why did you pick up so fast?
Yeah.
Um, Dr. Howell, why did you pick up so fast?
Well, I like to be quick on the draw, and I often pick up things before other people
will even put them down.
Yes.
Hmm.
I'm Mr. Sinister.
Yeah, I, I...
Why did you pick up so fast?
Well, I...
Oh.
Well, it's, uh, it's an easy thing to pick up and a hard thing to drop.
Yeah.
Don't want to put it down, eh?
Donny, how about you?
I know, is it...
I have a bad habit.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
It always does.
See, you know, Doc, I wanted to bring something up to you, something that happened to me
today.
Okay.
I wanted to know if you'd mind this, but I don't know if I'd be able to hear it.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
See, now he's making weird noises, too.
The aliens are interfering with your translation.
You left the alien on the line.
Sorry.
Dad, I'm just getting some alien interference there.
Got me a telephone call from Jesus.
Got him on the line.
Let's hear the big question again.
De, de, de, de, de, de, de, de, de, de, de, de, de, de, de, de, de, de, de, de, de, de, de, de, de,
de, de, de, de, de, de, de, de, de.
Snow Toilet, what was your question again?
Hey, hey.
Hold on one second, one second.
He needs a second.
Okay, stop.
Okay.
All right.
Okay, stop.
I'm getting this really strange sound on my phone.
That's between your ears, Peter.
Those are the transmissions from the future.
We control the horizontal.
Yes.
We control the vertical.
It sounds like there's calibrations at all.
Whoa.
Steve.
See now that was another disseminated message.
message, the aliens
might indeed be involved
in sabotaging this broadcast.
Sabotage?
Aliens? You gotta prove it by me.
You know, we're in
with the aliens. That's what you guys
just don't seem to pick up on. I mean, we're
tight like that with these so-called
aliens. And a recent poll
said that they couldn't decide
whether they wanted Barack Obama
or Mitt Romney to deal with the
inevitable alien landing.
Yes. And here was what I wanted
to bring up back. Okay.
Okay. So after work, I went
up to the cash register, and I
threw up an iced tea up
under that shed. It's getting confessional.
I want a pack of Arbor Lights.
She says, no.
I says, why?
She says, because you need to quit.
Is that fair?
That kind of sounds like a pharmacist
who won't give out birth control.
The nanny state.
Exercise.
Using her freedom of conscience
on the job. It's a bit codependent,
if you ask me.
I mean,
one exists because of the illusion of a previous
one. That's why I can't work in a convenience store.
Meet the public.
All right, folks.
It looks like we're about out of time here.
Oh, thank God. Oh, thank God.
Now we're going away.
Oh, Jesus.
But we'll be back.
Yes. Stay tuned.
We've got a big steaming pile of crap coming down the pike.
I hope we're not back.
We'll be broadcasting from Planet X next week.
Yeah.
Until next time.
Beware of the saucers.
Beware.
Repent.
The end is here.
Until then, keep it surreal.
Wooden nickels.
You know, the Mutant Mountain Boys,
this will be their first performance at X-Day,
but I've seen them at the,
annual devotionals,
why, nigh on to every year since
0-0-0.
At which time,
get this,
the Mutant Mountain Boys were essentially
the only girls
at the Devo convention.
Imagine the energies
focused on them.
Well,
pardon me,
at any rate, they're not the only
female yetis here.
But Tam tiring it out.
근
This is the third work we have
oneg sons.
0-5.
9.
This was one,
The local dent and mine RutENS
foll
but I miss them.
DUTY NOW FOR SLACK!
We got another new one for you.
We want to hear you singing on this one and you'll know when to come in.
Praise God.
You all know what we're talking about.
Praise Bob.
Amen.
20 years of slack and he answered me.
Praise Bob.
Amen.
All my money now Bob's gonna set me free.
And a little pledge.
Neath nuclear plan.
I often screw with friends and bread.
Old time bull dodder still lives on.
And please do cause eternal spawn.
Praise Bob.
Amen.
20 years of slack and he answered me.
Praise Bob.
Amen.
All my money now Bob's gonna set me free.
Go get me wild.
Soon day long.
Or give me slingshot.
And a little pledge.
If I am wrong.
We'll talk together and get high.
But happy gathering in the sky.
Oh joy hallelujah.
Praise Bob.
Amen.
20 years of slack and he answered me.
Praise Bob.
Amen.
All my money now Bob's gonna set me free.
And a little pledge.
He set a baby free.
Oh joy hallelujah.
Praise Bob.
Amen.
He told him I was right.
20 years of slack and he answered me.
Oh joy hallelujah.
Praise Bob.
Amen.
He found me a new home.
I said to dog.
All my money now Bob's gonna set me free.
He gonna set me free.
Let it go.
Oh joy hallelujah.
From PR News in Washington, I'm frozen and contact with Americans outlawed.
The Turkish government is accusing Syria of PR news over the Mediterranean.
The Syrian government admitted to it and has apologized.
It is unknown if they survived.
President Obama addresses a large Mitt Romney PR spad.
That's the sound of gunfire.
Last check on Wall Street, 44.
But the BBC says you're listening to PR News in Washington, D.C.
PR News, Washington.
Iraqi authorities say...
The U.N. believes a humanitarian crisis is growing.
Traumatic post-psychological suicide.
Defense Secretary Leon Panetta is urging mental health professionals
to stop PR news.
PR News in Washington.
Friends, we're glad you listened to this show.
And we're even more glad that some listeners have donated enough
to help us keep on going for another couple of months.
Not just this show, but subgenius.com and all the other archive sites.
But if you truly love Bob and want some of that slack back to rebound to you,
you should go to subgenius.com front page,
or especially the radio page, or the catalog store pages,
and help out financially as best you can.
Now, we know what it's like to be on the brink of total poverty,
and we don't want any subgeniuses to make their own situations worse.
But some of you still have jobs.
Even five bucks makes a big difference,
even if it's only once a month from enough of you.
Fifty bucks makes an even bigger difference.
All we're saying...
is that blowjobs could go the way of Steve jobs if you don't pay Dobbs.
We also take checks and money orders to Subgenius Foundation.
P.O. Box 181-417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
Thanks for anything you can do to help let there be slack.
We'll see you next time.
Subtitles by the Amara.org community