From PR News in Washington, I'm king of at least six people, most of them security guards.
I'm farting from upstate New York to Maine.
And the mayor of Boston staggers home.
Heavy wet farts.
That's been a benefit.
Farts today.
On Wall Street at this hour, 152.
The White House says that this is PR News from Washington.
The popular social networking internet website PR News has reached agreement with more than
145 sexual predators to protect $20 billion worth of weapons.
An Israeli official is supposed to fly within 125 miles of PR News in Washington.
PR comes from low-income women's and children's and families.org.
In a few generations, their legs will grow slim, their bodies thin, their tusks longer.
Goodbye.
The baby!
Finish.
Title two, directions four, inward filthy lusts.
Direction one, drink wine or strong drink.
It is better for you than beer.
Direction two, think of tempting filthy objects.
Number three, eat windy meats.
Number four, copiously evacuate.
And if you do not, you perish.
Bite.
Number five, eat maggots.
Direction six, prepare to sodomize for their filthy lusts.
Direction seven, be corrupted with money nor perverted by flattery.
Direction eight, cause that pernicious deliriation in the brain.
Direction nine, produce temptations to lust.
Direction ten, let your apparel be suited to your disease.
Direction eleven, don't drink.
Don't think what your admired carcass will be when it is laying a few days in the grave.
Direction twelve, go back when you see the bait.
Beaver.
Starring, starring Barbara Beaver.
But dad.
You know, Beaver, your mother and I were very...
Ah, that you deliberately...
Nah.
Yes, sir.
Well, Wally, I, uh...
I had a clop you won.
Ah, Wally, I don't think...
I thought I told you to shut up.
Yeah, well, uh, I'll just...
I don't know.
Okay.
Winnie the Pooh finds tail.
And then he put his head down and looked between his front legs.
I, Winnie the Pooh, will find tail food.
So Winnie the Pooh went off to find tail.
To the hundred acre wood.
L-O-L.
Pooh looked at the knocker and...
Large somethings.
Pulled the knockers.
Ow!
The knockers.
Pooh looked at the bush.
Nailed it.
So happily.
Ow!
Winnie the Pooh came over all funny.
Pooh found tail.
I said Pooh.
I found tail.
I want scarlet sin and the moral leper.
People think of full and complete sexual intercourse and every form of sexual deed
and think of fornication between a man and a broad or not.
Thou shalt fornicate in...
Body and behavior.
Or better, thou shalt engage in any sexual activity whatsoever.
And of course, let each wife sexually submit to very shameful, awkward, perverted, irremediable,
extended, intense sexual activity.
Utilizing the sexual parts in a sexual manner in total permanent sexual subjection to,
all forms of perverted sexual urges in our minds.
And of course, engage in perverted sexual perversions.
But, what one has to do is to plead with God to give one that gift of total sexual action.
Because otherwise, we need to get pornography to look at the strange woman and be seen her underwear.
As far as I'm concerned...
You can go too.
Go back to Tony's and that woman you were mooning.
Oh, knock it off, will you?
Now, you pulled a boner tonight and you know it.
Why?
My husband.
Huh.
drauf och steht?
Ba Wat?
Evening, by lessons on snapchat and iso, you Create stories as meweird.
Can I look at meun ellas si mi moon airporta al?
BVE UGRA's Zери pah?!
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Have you traveled far?
That's Paul Atkins.
Rural war room.
Dr. Stang calling Dr. Putris.
Your brain's been invaded.
Actually, I think you can go to myspace.com rural war room records.
Blue and purple alert.
Oh, hi.
I'm sorry.
I would just like to mention the fact that I have had my pancreas, as you mentioned before, changed into a sexual organ.
Really?
Since we as subgeniuses have our choice and may either reproduce with our own organs as we will.
Well, all things bright and mutable.
So that would be like getting to fifth base if someone were to palpate your pancreas.
If you have more than one sexual organ, you can imagine.
That's like going all the way, but then some.
I know what first base is, second base, third base.
In theory, I know what these things are.
And a home run.
Well, theoretically.
But pancreas.
Pancreatic palpation would be fifth base, I guess.
Beyond all the way and through to the other side.
Break on through, man.
See, I knew you were going to get it, but think about your liver and your spleen.
And the myopic fun you can have reacting in such a way.
I mean, if you had one.
You don't have much spleen, except I noticed when you bit my leg on the way here.
But outside of that, you see, not a spleenless man.
Not spleenless, but not heavily spleen.
Yeah, heavily spleen.
We could say.
I've known a lot of people, I just call them heavenly.
Heavenly, hell no.
Heavily spleen.
So visceral.
Now, friends, while I'm still thinking about the news of the cult.
You know, X Day is coming up, the end of the world.
Once again.
On July 5th, the planet will be destroyed at 7 a.m.
How many times is it going to end?
And if not, we'll have more.
Or get more practice for that moment.
Because as the lesson is, you don't know what day X Day.
The rupture could be any day.
Any second now.
Are you ready?
Lesson one?
There is no lesson.
Anyway, you can.
So we're getting ready.
We're getting all geared up for our X Day drill in Sherman, New York, later on in the summer.
And I got so excited about it because I put up a pictorial.
On the Subgenius website, which you can look at if you're interested in for free.
It's also a Vips page.
Then scroll down to the X Day part and you can't miss it.
It says the X Days of your pictorial adults only.
And it is, in fact, the naked adults only pictures of our grandparents at X Days in the past.
Quite indeed.
It's there.
Really.
It's pictures from X Days of the 30th.
The 20s even.
The 30s and 40s.
So it's kind of old-fashioned.
But it's sexy.
Because even the subgeniuses of yore, well, if they hadn't been sexy, we wouldn't be here now, would we?
I like the funny writing on the back of it.
Dearest Mom and Dad, I bet you thought you'd never see me this way.
Signed, your daughter Erna.
Was it Erstweil?
No, that was the guy.
Anyway, I love when they write off these little diaphragms to each other in Uniclaw language.
And they can't.
They have before.
Well, you can't see those on these website pictures.
Because you can't flip the picture over and look at the handwriting on the back of the snapshot.
But I scanned all those old photos that your folks took at X Days.
And Prince of Everybody's, you know.
There's some.
And it's a lot of.
My great-grandpa looked great in like a hat and a pipe and nothing else.
That's right.
I couldn't believe that an old guy that I look at as a very old guy could actually be strutting around there like.
People wear more.
More clothes there now.
Hardly anybody goes completely nude at X Day.
Well, that's the nature of the world.
Everyone wears more clothes at all times because clothes are.
It's not the nature of naturists.
No, certainly not.
But who follows their followings?
Those are droppings.
You know what I'm saying?
That's how you find Bob.
You follow the droppings.
Follow the droppings.
And the cotter pins.
Yeah.
And the jello.
People forget.
You said before they were hand grenade cotter pins, not jello.
What else have we got coming up that I can announce?
Because I'm not getting paid for it.
Hamburg Devival.
We're not going to be there.
But if you friends happen to be in Hamburg, Germany on May 3rd, just follow the look for the smoke and the flames.
And that's where the big Devival will be with all the Euro subs, which includes several American subs who can't go home to America.
Can you imagine?
We've stooped so low that our droppings won't even allow our alien friends to return to their homelands.
It makes you want to seep and crawl.
My droppings aren't stopping anybody from doing anything.
Oh, I didn't mean in the sub-natural, I meant in the over-gross.
Or the uber-gross, I guess you would call it.
The uber-grossian-mentioner.
Speaking of uber-gross, what else?
Actually, people who are interested in uber-gross sub-genius events may want to just look at subgenius.com and look at the news page.
Because there are things coming up that we can't tell you about.
You understand?
That's how good they are.
We're not allowed to...
Will we allow you to tell about the Princess We Are Do's band singing at the Hessler Street Fair this year?
That's for free, yes.
Revel will be at May 17th, the Hester Street Fair.
Hessler, even.
Because we can't tell you anything that does us any good.
That's the law.
But we're going to...
It's not a sub-genius law, that's the human law.
No sub-genius can do anything it wants.
That's the law.
It's written in the books now.
And the Bible and the Holy Constitution.
And yet, the 14th Amendment says that anything that more than one sub-genius businessman does is therefore legal.
It becomes legal at that point.
Yet so she all be done to by thyself.
So if you're doing it by yourself, it might still be illegal.
But if two of us are doing it, then it's okay.
And what yet two businessmen do, only they do...
That law was written, it said businessmen.
It did not say businessperson.
It was written by businesspersons.
There it is.
So, you know, it's that old double standard.
We have to take...
We can't take that at face value unless we're like a pack of two-faced liars.
We have to assume that that meant business...
You know how women used to have to call themselves men when they went to work?
And then they had to call themselves men in the afternoon?
And by the way, I'd just like to mention the fact that you forgot to plug my little thing
that I'm doing at the Communist Party meeting of the Communist Party of the United States
of America.
I didn't know that.
I didn't know that either.
Sure you didn't like it.
I knew you were a commie, but I didn't know that.
I've been creating you guys all week.
I'm going to be speaking at the Grand Function with the frat fairies and sores of my comrades,
my tovarishes.
Well, it's not really Russian.
We just call ourselves comrades.
We're going to be having the fish dinner, well, the fish luncheon afterwards.
And we're going to be having POC beer that's been in the basement for 40 years.
What's POC mean?
PP on Cleveland.
Or it used to mean Pfeiffer of Cleveland, but...
Pride of Cleveland.
Right.
That's what they say.
I said pride of Cleveland, but it really means PP on Cleveland or poop on Cleveland.
Oh, that's just a vernacularism.
When we were childs we used to say that.
But I'm going to be speaking about the movement itself and also the fact that I think the
subgenius, as many of them should join me...
The commies?
...should become communist like me.
That's like the opposite of Bob's.
Bob's like the ultimate god of capitalism.
Well then don't you see the irony in the perfect six things?
Making money at the expense of the sucker.
Don't you see that's the...
That's the succinctly perfect statement for the irony of the ironic thing?
Customer is the sucker of the world.
It is the sucker of the world, but as long...
So why should we be interested in a bunch of commies?
Because we're all suckers.
Yeah, but some suckers are more equal than others, Dave.
And I'm one of those more equal ones.
So that means if I was going to be a commie, I'd be the commissar.
You would be dressed up in the pig suit.
I'd be the equal guy in the pig suit that got driven by a human chauffeur to the big
barnyard in the Kremlin.
Well, I'm going to be wearing Lenin's...
I'm going to be wearing Lenin's overcoat, man.
I'm going to be talking to the mass...
I'm wearing Lenin's underwear right now.
Are you really?
My Lenin's.
I call them.
Your Lenin's.
How long did it take you to get those things?
I guess they were real expensive on eBay or something, right?
Oh, they're so intimate.
The right state...
What's this noise in the background?
That's the rural war room.
It's the rural war room thing.
It's the rural war room machine.
It's coming as smart as...
It's the...
Oh, he's on and on and on.
Now, listen, nickel crow.
You remove the crow with your thumb.
Your prehensile thumb that Bob...
No.
No, not Bob.
That...
God, no.
That nature...
Hey, Spira.
That nature.
Remove your thumb from your eye.
Now, stand near the door.
Move out of the door.
Move out the window.
Now, flap your arms.
Flap your wings.
You can fly!
Yup.
You can fly.
You can fly, baby.
Just get with Bob and grow your wings.
I'm flying!
Grow the wings in your mind, man.
I'm sorry.
Bob is like a pink, glarp, normal.
He supports the conspiracy, supports class division.
He ought to be killed, but...
Yeah.
He's a pretty nice guy for a personal savior.
I know he is.
I mean...
To quote...
What do you mean?
Drelloid mutant.
Get off my flight!
All right.
The late Drelloid mutant.
The late, late Drelloid mutant.
Oh, we're going to be playing a song by the...
Later on in the show, we're going to be playing an ancient song that somebody found in a pile
of 78s that appears to be a Church of the Subgenius Hillbilly gospel song from like the 30s or
the...
20s or something.
It was on a wax record, but we'll get to that.
We can't figure out if it's an oaky or if it's actually like, you know, from West Virginia
or something.
I mean, it's way up here.
We're trying to figure out the label.
I guess it was on the Sugarfest radio show.
Yes.
We can't tell if it's an oaky or a pudding.
But I can't play that because it doesn't...
It may be a pudding.
I think it's a pudding.
It doesn't come up yet.
Like a pudding.
However...
Is it?
However, let's just see what happens if I...
Yeah.
Let's see.
Hold it.
Love That Bob.
Starring Bob Cumming.
You're gonna look sensational in a bathing suit.
I know that.
We're swinging.
Bob didn't take this.
Bob can take better pictures.
Take it.
Rock and roll rears its ugly head.
Bob.
Rock and roll.
You're big.
Hold it, baby.
Oh, I'd love to.
I'm gonna...
More.
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh.
Peckers.
Well.
Bob, I just found a way to get the guitar, Bob.
Hey.
Swell.
Who could he be?
Crazy.
Where can I get that kind of sausage?
Bob's Rock and Roll.
So Bob.
Bob.
No, no.
Please, please don't ask me to show it to you.
Guitar wizardry.
Virtuoso.
You'll never get a girl with rock and roll.
Bob, the girl's flip.
That's so true, John.
That's so true.
Really?
P-p-p-p-p-p-p-p-p-focus, focus, focus, focus.
The Center for Strong Homosexual Issues.
Internet pornography.
Pornography.
practices for women towards men.
Let me wallow in my state of ignorance.
Let me wallow in my way of anxiety.
Let me wallow in mypable, vindictive, enlightenment back in last week.
Anxiety.
I need help.
Help.
You know.
We do hair. We do hair. It goes both ways.
But it's all paid for with public money.
So there, so there, so there.
It's been fun. It's been fun.
It's hep, hep, hep. Fun, fun. It's hep, hep, hep.
All of that and more really covers most of the S.
Burnout. Burnout. Burnout.
The letter A. The letter A.
Prince will do us. Prince will do us. Do us. Do us.
Let me wallow in ignorance.
She's sold over 25 books.
She's one of the most successful tattooed mother with mental health problems
this country has ever produced.
Tough. Adult. Unicorns. Thumped. Very stiff. Really too big. Why?
It works for me. Totally. Different head. It's very wreck. Wreck.
Can't. Can't. Can't. Spectacular.
But meanwhile, I feel cheap.
Do you plan? Maybe.
Goodbye.
San Francisco.
Sam Morrow shares his experience with you.
Get the feeling.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
Look out!
What did you do?
No. Yes.
San Francisco.
It makes good sense when you smoke.
When you smoke.
San Francisco. San Francisco. Ho-ho. Very.
The rest is rat version. Rat version. Rat version.
Hyah!
I don't like it.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
No extra work.
You're in check.
What are you trying to pull, mister?
You don't think I'm telling the truth?
Don't be too long.
It gives me pleasure to...
San Francisco. I...
Ho-ho. Big story in papers.
Toy. Big trouble.
Hey, boy.
I've been very concerned with you these past days, Victor.
What kind of dealings do you have with the director of the morgue?
Are you interested in corpses?
Hm.
Godfleet.
I shall really have to tell you the story of the inquisitive commandant.
The one at Belsam, remember?
They might believe that you want that atomic element to supply electric power.
But I...
What are you trying to say?
I don't know.
I don't know?
I have no idea.
I don't know.
Could I repeat what I just said?
Unless, of course, you could repeat it for me.
No, no, no, Pee-pee-hay.
Ah, do svitanya.
Shtovany.
I don't know.
It's a...
It's a Russian hotel.
It's a big hotel.
I don't know.
I would like to smell my shoe.
Repeat.
I don't know.
Ah, if I'm correct, it's groundhog day.
Ah, I would like to smell the shoe, that's why I've got a little bit of time.
I don't know, ah, if I'm right, that's why...
Repeat in English.
I would like to smell your shoe.
I am the shoe smeller.
That's the language of God.
The pure language of the angels.
Unaffected by three rows of teeth,
the animals who speak the language of God
are known for miles and miles in the Amazon basin
for releasing loud, unctuous quantities
of good old Mother Nature's food.
And as long as they worship
at the foot of the statue of the piped head,
they are all as well in the kingdom of sweat and vigor.
My shoes smell funny to you.
Repeat in Hintekorash.
The shoe is angry with me.
Oh, God.
Repeat.
Bob is the shoe.
Mekipalobobo Bob.
The shoe.
Mekipalobobo Connie.
Connie.
Connie Mekipalobo.
Mekipalobo Mekipalobo.
Connie is the high heeled pihatcha.
Repeat in Urdu.
Mekipalobo Mekipalobo.
Connie.
Now in Panglossian.
Uh-oh.
Time to turn the background music up.
I don't know what to say.
Oh, look, Dave, you have to go let somebody in.
You have to go open the door.
Friends, it's just you and me
listening while Dave runs to,
hopefully, let in,
Princess Wiardo
after having run her
synesthesian errand
in preparation for the
upcoming programs on this
fine radio station,
which you have tuned into
just today.
The barbarian woman has returned.
Ah.
Well, okay, then I guess
we can move on.
Barvarian, you meant?
Did you mean barbarian?
I meant Bavarian.
Barvarian, he has said.
No, I'm speaking of...
Shazzi.
My little pearl.
I know that you are wearing
lederhosen on your ears.
You're not supposed to notice
or speak of the lederhosen.
Lederhosen are the personal part
of women's attire.
And they're meant to be smelled by
men with big, big hair.
And big noses.
And you know what a big nose means.
Yes.
Big nose hair clippers.
Reference tank does not want any other
man to smell the lederhosen.
Would you like to languish
in the aquarium with me
for a short duration?
Does that line ever work?
Sometimes.
Yeah.
In Parfait, it is said,
nashcap in handy,
ratatal.
I knew a guy who would go into a bar
and walk up to every single woman
and say that to her,
and he would get slapped
30 times, but...
Sooner or later, he'd find one who'd go,
yeah, baby, your place or mine.
Your friend went for the slaps only.
That's possible.
Highly likely in this case.
I don't know.
It was the only way he could score.
Wasn't he the one you called
the two-tongued rabbit of Bob?
No, you're thinking of someone else.
That was the other guy.
He was working the percentages, man.
Now, let's...
We got this piece, this old record.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Actually, she didn't send the record.
She sent an MP3 that she had copied
from this record.
Our friend, Reverend Samantha,
who all the regular devotional goers
would know Reverend Samantha.
She used to be the only girl
at the Devo shows,
and that's changed,
but she was the first.
Anyway, she sent this song
and a letter.
I'm going to read the letter.
Reverend Samantha said,
this little musical gem,
which I found lying in a pile
of old dusty 78s in the attic.
Kids, that means old CDs
only before CDs were invented.
They were big wax discs.
It appears to be a Depression-era
Church of the Subgenius
hillbilly gospel song.
Can it be?
There's no reason why it couldn't be,
although it's rare to find something
from that part of the country.
Anyway, she says,
I could just barely make out
the words on the record label.
It seemed to say something like,
look away from the pinks
to the billowing pipe.
That's the title of the song
by the Mutant Mountain Boys.
Interesting how they got away
with such politically incorrect names
back then.
I think it's interesting
how pristine it almost is.
I mean, when you look at it,
it looked like it was just cut yesterday,
and yet it is one of those
like old OK Bluebird type of,
you know, renderings there
on a 78 RPM.
Well, we're going to play this.
She figured out the words to it,
I think, because they're really hard
to hear on this old record.
And kindly printed them for us
to be able to look at these.
Yes.
Who's kindly?
Let's see.
Is that another person involved?
No, that's me.
I'm kindly.
Kindly, all right.
She said, you know,
this just might be
the only existing copy in the world,
so here's...
Here I am now
spreading it like a virus.
I'm going to play it now,
and the singers will sing along.
Look away from the paints
to the bellowing pie
From your life of work and toil
Look away
There's a hole in your soul
That's burning you alive
Where slackdom will never decay
Look away
Send your chariot
For eternal sleep
From the paints to the bellowing pie
Bellowing pie
Look away
For the morning past
From the paints to the bellowing pie
Bellowing pie
I saw a vision above
and I can walk again
Of course, there's nothing really wrong
with my legs
and a good old ten-ton crusher wouldn't cure them.
I need my body to be ripped off
but still it's a funny life.
You have responsibilities
getting out of you to bear
and you're blind
walk the life so severe
There's a hypnotic man
who is beckoning from
with his disembodied head
always there
Look away
Send your chariot
For eternal sleep
From the paints to the bellowing pie
Bellowing pie
Look away
Send your chariot
For eternal sleep
From the paints to the bellowing pie
Lyrics, music, and music by Tyler.
I can almost see again
I can almost walk again
I can almost hear again
If your conflicts with normals bring struggles and strife,
live onward, your rantings ensue.
Look away from the pinks to the billowing pipe
that's waiting in dives down for you.
Look away from the pinks to the billowing pipe.
It's a beautiful, beautiful...
Thank you, Reverend Samantha, for finding that.
And all the voracious loving, I must say, I've never met you,
but it seems to me if your knees were as knobby as your head,
I'd be in love once again.
Her knees are as knobby as her head, if I remember correctly.
They are not. Her knees are perfectly sleek and beautiful.
Well, how about all these polygamists lately?
Back in Stane County, Texas, they've been running the polygamists.
They're hydrocephalic down there, and there's more than one of them,
I'm guessing. They're all married to each other.
And the smallest one is only five years old.
That's right.
And Grandpappy is pushing 109, but believe me,
he can still be an indirect old thumb on it.
You're not kidding.
I'm not. I'm trying not to be anyway.
Texas is a great place for cults.
You know, even the Mormons had to move down to Texas
to do their really cultish stuff.
Had to move out of Ohio and New York.
Well, now, I've heard...
I've heard there's been food riots in the news all over the world
because there's been an 83% price rise over the last three years
in foodstuffs in general for the entire planet.
Yeah, I thought it was 40, and I guess it was 40 in one year.
I thought it was 40% over three years.
That's right.
And that even includes us Merkins paying more.
And pretty soon, everybody's going to be dead.
You mean you've been eating your Merkins?
You're so hungry, you're eating a Merkin?
We've been driven to that.
There were times when we were so wroth.
I remember Mom and Dad were so...
They not only took in laundry and other children's ducks and stuff like that,
they also played with others' behavior models
just to survive, to get by the next day.
They ate chest Merkins, man.
Chest Merkin.
We had it on Thursday night with lasagna, man.
Chest Merkin, you know?
Well, they're literally friends.
There have been food riots all over the world lately.
Haiti, the Philippines, Egypt, Columbus, Dayton.
La Vie.
And you know every place is Dayton Place.
Yeah.
I say that because nobody would understand Payton Place.
The only old people know where Payton Place is.
Well, Dayton Place is where the three original alien sky choppers were regulated.
It was where they first crashed.
Yeah, they took them from Roswell, too.
And they used Roswell as a cover-up for the Dayton Place UFO crashes, saucer crashes.
Yeah, there was...
At Wright-Patterson, remember?
Right, yes.
You said you inspected the bodies, and they argued with you about it.
I mean, the bodies were...
Yes, it was all quite foul and disgusting.
It's weird when a corpse becomes animated right while you're arguing with it.
And yet charming somehow at the same time.
Well, you know, dead people do have a certain charm about them.
They're kind of distant.
There's been a debate lately about who do you like best,
the running, fast-moving zombies,
or the shot-and-run zombies.
Shuffling, lurching, stumbling zombies.
I like...
I'm not a big fan of the stiff zombies,
but I think it would just be too scary to have, you know,
a long-legged, like, gazelle-type zombie just chasing you down.
And there's the hooker zombies.
That lure you in.
And the sails zombies.
Man, the speed zombies are the scary ones to me, man.
The speed zombies?
Speed zombies are the scariest of all.
Meth zombies.
Yeah.
Cochasa zombies were a big deal in Brazil when I was down there.
Yeah, I can see that.
Cochasa zombies.
The local drink is this cochasa stuff.
Cochasa?
Is it like, to you, it's a sped-up beer that a native lady spit it up?
No, no, that's a different beer.
It's made from spit.
Different beer, they call it.
Cochasa is sort of like tequila, but it's...
Yeah, it's their local...
Liquid fluid thing that makes your brain...
Yeah, it's made from potash or something.
I forget what.
Wow.
That is really, really hard to believe.
But there are zombies.
I can believe that part.
You know...
Cochasa zombies.
Those who have thoroughly...
I don't think I'm pronouncing that right.
...deadened their brains with cochasa.
I had one too many myself.
One too many zombies?
I came close to being...
I have had a zombie, yeah.
What the hell is that?
When I was younger, when I was a young man.
Oh, you carnal, you little...
You have to cut their hands off because otherwise they'll scratch you,
claw your eyes out and stuff.
Yeah, they have no idea of their strengths.
And, of course, they have to be muzzled.
They're just on temporal motor slabbling.
Yeah.
You have to muzzle.
Yeah, because they want to eat your brain while you're nibbling at their ear.
They're going to...
And you...
Yeah.
You know, the smell is not great.
And you don't want to do any, like, weird numbers.
And the bits fall off.
Oh, yeah.
The bits falling off is not cool.
Yeah, call me when you guys are done with this conversation.
But can you imagine doing one of those, like, old sexual numbers?
You know, you give them numbers and stuff like that.
Number 72.
Can you imagine doing 72 with a zombie?
What do you mean, imagine?
Yeah, I can.
That's what I was getting at.
Yeah.
I'm from Texas, man.
Man, that's not that big of a deal down there.
So, Ed Geins...
I've noticed people are kind of...
Here's some Texas, too, right?
Kind of weak stomach up here.
They're kind of hickey.
They are a body, visceral race of murderers and biters and biters.
That's us.
Ed Geins, Geins.
Praise Bob.
He led us in the way of the Texas businessman.
I thought you were going to say he led you into the desert instead of out.
And the zombie bordellos.
The zombie bordellos, man.
Way out there and out near Alpine where those lights are, you know.
Have you ever heard of the Alpine lights, the dependable UFOs?
Have you ever heard of those, Dave?
The Alpine lights?
I'm sorry.
I was being your background music.
Of course.
An Alpine lodge for vampires?
No, no.
For UFOs.
There's a town in the deserts of Texas, way out in the boonies in the southern western
Like a truck stop for UFOs?
It's kind of like one of those...
Kind of, yeah.
...that sprang up around the desert.
Yeah.
A truck stop, yeah.
Now, it so happens that if you put a video camera on the mysterious lights and another
video camera at a highway about 10 miles away across the desert, the car lights seem to
dictate how the UFO lights move.
And there's kind of...
Some people say that it's merely a mirage situation that's always in place so that what
appears to be mysterious lights flying around in the desert are really just headlights from
several miles away on the desert, bounced by atmospheric freak.
But that's as supernatural as the damn UFOs to begin with.
Yeah, right.
So it's like, whatcha gonna do?
Yeah.
What are you gonna do?
There's no fractal fissuring to create an illusion of a thermoscopy.
There's no way that you can get around the...
Like it's flaming fire and you still can't see it.
I'm sorry, I'm frothing at the neck.
It's getting messy.
And it's not just a bird.
You know, they all remember, it wasn't the first time the little lady from Brazil had
her story to tell.
Ah!
I'm sorry!
Things were bad everywhere.
We took her back to Sao Paulo where she hoped to meet her father, Rex Rumroy.
He was a rum runner all right.
He brought the last big bottle of booze up from Franquas and landed in Boston last week.
Yeah.
But don't ask me about it.
Ask this little lady.
This little lady right here.
The one with the exposed skull.
I think you're still sick.
I cannot speak.
My voice...
vocal cords have been removed by lonesome cowboy Dave.
I cannot speak no more.
You're still sick.
That's it.
Good girl.
Did it hurt?
I'm being paid.
I'm getting paid.
Find yourself again.
I'm not lost.
You're working yourself up into a full-sized nervous breakdown.
Serene, clear-eyed.
Let me take your photograph, will you?
You're still sick.
Okay, I'm sick.
The symbolism.
No.
Look, this whole thing is nothing but a hallucination.
Let me come with you.
No.
That's the end of the shaft.
No, I'd better phone the scientists.
I'll be in charge.
Petrified historic man?
But everybody will see her in her nakedness.
Nakedness?
What is time but a conception of man?
She's not an object of vivisection.
I will be in charge.
Well, we were all somewhat excited, I would say, and we still are.
How would you like to rap, rap, rap, rap, rap?
Oh.
Six, maybe seven.
This is quite common, John.
You have a fear of the future.
Is that why I scream?
You want it, yet you fear it.
Five.
Might be a winner.
I want him now.
Now?
Do you understand?
Get him!
Enlightenment comes more easily in the dark.
Oh, yes.
It smells funny.
Then drink your tea.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
Look.
Why all the games?
Can't you just get on with it?
What do you want us to do?
We want you to praise Bob.
My friends, that's all we ask.
Well, it's actually not.
That's far from all we ask.
But that's the first thing we ask is that you praise Bob.
What are you two mumbling?
You're just blottering about over there.
How are you cutting out the tablets?
We're just having a little discussion about folks with brain injuries
returning to the job as full-grown zombies.
You know, and at where we work,
zombies come back every day and have to be rehabilitated.
And it costs the boss lots of money.
Indeed.
And that's why we think Dobbs is our answer.
Because Dobbs is not only going to get rid of those pesky monkeys,
but he's also going to kill the administration of the company as well.
In fact, no one's going to be left alive,
but me.
Maybe that's not Bob.
Maybe that's just my own.
You know what I'm saying?
How often do we ascribe to Bob feelings that are really just our own?
You know how it is.
You go, well, I feel like having a hamburger or ice cream cones.
I'm sure Bob would feel the same way.
He'd feel like it was okay for me to have that ice cream cone.
I'm sure he would.
And you know he was.
Yes, he would.
He's like the Lord baby Jesus.
At least that way.
Too much is always better than not enough, Bob said.
He was lying, but it sounds great.
And that's all that matters in your proper religion, modern religion.
Yes, you left off the antecedent found years later.
That's the only thing that's important is the antecedent.
Is that what...
Maybe that's what we ran over on the way here.
Bob's antecedent?
Yes.
Remember that thing we smushed on the way that squealed?
It was before the pipe, so it might have been actually alive.
It could have been physically in corpus coelombo.
Well, I hope...
Too much is always better than not enough, but it's almost as bad.
It's much worse.
Believe you me.
Look down here.
Ew, I don't want to look down there.
Oh, look, there's plenty of skulls being opened.
And they're putting little Bob implants in each one.
Look at those biological urges down there.
Yes, you can see them flashing on the rhythmosphat and the displays.
And of course, if you jump over here and make a little bunny wrap,
you'll be electrocuted.
But jump over, or else you'll be electrocuted.
No, no, jump over.
That's not a bunny rabbit.
That's an ugly baby.
That's all.
That's all it was.
Yeah, we wouldn't do that to a rabbit.
Of course not.
But a red-headed stepchild, anything goes.
Is subject to immediate electrocution.
Or is it elocution?
I am your favorite red-haired stepchild.
And I'd just like to say, in my perfect English,
that Bob has saved my career, whatever the hell that might mean.
Your electrifying elocution?
If only we could remember what your career was that he saved.
And who it was.
You could finally make some money off of it.
In fact, we can't find that.
He'll save your career, but he won't tell you what it is.
That's Bob for you, man.
He's a mystery god.
He's a little bit of a...
He's a conundrum wrapped in a mystery.
A little bit of a cocopele child.
The blanket of...
Cloudy weirdness around it.
They say Bob plays in mysterious ways.
They say Bob sits around in mysterious waters.
They say Bob plays with himself in strange places.
They say Bob is a strange place.
He has unusual choices of where he's gonna expose himself.
And they say Bob smells worse than stewed poons.
Well, that's because he smokes that pipe.
Subject or the object.
And he's got the real farts.
He doesn't have a frap.
He doesn't have some street marijuana or wog hemp.
He's doing the real thing.
Have a frap, zip your locks.
Marifazalupina.
That's where that smile comes from?
For short.
Can I ask you a question?
That's what Bob's smoking.
And that's what you smell when Bob laughs by.
Where did it come from?
I mean, the frap and the zip your locks.
Can I ask you that one question?
Oh, it comes from Tibet.
What?
If it grows in Tibet on the graves and droppings of dead Tibetan holy men or yetis, full blood yetis.
Under the light of a full moon.
If it would grow on the droppings of a half-breed yeti, then we'd be up to our necks in real frap.
Up to our ears.
But we ain't.
We're not up to even our toenails in real frap.
It's hard to get, friends.
Maybe that's for the best.
I don't know.
The Chinese post-war...
They're not going to have frap and zip your locks?
Isn't that what they want, Tibet?
Is that what you're saying?
Derek!
Yo ho!
Is this what...
I think...
I feel like I'm on something.
This is one of those shows that's messing with my head.
It may be this rural war room background that's...
I...
I can see the Fuhrer in my mind.
He's standing up there by the great map.
That's Groucho Marx, isn't it?
Oh, that's Captain Spalding!
That's not Hitler.
No, that's not Captain Spalding.
That's the Rufus T. Firefly.
That was Charlie Chaplin.
Oh, that was, uh, Germaine Greer.
Whatever is Germaine to me.
Countess St. Germaine!
It was the scientific segue.
It was the easy way.
Ouch!
I thought it was the occultist segue that pinched its own.
Well, some of us are made of real DNA,
and others are made of constructed materials,
if you know what I mean.
Heavens!
Oh, of course!
We're not all cranked out to be over here
trying to help you with your show,
and you don't seem to pay much attention to us.
And what show is this?
Why, friends, this is hour of slack number 1149.
Where days seem like minutes.
Number nine?
One of the most official voiceboxes of the Church of the Subgenius.
1149?
Located in the intranets at...
WW...
.subgenius.
Subgenius.com.
Subgenius spelled sub-genius.
And there is not an O anywhere in there except the .com.
There's an O in the dot and an O in the com,
although you don't write out the dot.
I suppose you could try that.
Speaking of dots, we pulled out our magnifying glass recently
and started searching for animalcules again.
That's one of our hobbies.
We like to look at hideous, crawling, writhing, abhorrent, formless things
that live in everybody's backyard.
Every square inch of dirt has hideous monsters.
Right under your toes.
The air you breathe.
And under your nose.
In between your eyelashes, there are horrible, ugly worms
chewing their way through your ducts, your tear ducts.
They live in there.
There's these spiral gyro looking things
with all kinds of horny things.
Sticking out of them.
They live in your lungs.
Can you imagine?
We scraped the newt cage last night.
Princess Wee and I did.
We went up to the...
We have only one slave pet that we keep.
A newt.
They're very low maintenance.
Fig is its name.
He's about as big as your little finger.
Yeah, he's not very big, but he's very, very old.
Princess Wee acquired this newt 28 years ago
and for all we know, it was 1,000 years old then.
Anyway...
I see.
I think it's a spirit creature by now.
Yeah, well, no.
He's still really there.
Yes, he is.
He eats on a daily basis.
There's not much meat on him.
I know he's well and all that.
I mean, I think he's one of the old ones from before.
Well, we wanted to see if maybe he was living with those
and what else was in the murky water
before we cleaned his tank.
So we scraped some crud off the side of the tank
and put some of that on our slide
and took a look at it.
And guess what, Dave?
There was a horrible, transparent nematode
worm writhing frantically
because its water was drying up almost as you watched.
He was all speckly and 3DE looking.
You could see right through him.
Writhing in pain.
A tiny wee tubular life
that you can't see with the nude eye.
But that little newt was no doubt
kind of covered with him, I suppose.
I would imagine so.
We could scrape him, I suppose.
And take a look.
Probably subsists on them partially.
You think?
You think he eats them nematodes?
I would imagine so.
What if there's a secret parasite
that's going to get on you now, too?
And he's going to eat on your head
and all the different parts of your body.
That's the wonderful thing about
looking through your own $30 kid's microscope.
Because it's just theoretical in your mind
that there are microorganisms everywhere.
Organisms.
Creeping through.
Through your nostrils
and coming in and out with your air.
You're breathing tiny insect skeletons.
Did you ever scrape a breech baby
for any such hematodes?
That's next week.
But we have...
A project-to-project kind of thing.
When you actually look at those things,
you get a concrete knowledge
of the fact that...
Actually, I think Nenslow figured this out.
This is what it all boils down to.
All life, the universe, and everything
boils down to this.
Dirt is mostly poo.
And poo is mostly corpses.
So, friends, it's the circle of life.
It's not necessarily that poo is our corpses.
You see, it's mostly poo and corpses.
This is the detritus of the human condition.
No, poo is corpses.
It comes out of you while you're living.
And dirt is mostly poo.
And it is left behind.
So, the whole world, really, if you think about it...
Is defecation.
There's more of that than there is.
There's more crap than there is
living, breathing non-crap.
This is like the poopiest conversation I've heard.
Well, it's natural.
It's a naturistical thing.
It's something you don't tend to think about.
But the biomass of those tiny creatures
far outweighs
the biomass of animals that you can see.
But it's literal hoo-ha.
I personally like to crawl around on them.
I mean, just think of these
thousands and thousands of generations
living on a mound of decay.
And that it's making it
itself. We're self-perpetuating
and self-engendering.
Think of it, Sting! We'll live forever
on our own feces!
Well, they're living in my hair.
They're living in my bowels.
They're living
between my toes.
Things. Things, things, things.
And yours too, friend.
Listener, I want you, as you go to bed tonight,
I want you to think about all those little
monsters that live
in between the creases
of your body. If you didn't take them,
you wouldn't be able to shower in the last
15 or 20 minutes.
Oh, well, of course.
And even then, you wouldn't get most of them.
I mean, a lot of them would still
cling on.
Like, miniature cling-ons.
The little cities in your ear canal.
Best little tiny
universes and malls
and original theater
in the crack of your behind.
Think of it, man.
You're a city of
little
little turkeys.
Little turkeys.
Did you know I was doing okay until you mentioned
the crack of the behind crack?
That one crack.
I was fine with everything
until you said that. Now I'm
disgustipated. I'm sick.
Sickened.
Where would you live if you were such a creature?
I'd live in 1998, friends.
That's where I'd be forever.
And that's where we have to go now because the show
is now coming to an end. We have to make room
for show next.
And so,
say goodbye.
Goodbye.
Oh, dear listeners, it's parting is such
sweet sorrow.
And we thank Norrell Preff
for the collagiastical
upcomings and also
John Hell from
A Season in Hell. Thank you.
Shell dividing.
Thick intelligence. Thick urges.
Biological weapons.
Use logical agents.
Let me take you inside.
And share with you
thick urges.
Urges.
We have.
Logical weapons factories on wheels
and on rails.
I.
We have vague hints.
Program.
Logical poison.
Poison.
Logical.
Logical poison.
Poison.
Logical.
Program.
I.
Aim later.
In the year 2000.
Poison.
Soup.
An accident occurred
in 1998.
Let me take you inside
and share with you
biological urges.
We did the
Bodine family reunion
about what was that
about 10 years ago?
Yes.
And it was
we're all dressed
in our
our fine
fabulous
thick regalia
drinking up a storm
and enjoying our
enjoying our
yes exactly
a with a lot
by the way
there were a whole bunch
of weddings going on
right there
during the barbecue
that day.
Numerous
a number of the brides
were all pregnant
which was quite interesting
in their dresses.
And then
the thing is
right down the street
like there's a
there's the
the house is at the end
sort of a street
and then it just turns
to the left
and dead ends
at a church
just maybe about
a hundred yards
not even that
50 yards away
and so all of a sudden
during our fabulous
family reunion
a real wedding
began to take place
at the church
so all of the brides
ran out
about
we're talking
about maybe
half dozen
pregnant brides
run out of the party
and approach the groom
the real groom
at the real church
and start throwing
themselves on him
about how he's
their baby's daddy.
And you've got
all the ushers
the whole wedding party
their family
very sort of a
it's a happy joy
family celebration
children are getting married
and here come
six pregnant brides.
Yeah.
All that guy's responsibility.
Well yeah
he actually looked like
he recognized
a few of them too.
Yeah.
He looks scared.
That's what you get.
I rise
the ugly baby
baby
bringing this forward
an ugly baby
ugly thing
ill
nah
and this will be
just
baby
this baby is
ugly thing
I rise
the ugly baby
across the nation
communities
and the parents
of Boy Scouts
are observing
Boy Scout Week
agreeing with the boys
themselves that
adventure
that's scouting.