And now, a power well calculated to keep you in
SWAT
In a moment, the subgenius of
Sit still. Sit still or I'll have to shoot you.
Starring cigarettes, and written especially by cigarettes, and brought to you by cigarettes.
Rob
You're so small
And I'm so in there
You
I know you can't stand the taste of what you like to drink
The pain of a kiss
Please stop
I know that there is a taste of what you like to drink
And I've heard it all
I know that that drink that it is a lie
You can't have it
Please stop
Yeah
You can't have it
Yes
When these
Our
It
Fatal masochism
Our
Final
cure
Yes
Use the Force
Systematic. Great.
Rob.
Force.
Systematic. Great.
Job.
It's just too taboo to talk pleasure in this arena.
Slag.
Please stop.
Can I try?
Come on.
Let's go.
Come on, Bohamqu.
To my head.
정도
Right.
It's OK.
Subgenus
Sex
Oh, come on, got it
Pop
Oh, yeah
Hey, praise Bob!
Thanks to Cool Hand Crisp
And now, this
From PR News in Washington
I'm continuing sexual treatment
For an aggressive 55-year-old woman
Unable to cum in Brussels
Today, the Trump says
Senator John McCain and
Attorney General
John McCain
And Jeff Sessions
Will fleet their country
Saying, quote
Russian collusion, quote
The Irish Prime Minister says
I think
But not
He says he's glad
This is PR News
I do
a lot of life
I'm ready to
Don't I
I'll take
What I didn't
Want
On the
It, so
It's the key change
It happens all the time
I hope you enjoyed this video.
Thank you for watching.
Make a real good sandwich, bottle of beer.
Yeah.
Head cheese and bologna on garlic bread, little mayonnaise, horseradish, mustard.
How's that sound to you, Joe?
By the Rudy Schwartz Project from the new album Postal Code for Ham.
Look it up.
I tend to wear diapers sometimes because of daddy.
Fledged.
And his problem with drinking liquor on Tuesday, you know.
Is he still doing that?
Because I'm not.
I had to quit.
I was referring to you, but he, our other friend, he is definitely still doing that.
And I tried to stop him, too.
And he threw me out of his house.
He said, get the hell out and don't come back.
So, man, you just invited me over for some pizza and some frappin' and some beer and stuff.
Next thing you know, I made one small comment.
Maybe the size of a pinhead on a needle or something.
Now there's enough to send him flying into inner tube langsoria.
How dare you come over here and tell me you don't want to watch me kill myself.
I invited you over here to watch me drink myself to death.
And you're just taking it lightly.
Yeah, and then the next thing you know, we're talking about Irish Revolution going back to day one.
You know.
And he's suddenly, he's an academic.
He knows all about all that stuff the rest of his life.
He doesn't know the singlest thing about anything.
Except for Kibosh.
He does like Kibosh.
That's a foreign sounding name, but.
My very best friend turned into my very worst friend and died young.
He never got to see any of these great new superhero movies that have come out.
Actually, he probably wouldn't have liked them.
Anyway.
Yeah.
He's hanging on.
There's too much diversity.
Actually, that was his one of his many problems.
Oh, well, well, let's not talk about the dead.
Although there sure are plenty that I could talk about.
God, we've lost a lot of friends in the last year or two.
Yeah, definitely.
And they're not here around us.
Well, necessarily loud enough to be able to make say, Hey, shut the beep up.
You know, like when we say things, we can even make up things.
I mean, I don't know what else to say about people that aren't that either enlarge their
fame or diminish it.
A long time ago, Dave, it was actually after our friend Chaz died and we kind of regretted
not trying to take better care of him or something.
Pay more attention.
He wouldn't say he never said what was wrong.
He never would.
He never said that he had a chronic debilitating hopeless disease.
But he never knew that that.
But we you said afterwards, you said we should we should try to treat our friends like they're
already dead.
Well, I heard that from a very from psychopath finder.
Oh, but but he doesn't believe that anymore.
He's the opposite of his pronouncements.
He like doesn't show up a lot of times at many calling hours and stuff like that.
He refuses to refund my laundry tickets.
And I won't like last week I had $300 put in some kind of false fund in Argentina or
someplace.
Well, at least you have subgeniuses to talk to.
I'm most of the time.
I mean, I if I actually do have have several subgenius friends that live not far from this
little tiny town and I got all my relatives around me.
But but, you know, I'm most of the time I'm in this.
It's not.
It's not a big old empty house.
It's a medium sized house, but with one big, huge empty room.
It's like the living room and dining room and everything is all one piece and the upstairs
is all just a giant hollow room.
And I turn into my dad.
I'm all by myself here with these two dogs because Princess Wee has to stay in Ohio.
She's taking care of her old ma and other things.
And I have to be here.
I have to be here to take care of things here.
And so I found myself talking to the dogs, Dave.
I mean, having long conversations.
So it begins now.
Now you understand where I was feeling a little strange a few years ago with my dog.
Yeah, yeah, I do.
I was I often think about you because, yeah, I haven't my wife hadn't been around.
I'm used to being spoiled.
And baby.
And I have to do everything for myself now.
And and and I even have to to to tell my wife's cracks to somebody.
And it's just the dogs get to hear me talk a lot.
But they look at me as if they don't understand a word I'm saying.
They don't really mind me doing it.
But, you know, it's it beats talking to myself because probably the dogs are better listeners.
They are.
And they probably understand.
Not as much.
They probably understand as little as you think.
They probably understand a great deal more than many of us.
I hope not.
Because my dog, I could finally ask my dog questions.
I could say, where's so and so?
I went if I would lose something, I would say, where's so and so?
And he would point it where it was.
I wish I were.
We go over to where it was point like dog style with his nose.
I asked them.
I do ask them.
I try to get them to find lost objects for me.
But if it's not a furry little varmint, they're just they don't just give me a blank look.
Today.
Okay.
I took him to the city park because we had a brief respite from the rain and it was cool
outside.
And we went to the park.
I figured they might meet some other dogs.
Well, there was a bunch of people there doing elaborate remote control miniature trucks.
They're like monster trucks about a foot and a half long.
And they're run by remote control.
And out this park has these big smooth lumpy rocks that are perfect for these these little baby monster trucks to go, you know, rumbling up steep slopes and stuff.
It's really fun.
Plus, they they fall over and nobody gets hurt because they're just robots.
Well, anyway, the dog song from a distance and went nuts went completely.
I've never seen him so desperate to get their teeth around the neck of something.
In this case, it's a little plastic and metal thing, you know, it's a little motorized thing.
And these the good old boys that were running these things were really tickled to watch the dogs frantic.
So both hunting dogs, they don't never get to really hunt.
And they were going to whatever these aliens were, they were going to tear them to pieces.
Almost broke my neck having to hold on to them.
I want to carry three 7 ins lady.
Yeah.
And hopefully you like that.
Solungen is watching this.
Now, these are the ins and chicleteers and they are sometimes they zoom in and get stuck in there and fall off the edge and all of a sudden make this.
No put it on where somebody else is going to.
Just, just escaped out of the food from the catch.
Check.
OK, I thought.
Okay, wait a minute.
So you're going to.
I'll get the wrong result, if you know what I mean.
And then that's a whole 20-minute cleanup job.
Anyway, the rednecks, the redneck miniature monster truck hobbyist allowed his house.
Okay, if I let the dog sniff him.
And so I just, like Hercules holding on to oxen, I managed it.
Once they smelled it and realized it was just a robot, they totally lost interest immediately.
And thought we were all idiots to waste our time with them.
And, you know, went off looking for something to roll in.
Something really stinky.
Dead.
They didn't find it.
Actually, they did, but I'm pretty sharp-eyed about that.
I can catch them usually before they throw that shoulder down on the ground suddenly.
They have little tails, you know, they're little.
We're getting to know each other better.
It's harder dealing with two.
It really is.
It's not nearly as much fun.
I need my wife.
You should see these instructions I got from Reverend Stang.
They're so awesome.
Written out in minute detail.
Maybe I should.
I'll just read them.
Sure.
They're probably more entertaining than anything we have to say.
Instructions for Tarzan's radio station.
I can't.
Wait for this.
In the box is a lot of stuff.
And it looks confusing.
Because there are lots of extraneous, miscellaneous cords and connections.
Just in case they're needed.
Mostly in a clear plastic Ziploc bag.
And a little blue cardboard box.
Also an HDMI cable for videos if needed.
These can be left in the box.
I think it's supposed to be Hidme.
Hidme?
Hidme, yeah.
Hidme.
Yeah, Hidme.
Hidme cable.
Hidme again.
Yes.
Three main, the main components.
Three mics and two stands.
Use a Wisteria mic stand for mic three.
So guess which one is mic three?
I can't tell as long as the music is overwhelming the...
I did that.
And why did you do that?
And turned up a swelling...
He asked me if he'd made me.
You know, I had to follow these instructions.
I did.
Yeah, but nobody's going to hear the instructions.
Thanks to Craig Mitchell.
Craig Mitchell helped me last night.
Potter Nostril?
Yeah.
Well, Potter Nostril.
He's somewhere around here.
I don't know any Craig Mitchells.
I don't either.
I don't know what made me say that.
I was suddenly lost my mind for a minute.
Boy, here it is.
Okay, I'm all right now.
Is that from Mitchell's ice cream?
The nostrils have gone twice.
Oh, they're buying pancake supplies.
That's a good, good mission.
Well, Reverend Lucy and I brought some pancake supplies.
You got pancakes?
Yeah, we do.
You know, pancakes is the form of currency in several ancient countries.
Like ancient countries now?
Civilizations.
They weren't really countries.
They were more like civilizations.
City-states.
You could trade in them.
You know, they were like you could count them out, make them consistent.
In a sea of barbarism.
If you had salt pancakes, that'd be even better.
The polis of Athens.
Salt pancakes were one of the best.
Oh, yeah.
Well, because you have salt.
Which you can use as currency.
And lick.
Yeah.
Or gold pancakes.
Or you can use salt to pay the Roman army.
Celerium, they called it.
Nowadays, we use sugar, dough, and grease.
For doughnuts.
You say there's some more of those left over?
Hot damn.
Hey, uh, Bert!
Old mixer with separate power supply cord.
A very long mess of two long cords which together stretch from the mixer output to the sound booth.
The flaming sword that cuts the fiery cords.
Input at Caffeina's.
Okay, listen.
See, that was the one that we hijacked a minute ago and ripped apart.
The flaming sword that cuts the fiery cords.
It's very possible.
I think you should...
So you're gonna have to put those back together, I think.
Yeah, I don't remember any of that.
You were the one that did it, so I mean, you're gonna have to...
A weight of cords.
It's all in your body memory.
You have to remember your body remembers that.
Think about it.
Too much you can't have done.
You gotta do it on the subconscious level.
Put the cords in your hands and then just let your hands remember.
Huh?
The memory in your fingers.
Yeah, I know which one this is.
Wow.
What now?
For that four-way headphone jack, which otherwise isn't loud enough.
Wow, look.
We got the burgers and the slaw right here.
And you got the donuts.
You see, you just talk about them.
Wow.
There's a donut?
There are.
Look at this.
See, that's what it's all about.
Look at the outlandish donuts they give you around here, Philo.
I'm gonna eat my greens.
I'll start with them.
I was just gonna tell you that the two local libraries have put my books in the back.
They did?
I mean, our book comes out.
Well, it's your book.
I'm just a publisher.
I was recently told that there should probably be a glossary.
They said they liked the two up and two down.
Oh, you get that too.
I get that a lot from people that read the subgenius books.
But it's like, but it's defined in context.
And in fact, we usually, when we throw out a new word, we're describing what it means.
I mean, well, in the subgenius books, it's like that, because it's like, well, it's
because they're nonfiction.
They're like textbooks, science books.
But your novel is flighty work of imaginative fiction.
So yeah, it's got all kinds of crazy sounding stuff.
But you pick it up in context.
I didn't have any trouble.
You just have to read it closely.
It's not a thriller you can skim on an airplane ride.
It's something you really have to concentrate on.
That's what some people like.
In fact, my-
I'll take you away a little bit.
Most discerning science fiction fan friends, scholars of science fiction, such as the great
G. Gordon Gordon, who turned me on to all my favorite authors practically, he loves
it.
He thought it was a real, just like I did, he thought it was a real classic, instant,
I mean, really original and really fun to read.
And a strange kind of novel.
It's kind of a page turner.
And it sticks with you.
You know, you put the book down after you're finished doing your business in the bathroom
reading or extra meditating on it or whatever.
And then, but your mind keeps thinking in the same future vocabularies of the out of
control internet that's in your face.
That's cool to hear.
That's very lovely to hear because I was hoping that that would happen once in a while because
I noticed, I saw it as a vision rather than as a reality.
Some people actually kind of escape in this world.
I mean, escape into this world by reading it and stuff like that there.
Anyway, never mind.
I don't want to sound so highfalutin and-
Well, you know, the problem is, Dave, you don't have an agent and neither do I.
I can't be your agent because I don't know how to be an agent.
You know how you be an agent?
You have to know everybody.
Well, it's a little late for that.
I don't have the right haircut anyway and I'm not going to change it.
Yeah, plus all the people we know are all dead.
Well, that's not, I had an agent who was really good, Jane Jordan Brown in Chicago
and she died.
She'll show you.
And then later I had an agent and you did too, but he was a subgenius.
So he didn't stay an agent for long and he didn't really know everybody.
Because he wasn't as old and sophisticated as her.
In fact, he was just a subgenius from Houston.
He has a great band.
But anyway, yeah, we're not famous enough is the problem.
If you go to subgenius.com, the first thing it says in the first paragraph you read on
the homepage says we're publishing again and we have a book out called Neighbor World
and you click on that and you're buying it, you know, or even reading a sample of it on
the Amazon or whatever, because you can do that.
You can read the first few pages, I think.
That is so exciting.
It's wild and crazy.
It's like Clockwork Orange, but how come Stanley Kubrick's not making a movie of it?
Or actually maybe it'd be Zack Snyder would make the movie now.
Yeah.
Or Terry Gilliam.
That would be the loveliest of all to have an ex-python, which is once again, you said
it's not a reptile.
Right.
It's not a four-foot-tall panda.
No, it is.
A python is a reptile.
But a Monty Python is some sort of metaphor or something.
Well, metaphors and snakes are often confused.
Well, anyway, Terry Gilliam.
I mean, they don't know what's going on, so we assume they're confused.
Actually, they have a metaphor.
They have a higher sense of direction than we do.
Terry Gilliam would be the ideal director of the movie of Neighborworld, but that also
risks being cursed.
A lot of his movies have been cursed.
Although I understand he's finally getting to make his Don Quixote movie.
But who else would be a good director for Neighborworld?
Jim Jarmusch.
Jim Jarmusch from Cleveland.
Right.
Yeah.
He might even do it in black and white, just like Dead Man and the Beast.
Did you see Dead Man?
Oh, yeah.
Several times.
We showed it.
It was the last movie shown by Dr. Dark at X Day before he died.
Yep.
That left me with a strange, strange feeling.
And the funny thing was—
You know Iggy dressed up like a woman and all that?
I enjoyed that.
That movie was shown by popular demand.
There was a vote.
Dr. Dark, you see, of course, has done Dr. Dark's drive-in at Fox.
X Day drills for 20 years.
He's the only guy who is at every single 7 a.m. besides me up until last year.
He's quite a funny fellow.
Yeah.
And he would—his main drive-in fare was great, bad films.
Not the same old ones that you've seen a million times like Plan 9, but really unusual great,
bad films.
Yeah.
And the last X Day he was at, I think he suspected it might be, and he brought a copy
of every movie he had ever shown in those 20 years of X Days, which is always like two
or three a night.
And out of all those bad films and different movies, what the crowd really most wanted
to see was the one really good movie in the stack, which was Dead Man by Jim Jarmusch.
It's one of the most amazing Westerns I've ever seen.
And it's just bull-dada as hell.
Yeah.
All of the characters in it are great.
Johnny Depp is great, and Crispin Glover is in it.
It's just a creepy thing.
Billy Bob Thornton plays a transvestite bandit that just kills.
It could possibly—
Iggy Poppinsen.
Iggy's in there too as a weird woman.
Yeah, as the other transvestite.
And I guess it was Robert Mitchum's last movie.
Right.
It's really an amazing movie.
I lost my true love.
And you never know why.
That's fantastic!
That was fantastic.
Yeah.
I would've come over here, but I was stuck in traffic.
Oh man!
How was it?
How was that traffic animal?
It was great.
why was it great?
it was great, I mean we have the best traffic
everybody complains about it
they're like, you know, I noticed this
running theme of people being
able to show animosity
towards other drivers because of
their shortcomings
even though they're probably being
judged by the drivers in other cars
at the same time
you know
I always think of
when it comes to honking the horn
if not me, then who?
hoot hoot
who would honk
the horn in traffic if it weren't
if I don't
very Gandhi quote
I'm into
conservative use of horn
only when they really
deserve it
and you have a car
when you have a car
very conservative use of horn
I do yell at drivers
in the place of a horn
yeah, and that's the thing
wow, wow
traffic
that's happening
you know, but
that's actually more dangerous
because you don't have the false
sense of security that
very thin aluminum walls
or whatever it was that we drive around in
it's like paper thin walls
of cars that they now make
fiberglass
and
plastic
and the tears
of foreign children
yeah, there's some of those in there
that's why my headliner doesn't stick
because the kids aren't sad enough
in foreign countries these days
it's not as depressing as it used to be
is like the weather nice there or something?
probably
well, we should just leave it like that
not like it is here in Texas, that's for sure
but anyway, I was like
the traffic here is few
everybody complains
about how awful the traffic is
and we're like, the traffic is great
it's the best traffic there is
compare our traffic to anybody else's
maybe LA has better traffic than we do
but I mean, like the nature
New York's got some pretty great traffic
right, that's like the nature of traffic
it's traffic
it's like, look at it be in traffic
it's doing a great job
bumper to bumper, stop and go
really?
even just gridlocked
that is amazing
gridlock
that's beautiful traffic
one time I was in traffic with my friend
and I couldn't read her weird map
what's the point if you're not moving anywhere?
well, it was stop and go on like a highway
but it was in New York
so it was a lot of stop and go
so what we did
was I steered the car
from the passenger seat
she operated the brake
and looked at the map
and I basically told her when to stop
see, and it's so much safer that way
than the way I did it
when there was nobody else on the road
so zero traffic
which was horrible
yeah, because then you drive 90 miles
I'm going like 80 miles an hour
down the highways in Kansas
granted, they're all straight lines
you know
and well paid
because they're papers
and I'm sitting there reading
I think it was a
Thomas Pynchon
paperback or something
and my friend's steering the wheel
he's like, this will be hilarious
just, you know, kick your feet up
if you feel like it
and so he's basically driving the van
from the passenger seat
and I'm sitting there reading a book
and then I realized how stupid that was
but we didn't die
and neither did the people that passed us
that had the looks of horror
on their faces
when we saw what we were doing
I was in a
yeah, one time
who's to judge?
my friend got out of the driver's seat
in like his big rig driving
I mean, no, seriously though
in Kansas
who's to judge?
he just had on cruise control
he just stood up
and did some jumping jacks
because if you don't get caught
there is no judge
yeah, who is judging?
I thought it was fun
yeah
I didn't feel
jumping jacks in a big rig
I mean, where
you don't hear about that every day
what are you going to do
if you go off the road in Kansas
crash into a car?
cornfield?
yeah
you're going to gently graze
some like fields of grain
yeah, it's going to be so epically
flat
slightly rambunctious, I guess
you might be like
bump, bump
not really
bump, bump, bump
the sound of corn hitting the side of the car
and you eventually
the sound of corn hitting
you eventually come to a stop
and you know
your friend is going to be out of a job
but I just had a great adventure
so
maybe
they're going to be out of a job
who can tell
there's no damage to the vehicle
you just got to get that back on the road
yeah
right
I mean, there's probably some mud
you know, sprayed off
yeah, that's why they have truck washes
yeah
all this good
I mean, I don't even think
yeah, it's Kansas
yeah, traffic
so traffic is good
traffic is
it operates the way it's supposed to operate
absolutely perfect traffic in this town
I am totally impressed
impressed
we now resume
regularly scheduled programming
Freethink Radio
this is time for the show
welcome back
that was
he's a handsome guy
by
the pod
and Reverend Pease
and speaking of
Pease
and his pod
the Pease and the pod show
the podcast
starring Pease
is going to be coming out pretty soon
yeah
it's practically done
from what I heard
the theme song is unbelievable
so Pease
who was your first guest on the show?
and what was your first interview?
well
we're gonna do a dry run
because you're a dry man
I know
we've gone over it
exactly
oh look at you
pre-seeing my jokes
before I even say them
that's great
well it's because I have a wet sense of humor
I was ready
but
well it's true
but I thought
I thought during the pre-production meeting of the pre-production show
that we were gonna come out of this break right into Blind Eye
so I had my blind eye ready to go
no I think they said
I wasn't prepared to talk about my blind eye
I sent viewer mail
but what you're not prepared to talk about your show
but the show's ready
we said we would do something
the show's ready right?
right I'm ready
I'm ready
I'm ready to do my blind eye
I mean didn't you release the theme song today?
it's fabulous dude
it is
here's the thing
I tell Fid
like oh
I wanna do this thing
and Fid goes
I don't know who any of those people or shows are
and so I'm like well just google it
then he comes back to me
with this like
perfect
I mean it's like
wow I wish I was this talented
because this is exactly what was in my head
and I don't know if uh
all of our Patreon users got to hear it today
but it is a fabulous
if you know the concept of this show
which is kind of like a tease
uh
um
the concept of your show
the concept of my show
this show has no concept
as we all know
but my show is kind of like an intro
it's an interview based format
kind of like on a Mike Douglas or Merv Griffin
um
variety show thing
so we needed that type of music
Fid really stepped up and made some great stuff
um
we're
we're gonna have some bits that we do
I'm gonna interview some people
you're swimming in theme songs around here aren't we?
yeah
so here's the thing
here's the people that have agreed to be on this show
and I don't know in what order we're gonna do it
oh you're gonna
you're gonna bust this cherry now?
I'm gonna do it now
alright
Dr. Lobo
anybody who's familiar with Dr. Lobo
who is uh
a great patron of Monster Films
COSMAC'S COMMANDOS
well I didn't see
he's not Cosmac
he's Dr.
he's Dr. Lobo
I know
Mr. Lobo
I'm sorry I just wanted to say that
I'm sorry go ahead
but it's alright
Cosmac Commandos
you can always yell that out
um
but I think our
our big jewel in the sky
is gonna be
an exclusive interview from Portugal
with uh
J. George L. Martin?
Jordan Jordan
J. Jordan Jordan
yeah
also known as G. Jordan Jordan
by people who actually know him
who read the book yeah
now here's the thing
here's the thing
the book
Pease and
and Guy Duell
or whatever you wanna call him
uh
have
you know
they have a rocky relationship
a uh
a commudrenly
respect for each other
he
he does not like to admit that I saved him
from being kidnapped by the mimes
when I first came into the church
uh
started a whole
page
to help
uh
started a detective agency
to find him
and rescue him from the mimes
and he's been bitter ever since really
but uh
he's agreed to put that aside
and be on the show
we're gonna do a great interview with him
there'll be some musical guests
and of course
Fid's great uh
theme song
and there'll be
it's gonna be
a fabulous show
and we're only probably
24 to 36 months out
from the first episode
so
okay
so at least it's a realistic production schedule
that's right everybody
so uh
it's a real schedule
Disney makes four superhero movies a year
I mean
this is just a scale
well look at their budget dude
look at their budget
yeah
what
twenty forty dollars
so just tune your laptop to freethinkradio.com
put it on the other side of the room
and chain yourself to the radiator
because Peas in a Pod is coming to you
soon
in
the next episode
Peas in a Pod
we're gonna be
talking about
the
the the the the the the
the the the the the world
the time
the title
the dot
letol
uh
why
but
Wide open shutter
Shut up
Phases in
Eyes that shudder like a wide open shutter
Eyes that flutter like a wide open shutter
Shut up
Come with me baby
Come with me
Cottage cottage cottage
Going through
Good old Captain Beefheart
He was crazy as a loon
They were all
magnetic pirates
You know what I mean
They could see the future
Captain Beefheart
What about King Crimson in the very early days? 21st century schizoid man
21st century schizoid man
I think all of those guys
Especially Beefheart
Now you sound like Don VanVlein
You sound like Don VanVlein
Yeah, well I was listening to it today
I memorized all of those in my youth
I know them by heart
I know him by Beefheart.
All his earlier albums.
I didn't...
After I became a dad,
I didn't buy things anymore for me.
A lot of times you're not allowed to
unless you're an official dad
and have all the data that you need
to carry on your person.
But now that Captain Beefheart's dead,
we know about all his flaws.
You can read about how crazy he was
in all these biographies.
He's a very, very demanding fellow.
Yeah.
I've known some of these creative types.
They can be hard to live with.
Present company excluded, of course.
A friend of mine that you know also
who died recently, a friend of mine,
was invited to work with Frank Zappa
for a couple weeks.
And he said it was weird
because Zappa's kids,
I don't know whether it was his kids
or he meant his grandkids
or whatever they were,
had cameras.
Everybody filmed everything all the time.
They'd walk right up to your face
and take film of you.
Like, say, Daddy Frank Zappa's talking away
and stuff like that.
And a little kid comes up
and sticks a camera right in your face,
a source right in your nose.
I'm not real surprised.
He thought it was fun.
I can see that happening at certain times
at my house in the old days.
There was a time when my wife,
my first wife and I used to let subgeniuses
crash on our floor.
I hadn't met any of the crazies yet.
It was annoying was the worst we'd gotten
for the first couple of years.
And it was a real menagerie sometimes.
If there was a devival in Dallas
or Little Rock,
there'd be a whole tribe of weirdos in my house.
A messiah.
And a bunch of crazy,
crazy, crazy, crazy, crazy, crazy, crazy,
My dad walked in one morning
after a subgenius convention.
He probably had seen something like it, actually.
I later learned.
Yeah, but see,
we had to quit living like Frank Zappa
because we never got famous, rich, and popular
because we were subgeniuses.
And flying under the radar.
And all had jobs.
That was the really tragic thing.
Now, how can you say they were all a bunch of head jobs
while they were flying on radiators?
That doesn't make any sense.
No, it was the only way we could get away with it.
We had to keep a low profile.
Why did you want to get away with it to begin with?
Why wouldn't you want to be turned into
a full-blooded Christian hero?
Because it was there.
You know, how could we not?
How could Philo and I,
having once realized the truth of Bob,
just ever walk away from it?
You'll notice, I mean,
other subgeniuses have come and gone.
A lot of them come and go and then come back.
And then go and then come back.
And come back and go and come back.
And some just go.
But I expect those to come back eventually.
Some just come back.
They always do.
They have to.
How else are they going to spawn?
Anyway,
yeah, they...
But I guess where...
There's too many crazy people out there.
And also,
I hate having to clean up after some of them.
And get them out of jail.
And, you know...
The worst are the ones that would camp out
by the post office
hoping to see Bob show up to get the mail.
I actually had to hide from them a couple of times.
And a bunch of them thought you were actually Bob
and you tried to explain it.
And that one guy, well, he...
He went a little too far, didn't he?
Didn't they all?
There were a bunch of them.
Yeah, lots of them did.
Yeah, I've had to...
There's been many a time
so I had to cross my fingers behind my back and go,
look, man, Bob's just a made-up character.
And they'd go...
They'd be really disappointed, but they'd go away.
And then Bob would come out from the closet and go,
great job, Stan.
That was great.
You did just right.
I'll remember to have...
Remember to ask me to take you out to lunch someday.
I gotta go.
Right, you'd hit him in the closet
just like you used to have to do in England
with the religious figures or the figurines.
No, he'd hide.
It's because he'd be in there, you know,
doing number three.
Bob was kind of really rude about just going,
oh, I've got to do number three right now.
And he'd run off in a closet
and you'd hear all these weird noises.
And he'd come out,
I feel like a new man.
But no one could ever figure out...
They had to figure out...
He had a machine at Dobstown
that he could just walk up to and do number three,
but right in front of you,
but you couldn't figure out what was actually happening.
Well, why did you need a personal history?
You know, it was enough to know that he had done it
and everybody was aware of it.
Well, he acted like it.
He acted like so many other things.
Bob acted like that was normal.
It's like everybody had to do number three all of a sudden.
It was like most of us,
we only made it as far as number two.
We don't even know what number three is.
I got to two and a half one time
and it wasn't even the same experience
that I started with, you know,
number one or number two.
And I wondered about the time,
I was wondering if it was the same kind of experience
Bob was indeed having on level number three.
And I fell asleep.
I couldn't...
And I swore I was going to take notes
and everything like that.
And I had the notebook out
and a little handheld keyboard.
Maybe you did number three in your sleep.
It's possible.
All things are possible.
A lot of people do number one in their sleep.
Some people do number two in their sleep.
I'm doing exercises to try to preserve
my number two controlling glands
and brain and muscles.
Everybody.
Everybody has to nowadays.
Most of them don't.
You know.
Yeah, unfortunately.
The only reason I do is because I have to.
Yeah, it's small quarters there in the cantina.
I guess if you left the other restrooms alone,
you'd have to come back all the way
from halfway around the world or something.
I don't know.
I don't know what Bob does when he's not,
you know, like when he's just sort of out on the road
and in public.
Does he run into service, gas stations, I mean,
and say, where could I do number three?
Where's your second stage restroom or whatever?
You know, I don't know what he...
We just don't know.
You're just saying you're not an expert.
For all we know, it's a little time travel booth
and he sends some organ of his body
into some other time and place.
I have no idea.
That's what I was hoping.
I was hoping that.
For a long time now.
You know, it could be anything.
Literally anything.
With Bob.
Barkley like...
Ugh.
Call Bob.
Yeah.
Thank you.