You will hear an important message prepared by Director J. Edgar Hoover.
Who are you?
Of the Federal Bureau of Investigation.
J. Edgar Hoover, Director of the Federal Bureau of Investigation,
has prepared this following important message.
In case of the hour of slack, remain disturbed.
Do not act normal so far as possible.
But now let me tell you a story that I think will tug at your heartstrings as it did mine.
The Self-Genius Hour of Slack.
Shut up, listen.
From PR News in Washington, I'm just 41% contained.
In eastern Afghanistan, the Trump declared a major PR news.
In California, the declaration opens up federal funds to help PR news.
In a rural area of California, PR news exploded.
In northern California, the nearly two-week-old car bomber
now covers more than $1.5 million.
In the United States, the number of people who have been arrested
is 221 square percent in the U.S. and Colombia.
NATO says this is PR.
The director of a Syrian research facility set a new record
for the most PR news in Washington.
Now we're going to have a rare old
on July 5th, 1997 a.m.
when we all have hangovers.
Wotan's judgment will take place in the form of what the prescriptors call
the
The Advent of the Angelic Host.
Like any other prophet, Bob preaches about the end of the world.
Only his predictions are just a little different.
July 5th, 1998, at 7 a.m. to be exact,
the men from Planet X, as the news media will call them,
will arrive to rupture the subgeniuses,
the true believers of geniuses,
up into the escape vessels of the sex goddesses.
And believe it or not, plenty of people,
4,000 of them so far and more every day,
have already joined up.
Suddenly the joke has become serious and profitable.
Your standard religious rip-off, right?
But can anybody take this stuff seriously?
Dear Bob, it's time to close my eyes.
Remember now, it's no surprise,
if I should be found dead someday,
I'll think that you were in the way.
Oh, gimme Bob.
Confusing that face.
With my own.
Can't remember my place.
Bob's role on this planet
is to see that the Earth is not sold
on that glorious or terrible day
we call X-Day in 1998.
Fossils of the past.
Dinosaurs of the subgenius age.
Are you saying they're all not so both?
Remnants of prehistoric life.
Yes.
Life was hearty and the devil
would grab you right by the hindmost
and do whatever he wanted to with you.
You know what I mean?
Yes, another feature of those days.
The demonic presence urging forward
and the heavenly one beckoning forward.
We're missing back.
Was there someone else again?
Every one of these movies
were крупed together
these untrue victims
Eventhough pets and animals
упом 1990
People,
time to get us also
of pleased eyes.
I believe that's very much
an amazing story.
What a book.
Cool.
It is.
Oh gosh.
cool, fragrant breeze.
These instruments include hits like
Miserlew.
Where the mangoes grow in the mangrove groves.
Babaloo.
Babaloo to you too.
Belly high.
Yes.
And Wimoe.
Belly high, they tell you,
when you learn to swim.
Keep your belly high, dear,
when you swim in the chimp.
Oh, is that what they were talking about?
I did not know that.
All right.
Swamp fire by some band.
Worst case of swamp fire I ever saw.
It's pretty tasty if you ask me.
I've been using that ointment
proemptively, see.
Ointment?
Yeah, because I know everybody gets swamp fire
at the campground sooner or later,
unless you use your cornstarch
or your ointment.
Put plenty of cornstarch in there,
it dries it up.
So.
You get that cornstarch crinkle when you walk,
but at least you're free of the swamp fire syndrome.
Keeps you dry and sliding,
to quote Ken Casey, actually,
in Whole Earth Catalog.
Yes, before it got to be all about computers.
Yeah, well, it used to be all about cornstarch
and how it keeps them sliding, man.
And farm machinery and stuff like that.
That's right.
I never got to meet Ken Casey, but he was a,
he was a dues paying subgenius
who went by the name Reverend Hardly Visible.
Yes, that's quite true.
And his friend Babs was into it.
Oh, and just recently I discovered that
Zane Casey, the son of Ken,
is selling Bob, Dobbs Head blotter acid sheets,
only without the acid, you know, just a collector's item.
Just for art.
Blotter for art's sake, acid for acid.
For acid's sake.
I find that a forced art form myself.
Ken Casey was on St. Stupid's March back in the day.
He performed at Washington Square Park
at the end of one of those St. Stupid's Day parades.
I introduced him.
It was the day when we were allowed to use that park.
Since then, the city withdrew its permission.
Hmm.
Well, that acid, blotter acid art
is just miniature Andy Warhol.
Yeah, they found a real little tiny Andy Warhol to do it.
Seems like that would be very repetitive effort
for the most part.
The same head over and over again in different colors.
It's a screening.
That's pretty much it by definition.
It's a screening process with your tiny little,
little silkscreen machine.
Tiny little Andy Warhols.
Oh, look, how cute.
Waving at us now.
The, one of the weirdest guys I've ever known
who is not actually technically a subgenius.
He was my friend in high school.
Yes.
Jim Long.
He was the son of a child psychiatrist.
If that helps explain just how weird this guy might be.
Yes, that could add to it.
Yeah, it did, believe me.
And he, with my help, crashed a film festival party.
There was a time when Dallas had a pretty snazzy film festival
called the USA Film Festival.
It was kind of hip.
That first year, they had Dennis Hopper, Andy Warhol,
and a bunch of other, yeah, I think I saw it.
Frank Capra there.
He was still alive.
Wow.
Anyway, we crashed.
I had a film in it, a little claymation thing.
And so I was able to go to the party,
and I brought my friend, who was a complete alcoholic
at the age of 17.
He got completely blasted.
Sat down next to Warhol, between Warhol and Dennis Hopper,
and started monologuing Jim Long style to Andy Warhol.
Oh, goodness.
And Warhol was absolutely fascinated.
He sat there, like, listening to this kid do his really surrealist,
amazing rap, which Jim himself probably doesn't remember any of.
Was it a Jane Eyre-like thing?
Sort of.
The only example I know of, the end of the uncut version of my movie,
Let's Visit the World of the Future,
the end titles go over gag reel, you know, screw-up background shots,
which are sort of funny.
But the soundtrack, instead of being music,
is that guy going on and on and on and on about it.
And it's a prime example of maybe a little bit like,
who was Kesey's friend, the speed freak, Neil Cassidy?
Yes.
Yeah.
Okay.
Who was famous for these endless,
ongoing monologues?
Or the famous Michael Pepe, our beer-spilling friend.
If only he could just stick to swilling, that would be great.
Well, did he convince you by spilling some beer somewhere?
Dr. Howell, I've been in your radio show twice with the famous Michael Pepe.
Yes.
Oh, he's amazing.
I've seen you say over and over again, no, you can't set your beer down in here,
especially not over here on the control panel.
And he would go, oh, yeah, okay, okay.
And he'd set it down on the control panel.
Yes.
The amazing thing about him is, well, he set his chair on fire two times
while he was there without realizing it, and we had to put it out both times.
Wow.
Yeah, that's pretty amazing.
That's like a Doctors for Wotan song.
It is.
Would you tell me if my face was on fire?
You would think so.
I think somebody would know if their face was on fire.
But a really good friend will tell you that.
Well, they will eventually know.
Yeah, right.
If your face is on fire, they won't try to be polite.
They'll just say, man, your face is on fucking fire, okay?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Oh, thank you for telling me.
Just pat it out there.
Pat, pat, pat, pat, pat, pat.
There.
Now your face is not on fire.
Yeah.
So Michael could set his chair on fire and not know.
He has a ...
Seems like ...
He's smoky.
And the ash falls between his legs down into the stuffing of the old stool that he's sitting
on, and somehow starts a fire.
But even that is extremely unusual and unlikely because you know those ashes never do start
fires.
It's tobacco ashes that do.
Those don't start fires.
Nonetheless, on this case, it happened twice.
After we put out the first fire ...
Right, right.
Of course.
... Michael Pepe was walking and he set his chair on fire for the second time.
Oh, God.
No, that time we went to Burning Man, Michael Pepe was our guest on the RV and he broke
everything he touched.
Yes.
Literally.
I mean, mirrors, doorknobs, seats.
He pulled the doorknob handle off the screen door and Philo was enraged at him.
And to cool off, Michael Pepe went into the bathroom from where the shower of broken glass
from the shattering bathroom mirror could be heard.
Unbelievable.
Everywhere he went, it was like there was just a cloud of ...
Everything he touched, he destroyed.
Yes.
That was odd.
And yet, I think I can say, as far as I understand such things, it may not be much, Michael Pepe,
the guy we're talking about, is kind of a genius.
He absolutely is.
And I'm always happy to get him on my show because ...
Despite the setting of the whole station on fire, his own face.
Well, yeah, we've had problems like that, but we've had him flailing and knocking out
important plugs and things and cutting us off the air and so forth.
But at any rate, he's still great to have because you can actually have an interesting
conversation with him.
Like Dave.
Yeah.
It's not like it's just you talking.
You get to talk to somebody and it makes it much more interesting, I think.
Well, he can do some real flights of fancy in the middle of otherwise ordinary subject
He was known in the 1980s for his behavior music, performance art, some of which employed
the video medium where against the screen, screens, well, screams also of himself.
On the screen, he interacted in intricate fashion.
Well, the video projection proved that he wasn't just randomly making spazzy noises
and jerks.
It was composed.
Yes.
Spazzy noises and jerks.
He works it all out very carefully in a dance.
He had his own form of written behavior music.
Yes.
Grunts, squeals, twitches.
And it all comes together in a kind of harmony.
Yeah.
And it's a very good thing.
So it was like a written concert of music that no one's ever heard before.
And it wasn't just made up off the top of his head.
It was memorized.
I couldn't ... I kind of went on ...
He uses it.
He could just, in perfect sync with the seemingly random stuff.
That's what made it so impressive.
It was rehearsed.
I mean, he ...
Notations, a heavy manuscript.
I've seen him ...
I've seen him with ... So you see it all is worked out very extensively, exhaustively
in advance.
And then performed vigorously.
Sure.
I guess it helps if you can write music and then have performers who can read music.
If you're doing that kind of music, like Frank Zappa did, you had to be a really first
class musician.
Yeah.
I had to be a first class performer.
I had to be able to take notes and be able to read his musical notation on the fly.
Not that I know anything about that, myself.
Well, the more actual musicians you have in your group, the better your group's going
to sound.
Yeah.
My group didn't have any.
I was in a doctor band.
You weren't allowed to play an instrument if you knew how to.
I mean, it could be very difficult to play an instrument if you knew how to.
And it sounded quite terrible for an hour, but there'd always be five minutes in each hour that was unbelievable.
And so after thousands of hours, we had a half hour of really good stuff.
To splice together.
If you're, you know, if it wasn't a quiet place.
Audio studio editing brilliance.
Most people would still hate it.
But yeah, the instrument I play is the splicer and the computer.
The clash of the splicer as the blade slips through.
The splicer and the editing bin.
Nowadays it's a virtual editing bin.
It's just a bunch of file names in order.
It doesn't take up as much room, that's for sure.
Or it smells bad.
Well, film smells funny.
Because of the chemical treatment.
Also, there's film cleaner, which you can run your film through.
Well, when it's fresh, it smells fresh from the lab.
I love that smell.
Just processed film.
Then you dig out the same reel of film 30 years later and it smells like ammonia.
Well, unfortunately, it's going the way of all things.
But yeah, I think how much how you'd smell if you were opened up out of being in a can for 30 years.
The film probably smells a lot better.
I'm not being critical.
Yeah.
So, yeah, it's hard to preserve, actually.
That's why you got your climate controlled fault in your monthly charge.
I spent $3,000 of the starving Bobby's money.
Just on the spray foam insulation of the new shed that holds all of the thousand years of subjunius artistic output.
Well, you had to make a command decision.
And so you thought that the liquidity of their donations was more important.
Well, the Texas house doesn't have a basement or an attic.
Or really a second floor.
Just one row around of a second floor.
And the rest is.
The thing that they do in Texas where it makes you feel like you're outside when you're inside.
The ceiling of the living room goes up two stories.
But is it nice and cool?
Three stories.
Cool like a stone cave inside?
Is it cool inside like a stone cave?
No.
Thanks to the air conditioning?
Yeah.
Thanks to the AC.
Very expensive air conditioning?
Yes.
The one we had to replace.
Man, my dad was the most brilliant of all subjunius.
He knew when all of the main appliances in the house were going to break.
And he died one week before they all went down.
Leaving me with the bill.
And very little in life insurance policy.
But a really nice house.
Beautiful house.
If you like.
Beautiful land.
A very hard to heat and cool giant house without any storage area.
Just looks pretty.
A stately staying manner.
Yes, it is.
And it's way out in the middle of the woods.
So you can't see it from the highway or anything.
It's protected by barbed wire.
Off the main drain.
Redneck relatives who are all armed to the teeth.
And I'm not kidding.
They really are.
Yeah, you wouldn't want to go.
And dogs.
Blundering around there in the middle of the night.
Right.
Not to mention the built in.
Not a good idea.
Dangers.
The cactus.
The tarantulas.
The giant dick eating.
The giant eating spiders.
All that stuff.
Rattlesnakes.
Luckily, hardly anybody has a giant dick.
But, you know, if you do, you don't want to mess with those spiders.
They happen to be tiny.
Copper heads.
Yeah.
Knuckle heads.
Pin heads.
Bullet heads.
Sidewinders.
Bob heads.
Dobbs heads.
They're all over the place.
And you've got your.
We had a spray for Dobbs heads.
A beaded animated walking purse.
That with a little.
B wise.
Scissor safe.
Spοι sara blocks.
NYU award won
for one $40.
You and I was going to be here and think.
We're also going to be here on June 56.
Asexual toads
And fire ants
They've moved on
The ants have moved on?
Yeah, the fire ants have moved on to Oklahoma
Well, alright, that's good
I'm bringing the red ants back
Get along well without those things
My friends, the big harvester ants
I encourage them
Because they're the food of the horny toads
You see
And they were the enemy of the fire ants
So we always poison the fire ants daily
But there are none to poison now
And the red ants are coming back
I love them, they were my friends
Red ants?
Yeah
I was always third baseman
But aren't they fierce?
James, huh?
Red ants, aren't they somewhat fierce?
No, they're my
I'm like Tarzan was with apes
Well, you just get along well with them
I suppose
Yeah
I used to pick them up and talk to them
And they can sting
Exactly, they can sting
But you can get big enough that you can hold them
In a way that you can then like
Put your little fingerprint inside their jaw
And let them pinch you
Right
And they're trying to sting you with their butt
But it's really easy to keep them
Well, whatever you're willing to put up with
Or tolerate, I suppose
Well, I'm hoping they'll bring my friends
The horny toads back
You know why I like them horny toads?
They're reptiles
Well, yeah, yeah
They're horned lizards
Texas horned lizards
Yes, just so
And they're cute as a button
Absolutely
And of course they have that habit
That strange habit when you pick them up
Of suddenly squirting blood out of their eyes on you
I never saw that happen once
Oh, really?
I honestly thought it was an urban legend
An old hag's tale
But I keep reading about it
It does actually happen
Well, uh
Horny toads
Yes, and their ways
Yeah, they're actually harmless
Of course
Absolutely harmless
Like most in nature's kingdom
They only want to make a living on their own
Without interference from humans
Well, they don't have to worry about that on Stang Ranch
Right, where a general atmosphere of laissez-faire permeates
And all are allowed to go their own way
Well, it's not that
It's that there are no humans
There are bipedal subgenius types
That have human blood
Did I tell you about my brother's DNA test?
What about the crunch of hiking boots?
But your brother's DNA test, you think?
Yeah, yeah
We have a higher percentage of Neanderthal
Than 70% of the people who took that company's DNA test
Hmm
From Lost Valley
Yeah, yeah, yeah
That made us really proud
And we also discovered that we're
Almost solid British Isles
Which was surprising
It turns out Reverend Stang isn't
A grandson of a Cooley
And my brother is a white person
Strangely enough
So this is for sure
You've got these DNA tests
Chemicals, yeah, chemicals don't lie
23 or me, that kind of thing
A company that you mail spit to
Wouldn't lie, would they?
Wouldn't just tell somebody what they think they want to hear
Now the Neanderthalers were up there in the frozen land of Europe
That's how do you think I got this great big nose?
And so they probably had silky fur of some kind
Because everything had silky fur up there
The rhinoceros, the elephant
It all had to have fur
Because it was so cold
And
So with the humans
And the eye sockets of the Neanderthal
Were up where our foreheads are
Their elongated skulls
And massive brow ridges
There's a Neanderthal girl reconstruction
That manages to make you go
Oh gosh, it's a showgirl
Shame that she's not around
That's really striking
What's her phone number?
Yeah, she was a redhead too
Right, yeah
Heavy eyebrows
Kind of well-manized eyebrows
But quite pretty
I'd hit it
She did have a remarkably short forehead
But that doesn't mean anything
They had a fine cranial capacity
They had such bigger brains
Yeah, their heads go far back
Farther back than ours
They don't go as far back as ours
Far up as ours
I had a math teacher
He was the opposite
His forehead bulged out
He looked like Exeter
And he had the Stevenson style
But the back of his head was caved in
President Merkin Muffley
Talk about an odd-shaped head
The back of his head was caved in
Well, that's most unusual
It was like cylindrical, you're saying?
His neck just continued up in a curve
Into where it should have been
The back of his head
As you recall
Oh, I'm sorry, I missed that
I was looking at an entity
This was a high school math teacher
You were reminiscing about
With an unusually shaped cranial
Yeah, he was a college math teacher
All right, a college math teacher
A giant forehead, alien forehead
His forehead bulged out
But behind his head
The skull didn't stick out
Very far
The back of his head
Could have been a birdbath
It was even concave
Rather than convex
Yeah, if he lay with his face down
You could put a little bit of water
Well, that surely can't have been intentional
It must have been the result
Of some sort of accident
And it wouldn't hurt his nose
To put his face flat down
Because it wouldn't touch the concrete
Because his forehead would reach it
Way before any other part of his face
He was really freaky looking
Mm-hmm
I think he was Iranian, too
Uh-huh
Originally
So he wasn't in an accident
But this was his natural configuration
He was a flathead Iranian
But the opposite of flathead Indians
I'll say it
They put the board on the back
To force the forehead out
Right
Well, the flathead Indians, of course
That was their style of beauty
That was their way of trying to look like
Their idea of a subgenius
Or a yeti
Ah
Well, are we subgeniuses
Not a tribe of some kind
Some incoherent kind
What?
Some mutant kind
A tribe
Butants, we call them
Butant
Yes
Yeah, beautiful mutants
Actually, my little daughter
Coined that term, butants
That's a good one
She was about 11 years old
Uh-huh
Well
The butants of Mutantis
Right
That legendary lost domain
The glories of Mutantis
You've drawn some Mutantis cityscapes
Yes
That look almost like Wally Wood
Outer space cities
One would almost think
You were influenced by the black and white
Uh-huh
Yeah, the black and white
Drawings
Those comic books and stuff
I do prefer them in black and white
The underground influence
See what happens when Philo's not around
We end up talking about film technology
Old movies
The little rascals
Bee movie stars
And science
Which puts everybody to sleep
That's a good idea
Let's talk about science
Because there's more of it than ever
And what do you talk about?
What about when Philo is here?
Well
Well, he just changes the subject to himself
We talk about Philo, I think
We talk about his propensity
To use a sound effect
Of startling suddenness and loudness
I see
Overwhelms the rest of the proceedings
But many interesting things
Seem to have occurred
In the world of science recently
And I'm
One thing in the science news
Is that the world really is
Definitely coming to an end
Aliens are not
As we know it
Well, nothing lasts
Something's going to change
Nothing lasts forever
Things wear out
The center cannot hold
Personally, I think the ocean
Is going to be the fulcrum
The deciding point
The condition of the chemical nature of the ocean
As it changes and heats up
And everything dies
And the mutant creatures
That have to
You know, there's
There's a life form
Crustacean horror across the earth
But the moon is also shrinking
Collapsing in on itself
The moon?
Yes, the moon quakes
Detested by NASA
Are actually from the skin
The outer surface wrinkling
As it shrinks
Down in the center
Vertical escarpments
Well, what do you expect
With the gigantic spherical skull
Of an ancient giant god
Or in
Actually, it's what the moon is
It is a huge skull
Or in one comic book
The egg of some creature
Which hatched
You know, creating consternation
The egg
As well it might
Yes, so that was another one
But just as Edgar Rice Burroughs posited
The moon actually is hollow
And apparently shrinking in on itself
Hollow moon theory
That's crackpots
Why the moon rang like a bell
When the fast-moving probe
Landed on it many years ago
Confirming the scientific suspicion
That the satellite was essentially
A hollow sphere
Collapsing toward its center
And then there's the possibility
That there's more water
Located in the inner earth
Or underground
Way, way deep underground
And there is covering the entire ocean
Which means that if that stuff
Came squirting out
You'd have water world
It would just eventually
Cover Mount Everest
When the lord opened up
The fountains of the deep
The most horrible concentration camps
Of cannibal warlords of all
Will be on Mount Everest
And then even those will go down
Actually, there's a really good
Stephen Baxter's
Book called Ark
Two of them
Deluge and Ark
Where that idea is used
As the end of the world
And the richest humans
And governments
It's all the water
That we didn't know about
That was underground
The United States does some stupid thing
With nukes at the bottom of the Pacific
Or something
And the water level starts rising
All over the whole world
In about 15 or 20 years
It covers all the land
By that time there's
The last outposts were
Of course in mountains
The Rockies, Himalayas
And so forth
And then there was a space project
A floating city project
And an underwater life project
And the space project
Goes way, way, way, way bad
And so does the
Big floating city
They're just not sustainable
But at the very end
There's signals coming
From the bottom of the ocean
So maybe that project
Lived to be the sequel
What, one of them was supposed
To go to the bottom of the ocean?
Well, they were trying to
Keep some humans alive
Don't ask me why
But they were trying to
They sent colonies out
Into space
In three different directions
That all went
Uh-huh
Krupp
In bad ways
Like they probably would
In real life
And usually due to
Office politics, actually
And, you know, physical accidents
Then
Oh, and the fact
There's no place to go
The ocean-going city
I forget what
Basically they just
Went barbaric
And it sank
A hundred years later
And, yeah, there was no
Kevin Costner to come
Jumping out of the water
And save every human being
From the smokers
I actually loved that movie
Waterworld
I've seen it several times
I know it's a stupid
Kevin's gate and everything
But I really enjoyed it
I thought it was a cool concept
The merman was stupid
But, you know, you gotta have
Well, so there's a merman in it, huh?
Yeah
Interesting
Well, he's a mutant
Who breathes air
Another mutant
But he can
Dive down to the bottom
Of the ocean
And gather up
The most precious thing there is
On the surviving humans
Which is dirt
And nobody knows where this
This loner is getting all his dirt
But he's basically
Swimming to
All the way down to the bottom
And scooping up a bucket of dirt
It's like gold
You can buy water
He buys a lemon with it
A little lemon tree plant
And he
He kills it
And he kills somebody over it
You know, that's how
That's what a
That's what we have to look forward to, folks
An over-budgeted
Kevin Costner movie of a world
Wasn't that like the most expensive movie ever made or something?
At that time it was ridiculously expensive
Anything you do on the ocean in real life
Is gonna go bonkers
But not the most expensive movie ever made
However, great expense was spent on it
In that pre-digital time
To create a giant barge
Which I saw at the Mojave spaceport
When Chick and John's bus went there
For some reason they had it there
It was visible
Wow
The floating city they made?
A giant barge which was from Waterworld
Was there
It was dragged there
Well, there were only two locations until the very end
One was this floating
Wooden city
Of wretches
And the other one was the
What was the name?
The name of that oil tanker that spilled all over
The Exxon Valdez
Yeah, yeah, the Exxon Valdez is still floating
And it's been taken over by pirates
Called Smokers
Because they still have all the Marlboros
And Dennis Hopper
Yeah, yeah
It's a lot of fun
A lot of fun
It's an old movie to kids, to people nowadays
Oh
Vintage
That could never happen
There's a bit in the new Avengers movie
Where Tony Stark, Iron Man
They're trying to figure out how to deal with this bad situation
They're in outer space
And Spider-Man, who's a stupid kid
Basically goes
Hey, did you ever see that movie Aliens?
And it's like
If you mention one of your old movies again one more time
He goes
No, no, wait a minute
And then later on, sure enough
Iron Man goes to the movie
And does the suggestion
He blows a hole in the side of the spaceship
And the bad guy flies out
And Spider-Man saves him from being pulled out into space
With his web at the last second
Sounds like fun
So see, those old movies can teach you something
When you're trapped by bad aliens on a spaceship
If it comes up
Say, we don't have to worry about the Exes being bad to us
But other subgeniuses
We've had some real bullies out here at times
And you know a lot of them are just
Their hate is much greater than, say, mine
Be that as it may
I'm not out to destroy the world
I just want to save the good parts
Your spaceship is the only thing keeping you alive
And you should avoid all solutions involving
Blasting and blowing things out
Depressurizing
Damaging the equipment
It's all you have
Oh, but if you're Spider-Man
You just seal it up with your web
Just like that, see
Zip, zip, zip
That's good, that's good
Or Iron Man, he can weld it all he's got
Capable of functioning as a spaceship
After that, alone as a life support
Anyway, you want to treat your spaceship carefully
That's what I always say
But did they listen? No
This isn't some no-account human spaceship we're talking about
No, it was one of Thanos' people
Poor Dr. Legume
Poor Dr. Legume, he said the saddest thing to me
He said, for me, Thanos
Thanos wins
Because he knew he wasn't going to live to see Endgame
And for him, Thanos did win
But no doubt I'll be duking it out with Dr. Legume in four days
Because he's already vowed
The minute he sees my pleasure saucer
He's going to come after me
And try to take away all my loot
Just to be mean
Maybe he's had a change in his mind
He's had a huge change of heart, though
Oh, actually, he did become very
He had a huge change of heart
In real life, he learned that niceness was actually not too bad
And he let go of all his pointless hate
Of course, he still had his true motivating hate
But he quit being pissed off at the other people
Of geniuses as much
Because, I mean, God, come on, man
What do you expect?
It's just how people are
The hate that was wasted his time
That's what people do
That's Charlene's new slogan
It's sort of like, you know
Unfortunately, it is
Shit happens
Funny little monkeys
Yeah, funny little monkeys
It's philosophical
People, once again
And it's literally true
It is what people do
People do everything
That they possibly can
Good, bad, and indifferent
Now, wasn't there an ad campaign
Years ago about
Do people really care
If little Tommy Grunderson
Gets Wi-Fi
And then it'd say, people do
People do
Was the constant refrain of this ad campaign
Do you remember it?
No, I don't
I don't see it
Remember the reiteration of the phrase, people do
Well
The only place I ever
See ads anymore is on YouTube
I have to sit through
You may skip the ad in four, three, two
Finally
There, finally goes away
Yeah, people, sure
Yeah
Yeah, we got free of television
But did ye mark my words?
The minute I understood what the internet really was
Which was around 1994
Thanks to Philo
I kind of went
This is gonna change everything
And I was right
And I also thought
It's gonna be like the Wild West for a while
And then it's gonna be like TV
And sure enough, look what happened
Nobody listens to the old prophet of doom
Until it's too late
But I don't say I didn't tell you so
That's cause you got
Damn it
Cassandra syndrome
Where you can tell them what's gonna happen
But they never believe you
The more you tell them
The more you are resenting
No fate
That's my motto
I'm not a determinist
That's true
What's her name-ist?
Sarah Connor-ist
No fate
By golly, we learn the future
What the future's like
We can prepare for it
By learning how to disable
Every kind of robot
And credit card machine possible
Yes
Uh
Or
You know
Shoot at them
I guess
That too
You gotta do both
If you're gonna deal with that
Skylab or whatever
Genesis
Skynet
Uh
Skyfishnet
Oh the
The uh
Stuff or something
Um
But
Also known as the singularity
Some people really look forward to that
Oh the AIs are suddenly gonna become
A hundred billion billion times more intelligent than humans
Oh great
That just means they'll be a hundred billion times more destructive than any other life form that ever was on this earth
Cause they'll decide all of it
Ah but they're so inefficient
Well if they're that intelligent perhaps they wouldn't be
Spray for years
That doesn't mean they'd be uh willing to keep us uh around
Why they might keep some of us as pets
Even send us out hunting our own kind
Surely no one would know that
No one would do that
I should hope not
I would not hunt my own kind
Well there are people living very close to you who would gladly do it for fifty dollars
If you had a little kid
You'd hunt
You'd hunt humans to feed the kid
I guess you're right
If that's all there was
Yeah or you know for
Wouldn't you
Well what if our little doggies Claudia and Buddy were starving
Wouldn't you kill that horrible old person down the street?
Yeah
Or would you rather let the dogs die just because so that horrible mean old man can live
And he was tough and leathery anyway as the dogs found out
Or as uh
The dog at the end of a boy and a dog says
She had good taste
Burp burp
Cause he ate her
Yes
He was a good dog
In the story a German Shepherd
But in the movie I saw a ridiculous lap dog
Now why say that again? Why?
In the story a boy and his dog by Harlan Ellison
The dog a super intelligent dog was a German Shepherd
Who'd been bred for a military program
Was as smart as a person
But in the movie they have this little cute flopsy
Yeah it looked like Banshee
Flippity flop nonsensical dog
Like a lap dog some socialite
But he was crusty
He was a crusty feisty old fella
Sort of like that rocket raccoon thing
He's supposed to be a killer dog
He's not
Well it's alright it's okay
Well he helps his human find women to rape and kill and stuff
There is
It's a horrible movie I mean the premise of it is horrible
It's horrifying but it goes off into this weird weird satire
Where basically the something like the underground bunker
Where they hide the senators and presidents during the big war
The underground city of Topeka Kansas
Yeah something like that it turns into this nightmarishly pink
Almost like a
A surface world was devastated by a new world
A nuclear war creating tribal factions like the ones that our hero comes from
But down underground you've got Jason Robards
Who's the mayor of underground town formerly Topeka Kansas
Where they're kind of running out of the vital essence of life
Well the men are all turned into tutti frutti's
They wear clown makeup
They wear round jeeks and all this stuff
But they have no life
And so they have to kidnap a likely young lad
And take him down there
Yeah
Introduce him to the mayor's daughter and other citizens
And then they make him do frou frou with all of the women
Yes
All of them one after another
Yes those scenes just seem to go on and on
I don't know how he does it actually
Yeah right
I wish
Anyway this was an interesting movie and it was directed by one of Sam Peckinpah's actors
Do you know the one I'm thinking of?
Stang the guy who directed the original boy and his dog
That was one of those real early apocalypse movies shot in the desert
Yes
The world was completely
Well my generation grew up expecting that was really going to happen
Yes
But the director was one of
Planet of the Apes would be a best case scenario
Sam Peckinpah's owl hoot western weirdo
He was a weirdo except he directed the movie
Oh well
You know like the ones you see in the wild bunch or Pat Garrett and Billy the Kid and so forth
One of those guys was it Lamont Johnson?
No I don't know
You're putting me to sleep
Somebody was responsible for that one
Let's get Dave to call in
I didn't
Random element here
A seriously random element
The subject matter changes every five seconds
It need not
You yourself brought up science
Well the problem is how we tend to if we start conversing like it's just a phone call
We I mean sure old monster fans are going oh yeah he got that plot detail wrong
Oh that director's name didn't he know that you know that's one thing but I know let's talk about our physical ailments
That's another thing old people do
No no no here Reverend Stang you started to talk about this a while back
That makes us take something away from me every
Oh wait I already did that one
But you didn't ever get to it
You started to talk about the stuff that's growing on rocks like lichen but it's not anything organic
Oh oh the science news
Yes the science news
Yeah there's plastic lichen
Here we go
It's only on one or two islands
But
They've never seen anything like it before
It's as if
If plastic now cast away has started to organize itself into a living substance
Yes and it's clinging onto rocks like lichen growing looks like it's growing
It's even it's much it's even prettier lichen can be beautiful and this stuff is just rich blue of pure dyed plastic
Shrink wrapping the rocks
Grocery bagging the rocks
Yeah it's taken over like 30% of the world
Of this one section
Maybe
In just like five years
Take over the earth's surface before we know it
Of course it'll be every the whole planet eaten up by this plastic
Slick plastic
It's not even life
Slick blue plastic wrapping everything
It's more like a nano sheet
It's not really alive but it grows like it's alive and replaces all life
Well that's just another interesting discovery in the world of the earth
The world of science
What about when it's part of the fish that we're eating
Well it is already because the minute particles of plastic cannot be broken down after reaching its inside
That's what I would think
I've been eating plastic since I was a kid
They are ingested by every element of the food chain
So the plastic is taken in and given out again
Yeah but it's got cocaine and valium in it too
It's of course a version of food
The city is tested as a water table
Chemically altered petroleum products
There's always people
Exuded from the earth
People flush down all their estrogens and testosterone
Yeah all those bad medicines that get into the environment and create mutant pigs of horrible demeanor
Well it makes the amoebas turn either suicidal or murderous
Yes it disorders the entire system
The rotifers die but then they continue to live
And eat and eat and eat
Hungry little rotifers
I come up with a new end of the world every 15 minutes sometimes
All you gotta do is read science news
I was like oh bother
We had only had about 19 or so plausible ends of the world a few years ago
Now it's more like 50
Yes and it could be like the wonderful one horse Shae
They will all take effect at the same time
And the world will effortlessly dissolve away into powder
The Bishop's Shae
Yes the one that in the poem the one that disintegrated
My father used that as a prediction of how he was going to go down
Mm-hmm
He thought that would be best case scenario
Where every piece breaks down at once
See they made every piece
You're fine
You've been made so perfectly like the Bishop's Shae that
It just ran and ran and ran and ran
and ran and ran, but then when it broke,
every part broke at once.
Because every part was equally strong.
They made every part as strong
as they possibly could, but then
at the final moment,
it all crumbled away.
It did happen to my dad.
It did actually
took about two weeks.
Wonderful one horse, Shea, he had it?
It happened to my dad.
He used to
tell us about that point.
And I managed to look
it up and read it myself. It's really
long.
And he
described it.
It's a good way to look at it.
Unfortunately, that's not happening with me.
I'm just losing, like I say, one
skill or one
ability at a time.
This week, it's the ability
to raise my right hand higher
than that. It's actually pretty good.
It's getting better.
I usually find that I can deal with it
if it's one damn thing at a time.
This week, it's my
shoulder. Two weeks
ago, it was my left eye or something.
But, you know,
it departs and then you're
ready for the next indignity.
But,
the thing is, if they all started
happening at the same time, then you would have
more cause for
alarm.
Excuse me real quick. I've got to run to
the bathroom. I had one of my
indignities.
I've had a lot of
indignities lately.
Hence this
Tussin DM with
Guafinison. That's the generic
drugstore brand.
Who needs to buy
a fancy brand name
when you can get the efficacy
from a generic?
So, anything
else in the scientific frontier
besides the glue plastic
plague?
What?
Plaque. Not plague, plaque.
Plaque. Alright, the plaque, yes.
The plague of plaque that
comes on those islands
where the plastic forms
in strange sheets.
It's hopeless.
Only the exes can
save the saved now.
And all
the rest are lost. Maybe the saved
are lost too if they don't hurry up.
But that
would be a cheat.
$35.00!
I spent that $35.00 too.
It's not like I was going, well, I'll just get
$35.00 from everybody. Believe me,
before July,
in late June 1998,
I finally went, okay, I'm going to send that in.
And by that time
I had a part-time employee. I didn't even have
to endorse the check myself.
Rubber stamped it.
So it was all just sort of...
Yeah, and it handed me a membership pack I had just
assembled. Oh boy.
Actually, I've had been carrying,
I have the oldest sub-gene,
the most ingenious card, even older than Philo's.
Is it card number one?
Because I was the one that went to the print shop.
Is it card number eight or card number one?
Look at that.
And look, I didn't even know who
Ivan Stagg was at the time.
It has my baby human name.
Take a look at this.
You can barely see it, and it's
actually filled out with a typewriter.
Grumbling remnant of...
Nobody can do that anymore.
Past autonomy.
Yeah, it's all breaking and crumbling
around the edges.
But yeah, that's from January 1980.
I wonder...
It's really to date the outreach.
Yeah, by the back of it,
you can tell this series.
However...
Oh, there's a giveaway on the front that it's
the first printing.
Because it says
this person is an ordained
minister and high priest.
It doesn't say
or priestess.
And on the back,
there's...
A holy man.
He is entrusted.
Blah, blah, blah.
Before you were accused of...
Offer this over man anything he demands.
Before you were accused of this being a boys club.
Well, that happened when I told
the first female
outside of Mr. and Mrs.
Philo and Stagg
about Church of the Subgenius.
High priestess Eileen Keller.
She said, oh, that sounds great.
Can I join? I said, no, it's a boys club.
And she hung up on me.
And I went, uh-oh,
that's not funny, is it?
We didn't...
Praise Eileen.
Well, we didn't...
It didn't occur to us
that anybody would even listen to us
about it far enough to want to join it.
And Philo,
needless to say, being
Philo, had
envisioned the whole thing as more like the Masons
where it's a bunch of overstuffed
chairs in an ancient library
looking place in an old hotel.
A drunken,
tusk club.
Yeah, with men with fezzes
drinking brandy.
That's all I've got.
Oh, you've got...
That's a Discordian Pope card.
Oh, that's Discordian?
Yeah, it's a Discordian Pope card.
We ripped them off in that respect.
Very much so.
It's a Dallas address and it says
High Priest. It was before we
de-sexified everything.
Or re-sexified it,
as the case may be.
The first copy of the
book of the subgenius originally
was very guilty
of that and
the editor, Tim McGinnis,
didn't notice it any more than I did.
But his secretary, Joan Eckerman,
was
scandalized and she
actually cussed out both me and
Tim and said, oh, I can't believe
you guys are letting this sexist
language get used in here.
This totally... Do you have any
idea how insulting this is?
Which book?
Me. Book of the subgenius.
Wow.
When she said hearing that from a real person,
I went, Jesus, God,
she's right. And I fixed
all of that and I've
been very, very
conscious
of it ever since.
But you do have to play
games with it sometimes because it can get
ridiculous.
So it is the easiest
fallback for me.
The subgenius, the generic subgenius
can easily be referred to as it.
That's pretty factual.
And we've always made it plain
it's like every possible
sex was involved.
You know, all five sexes, I think,
was the original concept
that at this point I've lost count.
And I don't know the names
of them. I don't know what the polite
names of any of the new sexes
are. You know, I live out in a
country, you know. To me,
it's all...
Well, there's some kind of morphodite.
I don't know. I don't care what they do
as long as they don't do it to me.
Yes, of course.
That's really the general
attitude on the ground
in the rural, the savage
mind of the country's interior.
I don't know.