The Self-Genius Power of Bob
Friends, the virtual online X-Day drill was lots of fun.
It's going to take some editing, though.
But Reverend Susie the Flusie saved my boot-all by doing a superb, brand-new X-Day and Plague episode of Bob's Slack Time Funhouse on WREK Atlanta, as follows.
Enjoy the show, for one day, we shall die.
The 25.
I slept for 25 hours?
No, 25 weeks.
But you mean to say since January you've put me into a medically-induced coma?
Well, sort of, kind of.
Less medical, more cast-iron skillet with a little help from the street corner stop and cop.
But you needed the beauty rest, love.
Oh, that explains the headache.
Ah, when is right now?
Anyway.
Oh, it's Sunday around midnight.
Uh, which Sunday?
The Sunday that's July 5th this year.
It's July 5th?
Oh, holy hell!
My house is supposed to be an X-Day.
I gotta go.
Hey, hold your horse, Flues.
You can't go out.
What?
Why?
No one can go out.
What's going on?
Oh, that's right.
I guess you've missed a few things.
Let me help you get caught up.
Ah!
Oh, yeah.
Nothing like sleep learning.
The day it all began.
The day what began?
Oh, yes, yes.
It began far, far away from this lovely palace.
Far below the Earth's surface at the Institute.
Come on in.
Didn't mean to disturb your lunch.
Welcome to the Lymph Node Institute.
I'm Doc.
I'm Bugsy.
Governments don't dare try to kill me.
I've let them all know that I've planted biological bombs in seven major cities around
the world.
And, uh...
And released a biological attack on the population which will kill hundreds of thousands.
Then...
Oops.
Broke open.
Ain't that a bitch?
Run!
You ain't got a chance.
But that was just a prelude to what was to come.
You got to hurry.
There's a storm!
Storm coming!
In storm!
Huh?
And his name?
The Horned King!
The Darkman!
Oh, no.
Well, we're born.
Come on down.
And meet your maker.
Come on down and make the stand
Oh, I had been out searching with a black book in my hand
And I've looked between the lines and I know the pages that I've read
Left me walking to the edges and it's worn out cowboy boots
And it won't fly, no matter that way or no next way
Come on down and meet your maker
Come on down and make the stand
Come on down, come on down
Come on down, we'll make the stand
Look down, dark despite the wrong
In the shadow of a deemed dead
No secret of your damn strength
In your MY BIG HAND
And you're on the streets
Bet that you don't earn two crescent стать
In life
And you may not little Elliot
Oh
constant
Core
school
This is the night
course
pharmacies everywhere.
Flu buddy!
And now, let's get back to the Lone Star.
State patrol, Hap.
Hey, Joe Bob.
Want me to fill her up for you?
No, sir. I come by on other business.
Was that old geezer here last night?
He's here about every night.
Maybe he ought to hear this, too.
Hear what?
There's strangers crawling all over Braintree.
They're supposed to be U.S. Health Service guys,
but they came in a C-5A transport plane,
and they look like regular Army to me.
And then there's been three more big transport planes
land over Starland in Arkansas since noon.
It was, Collar. I knew it was.
I don't know nothing about that.
I'll tell you one thing, though.
If the feds are thinking about a quarantine,
then you might have a little bit more to worry about than cholera.
I just thought you ought to know what's stirring in the weeds, Hap.
If any of them other old boys that were here
last night come by, you ought to pass a word along to them.
Just don't mention my name.
Hap!
You ought to take care of that old-timer.
Them summer colds are the worst.
Oh.
What if it ain't a cold?
What if I got whatever he had?
That guy last night?
Oh, it's probably just the sniffles, that's all.
Hap!
Come on down, we'll make the stand.
As I crawl beneath the surface,
looking through the promos of this life,
I may cut this brain, but it's coming in full,
the box of time.
Hey, trash can, where I don't mind,
your eyes will be the path.
As at the end, you're a character.
Play the few marks.
Play the marks.
Come on.
Come on down.
And make the stand.
Maybe I ought to close up the station for the rest of the day.
Call the other fellas and see how they're feeling.
Might not be a bad idea.
Yeah.
All survivors gotta come with us.
What the?
Run, Jesse, run!
Federal marshals, head to the air!
Yeah!
Let's go, let's go!
You're on up-to-staff time now.
Move it!
Go!
Move up!
And it comes without saying, it caused him to empty his bowels.
Being hijacked by a bunch of government sons of bitches in spacesuits
does that to me every time.
It's okay.
We're here in quarantine with the other survivors.
Where is here?
The old army base.
What the hell's wrong with us?
Vomiting, diarrhea, dehydration, kidney failure.
Is it cholera?
Absolutely not.
You'll be getting all the details...
When?
Who told you to ask that question?
This press conference is over.
If that ain't true, I've never been this scared.
Us, our families, people we've been around since.
What's going on here?
It isn't the man with the little clipboard and the armed escort.
No, no, no, no, no, we don't take camps here.
Just a precaution.
Would you get the doctor a mask?
Wait, wait, wait.
We're moving this man to isolation.
According to who?
He's been misdiagnosed.
Health services has no authority here.
Actually, in a communicable case, I do.
You're making a big mistake here, honey.
I don't think so.
And it's doctor, not honey.
So, when are we gonna go public?
Well, we're not.
Not until we have some kind of solid information on how this thing is spreading.
We gotta keep a tight lid on this thing with the press.
This kind of an outbreak can easily cause a panic.
Meenakshi.
Now, in Washington, D.C.
Yes, sir.
On the outskirts of a one-stop light town in east Texas.
They killed him in a hurry down there.
Telemetry suggests even the ones that managed to get their respirators on died within 12 minutes.
The rest of them were gone in five.
You believe that?
Do I have a choice?
No.
Apparently, none of us do.
The National Disease Control Center, the Pentagon, says we'll know if it's actually gonna jump to the outside.
He says it'll probably mutate.
But that's not gonna help the people that catch it.
Listen, General, I have what might be something...
It'll just take them longer to die.
That's all.
Most people are gonna think they've got the plain old non-lethal flu right up to the very end.
And that's the biggest break we've had so far.
Contact with townspeople was minimal.
That doesn't matter.
We gotta shut that town down, lock it up, dig a moat around it.
That operation's already on the launching pad, sir.
What kind of cover did you come up with?
Anthrax.
New strain.
Ha ha, yeah, it's a new one, all right.
It's real new.
It's very good at its job, too.
I don't know, but the important thing is right now we got a shot at containing this.
Oh, God, this stuff has a communicability level of over 99%.
You understand what that means?
Any chance we had of containing it wouldn't...
But that was just a prelude to what was to come.
The time is now.
A nightmare is about to begin.
Demons were linksrix awesome cloud.
Galaxy
Here are the니까
Thank you.
Sir, we keep getting orders to let the virus win.
Lay down your arms.
All right.
Let's make some puffs.
Ew.
Chronic viral ulcerative lesion.
No, don't touch him.
Why not?
He's infected.
Viral infections.
Highly contagious.
I only hope there's no leak.
And suddenly things turned ugly.
I'd like to call to order this secret conclave of America's media empires.
We're here to come up with the next phony baloney crisis to put Americans back where they belong.
Dark rooms glued to their televisions too terrified to skip the commercials.
Well, I think...
NBC, you are here to listen and not speak.
I think we should go with a good old-fashioned public health care.
Yeah.
A new disease. No one's immune.
It's like the summer of the shark, except instead of a shark, it's an epidemic.
And instead of summer, it's all the time.
Now, I hate to be the guy who derails what everybody else loves.
He loves being that guy.
But, Janice, we do have standards.
This can't be a made-up disease.
The only moral thing to do
is to release a deadly virus into the general public.
We do have something we've been holding on to.
But it hasn't been tested.
Get over here, NBC.
Well, we certainly believe in testing, but I...
Wow!
So, we've got our deadly disease.
Now we just have to blame it on something that's in every household...
now we just have to blame it on something that's in every household...
that people are a little bit afraid of already.
Well, now, look here.
Thursday nights at 8 p.m.,
America's favorite TV show,
There's a Bat in My House.
Betty, Betty, Betty.
Starring America's favorite funny man,
the hilarious, zany B.B. Sanders
as Betty Boy.
Oh, absolutely.
I couldn't agree more.
Love it, love everything about it.
Excellent.
Betty, Betty, Betty.
Bat-a-jum-ba-ay, bat-a-jum-ba-oh-ah
The reports of the supposedly lethal flu epidemic continue to spread.
Many downtown shopping areas in southern Florida are virtually empty this morning.
And the flu rumor actually seems to be gaining credence despite statements from health officials in Atlanta and Vermont.
It's as simple as this.
An unknown bat germ is being blown around the world.
It's highly contagious and it's reached great proportions.
I don't know about all those people down in Texas, but you sure sound like you've got a dose of the flu, Johnny.
You better let me take a listen.
Listen, forget that.
Oh, come on.
You know how hot it makes me when you take your shirt off.
Here's something else.
You've heard about the bats they have here.
Animal bats, the kind that fly?
Yes, yes.
Look what it says in this magazine.
This is a report from the state health department and it says some of them bats is rabbit.
Well.
And that ain't all.
Now there's a rumor going around that it was the rabbit bats in this neighborhood.
Oh, that's ridiculous.
Oh, my goodness.
Blah, blah, blah.
Um, what?
Gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme.
I'm gonna bite you.
No, I don't want that.
Do I scare you?
Yeah, you do.
I hope so.
Why are you trying to scare me?
Because I'm gonna bite you, man.
Why do you want to bite me?
Because I'm hungry.
Because I'm a bat-pire.
I'm a bat-pire.
I'm a very polite bat-pire.
Get my stick, there's a bat in the house.
Ready, ready, ready.
Eating a bat cause the Chinese flu.
But don't knock it if you try it is my message to you.
I eat them flying rodents and I get a lot of flack.
But once you go bat, you never go back.
You may think I'm some sort of ghoul.
But I'm just a man who's a bat-eating fool.
I eat that bat all over this town.
You can find me sleeping, hanging upside down.
I like girl scrugs, but I prefer Lester Flatt.
I like a T-bone steak, but I love me a bat.
I never was much of a heavy metal dude.
But me and Ozzy Osbourne got the same taste in food.
Georgia, they gave me a ten-gallon hat.
First man ever ate a ten-gallon bat.
When normal folks go hungry, they go to a dunkin'.
When I get hungry, I go spelunkin'.
I've read all this stuff and it's not funny.
It's based on fact.
Wait a minute.
Whoa, whoa.
You don't actually believe this crap, do you?
All I'm saying is that there are some things beyond the can of mortal man that shouldn't
be tampered with.
It's terrible.
It's science run amok.
It isn't.
Is that what you really think or just what you'd like to think?
I cannot accept half-baked theories that sell newspapers.
I'm a scientist, not an alarmist.
I just can't accept the idea of universal disease.
Those are rumors put out by people who are afraid because they don't know the secret
truth.
Those people out there buy that crap and I thought you were smart enough to see what
was really going on.
We don't know everything, Andy.
There's plenty going on right now in the Twilight Zone that we don't know anything about and
I think we ought to stay clear.
This is a scam on a global scale.
Do you f***ing get me now?
Oh, Dad.
None of this is true on any level.
It's just something that I thought of when I asked him.
Yeah, yeah, oh yeah.
What can you do?
Dude, do you know wow or someday you'll»
You know?
C'mon, dude.
to them, I don't feel like I'm coming out.
I mean, I'm like, well, I just feel like they hell wanted me to call mom."
The other thing is, in the Science Fictionakin' smoothie, I like to call it Momatra and Twitter
It's the one that I recently reading super high quality movies about.
Can you guess where they go, Grant?
I don't have a clue.
Oh, stunning.
It's called See You and Meet the Secrets by Ross Harris and forçaIshom.
I tripped down a cloud and fell eight miles high.
I tore my mind on a jagged sky.
I just dropped in to see what condition my condition was in.
Yeah, yeah, oh yeah, what condition my condition was in.
guitar solo
I pushed my soul in a deep dark hole and then I followed it in.
I watched myself crawling out as I was crawling in.
I got up so tight I couldn't unwind.
I saw so much I broke my mind.
I just dropped in to see what condition my condition was in.
guitar solo
I pressed my shoulder and my although was broken.
I もっと UFFEEDED
You say this is dark.
Yeah,первых, I think you are.
is sleeping, Man겠어
Yeah, yeah, oh yeah, what condition my condition was in.
Someone painted a poor fool in pink black letters on my dead inside.
I had my foot on the gas as I left the road and blew out my mind.
Eight miles out of Memphis and I got no spring here.
Eight miles straight up downtown somewhere.
I just dropped my gun.
I just dropped in to see what condition my condition was in.
I said I just dropped in to see what condition my condition was in.
Yeah, yeah, oh yeah.
Oh chain just flows fast like a wave.
maisÉ
Everybody bottom and poor were smilesing,
Andrea
Well, if I told you, you probably wouldn't believe me.
I'm very polite vampire.
With all this trouble, I won't eat a bat.
So that should answer how I got so fat.
I'm like Trump, the way he gets grouchy when he's corrected by Dr. Fauci.
Dr. Fauci said earlier this week that the lag in testing was, in fact, a failing.
Do you take responsibility for that?
Yeah, no, I don't take responsibility at all.
This is an outrage.
My life for him.
Well, how do you feel, Ms. Breske?
The U.S. itself has overtaken China now as the country with the most cases of the virus.
It is the new global epicenter.
85,991 confirmed cases in the United States.
And I think our economy will start to pick up very substantially.
As soon as the states get open.
And it's happening as we speak.
And it's actually very exciting.
And people are just thrilled to see it.
Stay prepared.
Like the scouts taught me.
One step ahead.
Because they still haven't caught me.
Keep your hands to yourself.
And your money on the shelf.
It's a pandemic.
Stay sane.
In a world gone crazy.
We'll stand up to the challenge.
And we ain't lazy.
We'll do what we have to do to stand up to this pandemic.
The greatest generation is still around.
You can hear them every night.
If you listen for the sound.
If you can't.
They'll squeeze off another round.
It's a pandemic.
Biochemical weapons.
Also known as Project Terror.
Designed to take out an entire populace in a controlled landlocked area.
You're supplying it to them?
What about countering with atropine and PAMP2?
Interferes with the neurotoxin delivery.
Sets off the cell blaster.
And you're gushing blood and pus through every sacred hole in your body.
Hepatizing.
Correct.
But we found that a small percentage of people are not affected.
And within this small percentage lies a cure.
We have to get back to my lab.
This infection will spread all over the world to every man, woman and child.
All of the sickness of the world and its people are here in one motion picture for you to witness.
Yes, it's a sick, sick, sick world.
Follow this motion picture and its unbelievable cast.
As the camera takes you through a maze of unforgettable sights.
Sights that you will never, never forget.
History teaches us that when the great plague hits, those who don't die alone usually die in church.
So, we may find nothing in this one, but if we do, try to think of the bodies as cordwood.
Make it easier.
Cordwood.
We are dead.
And this is hell.
Come on down and meet your maker.
Come on down and make the stand.
Come on down.
And move it.
Make it stand.
Come on down.
Yeah.
Oh, come on down and meet your maker.
Come on down and make the stand.
Come on down.
We'll make the stand.
Bring out your dead!
The monster's coming!
He's coming!
Bring out your dead!
The monster's coming!
We're damned.
Yes.
I know.
Oh, turn on the radio, will you?
Hello there. I guess this morning there's only one topic of conversation.
You can call it the superflu, or by its West Coast name, Captain Trips, but it means the same thing either way.
There have been some horror stories about the Army clamping down on everything.
The Army?
Just be patient with me. Remember, I'm running the show all by myself. Everyone else called in sick.
The numbers are the same as always, though. 555-TALK and 555-CHAT. So let's go.
Hello there. This is Ray Flowers, and it's time to...
I'm calling from Portsmouth.
What's your name?
Leonora. Listen, Ray, I just want everyone to know that there are soldiers burning bodies across the state line in Kittery.
Also, my little girl died this morning.
I guess she's with Jesus now.
I'm sorry as hell, Leonora.
Ray, I think the soldiers did it. I think they made a bug that's like killing people.
That wouldn't be very American now, would it?
No, I guess not.
Of course, that's never stopped the real patriots among us.
Does it? You try to hang in there, Leonora.
I'm trying, Ray. But have you ever smelled bodies on fire?
I can't say that I have.
It's awful, Ray. It's just...
You just try to hang in there, hon. You're on the air, and it's time to speak your piece.
First of all, I just want to tell you that I love your show, Ray.
You say you saw these G.I.s gunning down unarmed civilians?
You're not going to tell me that you saw these G.I.s gunning down unarmed civilians?
Open in the name of the United States government!
Tell you what, Portland, it looks like the Marines have landed.
They don't look too happy.
This is a joke! Right? I mean, this has got to be a joke!
I don't think so, Franny. I really don't think so.
Hi there, you're on the air.
Ray, you alright?
Well, to tell you the truth, honey, it doesn't look real good for the kid right now.
Several soldiers have just broken into the studio.
They're fully armed and they're dressed in some kind of protective clothing.
They're wearing respirators on their faces.
Shut it down!
Hey, Bluto, you ever heard of a little number called Freedom of Speech?
Bill of Rights? Any of that ring a bell?
Folks, I've just been ordered by my uninvited fascist guest to shut down.
And I've refused.
Oh, Ray, shut the door!
Oh my God, what's happening?
I don't know, honey.
I don't know.
He's closer now!
The hard case!
The dark man!
He's coming!
He's closer now!
The dark man!
Whether a state of war between China and Russia still exists is not important any longer.
Our fellow countrymen are dying.
Naturally, we'll have more on this story as soon as it develops.
We now return you to the President's address already in progress.
Winning!
You are going to get so sick of winning!
USA! USA! USA!
My life for you!
There were a couple times when I didn't think you were buying him.
But this was an emergency.
This is a class one emergency.
All civilian traffic is barred from streets and highways.
Stay in your homes. Stay in your homes.
Those found without specific military orders are subject to summary execution.
Stay in your homes.
Repeat, Conrad Channel.
This is a class one emergency.
All civilian traffic is barred from streets and highways.
Please remain calm. Stay in your homes.
I am officially declaring a national emergency.
Two very big words.
It will go away. Just stay calm.
It will go away.
And it will go away.
And we're going to have a great victory.
It's going to go away. Hopefully at the end of the month.
And if not, hopefully we'll be soon after that.
He says a coronavirus is a hoax.
The fact is, the President himself is a hoax.
The White House has done a con.
She scoffs at holiness!
Punisher! Punisher!
I am an epidemiologist,
and I'm telling you, you are going to listen.
Now, if you would like to call a private physician, you can.
You're damn right I can.
I can walk right out of here, too.
Oh, no, you can't.
This is an infectious disease,
and if you do not cooperate,
I have the authority to detain you here for public safety.
Shall I call security?
No.
You won't take it.
This is a very serious disease.
Now, you can either take this medicine and hopefully not get sick,
or you can just sit here and wait to see what happens.
A cure?
That is not until we found somebody from the other side
who almost saw us batches at it.
Science comes first, but business comes first.
Then you realized
if you could infect a large enough populace
and experiment then at survivors,
you'd find a cure.
I swore to my men
that I'd do everything in my power
to keep them alive.
That's what I intended to pray.
Understand?
Understand.
I never had a choice.
It's real pretty.
Vomiting, diarrhea, dehydration,
kidney failure,
complete circulatory collapse,
your blood pressure plummets,
body goes into shock.
Within 24 hours, without medical treatment,
you are dead.
You're dead, you're dead, you're dead,
you're dead and out of this world.
You'll never get a second chance.
Plan all your moves in advance.
Stay dead, stay dead, stay dead,
stay dead and out of this world.
Run faster, stand in the fire.
There's too much work to be done.
You're down, you're down, you're down,
you're down and out of this world.
I'm a killer.
Don't ever talk with your eyes.
Make sure that you compromise.
You're dead, you're dead, you're dead,
you're dead and out of this world.
You hear the unloved
weeping like rain
Thank you.
I'm a businessman, not military.
You haven't had to do it.
But we have to get back to my lab.
No!
I don't suppose there are any other biochemical engineers around?
No.
Yeah, me neither.
What's going to happen, Dr. Wilson?
Is everybody in the world going to die before someone finds the answer?
No.
I don't think so.
We'll find an answer.
When, Doctor?
We need it right now.
I need it.
I don't deny there's some strange evolutionary process going on.
But mankind won't be destroyed.
Unless...
Unless what?
I don't know.
If you're a smart guy, you'll figure something out.
Those cells are still living off one another.
I'm sure you're right.
I'm sure they're still alive.
You heard that all communications are ended outside the Continental Limits?
Yes, I heard.
That leaves it in our laps.
So we keep trying.
You two stay on this virus theory until I decide it's exhausted.
Right.
And until further notice, this station will continue.
It's around the clock coverage of this national disaster.
And now we switch you to the State Capitol where the Governor is speaking from the Executive
Mansion.
The Federal Government declared this state to be a disaster area.
Public health is dependent on bodies of the deceased being burned.
You must notify the Health Department immediately.
Have a plague victim in your home.
Under no circumstances should you gather public.
If you're the dire emergency that exists, I intend to...
What's the matter with you?
Nothing, and I'm going to keep it that way.
Look, let's talk about this.
There's nothing to talk about.
You think I'm out of my mind.
You might be one of them.
Look, you're ill.
You ought to see a doctor.
No doctors.
You take care of your life, I'll take care of mine.
Now get away from here.
You understand?
Get away from here!
I'm going to combine you all into the station.
Being quarantined isn't that bad, is it?
Lonely.
So very lonely.
So very, very, very, very lonely.
Why must I stay here?
Why do I have to be in this lonely room?
Watching the gong show and thinking of you.
Loneliest chair, loneliest bed, loneliest deja vu
In the loneliest, loneliest, loneliest, loneliest room
In the world
I tried marijuana, cocaine and heroin
But they just can't seem to get the thought of you out from under my skin
I'm lonelier now, lonelier than I've ever been
In the loneliest, loneliest, loneliest, loneliest room
In the world
Phone never rings
Postman never brings the thing
Even the singles clubs won't give me a whirl
Plants all dead, even my cactus
Beer cans round my bed
In the loneliest room in the world
I tried marijuana
Cocaine and heroin
Can't seem to get the thought of you out from under my skin
I'm the loneliest man, lonelier than I've ever been
In the loneliest, loneliest, loneliest room in the world
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
I'm not sorry for myself.
I'm sorry for that Miss Wright who can't find me.
Miss Wright, I'm thinking of you tonight.
And you alone at night.
And you alone.
And some of the stuff won't even answer your phone.
You got the blues.
The low-down singles club blues.
And the lonely blues.
You might even be lonely.
My darling baby.
It's lonely.
Lonely.
And as soon as they bring back pork rinds and Monday night football, I'm going to be in redneck heaven.
Stay sane in a world gone crazy.
We'll stand up to the challenge.
And we ain't lazy.
We'll do what we have to do to stand up to this pandemic.
The Cougar.
The greatest generation is still around.
You can hear them every night if you listen for the sound.
If you can't, they'll squeeze off another round.
It's a pandemic.
With our gloves on, we reach our hands to heaven.
Wearing masks like we're robbing a 7-Eleven.
We keep our distance to secure our existence.
It's a pandemic.
It crept upon us like a thief in the night.
But we got what it takes to win this fight.
We'll do what we can and we'll do what's right in this pandemic.
Sacrifices are the price we pay for another chance to live another day.
Stay together, but stay strong.
Stay six feet away.
It's a pandemic.
Another question being asked forcibly is whether now is the right time to reopen the U.S. economy.
In Georgia today, hairdressers, nail salons, tattoo parlors were able to resume business,
even though coronavirus is still a serious problem in the state.
Now we're opening it up and it's opening up far faster than anybody thought even possible.
And there now.
It's a life.
It's got a life.
And we're putting out that life because that's a bad life that we're talking about.
Yeah, well, just don't forget what you promised when you get back.
Dinner, dancing, and all the paparazzi I can smile at.
Yeah, yeah, you got it.
Be ready in five minutes.
You bring the towels.
I get the penicillin.
Sick World is the story of vice, perversion, degradation that has infested the earth since the time of the pandemic.
We have a question that Adam and Eve send in the Garden of Paradise.
This is the shocking story of the world and its unholy inhabitants, feeling no pain or shame for the life that they lead.
Well, looks like things are finally going to get back to normal, I think we learned a lesson here.
What's that?
I don't know.
The unquenched desires of sex and the sensualists in their search for pleasures are unparalleled in this motion picture.
For a ringside seat that takes you into the lust-filled caverns of life, see, it's a sick, sick, sick world.
This motion picture has something for everyone.
This is a picture you must not miss.
A picture you will always remember.
It's a sick, sick, sick world.
And it's waiting for you.
This event will force us to totally restructure our intelligence system.
The Atlanta Disease Control Center told me that these masks wouldn't stop a flu germ with a hangover.
Oh, no, no, no. Shake hands, kid.
Sure. You old dog. How's that golf games?
That's nice.
I think that at some point that's going to sort of just disappear, I hope.
You still believe so?
I do. Yeah, sure.
In the thick of this crisis, the president travels to South Dakota July 5th for an X-Day celebration at Mount Rushmore.
There won't be any social distancing and mask wearing will be up to the attendees.
You are going to get so sick, sick, sick.
Please go.
And get tested.
Please wear a mask.
You're not listening to some loser public health doctor.
They destroyed the world.
Get them out the way.
Isn't that the...
We'll find an answer.
When, doctor?
Tonight.
It's a special night.
What's so special about tonight?
Let's see. What date is it?
What's the date?
July 5th.
We're in luck.
It says here the planet is going to be hit by a huge asteroid and blown to smithereens on this very day.
Hmm?
What's the date of July?
What the hell it is? It's Sunday.
Sunday?
Sunday I always dress for dinner.
Well, you turned something on. I'm starting to think.
The plague took the people, but it couldn't take the gadgets, could it?
No, they're all still out there.
Just waiting for someone to come along and pick them up.
Everything from electric can openers to cobalt bombs.
And we'll devour to him, brother, just a little nitro.
I can get the cannons out of the old God Armory.
We can have him out of there in no time.
I said no.
We could.
But then the curse will begin all over again, don't you see?
Here is evil.
Evil.
Unless...
What's wrong with this picture?
It's the old way.
And the old way was a death trip.
We say fine.
And then we go right back to tinkering with the power station, trying to recreate the world that damn near choked the human race to death.
And the sea is gone.
And the scavenger hunt starts today.
Big day today.
We should've thrown a party.
All he needs is one guy to target some scutt missile with an A-bomb on it.
Meanwhile...
God, I fear you.
Bombed him.
I, if not a robot, stick to this.
Stuck in my room.
Call me Genevieve.
Call me Lanceceğiz.
Call me Bruce.
My life for you.
Humph!
Surprised.
A big loud one?
Well...
It's time...
To make you stand.
Come on town, come on town
Come on town, we're gonna make this right
The challenge
Has just begun
The song must now be sung
For the world
Has now been spoken
The chance has just begun
On the wheels, on the wheels of life
On the wheels, on the wheels
On the wheels of life
Segway to the present
Morning
July 5th
South Dakota
Mind you, it's now 5 a.m.
It's a roadway in
The most disgusting hellhole on earth
For the room adjacent to it
Smelled like pee
And it was nasty
I didn't realize how thin these walls were
We heard people fighting in the other room
It's all slipping through your fingers
Everything you've made here is falling apart
Your time will end
And I'll be watching from hell
With your baby in my arms
Shut up!
It's daddy, stupid!
Where's my book?
Good evening, sir
Actually, I was only kidding
Everything all right?
The gracious, uh, is being handled
Like a child, put his hands over his ears
Now get the hell out of here
Is that all it has been?
Only three years
Seems like a hundred million
Oh
So why'd you get me out of here?
Me and some of the others are cutting loose
Cut loose where?
South America
It's nice
Fresh water, fresh fruit
And just plain folks
Once you want to forget they ever hooked up with
His infernal majesty
So what do you say?
I'm sticking
Why?
It's going bad here, can't you feel it?
Maybe
But it changed me, you know?
Man, you're nuts
You're probably right
The time is...
The president's next day celebration at Mount Rushmore
Ladies and gentlemen
The president of the United States
Very importantly
Very important
And
This kind of, uh, an event
He's been sick
I think his wife is gonna bring him some chicken soup
Oh, sir
Sir
This man is dying
Someone got a doctor
Suddenly
Now what?
Fading away
It's going to fade away
Apparently the joke's on you
What?
Just a few moments
Your entire planet is going to be destroyed
Oh!
We tried to warn you, Magnifico
But you would have none of it
You know it is going away
Wait a minute
Wait just a minute
One damn minute
Oh my God, no!
Oh, my God!
Oh!
Come, come, nuclear bomb
Oh, my God!
Every day is like Sunday
On your face
Win yourself a cheap trade
Share some grease to you
With a nice drink
Every day
Is like Sunday
Camping actively
What are you doing?
Parking actively
Don't cry
What the fuck?
I'm not sorry!
Did you see that?
Yeah, he blowed up.
Blowed up good.
Blowed up real good.
It is finished.
White magic.
That's all that's left.
The flu.
Who says it's gone?
Who knows if our babies are going to be immune?
Anyone here not a downer?
I thought you were going to be fine.
Why this is important.
In the event of a nuclear attack, there will be a three minute warning.
But everything will work out because
if at the moment that warning sounds you can take enough acid,
that three minutes will last for about 60,000 years.
The white light of the explosion will creep towards you very gradually over the centuries like an ice sheet.
The missiles will hang in the sky like the moon.
Over the years, a white hot bus will gradually inch its way through the front of your conservatory.
Your dead neighbour strapped to the front like Garfield on a bin lorry.
Many of your later years will be spent at quite a high altitude, watching your body gradually disassemble.
When your organs start to leave, you will have time to wish them goodbye.
You will say farewell to your penis like a first born son who's been off to work.
You will say goodbye to university.
You will wonder if there's a tear in your eye.
But it will just be the fact that your actual eye is boiling.
As you finally die, your consciousness will touch that of Buddha.
Someone will finally have understood you.
Buddha will have understood you.
And he will thank you for teaching him the meaning of contempt.
Flicking out a long frog-like tongue, he will consume you.
And a sign will appear in the sky that reads,
You have mastered 2% of this adventure.
Oh Jesus, when are you going to cut me some slack, huh?
Goodnight, sewers.
Thank you, Susie the Floozy and WREK.
For more information, see subgenius.com.