Well, boys, I reckon this is it.
The subgenius power of
SWAT.
Now, I want all privately owned radios to be immediately impounded.
After you've done that, report back to me.
Ladies and gentlemen, our grand entrance.
Thank you.
Hello, everybody.
I come here today to ask you one question.
I want to know what happened to the soul power.
See what we need today.
Hey, it's soul.
We forgot about from which we came.
But I got somebody here today just to let you know.
Yeah, you know what it's all about.
Okay, all right, well, cool, whatever.
All right, let's get started.
Okay, let's go.
Our first broadcast ever.
Yes, you are now tuned in to the sights and sounds of the
virtually unprepared and highly nervous.
And now I have an announcement.
I don't want any red-blooded fellow or girl anywhere to miss hearing.
And if any of your friends aren't listening in tonight,
I hope you'll do me and them the big favor of telling them
what I'm going to do.
I'm going to tell you right now.
Listen.
Now a message from the famous winner of the typical American boy contest,
Popsicle Pete.
I'd give my arm for good grass.
Who wouldn't?
It's over here.
It's the door. Stand back.
Here, in here.
It's right through here.
Cigar?
Is it safe?
Well, it's pretty good grass.
I was uncomfortable.
I was unconscious for about a month for six months afterward.
Ah.
So you'd better start saving bags right now.
Oh.
Here.
Uh-huh.
Dobbs?
Yes.
Dobbs.
Well, what do you think now?
Maybe I've stopped thinking.
Yes.
Hello?
Oh, just a second.
Is that man?
He's gone again.
Dobbs?
Uh-huh.
Okay, give me the phone.
Here.
Hello?
Hello, Dobbs?
Do you think he means it?
I don't want to believe him.
Sometimes I don't, but...
But what?
Two days later, Dobbs visits me in my apartment.
Well, it intrigues you, doesn't it?
It's a hoax.
The whole thing is a hoax.
But they laughed at me.
You see?
I'm known now as a crank.
Dobbs, I...
I don't...
I don't know.
Correct.
So, well, goodbye.
Hello, I'm Tony Perkins.
Having an abortion?
Boyfriend.
Abortion?
Depression.
Guilt?
Drug abuse.
Doctor?
No.
Fighting about everything?
Losing your boyfriend?
Domestic violence.
Relationship problems?
In most cases, had an abortion.
The moral of the story?
Choose psychological.
Drug abuse.
Babies.
Relative.
Christian Schiller.
Hello, I'm Tony Perkins.
On men.
O-R-G.
Uncle Bob was nice to you, wasn't he, Connie?
Always.
Well, what did he do?
Well, we were skipping some rocks along the water in the stream, and all of a sudden Uncle Bob hit me and knocked me down.
Sounds like he was under some sort of hypnotic spell.
Don't blame him for what happened.
He got up to leave and...
Then just passed.
He got on the floor.
When you praise Bob, you never stop.
You just keep smoking the frog, and you never flop.
No more poker terms.
No more biological terms.
No more bullshit.
A person burned like that, and you know he's conceiving.
Preferably Italian or Dutch.
Motherfucker.
Go back.
Smoke it.
Yes.
Men.
In just a moment, we'll find out.
What happens next in the strange case of Cremel, Herr Tani?
Now, Dr. Watson, what happened?
It's against my rule to take a drink before breakfast, but this morning I'll break that rule.
Oh, no.
Hold it.
Buy a bottle of Cremel daily for better gout.
Unseal his lips.
Here's the door.
Oh.
Come on.
Nobody can come in.
What?
Here, here, here, my boy.
Here.
Drink this.
You'll feel better.
You got leather?
Well, I'm afraid not.
Yes.
Here.
Oh?
Listen.
Sir.
We hope you will call upon us at your earliest convenience.
Faithfully yours, J.R. Dodds.
Come.
Come in.
Good.
Oh.
Ah.
You spoke of brilliant music.
of unearthly colors, of a distorted space and time.
All induced by the drug cannabis indica, more commonly known as hashish.
Good heavens, what shall we do?
Good heavens, Holmes.
After all, the best we can save him for is a living death in a madhouse.
To lock him up like animals.
Is that your opinion?
Certainly.
Poor chap's absolutely so defiable.
Perhaps it was best it ended that way.
But, Holmes, I still don't understand.
It's not difficult if you study the window.
Where there stands a giant figure in full evening dress, his hands covered by white gloves.
Just the weirdest pure nonsense that I've ever heard.
I wonder, Watson.
I cannot see.
Oh, I cannot see.
Sweet, sweet thing, do.
It's certain, it's certain, it's certain.
That is my do.
That, that, that, that.
Sweet, sweet.
Whoa.
I cannot see.
See, see, see, see, see.
It's stunning.
Ew.
Try the wine.
Huh.
I would like the subgenius.
Our old swank.
It made me real sick, a lot of it did.
Fear and nausea.
Sir!
Why me, Lord?
What have I ever done?
What did I ever do?
Wasted.
Try me.
Help me show.
Well, maybe.
No.
Wasted.
Can I ask you just one question, though?
What is it that is exactly the same about
every single vacation you have ever taken?
You.
You're the same.
No matter where you go, there you are.
It's always the same old you.
Let me suggest that you take a vacation from yourself.
And I know, it sounds wild.
It is the latest thing in travel.
We call it the ego trip.
You're gonna love this, Doug.
We offer you a choice of alternate identities during your trip.
I mean, face it.
Why go to Mars as a tourist when you can go as a playboy or a famous jock?
I don't want to spoil it for you, Doug.
But you rest assured, by the time the trip is over, you get the girl, kill the boy, and you're done.
You're gonna kill the bad guys and save the entire planet.
Cool.
Now you tell me, isn't that worth a measly 300 credits?
Easily.
Oh.
It's your foot!
Back up all right.
Where does it start?
Oh, that's it.
There you are.
It's expense, too much trouble out there.
And you declare your own.
Once you're out of town, you're equal to all those rich AmericansGameSkills.
They make me unhappy.
Really?
See, Dr. God didn't kill that little girl.
Fate didn't butcher her.
Destiny didn't feed her to those dogs.
God saw what any of us did that night.
He didn't seem to mind.
No, no, no, no.
God doesn't make the world this way.
We do.
None of you seem to understand.
I'm not locked in here with you.
You're locked in here with me.
This is the...
Funny show, huh, kids?
Come on.
Take a drink.
This is so awesome.
I love it.
Yeah, we're really partying tonight on the show, friends.
Awesome.
I love it.
Well, whatever.
Whatever.
I love it.
What is Liquid Crystal Dave going to call in?
So?
So, I don't know.
I don't know.
Licentious chrysanthemum, Dave?
Liquid Cowboy Display would be calling in soon.
But, meanwhile, friends, I'm not locked in here with you.
You're locked in here with us.
And us includes the material we've been playing,
which was mostly by Fernandinande Leemur,
the great mister.
Fernandinande Leemur.
And other great Reverend Norell Preff.
I say those names together, but they actually work completely separately.
And I don't know if they even listen to the show anymore.
They just do that stuff.
And I just keep playing it.
And also, there was a little bit of the kleptones.
You can find the kleptones spelled with a K, as in kleptomaniac, at kleptones.com, I think it is.
Yeah, you can look it up.
And Norell Preff is at Norellpreff.com.
And Norell Preff has one O and two Es in it.
As we record this particular show, friends, it happens to be Mother's Day of 2009.
And so I'd like to wish Happy Mother's Day to my daughter.
And to Lonesome Crystal Display.
Whenever he shows up.
Because he's one mother.
Oh, Princess Wee is here.
We want to wish Happy Mother's Day to all mothers.
Well, but you know, when everybody's special, nobody's special.
Princess Wee and I went to see Star Trek.
And before Dave calls in, I'm going to give you some spoilers.
Okay, so put your hands over your ears if you haven't seen Star Trek.
But Khan, the bad guy you may recognize from The Wrath of Khan.
Yes.
Is, goes back in time.
I can't believe you're doing this.
In order to kill, oh, they're going to hear about it anyway.
Khan goes back in time to kill the young Captain Kirk while he's still a space cadet.
And they get in this huge battle, of course.
And it ends up being like almost a sword fight.
And at one point, Khan finally reveals to Captain Kirk that he is Kirk's father.
And you're blowing the whole thing.
And Kirk's so freaked out, he lets Khan cut his hand off.
And I think this would be the man Dave.
We have noticed we have found many, many new artifacts in the zone that you have been speaking to.
Oh, I'm glad that you were listening and knew what we were speaking to, Dave.
And these artifacts we have taken to many libraries and museums and universities.
Yes, and carrying Captain Kirk's hand around like that has, you know, is a very important thing.
You keep it in a cooler, but sooner or later, you know, after all those people looking at it, it gradually starts to get stinky.
It's like Otzi the Iceman.
He is now preserved in his own juices and is no longer stinky.
And you can notice many, many different things on the body which have amused and enlightened scientists since this discovery.
Acupuncture, as we know it, probably existed 2,000 years before.
We believe it is.
Oh, yes, but acupuncture is primitive compared to acubeating.
Or wait, maybe I have it backwards.
Maybe it started with acubeating and then moved up to acupuncture.
Well, beating...
Acupuncturing is different from acupuncture.
Well, in combination with Doppler smacking and various refugees being stirred into the mix, we have a whole unusual tie.
Yes.
And these are unusual times, my friends.
As the old Chinese curse said, may you be born in interesting times.
And I'm afraid that fits us all.
How interesting.
One size fights all here.
One size fights all.
The church of the subgenius, the hour of slack, the liquid crystal of Dave.
Well, since we're in such forms of derision and smallpox, might as well talk about the other fronts.
So to speak, on the invisible warfare things going on.
I don't know what that means per se.
I know you know what it means.
We just can't say what it means per se.
If we had the fur...
Per sentence.
We can say it per hour, but not like per minute.
Right.
If we had the fur, we could infer it.
We could say per...
Say.
Yeah.
If you had fur, you'd smell a lot worse.
Especially if you blasted their juices at the same time you synchronistically mind-melded like Spoke, or whatever the hell his name is, into their heads.
He's not in the new movie.
Well, he doesn't have a fucking mind-meld.
No, Colonel Spoke is not in it because the actor wouldn't...
Go around.
They couldn't get, what's his name, Leonard Nimoy for it.
So they used...
They did use a clever simulacrum.
I wanna know, in fact, I'm curious to know who played Leonard Nimoy in that.
He's been dead for years, right?
Well, so has Mr. Nasal, our early childhood television star, and yet no one mourns his memory.
Captain Kangaroo, Mr. Peppermint.
Bob, when he had the pipe actually growing out of his snout as part of one large proboscis.
Howdy poody.
I cried when howdy poody got, well, whatever that dysfunction of the brain is.
Betty Bim.
Oh, I remember White Fang and Hippie.
You remember them?
On the Super Sales Show?
Well, let's see, yeah, and there was that other kid's show, The Baby, the Immigrant,
and the Guy on Mushrooms.
That was great.
That was my favorite.
Oh, man, that was my least favorite because my, you know, when your toes curl up real
bad and they actually grow into your feet?
No.
That's when your grandmother has to warn you for the last time.
She, uh, I never, you know, it's funny you should mention that because my toes have
grown all the way around to the point where if I cut them off, I wouldn't be able to walk.
I mean, my toenails, my toenails have grown, not my toes.
Obviously, of course, that would be ridiculous.
Crazy, I guess, yeah.
Talking crazy talk.
But so you can't actually walk with your toes or without your toes?
I can talk the talk, however.
It's the walking the walk.
As long as I don't chew gum or talk on the phone at the same time, I'm okay.
Like many subgeniuses, you know, we're a jack-off all trades and we try to just do
one trade at a time.
It's rough, rough trade.
But, you know, we're trying to open people's minds to, hey, look, you know, not everybody's
white bread same as you, you know.
Yeah.
What do they call it?
Metro sexual.
Yeah.
Metro.
We're not all, you know, not everybody's the same way.
Some of us happen to like, say, a prairie squid.
Not that there's anything wrong with that.
Right.
You can like it or you can love it or you can, you know, it's like, oh, I love that
food.
It's also, you know, oh, I love her.
But, you know, some you'd love like your grandmother or I love it because it gives me so much pleasure
when I, you know, do that.
I love that thing that we're not allowed to anymore.
But I think when anybody's around.
Well, it's clearly an observer created reality.
Everybody's blind.
Right.
You have to wait.
And so I told my little boy that one time you have to wait until nobody's around to
do your private thing.
And as he said, well, Dad, would you leave then?
I want to do my private thing.
Wait a minute.
The part I don't get though is your son actually had one of those like Native American sounding
names was that one time?
No, no.
I was just saying I was talking about that one time.
The boy has a perfectly normal American name.
It next.
Oh, it next.
And it next.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
We just we just call him Eddie.
What does it mean?
He's not referring.
I can't even tell you what they used to call me.
Why not?
Because it's illegal to say it on the radio.
Well, both of the words are illegal.
Well, no, the first one's OK.
Dumb.
You can say that.
It was what followed.
But it rhymes with my human slave name.
So it was a takeoff.
It was a joke.
They didn't really mean that I was a dumb.
Turtle egg.
Oh, man.
There's nothing worse than being called that or actually having to resemble one during
the process.
I wondered if you why you didn't take the same name as your estate like so many slaves
did.
Yeah.
I was.
I was only quote whatever they were, you know, stanks the stanks.
Yeah.
My real name is my my actual name would be from my original tribe is Rasputin.
Rasputin.
Well, Rasputin slash Romanoff.
So nobody believes me when I say that.
So just forget.
Don't even you can just pretend I didn't even say it.
I don't understand.
I'm referring to listener.
I.
I will never ignorant, stupid listeners pretend you don't know who I'm referring to.
I will never mention slash Romanoff.
Yes.
I will never mention that you claim to have an ancestor or you are the ancestral line
of the illegitimate child of Rasputin.
And what's your name?
Zarina.
Alexandra.
Alexandra Romanoff.
Yeah.
Because.
Because crazy people have been known to claim that they're the heir to the crown jewels
of the Russian throne or that they're a secret agent, a part of the intelligence community.
Because then when you go, well, do you have any proof of that?
Of course not.
It was secret.
So it's you find then many people claim to be psychics, spacemen, people from the future,
or even from the distant past.
I'm from the far distant past.
I thought you said you don't wait for me from outer space.
No, no, no, no.
You said.
Some people actually are from outer space.
Princess.
Right.
Is queen of all the UFOs.
But I agree with her.
Unidentified FOS.
See, but you don't even understand what she's saying.
I agree completely with her.
And I forgot what I was going to say.
I'm going to have to agree with her for she is she who must be heard.
I feel something.
What's that?
I don't know.
She is she who has must be whatever she says to do done.
What's that tinkling sound?
So now do it.
It sounds like a tinkle tinkle in my ear.
Like it looks like there's a little mouse in there running around in my head.
It's we.
It's weird.
Oh, it's a tinkle tinkle.
Now my brain swelling.
It feels like it's going to pop out of my skull.
There went Dave.
The lonesome.
I'm going to go.
Chris.
Dismal display has shut off, but I bet we can tickle it back into shape.
I'll just run around inside his ear a little bit more.
Things inflated here.
Hope that shows the subgenius is actually can use tools under some conditions and have
been known to make the show to give it kind of a hook shape, then dip it down into the
ear of the listener or of the day.
That's the case.
Might be.
Yeah.
That's right.
The other.
And then the only.
Yeah.
Attention.
You're in this.
And eventually suck the attention out of the listener or the days.
Of course.
We have some actually.
Must be placed close to the.
It relates to the cerebral cortex.
And that way I've lost it.
To get out here.
Go be closer to the table.
Take a look at what I'm doing here.
Opening up the.
Well, is that.
It's not.
The force.
We all know.
Choco Choco.
This is the actual force.
And it's the.
Corruption.
Which we can find the.
Way.
Get out.
Or it is.
You're breaking up.
You're cracking up.
You're not cracking me up.
No, no, there's no way to do that.
Short of a.
Hammer.
You have to have a very expensive filter to do that.
We obviously can't.
Afford the good filters.
So we hold our mouths real close.
And then we cut them like this.
So that.
You sound this weird quality.
Is cracked.
Cracked.
Cracked was a.
Cracked actually was a crappy.
Imitation of mad.
But.
The cracked.
Dot com.
Website has actually shown some pretty funny stuff.
But they're out.
If you're into humor.
They're out.
For the.
Human.
Was.
You.
Are.
Dopey.
E.
Guy.
Or.
Something.
Like.
That.
Yeah.
They were obviously.
A.
Rip.
It was like a Canadian rip off of the original true Dobbs.
You might say.
I just think of all the things.
Those.
Rats.
Think.
Canadians.
Have stolen from us over these years.
As well as the Mexicans.
All of the country.
Right at the neck of the Mississippi River.
They will eat your brain.
Watch out.
It's a cyclops.
Type of suction.
Friends.
There's water leaking out of our country every second.
Pouring into the ocean.
Through the Mississippi River and other culprits.
What are you going to do about it?
We must bring these tributaries of the water and watersheds to justice.
And we must do it now.
It's scandalous.
What the hell.
Millions for defense.
But not one cent for tributaries.
Small degree of help.
But we need a big fence.
A really big fence.
Friends.
A fat one.
Around.
Yes.
A fat fence around America.
Especially the oceanic parts.
Because people could swim ashore.
You see.
Yes.
So we must.
We must wall off the ocean.
As well as the borders.
With Mexico.
And they have to be really high walls.
Because people have planes now.
Airplanes.
So they have to be high enough that a plane can have two planes fly.
40,000 feet.
We need a wall more than 40,000 feet high.
Going all the way around the contiguous continental United States.
Mr. and Mrs. America.
You can do it.
We can do it.
We'll pull together and build the largest wall ever created on the face of the earth.
The artist Christo could do it.
Communicators and satellite will notice the wall.
People in outer space will notice the wall.
The Venusians will finally take note.
Are we going to let the Chinese outwall us, friends?
Yeah, look what they did 5,000 years ago.
Right.
That was 5,000 years ago.
And their slaves were hardly paid compared to our slaves.
They had more fish.
We have more prisoners than they do now that we could put to work building the great wall
of America.
But they still had more fish.
Not North America, but the United States of America.
Because you know, North America includes the Mexicans and the people in Canada.
And also the people in Papua New Guinea.
Right.
And the electorate.
And I say just to, because it'd be too complicated to deal with Hawaii and Alaska and Puerto
Rico, I say just let them go.
Sink them.
Drop them.
Cut them off.
They're too far away from the precious bodily fluids which we're extracting and re-expreting.
That's right.
We've got to protect America.
And you know, once you've got a 40,000-foot wall in place all the way around, and it would
have to be a mile thick or so to stand that high.
Then you've got to put a 9,000-foot wall in place.
And you've got to put a net over it.
A large, very finely meshed but impenetrable net.
A net not just of jet planes armed with bombers, but a literal, physical net.
So things might be a little bit shady inside the United States after we've boxed it in.
Well, essentially what we need to do is get a giant U.S. shaped box.
That is perfect.
That we can open the top.
Oh, yeah.
And we can lock it up every now and then, let the light and air in.
But keep it to where we can't let anybody else out.
We can actually lock it up.
We can actually figure out.
That's all we've got to do is just build a big enough box around the country.
It won't even really be a wall.
It'll be hermetically sealed from the top to the bottom.
We can even dig underneath and build barriers close to the center of the earth so nobody
can actually seep up into our native land.
We would need...
Somehow desecrate our precious potluck.
Yes, yes.
You could put the whole nation on lockdown.
We would have to actually put the walls out.
How far out in the ocean do we have territorial rights?
Well, we take whatever territory.
50 miles or something.
Let's put them in Europe.
Let's put it right next to Europe.
Let's spread it all as close as we can to those places that might want to...
Oh, that's crazy.
We have treaties and things with those people.
I'm sure everybody has treaties.
Treaties.
We'll take care of that problem too.
We'll kill all the trees and then we'll use them to fill the box.
Chop down the treaties.
Like we did with the Indians.
George Washington chopped down the very first treaty with the Native Americans.
That is true.
And then he said, I won't lie about it, I chopped down that treaty.
He used that accent, by the way, because as we know, George Washington was a native Texan.
We can only imagine what George Washington...
He might have sound like...
Texas belonged to Mexico then.
So technically, our first president was a Mexican national.
And he was skilled at cunnilingus as well.
Many artifacts don't understand that because the pipe's growing out of their snout.
I missed that.
Okay, he wasn't as good as you are.
I know what you're trying to get me to say.
Yeah.
I don't know what I'm trying to get you to say.
I don't know what I'm trying to get me to say.
I know.
It's been a problem for all of us for the last several, I don't know how many years.
But that won't stop us from doing a radio show.
Not having the slightest idea of what we're going to say.
Never.
It's never slowed us down, not for a minute, nay.
And why say anything to begin with?
Just the sheer luxury that those people out there enjoy, listening to us violate all the rules and tenets...
Lucky, they're so lucky.
God, I envy those listeners who get to listen to us.
I wish I could sit and just listen to us go on and on and on and on and on...
Well, Mr. Stang, I'm a little reluctant to tell you this.
But I'm afraid it has to be told.
I've been reading the demos, you know, the demographics on some of your shows.
I've been running through the Nielsen's and checking out some things.
And apparently there are, let me see if I got this right, I don't want to hurt...
Three people who listen to the Hour of Slack.
Yes.
So we've decided...
Actually, it's four now, counting you.
Well, counting the guy in the other room there.
Well, actually, I've never really listened to the show.
I'm just supposed to...
The legal department here wants to...
They wanted me to call you and let you know that we're...
After next season, we're going to have to either let you go or something here is in the works.
You're just not picking up all the people you said you were going to pick up.
You mean...
Wait a minute.
You mean we don't have to keep doing this every week for the rest of our lives?
No, unfortunately...
Oh, my God!
No, no, no, no, no.
Thank you.
I'm getting out of here now.
I'm afraid...
Wait, Mr. Stang, I'm afraid...
Mr. Stang, you can't.
We need you.
Mr. Stang, I'm afraid...
The listeners need you.
I'm afraid you misunderstood something.
You still are required, as per the contract, to perform and submit the show on time as
per usual for the remaining 24 years of the contract.
Unfortunately, there will be no re-witness payments or any sort of reimbursement as
you have, as you know, already been paid.
Unfortunately, you're not going to be able to do that.
No one will hear you, but you will still have to do the show.
I'm back now.
Did I miss anything?
Hey, uh, Stang?
Yeah, uh...
Dave?
That legal guy just got off the phone.
We still have to do it.
Oh, one of the legal guys?
What?
The guy from the network said that we got to still do it, even though we won't get
any more money and nobody will be allowed to listen to it.
What do you mean, more money?
We never got any money.
Well, I know.
I think it's just a little bit of a change.
I think we were about to explain that to him, but he was very, uh, just did his
appeal and got off there.
Bob is that way, man.
He just, he will not do small talk.
He just, he comes in and goes, nope, sorry, you're not fired.
Stay.
It's all business.
And then, yeah, it's like, uh, and then he just turns...
No small talk.
Right.
And then, yeah, no, not even the common human decency to give you a reach around, you might
say.
Yeah, and why, what I want to know, if you're supposed to be so palsy-walsy with him, why?
I don't know.
Maybe he's just not the type of guy that you want to be.
Yeah, I mean, you know, somebody from the legal department called up instead of him
and say, hey, uh, hey, uh...
Ivan.
Hey, Ivan.
You know, um...
Yeah?
I've been wondering, man, uh, things aren't going too good for the show.
I mean, you've got like, you know, marginal one listener or something like that.
I know.
That's why we quit.
That's why we're not on the air now, are we?
I mean, I've walked out.
I'm on my cell phone now.
So, yeah.
I'm not talking to the show.
I'm just talking to you out in the parking lot.
Yeah.
Yeah, Stang came in and said, wham, man, you still gotta do it, man.
Well, I left the phone thing open.
I mean, I left it on the...
It'd be illegal to just leave empty air space.
You can't do that.
Well, no, unless the parking lot is animated with many technotronic sounds, I would say
that you're, um, either...
See, that can't be here.
I can hear the background there.
That can't be in the parking lot, can it?
No, that's...
I left, um, I, uh, this excellent CD running in the background when I left the station.
Of your head.
Yes.
Boy, excellent.
Yeah.
No, because, see, we're actually on the air hearing a...
We're on the air right now.
That's what I'm trying to tell you.
So, if you're in the parking lot, simultaneously in front of the console there...
Well, eventually, um, Rob or somebody will come into the station and turn us off.
That's what I'm praying.
That's what I've been praying for 20...
How long have we been doing this show?
53 years?
24...
No, more like 30.
I started...
It was October 13th, 1985, was Hour of Slack number one.
This is Hour of Slack number 1205.
So...
Oh, my God, man.
That translates to 24 years of slave labor in Dobstown.
Well, that...
No, that means I get 24 years off of slavery.
I've only got 50 more years of slave labor in Dobstown that I have to put in because I've
already done Showtime, you know, for 24 years.
But that's the point I'm trying to make.
But I'm ready to quit.
I've had it.
I've had enough to hear with you people, hoss and hosses.
That's the point I'm trying to make.
And don't cut no ice with me, see.
He just wants to quit his job for Bob.
Right.
That's what Bob said.
Quit your job, repent.
Quit your job and slack off.
Well, it's about time we followed his advice, don't you think?
No, I don't understand a damn thing you're saying.
Throw our microphones to the stage.
Bob is not going to let you do that.
He listened to their cost to the producers, as Pope Meyer used to do.
Man, he had spirit.
Back in those days, preachers didn't care how much Stang would have to pay for the microphone.
They'd just slam it to the stage to show their passion.
Bunch of rotten kids, if you ask me, just ruining everybody's life.
Spoiled, rotten, spoiled, spoiled, spoiled.
They'd hit you head.
They were giving too much slack.
I know I wrecked your stuff, but I was really having fun.
I hope you don't mind, Rev Boy.
Well, Bob used to dunk people in slack, and he didn't even charge them.
But then they'd come back and go, Bob, dunk me in the slack again.
He'd go, well, look, I showed you how to dunk yourself.
Well, it soon became like an opaque pitch.
But they couldn't dunk themselves.
They couldn't dunk themselves.
It's like once Bob dunked them once, they'd have to come back, oh, Bob, dunk me again,
dunk me again.
It also had the anti-dunk repellent shield built right into the substance itself.
He gave them
And that's why we advise anyone to use the dunk to use the repellent as well, or else
the dunk will never work again.
He'd give them the fishing pole.
He'd show them how to put the worm on the hook.
He'd cookhe'd show them how to catch the fish.
He'd cook the trout.
He'd fix them some trout almondine.
And they'd call him up the next day and go, Boband he'd give them the pole.
And the worms.
And go, now you know what to do.
And they'd call him back the next day and go, Bob, I'm hungry.
Fix me a trout almondine again.
But that wasn't the fine part, was tooting the knobs.
Well
Bringing it up here, tweaking it down there a little bit.
Needless to say, tweaking and turning the knobs is what it's all about.
The pots and pans coming up and down.
Reverend Stang said as he tweaked and turned a knob.
Mmm, that fish is good.
I got more than one knob, too, honey.
That fish is bad.
There's some things I only got one of, but there's a bunch of things that I got a bunch of.
Oh, one of these almonds actually flew into my nostril and it lodged there.
It gives new meaning to the term cluster love.
Mmm, mmm.
And that's what this show is, friends.
It's a big cluster love.
Pounds of monkeys pounding each other.
They're regeneratively and figuratively and literally and furiously as each and every one of them longs for something better than they ain't got.
There's only one way around it, friends.
Let's sign up and reenlist or die.
Or join the church of the, uh, uh, uh, Mr. Ding Dong, the O.M.E.
It's the slickest poo flinging you'll ever experience.
Mmm, yeah.
Whether you're the target or the flinger.
Whether you're the flinger, the flingee, or the flinglonger.
It's lots of stinky fun for everyone.
Yes, we will...
Ha...
We'll stink up the airwaves for a good long time, won't we, Reverend Stank?
And we won't only get not a dime.
We'll only not only never be seen.
We'll not only only not not not only be never heard.
We'll not only only not not only only not not not only.
Only, only, no, only, only, no, never.
We'll never be allowed to perform.
And the, and the dude in front of so few people again.
And then...
Well, we do have one more X Day before the saucers come and take us away.
Take away us faithful subgeniuses.
And the, yes, the saucers always come and take us away.
Every year.
In our minds.
In our dreams.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
It's a trap.
But I'm not going, my faith remains unshaken.
An X Day is, you know what's surprising?
It creeps up on you.
It's a concentration camp.
We're surrounded by barbed wire.
Big, rough German shepherds with sharp fangs and stuff.
I have a song.
Don't mention that.
Barbed wire, barbed wire, barbed wire, you're mean.
The black choppers slobber overhead.
You rip up my britches and tear up my jeans.
Oh, down below they're having parties and flinging, uh, slings.
And having a hell of a good old time in the name of Dobbs.
That's what the hour of slack is all about, baby.
Meanwhile, all around them are the instruments of the megastate.
Of the authorities from outer space.
Meanwhile, they're having fun and saying, let's get slack and ha, ha.
And there's barbed wire.
It's metal, but it's like sharp as any real barbed wire.
Actually, although I'm not a fan of barbed wire, I'm not a fan of it.
I certainly can't do a call to action or anything.
I can mention that some of the features of the upcoming X Day will include brand new
electrostimulo negative reinforcement wristbands, which are actually labeled as such and are
collector's items.
The 13th person there will get number 13013, which spells out Bob, by the way, for you
ignorimuses.
And...
Also, we have John Deere tractor beam beach party.
Well, that's another great thing I was just thinking about, too.
The never ending searchlight beam.
That's another thing that we got going on full time this year.
The never ending searchlight and the beach party.
Like I said, if somebody wants to bring bikinis, hula hoops, beach blankets, bingos...
Explosive beach balls are what we're really looking for.
Beer and whatever else.
But what do people, what do men wear at the beach today?
Heavy fur cover ups for your bathing suits.
Because it gets to be like 30 degrees at night there.
Yeah, the hot plasma balloons.
Yeah, the baby will be so...
You have hot metal, hot plasma balloons will keep everybody warm.
And the hot foam.
It's one of those hot foam...
Oh, man.
Hot foam.
Self-heating foam beach parties.
There's no ocean for many, many miles from Brushwood to the site of X Day festivities
where we await the end of the planet.
The total and utter destruction of everything on planet Earth.
Except for what we, the saved subgeniuses, save.
Exactly.
There are oceans of smiles and slack though.
Oceans of smiles and slack that we must preserve and keep in our escape vessels if we want to preserve them.
How about the flying chest merkin?
The huge flying chest merkin that resembles a flying carpet man.
If you want dubs on...
Literally by the device hitting me in the head.
You can have that.
You want milk dubs on?
If you want dubs on that, then you have to toss them yourself.
It was wonderful.
And in some really oblique way.
I'm still trying to deal with on both an emotional and whatever level.
But it is often very great just to smell the rarefied air of the helium balloons and...
It's grating to me.
Exploding children out there in the woods.
It grates on my nerves like this show does.
And like the woods do.
And like...
But, you know...
You've become an existentialist and not a slackie.
A slacker.
Oh, no.
I am...
This year, I am going to be a slacker.
You know, I used to knock myself out to make sure everybody was ready to get off on X-Day at 7 AM.
But this time, I'm letting the kids do it.
The little babies.
The babies that...
Baby subgeniuses are running X-Day this year.
Baby priestess Pisces.
Baby Moda Mac.
Baby Dr. Legume.
Baby...
All the little...
Baby subgeniuses.
The ones who didn't join the church by 1982.
Which is pretty much everybody on the planet, if you ask me.
But why are they still babies then?
They're so small and stuff.
Are you...
Have you perfectly pigmented them?
Compared to Philo and me, everybody is a baby.
I thought you had maybe even actually pigmified them in some sort of weird bonsai tree way as your child slayed.
Yeah...
I like dog spirits.
They're unrivaled...
You know what I'm talking about.
It perfectlyifies them, but we'd love for them to dance or swim around.
We have them dance around the tables, catch and run.
They all dance and what side will they push me, give me a Ace?
people we don't even know.
The crazy
magic stories made up by
preacher types.
Imaginative, nearsighted
dorks who couldn't
work like regular folks.
They come up with this mumbo jumbo
and the next thing you know, you got
everybody facing the same direction
every five minutes.
Making the same movements and saying
the same things.
Praise Bob, every five
minutes. It's the same old song.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yep, praise Bob. Praise Bob.
Praise Bob.
Because you know what, Bob don't never
change. Unfortunately.
He bites the same Bob.
It's the same Bob that you saw
this morning. It's the same Bob that you
see tonight in your bed
but creeping up behind you.
Bob does not change.
He's got your...
He may appear to you to change
when he's handing you
a free ticket to Key to the
City, then he's a good Bob.
When he's taking away your
virginity from
the same direction, he's a bad Bob.
But Bob himself
does not change. Only your
attitude towards Bob changes.
He himself is the eternal
good, evil,
good, bad.
He's the ambiguity
at the center of the universe.
Virginia!
He's where you zero your meter about
good or evil.
You know, in reality, that Bob
represents the wellspring
of all variety.
Bob is not only the only
one and only one and only.
No, he's ten. You're zero.
Huh?
He's one and one and one and one and one
and one until he's ten. He's like
the father, the son,
the mom, the Holy Ghost
and a whole bunch of little
rugrats. He's the perfect
balance of what is right
and what is wrong.
He's like a whole neighborhood unto himself.
He's the village.
It's a danger. Not a pleasant neighborhood.
Not a very clean neighborhood.
But it's a homey.
And it smells like an ashtray.
The whole Bob neighborhood.
It's a funny kind of place.
His love for you is like
an ashtray.
It's almost as if you yourself
were...
Think about it.
Now, my friend, think about it.
Aren't you, in a way, aren't you Bob's ash?
Don't you wish you could
slice him?
And it produces
waste matter.
He's gotta dump that waste matter somewhere.
He pries something open and dumps out that stuff
in that pipe. What's he dumping it into?
He's dumping it into your head.
Oh, he keeps talking
to your head, but you keep listening.
He opens up your ear
pan and pours the
fruits of his smoking
in.
Everybody have a burger.
Which is out.
That pipe grown out of my snout.
So, if you're a religious
subgenius, if you truly believe,
then you're Bob's ashtray.
It means you're bound to get snuffed
one of these times.
Why not get snuffed early?
Well, you get emptied every now and then.
That's the thing. He fills you up and then he empties you.
I want to go next
to the aloe plant.
No.
You're going to go into the
trash bin along with every other
Bobby.
I want to be fertilizer for living
things. I don't want to be
discarded like a piece of
You won't go away forever.
You'll be part of the great
dump heap of Dobbs Town.
The compost, as it were.
Nothing ever dies.
It's the circle of life, Dave.
It's along with the worms.
Think of the worms.
You wouldn't
deny the worms
that they're just
dessert, which is you
after you've been ripened in the ground
for a few years.
Build up those sugars.
Enriching the loam.
The worms.
Why, they're Bob's greatest
customers. There certainly is
most numerous. And they
outweigh us as a
life form. Did you know that, Dave,
that the creatures that live in the ground
outweigh the
creatures that live above the ground
all taken together?
And rich in the loam.
Come on, we all
headed back home.
Come on, come on, and take
a bunch. We're all gonna
fructify in the sun.
Yeah. Hi, kids.
I'm Dr. Death. I mean, Mr.
Hello, I'm Mr. Death.
And we're all gonna be like French-fried
bananas someday.
Out in the hot, steaming
blue sun. So wake
up and go back to sleep.
Shhh!
No!
Friends,
you too can be a master of the
stoogely arts.
And they're
heard in the background here.
In the far skin, there.
Uh.
The background is getting louder, Stank.
Ooh!
Yay!
There she is.
She's so beautiful for a reptile woman.
She kind of resembles
Dole.
In some kind of cheesy...
Oh, and here's another spoiler about
the new Star Trek movie.
Kirstie Alley
appears as one of the green-skinned
naked dancing
girls.
I can't believe you're telling him this.
It's like a cameo.
It's kind of funny. They play it for laughs.
Stank!
Or, um, uh, bazoombas.
How can you ruin that movie
You can...
Everything's a bazoomba.
Your precious listeners.
Anywhere you grab on that thing, there's a bazoomba.
Or something like a bazoomba.
Some flappy, flab...
floppy thing.
Some soft, round thing
that you can
do things with.
Oh, yeah. Look, I think it's the
self-perpetuating fly.
Fly in flyswatter.
Look, here it comes.
Here it goes.
See, it recreated itself
in one little fell swoop.
One swell foop.
Yeah, my Australian
boss used to say that.
One swell foop.
It's swelling. It's swelling
more and more and more and more.
Uh-oh.
I can see the light
coming in through the window on it.
It's getting bigger
instead of...
Help!
No, wait.
It's supposed to do that. Some guys have to take extra pills
just for that to happen.
If the foop swells up enough, it can explode,
can't it?
It can, and I took my pills.
What's wrong with my skin?
Wait, that's somebody else's skin.
What's wrong with my...
What's conceptually wrong with me,
Dr. Stang?
I want to know what...
Dave,
the list would require...
a scroll that would reach from here
to your scroll-tum on the moon.
It would require
a computer hard drive
so big that it would
keep the entire Akashic
records of all
time and space.
That list of your
flaws would be so
very long, but
the list of promises
that Bob makes to you
is a thousand billion
godzillion times longer.
So you're saying, in effect,
that Bob is flossing us
of our flaws?
Bob is the ultimate fluffer.
By slackening our...
What did you say?
He's fluffing you.
He's fluffing you are.
He's preparing you, but not all the way.
Just for the right kind of
photograph, sir.
He could be plumping you
for the right juices?
If you're prepared to...
plump up?
If you're ready to step behind
the new X-ray machines at the airport
where we can see just how fat
and out of shape you really are.
And mock you.
We actually surround the electro-sphere
of the body with... But don't worry.
Ray radiation, which is
quite exciting to watch on the...
It tickles. And when you're going through that new
fangled X-ray machine, friends, remember...
On the other end,
if you're going through the...
You'll notice you'll go through a different...
Men go through one line, women go through another line.
Well, the people
watching the screen, it's always
men watching the women
on the see-through X-ray machine
clothing-removing
vision device.
And it's always women looking at the men.
Homeland security
trained men and women
looking at you.
The opposite sex.
And leering, drooling, drooling, drooling, drooling, drooling.
But more than that, laughing.
No, have you ever seen
how those new
X-ray things work?
They see through your clothing
and your bags of drugs
and explosives.
But not your skin.
So they don't have to look at your ugly old bones.
They get to actually see
why you're wearing that truss.
Exactly.
How much that bra is padded.
They can really see through you.
If you know what I'm saying.
The dagger within your boot.
Right.
Wow, that was really succinctly and
eruditely put.
Why, thank you.
Princess, we've been smuggling daggers and boots for a long time
but we can't do that anymore.
No more.
No, sir. Ever since 9-11.
It changed everything.
At least when they bombard us
with this dose of X and gamma ray
radiation, at least
only our clothes get the tumors
and not our bodies.
And we can thank Mr. Homelander for it.
And he is a great...
He's...
And that's wonderful of him
to do that for me.
Don't you think?
Every time.
Let's not mince words.
Let's slay them.
It's explosively wonderful.
Let's set them on fire.
Let's torture them first.
Let's mince words, but first let's torture them.
Until they talk.
Underboard those words until they...
Until they spill.
Word.
We'll spill words all over.
We'll wordboard them.
No way. That doesn't work.
Boy, that is even more erudite.
I can only sit in lackluster abandonment
back here in my
uneasy chair listening to that.
I don't think it's ever been put better before.
It might have been taken away from us,
but it's never been put...
Bob will put it to you, friends.
J.R. Bob will put it to you, friends.
Bob Dobbs and his spokespeople,
we, and myself,
on the Hour of Slack,
and Dave. All of we.
It's listless curmudgeon, Dave.
Listless curmudgeon.
I actually like that.
I personally wish
in all his holy
sanctum, whatever it is,
that Bob would at least
allow us three more weeks
with the national audience
we have for crime and murder.
I don't think we're allowed.
I mean,
they say three people were listening.
Three more weeks!
How long is it till next day, though,
actually, as of this broadcasting?
It's like
a month and a half.
A little more than a month and a half.
Up to the
most of our listeners who hear it
tragic numbers
of days later than we
broadcast it, or even a week
or two later, it's only a month away.
Friends, are you ready?
No, I don't mean are you ready to
look at subgenius.com
for information. I mean
are you ready to meet your
maker, or your un-maker?
Are you ready? Because you ain't gonna meet your maker.
Are you ready to mince
your monkey? Unless your makers,
your parents, are subgeniuses.
Then the whole family gets to
escape to Planet X on your
own personal escape vessel.
You're not gonna be stuck on board with a bunch
of Bobbies. Nope.
Nope. You're not. It's not like that. Answer my question
right there. You're not gonna be stuck on
board with those idiots, the fellow
numbskulls at X Day. You're gonna have your
own, well you can be if you want to,
if you can force them to.
Friends,
we're approaching
the end of this hour of Slack.
And Dave, I'm gonna cut
you off forever.
Could you cut me off in a
sentence so it sounds kind of...
What were you saying Dave? I didn't
get that. What was that Dave?
Okay.
Okay. He's gone.
A little bit unusual. Oh no, no, no.
Bye Dave.