From PR News in Washington, I have the ability to short out industrial equipment.
There are continued reports of pirates. Officials say there's no direct evidence.
I'm expensive and difficult.
Britain is registering its hottest October day in recorded history.
Right, the Sid Barrett enigma.
There's an outbreak of 15,000 pirates.
NATO says it's captured a senior leader of the biting ants.
They're known as hairy crazy ants, and they tried to bring down a jet on Christmas in Yemen and potentially heading toward Bermuda.
This is pure.
Was it gray aliens? No.
Was it reptiles from another dimension? No.
Was it the Vatican? No.
It was the.
And is what do you call it? It's normal.
I don't know what it is. I don't know.
But, you know, of course, Hollywood's going to convince us differently.
All right. Bob, I think so. I'm not sure.
Beth, I hear you calling, but I can't come home right now.
What are y'all doing, like probing each other?
Just a few more hours and I'll be back home to you.
Oh, Beth, I hear them calling. Beth, what can I do? Yeah.
A load of crap. What are we talking about, Bob?
If I'm feeling generous.
I will surprise you.
The Illuminati!
I'm undergoing a personality transformation now.
And, oh, yeah, white Southern American poor people.
Yeah, that's that.
Stop being stupid, people.
OK, are we that so brainwashed?
No. No.
Well, maybe yes.
Although, you know, Bob.
Oh, my God.
Obviously, Bob production.
I'm guessing something like that.
Yeah.
And that's why there's so many wonderful songs written for your children today,
like Booty Love and Booty Meat and Shake Your Ass, Bob,
and let them see what they get.
You.
You got and all these wonderful songs that will inspire your daughter to grow up and become a.
So where were we?
Bob, what are the odds of that?
And gee, let's see.
You know, I bet don't have to sneeze.
I don't have to sneeze.
Anyway, back to.
I.
So I witnessed more violence.
I'm.
They adore me.
They love me.
So anyway, women are big fans of Bob and the rednecks.
OK, they're good people.
Anyway, all of a sudden, the police, the police, like everybody's freaking out.
Damn, there's always a catch.
I don't want to talk to these cocksuckers, but you have to.
In life, you have to do a lot of things you don't fucking want to do.
Many times.
That's what the fuck life is.
One vile fucking task after another.
But don't get aggravated.
Then the enemy has you by the short hair.
Well, God damn it.
That cocksucker motherfucker shit.
Fuck his dick.
We drove all the way to Fredericksburg, Texas, and got a motel room specifically so that
we could go to Enchanted Rock, one of our very favorite places.
And as we left Fredericksburg for Enchanted Rock, we saw a sign that said park closed.
We pulled over and called the park.
And they said,
Yes, until three days from now, Enchanted Rock is closed for a public hunt, which has
been set up by the public cunt, who is, or cunts.
The park is closed so that people who signed up six months ago in advance can go shoot
innocent animals.
And people like us who just want to hike around the rock.
And explore the cave.
And fuck and fromp.
Can't do that.
All you can do is kill and shoot.
And we could not even park by the sign to take a picture of me in the Bob mask standing
with the rock and the Enchanted Rock sign in the background.
The minute we pulled over to take a picture, this rather unfriendly Texas redneck park ranger said,
You can't park here.
You can't even stop here.
I said, we were just going to take a picture with you.
No, you can't even stop here.
He didn't say why.
I said, the park is closed, right?
He goes, yeah, there's hunters and they aren't supposed to shoot towards the road, but you
never know.
And then he hung around and waited to see us leave.
So we have been fucked running.
It's a long, you know, we went out of our way to go to Enchanted Rock.
We really did.
To go to Enchanted Rock.
We've been here before.
We wanted to explore a certain cave that's kind of hidden away in the back that we didn't
get to last time.
Well, it's not going to be open again for three days.
We've got to be heading for California by then.
This natural place enchanted us and now it has infuriated us.
Yeah.
So I called the park services and they said, oh yeah, it's got cows.
He can't come out until January 13th.
Now she was kind of upset.
I said, oh, yeah, well, I'm going to leave it at that.
I said, do you have any other suggestions?
And she said, oh yeah, there's Inch Lake about 45 minutes from here.
But you better call.
Yeah.
But you better call first because they might be having a public hunt too.
So I did call and they're not having, and they are, they're having a public hunt on
the other side of the lake, but they do have two hiking trails open.
And Inch Lake was a place we considered going today.
We thought we might go there today and then spend all day tomorrow at Enchanted Rock.
But it looks like we're just going to be leaving this part of Texas and heading out west through
the most desolate parts of the world without ever getting a chance to get our rocks off
at the cave at Enchanted Rock.
So all we can hope is that Inch Lake, which is another
hour from here actually, is worth the hike.
All we want is a nice little privacy hike with some gorgeous earth, eyeball shattering
landscapes and eroded rocks everywhere.
That's all we ask.
Blind railing scenery.
That's it.
Just, you know.
Oh, and just so we don't sound totally stupid, it's not like we didn't read up every possible
aspect of Enchanted Rock, even though we've been here before.
I've got like dozens of tourist books and guides and websites and not one of them mentioned
this public hunt.
God damn!
Oh, fuck you, Jack!
And your dick shit!
God.
Oh, fuck you, Jack!
None of them said they'd ever be closed ever!
No, that's an extra little surprise that the Texas Parks Department and everything leaves
for you.
Why don't you just recalculate your goddamn ass off, Jack?
Or dick, or whatever your name is.
I'm fucking high on the road.
I wanna face camera when you're old.
Don't you want a snitch from blah blah blah.
But you're a snitch from blah blah blah.
But you and me never had a laugh.
I'm fucking high on the road.
I wanna face camera when you're old.
Don't you want a snitch from blah blah blah.
But you and me never had a laugh.
I'm fucking high on the road.
I wanna face camera when you're old.
Well, it turned out to be a good thing, despite all my cussing, that Enchanted Rock was not
Tanted Rock was closed for the public hunt.
Indeed.
Because there wasn't much else we could do, but sort of a secondary choice on our list called Inks Lake.
And Sphinx said that Inks was not all that hot, but he didn't know.
No, he really didn't know.
Most of Inks Lake is pretty ordinary, but there's a section called the Devil's Waterhole, or as Princess Wee and I call it, Bob's Waterhole.
I think they call it the Devil's Waterhole because it's so cool, they don't want the uncool people going down in there.
They want to scare off the idiots so that only the subgeniuses will be attracted to a place with a name like the Devil's Waterhole.
It actually looks like God's.
It's an incredibly beautiful section of river rocks that are granite.
It's kind of like it's part of Enchanted Rock, but it's a more crumbly part and is carved as if the...
I would say it is kind of carved as if the devil was let loose on it before he was cast into hell.
You know, because he originally was one of God's favorite angels of life.
His waterhole looks like an angel carved it.
It really does.
It's just beautiful.
It was a bit of a climb to get down in there because that's what we like to do.
That's the whole idea on these hikes is to get down in there.
Anyway, ironically and yet subgeniously enough, the fact that our original goal, Enchanted Rock, was closed turned out to be a stroke of luck.
Because otherwise we probably would have blown off the Devil's Waterhole at Inks Lake.
Yes.
And I'm really glad we came here.
Me too.
Because it's an out-of-the-way hoodoo-filled amazing spot.
Mm-hmm.
Not too many poe-buckers here at all.
Now we have to go back to Fredericksburg though.
That's an hour.
And then I have to do an hour of slack, which I don't think will be this one.
No.
I think this one will be heard months after.
It's recorded.
So, praise Bob.
Blah, blah.
Whoo!
You know, I was walking down the beach trying to get to my woody.
Well, I had my suds cold and my buds was gold.
I was walking down the beach.
I was trying to get high and get real drunk.
Huh!
Lay in the sand.
With my beach buddy.
But out to the side of my eye, I saw the ultimate wave.
The super wave.
It was the most stoked-out stud wave in all reality.
It was 900 feet tall.
And on the backside of reality too.
I saw a black hole right in the middle of it.
A vortex.
Where the...
I was ready to shoot through that black hole.
And my molecules rearranged.
I'm going to hang five as I shoot through the black hole and the vortex of the super
wave.
The most God awful wave in reality.
On the backside of reality.
I'm going to hang five at the back.
The front side and the left and the right side
Whoo!
I was tubing
I was fixing to cut out
Whoo!
And then
The giant
Whatchamacallit
It was one of those whatchamacallits
Just opened up right out of the sea
String on that one and start sucking me down
It was like a vortex funnel
Sucking me down to the bottom of the ocean
I was getting sucked down
And you know
As much as I hate to admit it
It felt pretty good
Getting sucked down in that vortex wave
All the way down to the bottom of the ocean
But God, I hate to admit it
Whoo!
It felt pretty good
But I hate to admit it
Whoo!
Moving on
On the backside of reality
My bad boy's on the side
Right the way
I'm stoking on my five things
And on down to the backside of reality
Riding on my bad boy's
Stoking on my five things
guitar solo
Our hands in pilgrim bags
And slugs
guitar solo
That was the Swingin' Love Corpses, dear friends.
The title tune from their late 80s or early 90s album,
The Backside of Reality.
Colonel Sphinx drumming on vocals
with Dr. Philo drumming on vocals and sax,
Ray Hay on guitar,
Doug Fowler on bass,
and Skippy Mojo Butcher on drums.
You can find infinite hours of this band,
the Swingin' Love Corpses,
is on Philo's website,
quiveringbrain.com,
which also leads to
high-quality puzzling evidence show recordings.
The music in the background
is from that same album.
Before that,
some of The Devil's Family Vacation,
which is the theme of this hour of Slack,
number 1,358.
The new PR news
is by Reverend Cosmic Debris.
The intro collage
was by Reverend Royal Debris,
the Decapitator.
We heard my hero,
or Shorderpersav,
Al Swearingen,
from that ancient show,
Deadwood.
And the little bit of music mash there
was by The Large.
Now, back to our vacation recordings,
which, incidentally,
we were inspired to do
by similar ones
made by Reverend Tawdry Milktoast
and Dr. Zeronius
on their way to 14X Day last year.
Incidentally,
probably by the time you hear this,
we'll have selected photos
and or movies
of these various places we visited.
All I can say now is
check the news section of subgenius.com,
which gets you to my blog,
or the log for this episode
in the radio section,
or, for that matter,
you can look at YouTube,
RevStang,
one word, RevStang,
and look for
Subgenius Family Vacation.
It's probably no surprise
that everywhere we went,
from friends' yards in the cities
to state parks,
we saw endless numbers of...
Hello, little deer.
They are so tame.
I guess they're just used to
humans feeding them or something.
There's tons of them.
There's people everywhere around here.
Oh, well.
This guy's right in the road behind us.
There's one...
Yeah, oh, they're waiting for us
to hand him an apple.
They don't even know how to eat
deer food.
...food anymore, probably.
Poor deer things.
Poor, poor deer little doe.
Oh, oh.
Dope.
Hey, watch how you say that.
Yes, princess, we are tame.
Turn left at park road four.
Oh, shut up!
A listener has sent a letter in
to the show.
But what did he...
It's not a letter that was meant for the show.
It was a letter that was obviously
found somewhere.
Like, outside of a junior high school.
Oh, yeah, Violet's got this crazy letter he found.
A junior high school?
Actually, it was found by a chaos maker.
Mama Cat.
Now, what's the thing about the junior high school game?
I found a letter.
You should see this letter I found.
It's just amazing.
But it's about a junior high school?
Yeah, it starts out,
I like rainbows, do you?
And then it's addressed to someone named James.
James?
Says, hi, this is a little odd.
I'm not a junior high school.
I know, lol, but I'm bored.
Lol, it's that damn three-letter acronym again.
Anywho, how are you?
Well, I probably know
because I'm probably texting you.
This is torture.
Lol, jeez.
Really, wish I did just like you.
In a way, I do.
Maybe we can hang
and chill like you.
I hope you make
a football team so I can go
to your game and cheer you on
and cheer you on.
My cousin said
she will drive me there.
I just need money.
I like giraffes.
Just thought you should know that again.
I kind of wish you did stay
the week at my casa.
Lol.
It would be fun.
This is real.
It's written on lined paper
with different colored pencils.
Play with my dogs, chase my goats,
go on walks,
ride my quad.
I don't know what else.
Holy balls.
My wrist hurts.
I haven't written this much since school.
At the moment,
you're not texting back.
I'm going to draw you a picture
with a giraffe
and a sexy dragon.
Ten minutes later,
look on the back.
Oh my gosh.
The dragon and the giraffe
are having mad sex.
That didn't happen.
There is a dragon says,
I just jizzed.
And the giraffe says,
Oh, harder, babe.
Oh my gosh.
Sorry, I was bored.
I didn't want to wait.
My ass hurts right now.
And I need to shave soon.
Balls.
Writing this letter
kind of made me like you
a wee bit more.
I'm not the best drawer.
And my ankle hurts too.
Ball, do you like my ladder?
Hey, anyways,
I can't wait to hang with you.
We can make sandcastles.
I wish that the listeners
could see this lined paper
that Philo's reading from.
It really was found on the ground
outside of school.
It kind of looks like sandwiches.
And it really is written
in multicolored
colored pencil.
It's a colored pencil.
Certain words like lol
will be in blue or red.
Well, I'm a go-go now.
Talk to you later.
Duh.
Bye.
Wait, here's my address
and my phone number.
That's...
Do you think that that's a girl,
a young girl writing to a young boy?
Or a sleeve to a master?
A dominatrix to a Eugene?
Dr. Bell?
What the?
Here it is.
This is the document in question.
Oh, my gosh.
I'm touching this special...
Look, on the...
There's a rainbow on the top
and on the back.
It is.
It's decorated.
It shows the giraffes
having intercourse.
Giraffes and the dragons
are rainbows and...
Yeah, well, I can't see
what it says.
Oh, my.
Living life together.
Well, this is certainly
an explicit illustration here.
Singing in harmony.
It does indeed show
the intromission.
It certainly brings back
the...
The memories of the vapid conversations
I heard driving carpool
for teenagers
back in the 90s.
It is a dragon
and a giraffe.
It's almost like an aboriginal picture
of a Komodo dragon.
And it's reared up and then
inserting its...
One of them said
they just released
this ejaculatory edition.
This giraffe.
And it is immaculate giraffe.
It's a colorful...
It's a profound letter.
Maybe we should send it
to Found Magazine.
But I like rainbows.
To do a year-long...
Found Radio Show.
Well, she starts off
as being this cute little thing
and then she gets into
interspecies bestiality
and then...
We're leaving Llano
after a nice day
at the Devil's Waterhole.
But we...
On the way there,
we went by this yard
full of art really fast.
And Princess, we went out there.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
I want to stop and turn around
and go back there.
I said, no, no, no.
We have to go and do the park
before the sun goes down,
which was true.
But on coming back,
she kept her eye open
and just outside of Llano
is a shop.
Or rather,
it's not really a shop,
I don't think.
It's more like a museum
in this woman's yard.
Her name is Kathleen Smith.
And her shop is called
the Tin Lizard
or her museum
or her website
or something.
But she basically
welds metal trees
on which you can hang
anything you want.
But her artwork
consisted of these metal trees
peppering her yard.
Dozens of them,
I would say.
Some were symmetrical.
Some were asymmetrical.
Some were whimsical.
They're metal trees
and they're covered
with glass bottles.
That was her art,
was putting glass bottles
on the ends of these trees.
Wine bottles, mostly.
So one tree might be all
a certain type of
big green wine bottle
and another tree might be
a certain type of
small bright blue bottle.
And others would be
all colors of bottles
plus kitschy coffee cups
and beer mugs
and stuff with funny animals
or faces on them.
Or one was fested
with ice.
Eyeglasses all over the place.
One had model birds
all over it.
And one had Elvis
at the top.
That was the one
that caught my eye.
So it was a psychedelic feast
of kitschiness
and bright colors.
And Kathleen herself
was hot.
Yeah, she was.
She's our age
so it's okay for us
to say a thing like that.
She might even be
a little bit older.
She might be a little bit
older than us.
If that's possible.
I don't think so.
Her grandkids were older
and her kids were older.
But I think she started young.
Anyway, she was a
really nice looking
Texas gilf.
Classic Texan gilf.
For your information,
Princess Wee.
Really?
Yeah, that was a
classic Texas gilf.
She just had that.
And look,
so the Tin Lizard
in Llano, Texas
is a great place
if you're rich.
We end up
in a lot of places
that are,
and they'd be great
if you're,
especially if you were rich.
They're great for us
to just look at.
And evidently,
if you happen to be
passing through
Fredericksburg or Llano
in sunset time,
she said the light
shining through
all the different
colored glass
vases and
glasses
is just
extraordinary.
But we got there
about five minutes
after sunset.
We missed it.
But maybe,
you'll see it.
Yeah, so.
When you're passing through.
Eleventh,
tenth,
ninth,
seventh,
five,
three,
sound,
one,
start.
Murphy Classroom Films
presents
educational film
B-151,
Exorcism
and Your Daily Life.
Music
Gee, Dad,
what a bummer.
Why, what's the matter, Jimmy?
My civics teacher assigned me
this dumb paper on exorcism,
and I'm supposed to go
play ring ball with Bruce.
I mean, what does exorcism
have to do with me,
and ring ball,
and Bruce?
More than you can ever imagine.
I used to feel
the same way
you do about exorcism,
Billy,
but your mom and I
learned long before
you were born
the real importance
that it has
in all our lives.
But I don't even understand
what it means, Dad.
Oh, well,
in a manner of speaking,
Willie,
exorcism is a transitive verb
meaning to expel
an evil spirit
from or out of
a person or place
by invocation
or use of holy names.
It's akin to the Greek
herkos,
offense,
with its cognate
horkos,
an oath,
whence hokazine,
to bind with an oath,
thence exocesare,
exocesare,
that's low Latin.
Gee, Dad,
I still don't understand.
Oh.
Well, Timmy,
let's go see
my old friend Bob Brown
at the bank.
Again?
Good morning, Bob.
Morning, Bob.
Morning, Tommy.
Hi, Mr. Brown.
Well, how have you been
since you were here
this morning
asking about capillary action?
Fine, Mr. Brown.
Good, good.
Well, what is it now?
Wheat production
in the great northwest?
No.
The gross national product
of Sweden?
Golly, that's close.
Our animal friends?
Cold.
Exorcism?
Yes.
I have to write
this dumb paper.
Now, hold on.
Hold on, son.
You wouldn't call it dumb.
If you knew
about exorcism
what my old friend
Mayor Simmons
knows about exorcism,
why don't you
go and see him?
Good morning, Mayor Simmons.
Morning, Bob.
Morning, Freddy.
Well, what is it this time?
The Australian ballot?
Representative government
in post-war Indochina?
The cultivation of sea kelp?
Our internal waterways?
No.
Exorcism, Mr. Mayor.
Now, Billy,
I can tell you this.
If it weren't for exorcism,
Merleville wouldn't be
the town it is today.
Take a look at this graph.
Oh, that's very interesting,
Mr. Mayor,
but I already know
about the pancreas.
Oh, well,
then take a look
at this other graph.
Hmm, it's shaped like a pie.
Have a piece, Sammy.
Now,
that piece of pie
is equal to the 14%
of the Merleville town budget
that goes for exorcism.
Hmm.
Sounds like a lot,
doesn't it?
It sure does.
As a matter of fact,
I was meaning to talk to you
about it.
Well,
if it sounds like a lot now,
ha-ha,
just remember the trouble
we had when I first proposed
it at the town meeting.
Ah!
Boo!
Get him!
gentlemen,
get him!
Gentlemen,
citizens of Merleville.
Mr. Mayor?
Yes, Miss Cratch?
How can you expect
the citizens of Merleville
already bled white
by your corrupt machine
to spend another 14%
of our pie on exorcism?
Whatever that is.
That's right.
Tell him, Miss Cratch.
Miss Cratch,
as our civics teacher,
you of all people
should realize
the importance of exorcism
in this efficient
and democratic
working model township.
That's all very well,
Mr. Mayor,
but aren't we here
to talk about the corn smut
that's ruining our crops?
Ah, grumble, corn smut,
grumble, grumble.
Exactly, Ollie.
Grumble.
Take a look at this working model.
We already know about
the refining of petroleum byproducts.
Shh!
Exactly, Miss Cratch.
Let me turn the working model on.
Now,
as you can see,
these little red trucks here
with the two and a half men
on the side
drive up with their 118%
of 1964 capacity
oil loads
and deposit them
in those five and a half
black buckets,
which are then lifted
to the 75% over parity mark
through these little broken lines,
ending finally
in John's gas station
as fuel for our cars
and farm machinery.
At the lignite mine
as kerosene
to light the lamps
of the workers.
To Mr. Foster's cola factory
as artificial coloring.
And the rest
is exported abroad
by Mr. Artunian
to make nylon stockings.
Then there's none
left.
And therefore,
insecticide.
Exactly, Ollie.
And that's why
we got a corn smut epidemic.
Impeach him!
Awesome, man!
Exercise!
And that's...
And that's how
it all happened, Frankie.
Gee, Mr. Mayor,
I sure see how exorcism
ties into oil refining,
but I still don't think
I have enough
for my dumb civics paper.
I mean,
how does it all fit
into our American way of life?
What Ronnie means, Mayor,
is how does it all fit
into our American way of life?
I might be able
to fill you in on that.
I've got a working model
working over here somewhere.
Oh, but actually,
you'd probably do better
to talk to my friend
Bob Brown
down at the bank.
Again?
Well, actually, Mayor Tweed,
we just came from Bob's office
and, you know, we...
Oh, I see.
Well, let's see.
Who else is open
at this time of night?
Uh, you might try
kindly old Dr. Philith
down at the
Armenian Medical Association.
Now, just soak it
12 times a day
and keep off your side
as much as possible.
I'll give you a subscription
for petroleum jelly.
Oh, hello, Kenny
and your dad.
What's troubling you?
You don't look at all well.
Want an upper?
Uh, no, Doc.
No.
No, my teeth are fine.
It's Lenny here.
He's got to write
a dumb civics paper
on exorcism
and Mayor Simmons
suggested that we visit you.
Well, fine, fine.
You just take off your shirt
and sit over there.
Hmm.
I'll turn the lights out
and...
No.
This first slide
is the gestation
of the frog.
Gee!
Uh, no, no, no, Doc.
What Mickey wanted
to learn about this week
was something entirely...
This is one of the many
great Impressionist cathedrals.
Uh, no, no, no, Doc.
Wowee!
No, no, exorcism, Doc.
Oh.
Well, why didn't you say so?
Let me just set up
this audio-visual projector.
Yeah.
Here we go.
11, 10, 9, 7, 5, 3...
Sound.
1, start.
1, 2, 3, 4...
Herpy Classroom Films presents
educational film B-152,
Ring Ball and Your Daily Life.
Gee, Dad, what a bummer.
Why, uh, what's the matter, Jimmy?
My civics teacher assigned me
this dumbass to do.
I'm supposed to do some paper
on Ring Ball,
and I'm supposed to go
exercise a dibbick with Bruce.
I mean, what does Ring Ball
have to do with me?
Or exorcism?
Or Bruce?
Ah, more than you can ever imagine.
I used to feel the same way
you do about Ring Ball, Harold,
but, uh...
The Firesign Theater did that
in the year 1970, I believe,
from the Duke of Madness
Motors collection.
Some of you may understand
that subgenius radio
owes much of its existence
to those guys.
Before the Texas Guild
of Art commentary,
and again, we'll have photos
up soon at subgenius.com,
we heard Dr. Drummond
reading an actual found letter
on the puzzling evidence show
from KPFA Berkeley.
And now, back in time
to January,
and a race against time.
It'll be dark soon
in the Devil's Hall,
which is where we are.
We're in the Devil's Hall.
It's a slot canyon
with incredible layers.
Like...
You just have to see the pictures.
That's subgenius.com.
But, uh...
It's part of the
Guadalupe National Monument.
Guadalupe Mountains
National Monument.
Where we are hiking back,
having walked for two and a half hours
clambering up rocks
the last half,
which was fun.
But now we...
kind of have to make time
getting back
because it's 3.30 and...
it'll get dark about 5.30.
So we have to go faster
than we came,
which I think we can do.
Don't you, Princess Wee?
Yeah, I think we can.
But the Devil's Hall
was, like all the other
devil-named places
in national monuments
and state parks and so forth,
is so named
to keep the pinks out.
Because it's too cool
for the pinks and nerds.
They give it a devil name
to scare them out.
And only subgeniuses come
and enjoy the incredible scenery.
It's as incredible
as the Devil's Waterhole.
So we've been to his hall,
his toilet,
his waterhole.
I've been to his kitchen.
You haven't been there yet.
But I've been to the Devil's Kitchen
in Utah.
And...
They're wonderful.
But it is a bit of a...
Well, they called this one
a moderate hike.
And if this is moderate,
we better not try strenuous.
This involved
quite a bit of rock
clambering.
Not exactly climbing,
like you see in fancy magazines.
You have to watch out
for the twist-your-ankle rock.
Because that's every rock.
It could be.
This is kind of tricky
where I am now, in fact.
But it's incredibly cool.
There is a devil's staircase
leading to the Devil's Hall.
And it really looks like
somebody carved a staircase
out of this rock.
But it's really just layers
of whatever this is.
It's darned cool looking.
And multicolored.
And textured and layered
as if by an incredible
abstract artist.
Or landscape artist.
Hence the name
Bob's Staircase
and Bob's Hall.
Where I don't want to end up going
is Bob's Hell.
Because that would be called
on the maps
the Devil's Hell.
And think if hell is bad for us.
Think how bad the Devil's Hell would be.
There's some nice craggy
mountaintops
around here.
And lots of stabby yucca
and cool trees.
The bark looks like
it's made of tile.
It really honestly does.
And the striata
in the rocks
is fantastic.
Well defined.
The colors are many
and varied.
So this is
Princess Wee and Reverend Stang
at Devil's Hall
Guadalupe Mountains National Monument
over and out.
Look at this.
I'm hauling butt
to Bob's Hall.
I feel like I'm in Bob's Hole.
Man.
That's Steve Jobs.
And his son.
I dared not get a picture of him
because somebody would probably kill me.
But Steve Jobs is supposed to be dead.
He died a few months ago.
And I'm certain
that that was Steve Jobs
who just walked by
with a teenage boy.
That was him.
It was.
The teenage boy is probably
like his ninja bodyguard.
Yeah.
I made it up here
on Cory's Spirits.
Greed.
Or Cory's
Sleed or Sneed.
I think it was Sneed actually.
It's amazing.
It's beautiful.
Okay.
Rocks.
Path.
Where's the path?
Sun going down.
Must find path.
Must not be caught in desert at night.
Where's path?
Oh there.
There.
We got out of the park
with one minute to spare.
These three park guys
were standing by the gate
waiting.
In fact, yeah, there they...
And there is a gate.
We would have been locked in
and we were literally like
one minute till closing time.
That is the kind of thing
I have to deal with
having a princessly wife
who has to take her longest possible
way to do anything.
And now we're going into the sun
but I honestly don't know
where we're going.
I don't know where we're going.
Somewhere in New Mexico.
From PR News in Washington,
I'm sounding the alarm
about the Republican borrowing limit.
All they would do was criticize.
Scotland Yard is opening
a new investigation
into possible crimes
by the Republican proposal
seeking to oust
Yemen's longtime president.
House Republicans are aiming
to reject it.
It's being reported
that a senior military official
was infected with a Trojan worm.
The budget struggle in Washington
is raising anxiety
among seven Afghan soldiers
and a translator.
There's now enough evidence
to move the investigation forward.
Circumstances are extraordinary.
I stuck my neck out a mile.
PR's David Wellner reports
Speaker John Boehner
has crashed and broken in two
while landing in Guyana.
Had four more done the same
it would have failed.
And on PR News,
I didn't even hear.
What's this talking about
unscrewing and...
I carry this thing all the time.
Pantiera gave it to me
about six years ago.
What is it?
Is it a special opener?
You go through the airport with it?
It's a...
It's my utility...
Oh, sorry.
Please, be careful there.
It's my utility belt.
It's just one little plastic
and metal or two-piece thing
that Reverend...
Pope S. Pantiera gave me
about six or seven years ago
when she was like eight years old.
And look at it.
It's got a magnifying glass,
a compass,
a laser.
It has a flashlight.
It had a little tiny screwdriver.
It's got a little bit of everything.
An opener, a saw.
And yet it doesn't unfold
like a Swiss army knife.
It's one piece of metal, basically,
with a few insets.
Well, the fewer parts...
And did she get through
the airport with it?
I don't know.
I have...
I've been avoiding airplanes
since Princess Marie retired.
Yeah, me too.
One avoids them
if it is possible.
Yeah.
It changed.
Is one of these bottles
of beverage for me?
Well, then let me
drink your health.
It's not every day
that we have both
Philo and Stang together.
Yeah, we haven't been
on the radio together
in years.
In the studio.
Hours.
That's right.
Actually, I come out here
every year.
Let's measure
every meaningful pulse.
That's true.
We haven't been on the radio
that we could say
bad words on in years.
Well, that's true
because we have to keep
a certain consistency up
with...
our friends at KPFA.
We don't want to harm
Puz Ev's show
by being our natural selves
scratching and belching and...
I can use almost all of this
on our slack
without cutting anything.
This is good for prime time,
mostly.
Yes, I know.
It's astonishing
what people will put up with,
isn't it?
I mean, what they'll listen to.
The worst tripe.
Oh, is this on?
Well, let's see.
How long have we been
doing this?
Power?
You mean doing this?
The first...
Okay.
Bob founded the Church
of the Subgenius
in 1953
after his immaculation.
He kept it pretty secret
until he told Philo
to go ahead
and hire somebody
to put the publicity together.
And we studied...
He and I both studied
the Masons
and the Rosicrucians
and other really popular ones.
Yes, there was Jackie Mason,
Mason Reese,
Marsha Mason.
But Eckhinkar,
and...
Right.
Scientology.
Yeah.
All those very...
The Mayans.
That was a little-known one
from...
Oh, you're out of your minds.
And we got ordained
in the Church
of Universal Life Church.
Oh, yes.
Of course.
Very important.
Now, when were you ordained?
What year was your ordainment?
I think mine was
around 1977 or 78.
Mine was in 69.
Wow.
And I've got the certificate.
I've got my certificate
in my pocket.
They sent me
a new certificate.
Well, Doug, my...
I had to prove it.
I married a couple in New York
and they...
The city
wanted to see proof of me
and they also wanted
15 bucks from me.
New York makes you do paperwork.
Yeah.
That's how they pay
for all those people
that are on their payroll.
No, on the other hand,
in rural New York State...
They've got checkers
checking checkers
and supervisors.
I'm married...
Supervisor, supervisor,
supervisor.
Pope S. Lilith
with Reverend Thea
and they were both
technically women,
although he had
a man's driver's license
at the time.
Why didn't he change
that particular detail?
Well, he was working on it.
But at the time,
Lil...
I see.
When they went to the court
to get their marriage certificate,
Lil's legal name had changed.
And...
And it said
Lilith Dawn...
Let's say Williams.
Williams.
Which it's not.
And they said,
why is your name Lilith?
They actually asked that of...
Lil.
Yes.
And Lil said,
my parents were hippies.
And the lady
in the little town,
you know,
called,
didn't blink,
and went,
oh, I get it.
Okay.
Throw it all over on your parents
when it's your own willfulness
that has made it.
That was one of the
ex-day weddings.
Jesus and Magdalene
were married there.
Where?
At ex-day.
Oh, yes, of course.
Nikki Death Chick
and Bob Wilde
were married there.
Truly, it has been a place
of coming together.
I'd like to marry somebody,
some people.
You could.
You haven't?
Not for more than
a short-duration marriage.
You know,
I've done those too,
of course,
at Chick and John's
at Las Vegas.
Especially in shorter...
In marriages of 20 minutes
or less.
But I'd like to ask you,
other guys
who have married people,
how many of your
couples have been married?
have stayed together?
And how many have divorced?
I'd say about half.
Same as the human average.
Well, so far,
all of mine
have stayed together.
But, of course,
I'm sure
someone will break
that record fairly soon.
I had a subgenius minister
marry me
in my last marriage.
And then I performed
some sort of marriage
at Burning Man
this year
when a couple
requested that I do it.
On the steps
of the Temple of Oblivion,
actually,
it turned out
to be a great place for him.
I'm not sure
what Reverend J. Kenny's
rank is in the...
In the Gnostic Church?
In the Gnostic Church.
But he's a high-ranking member
in several churches.
So we thought
it was extra special
to have him marry us.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, I guess so.
He really knows
what he's talking about.
When he wore
his highfalutin garb
and stuff, you know,
with arcane symbols
and things,
I thought,
yeah, my highfalutin garb
all looks like cheesy
leftover theatrical costumes,
which is exactly
what they are.
Well, that's all
just part of showbiz,
isn't it?
Right, exactly.
I mean, we have to look
at this legitimately,
realistically.
Religion is just showbiz.
Oh, I've been to
the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame.
All those costumes
look pathetic
up close in real life.
And they're tiny.
But they look great
under the lights.
You see, it's...
You're looking at a piece.
A piece of the illusion,
not the entire illusion.
Right.
Just a piece.
All those dead rock stars.
Their ghosts add glamour.
Do you want to be free
yet find that credit cards
are still tying you down?
Month after month,
payment after payment.
Do you wish that there was
some way to end this slavery
and save your family?
The cult has a solution
you've been waiting for.
Since seven,
we've been implementing
an advanced program
which legally ends
money and property.
This is a true process
that's helped
hundreds of Americans
all across the country
start living
and prepare
for an uncertain consultation.
To learn more,
give us a call today
at 777-RIGHT-NOW.
That clip was from
Reverend D. Cappell.
Apetitor.
Before that,
by the large.
some church history
from the Ask Dr. Howell Show
podcast on Radio Valencia.
See AskDrHowell.com
for more.
And before that,
PR news by
Reverend Cosmic Debris.
You're listening to
the Hour of Slack
from the Church of the Subgenius.
Everything you might want
to know about anything
can be found
at subgenius.com.
You might want to
actually examine
the buttons at the top
to avoid confusion.
Sometimes,
people ignore
those first prominent parts
then tell me
it's hard to navigate.
Coming up,
we'll have more
puzzling evidence.
Pardon me
if there's some
gag repetition
or reflex.
Clips by Ministry of Slack
and Decapitator.
Al's greatest rant.
But first,
we cut to
WCSB Cleveland's
Radio Synesthesia,
which I started recording
from the WCSB.org stream
just after
frequent caller
No Money Mark
pointed out
that Mitt Romney
in certain ways
bears an uncanny
resemblance
to our guru,
the high E-pop
J.R. Bob Dobbs.
Actually,
now that you mention it,
that really
scares me.
That really
Although,
I think that
the comparison
is not apt
because,
I mean,
Bob,
he's a
quintessential
salesman.
He gets
people to like him,
whereas,
if Mitt,
he can't sell himself
to anybody.
The only reason
that he can't
That's it.
He's the fake Bob.
He's the anti-Bob.
Anti-Bob.
Romney is the anti-Bob.
Big Romney
has no Bob in him.
I'd like to see
Oh my God,
that's uncanny.
I can't believe
I never noticed that before.
Does Bob Dobbs
know how to fight?
These really are
the end times.
Bob doesn't have to fight.
Yeah.
Bob just
What can he do?
You can't fight.
Bob.
No, but can Bob
Well, you can,
but, you know,
he'll be fine.
Yeah.
Even if you,
even if you kill him,
he'll just come back.
It's okay.
He can respond.
He's already done it
like dozens of times.
Yeah, like Dick Cheney.
You kill him
and he comes back.
You know, see,
Jesus only died
and came back once,
but Bob Dobbs,
people lost count
of that centuries ago.
Probably died
billions of times.
Anyway,
I just wanted
to make that point.
Keith,
hopefully I'll be
calling crap later.
Until then,
everybody have a good night.
And watch your phone.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Whoa.
Man, this is giving me,
this is going to give me
nightmares now.
It's really going to
give me nightmares.
Yeah.
That door's open.
You can't close it again.
That was the issue
with me and Bob.
They stopped finding time
for each other.
Bob sought sexual fulfillment
outside the marriage.
Dr. Bob.
I'll tell you something.
I like to,
I like to really
teach that bastard a lesson.
I happen to have
this new address.
Perhaps you and I
should sneak in there
one night and plant
a tiny explosive device
in the stove.
Make it look like
a gas leak.
Yeah, yeah.
Hello?
Sorry to interrupt
your recreation.
Hello?
Oh, I'm there.
Oh, you need to take
your doctors
and sleep with your medicine
and drink plenty
of bodily fluids.
Yes.
Bodily fluids?
That's what I had
to say.
Bodily fluids?
Bodily,
they come in little
boblets and the bottles
and the,
you gotta take them.
Who's volunteering?
Well, it's,
it's a group effort.
We all contribute.
We all do.
Put them in the cups,
the glasses,
put them around
like musical chairs.
Just try to make you
drink them without
making you do this
shit call over.
By the same token,
whenever they name
a spot in a national park
or a state park
after the devil,
they mean just the opposite
because those parts,
those areas,
usually look as if
they were carved
by angels.
Did you ever go
to the park?
They name them Devil's Waterhole or Devil's Toilet or Devil's Punchbowl because that scares the pinks away.
Yeah.
And only the cool people go.
Did you ever go to...
What it really means is Bob's Waterhole.
Right.
Bob's...
It really means cool place to go.
Bob, the Valley of Bob.
What about...
Have you ever been to the Devil's Wishbone?
I haven't seen your face.
No.
I've been to the...
I've wanted to go to the Devil's Pelvis, but that's so...
Did you ever see the Devil's Backbone?
Right.
From the Devil's...
No, I missed the Devil's Backbone.
I wanted to see it.
Because that's kind of south.
I've been to the Devil's Clavicle.
Have you been?
It's north of the Devil's Wishbone.
One time you did.
You pulled on the Devil's Wishbone.
The Devil's Skull is way up in Canada.
But the Devil's Mandible and the Devil's Atlas Vertebra.
I fell into the Devil's Nostril once.
After Nostril.
Those are always cool places.
And I don't know why they always call them...
They attribute them to the Devil, but I assume it was...
You know, he's a fallen angel.
Satan's scapula.
And these places named after the Devil always look as if they were carved by angels, not devils.
Not like that Satan's anus.
That was a bad place to go.
What about that photo?
That color photo that I have seen of you standing with the Devil in front of a big fire.
What about that picture?
That's from Last Starwood.
The Satan...
Actually, Thayton.
He has kind of a lisp.
The way he pronounces his own name.
Thayton appears almost every Starwood...
He was at X-Day this year.
Oh, he was?
Yeah, he played...
And in his human guise, he played guitar on stage with a bald head.
The nice one.
And the chum bag.
Not the obnoxious one.
Yes, I make my lumbago.
Yeah, that famous photo shows me, Thayton, an angel of light who looks similar to Potter Nostril.
And then there were the two babes.
Two beautiful babes.
One was kicked off.
One was kicked off the stage at X-Day for interfering with Fat Mandy's eye.
Why?
Two years ago.
Oh, is she the one who...
And the other one is Carissa Bragg, who's my favorite young singer in Cleveland because she's so pretty.
Was that one who jumped up on the stage naked?
Is that the one?
Yeah, that's the one that's in that same photo.
I didn't realize that when the photo was taken.
I didn't realize it either.
No, in that same collection, there's a nice photo of me with Oberon Zell, the head of our rival cult,
the Church of All Worlds.
Very good.
I'll file this under A for All Worlds.
I was on his podcast.
I was on the Church of All Worlds podcast.
Well, we hope you'll join us for one more world, the Ask Dr. Hal show on Radio Valencia.
I'm filing it in the X.
The Ask Dr. Hal?
I thought it was Ask Dr. Hal.
It is.
It's Ask.
Ask not what you can do for Dr. Hal.
Ask Dr. Hal.
Originally, we were a giant.
We had buttocks in the desert.
It's not Dr. Hal's buttocks.
But that was an early version that has passed away.
What happened to Princess Wee?
You mean it's not Axe Dr. Hal?
A what?
There's no tax on it.
It's not Axe Dr. Hal?
Oh, no.
It's an axe.
I think not.
No.
It's more like Occam's razor.
The finely buttocked one.
Oh, Occam's razor, Dr. Hal.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Wait.
Now you turn on Shaw Street.
I know.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
.1 miles.
Turn left.
It's Shaw Street.
I can't move to the next.
Oh, this is Steve's.
Look at the traffic cameras.
Where?
What?
I don't see traffic cameras.
Way, way up there.
You think that's funny?
Yeah.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
I think the whole world is laughing.
Well, that was funny.
I'm gonna go.
What's up?
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
You know, you keep...
You just have to go around the block.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Continue 200 feet.
I have pain in my belly from laughing now.
I'm not kidding.
You, you, you...
.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
.
I've had it with Bob
making phone calls
and then the movie
Now I see what the fuck's in front of me
and I don't pretend it's something else
I was fucking her
and now
I'm gonna fuck you
if you don't piss me off
or open your yap at the wrong fucking time
The only time you're supposed to open your yap
is so I can put my fucking prick in it
Otherwise you shut the fuck up
Now hold on to that
Point is
this minister's gonna fucking die
I mean that's the
that's the fucking point
He's gonna die sooner or later
I mean he's making a fucking jerk of himself
I mean well
what's the point
Why go on with that?
Who's gonna benefit from that, huh?
You just gotta
kill it and
put an end to it
You don't linger on about it
You don't fucking go around weeping about it
You don't behave like a kid with a sore fucking thumb
You know, a loco sucking it
My poor fucking thumb
I mean you gotta behave like a grown
fucking man
You gotta shut the fuck up
Don't be sorry
Don't look fucking back because
believe me no one gives a fuck
You understand?
Yeah
Shut the fuck up huh?
Give me that
Hey
You
suck my dick
and shut the fuck up, huh?
Come here
Come on
Now then, here
The place where I found you, huh?
That's where this warrants file
Could you believe?
Yeah?
that I may have stuck a knife in someone's guts 12 hours before you got on the wagon we headed out for fucking Laramie?
No, because I don't look fucking backwards.
I do what I have to do and go on.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
You got a stagecoach to catch or something, huh?
Friends, we're glad you listened to this show,
and we're even more glad that some listeners have donated enough to help us keep on going for another couple of months.
Not just this show, but subgenius.com and all the other archive sites.
But if you truly love Bob and want some of that slack back to rebound to you,
you should go to subgenius.com front page or especially the radio page or the catalog store pages
and help out financially as best you can.
Now, we know what it's like to be on the brink of total poverty,
and we don't want any subgeniuses to make their own stuff.
We want to make our situations worse.
But some of you still have jobs.
Even five bucks makes a big difference, even if it's only once a month from enough of you.
Fifty bucks makes an even bigger difference.
All we're saying is that blowjobs could go the way of Steve Jobs if you don't pay dogs.
We also take checks and money orders to subgeniusfoundation.com.
P-O-B-O-X.com.
181-417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
Thanks for anything you can do to help Let There Be Slack.