From here on out, it's up to you, Mac.
All right, Mac.
You got it?
Yeah.
Okay, now, it's coming at you, too.
Handle it gentle now.
All right.
I've got it.
Here.
All right.
One, two, four, three.
The subgenius.
Power of the subgenius.
I'll crawl in first.
Good, though.
Yeah.
Okay, now, let's get to work.
Here.
Here are the time bombs you rigged up.
Six grenades.
Yeah, that ought to do it.
Here we go.
We're walking overtime.
Ah, yes, praise the Fantastic Plastics who did that song over time.
If you ever get a chance to see them live, their show has great visuals.
Meanwhile, we're still at the 9th Megafist Temple Lodge in Stangsville, Texas,
not in the WCSB Cleveland studios, and I could do reruns and will later,
but when possible, we'd rather present recent call-ins to Radio Synesthesia.
And these particular show clips were recorded January and February 2016 with host Dr. Sinister.
No topic is too strange or abstruse.
And hello, you're on the air.
Oh, I was wondering if I was on the air yet.
Anyway, oh, I'm sorry. I don't talk like this right now.
Hey, how you doing, man?
Not too bad. How are you doing?
I'm dysfunctional.
I just put down.
I'm brought in by Curtis Lee Mayne, one of the seven generals in the seven generals in May.
I like, or I think it was General Walker who attacked it.
The U.S. Post, believing that he was going to save us from communism,
and he was the inspiration for Jaxie Ripper, General Ripper, and Dr. Strangely.
That's right. A real American.
Yep. Something we all aspire to, especially nowadays.
And there's so much division and complicated mathematics involved in something or another, I guess.
I don't know.
You know, and not to mention the fact that, you know, all of decorum has just gone out the window.
I mean, people actually fight in the war room now.
Oh, I heard there was a big builder-buyer meeting somewhere in Andorra or something like that.
And one of these secret Illuminati leaders of the world broke wind loudly as they passed the cafeteria window.
Well, that is...
I guess maybe it was just, you know, slumming or something.
No, it was a cafeteria here, but of course it was for the slaves, you know.
Well, crop dusting the slaves in the cafeteria is one of the initiation rituals.
I'm sorry, but that was a male prescription.
I could just see one of these windbags doing just exactly what you said.
Yeah, I may have a big target on my back for revealing that Masonic secret, but...
Well, I don't know.
Well, as long as you know the three fingers are the...
What is it again?
Something that's on a handshake or something, right?
There are a few secret handshakes I've learned over the years.
A few secret passwords, signs and countersigns.
Yeah.
Yeah, I remember a lot of those.
They take them away from you as soon as they...
Responsibly, of course, they take them away from you.
But they be giving to you.
Mm-hmm.
It's some new edict or something.
Some platform.
Mm-hmm.
Yep.
Hey, we got another caller here.
Let's see what this person has to say.
You're psychic, you know?
You're on the air.
Hi, Dr. Sinister.
Welcome to the program, Reverend Stang.
Yes, I.
Well, we were talking briefly about, you know, Illuminati initiation rituals and secret handshakes.
Yeah.
And we just, we kind of imagined this, a real top leader, you know, perhaps with a few bodyguards walking by.
And it's built by Vader Meadey somewhere in Slovenia or Arctic land.
You know, someplace way far out there.
And he breaks wind loudly as he passes the cafeteria window.
But there's, you know, the cafeteria, of course, wasn't for one of the most powerful men in the world.
But as you know, that's the secret of the secret masters.
Those rubber pants they were.
Well, actually, they're...
Well, yeah, that was a...
That was a great...
As a matter of fact.
I don't know.
I don't know where to buy rubber pants anymore.
We based our rubber pantsuits on some of the Illuminati lower echelon ones.
But I've forgotten all the secret handshakes.
Well, don't you need to use some of those handshakes to, like, unzip certain valves and things that look like, you know...
Well, I used to when I was a Bobby, when I first joined the cult.
I had to...
I actually had to stand behind Bob and unzip his pants and stuff like that for it.
Just to prove that I was faithful and loyal and trustworthy.
But I haven't had to do any of that stuff, you know, since I kind of rose up in ranks.
And nobody's heard from Bob.
And somebody had to, you know, countersign the checks.
You know, right?
Well, I thought that's when you and Bob and Connie got married.
Not got married.
What is it?
You cohabitated someplace near St. Louis.
No, I never...
I mean, you tried to divert the Mississippi with the power of your mind.
And you were arrested by the Oricon Police.
Police.
At least the flags are the ones we're talking about.
How do I...
We've got a new political party for subgeniuses.
To make Dobstown great again.
And I think both of you guys will get behind it.
Just because of the name.
The Loudly Complaining Party.
I could get behind that.
Although, I do have some...
What about...
It'd be like...
It would be like all political stupidity rolled up into one huge clique of whining assholes.
Whatever happened to the...
And the whole point of it is...
My one-cent solitary complaint...
Why?
It can be quoted easily.
...express your anger.
And that's all.
That's it.
That's the whole point of the Loudly Complaining Party.
Whatever happened to the...
Just to show people how mad you really are.
Whatever happened to the Patriot Psychotic Anarcho-Materialist Party?
That didn't feel as good.
That was a little too sensible.
I see.
A little too, you know, gender-specific.
Gender-specific?
It was probably the most general.
Patriot Psychotic Anarcho-Materialism encompassed almost all extremism and middle-of-the-road.
As long as you left us alone.
That was the problem.
But the prattling prey bobs of positivity had to go and sweeten it up and make it nice.
So I'm just saying...
Just cut all the...
Just cut all the crap.
It's the Loudly Complaining Party.
That's what we do.
We're always going to do.
Whenever there's work to be done in government, we will simply loudly complain.
And I bet you we get re-elected because that's what everybody wants is to loudly complain.
The louder the louder.
You need to release all these pent-up emotions that are created by government and capitalist lobbies and compliments.
You know, the over-the-hill handshake, the old under-the-sideways-button-removal technique.
Yeah, the under-the-arms sniffle.
Yeah, yeah.
So these guys have been at it for a long time.
I'm sorry.
I got tired of going to those meetings.
Of course.
I'm just, you know, I've quit hanging out with the secret rulers and Bob's friends.
I just can't handle it.
I'm not cut out for that.
I don't have the right haircut.
Right here?
They laughed at me.
Nobody has.
You know, they pranked me and made fun of me.
It's like, well, okay, if you don't want to subgenius sacred scribe around, I'll just come to these parties.
So I did.
I guess they didn't want to subgenius sacred scribe around.
Well.
Well, maybe it was like cursive writing in the old days.
They didn't really want...
Actually, I really do have a bad cold.
I'm probably not going to want to stay on for long, guys.
You don't have a sump pump now that you're taking care of?
Yeah.
I called you up in order so that everyone hearing the sound of my voice now will get the cold I have.
I did this a couple of years ago.
It was so contagious that just over the radio waves, people caught the cold.
Well, Charles...
Believe it.
You don't want it.
You do not want this particular winter cold.
This is infectious radio here.
Yeah.
And I'm just a...
Like this one kid said to me in Fort Worth when I was 10 years old.
Well, heck, Smith, you're just a bucket of snot.
And I quote.
That was...
They called me Smith then.
Snot bucket.
Bucket Smith.
Yeah.
So, snot bucket Smith.
It was accurate.
And it is accurate again.
If I could find that guy now, I'd say,
Sir, Sirah, you were right.
Standing there as a crossing guard in sixth grade, fathers in fifth grade, you were right.
I was a bucket of snot.
And you will too, B1, for just being this near to me so I could say that.
Gotta spread the love, man.
My favorite part about getting sick is spreading the disease to others.
Me too.
I love that.
Well, I've been pretty nice.
I mean, all I did was get on one radio show that would spread it to.
And it's a college station without a really huge reach.
So, unless we put it on the internet or something.
Oh, that's right.
The internet.
Oh, man.
People in Germany are going to be getting sick.
Oh, yeah.
It just sucks me from having kind of a tubercular nature.
That's why I just expel some earth there during that cough.
You said you have a tubercular nature?
Yeah.
Don't we all in some way or another?
Consumptive.
We really think about it.
Doesn't it all make sense now?
You sound like you're sounding better than normal.
Yeah.
I've laid healing down.
power on you. It's not in my
hands, it's in my feet,
but it works at great distances
and I can point
it pretty much like a turret of a gun,
like a whip around on one of them
and Humvees and stuff like that.
I've gotten quite good at it
on my hand. You know what's funny? Today I saw a train
with a whole bunch of
Humvees on it.
One of the train
cars was stacked with
like two layers high
of Humvees.
I just wonder if it made you think twice
or if you noticed it
and it was like out of the ordinary.
Well,
most things make me think more than twice.
Think what?
More than twice.
Thrice even.
I've certainly
think things multiple times.
I sort of know what you mean. There's times
when I'll think of something and then later on
I'll think about it again and I'll think about it
some more and then I start
getting really confused.
And I go back to the story.
Now I know what you're talking about.
That was so much simpler. That first thought I had.
I'll just ignore all those complications
that I layered onto it.
I'll stick with that first simple thought.
Simple thoughts.
Which I think was along the lines of
I think I'll have a beer now.
Something like that.
You think twice about it
and you go, no, I shouldn't have a beer.
Then you think again and go, but wait, why not?
Then, you know,
it snowballs.
The next thing you know, you're drinking the beer anyway.
So why not just
go back to go and
as Bob said,
too much is always better than not enough.
It's not true.
It sounds so great.
I think you're inferring that
thought is a form of sickness.
Bob taught that
it is. That in fact,
if you can break thinking and break
your habit of thinking and simply
react instantly.
But pure
instinct.
Surfing the luck plane entirely.
You may end up in jail,
but you'll be more like Bob.
I don't know if that's good.
Try it and find out.
Kids, go ahead.
I remember when he was 11.
It says on everybody's subgenius minister
card that the church is not
responsible for his or her actions.
That's right.
Point there.
That's my way of
my raison d'etre as well.
Rationality and then
uh,
I don't know. Hey, how do you guys like my new
phone? I got a brand new phone.
I mean really new. I got
it Friday.
I haven't dropped it in the toilet once
yet. Sounds alright.
I can't hear you guys
any better than normal even with it on
speakerphone and with it.
I'm plastered against my one good ear,
but I would think you could probably
hear me better.
You sound okay.
I noticed that as I get older,
I have to look down much further when I
watch myself make peepee monsters and stuff.
And I was my glasses always fall in the
toilet.
As I look down.
I'm surprised,
Gabe, with a nose like yours,
I'm you'd have to be bending over pretty
far for me to get over that hump.
That's what I was trying to say.
Hey, there's a kind of a crook,
a hump thing, kind of a dick.
Dave, for the radio listeners who don't have
vibraphones, Dave has kind of a Dick Tracy like
nose.
He looks kind of like if Dick Tracy was an
Indian and and balding.
Hmm.
Remember about always.
It's important to know.
Never saw that until you mentioned it.
Were they tonight on what?
Whereas I look more like the Dick Tracy
character, prune face.
Good old prune face.
Doesn't wear a beard so you can't tell.
So it doesn't look that bad.
There's also a slight demonic thing going on there.
How would you put it?
Um, demonic thing too going on.
Demonic mnemonic.
Demonic mnemonics.
Oh yeah, man.
That's that's subject well worth exploring.
Demonic mnemonics.
Hell has a long memory.
Discuss what?
OK, if there was a doctor, if there was a
radio synesthesia movie, a big budget movie
directed by, say, the Coen brothers who would
play Doctor Sinister?
I don't know.
Um, I mean, ideally Johnny Depp, but he's too
short.
If if if Ivan Stang was right, if if if I was
going to be a character and then of course
Johnny Depp would have to play.
Seymour Interrelated with Michael Gibson
I've made from the movie.
Okras as a textbook
genealogy.
He's young man but rather than
George 이것
cled in P shit as in Bill
よو
now
Nothing.
I could play myself.
Yeah, yeah, that would be the best way to go.
I don't know.
No, no, that never works.
I don't think any famous actors really look that much like me.
Let's take another caller here, though.
216-687-3515.
I knew he was going to change the subject.
I knew that he would change the subject.
That was why I did that.
Hello, you're on the air.
Dr. Sandberg?
I've heard that Sinister has a slightly, you know, potterish...
I'm Edwin Brody.
Edwin Brody as Dr. Sinister.
That's it.
Dr. Sinister.
What's up, skeptic?
This is the management.
The management.
I'm the management.
Robert Anton Wilson has come back from the grave?
He used to post as, well, the MGP,
which people assumed was the management,
but it really meant the midget.
No, no, I'm the management.
I'm the management of the show, actually.
I'm calling in to let you know that
I've been speaking with the consultants.
It's okay if you're a midget.
No, he's my manager.
That's right.
He's like my agent, you know.
It's a new year,
and there's going to be some cuts
because that's what consultants do.
And I don't know if they've told you,
but they're cutting some of the phone lines,
you know, from four to three,
and maybe three to two.
Going to have to have some lean times here.
You know, we need synesthesia to go lean this year.
Well, I've been going...
I've been pretty lean on the callers
for more than a year now.
I know.
Does that mean I get to hang up now?
We need to bring those callers back in.
We need to stop the lameness.
We need good entertainment
for the airwaves, the CSB,
and all the listeners of Cleveland State, right?
That's true.
That is certainly true.
Right.
We need management with energy.
If only we could be louder and funnier or something.
We need change.
So, how are we going to change it around this year?
We need big, bold ideas.
Bold ideas.
Okay.
Right, Chief?
I mean, sure.
Big, bold ideas, huh?
Oh, you're...
Old Christmas balls.
Don't be afraid.
We need big ideas and...
Different, fuzz and different.
That's what we need.
Indifference and fuzz.
Yeah, you see, when people call in,
they want to hear more.
They want to hear more than indifference.
They want to hear alacrity, alarm.
They want to hear...
Subversion.
They want to hear people crying out in the wilderness.
Or they just want to talk about being drunk.
That's just so much to a lot of people.
Falling asleep right now.
I need some bigger, better ideas.
Well, let's make use of the four phone lines while we have them all.
Hello, you're on the air.
Hello.
Welcome to the program, Mark.
Yeah, good to talk to the subgeni again.
I'm not on the air anymore.
Reverend Spade,
okay, first, I was very moved by the...
your father's, you know, elegy
that I heard on the previous program.
That was...
He really did a great job of...
writing up his...
something to read upon his own death.
Yeah, I can see where you got your sense of humor
besides the Fireside Theater, of course.
Huh?
I said...
I can see that you got a lot of your sense of humor from your father.
And of course, you know, the other half from the Fireside Theater.
Yeah, two totally separate sources, believe me.
Mm-hmm.
I don't think he ever heard of the Fireside Theater.
And to tell the truth, although my father was a dues-paying subgenius
and proudly displayed his excuse and doctorate on the walls of the house here,
I don't think he ever once listened to the hour of slack.
Huh.
Not once.
My mom did a few times, although it was a bit disgruntling.
Mm-hmm.
I have a niece.
Out of everybody in my huge clan,
I have a niece who appreciates the hour of slack
and radio synesthesia.
She might even be listening right now.
Well, we all appreciate you having a niece for crying out loud.
He's got these body punches.
Well, I guess we're not...
We're so thankful for it.
Did anybody even listen to this boring, terrible radio?
It's just...
You're so charitable and kind.
Well, it's just because I have both my fingers in both my ears
and in my nose as well and stuff
that I'm not exactly understanding what you're saying.
I'm falling asleep.
Wake up, wake up.
Come on, come on, snap out of it.
I did have a question for you, Reverend.
As a Texan, what do you think of Ted Cruz?
Ted Cruz?
Well, I'm not really one to ask
because I'm not really a Texan.
I wasn't born here.
I only grew up in Texas from the age of 5 to 40-something.
And then I became a nice old Ohioan.
But like most Texans,
I think Ted Cruz is something out of a Stephen King novel.
But so are...
All of his competitors.
So, you know, it's nothing new.
Let me put it that way.
It's certainly nothing new.
I think most Texans are intelligent, educated people,
but they're all in hiding.
They've mostly been in hiding
because the other half of the Texans are so unbelievably violent.
Jesus.
I'll say one good thing about Ted Cruz.
He has the integrity to tell one of those dreamer kids,
yes, I will...
I would try and have you deported.
Said it right to her face on camera.
Ted Cruz is not stupid.
What does he mean?
He's capitalizing on his Hispanic heritage,
but he's really born in Canada
and he wants to deport everybody tomorrow or something?
Oh, what's even worse,
I heard he actually likes Nickelback.
This is what I'm talking about.
This is a big idea.
A presidential candidate who likes Nickelback.
I like Ted Cruz,
and as I'm getting older,
I'm really seeing the point.
Of his policies,
I really think it'll make America great again.
Well, they play all kinds of...
I think they'll make America great again.
...metal and rough metal
and everything in these right-wing stations.
Now, they're trying to activate a segment of the population
that might believe everything.
Let's move it right.
Hey, we want to be fair and balanced here.
Make America great.
No, we don't want to be fair and balanced.
We just want to go slightly right.
Well, see, that's difficult to understand.
Most of those people...
People have already had prefrontal lobotomies,
you know, throughout their entire careers.
They, like, chip out little tiny teeny-teeny pieces
one at a time until finally
the whole article is channeled into the speech.
If America goes any further right,
we're going to go right over the cliff.
Yeah.
That's...
Yeah, that's...
You know, I heard the leader
of the white supremacist organization
that inspired the shooter in South Carolina
is actively campaigning for Trump.
Huh.
Wow.
That is not good.
Geez, they won't get to shoot people anymore
than they just did in every location
where he was.
Great, Donald Trump.
That doesn't mean he subscribes to the beliefs
of all of his supporters.
Not that he would deny any of those beliefs.
He speaks at a fourth-grade level also,
according to a new analysis by the Boston Globe.
The gay people came out of the closet.
Finally, dumb people are coming out of the closet.
It's...
It's time.
The stupid people came out and said,
I'm damn proud to be stupid.
Being smart just gets you killed quicker.
And I'm...
I'm okay with being stupid.
And I'm proud of it.
And I don't trust them smarty pants.
Dare to be stupid.
Because I don't understand them.
And I'm proud of that, too.
And, uh...
And it works, you know.
That's going to...
Thanks to the internet.
Yeah, I...
I had to say one more thing about them
and then I'll let you go.
Um...
Okay, uh...
He...
Uh, yeah.
He was, uh...
At some campaign event
and he was talking about, like,
other candidates lying about him.
And, you know,
I have a young daughter.
Whenever she tells a lie,
she gets a spanking.
Um...
My two comments about that are,
one, that's another reason for me
to despise the guy
because I'm really against
corporal punishment.
And, two,
if Ted Cruz got a spanking
every time he told a lie,
he'd have to be hospitalized.
That would be a good thing, I think.
I think he should be spanking
right across the forehead right now.
with a delicate feather, of course,
so I don't sound like I belong
in the, uh...
in the salt mines.
Okay, um...
At the end of the gravy train
right where the Petri types live.
Okay, I want to type the phone line
so I'll let another caller, uh,
have a chance to come in.
Uh, talk to you guys later.
Happy New Year.
Thank you, Mark.
The selfless and moneyless
enough money, Mark.
Dr. Sinister, I've got a great idea.
All right.
What if we have a synesthesia parade?
A synesthesia what?
Parade.
A parade?
Right down your favorite avenue
in the greater Cleveland area,
you can...
Not a really hot-looking
major red, some stuff like that?
Parade.
And you can finally get
the notice that you are deserving of.
Everybody loves a parade,
except for the people
who would be using that street
ordinarily at the time
that the parade is taking place.
Well, you know...
Hundreds of poor mom-and-pop stores
have had to forward a meal
and have to serve them.
Again, because of the synesthesia,
Dr. Sinister parade.
Yeah.
So skeptic.
Who should play Dr. Sinister
in the synesthesia movie?
No money, Mark.
It's really irrelevant at this point
because I'm not doing my job
as your management
unless we take this global.
We have to expand.
We have to have progress.
We have to have...
Content floss.
Really push forward.
Okay.
It's international.
Content floss as Dr. Sinister.
Content floss?
Is it...
Content floss as Dr. Sinister?
When are you going to book
your first huge guest?
I mean, just huge guest.
You got to get him out.
Or her.
Or it.
I don't know.
You got to get somebody big.
Somebody really big, huh?
I mean, huge.
Huge.
Why don't you see
if you can get Governor Kasich
with his rampant neofascist ideas
to come on and defend himself
about all of this?
Sometimes he done lied
to all the people
of the great state,
of the Buckeye State,
on the Great Lake of Ohio.
I...
I don't know.
I just, you know...
That would be a great pick.
That would be...
That would be funny
if we got the governor up here,
but I seriously doubt
that's going to happen.
Can you get Lenny Kilmeister
on this week?
Can I get what?
Lenny Kilmeister.
I heard he's doing big things.
He's...
He's not available
for interviews.
That's just...
Just call his agent.
Well, yeah,
you don't know that.
A little persistence
pays off here, okay?
I heard he was
in a mental institution.
There'd be no way
you could get in touch with him
unless you're family
or something.
Well, maybe...
Okay, maybe I had
the wrong information.
It's happened before.
I'm sorry.
Well, it's...
The next best thing here...
Hello, rubber city.
It's very popular now, isn't it?
Motionable.
This is Lenny from Motorhead,
which serves you right anyway.
And you're in Cleveland,
You're listening to WCSB,
which serves us all right.
Anyway.
So there we go.
There's you.
I knew you could do it.
This is why I'm getting
a big bonus this year.
I've been working
for Optimist Prime Consulting
for a long time,
and I knew it would come through.
This is...
This is a big bonus area.
I knew I could...
More than meets the eye.
Within a...
Marvin meets the eye.
I think that sounds like a name
for a really cool woman.
Marvin meets the eye.
No, no.
You're talking about his boss,
Optimist Prime.
I'm talking about my bobs, too,
and there's plenty of them
leading them this side of the screen
if you're so out of it.
Well, this is not Dixon
or some kind of, you know,
semantics class or something.
They have to shoot
when the rain is clear
and blow smoke
or anything else you can find.
You know,
once upon a time,
blowing smoke up someone's butt
actually was a form
of medical treatment.
No, it wasn't.
And we probably not talk about that.
No, that's true.
That's taboo.
That's...
See, there you go
for as far as, you know,
your needs of having
a better show or whatever.
They used to think
it would revive someone
if they had just...
If they had just drowned.
Well, if it was black smoke,
it was no.
If it was white smoke,
it meant a new pope.
A black smoke
indicates a new poop.
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
I'm a child.
I'm a real child.
Hey, you know,
the pope poops in the woods.
Just like the bear
in the necklace
and the holy motel mount.
You remember,
I think it was a bear
would whiz in the water
or something
and then it would drink the beer.
And that was like
their theocracy
or something
and their religion.
Bear whiz beer.
But like everybody else,
they all had the...
Why is it yellow?
By a well-armed militia
passing itself off
as a local Gestapo unit.
Yep.
I'm sorry.
Can we get
Crispin Glover on the air?
I don't think so.
There you go.
Crispin Glover
as Dr. Sinister.
That's perfect.
I don't think that'd work.
Crispin Glover
would make the perfect
Dr. Sinister.
He was born to play
I don't think so.
Why?
I don't think that would work at all.
Because he was not born
of humankind.
He's tall.
He's skinny.
I'm not skinny.
But, you know,
slowly going to pot.
Yeah.
So...
Dr. Sinister's not pink.
What the hell are you?
Yeah.
And he's aging.
Crispin Glover
would be perfect.
He's too old.
He's still efficient.
I mean,
just think of the mileage
you can get out
of having somebody else
play yourself.
You wouldn't have to go places
and just think
if he's cold for you.
He's probably only about
50 or so.
Yeah, that's a lot older than me.
He's only about five or six.
Yeah, about five.
Okay, okay.
We're getting close.
Can we get
Sweetass Sassafras
on the airwaves?
You'll have to contact
Sweetass for that.
I, you know,
maybe you can reach out
to his booking agent
and we can make
something happen.
Maybe like a
two-for-one deal.
I actually...
We've got to get
outside the box here.
You know,
we've got to start
generating some interest.
He actually made
a guest appearance
a couple years ago.
I think the only way
to do this
is to regenerate interest
and combine all the
ideas expressed tonight
and perhaps launch
their counter
as a candidate
of us to keep
complaining
as long as possible
with Fan Party.
Yeah,
the loudly complaining
party.
Well, I...
...or nominated, perhaps?
Well, I belong to the...
I belong to the
Nuclear Apocalypse Party.
Nuclear Populist?
Nuclear Apocalypse.
should have one, right?
I said, you know,
my one...
the one plank
in my presidential platform
is the promise
of nuclear annihilation
for all.
The Green Apocalypse?
That sounds
pretty PC.
The Green Apocalypse?
No, I said nuclear.
We went into things
again.
There was the past...
Anyway,
speaking of...
speaking of apocalypse,
you have been warned.
Give us a call here,
216-
now, if you're from
the SDS,
15.
You can talk about anything.
And what is the current time?
What is the current time,
I was wondering?
So...
1134.
I get scared.
You're living in the past,
Stang.
1034, God.
I get it.
If it was 1492
all over again,
he'd be one of the first
barbarians to conquer.
I mean,
we'd have to...
There's the same
belief systems
and everything involved there.
Senator,
can you give away
a new snowmobile?
Yeah.
I could give away
a whole fleet
of new snowmobiles.
I think that if you had
enough interest,
we could have, like,
a sweepstakes going on
of some sort,
and the person
who comes up
with the best idea
to promote the show
for this year
would win a snowmobile ride
to co-host
the show with you.
What do you think about this?
That sounds like
a great idea for a contest.
You see?
You gotta think outside the box.
You gotta be a problem solver.
You gotta have ideas.
How are you gonna...
Doesn't it matter
if there's not good ideas?
I mean,
we all have, like,
Stan was saying earlier,
that ideas are like snowballs
that just keep rolling downhill
and getting fatter and fatter
until they can't move anymore.
Wouldn't that be
a similar situation
if we had too many ideas?
No, they really have to do
a lot of thinking
first off.
Man,
if I think too much,
the place will start burning.
Yeah.
Well,
you can feel that stuff, man.
It's like smoke's
coming out of your ears.
Maybe in North Korea,
because didn't they just have
a big test over there
of some sort?
They're getting really excited
about synesthesia, right?
That's what that whole test
was about?
Yeah.
Yeah, as a matter of fact,
Kim Jong-un and I
are good buddies.
Right.
I mean, you can get him
to explain, perhaps,
the nuclear program there
and some of the civil rights issues
or human rights issues
they have and everything.
You'd be made for life
and you'd all be your, like,
worshipers and stuff.
You'd stop worshiping Stan
and you'd start worshiping you.
We'd put you on a pedestal
just like we put him on one.
And then we'd start
making fun of you.
No, I wouldn't actually
allow myself to be put
on a pedestal.
I would put a decoy
on the pedestal.
Yeah.
Well, maybe we could all copy,
you know, the haircut
of Kim Jong-un.
I mean, it's a pretty
good-looking cut, you know.
It's fashionable.
It's very fashionable
in North Korea.
In fact, I think it's the only
haircut allowed by law.
That's what I'm saying.
Maybe you could, you know,
sport a new look yourself
and kind of come in
and change it up
and maybe make your guests
wear the same haircut.
Have, like, a parody thing
going on.
I don't know.
Yeah.
There goes the other button.
Yep.
I guess they know
the strike zone right now,
so if you guys want to,
you know, you can duck
under the console there.
I don't know if it's going to help.
Duck and cover.
I really like to come up
with something here
for the new year.
I'm looking forward
to lots of laughs
and lots of drive-by callers.
You have come to the wrong place,
my friend.
But there was a time
in this glory day.
There was a time.
I remember that time.
And you know,
I don't want to talk.
Callers, you know,
They would come in
and do their shtick
and, you know,
Bernie would do
a drive-by call
and stun the world
with what he was saying.
And then,
just as soon as he came in,
he'd disappear.
And I said,
who is this guy?
Who is this guy
running this show
who's got all these
great callers calling in
and just keeping everybody
on the edge of their seat?
What's going to happen next?
No, this show
has really devolved.
This is all about
de-evolution.
Well, you know,
the stock market
went through a recession
or a depression
in the 30s,
but it bounced back.
And now,
look,
things are doing great.
So, take that,
that,
you know,
you go down
for a little dip
and then you come
right back up
and you're stronger
than ever.
And you give it
that good old
college try.
That good old
college dropout try.
Well, you know,
there are many
dropouts who have
succeeded in life.
Mm-hmm.
Cliche,
but Bill Gates
is a dropout.
That's right.
I was.
You see?
There are success
stories out there.
We can make this happen
for Sinister 2016.
Synesthesia,
super great.
We got big plans.
Big plans.
So, what you're saying
is every much as...
Huge plans.
Huge.
It's going to be great.
Well, there you go.
Huge plans.
So, we...
Yep, we are going to spend
more time than ever
this year talking about
all the people
who used to call in.
Oh, yeah.
Yuppie.
You have massive
lesions on the brain,
a congenital
dysflexion,
and then something like...
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, but that guy,
he disappeared quickly
after causing
all kinds of havoc.
Don't you remember?
Oh, yeah.
I miss Master Sean.
Well, it's Master Sean now.
Well, masturbating Sean.
He'd always ask us
to play sex music.
That's what he's
about, right?
Actually, Princess,
we and I owe
a lot.
We owe a great debt
to masturbating Sean.
When he would call
in saying,
oh, yeah,
all the time.
Some said,
well, he's masturbating.
But we said,
no, it's a mantra.
He's reciting his mantra.
He's an ascended master.
And we started...
Yeah, he wasn't saying,
oh, yeah.
He was saying,
oh, yeah, come on.
Whenever we were
in a stressful situation,
we'd start going,
oh, yeah,
oh, yeah.
And it worked.
It was a great mantra.
There's a kind of
language
based on the
oh, yeah mantra
of the great
masturbating Sean.
I can't prove it
or illustrate it,
but it is a language
and it does exist.
See, in all this time,
I thought it was just
some kind of like
a pigeon Spanish.
Can I make a really big
idea presentation?
I'm going to have to
get off the phone
because my cold
has caused me
to need to get off the phone.
All right.
I'm going to say,
goodbye.
Well, thank you for your call.
Thank you for everything.
I appreciate all the things
you've all done for me.
Yes.
Thanks for your reference.
All the little people
have been so,
and so,
and I must
slowly fade away
and say goodbye
and finally.
And hello,
you're on the air.
I think we should take over
some public land.
Yes.
Let's take over
some public land
that we can't take care of.
Let's take over
Yeah.
We're toy guns,
so they're shooters.
Seriously.
Yeah.
You can only,
you can only,
you can only get away
with that if you're white
in this country.
Well, we could pretend
we weren't,
and they could pretend
to kill us,
but it would still be
the same thing,
only different.
If they,
if they even had
a slight suntan,
they'd be labeled terrorists.
And they would have been
shot dead without
any kind of trial
or anything.
Have any of you gentlemen
ever heard of the white train?
The white train?
No.
By the way,
I am against
the kinds of racial disparities
we have in our justice system.
No, it's not.
It actually was a train
and all the cars
were painted white
because it carried
nuclear,
you know,
nuclear weapons.
Nuclear stuff.
Weapons.
Probably the best way
to put it.
Nuclear weapons
or just nuclear materials?
Nuclear weapons.
Nice.
Which they stored out
in,
around Warren, Ohio.
Ooh.
Ah, Warren, Ohio.
That's Princess
We Are Doe's hometown.
Warren, Ohio, man.
We'll have news.
Well, there's an airport
that's big.
There's an airport
nearby, too, there.
Howland Air Force Base,
which is,
it's a lot of weird
howls.
You know, it's funny.
I've been through Howland
and I didn't know
there was an Air Force Base there.
If the FBI stops you,
that'll mean
they're trampling our freight.
I knew about Wright-Patt,
but I didn't know
about Howland.
It sounds like
he's losing his marbles.
I lost my marbles
years ago.
I have no idea
where they are.
I used to play marbles
all the time as a kid
and then the other day
I was going through my stuff
and I couldn't find
my marbles anywhere
that were lost.
Let's incite Warren.
Get the nukes.
Then go to the Grand Canyon.
Take over that
wildlife refuge.
And we can do it, man.
You know, I think maybe...
We can get away
with anything, basically.
You know, we could just...
We could just turn Warren...
We could just turn Warren
into a wildlife refuge
and nobody would know
the difference.
I'm joking.
It would be an improvement.
You know, I jest.
I jest.
Actually, I have some
Warren roots myself.
Some Warren G. Harding roots,
whatever the hell that means.
The war on God.
That's my roots.
Yeah, Warren.
Warren against everybody.
Warren the other Americans.
Warren, Warren.
Why not?
Let's go for it.
Yeah, why not Warren?
We can do anything.
Yeah, and why not Warren?
Warren.
We're going to go
with these powers down there.
We should go in
and abrupt them
and, you know...
Oh, well.
God, I missed something
and it goes on well.
Here's where we're going
to take a second here
to remember
all those people
who used to call in.
Buda, you still there?
Stang, you still there?
I'm still here.
Dave, you still there?
Buda's still here.
All right.
I think Stang got lost.
Stang got lost.
Well, not all who wander
are lost.
Oh, you said not, huh?
Yeah.
But yeah, it was just...
What were we talking about?
And right now,
you are on the air.
Why, Dr. Sinister,
you picked me up first
for the first time ever.
That's because you, uh,
you don't first come
for a serve, as they say.
So, welcome to the program.
Reverend Stang,
welcome to the program.
So, what's new in your world?
Well, I'm already
in the end
to the television thing.
Remember last time
I talked to you,
I was afraid
I was turning normal.
Guess I've started
watching television.
What, regular television commercials?
Mm.
Oh, yes.
I already got burned out on it.
My favorite commercial
was the one for the drug.
Now, this is great.
This is how great
pharmaceutical technology
has gotten, all right?
If you are all strung out on heroin
or strung out on Oxycontin,
or you're addicted to opiate painkillers,
right now the pharmaceutical industry
has a pill for you.
All right.
You can keep on taking your opiates,
and you don't have to worry about
getting constipated from them.
But, you know, I'm not going to be constipated from them.
Because now,
now there's a pill you can take
that will relieve your opiate-induced constipation.
So you can be a junkie and still poop.
It is possible.
I was just very disappointed that they,
I was just very disappointed that the commercial
didn't include the poop emoji.
...painting in blue
with the squishy, squeezy blue paint on.
Why are they,
why are they not using the poop emoji
in these commercials?
That's what I want to know.
I mean, how awesome is it that there's an emoji,
there's an emoji just for poop?
Brown paint people would throw up,
but the blue gets the idea across,
because it's really squeezing out fast.
Hey, I started this show off with,
with a whole bunch of poop songs.
Yeah, this is, this is our thing here.
This is, it's a great time to poop.
There's never been a better time to poop than right now.
Hello, you're on the air.
Good news for people with credit problems.
Welcome, No Money Mark.
If anybody knows about credit problems, it's you.
Yeah, well, let's not get into that tonight.
But I'm not sure I,
I have a topic this week.
I remember hearing about a rapper who is a flat earther.
The flat earthers are still a thing.
No topic, Mark.
No topic, Mark, yes.
How you doing, Reverend?
Great.
I just, it's good to finally hear some drops
from Bob's Burgers on your show.
What would that be?
Well, I mean, you know,
I mean, you know, some stuff from,
from the Fox News animated sitcom,
which has a main character named Bob,
which was, I was wondering why I'd never heard anything
from that show on the subgenius hour before,
and tonight I did.
What was it that you heard tonight?
Somebody else sent it in.
I have no idea where those clips come from.
Isn't that the same show they played last week?
Yes, because we have not been receiving,
I'm not saying you didn't send them,
but we have not been receiving the,
the new hours of slack that have been sent in.
Or they're not being put in the special,
the special box.
I do not know what the situation is.
Well, listeners to Synesthesia would have heard
this week's hour of slack last week on your show anyway.
So it's a moot point in Cleveland.
That's right.
It was a pretty good show though.
But yeah, I don't, I actually,
I think that the collages that No Money Mark is talking about
came from some other artiste,
I think Cool Hand Chris,
and I wouldn't recognize,
and I wouldn't recognize clips from TV shows.
In fact, there have been times when I've been really embarrassed
because I used lines that I thought a subgenius had come up with.
And I only thought that because I was so ignorant of pop culture television.
You know, it'd be like a famous TV ad line.
And I wouldn't know any better.
I think it was original and treat it that way.
Well, maybe it was like the case of,
like the case of Newton and Leibniz,
both inventing calculus independently of each other at the same time.
Right, except that Leibniz was ready to share the honor
and Newton was paranoid.
Right.
Well, you know, he was hoping he might be able to use it
to finally turn lead into gold.
Never got around to it though.
Isn't it funny how the super geniuses of all ages are also the craziest?
Well, you know, the whole idea of alchemy and transmutation,
of one metallic element into another,
that was a very ancient idea.
And little did he know that all it takes is a nuclear reaction to turn lead into gold.
And for the price of three tons of gold,
you could turn one ton of lead into one ton of gold, maybe.
I don't know.
Not cost effective exactly, but it could be done.
Well, it's funny that this guy who's sort of almost intuitive,
who's intuitive the mathematical patterns inherent in gravity,
for instance, among other things, life as well,
also was convinced that the world was going to end at a certain year
because he had calculated all the numbers in the Bible.
Gosh, it sounds like somebody else I know.
The smartest guy in the world in the year 1700
believed that the Bible was literally correct all the way through,
and that was it.
Guy who gets clues from religion about when the world is going to end.
Boy, that sounds like somebody else I know.
Well, and I also invented the calculus,
but I didn't know that somebody else had already done it,
so it was kind of a waste of time.
I didn't even bother to take credit.
I felt embarrassed that I didn't know that it already existed.
Darn. Beat out once again.
I know my calculus.
Every time I could come up with a really good original gag,
Futurama would use it, but that week.
That's just they were reading my mind, which I know they weren't.
But it was a good sign.
Well, you know, some jokes just write themselves.
Some jokes just write themselves.
Yeah, some presidential campaigns just write themselves.
Speaking of which, did anyone watch the debate Saturday night?
I saw a little bit of it, actually.
I lost interest in that, too.
Well, that was, you know, I don't have cable,
so if it's actually on one of the broadcast networks,
then, like, that's all I'm going to get to see.
Yeah, right. I was just saying,
I had to go over to my Republican buddy's house to watch the debates.
Because no Republican is going to not have cable
because they need to have their Fox News.
Otherwise, they wouldn't be Republicans.
I don't know.
Well, I don't like to, you know, generalize.
You know, it's like without Fox News,
we wouldn't know about all those baby parts being sold.
Well, without the conspiracy, there'd be no reason for Bob
or the Church of the Subgenius.
We owe our existence to the conspiracy of the normals.
That's right. That's right.
The conspiracy of stupidity.
It is.
Which doesn't just, you know, let's say,
let's face it, Republicans aren't the only people who fall into that category.
Of course. Of course.
But, you know, one thing that...
And we're about to prove tonight.
Right. And it was a wise man I know who once said that, you know,
the really insidious thing about the conspiracy is that it's not even self-aware.
It's the conspiracy...
It's not even known as a conspiracy.
It's the conspiracy of...
It does everything automatically.
Right. It's just stupidity in force. It's...
The mail that sticks up will be held.
It's just hammered down.
Yeah.
If you're a hammer, there's nothing stupid about that.
Everything looks like a nail if you're a hammer.
If you're a nail, yeah.
It's back in that little hole, buddy.
So, yeah, man, I played some heavy metal in honor of Flint, Michigan.
Ugh.
Seriously, that's...
I was enjoying the music when I heard of it.
That's the new heavy metal capital of the world now, Flint.
How about...
Well, you know, that's...
That's only the one that we know about.
That's the...
Right, right.
Well, there's also Sebring, Ohio, but Flint is bigger.
No, they used to say, you know...
If it wasn't a really old house like mine, you probably got lead pipes.
There may be lead pipes, but depending on the quality of the water coming into your house, it may or may not be an issue.
If you put the wrong...
Right, they use special water that has...
Yeah, no, if you put the wrong treatment chemicals in it, then it can cause the lead to start leaching out, and that's what happened in Flint.
The water...
See, it's all chemistry.
Black Alpena.
They say the...
Black Alpena stuff, they finally led to chemistry.
You gotta start somewhere.
Yep.
Why not try turning lead into gold?
Hell, the Church of the Subgenius turned damn near anything into slack.
That's right.
Well, that's the thing about the Church of the Subgenius is we have the advantage of Bob...
J.R.
Bob Dobbs on our side, all right?
And, you know, he is...
There's...
He surfs the luck plane, but he is also like a black hole.
Yeah.
But he's different from a black hole.
Yeah, a black hole.
He's a black hole with another side, because the luck will... all the luck in the universe is eventually gonna end up coming to him.
Maybe it's good luck.
You're right.
Maybe it's bad luck, but ultimately, it's gonna be compressed into that high gravity, and it's gonna come out, and the pressure is so great.
Neutron star...
Yeah.
Neutron star density luck.
Right, so the pressure is so great that it's no longer good luck and bad luck. It's just luck, and that's just what comes out of it.
And sucks in...
You know...
Good and bad.
You know, Jesus Christ said that he was the Alpha and the Omega, but J.R. Bob Dobbs, he is simultaneously the mouth and anus of the universe.
How's that for your Alpha and Omega, huh?
Oh, we had a little phone malfunction there. Can you repeat that, please?
No, it was the punchline of a joke, and I probably shouldn't repeat it.
Ah, okay. Hey, that could be said for this whole program, week after week, of course.
Yeah.
Yeah, I've been repeating it, but...
I've been repeating it myself, anyway, on to other states.
You've really got nothing better to do, huh?
That's it.
Might as well go and sniff some glue.
Yeah.
Maybe, you know, I played some poop songs this week. Maybe next week I'll play some glue sniffing songs. There are actually some very good songs out there about sniffing glue.
I can't remember any myself, offhand.
Well, that's because you sniff too much glue.
Could be. I can't remember any of the songs about marijuana or codeine or anything.
Just...
Just because people sing about it doesn't mean you should do it.
Don't try this at home, kids.
If everybody else jumped off a cliff, would you do it?
Actually, you know what? I might. I might.
Would you do it, Maul?
I think I actually probably would. If literally everybody else were jumping off a cliff, literally everybody, yeah, I probably would, too.
I might wait a while. I'd probably enjoy having the whole planet to myself for a little while, but then eventually I'd realize I can't survive on my own, then I'd jump off a cliff, too.
My friend, Paul Mabridis, when he was young, his dad said, well, if everybody's gonna jump off a cliff, would you do it, too? And he goes, Dad, I'm the one who gave him the idea.
Oh! That's clean living.
Copyright 1969, Paul Mabridis. But you can still use it on your dad.
Will do.
When he asks you if you're gonna jump off a cliff, too.
Yeah.
If that's the only way I can get laid, Dad, you better believe I'm gonna jump off a cliff, too.
Oh, yeah, and the best thing is while you're in free fall, you know, it's like that's, you can, that's the, if that's the only way you can get laid when you're in free fall off the cliff, you know, you're having sex in zero G's then.
If jumping off a cliff is the only way you can get laid.
Well, back when I was in high school, my dad would go, you're just wearing your hair long just to be like everybody else.
I was going, no, I'm wearing my hair long in the probably vain hope that something will help me get laid.
Like all I've been bragging about or getting and I still don't know if they were just bragging or for real.
I keep my hair short so I can look like everybody else. It's hip to be square.
Well, it also doesn't scream out, bust me, please.
Yeah, it's all about camouflage, you know.
Well, I was kind of a parent.
I remember I, I, I,
I was still in Texas.
Yeah, I had long hair when I was a kid living in suburbia up in northeast Ohio.
Yeah.
And boy, you know, I noticed cops got a lot nicer to me once I cut my hair.
Oh, everybody's nicer if you look respectable.
Yep, yep.
I, I, up until just recently, I've been, whenever I was out driving around here in rural Texas, I'd keep my hair tucked up inside my hat.
But it finally sunk in that everybody my age in rural Texas has long hair.
Hmm.
You know, they just finally figured, they figured out that it was cool around 1980 or so.
Yeah.
And have kind of, the old ones stuck with it.
Of course, the young ones are all have bald head and have a little goatee.
Life was cool in the late 90s everywhere in the big cities.
You wait long enough at the side of the river and eventually the whole world will float by.
Yeah, man.
All right.
Well, folks, that is all the time we have for this program.
Thank you very much for calling in Lonesome Cowboy Dave, Reverend Ivan Stang, Domani Mark.
Till next time, kids.
Ladies, keep it surreal.
For free information, see www.subgenius.com.
Praise Bob.