Somewhere in the forbidding tundra mountains of Lapland, high above the Arctic Circle,
a group of mining engineers were prospecting for copper.
But what they unearthed was a story. A story that was to terrorize the whole world.
I'm in there and have to dig life with father, and I mean Father Slack.
The Soft Genius Power of Slack
I'm in there and have to dig life with father, and I mean Father Slack
But wait! This Hour of Slack, number 1648, is actually a rerun of number 775 from the year of 2001,
mostly recorded at or around the winter season.
It's the first star festival of that year.
Price Bob.
Let me get you radio boneheads going.
Watch out! No, no, no, no.
Okay, okay, watch out now.
Okay, alright, get us going. We're waiting.
Free before me, Earthman!
Hey, he said he's gonna get us going.
Ivan, come on, let the guy talk.
Emperor of Planet X!
Okay, shut up, Ivan.
And I have come to destroy your puny...
Come on, man.
...Lamo! Both of you are Lamos!
I know, I think it's time for the world...
...the first group, right over there behind Reverend Patterson or Rappertino.
How do you know there's both of us?
How do you know there's not three of us being Lamos?
Each time he says it, he has to pay that...
Obviously, there's four of us being Lame here, not two.
Both would imply a couplet.
Yeah, it's easy to say Lame. It's easy to say Lame.
I can say Lame. Lame, Lame, Lame, Lame, Lame, Lame.
The lamest show with the lamest callers.
So if you get really close to the mouthpiece, does that mean you're...
...can you talk a lot more loudly?
I don't know.
But you can say Lame. Come on, say Lame. One more time. Lame, Lame, Lame.
Oh my God, there'll be a molestation.
You're an adolescent and you overcompensate.
Support all of us on this with your work.
Oh, no. How many cans of Red Bull have you had?
Adolescent.
I'll support both of us.
Adolescent?
Yeah.
I'll have you know, I just reached puberty.
Hey, I have some... I got four hairs on my nutsack.
Are you sure?
Just stop the show.
Hey, we're cruising now.
That's not what your mom said.
I should make jokes about Lame over the water.
Because we are cruising, man.
Now we're cruising. Thanks to that caller, we're kicked off.
We are cruising down the road.
I feel the wheels turning.
Yeah, and I have to jump Michael Pepe's phone machine for that.
Michael Poopy.
Because this is the last show of the millennium, folks.
Michael Poopy on the last show of the millennium.
Yep.
It is the last show.
The show is cooking now.
Have you noticed that?
There's a little smoke coming out of that box over there.
Oh, yeah.
Nice.
Eggs Benedict.
Smells kind of like Eggs Benedict or you could think...
Some could say it smells like burning rubber or electrical conduit in a state of hyper thermal activity.
But you know, friends, the real subgeniuses are the ones who literally, totally gave their brains over to Bob.
Now, that turns some people off.
That's why we're not...
Maybe we're a little faster growing than, say, the Scientologists or the Mormons.
But we're not there yet.
And I think it's a lot of times.
Because people, they see these subgeniuses who are really into it and they're acting just wrong.
You know, there's just something.
But friends, you can't imagine how much those are the ones who truly, truly believe in Bob.
They have given their brains to Bob for good.
Forever.
They're never going to get those brain cells back and they don't want them.
Those weren't the brain cells they needed in the first place.
But friends, you too can give your brain to Bob just temporarily.
You don't have to do it for all time.
Just say for tonight, you know.
Once you've been slack, you'll never go back, my friends.
If you could be slack for one Saturday night, you'd never want to be pink again.
And, you know, as...
Now, some people also question the church because of our track record regarding ends of the world happening every July 5th or not.
And as I've said before,
Are we going to let the church win?
Jehovah's Witnesses out-cook us.
Hell no.
But, you know, Bob has held these...
They're drills.
They're sort of culling drills that we hold every year to weed out the faithless from those who have faith.
And friends, here in the Church of the Subgenius, we have no faith!
We don't use faith instead.
We use magic.
But it's a special kind of magic.
The Bob's keys to magic begin...
His first key to magic begins...
Get off your ass.
And his final key of magic is...
Wash your ass.
And I think I'll let you worry about the in-between stuff.
We can't, you know, give away all our secrets for free.
But, you know, depending on magic is kind of tricky.
Because, you know, in a way, what you're saying is you're feeling lucky.
You know?
So I'm going to go ahead and invest that money that I borrowed from my friend because I'm feeling lucky.
Friends, when you feel lucky, you're going to be lucky.
You taunt the subgenius demon, which is called Niiiigi.
You taunt him.
It's as if you're saying, oh, Niiigi, you are ineffective.
You can't hurt me.
I feel lucky.
No, no, no.
You have to get off your ass every now and then, friends.
I've been constantly, and I hope dispassionately, considering this very problem.
I have come to the unalterable conclusion that man is unfit as yet.
He receives such knowledge, such almost limitless power.
An invisible being that cannot be disintegrated by atomic fission.
That is our god.
That is a scientific impossibility.
There's your answer.
It must have been renewing its molecular structure from one microsecond to the next.
Trapped in your cage of only three dimensions.
Take it down now.
Take it down.
We're scoping this entire life for you.
Now listen to him.
Maybe if we reasoned with him.
A meddling idiot.
As always, Abe's brain could contain the secrets of the Krell.
Reason.
If reason would be the key.
They could hardly have understood what power would destroy them.
If reason could turn as quickly as a watch into the hand of death, do you have got the
reason?
I've said it.
You could hardly have understood what power destroyed them.
You know, I just don't think I've ever given me a chance to be me.
Nothing but smoking ashes, man.
For miles and miles, we found a stream, and, well, I keep this all pink.
Yeah, and it was slimy, but we drank, and where it moved, we cupped our hands, and
we took as much water as we could in, because our gills were already expanding, and the
mutations were starting to happen.
We knew it wasn't going to be easy, but we tried, oh, to have fun along the way.
Any way we could, our sensations were expanded.
Not much more.
The pain was more, and so was the joy and the pleasure, so we advanced ourself along
those lines.
Who hence had more lived than someone else...
Nightmare!
Somebody restrain on you.
Heat one quart of milk in a heavy utensil.
What are you, dude?
We're on the show with milk for fewer calories.
Is this beat doing something for you?
Yeah, man, I'm swinging.
Hanging mighty low, hanging low.
Get your damn old feet!
It's the devil on seat.
How you doing there, boy?
Sure, yeah, yeah, okay.
Well, things have taken a much worse turn.
Look at them all.
Spin their heads around like that.
We need a big old wad right on top there.
More recently, what if you had a shot at killing Hitler?
You see, it's kind of a slippery slope.
Justifying premeditated murder.
Oh, yeah, sure.
That's easy for you to say.
You keep saying that.
You say you can justify murder.
I don't believe so.
I don't believe you can...
Well, okay, I take that back.
I do.
I don't believe you can justify murder.
So now you have to kill me.
Under certain conditions, yes.
You have to kill me.
It's part of Cult Stock, 2001.
No!
You'll drop your weapon or I'll kill you.
Eli!
I have to see you.
Eli, like a dog.
Like a scurvy dog you are.
Want you to let me kill someone?
Kill her!
Sure, yeah.
Kill them.
Kill them all.
That's what they said.
You killed my bury.
They're beeswax.
It's a hard hard work,
to blend so many different spaces in your head,
yeaah!
You know I can't refuse.
Goose.
movie time here.
And...
You know I can't refuse.
Build it.
And you.
I believe as I did before.
In theory, it should work.
Always theories.
Jigsaw puzzles on paper.
Aren't you fellows ever positive?
I am golden slipass.
Look at my feet.
Touch me, levitate now.
Only about doomsday.
Yes.
Doomsday.
I have the power in my feet.
Look at my carpal toenails.
Look at the fungus, it shines.
I...
Now I look down at you.
See?
And I can move around the room with it.
You think being an insect is not...
Of doomsday.
We are all too sure.
Damn that man.
Spend too much time with the stars.
You don't know anything about living.
The law of the jungle.
The human jungle.
I do.
I've spent my life at it.
It's coming.
You don't know what your civilized people will do to cling to life.
I do because I know I'd cling if I had to kill to do it.
And so will you.
We're the lucky ones.
The handful with the chance to reach another world.
And we'll use those guns.
You'll use them, Doctor.
Yes.
To keep your only chance to stay alive.
Yes, I'll use them.
Right.
There it is.
If I can figure out how to make this thing work.
My friends.
It's backwards, sir.
It is imperative that you listen closely.
I was in the cave painting these pictures the way we saw them on the viewer screen.
Why were you doing that, Johnny?
So in case he did wipe out the human race, there'd be some record of how it happened.
Go on, go on.
I need guidance, great one.
For the first time in my life, I am not sure.
You sound like a human, not a Roman.
Can you not verify a fact?
I'm bossy.
You're so bossy, you ought to be milked before you come home at night.
Dominator 1 using a
NOOOOOOO!
AHHHH!
Frankie?
Have you ever had unnatural urges?
Do you know the way to the Hershey Highway?
Do you know the way?
Oh, you make me sick!
So how'd it feel, girl?
Felt good. Felt real good.
Yeah, I would have.
I had this big
particle on my toe
and I couldn't get off so I had to take a pair of
pliers and grab that sucker
and wrench him over.
What?
You had to grab them pliers and took them pliers
Hello Ivan, how you doing?
Oh, it's you guys!
Yeah, it's the show, man.
Do you have any pliers?
Yeah, I got some pliers for you, son. Right here!
I got your pliers swinging!
Must be 5 AM there or something.
And we're on the last show.
This is the last, last show.
What'd you do? Did you get up early?
Oh, you wish it was the last show.
It's the last show.
We don't have any more to do.
It's the last show of the millennium.
It's the last show of the old age.
But now
the new old age begins.
The newage.
Ever more infirm.
And Alzheimer's ridden.
We
hobble on into the future.
Yeah, you hob. Hobnob.
For this time,
young baby
2001 is actually
still just old man 2000.
What's that dripping sound I hear?
Is that you dripping?
Are you dripping wet?
No, I think that's just
the morphine drip.
What time is it there in
the middle, mid-America?
Oh, here
in the great salt mines
underneath Lake Erie.
6.57 AM.
Wow.
So you don't actually feel the cold
and horror of the cold?
No, I don't.
I don't feel the horrible temperatures
that other people are stuck with there.
No, no, not, not.
Well, I would if I let down
my concentration for a little while.
Yeah.
Like the Yeti, I may wander naked
through the snow.
Yeah, I saw those pictures on the website.
Melting the snow before it hits you
because of the radiant heat
you generate with your mighty brain.
Well, it's not my brain, actually.
It's the mighty bowl of chili
that I eat every hour.
Ah, yes.
To fuel them.
The huge cans. The one-ton cans being
emptied at one end and the thoughts
coming out the other.
I was one of the benefactors of the leftover chili.
I actually,
well, Dr. Drummond,
please,
you are my mentor in this
arena of
pyroflatulation.
Yes, it's an art form that
we all claim mastery of.
Some of us are still learning to be
ascended masters and
some are just...
I have often been burnt by the heat of your passing.
You quit your
assassin, boy.
I've pulled you out of your mother and I'll shove you right back in.
Now you get in that truck
or you skedaddle.
I like knockers.
Do you ever fantasize
about being killed?
One question, Frank.
This guy's screaming in here.
I'm sure he's a dead cadaver.
Why don't you open the door and find out?
No, it's all right, Frank. I'll take your word for that.
They report they can't use the
flame throwers. Can't get close because of the
acid slime. All right. We'll take other
measures. Anyway, you're gonna love this place.
It's a dynamite camping spot
and it's got a pond to piss in.
Sniffing butts is probably more the
articulate science you would prefer.
The combination of X-Day, all of them
subgeniuses, and Brushwood itself,
the weird energies of that strange
campground in Sherman.
That sounds like an immune system deficiency.
It changes people.
It does change people.
I've witnessed that first hand.
People do things out there
that they would never imagine doing
in the world.
Have you noticed a trans-dimensional drift
in some of the subjects
or unsubjected ones who are out there
perhaps floundering in the field
kissing a rocket butt or something
and the next thing you know they've disappeared off the face of the groin.
I believe that there is a reason for that.
An explainable reason for that
is that the National Transfers
I dare you not.
I believe that you will not.
What I have to say would sound so ridiculous
and so ludicrous to your ears.
What we've been saying so far was so erudite and clear.
It would almost guarantee disbelief.
So I might as well go ahead and say it.
I believe everything you guys have been saying
about Mojo's huge testicles
and the rockets coming out of his head
and everything so far like that.
Many of us feel like we're on the wrong planet.
Ha ha ha.
You know, right as Susie the floozy said
right hemisphere, wrong planet.
Ha ha ha.
I see. It's like a trans-dimensional gate
or like a Zardo's plane.
Maybe we really are on the wrong planet.
Now you know that it is possible to move
planets out of their orbit to in fact
even switch planets
and many of us have suspected of course
that the planet we now call Mars
the dead, empty
poison-atmosphere planet
is actually what was once Earth
the native planet
of some of us in our yeti days.
But it was polluted
by the humans.
It was made red with the blood of many many creatures
that came and went as the wind.
And what we used to call Mars
had brought it to this part of the solar system.
One second.
And we now move on what was Mars
only it is now called Earth
by the conspiracy.
And in fact they are trying to make it more like Mars
covered with concrete
or rock, whatever, concrete for now.
Painting the buildings red.
Poisoning the atmosphere.
Painting people's eyelids red as if they hadn't slept for days.
Exposing them to radiation.
And by doing that
making them take nitrogen and subcutaneously aniline.
They are recreating Mars here on Earth
and yet Mars
they are secretly planning to turn it back into the
20,000 million years to our
into their
special conspiracy hideout.
But it was our planet.
Earth back to Mars.
They are going to love the knife screens.
Earth. The danglings of the earth.
Earth back to Mars.
So few astronaut Americans
have been willing to come out and admit
that yes, friends sure
many of you at this point are going
yeah maybe Sang's right
this all makes sense. No wonder I felt so weird
in high school. No matter I'm such a
mutant. But
what if friends, of course you're
thinking but I'm sure they did this
switch thousands of years ago.
No! It happened in 1953!
In 1953
Earth
and Mars changed places
by the strange forces
wielded by the conspiracy
and their alien allies.
And to this day the mystery of it is
how did they do it without anyone
noticing? It is very hard.
If you look at the Hollywood movies
if you look at the comic books, if you look in the bottom
of the wine bottle after it's been finished off
you will see that what I say
is true. It did happen
in 1953. Earth was switched
with Mars. Okay
now let's elaborate on the substance of Mars.
Robert you MSNBCish guy
you made the point that Clinton was a dirty
liar or something whatever point you wanted to make.
I'm gonna miss Bill. Let's have the proof
I don't care what you guys say. It's hard
to change planets midstream.
Imagine Chaz over there trying to catch
an RTA fudge. That is why
it's... I don't expect you to
believe me. And yet
what I said was the one serious thing
I've ever said on this show. It doesn't matter.
You can burn it all down. Burn the whole
planet down because we're gonna get off soon.
Let them burn it down.
See Chaz that's where we differ.
But see they don't want to let us off.
They're trying to keep us here. They're gonna get off.
Chaz is like an Earth let's get off guy
and I'm like one of those Earth first guys.
I think we should turn this into a terrestrial
paradise. Yeah I believe in that. Earth first
then we can torch the other planets
later. But see
they've already done that.
Attila to Chaz. We're just now getting
the idea. The conspiracy's been doing this for
billions of years. This is the last planet of
the solar system. They've already done it to all the
other planets. Well I can't wait to turn it to cinders
either then. But man Neptune
was great before the conspiracy started
building walls on it. We swam on Neptune. We swam on
Neptune. We were like it was the air and
it was the water. It was like this nitrogenous
stuff and it was like a jelly.
And Saturn didn't used to have any atmosphere at
all hardly. Until we blew that up too.
It's really a small planet actually. Those rings
were originally a beautiful moon
sculpted in the shape of Bob's head.
It was our home. The conspiracy destroyed it.
We lived in that pipe and we blew it
up.
We're killing everything. We lived in the pipe
We are the children of the pipe of the ring of the
pipe of the ring of Saturn.
No.
That was pretty good. We are the children
of the pipe of the ring
of the ring of Saturn.
Whatever you guys are on.
I don't want any of it.
Talk about B-Wolf
and all them guys.
Jeez man.
Yes this is the last show folks.
The last show.
The very last show.
It's about damn time.
Can you believe it's lasted this long and they hadn't
killed us yet? Really?
That's the thing that amazes me. I can't believe it.
So now that
Stang and Phyla have gone to Burning Man
is Doug going to go to
Wellman Greenfield?
Yeah to Janer stock in New York.
Hey get out of the way man!
Hey shut the door.
There was a terrible controversy over
whether the giant subgenius
party of 4X Day
should be held after the world ends
or before. Yeah I like those questions.
Well what do you think? What's the vote count?
Well there was a vote and the
principal chose to
party aboard the escape vessels
after July 5th. In other words
the celebration of
X Day will begin
at 7am July 5th
which is Thursday.
Sure.
I vote maybe.
And it will never end.
This will be the X Day that never ends.
Bring your moon pants.
Breach them not.
As you enter the vacuum.
Ah yes.
Wow free watermelon.
Bring your moon pants
and your um
your moon rocks.
Bring your moon rocks too.
Bring your
your gland shoes.
Bring your mattress.
Bring your mattress back with you.
Go to camp man. I'm bringing mine.
Bring your old mattress back there.
Take her on down.
Back in that back room.
You know where all that stuff is.
Back where we made the real plan.
He he he he.
Wait a minute.
Are you talking about the place where
where Tenderly Convenience waxed
Sterno in the head? That back room?
Yeah. That was the corner room.
That was in Chicago.
That was a long time ago folks.
Well you didn't know that.
You could have hit him in the head too.
You could have.
You're just jealous cause Tenderly got there first.
Here's Tenderly dancing around.
Everybody wanted some Sterno head back in those days.
In a tunnel.
I really wanted some Tenderly head.
Now these people are old
crotchety men.
Sad old bags of
pissed off-edness.
I remember when South Jesus owned the world.
I remember when he was the
preeminent cult in America
and now the Mormons have completely taken over.
I've got
everything in sync.
And I don't mean
in synchronization.
I take a
load now
and then.
Some people flush it down the toilet.
I depend on the sink.
The sink.
And then the plumber happened to
arrive.
And they took that little
electrical snake
and they plunged it down the sink.
And you wouldn't believe
what they came up with.
In the sink.
So anymore
I don't do that procedure.
Cause it
stopped up the drain.
Cause it stopped up the drain.
It stopped up the sink.
So if you've got a
master bank
Don't use the sink.
Cause you're just
giving a dog
to a plumber.
Don't stop up the sink
with a cup.
Don't shoot your
barge
down the sink
with a cup.
It's not the kind of thing
that works against the sink.
Don't sink your
water
down the sink.
And the day
comes
when heaven and earth
belong to one.
You can look back
in the sink.
I hate
these memories.
the sink.
Everything goes
back to the sink.
How do
you make babies?
How do you stop
births short of
abortion?
How do you do it
with a sink?
How do you stop
babies
without abortion?
How do you stop
babies without
How do you do it
with a sink?
You bust
them little
spermies
down the
sink.
Oh,
yes dear
friends.
Well, that was
something you don't
hear every day.
A song there
called In Sink
or In the Sink
by Skip and
the Elite
posted to the
Alt Binaries Slack
News Group.
And friends,
we've also been listening to the last
show of
the millennium on KPFA
in Berkeley. The
subgenius, non-subgenius,
more than an hour, less than a show
show with puzzling
evidence and normally has Dr. Howell
but in this case, Dr.
Philo Drummond, the
overman, the true,
one true, the only
overman yet so far
that we have in the church. The only
proof we have that Bob is
even true. Oh,
no.
Oh, man. No wonder, well anyway,
that show was all
mottered up with the ESO
Swamp Radio
show at WCSB
Cleveland with Professor
Chaz Smith and
lonesome cowboy Dave
and yours truly and maybe
Princess We Are Doe got in there somewhere
and there's some
media barrage clips, monster movie
stuff by our friend
Noumonet, the
mysterious Noumonet.
The music
in the background is Einstein's
Secret Orchestra with
Ron Slade.
Recorded just a couple
of weeks ago at Winterstar
Symposium sponsored
by Ace. This song
called Trippy Beard
P-Boy Muff.
Oh, speaking of hippie weird
stuff, I've got the schedule
for Winterstar where we have
to work, boys.
What do we, do we have to slosh the kitchen or do we
have to remove the urinals and stuff? You have to do
a consciousness expanding
jam at the end of the evening.
I thought it was the P-Boy.
Get this man, Halim
El Dab. Halim El Dab?
Notice that name, Halim El Dab
who is a pharaoh.
An actual pharaoh of a pharaoh. I am proud to call
an acquaintance, perhaps even
a friend. Certainly I admire
his great drumming and his composition. I know you used to hang with
the Ramseys and Tootin' Common
and all the rest of the guys that are seriously mortifying.
He will be drumming across the great
rivers while... Sticks.
You can stretch
yourself out of
pain. Oh, string theory again. With
that Abnomi, that abnormal
girl. You can turn yourself into a G-flat or an
A-shark. And, um,
Halim El Dab
will guide you in
slack. And, uh,
at 3 o'clock, actually at 3.30, then I
give a scientific
talk about the scientific basis
of slack. Okay, now who's
to guide... My new neighbor, Nathar, will be
doing the electronic meditation devices.
Do you have a new home or domicile?
Something
is happening. You don't have to say where it is, I'm just saying.
We're tunneling, let me put it that way.
The tunnel is progressing. You're taking the bags
of dirt out and you're making sure that nobody knows
where you're going? We have to
hide the bags of dirt. Imagine.
That ain't easy.
Oh, and then Pope Bob Wilson... I noticed your toenails
were filling. ...after it does... will tell
it... give everyone a new map
of their consciousness. Pope... Pope
Dozier? Pope Bob... Robert
Anton Wilson is his fancy
author name. We'll connect our consciousness in the key of a
flat tire. But we subgeniuses know him as
just a regular feller...
Pope. ...who appears and disappears
magnanimously without any reason.
Sometimes in a bar or a kitchen.
It's the way.
It's the way. It's the way
above us. It's the way it's been done for billions
of years. So what was life like
to an early denizen of the pipe
of the ring of the pipe of the ring of the moon
of the Saturn? It was like
working at Playboy. I was gonna say...
It was like as if you worked at Playboy.
I was gonna say it was like working at Kmart.
The endless droning.
No, it's like working... The blue shirts, the red shirts.
You were the photographer's
assistant at Playboy. We are happy to help you.
No, the makeup person's assistant.
Can I help you? At Playboy.
And what else is happening then? The spritzerer.
I'm the spritzerer?
The one who comes and spritzes the babe.
What else is happening then? You're supposed to look sweaty.
Um...
Oh, and then, uh, that's when
my page ran out.
But what they didn't dare print
on my printer refused to print
was something about a
space jam... Glam's what's he? In the
middle of the frozen night.
In those cabins.
Covered with icicles. Did it say anything about
Space Trance 1 workshop
meditation
trance drone?
It may have.
I forget what time.
I think I'm on five.
I'm on right across from... Look at www.rosencomet.com
Yeah.
Maybein' it'd be best
to swear, Unre
as I spell the
name.
His business via
arna
Will you escape from the deep?
Will I live soon?
Will you wander through the wilderness of fall?
I know the moon is on me
And I know soon the body is coming
I've smelled it, heard voices, had an universal voice
A galaxy that numbered a billion
Will you escape from the deep?
Will I live soon?
Will you wander through the wilderness of fall?
Hey now, hey now!
Now, to abruptly change the subject,
this, the internet, um, I was, uh, there's several subgenius news groups
and of course a zillion websites and so forth, but, and chat rooms, all that kind of crap,
and one, one person was griping on, on alt.binaries.slack,
which actually has great stuff on it,
and, uh, he was complaining, he goes,
Oh my Bob, is this news group screwed up?
All the posts are coming in day late,
and even the goodies that I put there don't show up, and
he goes, yeah, everything's a day late for me too,
I think the conspiracy is screwing with Usenet
so that we'll all go web-based.
And friends, I think that's exactly what's going on.
And, I don't know, you know, some of you are probably a little newer to the internet,
and some of you probably have dealt with it for a long time,
but I suspect that in about a year or two,
we'll all have to have a license to have a website,
just like the radio, you know?
They, there was a time when anybody could have a radio station,
but suddenly, oh well, there's not enough bandwidth.
So, and of course, you know, some of these subversives might use it for,
you know, to spread something bad, like information.
So, friends, the supernational,
corporations don't like competition.
And they know that our one world religion is the only antidote
for the one world advertiser.
Down with the supernationals and up with the supernatural, my friends!
Up, down with the quote-less Bob, and up with Bob!
When they, as Bob said, in 1959,
Bob!
When they regulate websites,
only news group geeks will have free pornography!
He muttered that in his sleep.
Now, friends, I really do think that, of course, needless to say,
the conspiracy is not going to let us get away with murder on the internet forever,
like we have been. I certainly feel like I have been.
But, you know, and this is what the lesson that we must learn is that
a few subgeniuses must retain their power,
and they must retain the primitive knowledge,
and we must hand down certain paleolithic knowledge,
like of pre-website stone implements,
like news readers, and telex, and crap like that,
hand axes, you know,
and even, we must, even some of us must take it upon ourselves
to hand down skills like shoe repair,
how to clean a handgun barrel,
so it doesn't blow up in your face,
and how to change tires, and diapers, and dollars,
and so forth, because, friends,
I was shocked at how fast the internet went from 99% slack to 99% ads!
It was almost like it happened overnight.
Now, back in the late 60s, early 70s,
it took more than a year
to turn what was known as acid rock
into a sold-out conspiracy tool used to sell tires on Sears commercials.
By the late 70s, with what punk came along,
I remember kids telling me,
well, that old hippie stuff didn't do anybody any good,
but punk will save the world!
It will save the conspiracy cat fight!
It took six months to turn punk into a slogan and a haircut on a beer commercial!
And, friends, nowadays,
only little children still believe
that music can ever be used as a weapon of rebellion anymore!
But then, along came the internet.
We had to give up on rock and roll.
It's owned, lock, stock, and barrel.
But the internet, there was hope!
There was actual hope!
But how long did it take?
The wink of an eye, friend,
the blink of that red eye
that you see when the conspiracy cat fights,
the conspiracy moons you!
And, friends, I hate to say it,
but I am a, well, I'm proud to say I'm a subgenius,
but I am a dumbass!
Because I actually thought that it would be years
before the internet was castrated,
since I figured, well,
the government can't get their hands on it.
You know, it got away from them.
Boy, was I fooled
to think there was a government!
That was the, the damn government was the first to go!
Long before acid rock was even thought about,
the government was sold out.
The one world advertiser has been bamboozling us all along,
at least for the last couple of hundred years.
And no more of it, I say, friends!
Now that it's too late,
and it's a completely hopeless battle,
that's when we, the subgeniuses,
must fight back all the morgue insanely!
And viciously and mindlessly, friends!
What have we got to lose?
What have we got to lose at this point?
Most of us, we, you know,
people complain about civil,
we're just, our civil rights are slowly being taken away.
My friends, you give away all your civil rights
the minute you clock in at work in the morning.
You give up your civil rights from 9 to 5 every day,
you know, and don't even think anything about that.
You clock out from what freedom you pretended to have,
and then you go home and watch TV and go to sleep.
So what is left, friends,
except to use every spare second,
every spare stolen minute,
working like a crazed lab rat
with a wire up our asses
on anything that will give ourselves slack!
Even if that means laying in bed watching TV for hours.
Praise Bob.
But it could also mean energetic monkey wrenching.
And I don't mean monkey wrenching of machines.
Machines are our friends.
You know, the robots, let them serve us.
But the monkey wrenching of men's minds, friends!
Yes, you know, a strong pink back
is a terrible thing to waste.
And some of my fellow subgeniuses feel that
on July 5th, 19, well, uh,
2001, whatever,
when the aliens finally arrive and
the dues-paying subgeniuses are ruptured up
into the escape vessels of the sex goddesses,
on that day, some subgeniuses,
the holocaustal group,
feel that we should just simply
wipe out every normal human being
who didn't send Bob 30 bucks!
Now others, such as the evangelicals,
the schism that I got stuck with,
we believe that, you know,
why waste them if you can put them to work, you know?
If we can control their drone-like behavior
like is already being done,
like the toy robot stick men they already are,
why don't we do it, you know?
Now, how each individual does this,
that's between you and Bob!
Unlike every other human being,
even if you're a conspiracy and religion,
we're not gonna tell you what to do or what to think,
we'll just tell you how to think.
That's the, really, that's the great thing
about this church, friends,
because only you paid Bob
to tell you what you really think slack is.
No other subgenius will even try to tell you
what your slack is,
and the real subgeniuses,
they know that if they could telepathically gaze
deep into the soul of another subgenius,
all of the other ones would seem utterly incomprehensible
and completely insane
at the basis of their very soul.
And they are!
But we know that,
and that is the difference!
Praise Bob and hail Connie!
Soon a Star Wars battle will be fought among the planets,
and the headquarters of these spirits will be transferred to the Earth.
Who are these ETs?
Lucifer and his fallen angels,
the Devil and his demons.
Who's behind it all?
Well, this mysterious ET called Satan.
We must have all good wrong blood for this tight war.
The evil is free.
May God have mercy on us.
We've got a card to order this startling new video
for a gift for just $24.95.
Plus $3 shipping and Halloween.
Space.
2001.
Download.
Transporter.
Conquest.
Thamara M dance.
expands to plastic and
stop your
Insects don't have politics.
They're very brutal.
No compassion.
No compromise.
We can't trust the insect.
I'd like to become the first insect politician.
You see, I'd like to.
And don't we have one?
Isn't George W.
I'm afraid.
W.
I don't know what you're trying to say.
I like what you're saying.
I'm saying I'm an insect.
Yes.
Who dreamt he was a man.
And loved it.
Loved it.
But now the dream is over.
Now the dream is over.
I know.
And the insect isn't.
We're all insects.
Saying I'm an insect.
Who dreamt we were men.
But now the dream is over.
They're saying I'm an insect.
At the board of unemployment, they're saying I'm an insect.
At the job I'd like to give, they're saying I'm an insect.
My church and in my home, they're calling me an insect.
But I don't believe.
They're not.
They're calling us.
Why aren't we supposed to call?
We want a lie.
It's important that you stay from the dates of the year.
Other people probably have a homeless family back there.
We're heard, but we don't now what story's going on.
Oh.
You're the only one who knew this story.
By the way, Ivan, have you ever listened to this show on kpfa.org?
I just did. I listened to the whole first half of it just this morning.
It was your show.
It was the same damn CD that I just sent to you, only it sounded all watery.
That's right, because we were upstairs conferring.
Yeah, we had to be upstairs conferring to get my drift.
If you catch my meaning there.
Let me do some more show here.
We had to snort some show.
Oh, man, this is a great show.
All right.
I think this show's been stepped on.
See, that's our version of Popus Lilith doing her, you know,
Hey, is that?
That, uh, frop?
I thought that was hilarious, actually.
And you know what's funny?
I recognize it right away as Popus Lilith.
Did you know that the average...
It was Popus Lilith pretending to be a guy.
Did you know that in his lifetime...
I'm going to give you a little fact here, Reverend Stans,
that in his lifetime, the average person will have eaten...
I know this assumes that they're not a vegan or a vegetarian...
Or Phineas Narcos.
But they will have eaten 14 cattle, 12 sheep,
2 calves, 23 hogs, 35 turkeys, 770 pounds of fish, and 880 chickens.
I heard it was thousands of chickens.
Well, yeah, it could be thousands by now.
I mean, how does that help us with our last short of the lalunium?
Probably less calves and more chickens by now.
I don't eat as much veal as I used to.
Only 14 cattle?
Only 14 cattle, but they're big cattle.
They're like ox.
I don't even want to think about what they do to calves.
Cows!
Cows.
Oh, they torture them.
They eat them mercilessly before they kill them and feed them to us.
They make us eat them.
But that's okay because it's people doing it.
It's not other calves.
Yeah, it's okay if it's...
It would be brutality if it was another cow doing it.
My God, that would be unthinkable.
That would be... I couldn't think about that, but...
As long as I know that's not happening...
By the way, folks, if you're watching on Channel X, you can see Ivan saying they're eating psychopops.
I've heard that they do that.
They force the animal's parents to do it in other foreign countries.
Oh, it's going to be an exciting subgenius show.
The one and two's gone.
In some foreign countries, they force tigers to eat antelopes.
They force lions to eat zebras.
Did you know that...
That's how cruel people are to animals.
In this country, they force cats to eat songbirds.
We raise house cats so that they can go out and kill the songbirds.
And that's why we have so many bugs.
Good night, bird.
400 million girls were interviewed after why they had their legitimate babies.
They said not just the words, the beat.
They don't believe I'm crying, do they?
No.
They will when they make me feel conscious, though, won't they?
You figure that out if you want to.
They instigate wars, terrorism, assassinations, murders, rapes, and every other evil.
They're all committed globally.
So you're too naive.
You don't know what Jim Jones is all about.
You can't even follow him.
They said not just the words, the beat.
The fertility rights of the jungles are the same beat.
Incorporated in this modern rock to spill it all.
We haven't got next to him, but I've got all kinds of things in store.
Who and what are these ETs?
Who created them and why?
Can their existence be proven?
Sex on the street.
You who are stupid piss ants and reptiles and lower than the primates,
you can make a hoopie if you want.
Sex on the street.
So you can make your hoopie while I do something.
Do you feel blamed?
Are you mad?
Do you feel like moose about to run planet?
That's where the music comes up and everybody gets really, really, really scared.
Man, this has been a lot of fun because we've had the, uh...
We've had everybody here tonight.
We've had the only three important people in the Church of the Subgenius, that's for sure.
Yeah, that's true.
Phineas, me, and Wellman.
Wait, no, let me look at my card here. I can't...
Hey, what? What?
Yes, you've been listening to the last show of the Malunium.
I don't think so.
Only the three most important, but not the greatest of all subgenii.
But where was Bob in all this time?
Well, Bob's just the made-up guy. Don't worry about that.
And where then was Bob in all this time, son?
I'll tell you about it.
Bob's in your mother.
Where are you thinking of, Bob?
If I were one of the subgeniuses, I'd claim that I made up Bob right about now.
Did you even have the common decency to pull your knife out of Bob's belly that day, eh?
I'll tell you where he is, Stans. He's at your mama's house.
Heh heh.
Eating the black stuff inside his skeleton.
I was gonna ask, sir, what about the black stuff?
Hey, uh, cut your belly open and I'll show you the black stuff.
Sounds like a rub, you know.
You're gonna cut your little round belly with the black stuff inside your mother's skeleton.
Heh heh heh.
Is Sal there?
Let the rabbit suffer.
Heh heh heh.
Sal?
I'm gonna go to the rabbit stew!
Sal who?
Salami?
That's funny.
Salami!
It's just Sal Roman.
This, this show has been very good for me.
Thank you, thank you.
This show has been good for me, too.
This show has, like, brought, delivered me.
It's like, I'm in a place where I can be myself.
It's brought me forward.
This show has been arthritic for me, too.
This show has been a frightening experience.
It's been a carbuncle on the butthole of society.
But other than that, it's, it's been great.
Yeah.
And this, you know, last five minutes of the last show.
The last, theoretically, second of life.
The last five minutes of the last show.
...known on this plane.
The forces of good are a sworn enemy.
And I repeat, they must be exterminated.
And I mean, lethally.
I don't mean to be a
little man has done it to us again.
He's made a monkey out of the forces of evil.
Is he dead?
Yeah.
He's messed up as bad as those two back there.
Suppose that saucer or whatever it was had something to do with this?
Your guess is good as mine, Larry.
One thing's sure.
Inspector Clay's dead.
Murdered.
And somebody's responsible.
I'm sure.
I've got to get toinnenment, briefly with the most serious questions.
Uh, I have to.
His around here, probably stay out there today, li'l
my mennyt with to then with fellows you just got guess myself, isending out there.
Even though there's nobody left there, there's just a P.O. box.
It's just a town that used to be there, but now it's just only a stick in the middle of town with a box on it.
And it's the P.O., sacred P.O. box because the rest of the city is gone.
And that MTV tape, folks, that you saw on MTV so many years ago.
There's a picture of the guy that answers that box with his family out in the middle of the wrecked city.
And there you can see in the foreground a little box, a little mailbox.
The sacred golden box. It's made out of solid gold now.
It glistens in the distance.
As people draw closer to Dallas, they see the shimmering, gilded sky as they approach the golden P.O. box.
That is Dallas, Texas now.
Next day's coming. That's Bob at Post Office Box 807, Glen Rose, Texas, 76043.
That's Box 807.
Box 807, Glen Rose, Texas, 76043.
Order now.
Shine the light of whatever.
Not available in any store.
Shine the light.
Batteries not included. Some assembly required.
Not stored in souls.
I'd almost forgotten that old saw.
That clever play on words.
Not stored in souls.
Not stored in doors either.
So sad not to have it anymore.
But you can get it back. You can get it back.
From, with only a self-addressed stamped envelope.
From just what they said.
Post Office Box 140306 Dallas, Texas.
And the zip code on that, friends.
The all-important zip code of Bob is 75214.
And friends, amidst the puzzling evidence,
Einstein put a zip code on that box.
And we have a new one.
It's called the Einstein Secret Orchestra.
Radio Swamp, Philo Spew, and Dave Brain.
We also heard some of the Satanic Jamboree Clips
by Jupiter Research.
And the song Wilderness of Bob by Chaz Smith.
We heard they were recorded at Winterstar.
And also my rant from Winterstar.
There, friends.
Congratulations, by the way, to Einstein Secret Orchestra
for winning the Free Times Music Award.
Here in Cleveland for Best Instrumental Electronic Music, of course.
And, oh, and while you're at it, friends,
check out on the web www.subgenius.com.
And then go to www.pandromeda.com.
I did that finally.
And the promise of Mojo World is so great.
It is.
So great.
Grandiose.
So truly grand is the promise.
Yes.
Ah.
It is a...
I...
And it...
It pulls and tugs at me like a Pied Piper.
I'm like a rat of Hamelin wanting to follow the promise of Mojo World.
That's www.pandromeda.com.
The Pied Piper.
Where the Pink Bob rules.
And the Mojo.
The Bizarro Bob.
Me no like slack.
Ugh.
Me Bizarro Bob.
Me hate slack.
Get to work.
This man...
Legume has slack.
If you call him a man...
Take it away.
...has designs on your consciousness.
That was an actual quote, wasn't it?
Look into your computer screen.
Don't you see what's happening?
Your mind is being Mojo-ized and you don't even know it.
Stand back, Dr. Grinnecke.
I have to disconnect the wires.
It's okay, Dave.
I've seen Dave...
Dave, don't freak out on it.
Just accept it.
It's the new paradigm.
I have seen Dave get freaked out just looking at an ordinary videotape of computer animation.
Just some real trippy computer animation.
And Dave, late at night, we exposed him to this stuff and he was going,
Man, it's getting too...
This is too intense.
They're gonna watch us back.
He watched it.
It's all virtual.
Nobody has a real life anymore.
He pulled his head right up to the screen and he said,
I need blue light, baby.
I need blue light.
I need blue light,funnya.
Well scream blue light if you're Radio Robocop.
di da zang
And they said,
they want green light.
and then the telegraph guy went,
it's gusta- ular.
and then whoever told him to candies
Thank you.