Well, isn't it amazing dear friends what twisting a little knob can do?
Oh, there's so many little knobs one could twist.
Like for background music, there's so much material here, why, I can just fill up this box.
I'm using a cardboard box here next to me to put the Hour of Slack background music out.
Well, I've got my main tapes here.
We have so much to do together and listen to together dear friends,
because I've been gone for away from the studio for almost a month,
and all these new tapes have stacked up.
Let's just see what this one sounds like, shall we?
Well, that sounds pretty good.
That sounds pretty terrible.
Well, let's see how this one goes.
The Subgenius Hour of Slack.
This is the best of all the one true religions.
I guess every religion is the one true religion, but this is the best of all the one true religions.
Well, they all say they are.
And I think what you have done, as you said earlier, you have stolen from all the best.
Is that correct?
Yeah, we've pared it down to the essence of every religion.
Us versus them.
There's no Bob with Bob.
Bob is a sex god.
Unbelievable.
Unspeakable.
Unbearable.
Oh my god. Is this for real?
No, no, no. This is just a tape.
Relax.
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh!
.
We'll be right back.
We've been going on, and it has been, this has been the busiest subgenius month ever.
I mean, is this what slack is all about?
This slack work, friends?
I got back a couple of weeks ago from two weeks on the road traveling, preaching,
preaching on car hoods and selling subgenius goods and taking love offerings out of the trunk of the car.
And I'm not exaggerating.
I actually did that at one point.
It was lots of fun.
And, yes, although I've got to admit, it's hard to rip myself away from the Internet to do this show.
That's a whole other show.
The news group called Alt.Slack on the Internet.
It's been a lot of fun this week because all the college kids have gone home from school,
and there's nobody left on the board but Nenslo, Philo Drummond, and myself, and Reverend Townsend from the, what is it, WMPG, I believe, in Maine, in Portland, Maine.
Good to be back on the air up in Portland, dear friends.
And Onan, Dr. Onan Canobite.
All the college student subgeniuses, I guess, cleared out.
And I know not everybody.
Everybody is being flushed down the digital sewer.
Have you gotten sick and tired of hearing about this info superhighway yet?
I haven't.
Because I think there's big money in it, friends.
I want to be, when they figure out the perfect way to encrypt electronic money, that's the company to invest in.
That would be like owning a patent on the zipper.
Or the button.
It would be like owning a patent on money.
So, anyway, like I was saying, friends have been gone for two weeks doing devivals and radio shows and even book signings.
Yes, we're very busy because our new book, Revelation X, is out.
And I can't tell you to run out and buy it or anything like that.
I mean, that would be a conflict of interest.
You know, we've gotten in trouble before for not empowering.
Low in money.
Moderate income people.
But believe it or not, as I do this show here, it's the day before the night before Christmas.
It's Christmas Eve, Eve.
And this show was supposed to be finished two weeks ago to stay on schedule.
This is subgenius time control in action, dear friends.
The time control that lets the tapes run out in the background.
But, boy, there are some good tapes here.
Just look at them.
All this cool music that people have actually, we have no idea how cool some of it is.
I haven't heard all of it.
But best of all, I've got this massive taping from the ESO radio show in Cleveland.
When we went out to Cleveland, we once again got to be with Lonesome Cowboy Dave and Chaz,
where we did many hours of the purest, purest transpilation.
Lots of that coming up over the next, yeah, I mean, when I get three hours done there,
that's good for, somehow it turns into five hours of slack.
And, yeah, we've been a bit slow.
But there was divivals in Cleveland and Akron.
Oh, God, the Akron subgenius revival.
It was like in the good old days.
Good old-fashioned revival called a fetish ball with men and women showing up.
All dressed in very little leather and spikes and indulging their nakedity and roiling and rolling around on the floor.
And Dr. Legume killed Bob and yanked his heart out of his chest while the girls gyrated
and actually ate the brain of J.R. Bob Dobbs right there on stage.
I saw it happen.
I've got videotapes of it.
While forms of insanity, Reverend Toth Wilder's band, burned money, set fire to Dollar Bill.
And the audience was throwing at the preachers and inserted those flaming dollar bills in the half-eaten mass of flesh
that was the brain of J.R. Bob Dobbs that night.
And that is an event that actually happened that I, as a preacher, witnessed, and as a technician, videotaped.
So I even witnessed at one point no less than 150 people showing up for a subgenius book signing.
Now, that is a new event.
Usually when we...
When your dear host and prayer partner, Reverend Ivan Stang, is invited to a book signing,
about three kids show up, and it's embarrassing for everybody.
But praise Bob, I walked into that Borders bookstore in downtown Philadelphia.
There was 150 people waiting there to be saved, and half of them bought the book
after I finished scolding them about it.
And so there was more nakedity at the Philadelphia revival, strange goings-on,
and procuring...
and pimping and so forth by Pastor Craig Roll.
Dr. Legume performed his last rant.
People's hands were pierced by the spike, and people's minds were set free.
Ah, yes, yes, yes, yes.
It has been a busy, busy month, and it's just getting busier.
We've got to pay the book authors.
We've got to complete all the proposals.
We've got to...
Ugh.
You don't even want to hear about it.
You don't want to hear about it.
I'll tell you what.
Let's listen to something that might be mighty nice.
Let's see.
I believe it was the fourth song here on this CD that we got.
This was...
Whoa.
This CD was given to me, I believe, at the Philadelphia revival
by this band called Punch Drunk.
You callilla L'Plaza, right?
Yeah, Philadelphia.
Punch.
Here's their e-mail.
.
We'll give that address in just a few minutes.
?
Pump Drunk Drunk.
!!
Drunk Drunk Drunk.
As I kept on hearing their music, I started to sound around...
I can smell College.
College.
Thank you.
It's a hangover inducing sound.
Didn't have a thing to drink.
I got a hangover anyway.
Thanks to this show.
.
when it goes down,
the perforations can be properly...
The spell it is trepanation
to pound little holes in the skull
to allow the brain to breathe.
When I signed up for that trepanation,
they didn't tell me about the echo side effects.
But it opens the third nostril.
I can breathe again.
Oh, sure, I can see people's auras now.
Hey, man, you're always black, dude.
I don't see anything.
But I can hardly understand anything.
I can't echo.
This is the funhouse.
The sound of the drill going into my head
was the last thing I heard
was the echo.
And this weird music in my head.
The living world is escaping me.
My head always hurts.
Thanks, Bob.
This music is horrible.
Louder. Louder.
More.
Thanks, Bob.
I hope you guys enjoyed it.
Bye-bye.
¶¶
Gristle Twist says,
Yes, I finally managed to view these books, the only two in the entire store.
They were back to back in a sort of mating position.
I can't explain.
So I interrupted them and was overjoyed.
It's been a good while since my mind has been so inversely gyrated in such a manner.
What I'm saying is, these books hurt, plain and simple.
Hurt me good, yeah.
I felt just like a plate full of steaming and scrambled eggs, or worse.
And that was just from skimming through them.
A fresh head wound have I.
Thanks, Bob.
My head always hurts.
Praise your sweet nature, Bob.
Now you notice some of the people, for a long period of time,
there are dark circles about the eyes.
And a strange...
glazed glass.
Uh, they either look inward, but there's nothing to see.
You can't see your own eyes.
You can't hear your own ears.
Can't run from your own feet.
You can't spank your own poodie.
Can't swallow your own throat.
You can't think about...
your own brain.
Don't do it, kid.
It's fuzzy. It's fuzzy.
I can't think about my own brain.
You can't rip off your own chainer.
It's a vague feeling.
It's a very, very hazy, fuzzy... fuzzy?
Yeah, ever since I got this hole in my skull,
my vision has been great, but...
God, this... my hearing...
It's like I hear these little bongo noises.
And squeaks and...
ghost violins.
It's confusing. It's disorienting.
Well, see, you can not only see people's doors,
now you can hear them too, see?
And their auras sound awful.
It's disconcerting.
It makes me nauseous.
The room's spinning again.
I... I... I can't... I don't like this anymore.
Bob, make it go away!
Make it come down, Bob!
Ah!
Ahhhhhhh!
Cassien obtena to uniken bwreemen
Is obo цен
Forms of insanity, friends.
And I guess that takes us out to side two of show.
Thank you.
Will the same thing happen to me when I get to be a man too?
Yes, son.
You'll go through the operations too.
The doctors will open your third nostril with their musical instruments
and you'll be able to whiff-read the stenches of all the normals and pinks around you.
You'll be able to sell them anything, son.
Just like me.
Gee, I can't wait till that Bob-time train comes around the bend.
Oh, look out, son.
Here it comes now.
Step aside, Earth fools.
It is I, Jehovah One,
the evil alien space god from a corporate sin deli.
Dixie, bow down and pray to me
or I will threaten you with stories of a hell.
They're not bowing down.
They're just bending over.
This isn't hell. This is some genius hell.
No, we took you to hell and then we took you and set you adrift in outer space,
but now we're going to drag you through the internet.
You're going to surf the digital space.
You're going to go through the sewers.
From now on, Dave.
Here, we'll just enter him in.
Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
They'll see.
That's the subject. Let me see.
And this is coming from...
Wait, I better mark off the beginning time.
Sub-Gstang1 at AOL.com.
Okay. Date, 22 November 1963.
And we'll put him in the location, Triple Underpass Dealey Plaza, Dallas, Texas.
And as soon as I hit exit, off he'll go.
Oh, no, not exit. That'll erase him.
Return, that's it.
I'm learning all this internet. I'm a cyber surfer now.
Okay, now we're going to send Dave to Dealey Plaza. Let's go.
What? Wait, wait, what?
Oh, it didn't work.
Oh, it says the modem's at the wrong speed.
It's 96,100 baud instead of 24.
And I...
I paid 89 bucks extra. It was supposed to be able to run that pro...
Oh, well.
Oh, dear friends.
Have you ever faxed someone from the beach?
Have you ever produced a radio show from a hell hole?
A pit of hell?
Have you ever had your email intercepted by a government agency?
You will.
I have.
Yeah, I remember.
I was reading...
I was reading on the subgenius news on the internet, alt.slack.
There, it's...
Yeah, you can tune in.
It's been a subgenius board.
It's been there for years, and we just finally got the stolen modem working.
And why, I remember looking at that little screen, and up came an ad for the upcoming Cleveland DeVival,
which happens to be tomorrow night.
And this came from our dear friend CXT18 at POD.
CWRU.edu.
Honorary Reverend Christina Tate, the queen of all hate.
And on November 23rd, while Susie DeFluzzi and I were preaching at the Dallas Kennedy assassination convention,
this message ID came through.
And I...
Well, I could just envision lovely young Christina sitting there typing up this noble ad.
I'm just gonna have to wait for it to come out.
Get your saggy asses to the most benighted CIA...
Maybe it's that CIA...
Building for the December 2nd DeVival at 8.30pm.
Fill your little tummy with hatred of all things normal.
Crawl out from under your parents' couch.
And come screech with the rev and the whole local directorate.
And if you're a little too old, you can't even get a good look at the
And then explore the crusty caverns of depravity in the name of Dobby Bob's.
As the termination of the conspiracy's grip on your essence.
Scurpy.
And when it becomes a matter of trust...
My neck hurts.
Confuse and frustrate parents and other authority figures...
My mom's wondering if I can have the car.
It's just gonna go off for half an hour.
As you fill the holy coffers of Bob's sacred trousers.
Delight in the visage of the one true slack master.
As your own life burns away.
And your hate lust is quenched in an endless ejaculation of loathing and scorn.
Feel extra cool as you carefully remove the road grime from your civic's rear bumper.
In order to apply the groovy Bob bumper sticker you drunkenly purchased the night before.
And boy, I remember thinking...
I'll just use that lovely description of the DeVival from now on for our press releases.
Our church press releases.
Because...
Maybe then the air will be...
The echo will go away.
It hurts so bad.
Just...
Pantone the echo.
But isn't that a...
But you know what she didn't add to that was that this...
At this event, Lonesome Cowboy Dave will be available to be tortured, pelted with coins, tomatoes, eggs...
Pieces of holy artifacts.
Holy artifacts, pieces of the one true cross, the thigh bone of Saint Josephus...
The holy toe bone of Saint Germain.
The bear...
The claw of Anshi Bear.
The buttock of Witchy Tartai Woman.
All of these things can be thrown, tossed, uh...
Can be used to pelt Lonesome Cowboy Dave...
Who will be chained up there by Dr. Chaz...
And live...
Long confused...
In person...
For that murdered woman.
For your edification and cruelty.
And you yourself will be strewn with religious artifacts.
The Reverend Ivan Stang.
Oh, but Princess Weave, what building?
Where is this revival at tomorrow night?
The subgenius devival?
Why, it's at the Cleveland Institute of Art Factory Building.
The Cleveland Institute of Art.
Oh, I guess this religion is just an art thing, huh?
It's just some...
Oh, fronted by the CIA.
Performance art.
Or, uh, is that what it is?
So they can just get up there and act weird and crazy and...
They keep their names down.
That's why they're holding it CIA.
You see, it's just some mnemonic mnemonic.
That's what you remember.
When it comes up later, they took your name down.
Come out.
Come out and be seen and have your picture taken by...
By...
ABC, NBC, CBS, they'll all be there doing specials.
So show up in costume.
And, uh, if you want to say something right now, please keep it to yourself.
Because I, uh, wait...
There was an article about this devival in the Scene magazine.
Oh, here it is.
And, uh...
Reverend Grinder, an Akron area subgenius minister and one of the organizers of the
subgenius fetish ball happening in Akron this Saturday, December 3rd night, sums up devivals
this way.
Quote...
In a world where supposedly normal people succeed, get rich and live happily, the rest
of us appreciate the chance to give the finger to society and have a whole new life.
Hell of a good time while we do it.
Yes, friends.
Why sit by and watch those mentally healthy people have success and get rich when you
could join us in an orgy of vindictive hatefulness against impurely people...
It's beyond Satanism, dear friends.
So far beyond Satanism.
It...
We're...
With Bob's help, we're building a new heaven and a new earth on the rubble of the old.
Yes?
With Bob, the church, the book, you get something for nothing.
Eternal salvation, dear friends, or triple your money back.
Can any other religion offer you that?
Nay, I think not.
It's $30 now for salvation.
I'm sorry.
That's just the way it goes.
But why must one pay for salvation?
Isn't salvation drop from the rains, from the heavens like a rain?
Isn't salvation a gift of grace?
Yes.
Well, actually, we would have kept the prices normally at $20, but the church was bought
out recently in a hostile corporate takeover.
I'm still working there.
But Dobbs sold the church to Dr. Bronner, the soap manufacturer.
Oh, my God.
Have you seen those odd little soap bottles you see in health food stores?
Yes.
The rant about the moral ABCs.
Yes, yes.
Rabbi Hillel.
Yes.
Okay, okay.
Dilute, dilute.
Slack, slack.
Yes, he bought the church.
And so things, there have been a few, we're praising Dr. Bronner instead of praising Bob.
He's the same guy that makes the celery soda, too.
Well, he wrote a lot of the early subgenius material anyway.
I thought he was dead long ago.
He's still writing his tracts on the ...
We got a letter from him just the other day.
This is from Dr. Bronner.
It was an inter-office memo.
He sent it by email.
It says,
Dear Reverend Stang, you are doing great pioneer work, so much so that in one world
with nuclear bombs, you can teach the moral ABC, the Essene teacher of righteousness of
light, the real Rabbi Hillel taught Jesus to unite the whole human race, lightning like
in our eternal Father's great all one God faith.
You can teach the moral ABC, Hillel taught Jesus, to unite all mankind free.
Its four outstanding points are, first, perfect yourself first, like my father, and second,
mark, spit.
Second, absolute cleanliness is godliness.
Third, Essene, Earth control must limit birth, or we destroy God's spaceship Earth.
Then we can enjoy the greatest freedom.
Fourth, teach how to love, for God is love, uniting all one above, above.
For when Tom Tom, our male cat, sexed Boo Boo, another male, Boo Boo hollered bloody murder and ashamed.
Ran away to die.
So instead of teaching how to sex, Dr. Bronner writes to his new employees,
In his inner office memo to you.
Yeah.
So instead of teaching how to sex, like it does in our new book, Revelation X, he says,
we must teach how to love, for God is love, uniting all one above, above.
So as Einstein's kin, we wrote in 1944,
the poem, Hug to Love, for God is Love, uniting all one above, above, above.
Send the checks here, Reverend Stang.
Yours truly, Dr. Bronner.
Oh, I can't, I, you mean, this is now a part of the Essene conglomerate?
Yeah, the Church of the Subgenius is now part of the moral ABCs of the Essenes by the,
what we once called the crackpot, but great soap maker.
Oh, yes, I love his almond, yes.
Yeah.
So now, you'll have to get the, all of our new books,
all of our new material will be printed on soap bottles.
100% recyclable, I, I.
Yes, you can, and you can use Dr. Bronner's soap for birth control, for shampoo.
Cancer cures.
Cancer cures, you have.
Swash your sideburns.
Huh?
Clean Sprott stains.
It, it will, you can use it as Sprott.
So you'll have Bob doing, you'll perhaps maybe see that.
Bob's out of the picture now.
Now we're doing, tomorrow night's the Bible, we will still.
He's given, he's like given haircuts to Bum somewhere now, down in Skid Row or something, or?
He's probably been doing that all along anyway.
Yeah, yeah.
You know, Bob really wasn't that, he was really kind of a silent partner.
Oh my God.
He just, you know, it was just one of his experiments.
He sold it off to Bronner.
Bronner's 89 years old though, so.
So when he expires and goes to the all, all one Castile soap in the sky, what happens then?
Then, then Dr. Bronner's daughter.
Chacha takes over this radio show.
Oh, Chacha?
Oh my God.
Yeah.
Bob had it all planned.
He sent me a shot of her at the office.
Dr. Bronner's daughter, Chacha, is like the coolest subgenius of all.
Oh, it's one of Bane too.
Uh huh.
That, that third leg on top.
I like it that kind.
What am I gonna do for a little girl with three legs?
Ah, to think of the pleasures.
Oh, oh, I'm sorry.
Who left this trash on the radio station?
This is not trash, this is litter.
Oh, this is tripe, radio tripe.
You know in the old days we called these people geeks.
Nowadays we call them sir.
Geeks walk into a bar and there's a comic up on stage saying this joke about there's two geeks walking into a bar.
And there's this comic up on stage with these geeks.
And it, yes, everybody wants to be Jayner, but only one person can be.
Caller, I don't believe you were there at the show.
Me?
We don't allow callers on that haven't shown us the stuff up on their tickets.
Wait, which, which one's Jayner?
He's right over there, officer.
Oh, I thought you, man.
Do your duty.
Oh, my God, my God, why did they, what, what are they doing?
Why don't they stop me?
Okay, so Jayner, you can probably go home.
This guy will do the lines.
I can never get in town.
He'll do all the lines.
Does he know my stuff?
Yeah.
That's it.
Yeah, we can just all go to sleep now.
Have you ever heard the one about that guy walks up to the other guy and then that guy
walks up to the other guy and that guy walks up to the other guy and then.
I heard that one, I heard that one, yeah.
You hear the one about the comic.
Tell Jayner the other one.
I've never heard the, you hear the one about the comic, it just says you hear the one about
the comic.
Ditch this loser.
Okay.
Now, for the real question about it.
So, I'm ripping off my own material, I admit it.
It runs your guitar.
I want to be on MTV.
I want to play alternative music.
I want my hair to hang in my face
So I can look like Kurt Cobain
Kurt Cobain, Kurt Cobain
Hey, we know it's a valid musical style
You know it's really nothing different from
The crap the 60s underground bands used to play
But the music industry has grown a lot since then
Now it doesn't matter a sound
If you're talented enough
Just as long as you sound like you came from Seattle
Seattle
Yes, dear friends, and we're listening to Dr. Bizarro here
Now in the background, once in the foreground
Dr. Bizarro, what we might call Zappa 2
Amazing
And that's available from, dear friends
This particular cut is from Dr. Bizarro and the Disgustos
A tape album
Every Back's Always Thing Words
And that's available from iBob Digital
At P.O. Box 3405
That's right, that's Box 3405 in Skokie, Illinois
Skokie
A 60076
Yes, 6405
That zip code is 600766405
And, uh
I mean, there's an obvious contradiction here
Dr. Bizarro is, uh
Often is hitting bands for sounding like each other
But it sounds so much like Zappa
In some strange
I just
I don't
And what else have we been listening to here?
Friends, well, there was a little cut there
Of the Berklee KPFA show
In the olden days
Uh, when, uh
Well, Dr. Howell, of course
And Puzzling Evidence
But we had Janer as a guest on there
Janer Hyperpleits
The great Arkansas anti-comic
Uh, and, uh
The fearsome father Joe Mama
Um, before that
Uh, oh, well, it's been a lot of, uh
Cuts from the ESO
The most recent collaboration
Between yours truly, Reverend Ivan Stank
And the other subgeniuses there
Princess Wiardo
And
ESO Radio
Uh, that's, uh, Lonesome Cowboy Dave
And, uh, Chaz Smith
And, uh, and Michelle
And Mrs. Chaz
And, uh, Fred
On the baboon
I think his name comes up properly again
I'm sorry
And that's all
That all gets done
On WCSB in Cleveland
One of the foremost college stations
Ever, anywhere
Praise WCSB and, uh
ESO Radio
As much as it's a good thing
It hurts
It hurts, yes, friends
To feel that show
The echo really does make the walls
Twist around, don't you think?
Yes
But in the meantime
I think that it's time
That we go to this
And
And it's time that I tell you
That you are listening to the subgenius
Radio ministry hour of Slack
The voice of the church
Of the subgenius
Praise that man, J.R. Bob Dobbs
And I'd like to give you
The address to write to
For general overall information
About this mighty church
And this radio show
And the publications and so forth
Also available
And, uh, but that information
Is free
Yes, it's free to you
You
Because you've been singled out
You, the listener
I can feel you
I'm in the spirit
I'm a minister
I know these things
I see these things
I see a young man out there
He's, he's, he's bereft
He's, he's, he's, he's
He didn't know what's missing
But he knows something's missing
He knows he needs slack
I feel you, friend
And, uh, Bob wants to feel you, too
So why don't you write to Bob
You got that pencil ready?
Just write for free information
A self-addressed stamped envelope
Always gets you more
And that address is
Well, just write to
Bob
At Post Office Box
Dallas, Texas
Once again, that's Bob at Box 140306
And, uh, we'll be going back into that revival, uh, soon
What else did we have on here earlier?
Oh, uh, the music
And there's other takes of that available
Hey, Bobber Rebop
That classic old tune
Uh, was heard being done by Forms of Insanity
I'd love to play the whole song
But it gets wrong
I'm not sure if I'm gonna be able to do it
It's got a different kind of rhythm
And it's just a little bit raunchier and raunchier
To the point where the FCC, you know
And, uh, yes
And this is in the background
This lovely music is Osric Tentacles
Yes
We'll see what happens next
I honestly don't know
And, uh, was there
Was there anything else in the news?
Yeah, well, we're gonna go back and see
What happened to the
The
This music would make you feel familiar
You feel familiar
When I say familiar
Yeah
Your wife knows
You're going to
A recently
Haven't called your iy
I don't make bills
Can't afford the
Age
Yeah, I've heard of it.
And they also take the lactate from a baboon's knee.
And they can work wonders with that, too.
But, you know, they're raping the rainforest.
And those are the rare, yes, raping the rainforest for the fruits of the breast-kneed baboon.
The lactating breast-kneed baboon.
And the snake oil was an old Indian cure, which nobody ever gave them credit for.
They just laughed and danced until sun came up and then talked about other stuff.
Oh, people thought it was a placebo.
It was a placebo, but it worked.
That's just like Bob Dobbs himself.
Yep.
You know?
It's like it doesn't matter what's in the bottle if it was him that sold it to you.
100% sugar cure cube.
Damn it.
But guaranteed to work.
Work.
I said the word.
Yeah, and here's some work for you, friends.
Write down the address of ESO Radio.
Yeah, they make funny tapes, too.
Check out ESO Radio.
Got that pencil ready.
And that is at P.O. Box.
Just write ESO at P.O. Box.
1-4-7-7-6.
That's right.
That's 1-4-7-7-6 in Cleveland, Ohio.
Yes, Cleveland.
Oh!
And that zip code is 44114.
Oh, and it feels so good.
To do a zip code like 44114.
And to do such a fun, fun show where I can listen back to things I don't remember doing.
By the way, pardon me if I replay KPFA things.
I honestly can't remember a month ago when I put those other shows together because we're so happy here.
Oh, yes, we're happy, happy at the Church of the Subgenius.
We have slack, slack dripping out of our ears.
We just love it.
And it's...
It's a joy, a joy to behold.
In fact, I'm going to pull out this other music donated by Nensla.
Good old Nenslo there in Portland, Oregon.
Coming right up.
Although, let's just...
Let's just tune into this piece for a while.
There's some other bits from Nenslo's collection.
Oh, well.
So much for that one.
As I was saying, friends, we are happy, happy, happy.
Happy, happy, happy, happy here at the Church of the Subgenius.
They can look at us and laugh.
For all the fun we have, they don't get half.
They say you are the fly, but I know that you're mine.
So leave your camera on the bed.
Bye.
Well, I don't care what people say
You know what?
We make ten new friends each day
And when you got love, you can really have a ball
You see, we're not so different to you after all
When we go out a-walkin' in the town
Frankly, honey, you should see them try to bring us down
But I just put it aside
Because I'm off to a high
So you can look at them and laugh
Yes, dear friends, we and that great set of musicians there, Adam and Eve,
can look at them and we can laugh.
We as subgeniuses may gaze upon those normals laughing
and tittering as we go.
Thank you.
The number you have reached
1-800-OUTBEND
has been changed.
The new number is
617-LICK-OBE
Please make a note of it.
At the tone, record your message.
J.R. Bob Dobbs told me to call
and here's my really weird message.
Still distorted.
No one could have anticipated
this thoroughly modern telephone
could wreak such havoc.
Hello?
I love it every time I call.
I love it.
You guys are sick, but I think I love you very, very much.
Call me to get me free information by mail now.
Call my daughter.
I'm sorry that noise is going to drive me into
all that mess.
I'm sorry.
Sick.