You are about to participate in a great adventure.
You are about to experience the awe and mystery which reaches from the inner mind to...
The subgenius hour of SWAT!
After relaxing on the lake, Bob's ready to have a great time entertaining his friends.
Right, Bob?
Bob?
I want...
What?
If God were to come to Earth, would they find him so strange?
That they would be afraid? And would they shoot him?
Did not his son come once, Pedro?
And they kneeled him to a cross.
And then spent two thousand years learning to believe in him.
All things take time, Pedro.
We will certainly come out on top again if we succeed in being defeated.
This is Jason.
All right, now how did he get back on here?
Magic.
Turn him off right now.
See?
It's just...
There's another setup here.
Is he the kid that says he's Jeremy?
See? It's just a demonic setup.
Tamara, I can't read those cards there on top. I don't know what the last word is. I don't know who's to what.
Let's stop here and pray again here, okay? We got kids calling in, lying.
We have him breaking in in the air, over the air.
And I will not argue with a kid that heavily involved in demonic activity.
I will not, I will not, in the name of Jesus, turn this show into a Marilyn Manson Satan praise show.
I ain't into that.
And I have no idea how that happened.
Lord, we just really ask you tonight, Lord, we just want this show to be so in your will.
And Lord, you know, I'll wrestle with Marilyn Manson.
I'll wrestle with Marilyn Manson fans all night, in the name of Jesus, for you.
Go toe-to-toe all night long.
But Lord, you know, this show was never designed to praise Marilyn Manson.
And all of those hostile, demonic kids who...
That's right, dear friends. This show was made to praise...
Lord, I just pray that you would...
Ah!
Oh, she...
The one that just called in was at the same phone number and she was setting me up like she was a Christian and all that.
Well, who the hell is this guy?
Back at this point?
Now, this is about having a program where I can have the whole season of derpy- 송
This crap's getting baconActivated.
Hey, you want actionắc
Back!
Won't you come So you think I need to go to bed?
Well, I think I just need to lie down over here for some time at night to calm myself down...
and so you may have gotten a cheap laugh tonight
but there'll be many tears in hell
unless you repent
unless there is no hell buddy
unless there is no hell
well
what's next
oh the show that's right we have to do our own show
we can't just pester
their shows
oh friends have I got some wonderful tapes
of crazy
lunatic street preacher
Christians going toe to toe
against Jesus himself
amazing but true
hey you better start bird
domination
this isn't going out of the
air no we are
wink wink
right there so are we real damn funny
yeah we are
we are
I mean what I'm saying right now
because this is stupid
I mean this isn't
I mean I had to prepare
something that's going out over the air
and we just want to start doing this
do the funny stuff right
this sentence right here
okay here we go
funny music
okay
I mean that last sentence wasn't funny
but do you think this sentence is funny
the next sentence
if I thought it was going over the air
wait for the funny music
okay
okay now
I mean if I thought it was going over the air
I would have said something funnier
than that last part we were saying earlier
but you could say something funny right now
but that's not very funny
if you could say something funny
it would be funny
yeah
if it was going out over the air
I mean that's probably just a tape deck
we were just talking to a tape deck
I mean
because now I'm nervous all of a sudden
because it was funny until we found out
we were going out over the air
we were driving up here it was funny
but now
going out over the air
it was funny
I don't think what I said
was very funny
but this is kind of funny
this one's working on it
if I could come up with a punchline for this one
I mean going out over the air
is that funny
but then you can see
what he did
you can't imagine
talking shit about your Natürlich
thego
crappy
I don't care about your shit
oh man
Yes, dear friends.
Welcome to Hour of Slack number 613.
The I'm stepping on Ivan Stang's neck so he can't do the show show.
Oh, yes.
We just come back from Austin, Texas, where we had a wonderful revival down there
with Dr. Dinosaur and Reverend Nicky and Reverend Stang and myself
and some other people who will be awful POs when I don't mention their name.
Oh, yeah.
The show itself went pretty well down there,
but the real highlight had to be the nuts out in the street out front.
You pervert, you big hoo-ha.
You big subgenius whore.
You wicked, wicked man dressed like woman pervert.
Hoo-ha.
You're lucky you not get raped.
You subgenius whore, you get raped by big Christian man.
Well, as you can see, I...
Let me make a fire.
As you can see, I relented and took my foot off Reverend Stang's neck so he could talk.
Yeah, we just got back.
It was great.
The fundamentalist idiots actually showed up for once.
They really did.
Yeah, I thought they were fake protesters.
Because they were just too stupid to be Christians.
I mean, what...
Imagine.
Dr. Legume and I have both had a lot of experience with dumbass Christians.
You know, of course.
But I swear to God, I...
Well, partly Paco of Fringeware, our sponsors,
had said that he was going to try to get fake protesters.
And I walked out of the club, and here was this guy in the street.
We'll play the tapes, but he was essentially saying things like,
Avert your eyes.
Don't look upon these girls.
They're inappropriately dressed.
They'll corrupt your virtue.
You...
Read the Bible.
I thought to myself,
Man, fake protesters never are any good.
You can always tell they're fake.
No Christian is this stupid.
But we were fooled, weren't we?
Yeah, they were that dumb.
They were that dumb.
And, uh...
And luckily, we had, uh...
What...
The scene around the Bob Popular Club,
and the subgenius revival,
looked a little bit like their idea of hell.
In other words, a real good party
with some gorgeous babes dressed in slinky, lascivious outfits,
and lustful-looking, sleazeball, pimp-like men in cheesy suits
that were also false prophet-type preachers.
Just happened to be true preachers.
But you can imagine, friends, it was a beautiful...
It was way, way more intense than any of the other preachers I've seen.
It was like the, uh...
The Bible preaching to the choir that was going on inside.
It was...
That was...
It was a beautiful, beautiful moment.
Oh, yeah.
I...
I've met lots of Christians before who...
When you meet them, they'll come up and they'll put their hands on you,
and they'll tell you that you're following a wrong path,
and they want to pray with you, and they want to pray for you,
and they'll put their hands around you,
and they'll come snuggle up and rub their soft breasts,
you know, and they'll come up and rub their soft breasts,
and they'll come up against your arm,
and they'll look up at you with those little puppy dog eyes.
Well, I digress.
But they put their hands on you, and they'll pray with you,
and they'll try to be nice to you.
Even if you're a total jerk, they'll try to be nice to you.
But these people were the complete opposite of that.
I don't know how they expect to win people over to Jesus
by standing on the corner calling people homosexuals and fornicators.
Yes!
I said fornicators if fornication was bad!
They're standing on 6th Street in Austin, Texas.
This is like drunk frat boy party land, okay?
Austin Gamora.
Yeah, and they're trying to get recruits by telling them that fornication is bad.
That's the whole reason everybody's down there is to find somebody to fornicate with
or to get fired up for later fornication.
Praise Bob.
I've been fornicating for years and years and years,
and never has it crossed my mind while doing it,
am I doing something bad here?
Well, I've only been fornicating for a few weeks myself,
but I've never had any problem,
and I just don't understand how these people can expect to bring believers around to Jesus,
who, after all, is the Prince of Peace and the embodiment of love.
By being more hate-filled than subgeniuses?
I mean, give me...
I...
I kind of was abashed and felt a little ashamed before them,
not for the reasons they would have thought.
I thought they were better...
They were more hate-filled than I was.
I was thinking, my hate's been sullied.
It's been half-assed.
It's been corrupted hate.
Theirs is pure and uncorrupted.
Theirs is the hate of the true believer.
Yes.
For the true unbeliever.
We've taken the wrong path, Reverend Stagg.
We've taken the wrong path.
They're right.
If we really want to hate, we've got to get down on our knees and beg Jesus for the power to hate.
Jesus, come on, get down on your knees.
Come on, get down on your knees.
Come on, Jesus.
Jesus, I'm getting down on my knees, too.
Jesus, Jesus, in your name, I open up my heart to you.
Open up our hearts.
And I want you to fill me with the kind of hate that I've seen you put into your servants.
And, Jesus, if you'll let me hate like those servants will,
come on.
Come on.
Jesus, I love you so much.
And, Jesus, please bless all the people of the world.
All the people of the world, except for the homosexuals, the fornicators, the Democrats,
and the butcher shop store clerk, and people who hurt animals, especially people who hurt animals.
Yes.
And Disney.
And Disney, yeah.
And, uh, and, and.
I'm getting off my knees.
I'm getting tired.
Yeah, me too.
You know.
I just can't build up that kind of hate.
That's the wrong kind of hate.
It just doesn't feel right.
Yeah, it doesn't.
It's self-righteous hate.
It's not, it's not true Bob-filled hate.
It's not Bob-powered.
It's ego-powered.
It's egocentric, self-centered, silly, limited human hate.
Pathetic, silly, frustrated, impotent hate.
Not the ground.
And glorious military-style hate of the true subgenius brothers and sisters.
We hate them too.
Yes.
I'd sure like to be hating some of you subgenius gals some more.
Huh.
Oh, yeah.
I hate him.
I guess.
All kinds of hate you've been bottling up inside you.
I've got a hate on, baby.
Oh, yeah.
And the time's coming to release that hate.
It mighty spurts upon the very visage of Mother Earth.
And all of her.
Earth first.
The rest of the universe.
Then Mars.
Then Venus.
Mercury.
And finally.
Finally Uranus.
Uranus.
Uranus is mine.
No, it isn't mine.
No, no, no.
Evangelicals shall lay first hand on Uranus.
No, no, it must be a holocaustal.
All right, you holocaustals.
A holocaustal who puts his hands on Uranus first.
All right, all right.
You holocaustals can have Uranus.
You holocaustals may have Uranus, doctor, like you.
It's all you, then.
That's all, then.
Have at it, boys.
It is the great holocaustal dream.
The dream that one day you'll be able to join Legume for a nice journey across Uranus.
The great battle of Uranus, where all shall fight and battle over the future of Uranus.
And the winner will be able to pack Uranus with broken glass.
The planet of broken glass will be Uranus.
Okay, friends.
We're at Bob Poplar's nightclub disco type place in Austin, Texas on 6th Street.
Big, popular, thousands of pinks outside milling about.
Lots of pinks disco dancing downstairs.
We're following-
I'm gonna offer my soul in exchange for his.
Sir, I have a proposition for you.
Okay, friends.
This is, um, that was the voice of one of Satan's cheerleaders.
There are, uh, three of them out there dressed in lovely cheerleaders' uniforms, uh, of a dark red and black color.
And a big 666 across the front.
And they've got sort of goth-looking makeup.
And, you know, they're modern-day looking, uh, but lovely, lovely young ladies.
Um, and so sweet.
You'll hear them, uh, they're all this sweet.
They're the kind of, if you're an old dad type like me, you know, gosh.
You know, she sounds like she'd make you proud.
If she was your daughter.
Well, um, they're out there just being as sweet as they can be.
And you'll hear the, um, there are two main fanatical, uh, Christian street preachers.
The Gomer-pile-well, actually three.
There's, uh, uh, the-a couple of Gomer-pile guys.
And then, uh, an-an Asian woman who you can tell by her voice.
And she is, uh, she gets into it with, uh, Reverend Nikki Deathchick at one point.
And, um, another, uh, sister, Sarah, a subgenius who had come up from Dallas who we didn't even know.
And this is a pretty amazing sequence.
I hope I don't have to edit too many cuss words out.
Uh, praise Bob.
We are taking a soul check tonight.
It is one dollar tonight to sell your soul to Satan's cheerleaders.
And we are so much fun, let me tell you.
I also want to offer you, if you sell your soul...
There's rest in a poker.
...Sell Hellbagnos.
This is worth so much!
And you're getting a pair of Satan's Cheerleaders underwear.
If you join, you get to wear Satan's Cheerleaders underwear and have 10,000 Hellbagnos dollars.
Right here.
Your underwear is really cool.
It's gonna cost you a dollar.
Cover your eyes!
They're unappropriately grand.
Cover your eyes with our panties, definitely.
Yes!
I-I see a dollar right there, sir!
You can sell your soul.
Right here.
We have a pair of pants.
A pair of pants.
It's a bargain.
Oh, here.
Okay, fill in your name and keep this in your wallet, okay?
Here you go, sir.
These girls might steal your virginity.
Thank you so much!
Be careful!
How many people out here are virgins?
They may take away your virtues.
These women...
Jesus!
They're probably fornicating.
One dollar?
You sold me!
Stay away!
One dollar?
Come on!
Oh, what?
Did you guys pay?
Read the Bible.
Oh, no!
We paid him the whole thing.
This sound is off of my video camera.
People are giving her dollars.
She has a roll of dollars stuck in her bosom.
I was selling a couple of souls in the world, generally.
I didn't really want them, but it's okay.
Do you know the one you serve?
We're gonna burn!
You don't know the one you serve?
I serve bees, and I am selling souls tonight, let me tell you.
You sold yourself to the devil, obviously, and you think you can stay in the world.
They'd have a lot more money if they sold their soul to the devil, honey.
I wouldn't live in an apartment if I sold my soul to the devil.
You are gonna have problems on Judgment Day, because you, all of you, will have to give
an account on the Judgment Day.
You're gonna stand by yourself and stand before the almighty God and give an account
of what you've done in your life.
And you're gonna have to say, I've sold my soul to the devil.
and all this other stuff and what you're doing.
And I have a diary!
And you can find my diary in one year and you can see.
You can do that now, sir.
You can cheer and you can clap.
But God is not going to cheer.
God is not going to clap.
He is going to cast you into a lake of fire for eternity.
Woo! Right at the beach.
Down in Mexico, maybe.
Here's 10,000 health factors.
God! God!
Well, this is Pope Angus.
Kill me!
You know, when the Christians came to Alaska,
I told the Eskimos about the hellfire.
They were like, where can we go?
It's fucking cold out here!
Woo!
Thank you.
Lady, you're wicked.
You're way to hell.
You better fear God.
You know, I want for Jesus Christ himself.
You're a good man.
You're a good, good day.
He's a devil!
You're a devil!
You wicked woman!
You oppress yourself like a whore!
You know what?
When you get raped, it's not going to be that funny.
It's not going to be so funny when you get raped, lady.
Because of the way you dress.
You dress like a whore!
You're a woman.
I have seen you.
I am like a whore.
Okay, now Reverend Sarah runs up and gets in the creature's face.
I am a whore.
Oh, definitely a whore.
Oh, men should control themselves.
If women can dress however they want.
Oh, women should dress modestly.
I am not a whore.
You are a whore.
And now suddenly some Austin cops, two big Austin cops run in and grab Sister Sarah,
shove her.
I guess she touched the creature.
She was talking about controlling themselves.
She was talking about controlling people.
They should have self-control.
And she was the one that did not have self-control.
She was the one that offered her.
And the cops are hauling Reverend Sarah off and really roughly shoving her away.
Away comes the righteousness.
They are putting her in the paddy wagon.
This judge, not a best to be judged, is nothing but just a whole bunch of hoo-hahs.
You need to understand.
You need to understand the concept.
The concept is hypocrisy.
The mean whore is hypocrisy.
Meanwhile the cop, I'm filming the cop pushing his mother away.
Do you see this? I'm being pushed by a cop.
They then haul her off to the paddy wagon again and stick her in there.
Do not judge somebody else.
Don't ask me.
Who did they take away?
I don't know.
She, um, killed herself.
You're not going to leave your kids.
You're being a child molester.
That's making a judgment.
And that's making a righteous judgment.
It's good that you don't want to let your children be the child molester.
People, you need to have some brain.
Use your brain.
Does anybody have any questions?
If I don't masturbate, is it okay if I have a wet dream?
Listen.
God will hold your camel for the love of your heart.
If you have lust in your heart, you are already committing adultery on the side of God.
Uh-oh.
Oh, well, in that case, if I'm already gay, I'm sure I'm rescuing her.
I don't think she has the means to do anything.
She managed to do something.
She did.
Yeah.
Well, friends.
Anybody else have any questions?
Yeah, you can hear the paddy wagon backing up to take the dangerous subgenius out.
Yeah.
Anybody else have any questions?
Oh, I have a question.
The law being upheld in this place.
They only uphold the law due to the fact of what you just said.
That person needs to be put in jail because that person will be dangerous.
You're not getting drunk.
Good Muslims don't get drunk or fornicate.
No, we do not.
You're submitted to God keeping his commandments.
You're no good Muslim.
Are you married to her?
Yes, I am.
Let me ask you something.
She was indicating a fight.
And what the girl was saying, they bumped.
She bumped her.
But still, but still.
But what is the book about turning over teeth?
It's also about choosing.
Friends, it was an amazing.
It's the kind of thing that the Church of the Subgenius is really good for.
It's like when you see the contrast between those people and the lascivious looking,
but obviously fun loving and I don't want to give away too much.
I'm not going to stop here.
They might.
I decided to go in there and let people know that the real action.
Oh, man.
Oh, it was amazing.
Okay, friends.
Well, onto something else.
My thoughts are illegal.
This isn't this song.
Stop me before I compose myself.
Don't make me use this.
I can't turn it off.
Stop me before I compose myself.
I know I can't.
I mean, no one can be both himself and little.
Stop me before I compose myself.
I'm thinking.
I'm thinking as blank as I can.
Or am I just saying that?
Who is it who's saying that?
Can you really tend to forget what's true or was I just thinking that?
Or was I just thinking what?
Why race to a future that's missing a now?
Or did I just answer that?
We're all faster than we can catch up to anyway.
Stop me, stop me, stop me before I compose myself.
So you can't get a real cure, they cost too much.
Stop me before I compose myself.
They're just gonna train you to build a dumber you.
Are you sure of who you're thanking for letting you live?
Stop me before I compose myself.
Am I allowed to treat myself at all anymore?
Or can the doctors tell me that?
Are they allowed to tell me that?
Am I stupid, stooped to turpitude and torpor?
Or is that just a Prozac?
Make mine on the rocks with a twist.
Is it still prosaic, just with no more eye?
Is that why they call it that?
They can't determine if it's a boil or a jewel.
Stop me, stop me, stop me.
Stop me before I compose myself.
Are you a good witch or a bad witch?
Are you ever gonna let me out of Kansas again?
Stop me before I compose myself.
Is your lollipop blood breath or cabala?
Could you whiz me home in that balloon of yours?
Or is that just a bump on your head?
Do you think you should sell me a heart?
Is that the tornado that's talking up there?
Or should I be paying attention?
Whatcha doing behind that curtain?
Is it ritual throwing yellow bricks on your feet?
Can you hear me asking you that?
I don't think I want to be in your magic shoes.
Stop me, stop me, stop me.
Before I compose myself.
Just a little time.
A-ha.
Ludwig Sears, friends.
The music of Ludwig Sears.
From his tape.
Stop me before I...
Well, what is the tape?
The tape is hand labeled.
And it is from our old friend...
In Minneapolis.
Who disappeared for a long time.
Then came back with that.
Amazing.
And earlier in the show...
The business about...
You're gonna have nothing to handle.
Reality sport.
from Ludwig Sears,
End of the Bhagwan Rag.
We heard a little bit of tape.
I think Ugly Shayla sent us of that show,
Let's Talk Jesus.
We heard some Jane or Hypercleans
on the KPFA show in San Francisco
from Phineas Narco's tape, 1997,
the Are We on the Air business.
Of course, Dr. Legume
and the street preachers.
The foulness of the blueness of a wound, friends,
cleanses away the evil.
I don't suppose anybody has a big jug of coffee here, do they?
Have you ever noticed that in places like this,
they only sell drugs
that are central nervous depressants?
You cannot buy a cup of coffee,
and yet you can buy a drug
that if the leaders weren't all addicted to it,
they'd talk about it just like they're talking
about the world.
I guess that bad-mouthed alcohol
is kind of a dumb thing to do in a bar.
Well, false slack is better than no slack at all.
That's for damn sure.
But really, think.
Imagine how absurd it would be
if you lived on some crazy planet
where they made an ordinary plant
like coffee beans, say,
that grows on the ground,
where they'd make that something
if you had even just a bean of coffee,
not even a cup of brewed coffee,
just for having some beans,
they'd throw you in jail for a year or two,
maybe for your whole life.
And yeah, imagine such a world
where heroin,
which makes you want to, like,
drive real fast and get in fights,
was not only legal,
but advertised on billboards, television,
and you could buy it,
not only at every 7-Eleven,
but right here in this room,
and you could buy it for $2.50.
Fuck, fuck!
Fuck!
My face is...
Thank God we don't live in a world like that!
Help!
You know, you opened yourself up to demonic activity.
You know what I'm saying?
Well, you saw, you thought you saw Satan,
you saw something pretty awful.
Probably was a demon.
.
It's a beautiful world we live in.
A sweet romantic place.
Beautiful people everywhere.
The way they comb their hair makes me want to say it's a beautiful world.
Welcome brothers and sisters.
Prozac Free Radio is not on the air tonight.
Tonight we're here to bring you Up With Jesus.
That's right brothers and sisters.
We have taken that sinful show off the air by popular requests.
And we have decided to put on instead a show which serves the Lord Jesus.
Praise the Lord Jesus.
Jesus loves you all.
Jesus loves WMUH.
And Jesus loves me.
Oh yes.
Jesus loves me.
This I know.
Because the Bible tells me this.
Oh so.
Oh brothers and sisters.
Can you feel the Spirit of the Lord coming through your radio?
Flying around your room.
Flying into your brain.
Flying into your ears.
Flying into your heart.
Oh yes brothers and sisters.
Jesus is here tonight.
He's here tonight to share with you his words of love.
Um.
This is the Bible.
This thing could be um.
You know it's never going to appeal to everyone.
We don't want it to appeal to everyone.
But we'd like a chance to it to reach the people that it should reach.
Um.
And so you know it's part of our policy of selling out.
And we've come up with these slogans.
And this is what I'll end with.
Just in case you're from any of these companies who've already started the ad campaign.
We'll design your own ad campaign.
We'll design banners for you.
Um.
This one's for Levi Jean.
The subgenius must have slacks.
What?
What's that?
Repent.
Quit your job.
Slack off.
But.
Don't squeeze the Charmin.
No one can sell off quite like us.
Alright.
Trojan condoms.
Fuck them if they can't take a joke.
Burger King.
Don't just eat that hamburger.
Eat the hell out of it.
Oh yes.
It's a beautiful world.
Because it's the Lord's world.
God created earth and all of it.
And it has all of the beautiful things in it.
Ah yes.
He created baseball, hot dogs, apple pie, and Chevrolet's.
Oh yes.
The Lord created everything on this beautiful world.
He created me.
He created you.
He created all of this wonderful broadcasting equipment.
And all of your wonderful receiving equipment.
For one simple purpose.
To do his mighty work.
For earth's spirit.
He drove us to create great weapons which we once turned against each other.
Now to turn against the alien threat.
Against all other planets.
Except ours.
Until only mother earth we may.
We declare war against the planets.
War against the universe.
War against God.
Earth burn.
We will destroy all of the planets.
But earth first.
If we cannot conquer a planet.
We will destroy it.
If Bob cannot have it all.
He will destroy it all.
If Bob cannot have all planets.
No one may have any of it.
All worlds.
No one could have any of it.
All worlds or none.
Play spot.
One house, one goal, one soul, one toilet bowl, Bob Dobbs.
Bob Dobbs.
One house, one goal, one soul, one toilet bowl, and you're in control.
Said you're in control.
Control.
Well ever since I was a young boy I played all eighteen holes.
From Catahoula down to Dobbs Town, Tadahassee up to Muscle Shoals.
I ain't never seen nothing like it when I was flipping the remote control.
That bleeding head of our Palmer sent fear into my soul.
Well it flies on a volition, don't need no rocket fuel.
It has its own incision from which the red blood spews.
It always gets the playback, I ain't never seen it drop.
That bleeding head of our Palmer is a force that can't be stopped.
Ow!
You other golfers think your day in day you better run like scally dogs.
Take your big red strap and down into Mobile and truck it down to Omaha.
You better keep your faces up to the light in the air where it is clean.
The severed head of Palmer will meet us on the green.
With Bob inviting Jesus.
After the war is won.
There won't be nobody left to kill and we can throw away the guns.
Yes dear friends, an amazing piece of music.
And obviously there's another one coming up here.
Which we will bypass.
Okay, here we are.
It's a Cardinal Synapsis.
And the In Control Gang.
Oh yes dear friends.
I don't know anything about them.
But I like their accent.
And I guess they sound like they're from Mobile.
Some place in Bob's country.
It ain't quite the same as God's country.
But friends, you know what we're getting at.
Do we have to spell it out?
You know, those who know don't say.
And those who say don't know nothing.
I've got some more street fighting coming up.
But I wanted to read you a little bit.
Oh, this is Einstein's Secret Orchestra in the background.
I wanted to read to you though this bit of news.
This is something that would qualify for the Darwin Awards.
Pardon me, I think I have Ebola.
Michigan, USA.
A guy buys a brand new Grand Cherokee for thirty-some thousand dollars and has four hundred plus dollar monthly payments.
He immediately gets a hold of his friend and they go to do some mail bonding.
They go duck hunting and of course in Michigan all the lakes are frozen.
These two atomic brains go to the lake with the guns, the dog, the beer and of course the new vehicle.
They drive out onto the lake ice and get ready.
Now they want to make some kind of natural landing.
Something for the duck, something for the decoys to float on.
Remember, it's all ice.
And in order to make a hole large enough to look like something a wandering duck wants to fly down and land on,
it's going to take a little more effort than an ice drill.
An ice hole drill.
Out of the back of the new Grand Cherokee comes a stick of dynamite and a short forty-second fuse.
Now these two rocket scientists do take into consideration that if they place this stick of dynamite on the ice
at a location far from where they're standing, them and the new Grand Cherokee,
they take the risk of slipping on the ice when they run from the burning fuse
and possibly going up in smoke with the resultant blast.
So they decide to light this forty-second fuse and throw the dynamite, which is what they end up doing.
Now remember a couple of paragraphs back when I mentioned the vehicle, the beer, the guns and the dog?
Yes, the dog.
A highly trained black Labrador used for retrieving, especially things thrown by the owner.
You guessed it, the dog takes off at a high rate of speed on the ice and gets the stick of dynamite with the burning forty-second fuse
about the time it hits the ice, all to the woe of the two idiots yelling, stomping, waving arms and wondering what the hell to do now.
The dog, well, it is happy and heads back from where it came from moments before with the stick of dynamite,
only to the mounting woes of the two bozos now really waving their arms, yelling even louder and jumping to new and higher heights than ever before.
Now one of the guys decides to think, something he's never done before this moment, grabs a shotgun and shoots the dog.
The shotgun is loaded with number eight buckshot, hardly big enough to stop a black Lab in its appointed round.
Dog stops for a moment, slightly confused, and continues on.
Another shot!
Then this time the dog still stops.
The dog, standing, becomes really confused and scared, thinking these two Nobel Prize winners have gone insane,
and takes off to find cover, with the now really short, short fuse burning on the stick of dynamite.
The cover the dog finds?
Underneath the brand new Grand Cherokee thirty-some-thousand-dollar, four-hundred-plus monthly payment vehicle sitting on the lake ice.
Boom!
The dog dies, and it and the brand new Grand Cherokee thirty-some-thousand-dollar, four-hundred-plus monthly payment vehicle
sinks to the bottom of the lake, leaving the two candidates for co-leaders of the known universe standing there with this
I-can't-believe-this-happened look on their faces.
Later, the owner of the vehicle calls his insurance company, which tells him that sinking a vehicle in a lake by illegal use of explosives is not covered.
He had yet to make the first of those four-hundred-dollar-plus-a-month payments.
And, um, friends, I'm not sure where exactly that came from.
It may just simply be, um, well, Reverend Augustine, Sybil Augustine there, uh, sent it to us.
Praise, praise, rev-sister-ish Sybil.
It could be an urban myth, but friends, who cares?
You can tell your friends, and it'll be just as so true to them.
And, uh, here's some Einstein secret orchestra as we figure out what next.
You don't have the Christ nature. You don't have the human nature.
You're not here. Let's get those phones ringing. Good night, Abel.
Now don't you go until I come, he said, and don't you make any noise.
He said it, he said it, he said it, he said it.
He's talking to the guy, he went up to the third guy, he went up to the Jewish guy, and the Italian guy, he goes in and he's talking to the prostitute.
A devil's puncher.
That's January Boyd.
Well, I can't remember the punchline,
but I've got another one that's funny.
The years are long, but the little toy Bob stands true.
I want one of those toy Bob's, too, I think.
Yes, Church of the Sob Genius, you
need to quit your job for Bob.
Yes.
For only $5, find out about the world's fastest growing cult.
Yeah, I'm slowly gaining control of my life,
and it's scary because I've never been this close to God
in my whole life, and I feel his presence everywhere I go now.
That's cool, man.
We need as many people to be missionaries back
into the heavy metal crowd as we can get.
When you're done looking at the fire,
come on down to Bob Populer for sex, alcohol, and slack.
If you thought those spots were
fires were sensationalistic, you'll love the fires of hell.
The fire that's burning down that building
is nothing compared to the fires that you will burn in if you do
not give your money to JR Bob Dobbs.
Yes, you, too, can learn the path of slack
and become rich, famous, and good looking.
Amen.
I can feel the Lord tonight.
He's here in my heart.
We're all part of a great big puzzle, and you and I are part.
Will you be on the saucers July 5th, 1998, 7 AM,
or will you die like a pig boy?
For only $5, you can step right in through these doors
and see Reverend Ivan Tsang.
He is here and in person, and he is alive.
Alive, alive, alive.
Right behind these doors, right behind this curtain,
come see the weirdest, the sickest, the most twisted.
Uh-oh, I ran out of words.
Sex odyssey.
On the earth.
What the hell?
We are the Jews who are thrown into the lake of Christ.
That's right.
And all true devils, by the sense of God,
would not go into those wicked lakes.
Wicked, wicked, wicked.
OK, not the church.
Shut up.
What?
Things.
I am the Lord, Jesus Christ, of the church of the soft genius.
Oh, my goodness.
Me not deceive all you homosexuals.
You shall not be.
Oh, you're a coward.
My God.
The only thing you're gonna get is sleeping, wailing, and
That's what you're gonna get from me.
We love homosexuals.
We welcome everyone.
We just need to keep the ground on.
I'm not the dad of all you drunkards.
I'm not all you fornicators.
What is he upset about, fornicators?
Wait a minute, what's this about fornicators?
He has no fire.
Wait, wait.
God's back, we love God.
What's he got a problem with fornicators?
He's doing that job for us.
You're decadent.
You're just crazy.
We are bad.
We are decadent.
We love God.
Yeah, you know, sometimes when I get hard on Marilyn Manson, people like that last girl
that set us up.
It's not that I'm mad at her.
She's gonna pay, but it's the demons behind her.
I mean, I don't see no, no sense in a man that goes on stage and cuts himself.
That's just...
Well, we'll get into him.
We're doing some pretty heavy research on him now.
This guy gets hard on Marilyn Manson.
He's gonna get into him, too.
No, no, no.
We don't, you know.
And of course, the collection.
Oh, yes.
Because Jesus is a little light this week.
And in order to do his great and holy works,
he needs your cash.
You know, it cost a token
to go through that great turnstile into heaven.
And somewhere up there
is a little child who cannot afford that token.
For we're not born with the privileges
of being an American Christian.
And we are going to burn in subgenius hell.
Woo-hoo!
And Bob has always fornicated.
And Bob will always fornicate.
And he will take you to a new heaven.
And he will take you to a new place.
Yes.
For only $5,
you can listen,
you can come into this place
and show the Christians
what they can do with their God.
Yes.
Tonight, we declare war on God.
Why worship an alien?
When you can worship Bob.
If God is so powerful,
why does he need guys like that to defend him?
This and more questions will be answered tonight.
I am Jesus Christ.
I'm not the church.
I don't know anybody that says that.
Jesus Christ is the Bible.
Your Bible's so old.
It's so dusty.
I could write damnation on the front cover.
Most of you,
you've probably not even read the Bible.
You're so arrogant.
You make judgments about the Bible
before you even tell us.
Before you point out the splinter in my eye,
take the log out of your own.
Before you judge us and criticize our religion,
why not find out something about it?
I've read the Bible.
Why don't you read the book of the subgenius?
Find out about the spaceships of the alien sex goddesses
and the fornicators and the homosexuals.
Right here tonight.
Be not deceived.
God will not be mocked.
You know you are buried in the soul of the conspiracy
when you see your own face before you
and you realize it's a reflection in a mirror
and that the mirror is on a coffin
and that it's on the inside of the lid of the coffin
and the lid is down.
Now you've caught yourself using your own ass,
Mr. Duchess.
Goodbye, bon voyage.
Have a nice trip.
You are such a damn fool.
You lost your grip.
What the hell does it take to get you to awaken?
No matter what you say, A equals A equals A equals A equals A.
Black is black.
White is white.
Day is day.
Night is night.
Nature is what it is.
Regardless of what you would like.
Man of sicker nonsense.
Go take a hike.
Have a nice trip.
This builds a battler.
You're a robot.
I am a little להיות
Mm-hmm.
Adíváњa ho.
You know I love theitarz?
That's a fair quote.
area
You want to see theatarz?
Uh, yes, friends, when you hear that feedback coming on,
you know that old Reverend Stang is confused,
but trying real hard to get the mic up to give credits.
You're listening to Zeus Rift from his promo pack special tape
although this is also on CDs.
I'm going to give you Zeus Rift's address.
Write for a catalog from Zeus Rift.
I'm sure a self-dressed stamped envelope would help a whole lot.
And that address is King of the Pacific,
Post Office Box 18765.
That's Post Office Box 18765 Encino, California.
Encino, California.
California, 91416-8765.
That's a zip code of Zeus Rift, 91416-8765.
And, you know, when you get confused about things like that,
you can always write to us.
You can ask me, stang at subgenius.com,
or,
you can possibly write Jesus,
but you'll probably just get the robot at slack at subgenius.com.
And, friends,
you see,
you can get all of the information about everything
from old Bob.
By mail.
Here's where to write.
Got that pencil ready?
That's Bob at Box 147.
4-0-3-0-6.
That's 1-4-0-3-0-6.
Dallas, Texas, 75214.
Should we be at that old box for nine,
I don't know, time,
double eight, 19 years?
19 years.
I know J.R. Bob Knox for what he was.
I know him for what he was.
I know him for what I was.
He has given you one hand?
His emaculation, his divine emaculation happened when he was a young man.
Oh, ho, ho, ho.
And it was, I think, personally, as far as I can tell,
it seemed to have been about 1940.
And Bob's contract with Earth was, wasn't he responsible for the puffer fish?
He was, well, I think the puffer fish is what he was responsible for.
That's where it started.
When the aliens abducted him, he, I hate to put it this crudely,
but he more or less got them high on puffer fish.
Not that people should do that.
This was Bob we're talking about and a bunch of aliens.
Bob was a, was a who-who?
I wouldn't want any, any, any humans to try to do that.
By the way.
Very few subgeniuses and no humans at all can deal with a puffer fish.
But the main point of X-Day is that the aliens liked the puffer fish,
so much, they said, what do you have that's even better?
And Bob said, well, human soul.
And that's what he's trading to the X-S in 190 days,
or however many it is now.
The countdown has begun.
Oh, my gosh, I was so dry.
190-something days to X-Day, July 5th, 1990.
Have y'all heard about the other end of the world saucer cult here in Dallas?
No.
Yeah, we know, I actually have.
I heard that there's like a couple of other saucer cults in Dallas,
and they're calling it saucer cult capital of the world, Dallas, Texas.
And this nice, pleasant-looking Chinese fellow with a pyramid hat says that on March 18th,
no, on March 25th of 1998, God will appear on Channel 18 all over the contiguous United States.
Oh, go to the roots of the lie, Dave.
No matter whether you have a Channel 18 or not, turn to Channel 18.
It's not that serious, by the way.
18, 18, 18, and I like it.
God will appear and will announce, as this man has already announced,
that God will come to Earth in Dallas, Texas at 10 a.m.
In a parrot diaper.
March 31st.
God will appear.
And if he doesn't, this preacher, this Chinese preacher, will kill himself.
Then he's saying the appearance of God will take time at the appearance of the sign of the Ramseys.
And I'm surprised.
I'm surprised.
I'm surprised this hasn't made national news.
I first heard of it on the Internet.
And then the local news people pounced on it.
Oh, great.
Another saucer call.
Lots of bodies right here in Dallas.
Man, we'll be in the news again.
Well, you'll be able to manipulate it once again.
At least if you want to think of it that way.
It's kind of a demonic ploy.
I kind of feel like we've been upstaged one more time.
I think that it's fine.
I think it's fine.
Yeah, you know, Dallasites have never gotten over that one big landing in 1963.
I was there.
I was only 11 years old.
But man, that was the high point of my life.
Watching that tiny flying saucer land inside the skull of the president inside his face.
They said, take me to your leader.
And went straight to it, to the core of the president himself.
That was a, you know, what a colossal screw.
Being microneon neutron people, they travel at nearly the speed of sound.
To them, it's a slow pace.
They slammed into our leader.
And then they exhume his brain.
They steal his brain for all this conspiracy stuff.
And where's his brain?
That's where the brain went.
Stuck in the damn brain trying, hey, let us out of here.
And they're still giving commands to that brain.
And it's decomposed.
And where the hell are they?
Yeah.
I mean, you know the answers to that question.
Well, I think that the Onassis thing is a little bit more complicated.
I think the Onassis family could probably tell you more about those aliens than any other group on Earth.
Oh, I guess the fridge is full of them.
The fridge is full over there of the little tiny glimmer.
Actually, Princess We should probably be able to tell us a bit.
She's the queen of all the UFOs.
But she has so many subjects that I know it's hard for her to keep track of.
Well, she's wearing pantyhose right now, so I don't know.
Red ones, Christmas red ones.
Princess We, are you all Christmassy looking?
Well, I guess I really don't know.
She doesn't even know that she's hovering.
Talk about the mistletoe.
She's wearing a whole damn mistletoe over her head.
And it's ready to take off, buddy.
Oh, man.
She's wearing one of them psychic ICBMs that's headed right for Dallas right now.
And she's also wearing them long, long sticky fishnet stockings.
The ones with the one of them pump heels and stuff like that.
And I guess, what do you call that little Santa Claus number thing?
What is that?
Well, it's...
Popcote.
The space goddess saved.
I'm telling you.
It's fluffy.
Boys, if you haven't signed up for your Church of the Subgenius membership, you don't know what you're missing.
Really?
Because when Santa comes, I mean, he really comes.
Or she comes.
You know what I mean?
He holds his big red sack up down your chimney.
You better be ready.