The Hour of Slack!
That was the Ballad of Oshama.
Wait, wait, don't start anything yet.
Okay, we're pretending we're getting ready to try and be funny in one more minute.
Yeah, let's do that ritual we do when we're about to get funny.
Hey, I'm really sorry to the young lady who came up and left the pictures from the guys on DJ A's show.
I mean, if you just would have showed me those pictures, I would have said,
yeah, cool, you can wait.
So, I don't know if you're listening, but I'm really sorry that I didn't let you stay in the station.
But, you know, it's weird up here.
You know, put yourself in my shoes.
Someone just knocks on the door and wants to hang out.
Smelly shoes.
Smelly shoes, yeah.
No, you didn't have to.
But, you know, so, but come back in a half hour.
I'm sure DJ A will be downstairs, talk to him or whatever.
But if you're listening, I'm sorry.
He just called up and called me a jerk and she sounded like she was crying even.
She wanted, he wanted to smell.
Smell your feet, girly.
And you, and you let him on and then you slapped his knuckles like a, like a rude stunt.
Somebody that was just here.
We just have security things that we have to pay attention to here.
That's all.
You know.
I was just following the rules.
Are you talking about just tonight?
Yeah.
I saw her leaving.
Oh, well.
I saw her escorted from the building.
If she's listening, I thought she was kind of cute.
I thought she was more kind of.
And she was all dressed in camo too, man.
Yeah, the same one I saw.
She was on a mission.
Yeah, you know that.
But she did, she did look pissed off and suspicious of me.
Like, what the hell are you doing in here?
I was looking at her like, what the hell are you doing in here?
Because there's usually nobody here but the dead guys and Dave.
Well, she showed me part of her brain.
Unlike the dead guys who she just walked by letting.
You got to see her brain?
Her alacrity perfume waft by their buttocks.
Whoever you are, I'm sorry.
They're frozen.
I was imagining what her brain would look like.
I'm sorry that the envelope had the pictures of the guys on the radio show.
That's on after me.
I would have, you know, been totally okay.
And well, maybe even, I don't know.
It's hard to tell what you're going to do in those crisis situations.
You know what I mean?
Well, there's a lot of mad bombers running around in camo outfits these days.
What are these mad bombers?
Mad patriots, mad anti-patriots, and mad magazine readers all wearing camo.
I'm one of the mad magazine readers.
There's also a lot of muscular gorillas around wearing their.
Camouflage perversely.
I must say.
And I'd love to see their brains.
No, you know what I mean?
They're like, I could see it.
They're fessing, you know?
Yeah, I know.
But it's like they're, they have that vibrant animal brain.
You know that inside.
Oh, it's good for sucking.
If you could look inside.
Okay, dig this.
Some of those chicks heads, you'd see the nastiest.
Okay.
What do you think about this, man?
One, two, three.
The devil's after me.
Four, five, six.
He's always throwing sticks.
Seven, eight, nine.
He misses every time.
Hallelujah, hallelujah, amen.
Nine, eight, seven.
I'm on my way to heaven.
Six, five, six.
Five, four.
I'm almost to the door.
Three, two, one.
The victory thou wilt won.
Hallelujah, hallelujah, amen.
If you ever attempt to use LSD.
Bring him to his drive.
Maybe cost you your life.
And use up all your gold.
Well, hey, you know, I used to do that too.
An LSD monkey on his back.
That's his scary monkey.
The green monkey.
Yeah.
A multicolored moon saw.
I'm listening.
You remember those LSD monkeys?
The ones with the little purple rectums?
Or was that a gibbon?
Dude, I was one of those LSD monkeys.
Oh, man, you were so lucky.
I tried for 13 years to get that gig.
Well, yeah, I joined the army.
It was part of the, you know, I was one of those experimental monkey guys.
They gave the LSD to.
Did you get the special powers?
Yeah.
That's how I became a man.
Did you get to fly?
Or were you just like one of the walking monkeys?
No, I was just a monkey.
I was just a purple-budded yellow monkey.
I'm a Christ, man.
I was a monkey.
That's all.
I was just a freaking little monkey.
Now I am a man and a brother.
Am I not a man and a brother?
Go, go, gorilla.
Yeah, that was a time when you was all monkeys.
Yeah, that was a long time ago, but it's not so long.
We've all got that memory, don't we?
Yeah, yeah, sure.
Somewhere in the back of the piney oak land.
Somewhere where you're far away from everything.
Maybe sticking your feet at the edge of the beach.
Relax.
Would you rub my feet while I...
Sure.
Oh.
Just one poor monkey doing that won't smell anything.
Oh, squeeze harder, Dave.
Oh.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, don't ya?
Hey, you hear this guy?
Oh, man.
Calm down, calm down.
Here, have a little one.
Here, too busy singing to put anybody down.
Oye.
I did not agree.
Oye, unos tardes.
God has given this...
Deben decirle alguna cosa.
A message of faith.
Pre-warriors!
It was magnificent.
I'm glad you liked it.
I don't know if I can do this!
Please, please.
Oh, no!
It's killing me!
I don't know if I can show me anything!
Where there is war, dear friends, there are doctors.
The doctors did this to me, and I shall explain.
Way back when the day was 1980, when the first subgenius clenches were forming in the wilds
of America. In darkest Arkansas, there arose a new type of creature, the subgenius doctor band.
A Dr. Snavely Eklund, owner of Beans and Grains and Things health food store in Little Rock,
who could play no instrument, started a subgenius band with his employees, Pope Sternodox,
Gene Sply, St. Jane or Hypercletes, Martin and Linda Pitt, and others.
In Dallas, co-subfounders Dr. Philo Drummond and myself, with the Helswami Satellite Weavers,
emulated Doctors for Bob with our band, Doctors for Wotan.
The San Francisco Doctors, like Puzzling Evidence, Lies, and Gary Gabrogkran formed the band that dare not speak its name.
These were giants.
But they were not the only ones.
There were many others.
In the meantime, the lone subgenius in Los Angeles, St. Byron Werner,
while making his now-famous music collection Space Age Bachelor Pad,
created, using his Museum of Bull Dada Record Albums,
the ultimate doctor-oriented audio collage tape,
which was incorporated into the subgenius media barrage called Bad Doctors,
the ancient 1980 reel-to-reel tapes of which I have been tweaking up.
In digital format, to intersperse with our recent ESO Swamp Radio live broadcasts from WCSB Cleveland.
There were doctors on the earth in those days.
Great combination, isn't it, Jim?
What's that?
Armful of narcotics and a loaded gun?
Let her go, Bob.
Boy, did we get high.
Yes, sir.
We sure got relaxed.
A physician must determine if tendon repairs are needed.
There it is.
But if the chief ever caught me taking these pills, he'd snap my head off.
Here, try one of mine.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah, the chief himself's been on these for a week, and he's a changed...
Our favorite area for clairvoyance...
...has always been in the field of science and medicine.
What's your trouble, young man?
The Venusian goop rod, Doctor.
Now, see here, young man, my time is valuable.
Doctor, this is a medical emergency.
I hope you like that nonsense.
I try to make the audience a part of the entertainment, and they go along with it all just great.
That chatter with the doctor is no phony bit, really. It's just the way it happens.
You'll have to make it in one night when you're down Florida way.
All right, nurse, bring the next patient in.
Get up on this table.
Pull off that gown.
Raise up that right leg, let that left one down.
Pull off them stockings, that silk underwear.
The doctor's got to get you, mama, Lord knows when.
Doctor.
All inner or non-existent void particles.
You can send negro-influenced voice waves, tap-shoe disc patterns.
You can send us cow vomit, tooth broken, leaven-gated, elongated, creation-oriented,
spear gum, restaurant scars.
You can send us...
Niki.
Don't look at me that way, Douglas.
You're mad.
Don't be frightened, Douglas.
You're about to see what service do we call.
Give me down your arm!
Doctor.
Good night, Docs.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Make me take off my clothes and make me go out normal, and I have to go outside and check.
I've got to change before I come here.
Do you love your parents?
Yeah, I love them, but they're...
In countless schools across the land, mere infants are taught all about contraceptive techniques
and are provided with a plastic phallus in the classroom upon which they are trained to fit rubber...
Did you hear what he was saying?
I don't like that last sound.
The Lord is my shepherd.
No, that won't do.
All right, close your eyes, please.
And repeat this prayer after me, right out loud.
Ing, ing, ing, ing, ing.
Like this.
Ang, ang, ang, ang, ang.
Eve, meet, concrete, eel.
End, pet, let, lend.
Dude Hughes, do you choose to toot?
In some cases, the individuals who have come have tried various things,
but they've failed.
I love rock and roll.
So put another dime in the jukebox, baby.
And then because we are Christians or Americans or something, I don't know just why, we began
to get conscience pains.
And we began to hear people say, well, don't just do something, stand there.
No.
We're ready for a TV.
He's got a rod that's about two foot long.
Went to the doctor.
Doctor says, shy, I'm going to have to cut your dick off.
He said, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Shy said, doctor, said you better cut it off down to the motherfucking bone.
Because if you leave any meat, I'm going to fuck right on.
Let her go, Bob.
And I predict that our local American doctors will go on strike and be replaced by African
witch doctors.
Beach party, beach party.
It never stops.
I'm tired of this nightclub.
This is the beach party.
This band is so bad.
It never stops.
Why do I have to pay $5 every night to stay alive?
Beach party will destroy.
Well, how many times do we have to play this worst song over and over and over again?
OK, what do you think about this, man?
Did you hear about the rave act?
Psychoskeptical.
The rave act.
The rave act now is a federal law.
We're not talking about a city law, a state law.
We're talking about a federal law.
And what does that do?
Federal law is something.
It now outlaws those glow sticks.
What?
Glow sticks are now illegal?
I am not kidding you.
You fuck.
Look it up.
Little skulls that you had on your dashboard are now illegal also.
If you're at a rave and you have a glow stick, it is considered drug paraphernalia.
Well, of course.
They look so good on drugs.
But they don't have anything to do with taking drugs.
Well, I think it's from Somalia.
Bottled water, I am not kidding you, is now drug paraphernalia at a rave.
But dig this.
A rave promoter cannot put on a rave legally without providing water.
But you can't give it in bottled water.
So I guess you get a trowel going or something, you know, a trowel.
Chronic pelvic pain or abdominal pain.
It's only if you buy store bought.
In rave.
Wearing a trowel.
And then you put lights on your body of any sort is considered drug paraphernalia.
A joystick and a bumblebee.
Because only drug users like lights on their body, right?
I don't know how you smoke anything with a glow stick.
I don't know how you snort anything with a glow stick.
Well, that's terrorist paraphernalia.
A glow stick has now been used by Al-Qaeda.
They know it for nutrition.
Okay, here's another one.
Here's another one.
Well, it's true.
I know, this is true.
Here's another one.
It's science fiction.
No, I'm taking this out of the news this week.
This is science falseness.
And we all know how false science can be.
I'm not kidding you.
The rave ad.
And there's rave kids in my class who knew all about this.
I thought that was act three of scene four.
We had a great discussion.
I don't care if it's Henry V.
All right, here's another one.
It is now legal for the CIA to kill Americans overseas if they think they're involved with
terrorists.
Well, thank God for that.
We can have Chuck Beres go out there and slap him.
Slap him with a whoopee stick.
Or one of those glowing sticks they use at the rave.
Did you know Chuck Berry was a former CIA agent?
A contract killer.
No way.
No, I knew Elvis was, but not Chuck Berry.
Well, they both shared the same plane cabin.
I'm a number of-
Chuck Beres was working for the CIA.
And I was sitting there with a bunch of other radio television hosts.
I was telling them that I'm a great ad.
Yeah, they're wearing glow sticks.
They're not your body.
I'm having bottle-clawed forehead.
I'm a little bit of a
I guess the kids like to put Vapo, mixed Vapo rub inside of there just for a check.
It is quite a trick.
And my mom said that is now illegal.
All right.
Let's get you vocal rubs are now illegal.
What is part of the plan?
We've got sour drop candies.
My wife and I, when we're dancing it right.
I've got my-
We've got to use those super sour drop candies to stay-
What about the Fizzy Pop?
Right, same thing.
Well, those are illegal also.
Those are illegal.
Those drugs are terrorists.
The Fizzy Pop candy.
Yeah, they're terrorists.
That's got to be a drug paraphernalia.
Every time I went to a rave on drugs, I wore clothing.
And I didn't have any of that.
You can cut your ecstasy with the Fizzy Pop.
Well, you can hide the drugs in your clothes.
So how can they, I mean-
Your clothes came to the front.
I just closed my-
My clothes came to the front.
Look the other way.
They don't know that you can only just chew on your collar and you stand like this.
Like my shirt, like my shirt, and I didn't.
My watch isn't sold out.
I can't believe it's such a good thing.
It's on the way now as it's a quarter after K-
It's rather interesting, though, that the CIA can now legally kill Americans as they
so desire anywhere in the world.
Well let's-
They can legally do it now or-
Or as they're able to-
Forever.
Yeah.
Ever.
At a rave.
If you're wearing a glow stick at a rave, the CIA can now...
Now, if she can make a run for it.
Get colors and signs and...
It doesn't at all.
It's just young kids dancing and having a good night trying to, like, you know, get some, you know, nookie on the side there.
There's another thing that's now illegal.
You know, I think that's why it's now illegal at rave sessions.
Also, if you...
That's why they're passing these laws, because those people never get laid.
And that's just that the young people are, you know, having all this fun.
Well, it's kind of sexy and all that stuff.
I mean, they thought they nipped us in the butt.
You know, they brought out AIDS and they thought, well, this is slow now.
Well, there you go.
There's two more legal exceptions for nips in the butt.
They're talking both, not only the internet, but me time, like, you know, when I'm sober.
Anyway, let's go.
Okay, here's the topic.
It's outlawed.
I haven't called it.
I'm going to carve a little booty.
Now, did you say you were on LSD now?
Do you want us to talk you down?
No, I feel like I'm on LSD.
Listen to this joke.
Well, that's the point.
We're trying to induce that.
We want to create flashbacks of those people that have them.
But if you get in a bad trip, we can talk you down.
We have the expertise.
Put on some Allman Brothers.
So tell me, are you tripping now?
LSD trip.
This is your essential.
Okay, well...
Let me ask you something.
Does that mean you know the experience of being on this drug?
Yes, I do.
Can you tell me what that's like?
Being on LSD?
Yeah.
You don't know.
What was that like?
I was shot out of a cannon for six hours.
Being shot out of a cannon.
While listening to the show, right?
Yeah.
Of course.
While the show goes raging through your head.
How long ago did you do this?
In fact, it never happened.
LSD?
Yeah.
A couple years.
Yeah, the show was on when you did this.
This show has been on for 20 years.
You took it a couple years ago and it's still going on.
At some point, you heard the show on LSD.
And that's what has happened.
Well, he did about 23,000 hits, you see.
Who did?
But sometimes you never come down.
Awesome.
One time I went up to the top of Dockstock Mountain and I got trapped up there.
I climbed up to the very, very tip top.
I took every kind of drug, no demand.
I got so high, I was like smoking banana peels.
I was scraping up the inside of every kind of weird seed, you know, those Hawaiian wood
ropes.
Those seeds, weird stuff.
Yeehaw.
Those will make you crazy.
And finally, I was so high at the top of Dockstock Mountain that I couldn't come down.
Off the mountain or off the high?
I was stuck up there.
Well, both.
I mean, the mountain is symbolic for the high.
Phineas Narco knows that feeling.
The mountain is just a metaphor.
Have you ever done a port-a-potty at Grateful Dead concert?
You mean like snorted port-a-potty?
Which is related to port-a-potty at Burning Man concert.
I've injected port-a-potty, but I've snorted it.
As a ranger, I've had to peel.
Peel people's minds out of the port-a-potty.
I snorted some port-a-potty one time.
Some bad, that blue stuff, man.
Don't do that.
It'll really rip your nose.
It's like little fish hooks.
It's like snorting fish hooks.
You have to dilute it with something.
You can't just take great port-a-potty.
You gotta mix it up with something.
Yeah, you gotta cut it, man.
You gotta buff it.
Well, you gotta let it crystallize.
I have always used baby powdered milk.
Phineas Narco was always snorting red ice.
Lactose.
Lactic acid.
Shut up or stand up.
That's the main thing.
Station are we listening to?
That would be...
On your radio dial with
me and Berkley.
And the fungus shrouded valley.
Don't touch the fungus.
You'll get so high, man.
You'll get so high, you can't come down.
Too late.
No, no, no.
And then you know what?
As soon as you get so high, you can't come down.
You have to move your tent.
I will.
There's a new other place.
Then you have to come back your tent and all your stuff.
So now all your stuff's in the tent.
And your tent's all up and you're too high.
You can't do anything.
In fact, you don't even pack your tent.
You just pick it up off the ground.
Come on, we gotta go.
If I could move the tent, I would move the tent.
You just drag the tent.
I have the intent to move the tent.
Some people just drag their tents behind them.
Some people would just pick up the tent and throw it in the truck.
And one guy is driving your car and he's so high that he can't breathe.
He's on tenterhooks.
He's like laying out of the side of the truck.
He's on a truck.
Dragging along the ground while the tent is being dragged behind the truck.
Somebody put bomb right under the word stop.
It's all over Arkansas.
Well, you can get anything.
Everything's possible.
I mean, assuming that it doesn't violate the law of identity or existence.
Blob stop.
Oh, I want to go to that movie.
In Amsterdam, it's November, but I'm not going to miss it.
Why?
Hydrate the kitty cat.
Yeah.
Awesome.
KPFA.
Dr. Hal Puzzling Evidence.
Philo Drummond and special guest Phineas Narco.
And now, back to the doctors.
Back in time to 1981 Byron Werner's Doctor's Collage and even Dr. Neuroberger.
Doctors for Bob.
Endocrinologists for Bob.
Farmers for Bob.
Gynecologists for Bob.
Carichristiners for Bob.
Illustrators for Bob.
Jailors for Bob.
Kidnappers for Bob.
Lawyers for Bob.
Mothers for Bob.
Neurologists for Bob.
Doctors.
Doctors Doctors.
Doctors for sane CCP.
Doctors for you.
Doctors for the mind of the doctor.
Doctors for the...
Doctors for Wotan.
Doctor for Wotan.
You have assumed control.
Your mind is no longer your own.
I have no mind.
My mind is not my mind.
Cast off the imperialized brains of normalcy!
You do what I do!
Cuz Bob told me to!
You do, what you do, cuz you want to!
I do what I do, cuz Bob told me to!
I do what I do, cause Bob told me to.
Let it go, Bob.
I told you, I want to see Dr. Hold-I-Read-Gypsy-Doctor.
Oh, wait a minute. Is that Dr. Repeat-I-Read-Gypsy-Doctor?
Dr. Stang, are you, in fact, a doctor for Bob?
I'm a healer, I'm a surgeon, I've got knives, scalpels, gas, pills, anesthetics, and musical instruments I don't know how to play. I am a doctor!
A doctor for Bob?
We bring him back to life and then we kill him again!
I went and seen myself a doctor. And he gave me a great big bottle of...
Don't take him there, kid.
Stop!
He's been killed, he's awake!
It's probably time for a little stimulation there, cadet. So why not get up and move a little? Comedy is comedy, but some rhythm tossed in can do anything but help. Let it go, Bob.
Whoa! They say the biggest headache, the biggest appeal, baby. Call me the big peel.
We're here to make dark with the War Change Jam with the Pub Network Chicago, and I'd like to know if St. Sulu-Lac of the Hogwoods are in the way.
Are you a doctor for Bob?
I am! This is the beginning of a new life for me as a saint of the hog butchers of the West. As a new man, I'm free! I'm free!
Yes, but are you a doctor for Bob?
This proves it! The fact that I'm a doctor for Bob proves that I'm free. Only a doctor for Bob can be free.
Thanks, Bob.
Dr. Bob, don't let him kill you.
I do what I do, cause Bob told me to.
No, I don't believe the charges of brainwashing here. I've been labeled as a subdued surgeon.
I do what I do, cause Bob told me to. You do what you do, cause you want to.
I don't use such techniques as brainwashing, uh, brain surgery in order to assure loyalty.
There's another better version here.
Dave can translate.
Votions?
We have a guest.
As the words in German, I'm...
Hurry up, baby. The dog is running.
Hurry up, bus.
My heart, my heart is humping.
Okay, we're surrounding the sushi shop.
Pumping, I think she said.
We're surrounding the sushi shop.
Sushi shop.
Looking for gas.
Fugu, too.
Then we jump up in the air.
And...
She said a song.
We goose a noon.
What she said?
A ganoon.
Those Finnish bands do these rock songs about mundane stuff like waiting for the bus.
They're singing about cardamom me bread right now.
I think they're singing about cardamom me bread.
Don't they have a cool word for cool? Like, cool.
Do we got any chai?
It is so cool.
It's spelled K-U-U-L-L.
You're in the cool hole.
I'm in the sea hole.
Cool hole, man.
Well, you are speaking of the sea hole. What is in the news today?
A huge, a huge opening in the ocean floor that is engulfing very many species of foul underbird.
You're not the underbird, the overbird.
Oh, baby, I see your sea hole opening.
Yes, when you see it, it's already too late. For you, anyway.
It's Sakiwara.
You don't hear of this? You don't know about this phenomenon?
Yeah, they suck you right in.
That's why most guys in Finland play in bands.
Is to get away from the sea hole.
To get into the sea hole.
Into the sea hole.
To flush, to be flushed and sucked down the sea hole.
I have personal experience of how they shoot.
Cool hole, because it's cool, you know.
And all Finns speak that.
Cool hole.
Like this.
We shoot the Russian.
Euro music.
Then we shoot the Russian again.
The goddamn Russian music.
And blow up the steam bath.
So we shoot the Russian again.
That's a real one, though.
I was born.
Oh, we're from the New Dakota.
Let's return to John Walters holds the office of director of the office of director of the office of director of the office of national drug czar.
What's it all about?
I think we want money.
John Walters holds the nation's drug czar.
I recognize.
My pleasure.
And we push back together.
But we want money.
Thanks for being here this morning.
My money outside.
John Walters.
Sorry.
Thanks.
So they might be.
I'm a doctor for Bob.
And let me say that prior to this moment, I had the least ability to understand the doctors for Bob of any subgenius in the church.
But tonight, with our artist elimination experiment being such a success, I truly feel that I am for the first time a true doctor for Bob.
But Bobby is bigger than I.
You're the best doctor for Bob.
Oh, I think he's caught it.
Doctor, give him something for his cough.
All right.
Here's a quarter.
Oh, that's not much.
Not much of a cough.
Well, thanks, Douglas.
I'll take over.
That's all right.
You'll be yourself again in a minute.
I'm, I'm so sorry, everybody.
Why don't you just drink this.
I knew you were a doctor for Bob.
I am a doctor for Bob.
I'm a mean son killing, wise beast.
And a man.
Asshole, reeman, eardrum split, hell of a doctor's for Bob.
I don't feel well.
What's the matter with you?
Oh, I don't know.
I was the doctor and he told me what to do, but I didn't do it.
He said to take one pill three times a day, but you can't do that.
I think I'd rather die than do that.
Man, it's a gas.
I figure, you know, some of those roaches they put out in grass and the glass acid will put you on the moon in an hour.
But reality, that's where it's happening.
What?
What's the use of pretending?
I can't stand this anymore.
Doctor, doctor.
Doctor, please.
Please, doctor.
Chandler said you went over to Georgia Street to see that doctor.
Yeah, that's right, Ed.
Short visit.
Poor guy.
Pretty bad, huh?
Well, the guy's really a mess.
The beatnik walked up to the epileptic and said,
Oh, I don't hear the music, but go, baby, go!
Here's my million dollars.
Bob's Beach Party.
So genius.
One dollar.
Is that one dollar?
Ow!
All right.
Bob's Beach Party.
So genius.
Beach Party.
Don't I like it?
Do you?
Some genius beach party.
I don't know if that's in commentary.
Yeah, because you see, I see.
Maybe all of the news is just pulling up instead of I'm saying it right.
It's like, we're going to get him.
We're going to do this.
We're going to make it happen.
Everybody in the Russian world is screaming shock.
But yeah, Osama bin Laden is back up.
He's making statements now.
He has another eye on him.
I don't know if I have the resources.
sources going into that.
Trying to find that guy.
And continue to find him.
And the guy who flew the planes into the world
trade center.
He must be many enemies.
He must be.
Give me a break.
What did I do?
That's what you're trying to do.
You're trying to confuse our
top of the mountain.
Yes, he's laughing gently and sharply.
He just read a story.
I know he's ready to punch him.
But folks, that is true.
I mean, why are we then the CIA?
Instead of, you know,
then they go over
and they're going to shoot Americans.
And then that's a great club.
And that would be the end of the world.
When it goes to the ground and water
and you go into federal penitentiary.
Well, it's a known fact that
John Mastrop is a perverse
and an ultimate monkey.
You know, he's been in all those evangelical groups
where he has pursued his mission.
He's going to be a president for the next 10 years.
Well, I mean,
you're saying what they say in other media
like Radio Netherlands, BBC,
Small Radio, Ireland,
France International,
the federal jail in Ireland.
No, no, no.
They're going to invite me to preach.
Please get off the seat.
I'm going to turn you into a man.
They push the right button to push your button
that holds you with more button pushing
to make you a button.
I can't deal with that crap.
Yes, but it's poetry.
It is poetry.
You've got to see that poetry.
I can't just rap and rag that glue.
You've got to recall it.
No poetic.
I know.
All right, I'm sorry.
Well, I'm doing all the right things
to make you shut the door.
Who do you see as, um,
coming out of the door
and slamming back shut?
Actually, that will save your life
for the next 10 years.
Watch, I'm going to go get shot right now
because somebody's in the door.
I'd like to see you reach land
or you're in a sand, folks,
doing the regular deal
at the road to Baghdad.
It's all 43.
If we were to have a USO group
for nowadays, you know,
in 33 seconds.
Right.
Wait.
Evangelical Christians
with very, very long earrings.
Headphones.
The kind that, you know,
they have those bowling ball earrings
that extract the ear stuff.
And, um,
who would be Ben Clausboy
and who would be Jeff Boop?
I mean, Bob,
I've heard that the bowling alleys
are now...
Kuwaiti stuff?
No, bowling alleys
are now trying to outreach
to more people to come in.
And they've made bowling balls
much bigger now.
Well, haven't you seen
the weird W with the K?
The crown on it
on top of the bowling ball logo?
That is an invitation
to every American
and their families
to get out
and blow some more.
So, bowling is...
There's something about that.
The rave clubs.
Now, what if you wore
a glow stick
to the bowling alley?
You would probably
be absconded
by a few shots.
Well, I'm a federal agent.
I would hope so.
I mean, I would hope
it wouldn't be the waitress
because they're armed, too, now.
But if a federal agent
got you,
there'd be no easy coming.
I mean, the kicks
are pretty good.
French fries.
Yeah, I mean,
mashed pizza.
You know what I mean?
French fries,
a little bit of beer.
Yep.
She's packing.
Absolutely written.
What do they call it?
A Mach 9 or Mach 12
or whatever it is.
Yeah.
So, everybody's
packing nowadays.
Heat, we're talking about.
We're talking about
how everybody,
including their own mother,
is armed to the teeth.
And the teeth
aren't included
in the army.
I guess...
No, sir.
I'm not going to
come in
and do the teeth
with arms.
I am toothless
and without arms.
And yet,
you kick me
with that jackboot.
I turn my other
body king
to the sky
and I pray
to whatever
invisible god
may come
to my assistance
to help.
I flinched
because I had
no books
and then I met
a man
who had no arms.
I don't want
to be a general
minister.
I don't want
to believe
names
means
helps
there's
an
let
till
the
day
on
the
planet.
now
is
certainly
that
says
up
there.
have
on
target
received
An Iraqi regime could launch a biological or chemical attack in as little as 45 minutes.
The UN Security Council must be disarmed.
These requirements will be met.
It may be too late.
The danger to our country is grave.
The regime is seeking the future of peace.
We know destructive technologies.
We know hatred.
We are engaged in a deliberate and continuing bad faith and deception.
The United States Congress has waged a war against its neighbors.
It has sponsored and sheltered terrorists.
It's led by a dangerous and brutal man.
He must be stopped.
And our friends and our allies.
When they fully materialized.
The danger to our country is grave.
The Iraqi regime is the only choice.
I want to thank the scientists and Al Qaeda terrorists for their tremendous support.
They have done tremendous work in building nuclear weapons.
Women have been systematically raped on the floor of the Senate this morning.
Political prisoners are made to watch their own children being tortured.
Leaders of the House and the Senate from both political parties after the order was given.
Because they are different faces of the same evil.
To ensure compliance. Period.
The course of action may bring many sacrifices.
Yet delay, indecision and inaction could lead to a massive and sudden horror.
And we will face it together.
I'm confident that members of both parties will violate every pledge to friend an enemy alike.
To escape.
By timely and resolute action we can move incriminating evidence.
Thank you all for coming.
Apocalypse number nine by T. Watts.
Also known as Brainwave93 at Hotmail.com.
201.
1-1-2-1-1.
And I'm all ears.
This is a
famous
In- sausage.
Thank you.
Bye.
video.
Here we go.
Watch this.
Long live the new Flash Man.
So is the
current 20-year-old
is the current
20-year-old ready to
take on the responsibility
of administering theft
around the world?
Is the MTV
generation
ready to kill?
Well, as long as you do it
in a push-button style,
you know,
in their style,
like they've been trained with the video
games, computer games.
Right.
If they can run the robots
correctly,
that's the way to train
a robot.
You have to know how to deal with the robot.
The robot rejects your treatments.
Because the robot didn't have a mother,
so it doesn't help to, you know,
you can't really insult it.
You are right.
In the same way we could insult one of our regular citizens.
A robot does have a
very delicately, firmly-tuned
safe.
It can be violated by certain
statements.
Certain ideas do
rub the robot away.
Oh, my.
And you can't say,
you can't say.
That's a
very much a
habit.
It's not a
What is your major malfunction,
you nut?
Didn't Mommy and Daddy show you enough attention
when you were a child?
In the army,
you can do as you please.
you can soften your knees.
In the army,
You can read me
Go, go, go
Go, go, USA
You guys gotta cross our nose, not hop it
Sorry, sir
Doing my best
Hop it, hop it, hop it
I've always wanted to live in a neighborhood
With you, so
Let's make the most of this beautiful day
Since we're together, we might as well say
You'll be my neighbor
Won't you please
Won't you be my neighbor
I'm glad we're together again
They're all prod of people
Powerful, rich people
Chaz, the wild
Wild, wild
Chaz, I'm looking for the new
But the hour of slack is not.
Continuing with our history of Doctors for Bob,
we first hear the band in its original 1980 incarnation,
little more than animalistic grunting by the great Snavely Eklund,
with fitful primitive drumming on tin cans and shoe boxes.
By contrast, we hear Doctors for Wotan,
with garage sale electric instruments played by non-musicians.
Jane or Hyperclete's ranting in this example.
There's no corpse there.
This is the first composition by the fledgling bassist Pope Sternodox
to gain mass airplay, the Doctors for Bob theme.
Doctors for Bob.
Doctors for Crager.
Doctors for Odie.
Doctors for Wotan.
Doctors.
Doctors for the law.
God!
Stop now!
Uh, yes.
How many more times do we have to listen?
Uh, by 1984.
1984's Doc Stock number one.
All the Doctor bands were destroying all instruments
in songs lasting literally for hours or even days.
They just want to fall asleep.
Yeah, the audience is going in every different direction possible.
Oh, they're sick of them.
They're sick of the Caf Depresso.
Oh, yeah, they're sick of everything here.
They only know three chords, but you're only going to see them play one.
I'm so tired of these guys.
This band's bad.
It's no surprise.
I wish they'd just pack it up and go away.
Well, how many times do we have to play this same song over and over and over again?
Well, how many times do we have to play this same four notes over and over again?
When I carried on the Vistach club, I thought things would be a little bit different.
But it's just the same old band.
In the same stupid shirts.
In the same stupid bleach ahead.
Yeah, they're like, why are we still here?
You think they could do something new after all these years?
But they just play that same song.
They just play that song all night long.
Well, how many more times do they have to play this same song over and over again?
You are listening to The Hour of Slack from Church of the Subgenius, www.subgenius.com.
One chord down.
Rotam music's got me down.
I played in this band for ten hours or so.
I ain't seen my check.
Where's my check?
Oh, where's my check?
Well, how many times do we have to play this song over and over again?
We'll have to ask for that same check over and over again.
Praise Bob and praise the doctors, dear friends.
And it's all at www.subgenius.com.
Over and over and over again.
This sure is a bad band.
They really won't make anybody.
Over and over and over again.
I don't even know why they're playing here.
Nobody likes them.
Everybody wants them to play quiet.
Well, I just don't know about this band.
I just don't know why they do it.
Well, I guess they're supposed to be on the radio tonight.
But I sure wouldn't know if I listened to this crap.
I hope somebody out there is listening.
I hope somebody can hear this band.
This is the international signal of distress.
We need to get out of this.
The poor little tan band.
These guys.
They came all this way.
Nobody wants to hear them.
We need to get out of this.
Well, how many times do we have to play this band?
Next call.
Go ahead.
It's Roger Ministers.
Hi.
Um.
um we we can think it's um they're still gonna die of disease yeah i have a disease
um you know i'm sure i'm sure that's the customs that you see
next call go ahead is your minister
why today oh hooray
how many more times do we have to play this terrible song
i hear it's red and blue give me a box
just like you
never stop
well
soon
two days later
never stop
my mind is not my mind
move on
My mind is not my mind