Ladies and gentlemen, presenting the subgenius of OVSLUG.
I feel real good. And then other times, I feel like I was going to get sick right in my stomach.
Well, that doesn't take much doing.
Hello, Bob. I need someone to talk to.
Hello, Bob. It seems there's nothing I can do.
Hello, Bob.
I need someone to listen to me.
I'm hitting all the locked doors and I need some help.
And I was hoping you'd have the key.
Hello, Bob.
Have you been listening to my thoughts?
And I'll tell you all the thoughts.
I've got.
Hello, Bob.
I can't seem to find the truth.
I read the books.
I took the drugs.
And I drank a whole bottle of Verluce.
Yeah.
Hello, Bob.
I seem to have misplaced my slack.
Well, I just can't seem to get it back.
Hello, Bob.
Can you point out what it is I lack?
I've climbed to highest heights, hit the lowest lows.
But now I'm on my back.
Hello, Bob.
Are you still here at home?
Are you in the world's greatest epiphany?
I can hear my heart rate racing in the background.
Even when I got nowhere to go?
Hey, what if I get a pen and ink on the wall?
Excuse me, may I have a
two glasses, please?
What is it?
Hello Bob
Am I coming through to you?
I thought I already paid all my dues
Hello Bob
I know that you can see me through
But it's damp and dim and I can't swim
What am I supposed to do?
Well hello Bob
I'm feeling better now you've listened to me
Hello Bob
Well the sun's out now and I can see
A great change has come over me
My eyes are wise, my thoughts are clear
And I'm as happy as I could be
Yes my eyes are wise, my thoughts are clear
Hello Bob
Dear Bob
Sometimes Bob
Bob
I get so scared
And I don't know why
I just don't know why
But
Sometimes there are things and they're after me, you know?
I mean, it's those kinds of things that, you know, how come hot dogs, you know,
the kind of hot dogs you get at the circus, you know, the kind of hot dogs, why are they so red?
And it's only at the circus that you get that, can get hot dogs of real red.
You know, there's a red kind of, it's more, more, more red.
And sometimes things live in walls, you know, and it gets scary.
Because, yeah, there are some things that are.
They're all better work.
It's a lot better.
Okay.
Is that okay?
That's okay.
I can't hear anything.
I can't.
You know, there's something wrong with this one over here.
Give me some of that noise.
Hey, I need some noise.
Is it working?
I'm number five.
Yeah, we really need some noise.
Hey, what'd you say?
I raised somebody.
I'll check.
What'd you say?
I'm down there.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Did you feel that big devil?
I didn't say nothing.
What'd you say?
Well, you said what?
Hi, officer.
Hey, what did you guys do over here?
No, I mean, we were on.
Get over there.
I saw what you put in your pocket.
Give me that.
Get over there.
Okay, get in there.
Get in there.
The battle for the mind.
how about your voice?
Are you going to allow them to out-shout you?
Are you going to allow them to be heard over and above your objections?
Boring.
Oh, too boring.
Boredom quotient.
Boredom quotient 9 to the 13th.
Wilson.
Warp 7.
Here's Wilson.
She's a Wilson.
Your name's Wilson?
Yes.
Well, I'm glad it's not.
Farmer.
But the Holy Ghost is God's authorized detective agency.
The Holy Ghost is God's high sheriff that has come to restore and get back for you.
Pastor, and be my hero.
Those things that the devil has stolen.
I know, Pastor.
The origin.
The original God.
Don't turn it off.
I've got you.
Oh, I've got to have Pastor Eftley.
He's telling me about the God that has taken him from your heart.
The smile that he has stolen from your lips.
Where'd my lips go?
The dream that he's stolen from your eyes.
I can't feel my lips on my teeth.
They don't all feel the same.
He's come to restore these things.
Pastor Eftley.
Now, son, I want to ask you to be quiet for just a minute.
I don't know anything.
So we can hear Pastor Eftley.
Okay.
As far as I know, you haven't told him.
Have you told him I stabbed anything about yourself?
You haven't.
No.
Then if I know anything about you, it would be because the spirit of the Lord has led me to you today.
Am I right?
Uh-huh.
I've got something for you.
I want you to leave your seat and come here.
Okay.
Amen.
My knowledge, I've never seen this lady before in my life.
I'm not saying that.
I hope she doesn't feel bad if she's come here two or three times.
I hope she doesn't think I've ignored her.
No, I've never been here before.
For a crowd like this, I can't remember everyone that comes to church.
Can you say?
Pastor Eftley, I read about you.
But the Lord told me that he sent you here today.
Pastor Eftley.
And Jesus is passing by for you.
I feel his presence.
Passing by for you.
I want you to take this envelope and hold it open.
I don't know.
This is Jesus.
I'm going to get back to you.
I want you to get back to me.
What a crime how they stole it away.
Oh, the devil wants to steal it from your friend.
But he's hard to keep that devil out of your back pocket.
A step less a thing.
What a shame how they stole it away.
Oh, it's a miracle, friend.
It's a miracle revival starting now.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Perform the salute.
All right, here's how to do the salute.
Yeah.
See?
Ready?
The finger is on the neck.
Hands, left hand up.
Up and down.
Left hand up.
Finger on throat.
Come on.
All right.
Perform the salute.
Yeah.
Excellent.
It's a miracle.
I think before we start the service,
we should have just a moment of noise.
Ah!
Yes, I can feel it.
The spirit.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Bullets can't stop them.
Oh, bullets can't stop them, friends.
No.
The mark of the beast?
Oh, you don't need to worry about it.
You've got your credit card.
It won't do you any good tomorrow, but it's okay.
Well, I guess now Bob's going to have to work through me, friends.
So, we're going to...
...snow mixed with freezing rain and rain.
We're going to...
...and we're going to...
...through the afternoon.
...on...
...we're going to...
...go...
...to...
...no accumulation at mid-morning.
...no accumulation...
...it's all right.
... affair,
fun...
...is that the suffines...
of the foreign city someone dropped onto...
...ne contestants.
No.
...pointing itself so far
that no one got worthy.
Go...
We don't need to get in trouble, friends.
... interpreter...
Sometimes I've got these rats, and they're like inside my stomach,
and I haven't swallowed them.
I mean, they're like hot, hot, hot dogs, but they're eating their way out,
and they're coming out, and sometimes I just want to take these hot dogs
and just shove them, and just shove them away.
I'm taking these hot dogs, and I have to go.
But please, Bob, send me some more pills, Bob.
Please, Bob, send me.
Some more.
Send me some more of those pills, Bob.
God, Bob, Bob.
Bob.
Oh, oh, Lonesome Bob says,
you got to get some pills.
Oh, Lonesome Bob.
Just telling me.
Oh, yeah.
Just give him some more pills, and Bob will kill you.
Oh, so long.
Be mine.
I'm upset.
But sometimes I just, I don't feel too good, you know?
I mean, I really don't feel real good.
And I don't know why.
But Reverend Booney says, my head is obsessed with the anti-bomb.
Oh.
And I don't really know what he means.
And so that's why I'm talking to you directly, because he isn't of much help.
But Bob says, if you don't give me some money, you just.
Oh.
Won't ever get any slack.
And then, you don't get no slack, you can't get no money, no food, and no pills.
So what we have there really is two rituals going at once on the radio.
It's a miracle.
What can we say?
We're used to them by now, but it's definitely miracles, and we've got proof.
Yeah.
It's amazing.
It's a miracle.
Signs, signs in the heavens, signs in the earth.
the earth we're seeing the signs everywhere and they still seem to be
washing the implements on the other side in this blood of the lamb
class
¡don use kwe punishment!
The cockatiel Doctor
!
And we'll all come back over men, we'll all come back over men, we'll all come back over men, or nobody for why.
Praise Bob, tell me Bob, I want to buy from Bob, I want to buy and ask the holy war fulfilled, the big boys and the gomels.
We can make them buy and we'll all come back over men, we'll all come back over men, we'll all come back over men, we'll all come back over men.
And we'll all come out over men, if we don't come out over men, there ain't no reason why.
All wives, gizms, they will fall beneath our laser blades, and we'll all come back over men, we'll all come back over men, we'll all come back over men, in victory for us.
Praise God.
And I don't care, I don't care if people laugh at me.
I did, Bob.
He ain't no man.
He ain't no God.
I don't want to walk the path that Bob's trod.
Ain't no man, ain't no God.
I don't want to walk the path Bob's trod.
Okay, let's do it right this time.
And people ask me, where do you get this energy, this life I see glowing in you, Jander?
And I just point it up.
And I don't even have to say it.
I won't even say the word Bob when I said it.
But I just point at the sky.
Because it's not me that's doing it.
And you know and I know who it is.
It's Bob.
Now we take you into a great Holy Ghost revival that is now in progress.
Bill, you want to say something to the clinch?
To the Dallas clinch?
It's too pink and they refuse to comment.
If they're so hip, what are they doing in Dallas?
We can put on the Bob tune tape and sing along.
Doctors for Bob.
You need your harvest.
Yeah.
Copters for Bob.
Proctors for Gob.
Bloctors for Snod.
Bloctors for Bob.
Doctors for Bob.
Sphincters for Bleed.
Sphincters for Bob.
I have something weird on my tongue.
Pills.
Pills for Bob.
Everything I know in my life.
Give me some of them pills, Bob.
That damn pickup gun run over my wife.
Got the blues cause Bob let that pickup run over my wife.
Hey, you got three points for hitting that hippie, girl.
Bob stayed fine.
He did.
He'll get a couple more.
If both stuff buttons gone wrong we'll be fine.
I'll believe you.
If both stuff buttons go wrong, you'll be fine, Rob.
That's what it is.
It's the fucking volts noises.
What's that?
effect on the sensitive youth who became, thanks to the pharmacy's wares, a chronic
alcoholic at age six. It didn't affect his precocious salesmanship, however. And he made
his first small fortune selling stolen prophylactics and other things to high school boys.
Wash it out, Bob. Freak it out, Bob. Zap it out, Bob. Hook it out, Bob.
Slarp it out, Bob. Slurp it out, Bob.
Munch it out, Bob. Punch it out, Bob.
Scrunch it out, Bob. Hunch it out, Bob.
Tear it out, Bob. Mutate it out, Bob. Slack it out, Bob.
Arf it out, Bob. Kill me, Bob.
Thank you. Thank you, Sterno.
Coming up next, we have the original Doctors for Wotan album, which is called Doctors for
Negi. And the song,
I'm driving a car,
Bob sold me.
You're so damn married.
Mac?
What do you mean, ha, ha, ha?
Take that pipe out of your mouth.
What are you grinning about, buddy?
Where'd you get that haircut?
Are those dots on your face, or have you got some kind of disease?
You look like Ward.
You look like Ward Cleaver.
I'm leaving.
You look like Mark Trails.
What's the deal, buddy?
You look like Mr. Appleton.
You look like Big Van Dyke with a pivoted mouth.
What?
What'd you say?
Did you say, yeah, sure.
Sure, I'll buy that used car.
I'll buy that used car from you, mister.
Sure, anything.
How much do you want?
How much is it?
It's only a dollar?
That used car is only a dollar?
Wow.
Wow, you got any other good deals, mister?
You got something else that'll only cost a dollar?
A little booklet?
I don't know, that doesn't look like it's worth a dollar to me.
Oh.
It does have a lot of print inside.
And some neat pictures.
Sure, I'll give you a dollar, mister.
Here.
Whoa.
I feel weird.
I feel, I feel really weird.
But I feel kind of, I feel, I feel kind of good.
I like this.
This little book.
Hey, where'd you go, buddy?
Hey, where'd, where'd he go?
Where'd the guy with the pipe go?
Hey, I gotta talk to him.
Hey, what happened?
Hey, buddy, where'd, he took off with my two dollars.
And he left me this little book and this car.
Hey, buddy, where'd you go?
I'll get in this car.
I'll start it up.
He left the keys in for me.
Okay, here goes.
I'm driving the car that Bob sold me.
Boy, I can go pretty fast.
Hey.
Hey, that Bob guy's okay.
He made me forget about, he made me forget about Odin for a minute.
That's really weird.
Boy, this car is smooth.
I like the way this feels on the road.
I like the way it feels.
It feels good.
It's throbbing.
Hey, it's leaving the road.
It's going up in the air.
Where's it going?
Hey.
Hey, it's, there's a cloud up in front of me.
A big cloud.
It's got a sign on it.
A big sign.
It says, it says, welcome, welcome to Odin's place.
It says, this is Nirvana.
Wow, Bob.
Thanks.
I can't wait to meet Odin.
Really.
Hey, Mom.
Yeah.
I love it when you're together.
You know that, Bob like, Zhao?
Thanh Phah.
identities of the Empoweracio한테's très bon tus fam Cath To my Tyrocuses.
Troke some the me that are following me.
The world looks okay to me
Oh, the world looks to you
Like some kind of big mess
Put a barbed line, fold on
The world looks to me
Like a nice place to be
Cause I got my barbed line, fold on
Like some kind of big mess
Bob's my friend and he's leading me somewhere
Is he waiting there for me?
He's not waiting for me
Bob's my friend and he's leading me somewhere
Oh, the world looks to me
What is waiting there for me?
Bob can stop the aliens from killing me
Bob can save me, but will he?
Bobby, Bobby, Bobby, Bobby, Bobby, Bobby
Bobby, Bobby, Bobby, Bobby, Bobby, Bobby, Bobby, welcome
What is waiting there for me?
Bob
Thank you
Doctors for Bob!
Doctors!
Meet Doctors for Bob!
Doctors for Bob, ma'am!
Can you name Doctors for Bob?
Are you sure you know Doctors for Bob?
Praise Doctors for Bob!
Can you name the Doctors for Bob album?
What is subgenius?
It's Doctors for Bob!
Can you name the Doctors for Bob album, ma'am?
You think you can know the subgenius without knowing Doctors for Bob?
Well, you're wrong!
What is Doctors for Bob?
Doctors of Bob!
I ain't no Bob, y'all!
Doctors for Bob!
Yes, about half the people I know will enter the before-life in the 80s.
Millions will die in a small nuclear skirmish with China in 1988.
Russia will invade Iran, Turkey, Africa, and of course Israel,
and there will be plenty involved.
Draft wars in the US.
Look for a tenth member to join the common market,
called by war.
A bad nuke accident in New York City.
Rockefellers will finally be implicated.
Long-spread famine in 86 and 87 when the 13 and 17 year locusts emerge.
Acid rain tough times the big screens.
German war in South America.
The great reformer, actually the Antichrist, enters Jerusalem through the East Gate
and is made superhuman after miraculously recovering from a head wound.
He starts the one world government which can only be stopped by a one world religion.
Russia develops an era of German educated only non-twined locusts.
Big Massacre.
The Great Rebellion.
This is Kevin Wilson of the Abominations from Boston.
I batter myself after 66.
I don't want to be nobody's Carolina.
They take me on a ship.
Put me on a motor.
Let me out in the water.
Let me go.
Cause I'm a subgenius.
Let me go naked in the park.
Let me feel like my head's coming apart.
I don't know.
But I have been told.
Everybody thinks that people gotta get old.
But I don't believe it.
Cause I'm a subgenius.
I take everybody for what they're worth.
I don't make no exception.
I don't like it when people try to talk back to me.
Cause I'm a subgenius.
I'm a subgenius.
I don't want you to get away from me.
You better like me for what I am.
If that isn't what pleases you.
Better make it right for me.
Cause I'm a subgenius.
And I'll never be a subgenius.
I'll drag you out like St2p2 or something.
You feel one close to get it before you know it.
But one night in the park.
And that night my friends can never get to see me again.
Cause Jesus sprayed upon my demás life own relics.
Cause I'm a subgenius!
But I don't believe it
Cause my head's coming apart.
Cause I'm a subgenius.
© BF-WATCH TV 2021
Well I never found Bob that day, they said he just had gone away
He was out to lunch or off to get shoes or gone buying groceries for people to blues
I must not have been in need of slack cause I never really managed to make it back
But I sent my dollar to those people in town, and I still keep getting them pamphlets sent around
And I feel a little closer and a little more in touch
And I know it's helped me a whole lot of much
But I sure do wish I'd been managing to hang out in the right place to actually catch a look at that
Shotgun order
Out of the face of Bob.
Bob.
Same.
Other reasons why you should buy some genius products.
Reason number one.
I am the one.
Reason number two.
You can know doctors for Wotan.
Reason number three.
We will not suffocate you or your wife with mayonnaise.
This has been a message from the Subgenius Church.
We hope that you will send us money.
Don't forget, if you don't have a check or credit account with the Subgenius Church,
you can send food stamps, money,
uh, Vulcan engine repair parts,
uh, pieces of a meaningless void,
uh,
half-forgotten personality forms,
and or broken tree rot caterpillar dung.
Doctors for Bob.
Uh, you can send brain-locking tree sockets,
or, uh,
Doctor Bob.
tree backwards mouth climb.
You can send
Doctors for Bob.
tunnel, inner, non-existent void particles.
You can send, uh,
Negro-influenced voice wave
Doctors for Bob.
tap-shoot disc patterns.
Uh, you can send us
Doctors for Bob.
uh, cow vomit,
tooth broken,
Doctors for Bob.
uh,
the, uh,
leaven gated, elongated,
uh, creation-oriented,
Doctors for Bob.
spirit gum,
rest-rut,
Doctors for Bob.
scars.
You can send us
Doctors for Bob.
sneaky flakes.
You can send us
Doctors for Bob.
broke,
Black,
Doctor for Bob.
whole, orange,
peel, vision-proof,
Single file,
Doctor for Bob.
single resin,
the,
Doctor for Bob.
Doctors for Bob.
You can send us
uh,
broken,
real chairs,
you can send us
Doctors for Bob.
void,
anti-matter,
form,
reality-shape,
form patterns,
uh,
that do not exist
within the given universe
of those who walk the path
of infinite void,
those who will not
write their names
and addresses
and or social security
numbers on pieces of paper
but can send these
in the forms
of credit cards
and or walking sticks,
broken or fixed,
it can be repaired glass,
it can't be broken mirrors,
however,
if you send us your tires,
be sure to remove them
from the car first,
you can't pay the postage
on anything smaller
than a pickup truck.
Uh,
if you want to send
broken pillows,
uh,
pieces of glass,
you can send out for,
uh,
please order our
handmade robot kits
of genetic findings,
the Venus does have
three life-form patterns,
uh,
these life-form patterns
are on,
uh,
site,
the
uh,
site,
and we ask,
uh,
by the end of the month,
get on your special
off-the-shelf
robot kits
on site,
9900 USD,
and
$100 for
or SMT,
Dr. Heads exist. So if you're gonna come in here wearing a pair of Buster Brown shoes trying to play high school lawyer on you on this
And we don't take no kind of it don't matter what color skin you have
whether you're a white person or
Dr. Spurs Bob
Don't matter to us
We will we know of
Things that you're not yet written within the human mind
Carl Sagan believes I look at art link letter his daughter sent us $2,000 before she jumped off
Avalanche
Some genius
Sabdinias, Sabdinias,
My little fatter half-doodle-do-do
Boo-ba-doob-ba-doo
Sabdinias, Sabdinias,
Do-do-do-do, do-ba-do-do,
Sabdinias
I'll do that one.
I was walkin' over Houston
You could change the name if you want to,
but he sang the song he changed it into a little town.
Just to see what I could see
And the angel, the angel
He was walkin' over me
He was walkin' over Houston
He was walkin' in the air
And I saw my friend was with him
Hallelujah, Bob was there
He was walkin' in subgenius
He keeps me high until the end
For as long as I am subgenius,
I know Bob is my friend
Now I know
Where'er we travel
In travail, Travolta view
Though the Fonz should walk beside us
We know Bob is my friend.
He's with us too
Keep on walkin' with subgenius
Ridin' high before the end
If I always buy subgenius,
I know Bob will be my friend.
And now this third verse ain't necessary,
but if, I know Bob said we should always be ready to sell out,
and if you wanted to play this on a tape or something,
you could stick an ad on me and like this.
Here we go.
Send your doll over to subgenius
So that Bob can love you too
Via Box 1403-06
Dallas, Texas
And 5214
Keep on walkin' on subgenius
I know he knows
And I've been too.
If you're runnin' in subgenius
Bob is runnin' with you too
I didn't have to turn him to the two there in the last, but,
but I just round it that way so as a casual I would have a heart attack if he ever hears it.
And I probably shouldn't have even heard a word of it
Yes, Bob?
Why would yourespond it with the profits to ed,
You are right,ownik.
I know this is real.
I was Кuayn-де-rane.
This was a得 buy if you ever heard a lot about him.
You better watch out.
Better watch out
Don't follow the wrong one, no
Go down the strings again.
There's a good bomb and there's a bad bomb
There's a real bomb and there's a school of bombs
People ain't followed the wrong bomb
Gonna end up with no job
Ahhhhhhhh
là là là là Das davt
à là là là là là là là là là là là là là là
On يعisión
orrava
ha ha ha
ahhhh
Oooooooooooooooooooo
ooooooooooooooo
yi yi
E-I-I, E-I-I, E-I-I, E-I-I, E-I-I, E-I-I, Dr. Sir Bob Walton, oh, die.
E-I-I, E-I-I, E-I-I, E-I-I, Dr. Sir Bob Walton, oh, die.
E-I-I, E-I-I, E-I-I, Dr. Sir Bob Walton, oh, die.
Now we're at Post Office Box 181417, Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118, www.subgenius.com.