🎵
The Soap Genius Hour of Slash!
Remember, remember, remember, we're sitting together listening to this.
And this was pleasing to God.
🎵
Ah, yes, dear friends.
Actually, we should start that one from the...
Let's just listen.
🎵
Ah, yes, dear friends.
Frank Zappa's classic Peaches and Regalia. Beautiful, beautiful piece of music that
many of us of us old folks cut our teeth upon and you know we don't play much
Frank Zappa on the Hour of Slack and it's because Frank Zappa may very well
be what led you here if you're over 30 and you know what we like to do for Bob
is to lead you on to the next thing help the next poor sucker down the line as
Frank himself said and recently I was given to hear of a conversation actually
something I picked up off the internet in which someone had had been griping on
alt Frank fan Zappa or something about how oh you know it's so sad Frank's dead
and Captain Beefheart only does paintings now
and maybe he's dead.
I mean what is what is there left and Zug's Rift our fellow minister and a
great musician Zug's Rift responded that well you know buddy it's not like there
aren't other musicians floating around there I mean are you just as
conservative as that guy that can't listen to anything but Led Zeppelin now
that he's 45 years old?
You know yep.
Frank's dead as a doornail and and the captain has gone on to other things and
he's not gonna make any more music but friends have you bothered to seek out
that Rudy Schwartz project CD or that Zug's Rift CD that Kings of Feedback
that silica gel Reagan's Pollock or even swinging love corpses or Doctors for Bob
have you have you?
Well I'm not sure.
Um Friends I was thinking about that and this is gonna be our nepotistic Friends of Stang music show but don't be afraid because
old Reverend stang has some very talented friends.
um so it will be a musical show a musical show indeed of
people might complain that well I sent my tape to Reverend stang...
It's true that it was unlistenable and I did not want to listen to it...
I did not put any label on it,
and I did mention in my handwritten note on the napkin
that it probably sucked,
but he never played it on his show.
He only plays his friends.
Well, here's why.
bass & drums play in bright rhythm
That was Joe Newman, and that's good music.
We'll be talking about Bob.
We'll have songs about Bob.
We'll have Dr. Bizarre's rap-a-like songs about Bob.
It's all right, we'll have Bob, we'll have Bob.
What are the possibilities of complete music?
Follow us at Mr. Slack.
Boop-bop, beat-up!
Bob is lucky, not smart.
That's for puke from people like you.
Would you F.I.P. to the FBI?
Would you tell to them a dirty lie?
Everything will soon turn out all right
Bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum!
Did you F.I.P. to the FBI?
Would you tell to them a dirty lie?
Slowly slid in both my wrists
Metaphorically speaking, that is.
Bob is lucky, not smart.
In fact, by the perverted conspiracy standards of intelligence,
he is gifted with incredible stupidity.
He lives in a perpetual state of contracted consciousness.
This enables him to act without thinking,
to surf effortlessly on the luck plane,
to float down the fabled path of least resistance.
In fact, to make a million dollars every time he screws up.
A catatonic stupid
Where do you think you're being?
You'll know you'll never again
Cole, what are you doing?
Cole, hi, man.
Hey, how's it going?
Christ, okay.
Oh, you brought me some tapes.
Yeah.
Oh.
From bearing gifts.
Oh, Jesus comes bearing gifts.
St. Andrew.
Cole, Jesus.
What's that noise?
Feedback from my great presence.
I guess either that or my little headphones here.
Tray full of lab mice.
Tray full of...
Now, this is what it's like, friends.
We're on the air, by the way.
See, I've been sitting here.
I've been playing.
This is a...
This is a show of nepotistic friends of ours music.
It's like Joe Newman, Zug's Riff, Negative Land, you know.
No, it's Doerr.
Oh, now, is that my Bryce CD?
Oh, Bryce.
Oh, okay, good.
I was worried about that.
Okay, well, what is this new CD?
Numersonic.
Frequencies of the Beast.
Oh, look at the titles on this.
Hippie Freakout.
The Mark of the Beast.
Creature Double Feature.
Martian.
Girlfriend.
Greetings, Earth.
Hey, I wonder if these are X Day.
This some...
You know what it might be.
Let's see what this letter is.
Tray full of lab mice.
Dear Ivan, I worship you.
I once contributed my little Jesus being crucified on Telephone Pulse collage.
So he's the one who did that.
You must immediately play Numersonic on your show.
Practically, the whole album is your cup of tea if you ever steeped a bag.
I also enclose Unbunny, which may not...
...appeal to your fine sensibilities.
Okay, here, Numersonic.
Make Unbunny and Numersonic household names by tomorrow noon.
My telex operators await your instructions as we just hatched our label yesterday.
I'll make the press kit short.
Unbunny just put out his first album.
He drives a flower delivery truck.
I guess...
It says Goiter Boy is the one to use if I use any of them.
But now the second CD.
Numersonic is the band.
Frequencies of the Beast is the album.
The lead singer is a credit to dementia, having been certified homeless.
Get the...we got another one!
We got another...this is like a...
The ultimate, quote, outsider artist and schizophrenic for the last 20 years.
Yet he's not just a novelty act.
He improvises wildly funny lyrics and sounds like Elvis with a sore throat.
The opening song, Hippie Freakout, will be the...
The smash hit of the album.
Most of the profits go to Paul's coffee fund.
Well, I was just telling that we only played stuff by our friends.
But now here's proof that if somebody sends us something wild enough...
We've never even heard this, friends.
We've...we have...
I hope it's clean.
You're hearing it for the first time just as we are.
Well, we are on tape, so...
You know, I'm lying my ass off to them.
Okay.
Here it is.
Hippie Freakout.
Thinking about a bunch of hippie in the parking lot.
All set out there ready for a bout.
I says, hey, you fellas, you better be careful because someone's gonna holler.
And we're sure gonna start there and we're all gonna shout.
And there's no doubt about it, someone's gonna call the cops.
One guy said to me, he says, hey, mind your business, friend.
This is none of yours.
I says, well, I'm aware of that.
But I'm trying to be concerned for you and what's gonna happen.
If you get caught.
So it doesn't really matter.
One way or another, they didn't seem to care.
I says, hey, listen, you guys.
Don't you realize that we all out here sitting out in the front chair?
So there was a bunch of hippies.
Yeah.
Hippie Freakout.
It's all set to go out there in the parking lot and get ready to do themselves a bout.
So there was this young lady.
I took a look at her.
I says, oh, ho.
Give me a, give me, give me a drag or two.
She says, hey, get away from me.
I don't want nothing to do with you.
She took a shot in her arm and I could see.
I says, hey, you're getting rather kind of dizzy.
She says, hey, hey, you can kiss when the sun doesn't shine.
I says, hey, don't tell me that.
Just do the things on time.
She just starts shaking.
She started wiggling, going from side to side.
She says, hey, come on over here.
You want to be my guy?
I says, hey, what makes you think that I'm any different from you?
Because I have a clean haircut and I just don't seem to know what to do.
She says, hey, man, let that reefer smoke it strong.
Pump that old needle up your arm.
I says, oh, yeah, I surely will.
She says, hey, brother, have a drink.
Have another or two.
This is one thing I want you to do.
Well, friends, we have no idea whether this song goes on for another hour or two or what.
It is definitely a hippie freakout.
Do you believe that you're mine?
You are for few in this particular time.
Do you believe that you seek guidance, understanding?
Do you think of yourself as being somewhat mentally ill and disturbed?
Do you think that your drinking problems will really, really cause you the troubles after all?
Do you really think that you're a drunk?
Do you think that your life is so bad that you know it wasn't?
Do you know what my hands are?
Now.
Yeah, go ahead, Paul.
My outer space machine.
The woman with the eyes so big and bright.
The woman that has to come through in disguise.
Yes, my outer space machine.
Well, friends, this show is a strange show.
We got a bit sidetracked there into some hippie freakouts when Jesus suddenly, right in the middle of being nepotistic,
Jesus showed up with a little bit of a show.
With some tapes or CDs from strangers.
And I went and played them anyway just when I was trying not to be democratic.
I was trying to just stick to my buddies and the graft and grifting of, uh,
Praise Bob Joe Newman and the Rudy Schwartz Project.
Oh, yes.
.
Thank you.
I'm having a heart attack.
Thank you for watching.
She got back to her residence on Sunset Boulevard, where the residue of her love had died through.
I got bit and stoned by a Ned fly, went swelled up into a baby, and floated away up in outer
space like a Jules Verne hot air balloon.
Jacob Barley took a doll axe and bled his tiny trim and all his little friends.
Disney from Starsdale!
That's why I'm having a heart attack!
Can't be the same till I get my baby back.
She's gone and left me broken hearted. Came to stay but now we've parted.
Like a trans-continental island, burning, floating across the seven seas.
Corporeal to cost information and delicate bacteria, chitted in a mustard keg.
Her lover made a beautiful sunset. She's not a lefty, what shall I do?
She got back to her residence on Sunset Boulevard, where the residue of her love had died through.
I got bit and stoned by a Ned fly, went swelled up into a baby, and floated away up in outer space like a Jules Verne hot air balloon.
Jacob Barley took a doll axe and bled his tiny trim and all his little friends.
Disney from Starsdale!
That's why I'm having a heart attack!
Can't be the same till I get my baby back. She's gone and left me broken hearted. Came to stay but now we've parted.
I'm having a heart attack!
Not fair!
Hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it!
Hold it!
Alright.
Zoot Zrift.
Dear friends, uh, that, uh, heart attack.
There by the great Zugz Rift.
And his amazing, um, poo-poo hands is one way to call that man.
Um, and this is also Zugz in the background.
I'm about to give the address of Dr. Zugz Rift and also the address for Joe Newman, okay?
And, um, so you know who to write to for the uncensored versions of these self-same tapes.
Zugz Rift got that pencil right.
And the address already is at...
P.O. Box 18765.
That's Box 18765.
Encino, California.
91416.
Yes.
That's Box 18765.
Encino, California.
91416.
And, uh, to, uh, get information about the, uh, CDs of, uh, tapes of, uh, Joe Newman's Rudy Schwartz Project,
that is P.O. Box 4542.
P.O. Box 4542 in Austin, Texas.
78765.
Yes, friends, it's P.O. Box 4542.
Austin, Texas.
78765.
For Joe Newman and I, yes, while I'm maddened with this great music in the background,
I probably ought to also give the background post office box number for B-B-B-B-Bob, yes.
And, uh, if you haven't memorized it by now, you will.
It's P.O. Box...
140306...
in Dallas, Texas.
75214.
When I say the word start, the test will begin.
Are you ready?
Start.
When was the last time you had your hearing checked?
Uh...
I would advise him to learn to lip read.
Insert earplugs now.
Watch out for this.
Crank it up, dude!
It's not what I'd like to listen to, but I don't think I should be able to tell the other people what they can or can't listen to.
Deafness is not only uncool, it's endurable.
I-I-I've shown my hearing.
Call now and receive a coupon for a free hearing test.
Guaranteed, you won't hear any of this music on Elevator.
It's rock and roll!
Please, go to 11.
If you suspect a hearing loss or thought nothing could be done about it, ask your family doctor.
Feel your eardrums explode!
Oh, my God!
This concludes this hearing test.
Thank you.
I'm your real enemy!
Look out!
Don't you want to be saved?
Fight the real enemy!
All this devil needs to have you, mister, but I won't let him!
What I'm asking people to do is accept that everything they've based their lives on is a lie.
Oh!
Dodgy!
I'm seeking salvation!
According to your beautiful ideals, I'm supposed to crawl away somewhere and die so that you and Bob can be friends.
Oh, there you are.
Bob, we were afraid you wouldn't get here.
Got here as soon as I could.
Oh, Julie.
Say, what is this whole thing all about?
I've got your belt the other way now, Dobbs.
Now, listen to me.
How do you...
Look.
How lucky I am, how lucky I am to have someone like you.
From the beginning right to the end, from the beginning right to the end.
How lucky, lucky, lucky I am.
Bobbie!
Bobby, baby!
Bobbie, bobbie, bobbie!
Robert darling!
LI voy a trapezar Shelley!
Where's our bare head Laz talent двух!
This all just a dream Job's coming home
Aw, motion blur switch!
Ah, Maimura!
Man this's a shame!
Use speech to describe dethrone Slavoj!
No, no, no!
Don't stop me here! Don't stop me here!
Fight the real enemy!
Don't you want to be saved?
Don't you want to be a cop?
We're all looking in the same direction.
We're not seeing quite the same thing.
You're looking at me and I'm looking at you.
But we're all going insane!
We're going insane!
We'll find the God!
Fight the real enemy!
No, no, no!
The mind is good and the heart is free!
Fight the real enemy!
I don't want to preach to people.
Oh, Bob!
Oh!
Turn on.
Tune in.
Why do you want to be normal?
The rupture is upon us, dear friends!
That fateful day,
July 5th, 1998!
Next days are coming!
And the peaks are bumming!
Oh, Bob!
Fun!
When we were born in here in this life
We were destined to make it right
That is prettyatellis
And this is our fate
We're singing this song
So you can read late
We are going to save the universe
This time
We are full grown
We are grown up men
We are all passionate
We came to reason it
It is our mission
It is our task
It's obvious
Yet you still ask
We are going to save the universe
This time
Don't you worry
Don't have no fears
Don't get out of sight
Because the end is near
We can't let
So there's nothing to say
We're in control
And we are more than fine
We are going to save the universe
This time
Well maybe next time
Sure when the rupture hits
We'll all be in our first class window seats
On the pleasure saucers
Watching the
Hey!
Turn on
Turn off
Amplify
You certainly don't want to teach people
Ins 반
N tex days are coming
And pe blacks are coming
And the pigs are bum consequenc
There's a whole bunch of people coming after you
You better stop n try to listen to me
Cause they want to ram a little something up your buns
And they call it the conspiracy
Well, they'll make you think and act just the way they choose
And they'll make you overpay just to sing the blues
And they'll tell you what to say and they'll never go away
Cause they got you in your work and they'll never let you play
Cause they kind of just designed it to work that way
And because of their design, well, it washes out your mind
And you think you're doing fine, but you're wasting all your time
Being very well behaved for the big machine
And they'll tell you what to say, but they'll never go away
Cause they got you in your work and they'll never let you play
Here I am
Stuck in the blood by the man
Here I stay
Free will just drifting away
Smile
And be happy
Here's the American dream
More noodles for you poodles
Means less coffee for your dream
And if you want to make more money
We'll take more of it for ourselves
With your caddies in the driveway
But nothing on your shelves
Get through all the confusion
Of this structured illusion
I get down on my knees
And I pray
Cause Bob is my savior
Today
Yes, I am Bob
The one high exalted master of slack
I am the carburetor of the universe
The rubbery wheels on a child's toy truck
I am the peloton of the universe
The cork of intercourse
I am the force behind all foolishness and humor
The laughter of the raving lunatic
The wisdom of ignorance
The death rattle of the infant of seriousness
I am slack
I have come
And my organ still swells
To spread the legs of your mind
And I will thrust my holy rod
Into the balkans of your kingdom
In your regresions
How merely the
How humble a sea
And iron
And потri
Is 내
Yes, dear friends, Dr. Bizarro there with his opera, his rock opera, The Big Machine.
And I'll give his address in a minute.
Before Dr. Bizarro, we heard, of course, the fantabulous Swinging Love Corpses.
The Swinging Love Corpses with We Are Going to Save the Universe,
interspersed with X Days of Coming and Fight the Real Enemy
by the great Bill T. Miller of Kings of Feedback and Out of Band Experience.
All of these bands have many, many names.
You see also in the background we're listening to a huge voodoo.
And D.K. Jones.
And it is so...
Oh, those addresses.
Okay, yeah.
Dr. Bizarro and the Disgustos.
Write for information from them from iBob Digital.
That box.
This is a P.O. box again.
3-4-0-5, Skokie, Illinois.
Box 3-4-0-5, Skokie, Illinois.
6-0-0-7-6.
Bill T. Miller and Kings of Feedback have an incredible CD
and several tapes available with information from Box 221, Boston, Massachusetts.
That's Box 221, Boston, Massachusetts.
0-2-1-2-3.
Or call 6-1-7-LICK-O-B-A.
Oh, this microphone.
And the sounds, you know.
Sometimes it's...
We get tired.
Even we get tired of hearing some guy
or even some lovely lilting voice of an angel girl
talking about Bob.
And we just want to hear sounds.
And this band coming up here, Silica Gel,
makes sounds.
I don't know if you could really even would want to call it music exactly.
They're a band that was...
that is distributed by the same company that distributes Negative Land.
It's another of our friends.
We'll be playing Negative Land as well.
In fact, let's just get to it, shall we?
Thank you.
This is Silica Gel.
I hope you have headphones on for this one.
Thank you.
Going into the music business is really exciting.
I'm really learning a lot about it.
It's really exciting.
you. I'll have a secret message just for you. I'll have a secret message.
We all need plenty of that.
I've always liked cars.
That especially makes my mom happy.
Police need your help in identifying a pedestrian killed on 285-
285-
Automatic!, Automatic!
Let the girl babies live!
Automatic!
Thank you.
North Carolina.
Raleigh.
Two
seven six
three six.
Bob
is at post office box
one four
zero
three zero six.
Dallas, Texas.
Seven five two
one four.
I don't want anything.
I don't want anything in the toilet.
Samples of bacteria.
Just throw 409.
Everywhere.
That's correct.
Do you think that's a dumb thing to do?
No.
Evil.
It's not dumb.
Samples.
You have sex dirt.
This is all nonsense.
You know better than that.
Wash wash wash wash your hands.
This is all nonsense.
Wash your hands.
And then you're gonna need to wash your hands.
To create a continuing communication of erotic stimuli.
Wash your hands.
That's it.
To create a continuing communication of erotic stimuli.
Wash your hands.
Get big butt out of the bathroom.
I may decide to use another device.
And some men are particularly fond of this.
The Hoover.
My affectionate mate for this.
And then you're gonna need to wash your hands.
I don't want anything in the toilet.
I'm putting lyrics right in some listeners.
Isn't that beautiful?
Play black.
Be black.
Seat.
Immunocid.
Conduction.
Seat.
You know, and then I started thinking, how come my moods are getting so...
The iodine, the 1, 3, 1, has got my thyroid on the run.
And the krypton, the 85, is making it hard just to stay alive.
But the iodine, the 1, 3, 1, the iodine, the 1, 3, 1, has no more run.
The metal manes, no more of everything in the mud.
Power, powers in the power team.
She could only have a chicken coop.
The very young, a 2, 4, 8.
His body is a 2, 4, 8.
His baby is sterile, I can't procreate.
And the plutonium, a 2, 0, 7.
So long, folks, I'll see you in heaven.
But the iodine, the 1, 3, 1, the iodine, the 1, 3, 1.
No more running through the metal manes.
No more of everything in the mud.
Shake the bony hand of the poison manes.
Shake the bony hand of chicken coops.
Inaccurate, inaccurate, inaccurate, inaccurate, inaccurate.
So there's over 2 million known pollutants that can cause cancer,
pancreatitis, bad blood sugar, gingivitis, bad breath, acne.
What's the use?
The iodine, the 1, 3, 1, has got my thyroid on the run.
And the iodine, the 1, 3, 1, the iodine, the 1, 3, 1, has got my thyroid on the run.
And the krypton, the 885, is making it hard just to stay alive.
But the iodine, the 1, 3, 1, the iodine, the 1, 3, 1.
No more running through the metal manes.
No more of everything in the mud.
Shake the bony hand of the poison manes.
Shake the bony hand of chicken coops.
No more running through the metal manes.
No more of everything in the mud.
Shake the bony hand of the poison manes.
Shake the bony hand of chicken coops.
Shake it.
I'm in the void.
Uh, yes, that was Einstein's Secret Orchestra.
And here is their sacred P.O.
Box 14776.
Cleveland, Ohio.
44114.
Negative Land.
And as well, Joe Newman's stuff is distributed by Negative Land.
And as is, silica gel are all available from Negative Land mail order.
Actually, it's called Negative Mail Order Land.
109 MINA.
That's M-I-N-N-A.
Number 391.
San Francisco, California.
94105.
94105 for Negative Mail Order Land.
And now,
Regan.
Regan, no.
Thanks Paula.
Regan, no relatives.
Diego, don't need you to take any part of this.
He's in position for all right of course on the animal Roti tube at a
okay now when want Exactly save the
guys and right here re so
Rub it in my back, rub it in my back.
A hunch of butter, a hunch of butter.
Well, you look like you're clean and you smell like you're shaving.
Climb up on the cigarette and make it like a monkey.
You pump, you're funky.
Hips until the hunch starts jumping and lap it up like a dog.
It's all over your chin and everything.
I can tell you like it, I like it too.
I like it on my neck and chest.
A hunch of butter, a hunch of butter.
Rub it in my back, rub it in my back.
Before the tape runs out, I should say this is Reagan's Pollock.
Information in uncensored versions available from Trash Fish.
225 West 105th.
Street.
Suite.
1FW.
That's 225 West 105th Street.
Suite.
1FW.
New York.
10025.
Ahead.
Austin key.
My,
Justin Clarke.
Um,
What I'm saying,
you
know,
Yeah, same thing.
Hot fly, hot smile,
shining blue, white, blue.
Give me a room.
Ain't no time to stop.
Hot fly, hot smile.
Give me a room.