Before the sermon, a message concerning Bob Dobbs, living avatar of Slack, and saint of Satan, on Planet Planet Planet Planet Planet.
You have to love Bob. He loves you, but you love Bob. You have to.
Or else what happens if you don't love Bob?
He'll kill you. He'll Bob you out.
He'll Bob you out, folks. You heard it here first. If you don't love Bob, he'll Bob you out, man.
You are letting yourself go. A little more. And a little more.
Every nerve. Every tongue.
90.90.0. F-ing.
And down.
That's Texas.
You just yelled to it.
No, no, no.
Ladies and gentlemen, please leave your sets adjusted.
We're having operating difficulties, which has necessitated a delay in the beginning of our Sunday movie.
It's a success.
It's a wonderful life.
We live so wonderful life.
No trouble.
Get set.
Get going.
Amen.
Recording.
Everything's going fine.
No trouble.
This is Doug Smith, radio operator.
I'm going to bring you a piece of that green cheese for sure.
I have Bob's luggage!
Bob?
That's your key phrase.
It will trigger the entire message without your being aware of it.
Welcome to the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
Sponsored by the Church of the Subgenius.
This is Reverend Ivan Stang, sacred scribe of the First Orthodox Megafist Temple Lodge of the Church of the Subgenius.
With Pastor Buck Naked of the First Naked Church of the Subgenius.
The opinions expressed are not necessarily those of this radio station.
Before the sermon, a message concerning Bob Dobbs, living avatar of Slack, and saint of silence on planet Earth.
Are we controlled by secret forces?
Do you ever get the feeling that free will is a joke?
Do people think you're strange?
Do you?
Then you may be on the right track.
Are you abnormal?
Then you are probably better than most people.
Yes, your time shall triumph.
Now, at last, the step-by-step process is revealed.
This is it.
The only faith that promises action, thrill, success in sex and business.
Bring your weirdest dreams to rampaging life.
Stand erect for your own.
Have normality.
Bob is a way of life to millions.
Yet half of them don't even know it.
He's the one true living Slack master with the spiritual know-how to help you bash through the locked doorway to financial heaven.
He is the one real shortcut to Slack.
Now, see another dimension on your TV.
Yes, fear the stark fist of removal no longer.
Become physically attractive overnight.
Attain status, luck, prosperity by blowing them off.
Bob's promise is to widen the scope and nature of abnormal behavior.
To explore new ways of going over the edge.
And coming right back.
Plus, to bring back those who couldn't make it on their own.
To help you create the highest possible earnings from the psychodynamics of abnormal behavior.
To turn conspiracy implanted personality disorders around.
And channel them into an illusion of creativity.
That will fool normals and get you sex.
Bob!
Thank you.
That was horrible.
I've never been smoked by dogs.
Oh, we're back in Rock and Roll Hill now.
Oh, no.
Is this Rock and Roll Hill?
Oh, man.
I always get stuck here at 2 in the morning.
Rock and Roll Hill.
Get down.
Party.
Shoot up.
Praise Satan.
Rock and Roll Hill.
Yeah, yeah.
Go out and kill some kids tonight.
Rock and Roll smells like body roll.
Rock and Roll Hill.
Be destroyed.
Destroy your life.
Praise Satan and Rock and Roll Hill.
Rock and Roll.
Sex.
Drugs and alcohol.
DJs on this show.
Corruption.
Here is a special editorial.
Doctors for Bob supports the Parents Music Resource Center in its efforts to bring rock music of its unnecessary properties to the economy.
》
It's
the
Desons
enjoy
today
and all the gas you want.
Awesome, Umba.
You can moat.
If that's what floats you boat.
Hey, you.
I'm talking.
You listening?
Or you can pout.
Or you can break out.
Get up.
Get out.
Come on, step on me.
Step into it.
Step into this league.
Girl, do what you please.
Cause you ain't no twit.
You ain't no twit.
Yeah.
Step out of your clothes.
Girl, step into hoes.
You'll be the latest hit.
The latest hit, yeah.
It's about time to let my hormones wake up.
Put off the homework.
Let's put on the makeup.
Don't wait a second.
Cause you'll stay in limbo.
I give my old stuff to my sister, that bimbo.
When I wear underwear, I'm liberated.
It's like the movies, M-I-V-G.
Or X-rated.
I dance just like a virgin in these clothes.
I hold my belly, but the lip won't show.
Step into this league.
Start being a tease.
Hey, you ain't no nerd.
You ain't no nerd, yeah.
Step into the streets.
Put guys into heat.
Be a little flirt.
A little flirt, yeah.
Wanna get to dress up.
Move around and prance.
Wanna get in front.
All my fans dance.
Don't try to fight it.
Cause your fist is really you.
Just burst your lips.
And flare your nostrils too.
I must be dreaming.
This is just too cool.
Cause in real life, I rip my lips and then I drool.
I really love in the life I wanna.
It feels so good to be a prima donna.
Step into the streets.
Girl, do you watch it?
Please.
Now you're not a wimp.
You're not a wimp, yeah.
Step into the lights.
You know it's alright.
If you wanna rip.
You can't rip, yeah.
You can take your mind where it wants to go.
Tell the boys to come.
Or tell the boys to blow.
Whether I'm awake or if it's a dream.
I can make my life feel like a magazine.
Step into this league.
Girl, do what you please.
Cause you ain't no twit.
You ain't no twit, yeah.
Step into the beat.
Put guys into heat.
You're the latest hit.
The latest hit, yeah.
When I start to strut, I wanna squish my nose.
My body really sweats, but hey, that's how it goes.
I'm in a world like Hammer Girl.
It's simple.
I'm never going back to clear or fill and purple.
You can take your mind where it wants to go.
Tell the boys to come.
Or tell the boys to blow.
Whether I'm awake or if it's a dream.
I can make my life feel like a magazine.
Be like a magazine.
Oh, yes, dear friends.
You can be like that.
You can be like that magazine, I suppose.
This is the horrible Madonna parody.
I might as well tell you what's going on here, friends.
This is gonna be a real hip show.
This was real cool a few months ago, I suppose.
Madonna parody here from Reverend Bleepo Abernathy up with the Hour of Slack show in Boston.
A little bit before that and after this, the Serious Abuse radio show from...
The Rat Cave, dear friends.
We'll be going back to that.
But in the meantime, friends, draft registration.
You do have a choice.
Do you have alternatives to military service?
I did, flat feet.
But you may have others.
Talk to one of the trained draft counselors at the War Resisters League for an evaluation of your particular situation.
It'll cost you nothing to learn the facts, folks.
Remember, know the facts before you make your decision.
For draft counseling, call 214-421-1984.
That's a good number there for a draft counselor.
421-1984.
I was number 30 in the lottery.
And they didn't believe any of the lies I told them until finally they looked at my feet and said,
Son, sorry.
Just two flat-footed folks.
I'm sorry for this man's army.
But friends, this is the subgenius hour of slack in Dallas, Texas.
And sorry, the phone lines aren't working tonight.
So we can't take your prayer requests right now.
I mean, they just flat out aren't working, friends.
You're going to have to...
They're trying.
But you're going to have to pray.
You're going to have to, you know, put something important in an important place and think about it and pray.
And say things like...
Oh, Dobbs head.
Silly pills, Bob Slack.
I want my pills.
Some devil works for me.
Give me your pills.
Bob pills, Bob pills, Slack Bob.
Give me pills, Bob.
Yes, that's the misconceptions of many subgeni.
That's your typical pink boy pretending to be subgenius.
Yes, he paid his $20.
His money was green, but he was still pink inside.
Yes.
It's a pathetic thing to watch.
He tries to quote all the slang that he got from the books.
Hey, pull the wool over your own eyes, guys.
Hey, yeah.
Yeah, you'd pay to know what you really think.
Oh, yeah, like repent and quit your job and slack off.
Yeah, really cool.
Do something to them if they can't take a joke.
What was that?
Let me open it back up here.
Oh, wow, man.
Like, are we punk rock, man?
I thought it was punk to talk about Bob.
I thought it was like cool or something to talk about Bob.
Hey, we ought to hassle the clerk at best because she's a capitalist, man.
Hey, you believe in anarchy, man?
Well, if you don't, I'm going to kill you.
Kill you, kill you, kill you.
We'll show you punk rock.
You thought it was hair and clothes.
You thought it was like big spikes and bracelets and leather and stuff.
Yeah, you thought punk rock came from a record company.
You thought wrong.
You thought it was like...
You are God participating in himself, just me.
Man, this guy's...
Wow, this guy's a real prophet.
Elder God may not be all that correct.
He's a surdeu for Sam, for sure.
They find more dominance when tomorrow becomes today.
Responsible for this.
All right, enough of this silliness.
Yes.
Say goodnight, Stank.
Ah, yes, friends.
I'm all hooked up.
I'm ready to answer your questions.
Now, we've been getting letters and phone calls from noble subgeniuses out there asking,
Reverend Stank, how can I be more subversive?
How can I be of more service to Bob in bringing down the conspiracy that enslaves us?
And friends, I'm afraid that that is entirely up to you.
Now, the conspiracy will tell you how to be more subversive.
And I'm not going to be aggressive against it.
So we sure won't.
But I can give you one helpful hint, friends.
There's nothing wrong with looking normal.
If you want to be more subversive, friends, you don't have to show off about it.
If you wear a uniform like a high-fashion punk haircut or leather and spandex and whatever,
unless it's really extreme, friends,
you're just playing along with the conspiracy,
joining a conformity of nonconformists.
You're labeling yourself as someone who the conspiracy doesn't really need to worry about
because you're going to follow a predictable pattern,
one that they've co-opted already.
But what kind of subversion are we talking about anyway, friends?
Bringing down the state?
Blowing up polluters?
Nay, nay.
That only kills people, friends, and gets you in jail to boot.
It's stupid, but not stupid in the right way.
Bob said, Bob said,
Thou shalt kill none but me.
Unless they're literally about to kill you or if they insult your ancestors.
That's what Bob said.
And, you know, there's nothing wrong with technology, friends.
We don't need to subvert technology.
After all, only technology is the only thing we've got to do.
We've got to clean up the mess we already made.
So who are we trying to subvert?
The Republicans?
Huh.
Friends, an awful lot of subgeniuses are Republicans.
But, you know, subgenius doesn't mean left-wing pinko or right-wing anything.
All it means to most of us is patriopsychotic anarcho-materialism, friends.
Every yard a kingdom.
Every child and dog a serf.
It doesn't matter what party is in control,
as long as none of the parties really have that much control over how much you party.
Besides, what you're fighting ain't just a political system.
I mean, as political systems go, the U.S. is one of the least evil.
Just as Jesus is okay.
It's just that some members of his fan club make him look bad.
Same goes with Bob and the Bobbies.
Surely some of you have met nerds on the street who started trying to talk Bob at you and you were just embarrassed.
Well, friends, see, the conspiracy is a great combination of things.
Work is one of the main ones.
That's how you're really controlled, friends.
You have to work for someone else to make a living.
Now, this subgenius actually likes to work at what he likes to work at.
But that's the rub and the bub, my friend.
The conspiracy is also ancient customs and new invented customs.
It's a whole background attitude.
The conspiracy is an attitude.
An attitude of hatred for anything weird.
So what you want to subvert, friend, is that attitude.
Now, some strange things are bad.
But all great inventions and ideas started out as strange ones.
So if you want to subvert the government or some manufacturer or blow buildings up,
that's just what the conspiracy wants you to do, my friend, so they can catch you,
make you look like a kook in front of millions.
Now, history proves that every time you overthrow something overnight,
ditch some old government, what replaces it always ends up just as bad.
We have to break that cycle, friends, and this isn't anarchy we're talking about.
Anarchy is just another political system.
Just like atheism is just another religion.
To truly subvert, my friend, you work alone at your own pace, casually,
but with alertness to subvert the attitude of hating everything weird.
Remember, leftists are just as guilty as rightists in this respect.
And you don't go out subverting by being an obnoxious, bobby,
enforcing weirdness down the throats of normals who can't possibly appreciate it anyway.
That just makes them hate weirdness more.
You should seduce them with abnormality, my friend.
You have to break them in a little at a time. It depends.
And you can't indiscriminately hate all normals,
because that only proves that you are a normal yourself,
because you don't understand yet that half of what you call normals are actually weirder than you are.
A
goes
Cause they're laying down the walls
I've been before so many times
I can't remember them all
And I say
Who do you want to be today?
Who do you want to be?
Do you want to be just like someone on TV?
Just like somebody on TV
I think I'll be a teddy boy
I think I'll be a hump
I think I'll be a tough guy
And I think I'll be a punk
I'd like to see a fashion star
All dressed in curly rags
Over half across the other side
And walk around in drag
Who do you want to be today?
Who do you want to be?
Do you want to be just like someone on TV?
Just like somebody on TV
Oh yeah
Do you like to live just like a rock
In the middle of the sea?
Do you want to suffer by yourself
In a pool of blissful misery?
Do you feel like a saint in honest clothes
With a rosary in your hand?
Do you want to be crazy like Fando
Like a stranger in a strange, strange land?
Would you rather push the button?
And be feared by all humanity?
Or perhaps you'd like to be a boss?
Do you want to be stupid just like me?
Who do you want to be today?
Who do you want to be?
Do you want to be just like someone on TV?
Just like somebody on TV
Who do you want to be today?
This is Man 1A
Now it's going to be on FM in Dallas, Texas
Praise Bob!
Who do you want to be today?
Who do you want to be?
To use my own
Super cool
Studly self as an example
Now in person I don't really appear
Like a mad prophet of the airwaves
I've been a fan of the airwaves for a long time
Very deliberately look like an innocent
Computer whiz or something
If a policeman stops me for speeding
I look like a regular citizen
And part of me is
And so he doesn't look in the trunk
To see if I'm carrying 5,000 copies
Of subgenius pamphlets
To hand out to grade school kids
Which I am
Get away with murder this way friends
And that time the secret service
Came to my house
They took one look and said oh
He's just a poor humorist
He isn't building bombs
Not physical bombs
Nay my friends
But me and perhaps many of you
Are from that 1970s
Post hippie
Nihilistic generation more or less
And aside from not working for a living
I and perhaps you
Are still that same
Devious hippie
Not a commie nay
Not a pinko but a soldier
For slack
A warrior
Against the conspiracy
Of the normals
And so
To truly suffer
To smite them
But not physically
Smite them psychologically
With your jokes
Your cryptic statements
Your band
Your paintings
Your weird car
Your whole attitude
Not just your haircut and clothes
My god
The normals can wear weird haircuts and clothes
And they do it all
The time
If they are normals
My friends
They'll recoil in fear and jealousy
To see a free man
Or woman
But for latent subgeni
Who are right to be saved
You're setting a good example
To be weird in your own way
Achieve slack in your own life
My friend and those
Who are worthy will turn toward it
As towards a beacon
As a moth dives headlong
Into the flames
They're
They're not trying to
To steal your slack
Or to imitate you
But merely to see
What is possible
Then and only then
Will they learn
To pull the wool over their own eyes
So you don't have to talk about Bob, friends
They have to just stumble upon Bob
In their own sweet time
And I'm not saying
Be yourself
Quote unquote
There are too many yourselves
You might end up being your own
Conspiracy normal lynch mob self
You must try
To try not to
Achieve the development
Of your Bob self
That in you
Which is Bob-like
And there is no rule book for this
My friend
Except the one you make
And the one that you buy
From Bob
Praise Bob
Help me somebody
Pull the lever
Down you go
Ha!
You are listening to the Hour of Slack.
I'm K.N. Olin.
Praise Bob!
Yeah!
Yeah, people will go off
And worship their stylish fashion gods
Their Madonna gods
Their Peter gods
Their Jim Morrison gods
Jim Morrison gods
Mick Jagger gods
All those are false prophets
They're false prophets
Jerry Falwell gods
How did you get in this terrible box?
Listen to this.
Can I get a T.I.?
T.I. man
Far out man
Slave labor in Nicaragua
Making electronic parts
A brain slave
Slave to their reality
Their world
Their society
Their way of life
Their religion
Their ideology
Their conformity
Because conformity
And creativity
Are the same thing
They're the same in their world
Imagination
What's that?
I've got super dynamic overdrive
The sidewalk surf
Was dancing with tricks
In that whirling circle
They love more kicks
They look each other
Like drugs to their blood
And drop trumps and traps
When they're playing studs
And they're pretty folks
Pretty folks
Bending the trend
They'll never mend
Splitting their cells
Looking for pills
They blow their change
And they're gonna blow their change
They don't pay their bills
Hard to find what you love
Spend X, D, K
Blocks of flash zeros
There's nothing to say
And they're pretty folks
Pretty folks
Bending the trend
They'll never mend
And they're pretty talk
Pretty folks
They're pretty folks
Bending the trend
Pretty folks
Pretty folks, pretty folks, they'll never met.
In funhouse mirrors, they don't seem to age.
As they decompose in memory's cage.
The total loss is not something to hide.
When the last big sleep has started inside.
Cause they're pretty folks, pretty folks, bending each other.
Pretty folks, pretty folks, they'll never met.
Pretty sure he's a psychopath.
Now, how do we spot him?
Well, if he's wearing a Napoleon hat, it's easy.
Otherwise, they come in all sizes and shapes.
11-year-old girls, 80-year-old men.
Yeah, they all look perfectly normal.
I keep telling y'all, this is a sick and perverted nation.
All tired.
And nobody wants to listen to me.
Nobody wants to hear about Bob.
Nobody.
I try to tell everybody what's going on.
They won't listen to me.
Well, to tell you the truth, I can't stand it anymore.
Bob.
The fist and the fear behind it.
It's not just the wars and the awards that win them.
It's not just the dull and empty distaste for a smothered culture
that expires all around you in pools of its own wastes.
It's not just the terminal folds of Nunu.
It's not just the child zombies that murder their mediocrity parents
and then cruise the streets with bloody feet.
It's not just those starry old vecks on the park benches
with looks on their faces like those who shuffled out of the boxcars of Belsen and Auschwitz.
It's not just the anesthesiologist for Negi.
It's not just the heaving pink meat masses that grope and clutch all around you.
It's not just the dino bones for Wotan.
It's not just the broken headlights, snapped antennae, and human excrement on your car hood.
It's not just that the old ways were best.
It's not just the bastardization and perversion of every honest means of self-expression.
It's not just the kill a ganja from the dark side of the bush.
It's not just the penoid snipers locking and loading on every high-rise car.
It's not just the high-rise rooftop.
It's not just the widescreen technicolor corporate daisy chain that has defiled the entire planet.
It's not just Mongo in the Congo with fa-fa-fas the size of basketballs.
It's not just the prophets crying lonely and alone in the wilderness.
It's not just the indignity of having to work for some bland, non-entity son of a bitch
who thinks workers are property.
It's not just the blueness of the world.
It's not just the wound cleansed by evil.
It's not just the battling eco-freaks who want to go back to nature
without realizing that nature is an open-ditch latrine in midsummer.
It's not just some asshole with a pipe and a 90 more than you do dog grin all over his homogenized face.
It's not just the horrible feeling of being entrapped inside a regimented, devolving world
that you certainly never made.
It's not just the doorway to doom.
It's not just wanting to know what the hell is really going on.
It's not just the missing H's or the stolen alpha-beta-max.
No, dear friends, there is more to it all than that.
Bob ain't no nickel-dime bum show.
I put it to you, he's on the square and a corking fine business proposition.
He's the grandest thing yet, and don't you forget it.
Shout salvation and fight in Jesus.
You'll need to rise precious early, you sinner there, if you want to diddle the almighty.
Bob, not off.
He's got tough mixture with a punch on it for you, my friend.
In his back pocket.
Just you try it.
Bob is a clump of mud.
Bob is a tape recorder.
Bob is things that don't always run.
Bob is masking tape.
Bob is a ballpoint pen.
Bob is a rooster.
Bob is a hen.
We want Bob!
Where's Bob?
Right now!
We want Bob!
Okay, Bob's probably not going to be here in physical manifestation.
Oh, no!
Whoa, where is Bob?
He's everywhere.
Check yourself and feel if you're Bob Glenn
and make sure it's overactive like it's supposed to be.
This is the headquarters for the Church of the Subgenius.
Now, wait a minute.
No, wait a minute. I love that area.
I represent a group of scientists
who work with but one purpose, to put an end to war.
Naturally, such a goal can't be attained.
Men of vision, men such as you, Doctor,
gathered here, exchanging information daily,
putting aside all thoughts of personal success.
We hope to achieve exciting new techniques,
leap years ahead of the others.
I don't think I need to tell you how effective our voices will be
when the world learns of our achievements.
Well, there you have it.
Nothing new, perhaps, but then, what is?
However, let me assure you, Doctor, that we are dedicated men and women,
and as such, we can accomplish wonders.
Like any other church,
the Church of the Subgenius
has divine tenets,
divine rules,
divine orders.
The first rule of the Subgenius Church is
too much is always better than not enough.
Can I get it too much?
What is it always better than?
I don't know!
Praise Bob!
Hello, Paul.
Welcome to the End Times.
In today's End Time essay,
we will be covering the difference between
the Bofram and the Bloodyhead Launcher Society itself.
As seen here in our first slide,
the Bloodyhead Launcher Society goes on forever.
end and there's no use resisting.
Look at those heads fall in slow
motion. Just beautiful.
Bouncing down the celestial stairs.
Yes, dear friends, those
are the things I want to tell you about today.
The very minute things.
The parables about the less traveled past.
Ha!
Bob gives you the bulldozers
you need to pave your own path.
Ignore those gray-suited hippos
and those third-stage fashion clones
are killing me. You gotta stand up.
You gotta stand up now and you gotta stand up
for all of us.
Stand up and make it legal.
Don't let them whitewash your
subconscious mind.
Just like the 50s.
Hey, if we're supposed to be moving ahead,
why is the scenery changing?
Do machines get smarter as people get dumber?
Well, forget it for now.
That's exactly the way they want you
to behave so they can have an excuse to
mount their gun turrets against all the
supposed fringe groups.
Oh, no, no, come on. Keep those thoughts to yourself.
You shouldn't depress anybody.
You'll be seen as a downer
spreading bad karma.
People don't want to be reminded of it.
Yes, this is the theme
of the neurotic 80s.
The human race is cracking up.
The toxic waste of the
me generation has seeped into our homes.
The McCarthyite witch hunters
are back, but this time
they're out for us.
Physical perfection
and mental vacuousness make us a little more.
Oh, but don't bomb us out.
We want to have fun.
Just watch that soft core
.0 soda can work
your boring job.
On some occasions,
Baphomet seems to be associated
with an apparition of a bearded head.
In any case,
we found hospital evidence
for the charge of
Well?
. . .
There's a world
There's a world going on underground.
Jeez, this is awful, Dad.
Lord Lord, I'm dope and he's killing people.
Tell it to the X-mas bunny, kid.
You watch the Astros.
How do I know I'm here?
Not in some very lonely place.
How do I know I'm not on a star?
Got a problem?
Bring it to the friendly people.
People touching people.
People running against people.
People developing the nuclear first strike capability to incinerate people.
Sound like a flash in the pan?
It's got to be.
You don't say.
Subtle for less.
You don't have to.
You're you.
And you've got needs bigger and more earth-shaking than your grandfather could have dreamed.
How do we keep bringing them to you, year after year, bigger and better?
By using the technology of tomorrow on the consumers of today.
The now people.
People on the go.
Going from the smart shopper to new low value in the time it takes to dial our number.
Call now, won't you?
For more of what you've come to expect from us.
Style.
Mood.
A certain dependable kind of image.
An image of the way you'd like people to be.
Passive.
Pretty.
White.
As white as the complexion of our finest women.
Grown right here by our special process.
As white as the hair of God.
White as it was in life.
As white as the blank sheet on which we write your mind.
Who are we?
We're the happy people.
Happy to live in a world of images.
Images of war.
Family.
Crime.
Fun images that help rinse away unsightly self-images so you can get away from the privacy of your own home.
After all, aren't you what everything's here for?
You're what we're here for.
That's why we made everything.
And that's why everything made you.
And that's why you made us.
Who are we?
We're the money people.
The people who take your money.
No more money hassling.
But what about little Dicky you say?
What's little Dicky gonna do when you're working late and Wilma's minding the fort and Sis is in and out?
Put away those straps and buckles.
Dicky's safe with us.
He's even learning to speak again.
Our way.
Best of all, he's safe with the people who know what it is you want from a world.
Simplicity.
Reliability.
A world you can go to without worrying about whether your money is safe.
You know, when we first got into this business, we didn't know much more than you.
Like you, we thought there was a world out there.
A world of value.
A world that needed meaning.
Beauty.
Love.
A world that needed a better product.
Uh-uh.
There's just you.
You.
And you want to know something.
You want to know just exactly what it is you're supposed to do.
You don't really care why.
Just so long as it's the right thing.
It's natural.
Everyone wants to do the right thing.
But sometimes it's hard to know just what the right thing is.
Let's say you're black.
And you've just lost both your arms and legs defending U.S. interests in El Salvador.
You come home and get thrown in jail for life for beating up four white cops.
You want to know just exactly what is it I'm supposed to feel.
We can't give you all the answers.
But we can help you flesh out your fantasy that there are some.
At our labs, we use only the finest homemade ingredients.
Love.
Children.
God.
And the purest blend of money your needs can buy.
Grown right here by our special process.
A process in use since our first mom and pop operation.
Who are we?
We're the normal people.
I am. I am becoming what?
That was Michael Pepe, yes.
Remember that name, folks?
Off his tape, Life Itself.
The Greatest Hits of Michael Pepe.
You can find out more about Michael Pepe
and more creatures like that
from the Church's thening Our T expreses of the ends of the broadcast.
You'll get that fox number at the end of the broadcast
Vamos. Vamos. Vamos. Vamos.
I am, I am, I am to come, I am, I am, I am to come, I am, I am, I am, I am to come, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am to come, I am, I am, I am, I am, I am to come, I am, I am.
Dynamic overdrive. I'm operating in 10,000 revolutions. My motor is being preserved because I'm operating in supernatural overdrive.
I'm certain you know what the reality is.
No matter what I do to change it, normal I remain.
Normal can be just as bad as riding in a wheelchair.
Today, serious heresy is a deviant state of consciousness.
Not so much deviant opinions as having a kind of experience which is different from regular experience.
We are taught what experiences are permissible.
And therefore, if a person has so-called strange experiences and endeavors to communicate these experiences to other people,
he is looked at in a very odd way.
And asked, are you feeling all right?
Because people feel distinctly uncomfortable when they realize that they're in the presence of someone
who's experiencing the world in a rather different way from themselves.
They call in question as to whether this person is indeed human.
The cigar is something.
They look like a human being.
But because the state of experience is so different, you wonder whether they really are.
And in rather the same way, in a very everyday kind of circumstance,
when you're sitting in a bar drinking, and you find you have a drunk next to you.
And he turns to you and says,
I say,
and you sort of move your stool a little way away from this man.
Because he's become, in some way, what we mean by non-human.
We expect a high of about 65 degrees tomorrow.
Increasingly cloudy skies.
Once again, with some rain in the forecast.
So I found this little dish, crawled in and I, I say I'm happy.
All right boys, Bob's got you hooked.
Bob's got a monkey on your back.
Hey, you know that, that...
Bob's is doing something spooky again ain't he?
That's what you're listening to?
Yeah.
That's the kind of Bob that comes up out of the shadows.
It's the kind of Bob that follows you home.
It calls you up in the middle of the night and hangs up and sees you.
Hey, let's kill Bob.
I got...
I, um...
I saw these hot dogs, Bob.
And, uh...
And they're like...
When my daddy got killed with a baseball.
Because those are the kind they sold there.
And...
Ohio.
She's gone...
To...
Ohio.
They've got paddle wheels there.
Paddle wheels...
Bigger...
Than a Panzer tank, Bob.
Bigger than a Panzer tank, Bob.
Bigger than a...
Panzer...
Tank...
Bob...
Ohio.
And...
You've got Ohio.
Ohio.
Panzers.
Highness.
impose equations on the
Oh, dear friends.
And now we come down near the end of an hour of slack with this song, this offensive song.
From negative land, I must admit, this is just really disgraceful.
Friends, that P.O. Box you can write to for more information about the Church of the Subgenius and its publications is Bob.
Friends, you can write to Bob at P.O. Box.
181-417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118 www.subgenius.com
Thank you for listening, dear friends.
And stay tuned for the Monday Morning Show with Johnny Horton and Norm Ward.
Other things.
And I'm on a date.
If I can't whoop it, I'm going down.
All right, man.
He can't whoop it.
He's going down.
If the last 50 years made such a change, just imagine the New York of 1980.
When everyone has a number instead of a name.
And the government tells you whom you should marry.
Let him that hath understanding count the number of the beast.
For it is the number of a man.
The number of a man.
His number is 603 score and 6.