Warhands on deck!
It's a killer!
And yes, here we are back at your lounge chair. Please sit down and strap yourself in. You're about ready for another ride.
And remember, when they come by, please just don't be alarmed. They may be offering you something.
Oh, I paid extra for that part, buddy.
Well, sometimes it's...
Bring him on! Come on, baby!
Hour of Slack, sponsored by the Church of the Subgenius.
The Subgenius Hour of Slack that you are about to listen to is specially designed only to be played on radio station and only in the city of...
Well, yes, dear friends, and this Hour of Slack number 928 is actually a rerun of Hour of Slack number 758.
The search for Dave's brain on the high seas.
Of Hell. From our 75th season.
About three and a half, four years ago.
Praise Paul.
I don't wanna look at the TV today.
Cause it brings me down.
And I don't wanna hear what the papers they say.
They go round and round.
Well, we'll see, Bob.
You will indeed, Steve.
You come tonight, you will see, Bob.
This is a rock and roll party church. This is a church that is for sin.
Don't come expecting no performance art satire, dear God, please.
This is not gonna be moral majority takeoffs, my friend. This is not a joke!
This is the one true church. The last church.
After relaxing on the lake, Bob's ready to have a great time.
Entertaining his friends. Right, Bob?
Bob?
Enjoy life like Bob.
Frankly, you know, the church of the subgenius is nonsense.
I mean, it's triviality. It has no significance for anything that anybody's gonna care about for any length of time.
You know, it may be lots of fun, and I don't mean to belittle it as such,
but when you're faced with a serious situation, you got a world that's on the verge of nuclear holocaust,
and the all-democratic institutions in this country that haven't already vanished are under severe attack,
and when all that comes to mind is the church of the subgenius, I gotta think that's one of the reasons we're in the trouble we're in.
Well, just to try and put the church of the subgenius to rest,
those of you who are not familiar with it, the church of the subgenius is essentially a group that,
and I'm sure that people will argue with me with this, but it's essentially a sort of a comedy routine.
I mean, they may have a philosophical point, but it's based on humor.
There are articles about it in John Rubenstein's, John Carroll's column in the Chronicle and things of that nature.
It's more or less a sort of a comedy affiliate.
It's about as politically weighty, or less politically weighty than, you know, Saturday morning kids' TV show.
There's nothing to it.
Okay.
I see.
Yeah.
Okay.
Here comes the funny part.
Let's play this one.
I'm using it.
Well, anyway, I'm choosing.
I never wanna lose it.
And I'm not gonna fight.
Got no need to be right.
I'm okay when I play in my room.
What about the other part?
I mean, I'm illuminating.
It's the themopods which have taken over.
Themopods?
They scared me in the elevator last week,
but I'm trying to find out about our side now.
It's the foundation, the undergarment of the false messiah,
the falsy messiah which has been prophesied
by the book of Romans in the book of Psalms.
But which side was the false messiah on?
Was he a themopod or an us-opod?
It was a themopod at the beginning,
but then, yea and lo, it became an if-opod.
Yea, he cometh in, he turneth on with the right hand,
and yea, he turneth off with the left hand.
Yeah, now it may sound ludicrous.
It may sound ridiculous,
to many unbelievers out there.
Satan is real, working in spirit.
You can see him and hear him in this world every day.
He can bring you down with power.
He can tempt you and lead you astray.
I attended service at a little church in the country not long ago.
A prayer was led by an old country preacher
who then raised his hands as everyone stood and sang,
My God is real.
A warm breeze through the open windows
brought in the smell of new-mown hay in a nearby field,
and the singing of the hymn,
and the singing of birds could be heard in the moment of silence
as the preacher opened his Bible to read.
And then a little old man stood up,
bent with age, his hair thin and white,
and said,
Preacher, tell them that Satan is real too.
You can hear him in songs that give praise to idols and sinful things of this world.
You can see him in the destruction of homes torn apart.
I know that Satan is real, for once I had a happy home.
I was loved and respected by my family.
I was looked upon as a leader in my community.
And then Satan came into my life.
I grew selfish and unneighborly.
My friends turned against me.
And finally, my home was broken apart.
My children took their paths into a world of sin.
Yes, preacher, it's sweet to know that God is real,
and to know that in him all things are possible.
And we know that heaven is a real place where joys shall never end.
But sinner friend, if you're here today,
Satan is real too.
And hell is a real place,
a place of everlasting punishment.
Please allow me to introduce myself.
I'm a man of wealth and taste.
I've been around for long, long years.
Stole many a man's soul and faith.
I was around when Jesus Christ had his moment.
No doubt in faith.
Made them sure of that pilot.
Washed his hands and sealed his fate.
Pleased to meet you.
Hope you guessed my name.
Cause what's hustling you
is the
Nature of my game.
And is your soul clean when the devil comes by your door?
Are you ready to meet the devil at the crossroads, my friend?
All hands on deck.
Are you going to have what he demands in the way of my seatbelt?
Dick.
Dick?
That's far too many.
We'll have to call you the Centipede Man.
Now sit down here.
You're not the first experiment to fail.
I was waiting to be hanged in the morning.
But I didn't care about that.
I opened the door.
And there was the captain and his first mate.
I swung the hatchet, splitting the captain's head wide open.
I turned and nearly chopped off the first mate.
I saw his head at the neck.
There was blood and gore everywhere.
And I was glad for what I'd done.
Cor, Captain, look what he's done.
He's dead.
Stand to, men.
Men, this swab is there.
Stand to.
Oh, yes, sir.
Murder on the high seas is no more or less a damn...
It's a law act.
...miss.
I have to start again.
Lieutenant Smith, could you start the...
Off with his head.
I'm going to the toilet.
And scoop it out and put a candle in it.
And on with his new face, thanks to Luxorant and the beautiful skin treatment you can wear like a hat.
I see she's a virgin.
Are you, uh, too?
She looks like a used virgin, Sash.
Quite used.
In fact, you can smell her a mile and a half off, three fathoms away.
She's as used as a dog in heat.
You could smell her three fathoms under.
Yes, you are of a mind to smell things in Poseidon's locker if you wanted to go to where the frozen food locker is.
And his body hung from the yardarm at the neck, and he dangled in the wind for the rest
of the trip to the Americas.
Is that an albatross, sir?
No, Paunch, it's not an albatross.
Have we seen an albatross?
Albatrosses would be viewed as a gnomon of good fortune.
I personally believe that this is the fetidest bird native to Central America.
It wouldn't be far off from the Cami Isle.
And, uh, friends, we'll be right back to the hellish trip to deep inside Dave's brain.
Here on the Hour of Slack.
Slack for everyone but.
Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
Oh, testiculoids and lactators.
It's an ESO radio subgenius night, or timeless day.
For inside Dave's water-filled head there is no time and less money.
Chaz Smith, friends, Lonesome Cowboy Dave, and we will continue with the devil on the high seas of Dave's brain.
But first, credits, friends.
That Sympathy for the Devil version was by Tiamat, and you will be hearing the rest of that.
Satan Is Real was by the Lauvin Brothers, posted to Alt Binary Slack by Magma3.
Usopods and Themopods is by, and the Bub Dubs radio, old radio.
Ancient KPFA Berkeley sub-show of Howl Robbins, Puzzling Evidence, Gary Gabrokeframe, and Bob Nelson.
Let Me Play My Music is Frank Marino's.
And Mahogany Rush.
You also heard Pope Meyer, Pope David N. Meyer, the Pope of All New York, and myself, Reverend Ivan Stang, on Media Barrage 10 remix, subgenius CD.
And Ghost Riders in the Sky was by Dick Dale, my friends.
The ESO show, which is most of what follows, is broadcast from WCSB Cleveland State University, friends, every Thursday at midnight on the net at WCSB.org.
With host Chad Hogan.
And Chad Smith.
Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
And now, this beefy message.
You like beef?
Mommy, I'm scared of the clowns.
Beef or my hood?
Beef by the pound, by the ton, and by the honey bun.
We got beef for you at Tim and Terry's Slaughterhouse.
Stop in and we'll smack them down and deliver it fresh and piping hot, or creamy smooth, the way it's supposed to have been.
Mommy, the clowns.
The clown scares me.
That's all right, son.
They're supposed to scare you.
The clown makes us laugh.
Yes, the clown takes away our fear.
Because it reminds us of our own absurdity.
Our own mortality.
The clown makes us laugh.
But the tightrope walker.
Death inspires us.
Yes, the tightrope walker makes us fear death.
Makes us fear death.
Shining in their silver suit in the spotlight.
Like high above.
We can't all be tightrope walkers.
And the Santa reigns.
Most of us have to be clowns.
Popeye, Ticklefish, and his amazing dangling unit.
There's more clowns than acrobats.
Even before more stunts and isoobs dump you in the buff than you've ever seen available or possible to any human-born woman.
You won't believe that something this hideous could survive.
But it's real.
It's here.
It's only 50 cents.
Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
See him.
Hear him.
Smell him.
It's alive.
It's real.
It's Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
See the freak.
See the hideous abortion of God's nature.
Step behind the curtain and see the freak.
Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
I'm afraid of fire, man.
Stop flicking that lighter at me.
Hey, man.
Look at the freak.
Yeah.
Well, if I looked like you did, then I wouldn't be pointed.
Where'd you get that rouge, you old bitch?
Yeah.
Hey.
Oh, man.
Come on, man.
I don't know no size, you old freak.
I'm just here to show you.
Look at the freak.
Kind of funny.
Freak.
Dave, how could things have gone so terribly wrong?
How did you end up here?
Once you were a strapping young lad with a peachy dark complexion and miles and miles
of good humor and look at you now.
Crawling.
Testicles are dragging on the ground.
Crawling in your own piss.
You were a good humor man, too.
It was a lot of fun back then, wasn't it?
You're wearing like eye mascara.
You made a lot of money in New York City.
Yeah, man.
Those were the days.
Now, what do you think you're going to do?
You're a good humor man, too.
You're wearing like eye mascara.
Now you have a schlong the size of an elephant's trunk.
Freak!
Those were the days, man.
I was hung like a horse.
Fly.
Oh, man.
Am I ever going to get out of here?
It's not cool.
And so Dave curled up inside the dumpster behind the jack-in-the-box.
A hated cold rain.
For the rain pouring down on his shivering bones as he waited for Bob to come and deliver.
He waited.
And he waited.
Taking the abuse of passerbys.
Oh, man, I can't live like this anymore.
Oh, my God, dude.
Hey, lady.
What are you doing over here?
Just passing by.
Don't talk to that freak, honey.
Come on.
Hey, lady.
Wait, don't go.
Let's do this, Nick.
Back here.
Dave.
Back here behind the curtain.
Come on.
Take a good look at him.
But his passage.
Take this envelope.
Go down to the pier.
This is a passage to America.
Just shut up and go now.
What's in the envelope, man?
Just shut up and go.
Give it to the man on the boat.
So Dave was able to escape London and made his way to America.
Where?
Where he was adopted by a tribe of Iroquois who took him into the sacred cave of the bear droppings.
And they showed him there the paintings which predicted that someday a cowboy would come alone.
Him here.
And no way.
White cowboy arrived finally.
Prophecy come true.
Better known as...
...the Pops of the Pops.
Moms and dads.
And made their way through Wolf Pass.
And we had a nice and tight.
There's your grandpa there.
Oh, he was quite a figure.
A little danger.
Knock him down.
Bring out the women that they might receive the seed of the Dave mask.
He was brave.
I can't go all the way back.
No, no.
I'm going far enough.
No, no, no.
Come on, come on.
You gotta see the rest of the exhibit, Dave.
Just, just hunker down.
Come on.
That's not a matter of moments.
Come on, now.
And hence when the first wood teachers came to our land,
and here's about four or five of us attacking about 300 of them.
No way!
La hay!
Cowardly day!
No dumb!
No, no, no!
...took them in as his... as a god.
They worshiped him tied to their totem pole.
Bring out the burning pot!
Okay, you guys.
They decided to feed him to himself as an act of sacrifice.
Okay, now, once you get the Papa-Namanskins ready...
And they danced around the pot.
...and the papayas...
...as the lonesome Dave ate his own self.
And you guys can all join in, too.
Once I get down to below my navel, I don't know if I'm gonna stop.
And here came the ballerinas.
...popping like a little pork.
...like a little pork.
Hundreds and hundreds of ballerinas in pink foofoos.
Oh, my God, I've never seen such a display of Hursuit masculinity.
The lady in the farthest corner...
...of your left eye...
They're all g-males!
...appears to be wearing a, uh, wolfhandsuit...
Oh, my God! They have no underwear!
...of some sign of a walnut-cocked-up Halloween day...
These were supposed to be okay Indian!
...Hursuits.
And as we can see from bottom undertop, the off-camera shot shows her...
with Pappy in the bar room beforehand,
and isn't it wonderful how she can move the lower thing there?
But slowly the drug began to wear off,
and Lonesome slowly awoke from his peyote-induced trance
of wonderful ballerinas,
and looked around him to see an altogether different reality.
I'm doing a power wedge.
And, uh, I, oh, man.
Oh, my God, I'm back in that thing again.
Oh, shh, shh, shh.
Oh, my God.
This is a freak.
Look at the freak.
He's a beautiful ballerina.
Thrimble his arms.
Remain calm.
Then remove his legs.
And reattach them.
Now your elbows.
I think the process is about to be...
Now he will remove his head and reattach it.
Notice how we are able to keep his head alive,
all by itself, hooked up to these pumps and bellows.
That's quite a sandwich right there.
It comes with a side of slow and fright,
and if you'll check closely, Dave's ears are actually paranormal.
That's what they used to call them in the old country.
He can actually hear sights and sounds below his own vision.
That is, if he's looking at anything,
he'll see something that's not even a sight.
Oh, look at that errand stare.
Let's scoop it out and put a candle in it.
Look at the freak.
Please evacuate me, Harriet.
Look, he'll eat a live chicken or veggie.
Please.
Look at that.
Hey, Dave.
Hey, Dave, come on over here.
Get a little closer to the window.
Can you hear me?
I can hear you.
You're just fine, man.
I got a little proposition for you.
See these things I got in my hand?
They glow in the dark.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
See, there are three of these things.
You hold them together like this, and you can do anything.
You could be out of here in a matter of minutes, see, Dave?
My eyes are so heavy.
We have brought you here to pass on the sacred orb.
Oh, my God.
Dave, listen.
I'm trying to make it go away.
You have passed all the tests.
No, I can't look at you.
I won't pay attention.
He has even passed the sacred stone on his kidney.
No, no.
No, I have not.
I have.
I've passed the sacred stone.
Oh, my God, a bloody wad of my own existence.
Now prepare to receive the orb.
This is what I was made to use.
This is what I was born for.
Bend over, human.
I can't even re-cross with my own legs.
Mm-hmm.
I'm going to have to get out of here.
.
No, no, no, no.
I am the colonel of the summer people.
Oh, thank your function and the daunts.
The protuberance appears to have been clipped off in one of the frost addresses.
We can see here the colon area is nice and shiny and clean.
Nurse, sutures.
They contain a few remnants of the toxic materials.
Scalpel.
Just scoop it out like this.
You have the vacuum cleaner.
Vacuum.
Vacuum cleaner.
Vacuum nurse.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to interrupt you.
You were playing golf while I was...
I was scooping out the patient's brain.
I was on the clamp.
Hold.
Nurse, clamp.
Hold it for me.
Where is that candle?
Suction.
Right here.
Five slaps.
Clamp.
And a little bit of cappuccino for the whole group.
Well, it looks like he isn't going to make it.
I don't think so.
I'm glad to say that we've wasted our time.
Let's go ahead and drink the cappuccino before it gets cold.
What about the next patient?
Do we have any of the same ones?
Let's move this one out before he gets cold.
He's going to start stinking, I think, in a while.
He was already cold when we were.
Yeah, yeah.
What was his name?
Jave?
Lonesome.
A so-called lonesome cowboy.
They called him Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
He lived...
Thousands of years ago.
He was a playboy of the streets.
A man with only one good rancid eye that did the work of many.
Lonesome bovine boy.
His legend lives today.
Across the great plains of Ohio.
Scrawled upon bathroom walls across America.
Rest areas across the highways.
And a plastic cathedral of hair somewhere in Oval and Ohio.
Truckers still fill the citizens' banderades with his name.
Late into the night, he's prepared to end his own life.
To fervor his bioparkal purportions.
Yes, Dave finally achieved fame.
But at what price?
At what?
Price.
Well, we'll be back on Larry King Live, talking about what price?
Fame and fortune.
You're on the air with Larry King Live.
Human.
Shut up.
Shh!
Humans.
A quick check into the background.
This man reveals that not only is he probably a remnant of the Pleistocene era or some bygone era like that.
But he's also well, well underdeveloped to intake.
And in comparison with other Pleistocene man's, or woman's of his same peer group and function.
Look here.
We see his liver and spleen are filled with tiny pieces of roots and drawings by inarticulate women.
And some men are like, oh, she's got a baby.
And sometimes when the moon is right, blue, blue artifacts emerge from the top of his skull.
All hands on deck.
All hands off my dick.
Have you seen the white whale in the trousers of the Dave men?
Eh?
You snobs!
Ha ha ha!
Have you seen the white whale?
Never!
Captain, you're getting a hernia.
Sit down.
You're going to disturb the metallic haircut.
Spit off the right test liquid.
Oh, hang on, lad.
We'll see the whale.
I'll never rest till I see the whale turn belly up in the sea.
Captain, I'd like to remind you that we are sailing on a kind of a psychoplasmic sea, if you will.
And the whale is bound to eat you alive.
I've no way around it because he's got control of your mind.
Oh, I'm well aware, mate, that the whale is but a metaphor for me.
Oh, I go, I'm a metaphor.
I'm a metaphor.
But I'll, I'll, hand me that harpoon and I'll go for it.
Well, Captain, I'm afraid I'm going to have to hand you the metaphoric harpoon, if you will, because the real harpoon resembles a large, large packing paper tube.
However, on the other hand, it is as fine a silver sterling.
A sterling steel harpoon capable of taking down any metaphoric whale.
Bend over, human.
Friends, bend over for Lord God, Lord God, for God.
God is coming.
Bend over, human.
This is a great sign for a change.
I killed the Tsar and its ministers.
Anastasia's green evade.
I'll hold a tank at the General's rank.
When the Blitzkrieg rage and the body's dead.
I'm pleased to meet you
Hope you guessed my name
Cause what's possible in you
Is the nature of my game
I watched with glee while your kings and queens
Fought for ten decades for the gods they made
I shouted out who killed the canadians
When after all it was you and me
Let me please you
Please introduce myself
I'm a man of wealth and taste
I lay traps for troubadours
Who get killed before they reach Bombay
Pleased to meet you
Hope you guessed my name
Cause what's possible in you
Is the nature of my game
Pleased to meet you
Hope you guessed my name
Cause what's possible in you
Is the nature of my game
Pleased to meet you
East, West, North
West, West, North
It's you, it's me
I can't wait
It's you
Satan is real too
And hell is a real place
A place of everlasting punishment
Satan is real
Working in spirit
You can see him
And hear him
In this world every day
Satan is real
Working with power
He can tell you
And lead you astray
It's what you need
It's time for your bath now, Stan
Don't be afraid of those tepid
I'm glad those tepid
Giant robot automatic
Butt-raping machine
Finally was shut down
Yes, it is
finally shut down but he's in a dormant stage right now take a look through the monitor there
he is he's waiting to go and in five seconds if you don't answer this question you're going to
be attacked by the butt raping hideous cyborg robot monster you just described i can't go into
it it's too long and the question is yes yes yes a lovely miss weed will read the question stang are
you ready you've got your lifeline open we'd like to close it up if you could it's kind of hideous
to behold oh whoa now wait a minute this isn't what i signed up yes it is an asteroid with a
sexual appetite but this wasn't in the contract now you're on time you're being i want to go back
this isn't funny we want to go back we need to help help help absolutely depressing uh no no no
with more feeling help help this can't be happening
i can't be hearing this
life out of balance
i never should have done it i knew i'd end up here if i kept doing it
i just couldn't stop and now look what happened
you see the hallucination and hallucination of what could happen
i mean it was just a satire i guess
um i guess i must have messed up real bad i guess if southern baptist was ronnie cox
after all. Don't leave a mess
where you go.
Leave a mess where you've been.
What good is this $90 gonna
do me here?
Money means nothing.
The soul means nothing.
It took
Salmaister to triple your money back.
I thought hell was a big joke.
I thought it was a big joke.
Hell is an illusion.
All my friends are gonna be there,
I used to say.
Hey, all my friends
are Dave,
Chaz, Princess Wee.
What are you guys doing
here in Cleveland, Wisconsin
for eternity?
We're not really here, we're just kind of like
a figment of your imagination.
It's part of
the Dave brain.
Oh,
what do you mean it's not real?
It's like
matrix to the tenth power.
Just part of the Dave...
No,
you,
you mean me,
my whole life,
all of reality was all,
all along,
it was just part of Dave's imagination,
not my own?
You mean Dave was the one who was holding it all together all along,
but now he's waking up?
That's right, Sting, baby,
he's waking up and he's got a problem.
He's grown 400 pounds in the last half an hour.
His hypothalamus is the size of a large tubular object.
You might call that bowling alley down there by your shoe.
And he's ready to sting like a bee and smoke like a smoke thing.
If you're not ready when he's ready, there's the door.
It's smocked.
Will the Dave ever wake up from the dream?
No, and void.
Or will the dream wake up from Dave?
Wow, man.
Well, I...
It was 1942, I think it was.
Dave, inside of Dave's brain, it's beautiful.
It's like a journey to the center of the earth.
Inside the brain is a whole other world.
It's sparkling.
Those waterfalls, those mushrooms, those sunsets.
I think it was.
Yeah, it was in Oca-hocca.
Those galaxies, those signals.
Those eggs and stars.
Look, those mountains.
Those palm trees.
I forget what the hell it was.
It's like a black light poster, only it's alive.
Those time-lapse clouds and roses opening.
She's still the same.
Well, I'd love to, but I'm not really a human being.
I'm not really human.
Wow.
Dave's brain is beautiful after all.
Oh, I...
It's nothing like the hell that I imagined it to be.
Oh, it's so shiny.
It's like the planet Xeron.
It's...
It feels like home.
Oh, my God.
Look at the little cherubim dancing.
Look off in the distance, scampering naked women.
He's drooling, but it's beautiful.
It's like a fountain of cherry candy drops.
Little magicians and sorcerers running around.
They're trying to put a little pointed hat on his head right now, but...
No, they're putting it on.
Shines from the land.
The plants and brownies resting under the mushrooms.
The most beautiful thing I've ever seen.
Uh-oh.
I'm in trouble now.
Who unplugged me?
Shit, man.
Man, somebody trip on the cord.
Man.
What the hell's...
What's...
Oh, my God.
Oh, I'm sorry, you guys.
I think I...
Who are you?
Pulled the plug on Dave.
Here I am.
Who are you?
Oh, could be someone.
I don't even remember, man.
There he come.
Who am I?
I was just walking in like...
A, but anyway, what was his name?
Well, I don't wanna, you know.
I don't wanna give up yet?
Hell, he's moving like a beast.
Making my head hurt.
the Dave brain.
Dave, Dave, come back to us.
It's
been 43 years,
Dave. We missed you.
These beautiful dreams.
I don't ever want to go swimming
again.
I know he'll come back.
Look at him laying there like a
seven-year-old.
Dancing to weird techno beat music and bothering me.
Call me
Davey.
I know he'll come back to me.
I think he's in Al DeMarco's in my closet
arguing with him.
Oh my God.
He's the weird toothless old mountain
guy.
He's only got one eye and he's pointing it right
at me.
It's okay, Dave.
You've clicked
your heels three times.
We're going home.
You've done your part.
It's over, Dave.
You're starting to smell a little bit, but it's okay.
You can stop.
It's okay.
No, really.
There is no more.
No more rapid eye movement.
No arms.
Wake up now.
Peace
is yours
finally, Dave.
Your rest has come.
On fronds.
They'll make a religion around you.
Your peace.
That will last for thousands of years.
They'll think that you died
back there
on that yard arm.
But it won't be true.
You get to go home now.
It's part of the protection program offered by
the powers that be.
If you believe in Dave.
If you believe in Dave out there.
Pick your nose.
Pick your nose for Dave.
Everyone who can hear me now.
You can do it.
Everyone within the sound of our voices.
Pick our nose.
Reach down there and stick your nose.
Stick your finger up there.
And then just twist it around.
And Dave will come back.
Just twist it.
It's working.
Take the mucus out of your nose.
He's coming back.
He's working.
He's coming too.
He's coming back.
He's picking kids.
I can see it.
It's
Is the eyes are quivering?
It's dead again.
Oh well.
Huh.
Figures.
Well how long can we go on reanimating the guy who died five times in the last half an hour?
It's like when a cat plays with a little lizard it finds down in Arizona.
And everything seems fun and then suddenly the lizard just sort of starts twitching.
And the cat tries to keep playing with it like it's okay.
Yes.
You can tell there's something very wrong.
Very, very wrong.
Maybe not.
Maybe everything is wrong.
At least there's no missing seems to me.
I mean the thing is we have to powder ton that piece every day the luck of math
And I takes it out just enough.
Throw him here as a
This mountain..
A while ago.
Yeah.
I've forgotten for a while now we were told to play stones.
Did it meet though?
Well yeah.
Thank you.
Oh.
Damn, that hurts.
I know that's really slavery.
ESO Beach Party.
ESO Beach
Party.
Yeah, well, it's
like that time in China.
And each and every one Sunday, Yanny Bunny and Nett Funchichello is down with everything else he's done.
It's a first and annual beach party, Bunker John.
Yours truly, the rest of the grade.
I'll bring the beach balls if you bring the cornstarch.
I'll bring the...
I'll bring the Saturn boosters if you bring the ocean.
I'll bring the sodium nitride pellets.
I'll bring the Apollo space capsule if you bring the sand.
And I'll bring Crashback if I get old again and die.
Can you please loan me it?
I'll bring Lonesome Cowboy Dave if you'll just get out of my hair, shut up, and go die.
And I'll bring your hair back.
Time to get out of here.
One wave, one magic wand.
We gotta leave the Dave brand for another week.
Thank God.
But it'll be there.
Oh, I'm afraid it will.
Pulsing like a diamond.
You don't think it's not there.
I heard that Dave died on your show, man.
That guy is out there.
That guy is totally out there.
That guy is so...
Man, where does he get that stuff?
Where do you...
Man, what is that dude on?
Where do you find that thing?
Yeah, where'd you find that Dave thing?
How'd you get that all the way up there?
How you gonna get that out of there?
Yeah, well, I just can't believe you got the whole thing in.
That's it.
Oh, is that a foot?
What's hanging out of the bottom?
That's gross.
Did you sit on somebody's whole body?
Pull that Dave thing out.
That's an animal.
I thought it was a human foot.
It's as big as a human foot.
It's a vomit.
That's not what that is.
Oh, look, it's growing again.
Yelly, yelly, yelly, yelly, yelly, yelly.
Yelly, yelly, yelly.
Yelly, yelly, yelly, yelly, yelly.
Till next week.
Keep your hat on tight.
You're back to the wind in here.
Sacking.
Saddle there.
There's always tomorrow for dreams to come true.
Give me that sack.
Believe in your dreams.
Come what may.
I know that's right.
There's always tomorrow for dreams to come true.
Come what may.
There's so much to do.
We have no eyes.
You'll see with our eyes.
We have no good night.
We all pretend.
The rainbow has an end.
We all pretend the rainbow has an end.
And you'll be there, my friend, someday.
I don't know.
There's always tomorrow for dreams to come true.
Tomorrow is not far away.
Thanks, kid.
It's been a wonderful time.
Thanks.
Thanks for pulling my chest.
See you, Uncle Dave.
See you next week.
Thanks, Nick.
Everybody wave bye-bye.
Thanks for the chocolates.
And hey, we'll see you all.
Bye.
bye.
Bah.
Here's our address.
Got that pencil ready?
P.O. Box 807 Glen Rose, Texas 76043.
That's where you send things to me to play.
The show, The Hour of Slack, is the voice of the church of the subgenius.
More about that at www.subgenius.com, which includes a catalog of books and other things.
Friends.
Like everything else that I've been through, it opened up my eyes.
And now I'm one toe over the line, sweet Jesus.
One toe over the line.
Sitting down down in a railway station.
Waiting for the train to go home.
Waiting that the train is at the train of your time.
Sitting down down in a railway station.
One toe over the line.
Waiting for the train to go home.
As mayor of the Monskin City, in the county of the land of Oz, I welcome you most regally.
But we've got to...
verify it legally to see if she is morally ethically spiritually physically positively
absolutely undeniably and reliably
higher
this podium with our unique distance around doing start the show with a
prayer up here yeah great big no I don't call him that
God has a poor empty
call man here's our air watch out for the trap door there we're boring that
don't take about a minute oh excuse me but I get a couple minutes of your
speeches