Bud Light presents the subgenius power of swag.
Real American heroes.
Today we salute you, real American heroes.
Don't stay in too long, or everyone will shout.
Finish quickly and come back.
Oh, well.
Anyway, it seems silly to talk about basic Bob-ology to a bunch of hardcore subgeniuses
who've come to this special occasion, and they know Bob backwards, forwards, and sideways,
inside out, and reversed.
And not a pretty sight.
Well, we've seen it all.
About every distortion that could be done to a Bob head has been done by this point,
many of them by Ivan Stang with his many colorful films of clouds and rocks and oceans
all over the world.
All turning into that leering, dripping, mutating face of Bob that's everywhere you look,
no matter which direction you look, trying to see something that, well, you know, I've
seen those films.
Well, my office is like that in real life.
You can't escape.
Yeah, everywhere you look, there's that face.
Imagine that.
Having your boss's picture everywhere you look.
Get to work, Stang.
You better get to work slacking off.
Right-o, Mr. Duck.
Bob?
I'm slacking off as hard as I can, sir.
I'm really, I'm about to die from slack.
Well, the proof is in the pudding, Stang.
Hey, memberships are down.
We're only selling...
Actually, I shouldn't give numbers.
It's so...
Yeah, don't give out any actual data like that.
Let's just say that if you don't work hard enough, there might not be a place for you at Bobco.
Take that advisedly.
And all the legends you've heard about us.
Using slave labor in Malaysia and children being paid in cigarettes to...
Nobody's doing what they don't want to do.
...draw dobs.
It's hard to get cigarettes there anyway.
We don't want to spend money on printing presses.
Yeah.
Those are mostly just rumors.
Remember that movie, King Kong Meets Godzilla, where they pass out cigarettes to the kids?
That's kind of like our outreach in Malaysia.
I don't remember that.
You don't remember that when they come to the island, they pass out cigarettes to all the little kids?
Does anyone remember that movie?
Has anyone seen King Kong Meets Godzilla?
Nobody?
I saw it.
Oh, Tempura.
But I saw it in the drive-in with my parents.
How sad.
Well, it's time you see it again, Stang.
It actually contains stop-motion tentacles during the giant squid attack scene.
But don't forget, it does show that they pass out cigarettes to the kids.
It's an amazing scene.
Well, how come that's not in Arise?
I couldn't say.
We'll have to talk to Court Holland about that.
I don't know.
He joined Scrub Genius about two months ago.
The guy that edited Arise, or co-edited Arise.
You'll never scrub that subgenius scene away.
He did most of the old movie clip stuff.
I more did the whole overall outline of it, and then he filled in a lot of blanks.
But yeah, he joined Scrub Genius.
A lot of people do this.
They join Scrub Genius, and I let them in, and then they never, they just lurk.
Court Holland made a movie of my personal judgment.
A personal journey to Dobstown.
Is that in your archives?
No, because he shot that in a really poor way.
Oh, well.
It was awful.
You couldn't hear a word.
All you could hear was, you know.
The motor of that boat going up that river.
Yeah.
And you could tell it wasn't a river in the Amazon.
Drowns out my narration.
Well, we have to take it easy on ourselves, you know.
We can't.
That was done when cameras were huge.
Like the size of that Jim Beam bottle.
Instead of the size of your thumbnail or your glasses.
How long am I supposed to sit up here just staring at this Jim Beam bottle?
Well, you can do more than stare.
That's not your house.
It's mine, and you're welcome to sample it.
Take some samples.
I bragged online that I had bought you that, and somebody sent me $17.50 towards your booze.
I'm told this is better than old girl data.
That's half of $35.
I like that.
He's a big spender.
I think old granddad's better.
I was told, though, by an authoritative person that this was better.
It's what they said.
It's a buck more expensive than old granddad.
Hey, I noticed you mentioned Kamchatka vodka.
What?
No.
Please don't associate me with that.
You brought it up.
No, no, wait.
What?
Hold on, hold on.
I disavow any mention of Kamchatka vodka.
Oh, shoot.
You can't turn her to an idle remark.
Mike C. Todd brought Kamchatka vodka.
Don't look at me.
I didn't do it.
I'm not responsible.
All these designer vodkas they've got now, lemon, lime, and so forth.
That's the one I bought.
Watermelon juice.
Cheap, but it's not too bad.
We can edit this part out of the show so no one else hears it.
I didn't do it.
I never drank Kamchatka vodka.
It's gross.
That you remember.
I take it back.
How about tequila?
It's not that gross.
It does have a bit of a motor oil taste.
But I always thought that was what vodka was supposed to be.
It's awful.
Oily?
It's like the worst.
Huh?
Motor oil.
30 weight.
Yeah.
It's got a...
You could probably run a lawnmower with it.
Not the lawnmower.
It's got like the shortest time span of hangover, drinking to hangover.
It's as soon as it touches your tongue, you're hungover already.
That explains it.
Anyway, it doesn't have sugar.
Maybe it does.
No, no.
It's just pure...
It's motor oil, basically, with some kind of...
Hooch in it.
Hmm.
Pouring oil on troubled waters.
Yeah.
Well, gin, of course, is oily.
What can you do?
Nothing is perfect.
You have to shop around for your method of getting slack.
Well, you can buy jugs of moonshine now.
The labeled moonshine, which it seems like that defeats the whole purpose.
The fun of moonshine is that it was illegal.
Yeah.
Right.
How can you...
Yeah, if it's bottled in some factory...
It lacks...
It lacks authenticity.
Making it authentic to today's life.
That's like legal marijuana.
It's just...
What is the point?
Yeah, what's that going to do to all our friends who are old, scruffy dope growers and dealers?
It's going to ruin their lives.
All because some namby-pamby goo-goos have to make marijuana legal.
Oh, man.
It's a good thing it's still illegal in Ohio.
Are we never...
Are we perpetually dissatisfied?
Yes.
The minute they legalize that crap, I'm mad too.
I'm mad too.
Bob.
Never touch it again.
Yeah, I'm too mad, Bob.
We can't be satisfied until we're aboard our personal saucers.
We have to give thanks for the conspiracy because elsewise, where would we be?
How would we know what to hate?
What would we have to fight against?
Yes, it's what repels us like the pole of a magnet.
Yeah.
We have other subgeniuses to fight against, which, if you look on the internet, is going over...
Well, they say they're subgeniuses.
They claim they're...
They're credentials, but...
Oh, it's always easiest to fight the enemy that's most familiar.
You know, your next-door neighbor or the other person in your members-only subgenius club.
The enemy that's most like you, but with one tiny difference.
Right.
It's the one you hate more than the one that's completely, totally different from you in every respect.
The Baptists and Methodists hate each other so much more...
Oh, it's so good.
I love it.
...than they...
Really, than they hate even the Catholics or the Muslimics.
We should just declare war on First Church of the Last Laugh.
Again.
I don't know.
Was that ever done?
No.
We declared war on them?
Oh, that's what Philo was saying then.
Oh, Philo just likes to stir things up.
Well, okay, if we haven't done it yet, then we should definitely do it for the first time,
especially if it hasn't been done before.
Death to St. Stupid and the First Church of the Last Laugh.
We want the last laugh.
Yeah, we want the last laugh.
Bob is stupider than St. Stupid.
Yeah.
But they have been ecumenically yoked.
And at the St. Stupid Pavilion at Burning Man, yes, Burning Man again,
they have allowed subgenius to have a department there, which has no other presence.
Gee, that's rather condescending.
Well, where else is subgenius to be found?
No one else will come forward and do it.
And they themselves are next to a heretical sect of splitters from the First Church of the Last Laugh
called the Fathers of St. Stupid, who go a different way.
They're the ones that like to get naked, right?
No, they don't.
But they sure like to say insulting things about St. Stupid and his church.
Well, that's, you know, as soon as the Church of the Subgenius got on its feet,
of course, there had to be anti-subgenius schisms made by the most dedicated subgeniuses.
The naked people actually do show up for the St. Stupid parade.
The bleeding head of Arnold Palmer Launcher Society.
We kind of disavowed them.
Oh, speaking of which.
Because they're all...
Ugly.
I just remembered something.
What was that, Stang?
I don't have...
Of course, I don't have the true, original bleeding head of Arnold Palmer.
I would think not.
We'd all be dead.
But I do have a really good replica.
And I would think, and it's been a long time since we had a head launching.
And it wasn't just invented by the hyperclites.
Papa Joe Mama did it a few years ago.
No, well, we all did it.
We've all been caught, you know, launching heads here and there.
Oh, right, right.
Yeah, that's right.
Here at Wisteria, Papa Joe did it.
Was that the first year?
The first year at Wisteria?
I don't know.
It was some kind of a head.
I don't know if...
It was some sports figure head, I think.
Mass Wisteria.
It may have been Tiger Woods.
I don't think it was.
But I do have a Palmer head.
I think it was some kind of alien head.
A recognizable, official Palmer head.
Hand-painted.
Bleeding.
Ever bleeding.
Like a fountain.
And that head, we could...
We have to think about that.
Well, don't let me keep you back.
You know, if you all have any good ideas about some new way...
Slingshot.
You know, we have these rockets.
Yeah, big slingshot.
With a...
We could stick a...
The light bulb's good.
Anybody got a giant rubber band like in a Warner Brothers Roadrunner cartoon?
That's what we need, is a...
Well, we...
We can put a rock in it.
We can put a rock inside that rubber head to give it some inertia.
We talked about possibly a monster was responsible for that little dog's disappearance.
Oh, that's silly.
But, of course it is silly.
But I'm just saying, if there were a monster, that launching that bleeding head might be the only weapon that could conceivably stop it.
If that comes up, we'll have to think about it.
Yeah, we should work on a big slingshot.
They have those big slingshots for water balloons.
Right.
And it's summer, which means they're out there somewhere.
Well, we don't need to go buy one.
They should.
They splattered themselves with the balloons.
He can make one out of logs and skin.
His own skin.
It's pretty stretchy.
He's very dedicated.
That stretches it all right.
He donated his hair to the church one time, and he had about as much as me.
Look at that.
Greater love hath no man.
I can stick it all the way out at the end of my arm.
He's been at it longer than you, baby bear.
You'll catch up.
We need to trim this.
It's getting way down in there.
Huh?
There you go, Stan.
You've nurtured this Delilah in the church who's sapping you of your strength by cutting off your manly hair.
Oh, bit in pieces.
Yeah, she did actually give me a haircut this morning.
I didn't know you messed with the bottom of it.
Clean up America.
Get a haircut.
That's the part that keeps my ass crack warm.
It'll grow back.
It's a living, growing hair.
No, actually.
I'm not so sure about that.
Oh, yeah?
Well.
It's getting kind of thin.
I can hide most of it in one of my ears.
Well, I could talk about my own ailments also, but I'm not sure that's of great interest to our audience today.
They don't want to hear a couple crotchety old people falling apart want to hear other such stories.
Well, we were talking earlier about how Bob is kinky and likes some kinky stuff.
Well, we'll get to that.
There have been times where he likes to flatline.
He gets a kick out of it because he knows he's going to come back.
Hmm.
He has had us flay him alive.
Oh, don't stop now.
Oh, please.
Finish it.
Get the rest.
This feels pretty good.
I might get to like it.
He's had us give him organ transplants while he's conscious.
He's had us.
He's had us blow him up with dynamite because when the smoke clears there,
he's sitting there with a few band-aids and dark smudges.
Just like those cartoons.
For a humorous effect.
Right.
He got tired of the little death.
He wanted the big death.
Yeah.
Or he gets the same from the big death that most people get from the little death.
But Bob does nothing by small niggling increments,
but always in one huge blowout blast.
Well, remember, it started with him tricking Puzzling Evidence into shooting him to death
right in front of us.
What a chump.
And then not six months later, he tricked Mark Mothersbaugh of Devo into doing it again.
I was there both times, actually.
So, yeah, he's...
And then he just moved up.
It's like we weren't deadly enough.
I understand he went to fight the Taliban single-handedly for a while
because he heard about...
That beheading stuff, that sounded fun.
You know, we can't pretend to...
We just got the we.
We can't put ourselves in Bob's head.
There's nothing there.
We doesn't agree.
We don't know what nothing truly is.
You know?
Is nothing sacred?
Space isn't really nothingness.
But what's inside Bob's head?
Well, it's the same thing that's in his pipe.
Our faith, friends.
Our trust.
Our faith in Bob.
The F.I.B.
Praise that man, Bob.
Right.
No Fliberty gibbet.
A living, breathing, sanctifying, slack-filled savior.
On the other hand, my butt's getting tired talking about him.
You've been talking with that, then?
No, no.
I'm just tired of sitting here.
Actually, what time is it?
Is it past my...
It's past three.
We finished one hour.
It's quarter after three.
Oh.
Wow.
We won't be here until five.
That's for sure.
I have a shift.
Oh.
Oh, at the swag table.
Which means someone else can come up.
All right.
Yes, we have room now.
Baby Bear is leaving the stage.
If someone else wishes to come up...
I want to leave the stage.
Well, you can do whatever you want.
Or you can go and sit at the registration shack.
But I think the sitting is the problem, right?
The lack of motion.
The lack of momentum.
Actually, I think I need to go meditate
in one of those...
sweat lodges.
They love lighting the room.
Well, make sure you do.
Pretty soon, too.
Well, I...
Princess, why don't you come up here
and just sit here and laugh
while Dr. Hal talks.
Laugh.
Let's hear that laugh in the dark.
And Pisces says Skull has stories to tell.
Oh, headphones.
Oh, boy.
I'll...
Yeah.
There we go.
Good Lord.
Now I hear everything in stereophonic sound
with all the sound effects,
the savagery and splendor,
the might, the music,
and the miracle of X-Day
blazing into my ears.
So how come there's only one pair of earphones
in this lousy...
in this...
on this historic occasion?
Yes, I must say
that it is a signal honor
to be seated here
with the subgenius Archons
and...
and, uh,
bobcasting
for perhaps a future Earth.
A better world than this.
A place where inexplicable insects
will not suddenly gang up on you.
Or maybe they will.
We must adjust ourselves
to an entirely new scale of values.
The old world will die
and the old beliefs along with it.
And after traveling through
many hundreds of years,
hundreds of universes
and sub-universes,
one ultimately comes to
the so-called
end of the rainbow,
the punch line.
I refer you to the
afterlife diagram
in Revelation X,
the undescended, uh,
new testicle of the
book of subgenius,
the second subgenius book.
Now out of print,
like the third one,
also out of print,
hard to come by,
accruing in value
constantly.
But, of course,
and I've said this before,
nothing is more valuable
or rare than the
lost subgenius comic book,
Bob's Comics and Stories,
because the run was small
and then they were all stored
in an illegal Chinese fireworks factory,
which exploded and destroyed
most of the run.
So although you can see these online
and order them,
they are expensive.
Except, of course,
to the true blue subgenius
who will spend on
any old subgenius thing.
And it's a pity,
because they've got
great stories,
including one horrible story,
so horrible that it's not
recommended for anyone
who is subject to
fits of depression.
That is, of course,
Care Bob Meets,
no, Care Dog Meets Pea Bear
by Ivan Stang,
illustrated by
St. Paul Mavridis.
And I have work in the book,
too.
There's a lot of good stuff in there,
but no one will ever see it.
Just as when they made
the medieval cathedrals,
sometimes those stonecutters
would make some little gargoyle
or something that was way up there
in an angle that nobody could ever see.
But God would see it.
God would know
what they did.
And that's why they're there.
And a lot of work done
in the Church of the Subgenius
is work that's done in the church.
That only Bob will ever see.
But that doesn't mean
it's not worth doing.
For one thing,
practice makes perfect.
It'll set you
into a better channel,
on a better path.
Do you agree, Princess Wee?
I absolutely agree.
Yes, I saw you shaking
your head at some of our
flights of fancy before.
Yes, but the audience
can't hear that, so.
No, but I definitely want to do
what you will approve here,
not the other way,
but the other way around.
Oh, I very much approve.
I agree.
Right.
So, when the roll is called up yonder,
I'll be there.
When the roll is called up yonder,
Right?
In the suite, by and by,
we will meet at the beautiful shore.
Yes, and I'll be there.
Yes, we'll all be there.
In our white linen undergarments.
Those are provided.
Provided for free.
We won't have to worry about supply,
chain, supply and demand,
all that stuff.
Are they magic underwear?
Apparently.
Won't we be in some transhuman state?
Well, obviously, the underwear
must expand to fit that, too.
Yes, I guess so.
Yeah, it's logical.
I'm only speaking on a basis
of what one might logically infer.
I possess no secret knowledge
about the mystery that lies
behind the veil.
Well,
Oh, sure you don't, Hal.
Sure you don't.
I'm just, I mean, it's,
nobody knows what happens
when the fellow in the bright nightgown
comes to your door,
takes your number.
Strange is it not
that of the myriads who before us
pass the door of darkness through,
not one returns to tell us of the road
which, to discover,
he must travel to.
Indeed.
And I would even add,
the revelations of devout and learned
that rose before us
and as prophets burned
are all but stories
which arose from sleep
they told their comrades
and to sleep returned.
It's a pity they didn't have the wine
that we do.
I mean, we know the way it really is.
Their religions are false,
ours are true,
but it's necessary to have the,
have something,
to kick against,
like the conspiracy,
as we mentioned before.
Subvert the conspiracy from within
and be a glorious subgenius without.
Huh?
Hmm?
Mm-hmm.
Indeed.
Uh-huh.
Yeah, anybody wants to throw anything in here,
if I'm leaving anything out,
now's the time to bring it out
when the secrets of all hearts are made known
and the sea gives up its dead
and monsters walk the earth
and so forth.
Meanwhile,
continue to enjoy the projections
to my left.
They are valuable educational assistance
which will bring you further in alignment
with the sacred doctrine of Dobbs.
Also, this could be the point to say,
if you have submissions for the Bull Dada auction,
we need to start collecting them
to make this Bull Dada auction
the greatest in subgenius history.
So we all go out with a bang.
Yes, indeed.
Bring them to the stage
and let them gather around here.
Follow in Mr. Sistar's golden footsteps
because he's already gifted us
with a bunch of ultra-watchable DVDs.
Yes.
But we'll even accept VHS
as we have in previous years.
And white elephants of all kinds.
Right.
That's your elephant.
Yes.
Anyway, we'll take them.
Just bring them up.
So on that great day mentioned in your schedules,
you can begin.
Just get a taste of the avalanche load of swag
coming your way when all goes right.
And visit the swag table over there
where Reverend Baby Bear,
will happily sell you
any number of Dobbs, Chucks,
Chkis, and Doodads.
How many of you don't have
a little Bob pin to wear?
You know, it's a little pin
and somebody will ask you about it.
And you can tell them about subgenius.
Yes, they'll ask you about it
at the worst time possible
when you are in trouble
by the side of the road or whatever.
And then you have to start talking about Bob
and so on.
And it's awkward.
But you can be a proselytizer,
an evangelizer,
and tell the good news
to these oafs and pink vapid glorps
and so forth
and maybe shock them
out of their somnolence and sloth.
And from what I saw,
there's only just a tiny bit of things
sitting out that are for sale.
I think that the sales department
has a lot of unfurling to do.
Just ask.
And, and,
and she'll get it out for you.
She'll share it for you.
I believe there are some pretty neat things
Might even model it for you.
that are here that you
aren't seeing out on the tables.
I'd like to look through them.
Including a pin that is by Suds Pasha,
our sound guy.
Really?
I hadn't heard of this.
A pin?
Yes.
And, oh, there it is.
Yeah.
Medallion?
Mm-hmm.
Yes.
Can be used
How about that?
in many ways.
Yes, for many purposes.
Yes.
Which we won't enumerate here.
You have to use your imagination.
I mean, do I have to draw your picture?
No.
Suds will draw the picture.
Same thing with Dobbshead's pins.
That's right.
Well, the Dobbshead pin,
I,
it's such an easy way
to stand up just a little bit
for your subgenius inheritance.
I always try to,
to stick it on me somewhere.
Yeah, here it is.
See, I wear mine.
They're cheap
as things like that go,
considering what they indicate,
what they say about you.
The cloisonne pin
is a really nice pin.
Yes, it is, isn't it?
Yes, you can pin the tail
on the tail teller.
Sew?
Sew or knit.
That's right.
You can knit it also.
You can have a knit cap for Dobbs.
And look at this.
Look at that.
A Bob T-shirt
held out there
by Pisces now.
Tripping Bob, isn't it?
Or no?
Tripping, you say?
Well, look at,
it's not so much
as Bob is tripping.
It's the way Bob looks
when you are tripping.
I don't have to look.
Well, generally,
we have them in small,
medium, large,
extra large,
extra, extra large,
elephantine,
and circus tent.
It looks great from here.
I can't see the tripping aspect,
but my eyes are not
what they used to be.
Too many thousands of hours
looking through.
Yeah, I know.
I have,
I haven't come down for years.
I once was at a gathering
where I had seven males
who my husband claims
are not fabric-oriented
talking to me about
that very op art T-shirt
that Pisces was just holding up.
Look at that.
They were all trying to describe
that T-shirt
which Potter Nostril had worn
the weekend before.
And they were stumped
as to how to describe,
I guess op art
just didn't come to them.
I should mention that the,
those extra black shirts
are ones that
we don't sell in our catalog.
They,
because I don't have room
in the Slacker Mansion
for stacks upon stacks
of all these shirts
of different sizes.
Anticonformity.com makes those.
And I ordered a giant box
of his extra specs
and special different designs
for last X Day.
They arrived at the end of Starwood.
So they're fresh.
And they're here now.
They're fresh and you'll never,
they're not in our catalog.
They're in his catalog
but you'll never find them for sale
right in front of your face
like this again.
It was destiny.
You see,
last year didn't come off
as X Day but.
That image there
was done by Don Truby
of the Dancing Cigarettes
using scotch tape
and fake cigarettes.
It was a fake magazine.
Well, I'll be.
He would lay the scotch tape
onto a headline
on fake magazine
which had crappy ink
and peel it off
and then put the tape down
on the Dobbs head
and it would still hold
the headline
or the ad from fake magazines.
So kids,
you don't need Photoshop.
All you need is a crappy pulp magazine,
a Dobbs head
and some scotch magic tape.
And there you go.
You can make a colon.
That is old school.
You need those things.
Old school.
Yes, but you also need zeal.
The zeal and zest
which cause you to make the art.
Just zeal.
Yes, you can zeal it down
with scotch tape.
You need the zest also
to clean it
but basically you need
a motive force,
a motive power
to inspire you
to make subgenius art
what it is.
And it is what it is,
ladies and germs.
Hey, I can switch places with you now.
Very well.
You don't know what to do
with those headphones.
There's nothing coming through them.
And you wouldn't know what to do
because you're not the engineer.
There was a subgenius
who lived in a shoe
when he had subgenius earphones.
He didn't know what to do.
That's right.
The subgenius engineer is back.
You could actually hear through his earphones.
A rambling wreck from Georgia Tech.
And a subgenius engineer.
Oh my goodness.
Wow, the Obey shirts.
Those are like...
That's a tiny one.
We don't have very many
of the tiny little lady shirts.
Oh, that's for the females.
Slightly, yes.
Makes it easier to read.
Make your own art
with your body.
Oh, the koozies.
The beer koozies
are $5 a piece.
That's another thing
we don't carry in the catalog.
Dobbshead beer koozies.
They matter.
Magically keep your drink cold
or at least lukewarm
or room temperature anyway.
Eventually, they will keep it
at room temperature.
Sold at X-Day only.
Improve your drinking experience.
Anybody else want to be
on the hour of slack?
Slack.
Yes.
All you have to do is just...
Slack.
Skull, come on up, man.
The soft voice.
Well, I know that...
Slack, the luminous cloud.
Look, he's got a script.
We in ourselves rejoice.
Slack.
Whack.
I have to sit here
because I'm the only one
who knows how to work
these complicated radio chat machines.
Well, you just keep doing
that razzmatazz, Stang.
We're all counting on you
to turn those knobs
and twist those dials.
I'm a star.
Hi, Mom.
Oh, God.
I can't even speak now.
Hi, Mom.
I mean, she's dead,
but she can hear me.
Well, I hope that didn't do it.
I've got a sort of
a related Bible story.
Well, let's hear that one, Stang.
And I even have music
that goes with it.
Music?
Yeah.
Sweet music.
Well, it's not exactly
a Bible story.
Is this...
If music be the food of love,
play on.
Okay.
Count Jesus
is the name of this.
Count Jesus?
Yeah.
All right, let's hear it.
How do I count the Jesus?
How do I count the ways?
We'll see.
I'm waiting for my background music.
Waiting for that background music
to cue in.
Here we go.
The tale begins with Simon Peter,
a newly qualified Judean solicitor
journeying from Jerusalem
to Lord Christ Jesus'
crumbling remote castle
on the border of Galilee.
The purpose of his mission
is to provide legal support
to Jesus for a real estate transaction
overseen by Peter's employer
in Jerusalem.
At first, enticed by Jesus'
gracious love,
Peter soon discovers
that he's become a prisoner
in the castle.
He also begins to see
disquieting facets
of Jesus' normal life.
One night,
while searching for a way
out of the castle
and against Jesus'
strict admonition
not to venture outside
his room at night,
Peter falls under the spell
of three wanton female
Nazarenes,
or brides of Jesus,
referred to only as
the sisters in the novel.
He is saved at the last second
by the Lord Jesus Christ,
because he wants to keep
Peter alive long enough
to obtain needed legal advice
and teachings about Jerusalem,
his planned travel destination,
so as to be among the
quote,
teeming millions.
After preparations are made,
Jesus leaves the castle
and abandons Peter to the brides.
He barely escapes the castle
with his life.
Not long afterward,
a Roman galley,
the Golgotha,
having weighed anchor at Galilee,
runs aground on the shores
of the river Jordan,
during a fierce tempest.
All of the crew are missing
and presumed dead,
and only one body is found,
that of the captain
tied to the ship's helm.
The captain's log is recovered
and tells of strange events
that took place
during the ship's journey.
The disappearance of the entire crew,
apparently owing to
a malevolent presence
on board the ill-fated ship.
An animal described as a large dove
is seen on the ship
flying ashore.
The paraclete,
the ship's cargo,
is described as frankincense
and boxes of candy.
It is described as a
of myrrh,
or perfume,
from Nazareth.
Soon, Jesus is tracking
Peter's devoted fiance,
Hail Mary,
and her friend,
Mary Magdalene.
Magdalene receives
four marriage proposals
in one day,
from John,
Mark,
Luke,
and Matthew.
Magdalene accepts
Matthew's proposal
while turning down
John and Mark,
but all remain friends.
Jesus has a notable encounter
with John's patient,
John the Baptist,
an insane man
who means to consume
insects,
spiders,
birds,
and other creatures
in order to absorb
their life force.
John the Baptist
acts as a motion sensor,
detecting Jesus' proximity
and supplying clues accordingly.
Well, I probably should skip
over the whole story
because you know
many of the details
from coloring books.
But they get him eventually.
At the end,
after the group sterilizes
all of Jesus' lairs
in Jerusalem
by putting pieces
of deconsecrated host
in each box of earth,
Jesus,
flees back to his castle
in Nazareth,
transported in a box
pursued by Pontius Pilate's group
who themselves are aided
by Pontius Pilate
hypnotizing Mary
and questioning her
about the Messiah.
Pontius Pilate and Mary
camp in the forest
outside the castle
where the Nazarene sisters appear
and attempt to entice Mary
to join them entirely.
Pontius Pilate manages
to drive them away
and during daylight
goes to the castle
and kills them.
Shortly afterwards,
all converge,
the Lord Christ
just at sundown
under the shadow
of the castle.
Peter and Mark
rush to Jesus' box
which is being transported
by rabbis.
Peter shears Jesus
through the throat
with a circumcision knife
while the mortally wounded Mark
slashed by one of the rabbis
stabs the Lord Christ
with a spear in the heart.
Jesus crumbles to dust
and Mary is freed
from his curse.
But he will,
he will return
in the sequel.
He will return.
Count Jesus.
Are any of us safe from him?
Well, we will be shortly.
Him with a capital H.
We'll be safe shortly.
Aren't you glad
I skipped over some of that?
Yeah, some of it is too grisly
to tell.
Yeah, it's too horrible.
The things that the...
With dead people coming to life
and all that stuff.
We don't want to scare our listeners.
Well, the Nazarenes
take, use mind control.
Yes, they do.
They have a lot of pork in there.
They do.
Now, I have a rant here
written not by me,
but by fellow citizen Bork,
a subgenius in Norway.
Bork, you say?
Yeah, fellow citizen Bork.
He's a Norwegian.
His English is considerably better
than most American writers.
I bet his English is better
than most Americans Norwegian.
Anyway, it's a short one.
And it's about where...
Your job, working at a job.
It was called,
I wonder if the asshole,
asoles, not assholes,
but asoles,
know how rare they are.
I mean, out of all the hundreds
or even more than a thousand people
I'm forced to talk to
in the smile prostitute part of my job,
I can count the number of true asoles
in a year on one hand.
They really are very alone.
Even though they act like they have
the full support
and the wrath,
of all right thinking society,
slapping their back and going,
you go big man,
rage and rant at that girl trying to help you,
until she goes hiding behind the closet to cry.
I wonder what they would do
if they ever found out how lonely they are.
How would they react if they knew
how freakish and disturbing
their behavior really is?
Even normal people,
being obsessed with normality as they are,
seem to have trouble rationalizing
the asolish mode of interaction as normal.
You can see it making the inner pigeon brain,
magnetic normality compass,
wobble a bit,
until it settles back down to pink.
It's like watching someone deliberately
and proudly piss themselves in public.
I don't know whether to be entertained,
mortified or profoundly saddened
at this deep failure at pretending to be human.
It's like their grip on their inner chimp
just slips and it comes brachiating out
at high speed,
howling and yammering,
hammering the walls with both fists
and smearing crap everywhere.
Isn't that what playing human is all about?
Holding down that damn monkey
and pounding it in the nuts
until it won't dare to raise
its beetle-browed little noggin ever again?
It's amazing there are so few slip-ups, really,
but it just makes having to experience it for money
infinitely sadder.
The end.
All these monkeys,
monkey references.
Thank you, fellow citizen Bork.
Yeah, no offense.
Are you making fun of my family again,
Ivan Stan?
Well, you know,
you should be used to that by now.
How do you feel about movies like Planet of the Apes?
Well, I always root for the apes.
Apes aren't monkeys.
Well, of course.
You know, apes are actually the superior intelligence.
We are apes, yes.
No.
Monkeys are...
No, they're really horrible.
Monkeys are stinking little chattering brainless animals
one step above humans
on the evolutionary chain.
Damn right.
I mean, you know...
I think there's a line like that in the Tim Burton
Planet of the Apes.
I need to catch up with that.
The best part of which is that some of it was shot at
the Trona Pinnacles
outside Death Valley.
And they move them around a lot.
I noticed in the movie they took some...
some real liberties with the placement of those
big rock formations.
Well, that's Hollywood.
Yeah.
But, you know, that Tim Burton version is actually
very, very authentic.
Sticks to the line of the original novel.
Yeah, it is a little bit more like Pierre Belay's weird novel.
You mean they got cars and buildings and things?
It ends in...
When they come back in time, they found that the apes
actually took over the world.
Right. It's not Earth.
It doesn't have the Rod Serling ending.
It really is a planet of go-realism.
And gorillas and chimpanzees and humans.
But at the end...
It's not Earth after an atomic war.
At the end of the Pierre Boulle novel,
they get off from the Planet of the Apes.
They blast off. They go back home.
And find that Earth now has been taken over by apes.
That's how the Tim Burton movie ends.
Well, that's the end of the Boulle novel, too.
An officer comes across the landing field in a jeep.
And when he gets out, he's a gorilla.
And the people who read the message in the bottle
that he found in space are apes.
Because the original novel...
That's right.
The story was like a message in the Bible.
You don't know who they are in the book until after the end.
And they're apes, too.
They're space-going, space-faring apes.
So the whole thing is a great comfort to the selectors.
And only these dirty, rotten humans...
One thing I really like about the Tim Burton movie, though,
they brought back Linda Harrison.
Is this the new...
Tim Burton movie?
Well, it's the one about six years ago.
Oh.
It's not the new, new reboot.
Okay.
There was the Tim Burton movie, which is too dark to see.
I'm so confused.
The one with Mark Wahlberg. It's not that one.
That's what we're talking about.
Oh, yeah.
Mark Wahlberg.
Okay. All right. Sorry.
Then there's the new CGI ones.
Just suck.
CGI?
Yeah. The plant...
Yeah. You've seen...
There's two of those now.
Yeah.
What's his name? Gollum.
The guy who played Gollum is the...
Right. Andy Serkis.
Yeah.
He's the go-to guy for motion control of apes in Hollywood.
So he has on his resume playing King Kong, Gollum,
and a super smart Caesar ape that takes over the world.
Yeah.
If I had my way, he would play Bob.
Because in a movie, although he's British, he can handle...
Or Australian or something.
He can handle... Or New Zealand-ish.
He can handle lots of accents. I've seen him do it.
Including American.
And if you were going to make a big Hollywood movie,
about J.R. Bob Dobbs, obviously he can't play himself.
And there's the problem of using a human actor.
I call the Sean Connery problem.
Or the James Bond problem.
You've got... The guy has you over a barrel.
If he... If Stephen Colbert plays Bob,
then for a million dollars in the first movie,
he can charge five million dollars the next time.
So...
But what about CGI?
Let's face it. If you study the head of J.R. Bob Dobbs,
that is not a human head.
Despite the fact that it's taken from a photograph of him,
back when he could be photographed.
It is not a head that will match any other human.
Well, you know...
And why not use CGI for Bob?
He looks a little off.
You're not sure...
You know, they call it the uncanny valley.
He's already made out of dots.
They make a CGI character that's as close to human-looking as possible.
Like in the Neutron remake.
But it just doesn't cut it.
There's something that gives you the creeps.
You know what a human looks like.
And...
Kind of like Mitt Romney.
So the fake one, that somehow shows.
In the case of Bob, that's the way he is in real life.
It's what you...
It's very hard to be in the room with the guy.
If he hadn't been killed that time, he showed up in San Francisco,
I don't know what would have happened to Hal and me.
And everybody else on stage.
Well, actually, look what happened.
Yes.
So, Andy Serkis being the go-to guy for CGI characters,
and having played King Kong, the greatest role any actor could ever hope for,
I say we're going to hold out for Andy Serkis to play Dobbs.
Of course, later on, we'll have built the model,
and we can have somebody else play him if Serkis decides to get hoarse.
Yes, that's the thing.
It used to be that the actor would have you over a barrel,
but now, once you've got his...
his looks from all sides, then you can simply generate him spontaneously.
Now, Stang, I want your input.
This new theory going around that Bob is actually some kind of shape-shifter?
What's that sound?
Is that that monster? That thing? Whatever?
No, it's just a motorcylce.
Just an internal combustion engine.
No, but there's a new theory out there that Bob is actually like a shape-shifter,
like on the Salt Vampire on Star Trek.
He looks at...
We see Bob, each person sees Bob,
and Bob is a different person.
So Bob wants your salt, eh?
Yes.
But, you know, he doesn't look the same to each person,
like the Salt Vampire on Star Trek.
What's your opinion on that theory?
I'm sorry, I completely...
What's your opinion of whether Bob is a shape-shifter
like the Salt Vampire on Star Trek?
When you mentioned Star Trek, that was where I spaced out.
I never saw any of those except the first season.
Well, I'll tell you. I'll answer that for you.
Did you say spaced out?
Spaced out.
Connie is described that way.
Connie changes shape and hair and makeup and everything.
May I answer?
Yeah.
The shape-shifting salt monster on Star Trek
looked like whoever you wanted it to look like.
It was actually this horrible shaggy thing, but...
It looked like your loved ones or your deceased wife or whatever.
In that regard, Bob is like the monster
because he looks like what you want him to look like.
It just happens that what you want him to look like most of all is Bob.
Right. Yeah, that's a good answer.
Yes, very good.
It's like his luck.
What's gonna happen just happens to be what he wanted to happen anyway.
That's his secret, and it's no big secret.
But he can't change it.
He can't share that power.
I don't think he knows he has that knowledge.
It's ingrained stupidity.
Knowledge is not what Bob seeks.
Contracted consciousnesslessness.
I thought he was an example of what they called unintelligent design.
Bob.
I don't know who's calling the shots with that one.
He's just too stupid to realize how smart he is.
Well, he's not the only one.
Intelligent but hallucinating design.
Nobody's ever brought that one up.
Intelligent but psychopathic design.
That sounds about right.
I can see, I can believe in that.
Psychopathic intelligent design is where people came from.
Could be.
And those crazy looking rocks that I like to see.
The old god was and is crazy.
So there you go.
The original creator.
That was a big part of Philip K. Dick's crack pathology.
He got there the hard way.
The insane creator god.
He discovered it.
He discovered that we're all in the Black Iron Prison.
But some of us know a way out.
Ex-day.
Well, if you don't want me to say something.
That's a good way to end the show, actually.
A way out.
I'm going to get up and shift my stones.
And get down there and look at some of the swag while it's still out.
I'm always available.
I think that's a good idea.
Continue.
Anyway.
Mr. Sister is shuffling up here.
You can take my spot if you want.
Mr. Sister is just a, now this is good news for once.
Tomorrow, when did you say?
About now.
Yeah, around about this time of day.
Around 4 o'clock or so.
Mr. Sister will be hosting a show.
She's hosting a socialist social in which he, with the means of production, will dole out bloody marriage.
The blood of the workers.
To the workers.
To you, the workers.
The blood of the workers.
So, you can, the big boss man, the cigar chomping capitalist is going to go lol socialist just for tomorrow and feed or get everybody drunk at any rate.
He was originally planning to make everybody a sammich, but that's a little bit ambitious.
And nobody's given him a black eye yet.
Some of the more sensitive subgeniuses didn't like one of Mr. Sister's fix me a sammich pictures.
Even though that's been going around the internet for a long time.
Yeah, yeah.
It's a common meme.
But I guess suddenly you were a sexist instead of a sexist.
I'm a manyist.
There are many things that I am a this.
Oh.
But above all a patriotic, psychotic, anarcho-materialist.
Anarcho-materialist, yes.
That's what brings us all together.
Republic pukes and lip tarts and all those, all the other ones that don't count because you're throwing your vote.
And, and, and it, let's get rid of that obabo as quickly as possible too.
Obabo the presa serp.
The presa serp.
You all may not have seen the, the, the pictures of obabo, the spirit behind what we think of as the President Obama.
Whether he's good or evil, we don't really know yet.
Yeah, he's the leader of the.
He would probably say evil, I would probably say, what's the difference?
The bizarro Washington D.C., the one that has, that has two capitals.
Right.
He presides over them, both.
The kingdom of obabo.
We know that he's watching us.
They, they, they.
He's listening right now.
Of course.
Making notes.
Right, and it's not even online.
No, usually they send a, a, a minion here.
And I recognize almost everybody here.
You don't think that some of these dragonflies are biological?
Right, the bugs.
When they say that they got your room bugged.
They're, they're trying.
They got you bugged with real bugs.
They're trying to get into our luxury RV.
Are they really?
We, we, yes, we, we lay in there at night and we hear them crashing into the sides just like the birds.
See, they love you.
They want you.
They don't want me.
They don't love me.
And yet I'm, and yet I so love the bugs.
You know, people used to call me Needle Dick, the bug fucker.
I will tell you.
You know, back in the day, but.
Should I tell you what I did with my.
Hold it, hold the mic closer to you.
My condo ants.
Yeah.
How bad did you kill the condo ants?
Well, this is.
You need to train them.
This is the ant killing technology that they have now.
Through scientific studies, they determined that the drone ants are just a few that go out and gather food.
And they eat as much food as they can.
And then they go back into the colony and they throw it all up.
And all the rest of the ants have a feast.
Oh, like.
Like some genius radio show.
Exactly.
Yeah.
So they regurgitate and then everybody has a warm meal, you know.
Well, the, the exterminator told me that the theory behind the poison was, is it's completely safe for humans.
Because the poison is micro encapsulated in a resin that the human body cannot digest.
However.
Is that a challenge?
The ants can pick it up.
And by the time they regurgitate it for their meal inside the ant colony, the poison is released.
They all die.
I'm still betting on the ants.
You know, there are ant colonies larger than several states right now, including the Argentine ants that march through this area.
Yes, this is, this is a Sandoz technology, of course.
Ants will win every time, I believe.
But maybe not.
We're pretty good at killing stuff.
Some people call them aunts.
Aunts.
No, those are different.
Constance was talking about her pet ant.
Yes.
That's not the same kind of aunts, dog.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
I'm sorry.
So, so I don't, I, I've had it.
Are we through?
I'm, I'm through.
If nobody else wants to get up here and take over this idiotic charade, I'm out of here.
You're welcome.
You can, you want to go?
You want to do a?
Okay, sure.
That'd be great.
We've got the machines running.
When the moon was new and the sun young, Of silver and gold the gods sung.
In the green grass they silver spilled, And the white waters they with gold filled.
Ere the pit was dug or hell yawned, Ere dwarf was bred or dragon spawned,
There were elves of old.
And strong spells under green hills in hollow dells.
They sang as they wrought many fair things, And the bright crowns of the elf kings.
But their doom fell and their song waned, By iron hewn and by steel chained.
Greed that sang not, nor with mirth smiled, In dark holes their wealth piled.
Graven silver and carven gold, Over elven home the shadow rolled.
There was an old dwarf in a dark cave, To silver and gems his fingers clave.
With hammer and tongs and anvil stone, He worked his hands to the hard bone.
And coins he made, and strings of rings, And thought to buy the power of gold.
But his eyes grew dim, and his ears dull, And the skin grew yellow on his old skull.
Through his bony claw, with a pale sheen, The stony jewels slipped unseen.
No feet he heard, though the earth shaked, When the young dragon his thirst slaked.
The stream smoked at his dark door, The flames hissed on the dank ground.
And he died alone in the red fire, His bones were ashes in the hot mire.
There was an old dragon under grey stone, His red eyes blinked as he lay alone.
His joy was fled and his youth spent, He was knobbed and wrinkled,
And his limbs bent in the long years To his gold chain.
In his heart's furnace the fire waned.
To his belly's slime gems stuck thick, Silver and gold he would snuff and lick.
He knew the place of the least ring Underneath the shadow of his black wing.
Of thieves he thought on his hard bed, And dreamed that on their flesh he fed.
Their bones crushed, and their blood burned.
His blood drank, his ears drooped, And his breath sank.
Male rings rang, he heard them not.
A voice echoed in his deep grot.
A young warrior with a bright sword Called him forth to defend his hoard.
His teeth were knives, and of horn his hide, But iron tore him, and his flame died.
There was an old king on a high throne.
His white beard lay on knees of bone.
His mouth savoured neither meat nor drink, Nor his ears song.
He could only think of his huge chest With its carven lid,
Where pale gems and gold lay hid In secret treasury in the dark ground.
The strong doors were with iron bound, And the iron doors were with iron bound.
The swords of his thanes were dull with rust, His glory fallen, his rule unjust.
His halls hollow, his bowers cold, But king he was of elvish gold.
He heard not the horns in the mountain pass, He smelt not the blood on the trodden grass,
But his halls were burned, his kingdom lost, In a cold pit his bones.
His hands were tossed.
There is an old hoard under dark rock, Forgotten, behind doors none can unlock,
That grim gate no man can pass.
On the mound grows the green grass, There the sheep feed and the larks soar,
And the wind blows from the sea shore.
The old hoard the knight shall keep.
While earth waits and the elves sleep.
Dr. Howell just makes that stuff up off the top of his head, you know.
He's just spouting.
Ridiculoso.
Who, is that Tolkien?
That is Professor Tolkien.
J.R.R. Todd Tolkien.
Yeah.
Originally printed in the Oxford magazine.
Back in the day when I was a little shaver.
Nerd.
Okay, I'm outta here.
You've been listening to the subgenius radio ministry Hour of Slack.
For free information write to P.O. Box 181417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44.
Or see www.subgenius.com.
Praise Bob.
We will lead this damn nation to damnation, as Dr. Leib gave us.
We will lead this nation to damnation.
Those weren't his real eyes, those were the subgenius fake 3D eyes that he bought from
Stank.
Or not, he didn't buy them from Stank.
Stank approved them and sold them and endorsed them.
Don't be jealous.