Take it from the top, boys.
Let's do it all again.
Oh, I hate when the stuff gets broadcast.
No, there it goes.
Not gonna be too happy.
Well, so how many more of these practice sessions do we have to do till the real show?
Real.
Real show.
Yeah, how many more are there?
Five.
Five?
Five more.
Hey, Chad.
Come on, can't we have one more story?
Come on.
Hour of Slack.
Sponsored by The Churchill of the subgenius.
The subgenius Hour of Slack that you are about to listen to is specially designed only to be made on radio station and only in the city of...
I have all the characteristics of a human being.
Flesh, blood, skin, hair.
But not a single clear identifiable emotion.
Except for greed and disgust.
Something horrible is happening inside of me.
And I don't know why.
Christmas makes me feel emotional.
String and strings.
Light and strings.
Feel and stamp.
Link of my brain.
As the shadows rush.
With their treasure.
And above all this mess.
You are the only one.
I'm so grateful that I knew the only one.
So I honor you guys.
I reallyient.
I repented from what I did to même.
Is a
Soon it will be Christmas Day
The Subgenius Radio Ministry are a slur
One, two, Santa's coming for you
Three, four, you better lock your door
Five, six, with a crucifix
Seven, eight, better stay up late
Nine, ten, Santa's coming again!
Over there!
The Subgenius Radio Ministry
Have you ever wondered
What it would have been like
If the baby Jesus were born today?
Now?
Maybe even this year?
What do you think it would be like
If it was all being reported to us
By the television and radio media
That we hear and watch every day?
It might go something like this
I'm an old man
And I've seen lots of Christmases
Come and go
And they're never white
And it's raining again
And again and again
Christmas is a-comin'
The geese are getting fat
Please put a penny in the old man's hat
If you haven't got a penny
A heypenny will do
If you haven't got a heypenny
Then God bless you
God bless you gentlemen
God bless you
If you haven't got a heypenny
Then God bless you
Christmas is a-comin'
Look out for Twinkle Elf
Making Christmas dinner at all by himself
If he hasn't got a filter tip, a ball of dung will do
If he hasn't got a dung ball, he's got some curly shoes
God bless Twinkle Elf, God bless me
Your Christmas shoes are curly and curly as can be
Voila, voila, voila, voila, voila
God bless you gentlemen, God bless you
If you haven't got a turkey leg, then God bless you
We all as children grew up dreaming of having, doing, wearing
What Barbie has. Barbie has it all.
Barbie is a prop for everyone to dream through
Barbie changed the course of a woman's life
She could have all sorts of adventures
She could get in her own way
She could even get into her own home
Barbie changed the course of a woman
Baby, you have my all!
Mam위だから
La bonda
The decline of romantic makeup
Have you ever seen such three hundred people being out there?
Let me out this way
elling your crush
The pänerä
Barbie dolls.
Women were able to be more with their lives by role-playing with Barbie.
A very important doll.
Barbie dolls.
Kanye West.
me
I
yeah
won't together
Maria, gratia bene.
Maria, vittorinus.
Dominius Dominius.
Stand up on his way.
He's loaded, he's loaded Lots of toys and goodies on his list
He's loaded, lots of toys and goodies on his list
Every mother's child is gonna want to survive
Bring me a rainbow, and a flower and a soul
I am offering this very simple phrase
To kids from one to ninety-two
All over to Santa many times, many ways
Merry Christmas, Merry Christmas
Merry Christmas
I am so giddy!
Thank you.
I chased old Bob through the field into the mall.
I pointed my shotgun and he began to crawl.
I said, I want them chickens back.
I said, I want them chickens back at noon.
But the aliens took your gal.
She sucked dry like a prune.
And I didn't bring the chickens back.
When I caught up with Bob, he was eating chicken pie.
He had piles of bones reaching to the sky.
And I'll never give my chickens back.
I said, I want them chickens back.
He said, I want them chickens back.
Ho, ho, ho, ho, ho.
That very last was some obtuse, dear friends.
And before that, Chicken Stealin' Bob.
The new greatest hymn to Bob from Gary Gabrogfran.
Yes, the legendary Gary Gabrogfran of the band that dare not speak its name.
And ah, yes, this is Christmas Hour of Slack.
2001 show number two.
And that chestnuts roasting on an open fire, just killer collage remix that we heard earlier
was by Corporal Blossom from A Mutated Christmas, which is from www.triagemusic.com.
Before that, we heard Brother Theodore in some kind of a mystery clip.
And I don't know who did.
Ave Maria.
But that collage about Barbie, Barbie Has It All, was by Obtuse.
And friends, you can get a free CD from Obtuse.
And the information and the place to get it is from obtuse.
This is a website.
Obtuse, O-B-T-U-S-E, .i-u-m-a .com.
That's .i-u-m-a .com.
And this.
More obtuse coming, friends.
Oh, oh, and also that very first thing we played, the cool, cool, cool, cool Silver Bells scary clip
was by Grassy Noel.
Also from A Mutated Christmas.
See www.triagemusic.com.
.
Keep the blazing yule beat for us
Strike in the harp and join the chorus
Bowering in their relation
While we're filled with yuletide treasure
La la la la la la la la
Pass away the old year passing
Share the new year lots and lots of
Sing we're joyful all together
La la la la la la la la
If something went unweather
La la la la la la la la la
La la la la la la la la
We'll see you next time.
Our monitors are good, for they have shown us how right and proper our own form of government actually is.
As the Lord spoke to Job out of the whirlwind, so do voices seem to be speaking to us, now and in our day, telling us not to abjure all hope.
Believe in our traditions.
And night will once again, as it inevitably must, give way to the rosy dawn.
.
Thank you.
Now, we'll be giving information about these things, but now let us plunge into the evil side of joy with James Kochauka, Superstar.
The snowman isn't very nice. His heart is cold, it's made of ice. And if you snap your fingers twice, he'll come to life.
Mother Lock, the kid's inside. Everybody's...
Everybody run and hide. Don't look in the snowman's eyes. You'll turn to ice.
Snowman, Wheel of the Skewer young man, don't run, just like the Shouts.
Estados Unidos, Peel off, the snowman, down.
quythor, Thomas the Superstar, dreamed, giving Dumbo his
suit.
Fuck it
And you.
Thank you.
Oh, baby.
Depression is touching my soul
I know what I want, but I just don't know
I gotta go out again
Feeling, sweet feeling, drips from my fingers
My fingers
Cause burning depression is catching my soul
Woman so hot, sweet toes in vain
We make love, we break love, it's all the same
This old heart
Music, sweet music, I wish I could caress, caress
Manic depression is a frustrated mess
Music, sweet music, I'd rather die
Music, sweet music, love is what there is
Music, sweet music, I've already been Suddenly taken and left only to let go
Oh I think I'm gonna kill myself
I'm going down, I'm going down
Down
There really ain't no use in me staying here and hanging around
I gotta get out
Music, sweet music
I wish I could rest
Yes
Man of depression
Is a frustrated mess
Yeah
A frustrated mess
Cause I never used it
Sorry
дев grup
I don't know what you've been shooting at
I feel like I'm owe translate
Right
Guys?
Get your ass contre
No
W ETF
Go
Yo
Why did I even want mo to rather in it
Absolutely
That saw myand
My
Thank you.
Satisfying a fundamental age.
Thank you, Todd.
What we as manufacturers are selling is fun.
That was Obtuse.
And before that, Manic Depression, the Hendrix song by Retaliation.
I thought that would be good for those holiday blues.
Thanks to Pope S. Lillith for 4K.
Forwarding that and other music we've been playing at times.
Mr. Sister posted the monitor clips.
And we don't know who did the drunken Christmas song.
But the scary Frosty the Snowman was by Lovecraft Technologies from Unmutated Christmas.
But now, friends, well, we got this interesting CD in the mail from someone named Sherry Elf.
And I thought this would be a perfect time.
To play this song by Sherry Elf from her debut CD, Forcing Goodness Upon You.
Help?
I told him no thank you.
And I got into my car.
But as I drove away, I said to myself,
S?
Elf?
You waited all your life for someone to notice how lost you look.
Now you refuse help from Jesus of all people.
Jesus.
Yes, I'm lost.
And I could use some help.
I just was not expecting you there.
In the parking lot of the hardware store.
You know, I'm kicking myself and my thoughts are full of what would have happened if I would have taken you up on your offer.
But now it's too late.
I went and sent you away.
If I know Jesus, he's still out there.
He's canvassing all of the parking lots of all the hardware stores.
And these great.
United States.
And he won't stop there.
Soon you'll find him in the parking lots of all of the hardware stores of all of North and South America.
And then he'll migrate.
Over to Europe.
And Africa.
And China.
Wait.
Do they have hardware stores in China?
And do they have parking lots?
Well, knowing Jesus, that won't stop him.
You have to have your act together pretty good to be the son of God.
Jesus.
Yes, I'm lost.
And I could still use some help.
But I think from now on you should wear a t-shirt or a button that says, Jesus, Son of God.
Jesus.
Your understated approach took me by surprise.
I thought you were talking hardware.
But no, you were talking eternal life and salvation.
I'm still regretting how in my haste I sent you away.
This song goes out to Jesus.
Wherever he may be wandering.
For his untiring perseverance in soliciting unsuspecting shoppers there in the parking
lots of all of the hardware stores of this great earth.
Jesus, we love you.
And we respect you.
And we look forward to seeing you again.
And we hope that you'll get your clever new marketing strategy.
Jesus.
It's all lost.
But I feel the problem is resolving itself.
From now on my eyes and ears are open and I'm much more prepared to meet saviors and
sons of God while I am shopping in hardware stores.
But not only hardware stores.
Wherever I shop.
Wherever I am, I look deeply into the eyes of my fellow human beings.
And I look for Jesus.
Jesus, yes I'm lost.
But I'm feeling a little better.
I still like the idea of a t-shirt or a button.
Some of us are a little preoccupied and we need to see a label.
Jesus.
Oh, Jesus.
I still like the idea of a t-shirt or a button.
Oh, J-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-s-u-s.
Have you seen Jesus today?
Uh yes, that was Sherry Elf.
Wasn't that pretty much it?
or something. She's distributed by herself. Her debut CD, Forcing Goodness Upon You,
is available only from her, but here's a website and address. That's www.sherielf.com,
which is spelled S-H-A-R-I-E-L-F, Sherielf.com, or Sherielf, P.O. Box 3585, Kansas City, Kansas 6, 6102.
The music in the background is by Mark Mothersbaugh from his Christmas album special,
Joyo Mutato.
And now, Reverend Sheldon DeWeer.
Jesus loves me, this I know,
cause my preacher tells me so.
If I argue, he'll use his tongue
till I scream out,
Yes, I'm wrong!
Oh, God, I'm a sinner!
I repent! Just make him stop!
Oh!
¶¶
Thank you.
© BF-WATCH TV 2021
And to think, it's all because they kept lights off when it didn't have to be convenient.
This holiday season, why not turn on all the lights in your house and keep them on for the rest of the year?
Maybe you'll make the load a little lighter on us here at Multinational.
And a winter reminder, citizens.
Carbon monoxide, the silent winter killer, lurks everywhere.
So, if you have a gas stove, oil burner, or open flame, make sure all the doors and windows in the room are tightly sealed,
so that none of that nasty carbon monoxide can sneak in.
Thanks, and happy holidays.
This is Mr. Abernathy, signing off from your town to you.
Reverend Bleepo Abernathy, dear friends.
And thanks to LeMur, Fernandez and Andy LeMur.
And I am...
BJR for the whiz and monitor clips.
The Jethro's, friends.
You need to know where to write to the Jethro's.
They're at...
They did that Wreck the Halls and so many other versions we've been playing.
The Jethro's are at 212 and a half Miller Avenue.
That's 212 and a half Miller Avenue.
Portsmouth, New Hampshire.
Portsmouth, N-H-O-3.
8-0-1.
Santa Claus is Coming to Town was by Corporal Blossom.
Information on that mutant Christmas is available from www.triagemusic.com
or www.detritus.net slash illegalart.
I'm Reverend Ivan Stang, friends.
You can reach me, send me tapes or whatnot.
Post Office Box 181417.
Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
And friends, as always, the Hour of Slack is brought to you by the Church of the Subgenius.
Free information from Post Office Box 140306.
Dallas, Texas 75214.
www.subgenius.com
Chocolate Como reservation.
Registration worn out.
Awe wait for a while y'all put the flowers in.
Is that some kind of a new song note boy?
It was the night before Christmas and all through the halls
Not a creature were stirring, not even a mouse
The stockings were hung by the chief
Merry Fuckin' Christmas
Merry fucking Christmas
Show you
Thank you.