Uh, hey, what's going on here?
Along with Bob, the pursuit of slack, and a conspiracy of pinks,
the subgenius theology includes a vision of the apocalypse.
According to church doctrine, on July 5th, 1998,
when the television signal of Amos and Andy reaches the men from Planet X,
the aliens will unleash their wrath upon the Earth.
And the men from Planet X are going to come down and take over Earth.
They're going to...
They will put us out of our misery unless Bob can explain to them
in ways that they can understand that there is something on Earth worth saving.
And only the subgenii, the dues-paying, book-buying,
receipt-in-the-pocket, paid-in-full-to-the-church subgenii,
have the tiniest prayer of survival.
The rest of them? It's a tough world, Jack.
The crowd, the slack, the bar, the bar down in the saucer road
Round, round the slack flow Bob, the bar down in the saucer road
And in that air, there was a ship, a rare ship
An exeship with a ship in the air
And the air threw its smoke at the spook from theessen prop
And the prop, and the pipe, and the pipe, and the grit in the grit in the bob
Bob down in the saucer road
Round, round the slack flow Bob, the bar down in the saucer road
And in that ship there was a bob, a rare bob, J.R. Bob Dobbs
With a bob on the ship and the ship in the air and the air through the smoke and the smoke from the prop and the prop and the pipe and the pipe and the grin and the grin and the bob.
Bob down in the saucer roll.
Gordon, everything's going fine.
No, we're not recording.
Are we on?
Is this thing on?
Yeah.
All right.
We wanted to start a new elevated hour of slack, right?
We're going to be high-minded.
15 minutes of collage stuff or songs.
We're tired of your phony fireworks.
Marshall, you have earned this.
What about this reputed Jesus Starfleet that was supposed to have shown up?
As you see, they have just left the hangar deck at Lunar Central and have cleared the airlocks into the colony.
The crowd of scientists and technicians are going wild.
What a space ovation.
Now let's feel another.
Now in celebration of this great occasion, we have planned a lunar party.
We hope all young people throughout the solar system will join us in celebration of this great day in outer space.
Bob?
What if there is a form of life in space?
Not on some planet, but just drifting.
Not life as we know it.
With intelligence, yes, but pure energy with no organic structure.
Invisible.
Invisible?
Now the rocket passed through its path.
It entered the rocket.
It found living specimens of our form of life.
Cell organisms.
Humans.
Exactly.
Now, if even by accident it could enter one of those structures,
what a way to end it.
What if you invade the Earth?
Now look, sir, I'm not over-intelligent, but...
You saw the film, you know what happened.
Only God knows where and how far that rocket traveled.
Something got into that rocket.
And it's found other forms of life.
The cactus.
The cactus?
You mean Kuruza?
The cactus.
He's now in the shell of a man being transformed.
If one of these cactus plants were subject to the same mutation,
there could be an affinity, a union between plant and animal,
with the ability to destroy.
And possess?
And multiply.
An alien cannot invade a dead man.
We're merely using this corpse for a demonstration of placement.
We're all extraterrestrials
on a cycle that is ancestral.
We're off to see the wizards
on a paradise among the stars.
We're all extraterrestrials
on a mission that is ancestral.
We're off to see the wizards
on a world among the stars.
You know that scientists have said
that the Earth will soon be dead.
Philosophers have told us long ago
you'd think by now we'd all be in the North.
Next year, we'll be in the North.
I want more.
More flirting.
More time off.
Yeah!
More money.
We must get off.
Now, in some shows,
they have half an hour of collage
before they start talking,
so they can go out on the balcony
and smoke joints of marijuana!
Not us anymore,
if that's what you're talking about.
We're not allowed to do that anymore.
Are ya?
Back in our salad days, though,
when things were green and growing
and the sap was budding,
and the devil took the hindmost,
because life was hot and merry,
Yes, my hindmost.
Yes, we were able to go out
and get endlessly stoned on the balcony.
Oh, there we start the hour of slack up again.
Yep, right at the moment when...
...the generator goes.
Internal combustion.
Right at the moment that they start driving by,
the hour of slack begins.
Yes, the internal combustion engine
circling the Earth with its petroleum products
and its fumes.
So we've officially started now?
Yes.
Yes, we have.
The exciting hour of slack begins.
I just wanted to pull down.
I just wanted to pull it down
to make it lowbrow the second that we started.
It's a pity Philo wasn't here,
because he'd be in ecstasy
if these sound effects...
I have a little bug around.
Sound effects are terrible.
Well, why don't you get it set up,
and then we'll have a symphony of sound effects.
We have, like, springs and, like,
slide whistles and stuff?
I think if you're in a room,
if you go into toy stores,
you can buy these little...
Ha ha ha ha ha!
...
Good Lord, look at Stang.
Oh, God, he's going into orbit.
Yes, somebody get a bucket of water.
Oh, I feel like a new man!
Well, you should after that.
And so, you see, we have unusual methods
of refreshment here at X-Day.
Denied to the world outside,
they know nothing of our ability
to divert ourselves with special esoterica.
Ah, if they only knew,
then all of those ignorant pinks
would be clawing at the gate,
trying to get in at the last moment
to become one of us.
They were. They were trying yesterday.
You guys missed it.
We beat them all back.
Is that what that...
We demoralized them.
I wondered about those claw marks.
The flame thrower up there,
is that what that was about?
Yeah, that's where the scorching came from.
Oh, the scorching by Stephen King,
America's most popular writer.
He's a national treasure.
Yeah.
So that happened while I wasn't following that.
Oh, I was still en route, of course,
to X-Day at that time.
Driving...
Yeah, I cleared out the path,
and then, who was it,
Fightsy Taj cleaned up the rest,
and then, well, not all of them,
and then Suds and Stick took it from there.
They sweeped out the rest
with the audio techniques.
Then mopping up started.
Of the bad sounds.
Yes.
Hey, it's time for more radio comedy.
That's how you know it's funny.
Yes, we'll put all these sound effects in post.
Squeaky penis.
Get it right in the mic, right in the mic.
Oh, there we go.
Another radio sound effect.
Radio.
I wish that the audience could see
the thing that is squeaky,
because it is...
Well, it's a...
It's a...
It's like a dildo, basically.
It's the shape of the masculine lance,
but with a funny little crazy face
on the head of it.
You mean they don't all have that?
And his mouth open and smiling like...
I thought everybody was like that.
Well, okay.
There you go.
Okay.
Well, what do I think of next?
Not to be confused with Reverend Dildonics,
who is new to Ag State this year.
Praise Reverend Dildonics on the nose.
Praise Reverend Dildonics.
He's here listening to the hour of Slack.
Where are you?
Unlike everyone else who knows
that they can download it later.
He's stuck working a shift at the Slack Jack.
Are you about to take some special medicine here?
Oh, yeah, actually.
Oh, well, how about that?
Yes, you see, we are augmented,
not only electronically,
but biophysically here at Ag State.
This is the time when Ag State is coming.
You just let your yard go.
Don't even mow your yard.
Don't pay off those credit cards.
I already wasn't.
Eat canned chili all day long if you want to.
I already did.
All the things that you normally won't do
because of your health.
Wait, did you say canned chili?
That was your...
You've made that item a staple of your diet.
I can't stop.
Someone should take it away from me.
I just won't stop doing it.
I'm going to throw it over there.
Oh, you're doing fine.
No, no.
I don't want to be responsible.
But it puts Philo's noisemakers to shame
because he's got these electronic flatulators
that don't sound nearly as good
as the rubber analog that she was using.
Oh, now we'll hear again the...
Actually, I think it's worse to give it over to Stang.
...over the lake.
The terrible elephant man.
I'm so mature.
No, back, Tantor.
Back.
No, Tantor.
Praise Bob.
Oh, okay.
There you go.
Also in the news...
The microphone's attacking me.
We understand there's going to be a change in the weather.
And instead of thunderstorms, hailstorms, and rainstorms,
we will be gently caressed by the flaring beams
of the sun's effulgent rays.
Yep.
There was a tornado last night,
but it didn't come here because it was scared of us.
Was there really a tornado?
There was.
There was one south of us last night, actually.
There was a tornado.
Cool.
It formed and then it got close to Wisteria,
and then it was like,
oh, no, I don't want to go over there
with those spooky subgeniuses.
I don't have $35.
I can't go in there.
I'm going to destroy that place.
It swept up the tiny inbred hamlets of Spinkville and Spudville.
And the thing is,
a tornado requires a flat place to race across
and a bunch of trailers to toss.
And so it just avoided the Wisteria refuge.
Is it...
Are they really attracted to trailers,
or is it that they hate poe-buckers?
Well, one or the other.
And the poor.
I should say, that's kind of an offensive thing to say.
Many of us may live in trailers and trailer courts.
It's quite true.
I never denied it.
In fact, Reverend Heathen does.
But...
More than I do.
So we shouldn't always associate trailer courts with poe-buckers.
Nor should we always look down our noses at the humble poe-bucker.
In Humboldt County, California.
Yeah, over there in Harrisonville.
Humble and dilligous.
Because they have the best dough.
Whole town full of them.
Right.
So, we...
But let me put it this way.
That's why I'm not moving to small town Texas.
Hmm.
But I thought you were considering it.
No.
Well, I move there for two weeks every now and then.
But then my dad and I start fighting, so we move on.
Oh, well.
You know, there's only one roaster to rule the roost here.
At Stang Ranch in Stangville.
This music is so soothing.
Stangville, home of the Creationist Museum.
Is this Monster Hunter music?
Yes, it is.
It's lovely.
Yeah, it's the official soundtrack album from Monster Hunter.
Monster Hunter 3.
Monster Hunter.
Believe it or not, that game is so huge in Japan that every year a big orchestra does
music from Monster Hunter.
The Monster Hunter Orchestra.
Actually, a lot of this was recorded in Prague by the Budapest...or the something something
European Fancy Pants Orchestra.
Well, we are a global village, I guess.
There's no doubt about that.
It's a huge fad in that land.
I guess.
A masterful beer after work.
Yeah.
Now that's a song I can get behind.
B-E-E-R?
Yes.
B-E-E-R.
Not B-I-E-R.
B-E-E-E-E-E-E-E-E-R.
Oh, a masterful beer after work.
Well, we don't got no beer here.
What?
We don't have no beer?
Where'd the beer go?
Not right here.
Not under the table right here.
Oh, really?
No.
There you go.
I need a beer and a really long crazy straw.
Crazy.
Or one of those beer hats.
It's goofy.
It's wacky.
It's wild.
It's wicked.
With the crazy straws on it.
See, Pobucker's come up with some good ideas.
They do.
That's a great idea.
That's efficient.
Yeah, but isn't that hat in the sun warming the beer?
Yeah.
So, you see, that's the flaw in Pobucker's ointment.
It's still beer.
It's not cold and frosty as it should be.
Well, just pretend you're English and drink your beer warm.
Well, there.
That neatly solves the problem.
This banner telling me to smile feels very threatening.
Smile, darn you, smile.
It's making me want to scowl.
What banner tells you to...
Oh, that banner tells you to smile, doesn't it?
Yes, I saw your impassioned rant about the glass being half full and...
and so forth.
That was a sizzling put-down of that one.
Which one, who?
A baby bear printed a thing online about how not only is your glass not half full,
but I will come to your house and utterly destroy you.
I don't know if that was mine.
I don't think that was mine.
I'm trying to remember it.
I'm actually kind of losing track of my rants now.
I can't remember them.
Oh, perhaps it was a post from someone else that you forwarded.
That's possible.
I'm sorry, I'm just out of glib.
I've run out of words.
The Church of the Subgenius is a no-brainer, don't you think?
That line came from Dennis Murphy, founder of the cult called the Living Bull Cult.
That's a pretty cool cult.
Dennis Murphy is this old hippie who...
is always at Starwood and those pagan things.
He's a pagan dude.
But he started his own cult called the Cult of the Living Bull.
And the way it works is he'll take you out in the woods or into the hot tub or whatever
and start getting you to talk about everything that ticks you off in life.
And I mean, it goes into great detail.
And he starts...
He'll remind you, you know, what about your job?
What about the...
Yeah.
The can of chili that you don't like?
What about that rotten chili?
You paid for it.
What about, you know, your health infirmities?
Don't get me started on those.
Those damn Democrats with the cubic cubes and so forth.
And at the climax of it, when he's actually got you kind of worked up,
that's when you and everybody else screams,
BULL!
And you kind of scream the bull out of your life.
BULLSHEET.
You'd have to have been there.
It's better when Dennis tells it.
I don't know what to say.
Now, Stang, you know a cow isn't a bull.
If he was cool, he'd be here at X-Day.
This table is making some interesting sound effects with the flapping.
Yes, that rustling sound that the table makes is a specialty of this broadcast.
Like the rustling of the wings of the fella in the bright nightgown.
Okay, okay.
Where are we?
What happened?
We're at Wisteria, a campground community inside Kevin's Cafe at Tarzan's radio station
with these Radio Shack mics and mixers and little beat-up Sony headphones
and an audience of at least eight people.
I guess they're the ones who can't download it later.
Amazing.
Incredible.
Unbelievable.
Fantastic.
Preposterous.
And?
And why are we here?
Why?
To praise Bob.
But I think we already did that for the last thirty minutes.
Rolling Stone says,
A masterpiece for those who can still laugh at the fact that nothing is funny anymore.
I think that quote was actually about Book of the Septuagint.
Jay Kinney says,
Genuine wisdom in the guise of utter bullshit.
What?
And Mark Mothersbaugh says,
Bob is an enema for a constipated society.
That's true.
He said that on Showtime television.
Yes.
And he meant J.R. Bob Dobbs.
Argumentum ad veracundiam.
Bob is here to help a constipated society blow it out their ass.
That's right.
You can't get it loose unless you get a boost.
The boost that you get from Looseners.
Looseners.
The all-weather breakfast.
Uh, so we're...
Yeah, so yeah, they were famous subgeniuses back in the olden days.
Of course, no one even knows who they are now, because they were famous in the olden days.
If we have any new famous rock stars, I wouldn't know.
I wouldn't know them by their human famous name, because I honestly don't follow that stuff.
Well, get with the program.
If the girl we know, Reverend Funny Name, is really...
Name, who's the biggest singer in the world right now?
Uh, Taylor Swift.
Okay, yeah, whatever.
That, him.
That's a girl.
Yeah, okay, sure.
I did that on purpose.
I knew Taylor Swift was a girl.
But that's all I know.
Not even a real Swift.
All right.
I'm going to read something about, uh, She Defied Apple.
I saw a headline about that and proceeded not to read it.
Whose mortal taste brought death into the world and all our woe with loss of Eden.
Actually, The Onion did an article about people like me who are so snarkily cool.
Oh, Madonna?
I've never even heard of her.
That's not on my radar.
But, you know...
The problem is, I really don't know about most of the things.
And then I discovered a room full of subgeniuses talking about hipsters.
Hipsters?
They're such posers.
How do you think they look to me?
These people calling everybody else hipsters, they're all covered with tattoos.
And they go shave their head, bald head, and look like circus strong men.
Why, that's what I call a hipster.
Well, now, just calm down and take your blood pressure pill, Stang.
It's the hour of slug time.
Funny.
Okay, that's funny.
Yeah, we're done.
Now the monster.
Over that little episode.
No more.
No more joy.
Yes, a time for melancholy.
Here comes old Sequa.
Whose saintly features are too bright to get the human sense of sight.
Oh, God.
Oh, no.
I feel something coming up under us in the water.
Wait, there's something hard.
It brushed against my leg.
Wait, it's rising.
It's like an island.
It's the size of an island.
It's a gigantic turtle.
It may be that his shell is thick.
He seems asleep.
But he's not.
But he is quick and floats now in the sea with guile.
Am I the one on the, is that me being about to be eaten by old Sequa on the pamphlet for
this year?
I was wondering that myself.
It vaguely resembles me with long hair like I had last year.
You can't look closely under ultra magnification to see?
I looked at it with my eyeballs as close as they would allow and it just, I can't tell.
But Stang, I sent you the large size version of that image.
Right.
And it was large enough to print about that big on it.
No, no.
The image of swimming with old Sequa is a separate image which I separately sent you
under separate cover.
I don't want to be eaten by old Sequa.
Well, you won't be because it only happens to those who are insufficiently respectful
of his domain.
Like fence jumpers?
Wow.
I heard a couple of subgeniuses jump that fence and make it look like they're going
swimming in the pond even though it's closed this morning.
Well, I hope they open it up soon because, oh it is?
There, see?
You merely need to wish something and it happens.
You can now go down there and baptize yourself.
Now I've seen...
You can yetitize yourself.
I've seen actually a majority of the subgeniuses who come down there to the baptism, they just
frog watch.
They won't get in that water.
They don't know what they're missing.
They walk up there and take one look and they're so fascinated.
They're like, oh, there's a water spider.
Oh my God.
Whoa.
It's perfect for those yetis that are the hirsute deficient yetis.
They can go into the pond and come out with a brand new coat.
Looks just as natural as if you were born with it.
Actually, that didn't happen this morning because the rain had pelted all that beard
of walnut oil or whatever it is away from the surface.
It's true.
The pond has this walnut oil on it.
And if you look much from it right, you look like you're covered with the fine downy fur.
Yes.
There's a great closeup of Susie the floozy's breast stitches looking just as if they were
gorilla tits or something.
They look like they have hair on them.
So friends, if you get in that pond and come...
If you get in the pond bald and shaved and get out hairy, then don't be afraid.
Yes, don't be afraid.
Further indignities are to come.
Towing a gigantic pyramid on the back of the truck.
Who just went by?
Lord Ferg.
Oh, all right.
There you go.
He has to bring his kingdom with him.
Apparently.
I guess a pyramid is really a monument.
Just in case he dies out here, he needs to be able to be in tune.
When we do these hours of slack on location here, we occasionally...
I'm sorry.
...hear the truck's trundling by.
Those are no sound effects, ladies and gentlemen.
The school buses full of subgeniuses are brought in.
We do.
They're not all these paying subgeniuses.
We hire people to cheer and...
Just like Donald Trump.
Yeah, right.
We hire audience collectors to come in and work it out.
Just add the cheering in post.
That's the best way.
I like adding these clinking sword effect sounds when we pretend we're sword fighting
and everything else.
It's actually very somnolent.
Nobody moves.
Everyone is sort of becoming part of the chair, sinking down, sinking into it.
Is this an audience or an oil painting?
Actually, I've often spoken of my late friend Pedro.
When you went to his house, the chair, you couldn't tell where the chair stopped and
the floor began.
The chair into which he was sinking over the years was also sinking into the floor.
It was a little bit of a struggle.
And really, you couldn't tell where the one...
The first time I saw photographs of Pedro's house, it wasn't explained to me what I was
looking at.
And I thought it was a haunted house, an abandoned ruins.
It very much looks like a haunted house.
Because no one could live among that much, that many spider webs.
Well, that's a different thing.
It was like a movie set.
The spiders, you come in the outer room, right above your head, the spiders started and they
went all the way up to the ceiling, which was 14 feet high.
You couldn't see the corners of the walls at all.
No.
You just saw a huge...
It was near the walls of spider webs.
A huge mass of webs.
And I saw a picture of that chair and I thought, God, who could ever...
And it was like cigarette butts reaching up to the top of the ashtray on a stand.
Pedro sat there, God bless him.
Anyway, the spiders, you could look up and see their little eyes glittering.
So it wasn't all dead spiders and old spider webs.
And I asked Pedro once, I said...
But...
Man, don't the spiders ever drop down on you out of there when you're going by?
And he said, oh yeah, sure, they drop down on you.
So...
That's it.
What was his deal?
He just wanted to live naturally?
They just do?
Okay.
He believed in laissez-faire, live and let live.
That was his philosophy.
And he never got angry, even though his whole reason for existing was smoking dope and telling
people the right way to smoke dope.
There's a right way and a wrong way.
Now, when you start to think about it, you start to think about the fact that you're
a fan.
When you start, you take little tiny puffs, little tiny puffs and then it burns evenly
all the way down, but if you go...
And pull on it, then you get a run and it ruins the joint.
He's telling this to Michael Peppy.
And Michael Peppy is not listening going uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, and then takes the joint
and pulls on it and immediately creates...
Just snorts the whole thing.
...a huge run down the side.
You don't think it would make anyone angry, but not Pedro, he said, now, there you see,
you got made a run down the side, just like I said and it ruined the joint.
I've seen this scene.
whole thing enacted.
He's like the Aunt Bertha
pot smoking.
Yeah,
we should
have another moment of sound effects
for Pedro, who died unexpectedly.
Yes,
Pedro died in the service
of what he believed.
Pedro was where you got your
frappy. That's true.
I'm still smoking
dead Pedro's stash,
which itself is dying
not a very wholesome setup.
Anyway, that's
just the way history works out.
You know,
there is a progression
from one state to another.
What, from alive to dead?
I've noticed that happening a lot lately.
Yes, there's
a lot of that going around.
Ah, but subgeniuses pass on to
another better world.
We're all hoping to do it.
It's called the grave.
That was
depressing.
That was. I thought we were going to get
cremated.
Now we have to be in the grave with those
ugly worms and skeletons and things.
I thought we were going to be
turned into a neat pile of
drifting ashes.
No, of course I was just trying to scare you, Dr. Howell.
Everything you ever
dreamed of will come true
and everything will be wonderful
and happy. So why don't you go ahead
and kill yourself now if you really
believe that. But all this work,
has to be done.
As soon as the bills stack up,
if you really believe there is a heaven,
you just kill yourself just to avoid paying the bill.
I don't see that many
people getting out of their bills that way.
I like not just paying back
what the checkers say.
Henry IV, part one.
I guess so.
I mean, surely there's a room for
various economic theories.
You don't get to the subgenius
heaven unless you buy that membership
pack from J.R. Bob.
I know that.
Well, that is true.
Then you just end up in the grave or the crematorium.
Yes.
But for only $35, you can live forever
or do anything you want forever
once X-Day comes.
If you can make it to X-Day.
That's why you can't kill yourself
no matter how sad you get
and no matter how butthurt somebody makes you
on the internet. You can't kill yourself
because then you might miss your chance for X-Day.
It could happen tomorrow. X-Day could be today.
We don't know.
We don't know, but we have a better idea
than most people.
X-Day probably didn't already happen.
Yes. Probably.
Did we get left behind?
Some people like to say...
No.
Not me.
Nobody got left behind.
I've got two right behinds.
Well, Voltaire was born that way.
That's greedy.
There was that old lady
with only one buttock
in Voltaire's Candide
who'd had a hard life.
That book is so good.
She lost one of her cheeks.
Yeah, well...
But of course,
you could be left behind
if you simply fail at the last moment
to observe the proper procedures.
I cried because the sex goddesses
have 23 vaginas
and I only had 22 dicks.
And then I met a man
who had 24 dicks.
Boy, you're just bringing
everybody down today.
X-Day, where's your cheerfulness?
Everyone looks to you
for some kind of
inspirational statement.
That's right.
Oh, oh, oh no.
I'm slacking in my duties.
Oh wait, slack is fine then.
You slacked in your duties?
I am the first subgenius morale officer.
Please note that I am saluting
on the radio, so...
Alright, look, she really is, ladies and gentlemen.
I can tell you she's saluting.
That really did happen.
I need to deputize.
I need to deputize people
because it's really hard
to be the cheery one all the time.
Well, we don't have to be
so unrelentingly negative.
That was my point.
We should be cheerful ourselves.
Yes, dang, help me out, man.
Cheerful Charlie here.
Come on, man.
He's got a million laughs.
You're just dead.
Now, none of that.
You know it's all rainbows.
Trying to cheer up subgeniuses is hard.
Subgeniuses are so cranky all the time.
You get a halo.
As soon as you get there,
they issue you one
and you get your wings,
you get your...
Palm branch, all that stuff.
Well, the way I've always put it is...
Get your nice long white robe.
If I die and I go through...
No, if when I die,
I go through a lovely tunnel of light
and meet the deceased loved ones...
Yes, there they are.
The spirit of Bob.
Winking and mugging and...
You won't hear me complain.
And if when I die,
I just rot in some grave,
you likewise won't hear me complain.
Are you sure?
Either way,
you won't hear old Reverend Stang complain.
However, oh, I've changed my epitaph
on my tombstone
or whatever you call it on the tombstone.
It was going to say,
Reverend Ivan Stang,
I'll get him for this.
But I've changed it to...
And this only works with a classic tombstone
in a graveyard.
Get off of my lawn.
How about not dead but living?
You can fix this all in post.
Hi, Reverend Stang.
Hi, hey.
You can just put another recording over this
and fix this whole show in post
by removing it from existence.
Oh, crap.
Now I'm being depressing.
What would you do to me, Stang?
All right.
Hearts and flowers.
I'm going to fix the depressing stuff.
That's right, boys and girls.
We've got a great cartoon coming up for you, too.
Well, you know,
I've been sitting here for an hour and a half.
This chair is really uncomfortable.
Yeah, it hurts.
There's something about it.
It's really uncomfortable.
My butt hurts.
I'm butt hurt.
Put a cushion on there and stop soldiering.
Soldier on.
Who's going to fight the next war?
Chin up.
Yeah, come on.
Let's see some military toughness here.
Buck up, buckers.
After all, puzzling evidence never complains.
Even when he's feeling physical agony,
he's always as bland as he usually is.
Maybe he's dead.
Not bloody likely because he's at home doing my radio show.
You can still do that and be dead.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, look at all those dead air.
Look at all those pinks working at their jobs.
They're dead.
They're not even cognizant of the fact that they're miserable.
They're happy to be miserable.
I'm so jealous of them, those bastards.
The thing is, though.
Able to be happy in their misery.
Is this the subject of death special?
All I ever get is bored with my misery.
And that's if I'm lucky.
You know, complaining about your problems, your pains, your miseries.
Your dissatisfaction.
The complaining feels good.
Yes, it's a great painkiller.
Moaning is an excellent painkiller.
Of course, it makes everyone else feel bad.
But when you make an omelet, you have to break a few eggs.
You know, what are you going to do?
That hasn't started working for me yet.
I'm not old enough to be able to fix everything by complaining about it.
Well, it helps.
Like when you...
Practice makes perfect.
When you hurt yourself, you scream in pain.
The scream is a way of dealing with the pain, you see.
The scream is therapeutic.
And in the same way, some of us make art, which is equally therapeutic.
It's just a long, drawn-out process.
But it's the same thing as the scream.
And some of us just get on the internet and make everyone who reads our stuff feel terrible.
And they should.
Because they're not doing it right the way we are.
And we're always right.
Actually, I get a lot of slack reading the miserable posts of the wretched...
...po-buckers and pinks who are so upset at the end of news articles.
Slack.
Especially if the news article mentions...
...the word climate, Obama, or...
What's the...
Nature, basically, or science.
Any of those things, you can...
Anything or just anything.
You just skip the article, go straight to the bottom...
How about anything?
...and enjoy the anger.
The sheer angriness of all those comments.
That comes vigorously boiling out.
A huge load of bile.
It's not even...
You don't even have to categorize it into different types of news articles.
It is literally any news article that you can imagine.
It could be about adoptable kittens.
Right.
And it will still become...
Thanks, Obama.
...just the most awful, evil...
I can't read it anymore.
Kittens are breeding wildly just the way liberal perverts want.
Well, the last week, after those Supreme Court decisions,
was so juicy.
God, they were butthurt.
They were waving.
That was fun.
That was actually fun.
They were fizzing like a Science Project volcano.
I could have done five hours of Slack just reading the comments on Yahoo News.
Well, you should have saved them.
No, I do that every now and then.
And it always angers the three conservatives of the Church of the Century.
Well, it's time that their horizons were widened, too.
I had...
Well, why don't you read the retarded comments by libtards?
It's like, I'm reading this stuff uncut.
I didn't edit these.
This is all there was on the internet.
And it's all funny.
Not if it's meant to be.
I enjoyed watching...
But it's reading a stupid accent.
The backlash of the whole Caitlyn Jenner thing.
I loved watching people get riled up over that.
And I actually delighted in messing with people.
Which I generally don't do.
I don't do that much on the internet.
Generally?
Generally.
Did you ever see the movie Can't Stop the Music with the village people, Valerie Perrine and Bruce Jenner in it?
No.
If you ever did, you would realize there was something hinky about that guy long, long ago.
I'm just saying.
What's the title of that movie?
Can't Stop the Music.
From the 80s, right?
From the 80s.
And it has Bruce Jenner as Bruce Jenner.
Yes.
In a midriff-bearing, short shorts-wearing portrayal with the frolicking village people.
It was the 70s, though, right?
Bruce Jenner was ahead of his time.
No, the 80s.
It was the 80s.
But the thing about this movie is when it came out, it got a good review in the paper.
And Alien, which came out at the same time, got a terrible review.
And I always thought, well, you know, here it is, a light-hearted gay musical.
This is what people like.
And what I like with weird, slimy monsters eviscerating.
You've got to admit, that's not for everybody.
So you should just stifle your irritation at the juxtaposition of these two reviews.
Then years later, many years later, at Bad Movie Night,
which is where a bunch of yocksters get together and make noise at the screen and show a terrible movie,
they showed Can't Stop the Music.
And it really is unbearably rancid and awful.
And Alien is a masterpiece compared to it.
So forget...
Justified.
Yeah, I was justified.
Vindication.
And Bruce Jenner, his behavior in this movie kind of illuminates everything he's done after.
I'm just saying.
Just saying.
Well, I think we've been complaining for 35 years about how fucked up the pinks are.
Yes, they are.
This is no surprise.
1969, the year that 2001 and Planet of the Apes and Midnight Cowboy came out, what got the Academy Award?
Oliver.
The musical.
Yes.
Oliver, Oliver.
You watch that every couple of years?
No.
But it was parodied in The Meaning of Life by Monty Python, so at least it had that good...
What lost out?
Was it Shawshank Redemption that lost out to Forrest Gump in the 90s?
That is sad.
Am I remembering that right?
That's right, Baby Bear.
It did lose out.
And it's a far more popular movie than Forrest Gump ever was or will be.
There's a scene in that movie, This is the End, which is my favorite Rapture movie.
It's a fine movie.
Two thumbs up.
Craig Robinson and...
Seven arms.
And Hermoine from those Harry Potter movies for making fun of this other actor because he didn't like Forrest Gump.
They go, oh, you must be a hipster, huh?
No, no, I'm not a hipster.
Yeah, you're a hipster.
You didn't like Forrest Gump.
No.
You were doing charming things, made other people feel good, and you don't like it, so you're a hipster.
And it's like, no, no, I'm not a hipster.
Again, I'll say it again.
They're all hipsters.
Only hipsters even use the word hipster.
Quite true.
Okay, I'll lay off it now.
I'll shut up about it now.
God damn it!
There you go.
But Forrest Gump, it takes something like that to bring out such declarations and to reveal uncomfortable and intimate psychological...
...truths.
Reverend Irazu and Shadow Coppet have entered the room.
It is true.
They are here.
Oh, and she has beautiful purple hair.
Yes, where's Crevette?
I was hoping to see the new Yeti child.
Where is the bean?
The little bean.
Friday.
Oh, okay.
She's going to give birth on Friday.
Okay, we'll all be there.
From the Dayglo Daygler Center.
Is that where the baptism is going to be?
Yes.
Baptism.
In the placenta.
Oh, man.
The baptism in the birthwaters of Rachel Weard.
In the Central Placenta Center.
Oh, no, the quote on that.
Now, the quote's all messed up on the other side of that sign.
It says, smell.
It says, smell, but then that means on the other side that the quote is missing from Bob, and that means it's sacrilege.
Somebody do something.
But we don't want you to have to see that thing say smile all the time.
It's harmful.
Smell.
Oh, that's what was probably making me so depressed.
Darn you, smell.
The sign that said smile changed to smell.
We're describing a special custom sign that Reverend Suds Basha altered.
It was a K-mark smile party favor sign with five letters.
But if you turn a smile upside down, it spells Bob.
Because it's still five letters.
Why is it necessary to...
If you count the quote mark as one letter.
Why is it necessary?
It's necessary to exhort people to smile.
It seems an exceptional mass of cruelty.
Space migration, intelligence increase, and life extension.
And you know what I really hate, huh?
What I really, really hate?
You know what I hate?
It's when they take their fingers and try to turn your frown into a smile by manipulating your face.
Oh, turn that frown upside down, little fella.
Catch your fingers out of my face.
Bite them.
Yeah.
Bite your fingers off.
I'll catch your belly open.
I'll make you look at the black stuff you got in there.
Oh, goodness.
You've upset the gods with those words.
The wind occasionally comes through this radio studio.
I caught that, and there's a little bit more nectar left.
Maybe later in the week we'll have thunder and lightning during the radio show.
Don't get...
Like that one time, Hugh Lightning cracked recording.
That's why.
Holy head.
Don't worry, folks.
Yes.
Well, we've been...
We've been broadcasting, and there was a lightning crash, flash right outside the studio here.
Oh, lightning struck the grindhouse.
Yes.
It traveled down...
Fightsy Josh had his antenna up, stealing all these movies off the internet, and the lightning...
God tried to stop and shut down the grindhouse by sending a thunderbolt, which we got an excellent stereo recording of.
Holy head.
Not so fast.
It's a very beautiful recording.
And it didn't get...
And none of the electronics were touched.
The power of Bob shielded those expensive DVD players and TVs and things against the power of God Almighty.
So maybe, maybe the war on God isn't going so badly after all.
Yes.
Well, see, I wasn't going to mention the subgenius war on God this time, but you have brought it up.
So you're saying that there's some evidence of...
That's a big order, a tall order to make war on God.
Yes.
Since...
Theoretically, God's the one who is making you make that war on God.
Well...
For his own amusement.
Yes.
Seeing as how you can't beat God.
Another one of those subgenius endless war campaigns.
God respects a feisty subgenius.
Exactly.
And the idea is that by opposing God, you get to heap damnation on yourself.
So it's allowed.
And John loves that stuff.
Jesus take the wheel of pain.
Obviously, God has a sense of humor, and it is a sick...
Sick...
Sense of humor.
Oh, yeah.
Sick.
One glance at the TV...
Wait, wait, hold on.
Is it sick or is it...
In the microscope.
Is it sick?
You'll know.
God is a tool.
Which one is it?
You didn't say...
Is it sick or is it sick?
The sickest way you can say sick.
Sick.
You need to specify.
The words are fluid these days.
I don't know what they mean.
They changed the definition of literally to now include figuratively.
That's part of the definition of it.
Now.
That's awful, but I think your...
It's true, too.
More dramatically articulated sick is better than the blandly articulated one.
Sick was a big word of the 60s.
There were supposedly sick humor and sick jokes, which were not that...
And tasty waves, brah.
Yes, that's true.
Well, Lenny Bruce was called a sick humorist.
And South Park makes him look like a lute-stroking angel in heaven.
So things change, you know.
Time marches on.
By the way, I just bought the South Park video game, The Stick of Truth.
I've heard that's actually pretty good.
I've heard it's actually pretty good.
Have you played it?
No, I have not.
So far, well, you know how when you start a game and...
At some point, you have to make up a name for yourself.
Yeah.
A cartman who's playing wizard demands to know my name.
I'm a little character I didn't get much control over.
And what did I call...
Oh, Lil Stangor was my character's name.
That word?
Lil Stangor.
And the game goes, are you sure that's the name you want?
Yeah, yeah.
Okay, are you sure that's the name you want?
Then cart...
Cartman says to you, okay, I see, your name is Douchebag.
Is that right?
And you push no.
And he goes, I see, your name is Douchebag.
Let's double check.
Is your name Douchebag?
No.
So you shall now forth henceforth be known as Lord Douchebag.
Now, Douchebag, you have to buy a weapon.
You know, and so forth.
Yeah.
It's just like every other video game, except it's South Park.
That's about it.
Well, I've heard it actually has really solid RPG elements.
In order to move ahead in the game,
I had to buy a wooden sword from Butters or somebody,
and then hit another kid a bunch of times with this stupid wooden sword.
And the kid would just go, ow, ow, ow.
And finally run away.
And at that point, you've learned how to use the sword.
So it's like real life.
Oh, okay.
In other words, very, very much like real life.
Everybody calls you Douchebag, and you hit other people with a sword.
It didn't really work.
Please, sounds like in the beginning of...
It made me feel young again.
Reverend Douchebag.
Sounds like the beginning of Roman Polanski's Carnage.
So no matter what name you choose in the South Park game,
you're going to be Douchebag.
Lord Douchebag.
The whole time.
Yes.
And that's supposed to be different from life, I guess.
Yeah, it's funny.
Okay, I agree with that.
In some of the old Zelda games, you could steal from shops,
or you could try to, and if you got caught,
you would be forever no longer.
And that's known for the rest of the game as Thief.
No matter what name you put in, it would always say,
Thief looked in the dresser drawer.
That's like being tattooed.
Yeah.
Having the A stitched onto your forehead,
or the V for Vagabond branded on your hand,
or the S for Subgenius.
P for Pirate.
F for Runaway Slayer.
With the boots of cops.
Yeah.
Wait, no.
No, that didn't happen to me.
Well, anyway, it's possible for these things to happen,
but not likely here at X-Day,
where we're away from the ruck of society's destructive path.
For me, I believe,
Lester, there was a rape, two murders,
a bunch of animal abuse,
and a lynching.
Yes, well, nobody's perfect.
These are ideals that we point toward.
They are not things that we are absolutely able to abide by.
This is a religion.
What is presented?
It is the form of ideals that we work toward.
We do not extend as perfect exemplars of what we're talking about.
Yeah, no kidding.
It was our guru, Bob, that did all those crimes I just mentioned.
See, even Bob used to blow off steam.
You know, boys will be boys.
Yeah, that's what they all say.
It's true, though.
We had some pretty disturbing events here at Mysterio Last X-Day.
We were just having a little fun, Sheriff.
Oh, let them up, boys.
My little dog, Snuckles,
has been turned inside out!
Right, a dog was turned inside out.
Well, that's the worst thing that ever happens at X-Day.
I swear to God, Sheriff Stang,
we weren't drunk.
We was in the car, and it was on,
and Bob grabbed the car,
and he started raping it right up the muffler tube.
But it ran better after that.
Yes, he had the Midas touch with that muffler.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
All right, that's a good one.
I miss the club.
I miss the climactic battle.
I had, like, a whole barbarian costume and everything,
and I miss the climactic battle because I felt sick.
Oh.
I managed to get almost 20 subgeniuses
not only off of their butts,
which was a great challenge to begin with.
But racing.
Now, when did this happen?
And not just off the road a little bit,
but actually about 100 yards into the forest.
Bounding through the forest like deer.
I got 20 subgeniuses to go.
They go into the woods.
It was majestic.
For a very brief time.
That was the greatest achievement I've ever had at X-Day.
That was my moment.
I realized that, don't push it.
After 20 minutes, they're going to start whining and complaining.
They'll come away telling stories about the mosquitoes
and the bugs and the thorns
and all the terrible things in the woods.
Well, nobody ever said it was going to be a bed of roses.
You know, we had to try to catch Bob and save Philo.
We failed.
You buttered your bread, now sleep in it.
You've made your bed, so now eat it.
Shut up.
It is.
It's not just subgeniuses.
During Starwood, there's like 500 people here.
And there's no one on those trails.
There's beautiful, natural trails all around this place.
Well, you know where to go when you want to get away from...
I mean, in the old days, there'd be people copulating out there.
You'd have to step over them every 10 feet.
Not.
No more nowadays.
Oh, since 9-11, no open copulation at Hippie Pagan Festival.
There might be Arab terrorists out there.
Actually, it's not 9-11.
It was the advent of everyone having a camera on all the time.
Well, there is.
That has cut down on the toplessness and nakedity terribly.
There's always someone photographing you
and you have no idea that it's going on.
I've had to take a lot of naked pictures down for years after these festivals.
It's a pain in the butt, too.
Well, I say...
They run around in front of me.
All the cameras naked.
The sun comes and puts a camera in my face.
Blocking in front of the stage, between the cameras and the stage.
And then when you put the pictures of them drunken on the internet,
then they suddenly don't want to be seen.
Oh, now, if our fans are sharing that on Facebook, please take it down.
I do it.
Maybe if we put some artful leaves and foliage in places.
But I'm glad to know that it's already gotten loose on Facebook.
Facebook used to be a different place.
And then everyone's parents got on it and ruined it forever.
I'm not kidding.
There were old starwoods where I did have to politely step over copulating couples.
After dark.
I didn't know they were there until I just about tripped over them.
But, yeah, the cameras.
The cameras changed everything.
The ubiquitous cameras.
How many people got in the pond with their clothes off for the baptism?
About five.
Last year.
Last year?
Yeah.
I didn't.
How did he?
What are you talking about?
Yes, I did.
I just do it after.
You didn't take your clothes off.
Yes, I did.
I do so after the ceremony is over.
Oh, after the cameras leave.
Well, people can stay around if they want.
I suggest there's better things to photograph.
Anyway, the people here are sensitive.
They will never betray your confidence.
Yes, it's true.
You're among friends here at...
X Day.
This is why I just keep my con Facebook separate from my subgenius Facebook.
Otherwise, they might see it work.
You know, my God, look what she does in her off hours.
Yeah, and then I don't have to worry about these things.
Princess Wee, my wife, worked for the county weather control office for 30 years.
Wow.
And at no point did any of her co-workers know that...
She was Jewish, a Democrat peace activist, a folk singer, and helped run a pagan festival.
Those main elements...
Oh, there she comes right now.
Let alone the church of the subgenius.
Her ears must have been...
And here comes Wee Mama.
Grandma Bob is here.
Yes, in mid-broadcast.
The queen of the queen of all the UFOs.
There's lots of them again.
Has made it to the building.
Thankfully, the show is almost over.
When do we actually go off the air, Stan?
Wee Mama, a radio audience, is 85 years old.
And doesn't look a day over 79.
She's super cool.
Maybe we'll get her on the show later.
Well, as we end at the hour?
We can end at the hour anytime.
Because I can put 10 minutes of collage stuff at the beginning.
I kind of want to.
My back really hurts.
Erazu, give me that shirt.
I'm not kidding about that.
Give me it.
I want it though.
I'm on a stage with a microphone.
You have to do what I say.
No!
Ah!
Listening to the radio...
Wait a minute.
What show is this?
The subgenius...
The church of the subgenius radio ministry Hour of Slack.
Broadcast live from Wisteria Community Campground.
From Caffeina's Restaurant.
In the center of the subgenius.
This maelstrom.
Brought to you...
In the days counting down to X days.
By Beer God Beer.
And by the...
Listen to subgenius.com.
And if I didn't say it earlier, which I didn't, the collages that I played at the beginning,
which I'll have to edit in, were by the great Reverend Susie the Flusie, greatest collage,
sound audio collage editor on the planet Earth.
You've been listening to the subgenius radio ministry Hour of Slack.
Yes.
We have got a great moment.
It's been...
Another week.
Another broadcast opening of ourtapplingastone104 channel.
Neeson Wesley-Rollins does not play music and he is closed.
Ed Jagat shows the sound of therites-
or see www.subgenius.com.
Please make a note of it.
Op, op, op, op.
There you have it.
Now you have another one.
Official sign-off of the Church of the Subgenius radio show,
broadcast here from the Wisteria campground.
As all eyes turn skyward,
waiting for the advent of the saucer ships from beyond.
God, is this the year that all our preparations will come to final fruition?
Please stay tuned and hear the answer
in the immediately following iteration of this exciting radio broadcast.
With Phosmo the Clown and Flatulo the Magnificent.
53 minutes.
Oh, God.
Seven more minutes.
No, that's how long we did it the second time.
All right, that's okay, because you need to put in the...
You see, I prepared for 10 minutes of collage.
10 minutes of sound effects and cheap gimmicks and trickery.
You can squeeze a song in there on the radio.
These really helped.
I thought these were like the...
A song?
I don't know how I ever did it.
Yeah, I mean, when he makes a recording later,
he can put in a song for next day at the beginning of that.
But not...
Not a song from you, I guess.
Actually, I didn't prepare a rant,
and the only thing that I have to do as backup is a song,
but I don't know if I'm going to do it,
because I might whiz out.
Well, we'll have to see about that.
I should just write a rant.
Everyone just writes their rants last minute.
Anyway...
I've got to write a rant for...
You've got to write a marriage service, man.
Yeah, that too.
You have to marry two subgeniuses.
I'm going to do that one off the top of my head.
That might be best.
Go to the well and font of inspiration.
Inspiration itself.
Who needs chicken scratches on paper?
Well, it's a lot easier if you know the couple,
although I don't know them that well.
And I know Reverend Fox.
You know they're card-carrying subgeniuses.
But it's fun when they're your friends.
Because you mean it.
That's a good one.
You actually mean it.
Yeah, there you go.
Bro, that's a strange sound.
The thing is changing.
Ah, no.
He's turning.
He's turning into a horrible monster.
Oh, no.
Good Lord.
Look at the size of that thing.
Back.
Well, monsters aren't what they used to be.
Oh, my ears.
So that concludes our Bobcast.
It's like talking on the phone for two hours.
Only it hurts both ears.
Thanks for sitting in there and elevating this sad presentation.
Hour of slow-mo time.
Okay, that's over.
No more joy.
joy.