against the sky
ich will官
Abtopsens Genius Foundation Reset
Untertitelung des ZDF, 2020
Wow!
Burma.
Oh no, I don't know how you spell it.
No, no, no.
You couldn't be from Burma.
No, no.
Look, why don't you do this?
Why don't you go home and have a nice cold grave in Burma?
Look, both of us will feel better.
He's got dance, he's got dance, he's got dance, he's got dance.
He's got dance, he's got treat, he's got treat, he's got treat.
He's got pants, he's got pants, he's got the little tiny pants.
He's got dance, he's got dance, he's got dance, he's got dance, he's got dance.
Hi, I'm the surgeon injured at home on a daily basis.
Ten years ago.
10 years ago.
I looked how he's doing.
Ich habe mich in alle Möglichkeiten gelegt und habe meine Mutter zu Hause gefunden,
weil sie eine immediate, lange medizinische und klinische Behandlung braucht.
Für ihre eigene Schutzwahrnehmung wollte ich, dass sie in der Backhaube für 22 Stunden
als beste Lösung ist, aber sie hat es nicht getan.
Es rippt und riecht, also ruft jetzt an.
Ruf 191-813-981-729-79-317272.
Bitte ruft jetzt an.
Oder bitte ruft jetzt an.
Oder ruft jetzt an.
Musik
Das war Molotow.
Produktion
Musik
Untertitelung des ZDF, 2020
Weitere Bilder in der Beschreibung
Long staggered Erdbeben
Hidden Dorian
Hidden D D D
Bei Artemia Salina
Artemia Salina
Antimina Salina
Imperio Salı
Artemia Salina
Ich bin ein Subgenius!
Und...
Schau!
Ich bin ein Subgenius!
Brudi!
Holy!
Und jetzt...
Die fliegenden Liebeskörbe.
Von den alten Tagen.
Sky King died in the sky.
Von Bern.
Mit der Disco.
I remember the day.
The day Sky King died.
I went to bed that night and I just...
Died!
I remember the day.
Und jetzt, wo Sky King bloggt.
I remember all the guys in the city!
Von Bern.
Flying by.
Und all Sky Kings.
All the guys up.
I know we really are식
I remember seeing that logos.
And the girls smart as dogs.
Whoa!
ả
Die Swingin' Love Corpses
Swingin' Love Corpses
Musik
Thank you, Mr. Sister.
I hate when he starts voting.
Well, that's why nobody will follow him.
Thank you, Mr. Sister.
That was by Fernanda Nandeli-Möhrer.
Before that,
a piece by Artemia Salina.
You are listening to
The Hourglass.
von der Kirche des Subgenius.
www.subgenius.com
Praise Bob and praise the doctors.
This is Reverend Ivan Stang
and you can reach me at
Post Office Box 181417
Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118
Ah, yes.