Frisbee
I started to drive home and I turned on the car radio
But no radio station came through
It was almost as though the radio was dead
And then the strange sounds began
Now that's very strange
I wonder what happens when I change the dial
It's almost like a signal
Is it a signal?
For me?
Wait a minute, let's get a code
Two for yes and one for no, alright?
Am I mistaken?
It's tonight, the night?
You're going to fly down?
I'm not being deceived
Frisbee
There's a radio program that gives you the energy to be a football hero or a rock star
It's so hip, Tammy Bay can't stand it
It lets you drink all the beer you want with none of the drawbacks
And it smooths out all the wrinkles on your brain that contain your childhood phobias
It's the subgenius hour of slack
With your bionically muscle-bound host
The only Reverend Ivan Stang
He wears more hats than Hedda Hopper
Bob gives him free shoes
Every week
He's such a wild driver
The only original parts left on his car
Are the steering wheel and the hood ornament
He's the only man known to science
Who can mysteriously turn a croissant
A can of three-in-one oil
And a tin-vinny nail into a lovely meal for twenty
Give him your undivided attention
Your undying loyalty
And all your spare cash
It's the subgenius hour of slack
9 p.m. Sunday nights
On the official radio station of the 1998 Olympics
KNON
90.9%
9 FM
And Dallas
A division of Subgenius Industries Unlimited
Along with a $20 donation
For this radio broadcast
All I can say is thanks a million
And I won't settle for a cent less
Oh, that's right, dear friends
It's the hour of slack
Hypocrisy you can live with
Or die for
Oh, why not?
Die for Bob
He loves you enough
Surely, surely he does
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha
Does it seem like somebody's working witchcraft?
Who do a voodoo on you?
Does it seem like you have a money jinx?
Or a money hex on you?
So that you can't hold on to money
So that you can't get your money
Do you seem to be unlucky in love?
Unlucky in romance?
Is your husband or your wife
Or your loved one
Running around on you?
Being unfair toward you?
Are you having bad luck in your home
With your children?
With your family?
With your friends?
I want to send you my secret of good luck
And my secret of good luck
Will set you free from bad luck
And bad luck will set you free from bad luck
And bring you the blessings of God
Of help, happiness, love, success
Sideband frequencies and high amplitude harmonics
Yeah, man, that's all cool
But, hey, man, you want to buy some drugs?
Well, uh, it depends on whether you're talking about a linear path or trajectory
Or the initial amount of velocity
Which is repelled by the pure gravity
Well, look, man, I can see you're a little flustered
But I got something to say to you, man, I'm going to get you some drugs, okay?
I got something for you right here
I got some Bob pills
Really?
Yeah
That sounds, uh, um, like quite, uh, placebo
It's legal
It's completely legal
100% FCC approved
Oh, well, I'll take anything that the FCC approves
Okay
Let's both take one
Wow, man, these are great
Hey, wow, boy, that really picks up your perspective on things, you know
All right, I'm doing very, very, very, very
I'm doing jumpy and really just kind of
The initial path of trajectory is modulated by the vector of a hyperscope
Which is
Don't talk to me that way
Possibly, uh
Why are you looking at me like that?
I'm not here, no, man, I'm just thinking
No, I'm just trying to explain to you the basic principles of the, um
Okay
The path of trajectory, right, yeah
As opposed to exponential, uh, algorithm
Which is projected by, you know, a linear curve
Hey, man
The vector, uh, bifurbulation is also, um
Inconsistent with the, uh, incongruent curves of, um
Dilating
Hey, wait a minute, I think I can already see that the piles are wearing off, um
Angles
You can always, uh, smear an oblong square
But you can't, uh, square an oblong smear, right
Uh, unless, of course, you take all the angles and subdivide them by, uh
Two, the ratio of two to one, um, the subcarrier
But anyways, getting back to the vectors
Wow, these pills really do pick you up
I have not talked this fast in a long time
The truth is, I think you need actually more pills
More pills?
Yeah, me too
Okay
You know what's really interesting is that the more pills you take, the faster you can take pills
Which is, which is kind of an interesting concept
Because the faster you take it, the pills, the more pills you want to take
I already feel like taking another one
Let's take another one
Yeah, I just keep withdrawing my pills
Let's go on to the bucket of pills
Go, go, go, go, go, go
Oh, well, yeah, this is really, uh, really quite the rush
I'm going to get some more
You want some medium, large, or small?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I think I'm going to go work on some more
Yeah, I'm going to get a lot of stuff done
I'm going to get a lot of stuff done
Go for it!
Let's go, I know, let's do some drawing
And in my dreams, I walk the earth with giant feet
I hear them sing to me
And the song is beautiful
And leads me onward in hope and joy
The way the future did when I was young
There is the promise of a secret
A secret that will not disappoint
The way love and wealth and power disappointed
A secret contained here
Touching it, there are golden dreaming forests
Cooling a fire
They sing to me, and I am golden
How did I get so old before this moment?
How could I have felt nothing for so long?
How could love have died into this?
There's no point of contact anymore
She doesn't even look at me anymore
She never saw the color draining out of my life
Never saw the emptiness, the weariness
It's been as if I was watching a TV show about someone else's life
It didn't matter
I was a successful man
With a beautiful, elegant wife
A home in the most expensive part of town
And it didn't matter
I had all of it
And nothing felt like anything anymore
Old life
Old
I had been dead
And then
A soft hand
Singing gold and need beyond mourning
Came to me
And was now alive
And every time I stumbled and fell
Something in me got harder
Harder
Became worse
Worse
And in my dreams
I walked the earth
With giant feet
And in my dreams
I walked the earth
With giant feet
Hell Pope Huey
Thank you Hell Pope Huey
Bob loves you.
Oh, wondrous and strange.
Hideous and convoluted are the paths to Bob's secret hideout.
His unobtrusive tract house in the neighborhood of divine transcendence.
Dare you tread that ancient way where shreds of flesh and gnawed bones hint of unspeakable rights and unpalatable half-truths?
Oh, there are no shortcuts to Bob, my friends.
Like a blast of hot wind through the very bowels of the earth, you must pass through the sphincter of the conspiracy's mental and emotional constrictions
into the disciplined dissipation.
Of true slack.
Where you can sit amidst the rage and fusion of nature's most elemental powers without a worry in the world.
What have you got to lose?
As it is, you may be fooling yourself and others that you care about
with smug assumptions that all those things you see and hear around you every day are solid.
Oh, my God.
And that the world is run by people who care about the future.
Or that the world is run by people at all.
Right!
You may as well put yourself in the hands of some smiling pipe-smoking bland-face innocuosity
whose seductive promises of satisfying sex and ill-gotten gain seem suddenly irresistibly attractive.
And that's why Bob's
Give yourself to Bob.
Freely.
Joyously.
Without an atom of restraint.
Now!
Do it now!
And all your worries are over forever, my friend.
Don't laugh.
Oh, God.
Every time I sit down on my kingdom's throne
and junk for the good book
That's my free hand
That will save my soul
Save me
From the vultures of conspiracy
From the chains of time
Save me
From the men in black
It's never such genius
Must have slack
Praise God
So relax
In your
own delusion
Find a place to hide
Get rich on confusion
Save me
From the vultures of conspiracy
From the chains of time
Save me
From the men in black
It's never such genius
Must have slack
Praise God
One, two, three, four
And let me hear you say
Whoaaaaaaaaaa
Thank you.
Sorry, we were that the new tape, Bob's Earwax,
a compilation of songs,
had already had all its labels and such like and masters printed,
but, oh, you'll be hearing from us.
But first...
The U.S. Customs Service is waging war on drug smugglers,
and you can help.
If you see any unusual activity involving private boats or planes
that might be connected to drug smuggling,
call the U.S. Customs Service 24 hours a day
toll-free at 1-800-BE-ALERT.
You can remain anonymous,
and you could receive a cash reward
if your information leads to the arrest and prosecution of drug smugglers.
Help stop drug smuggling.
Call 1-800-BE-ALERT.
Yes, it's subgenius boot camp.
Drinking coffee and staying awake.
Stand up there.
Here, have some old Bob Cologne.
You call yourself a subgenius coming to drill with a beard?
That's two demerits.
Okay.
All right, Mr. Cologne.
Three more demerits and I'll get that new baseball glove.
Look at the knees of your uniform pants.
That's disgusting.
I'm docking you five more demerits, Mr. Cologne.
Oh, gosh, gosh.
Get a new car.
What are you smiling about?
Order me that six more demerits.
Don't just eat a hamburger.
Eat the hell out of it.
My kingdom is on the earth.
Not that I want it.
A good boy.
A good deal is in the wallet of the beholder.
Know ye this.
Knowledge of earth, pagan love, and moons.
Not that the sun, extremists, and the Circus,
discard and mine the great order and patriarchy.
Through my discipline and armies and triumph.
The harlot will bribe thee with the reins of mine.
But anything that is unclean shall be to perdition.
The divine king will be killed in the closet by his own clowns.
Darkness will fall.
The door signs.
Rain.
If you act stupid, them creatures shall come indeed with their bestowals, and their minds and their tools shall be all stirred up together. The image will be made flashing, and I pray to clean the hounds, and that's what I want to talk to you about tonight.
The prophets shall be loosened from their mouths, and they will be made to stand in the midst of the world.
You may not know what you're doing, but that sign shall be known, and they shall command the source of all knowledge, which is likened to a book of the score, and which ground everywhere like a vine.
They shall receive the sacrament from the angels, of the light which preserves the rights in heaven.
The chariots of the Lord shall reign on the right well, and the right will be on the right.
I'll always lie.
Everything comes apart.
Inhibiting Factor, dear friends, a wonderful piece from Inhibiting Factor.
All the...
All the greatest quotes of that man Dobbs in one piece.
Yes, that man Dobbs.
I think Dr. Zedd and Chris Gross can supply the background here for a while.
Even as we sit here quietly pursuing our own ends, or...
Ends.
Alien forces.
Of annihilation.
Powered by dreams too hideous to contemplate.
Gather in a frenzy of normalcy just outside your door.
Just over your shoulder.
In the very stars overhead.
Drunk with boredom and abstraction.
They cluster around graphs and charts and maps which target with cool scientific...
Cool scientific...
Precision.
Any center of lunatic resistance.
Only Bob's embrace.
Only the refreshing and intoxicating cloak of his burning frop can transmute this coarse
material substance of our flesh into the glorious, invisible leisure of nothingness itself.
They won't even be able to see you.
Much less crush out the light of your Bob's soul in the dull routine of their monstrous design.
They'll be able to see you.
Trade in hours and weeks and years of tedium for an eternity of controlled abandonment.
So claim again your ancient genetic heritage, your bludgeon of prophetic and profitable irreverence,
your right to smite.
And when that stark fist of removal swoops low and makes such a mess of things during
the final days, squeezing a fine vintage wine from the harvest of believers and unbelievers
alike, you can sip that heady brew and toast the master of ceremony whose beneficent grin
spared you that senseless sin.
But never do you dream of Jess's leaving.
Better die than cả một chết, and that being a tale of true doświadозмu食енс,
Next debate
aszcz somehow
One of us
All
A lovely piece from the Reverend Parks.
I'm reading you secret previews of the Stark Fist, my friends.
That's what this is.
This is the Stark Fist ahead of its time.
We're busting booty on that magazine, friends.
You members out there, just to let you know.
It'll be worth the wait, more than worth the wait.
Thank you, Professor Gross, for the music.
And here's Clark.
Change takes time.
We don't want to feel bad.
There's no sense in that.
Just relax.
Contingencies.
I'm a human being.
Just relax.
How much do I really know?
Like a freight train in my veins.
I'm a human being.
Just relax.
Come, James, please.
We don't want to feel bad.
Change takes time.
There's no sex in there.
I'm a human being.
Change takes time.
There's no sex in there.
We don't want to feel bad.
Baby, you ought to be bad
Come, mio, baby
POSSIBILITY!
Just relax.
POSSIBILITY will never end.
Just relax, dear friends.
Don't worry about the screams.
The church of the subgenius isn't here to hurt you.
No, no, nothing like that.
That was Quark, by the way,
a tape sent to the church headquarters here in Dallas
from Atlanta, Georgia.
Never heard from him before,
but the other four songs on this tape are great.
You'll hear them next time.
You'll never hear them anywhere else,
because you never see the materials
of the subgenius church anywhere else
until years later after they've become famous.
You wouldn't believe how many people
you watch on TV now
that were subgenius $10 members back in 1980.
Saw one in a movie last night.
Interesting the way that works.
Yeah.
When was the last time you sank
to the untamed groove of white man?
When was the last time you witnessed
shallow rain at Deep Ellum's finest,
funkiest venue?
Club Dada.
When was the last time you were healed
by ultra-healer and inspirational speaker,
the Reverend Bob?
Not to be associated with the church of the subgenius.
Your favorite radio station, KNON.
Make this your first time
or your long-awaited next time
to do all of the above.
For on Wednesday, April 20th,
KNON and Club Dada Productions
proudly present white man, shallow rain,
and the Reverend Bob.
Two bands, two unique sounds,
one inspirational speaker, $5,
one night of healing and rocking.
2720 Elm Street at Club Dada.
I'll see you on Wednesday night, April 20th.
He instantly becomes another one of those dumb minorities.
And we can tolerate his kind.
Yes, friends, this is probably a good time
for me to just drop in and mention that
the Reverend Bob that you see playing in clubs
around Deep Elm and Lower Greenville
is a very, very funny individual
and does a great takeoff on fundamentalist religion.
He has been calling himself Reverend Bob
since long before Bob Dobbs
revealed his secret doctrine to us
at the church of the subgenius.
So though we do not know
or disassociate ourselves from the Reverend Bob
you often see in public,
we condone and endorse his humor.
However, what we're doing is not humor.
This is not a comedy show.
Everything you hear on here is absolute gospel truth
according to the word of that man, J.R. Bob Dobbs,
who would not be caught dead ranting or doing comedy.
Comedy!
I mean, not even me would be caught dead
doing comedy at some local dive.
I've had to get out there and try to preach the word.
They often call it comedy to attract people,
but that's what it's required.
For those of you who are brand new to this
and wonder what all this subgenius thing is about,
I'll give you a quick history here, okay?
Oh, this is from Prescriptures 1871.
In the book of the subgenius.
Simon & Schuster publication.
The music in the background is by Martin Mothersbaugh.
Long, long ago, during the years of trouble,
when all the northern fathers still slept beneath the glaciers,
there lived the being we now know as J.R. Bob Dobbs.
This man, Dobbs, was chosen by Jehovah One
for the primary communications from our alien benefactors.
As Bob moved through the stars, he changed the face of them.
His ten billion quasi-modalities now vibrate in each of us.
This has transformed him into the eternal incarnation
of slack.
From Dobbs came the unreasonable, unreasoned utterances
which have since remained forever unerasable.
His brave experimentation with extra-meditation
and fornicationalism on a mass scale
resulted in the rule of the subgenius for the next 12,000 years,
using all humankind as his test flock.
During his span, disaster followed Dobbs,
resulting in the outright obliteration of his physical shell.
Only by careful church-supervised studies
can we now have our first look at the Dobbs shell.
Here is the approved religiofficial bioreconstructoid
seen on slide number four in the corner of your screen,
perfect in every detail.
This is him, our salesman.
His skull is shaped a bit differently than ours is today.
It is somewhat flattened in the rear and bulges over the brow.
His brain was well devolved.
Some theocraticians think that Dobbs did not speak at all,
or that if he did, he did not have what we would call a language.
He wears the suit.
His hands and feet are like ours.
He was left-handed.
The briefcase he holds sent the signals that launched the rockets of cleansing,
the blessed vehicles of our birth, we the mutants.
He is seen here, standing in the wreckage of Earth, his native planet.
That's from the directions of the model Plasticos de Don Dobbs
and the
The
The The The The The The The The The The The Formula
© BF-WATCH TV 2021
The world ends tomorrow, and you may die.
Self-preservation came first.
Kill or be killed was the fundamental law.
© BF-WATCH TV 2021
After an infinity of groping in the darkness, man was beginning to find some answers, to understand the values which lay in group living and mutual assistance.
You do what you do because you want to. I do what I do because Bob told me to. That's all I need and that's all you should need.
Here's your instructions. Okay, you want instructions? You want to know what you really think? Here it is. Here's the truth.
Resist all conspiracy normal programming. Be different from them. Ignore or distort.
All fashion. Kill them in the streets. Hunt them down. Smash all governments and exterminate all leaders.
Resist all conformity. Speak out for complete mutant freedom.
Laugh at them. Laugh at them before you kill. Whisper rumors in the dead of night.
Build fallout shelters and arm them. Buy comic books and read them.
As religious tracts, for they are. Prepare for the end.
Mutter while walking along the streets. Eat junk. Run wild. Don't question authority. Destroy it in public.
Quote bizarre sources. Don't follow any trend. Lie.
Make bombs and guns validate all emotions.
Disrupt the orderly flow of life. Speak up. Speak up. Declare your difference.
Scream aloud the truth in public. Make them hear you. Store food. Hoard things. Carry weapons.
Die. Die. Cause the dead to walk. Play with toys. Spend all your money. Buy. Live it up. Be a man.
Behave poorly. Fire shots into the night. Argue with them. Practice death and fertility rituals.
Design your own church. Pray and invoke the forgotten ones.
Search for the elder gods. Steal and rob.
Make burnt offerings. Make sacrifices to childhood gods.
Believe in devils. Watch the skies for UFOs.
Or Jesus.
Break out. Mutate all over the place.
Strike fear into the hearts of normals.
Alienate all humans. Vandalize. Don't play it safe.
See what you can get away with. Get drunk. Watch TV all day long.
Indulge yourself. Stop caring. Never give up.
Declare your freedom. Quit your job and slack off.
Make the weird signs. Consort yourself.
Work with strange characters. Con your family and friends.
Listen! Look for art and beauty in the gutter.
Make tapes of winos. Go to bed.
Cure yourself. Invent things. Snarl at people. Be free.
Hooray!
Marry people. Levitate. Baptize. Cast out the false prophets.
Burn. Burn. Smite the arch demons.
Contact aliens, space gods and monsters.
Use black magic to probe the secrets of the universe.
Come out on top. Make up theories to explain everything.
Goof off. Tell stories. Don't give in.
Do things your way. Don't listen to the crap.
Understand the bowels that exist.
Make public your superiority. Laugh. Damn.
Curse. Get revenge. Play mean jokes.
Stay up all night. Go on a binge. Explode in a rage.
Take out your frustrations. Rationalize. Let it all seem unreal.
Fall in love. Punch out the boss. Control the world.
Create life in your basement.
The Savage Beat is everywhere.
We are the Savage Beat.
Hey! Hey!
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! Yeah!
Yes!
It's the scream that knocks you out when you go down for the count.
It's the dream becoming reality and the battle cry of success.
seduction. Estimal? It's true! I know you asked me how it all began, but it seems it's
always been like that.
Aye! Aye!
Whoa, whoa, yeah!
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
Yeah!
Saturday afternoon in my living room, I was looking for some housekeeping. He said he
was Nicaraguan, but sometimes he was Dominican, too.
It's true!
The star in his eyes could have filled the book of Revelations.
And after his lips wet, thinking no candles and 50 faces.
Really, it's true!
I know what you're thinking right now, but I was weak and backsliding, and I liked it!
Ow, yeah!
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
Do it to my fever now!
This has nothing to do with me!
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
It's just a simple realization.
There's a point in space and time where everything comes to a grinding halt.
Once you make eye contact like I did, you can't be responsible for your actions!
Fascination becomes participation as consciousness slips away into...
Ow!
Screaming at you out when you go down for the count.
It's a dream becoming reality and the battle cry of seduction.
Hey!
I really do these things!
I told you, it's true!
Oh, yeah!
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
Ow, ow!
Ooooooooooow!
Ov, ov, oerin', ho!
Spirit!
Get em out of here now!
Oh, yeah!
Oh, oh, oh!
Oh!
Oh, oh!
The Church of the Subgenius, dear friends.
Bob wants you to use the things you were born with.
Why do you think you were born with them?
Why do you think the Lord made it feel so good?
Oh!
Och...
Oh O родной Th Contact
Oh!
V Mt.
Become the mad scientist of your dreams. There's no reason why not to.
Bob is here. He's the proof that everything you know is true. You may now proceed.
Conjure monsters! Conjure monsters! Shout it out! Speak in tongues! Talk to gods! Give up on idiots!
Never pay for it! Get out of having to do things! Put it all off! Don't bother with it! Collect things!
Dream your life away! Study what is banned! Bone up on the forbidden sciences! Believe in the occult!
Have guts! Prove you're weirder than they are! Scare the beed Jesus out of them! Be sick! Do whatever you want!
Justify your guilt!
Never play into their hands! Be evil! Be good! Be neither! Size up the situation! Open your eyes!
Don't do what they say! Trick them! Walk on your hands! Make your house into a castle! Defend yourself! Write letters!
Expose them at every turn! Hide out! Go underground and stay there! Break promises! Cast off all responsibility! Don't accept anything!
There are others!
There are no laws! Everything is permitted! Get angry! Act ape-like! Become an overman! Band together with other true mutants!
Discover your history! Learn your past lives! Travel in time! Stripe back! Plot to take over!
Be unreasonable in everything! Dare! Battle with the arcane forces of space and time!
Know thyself!
Program the computer god! Confront the demons of your own soul! Arise! Stare into the void! Dance at the edge of the abyss! Use ESP! Travel to the stars on the solar winds! Jump in the leaves! Abandon the darkness! Embrace it all! Sell your soul to the old ones! Spy on them! Penetrate their lives! Make yourself be heard! Go crazy! Take a stand for mutant freedom before it's too late!
Start to penetrate their lies!
Protest it all! Don't try to be cool! Don't be a hip wimp! Get tough! Wake up! Discover the forgotten things! Fool them! Attack their beliefs! Get rich! Warp out on music! Unmask them or kill me!
If you want to support our work! Give us a thumbs up! insisted on providing grants from over 8 million supporters!
I'm burning this tape. I'mope to start praying to God!
i really.
Yeon hey, thoi.
terrier.
He's a demon.
God, I must be a demon worshipper.
I just gotta be.
Damn.
Bunch of Satanists like this.
Man, I just hope he doesn't
do that creature thing
where he doesn't...
All that talk about Bob, man, makes me
puke, you know what I'm saying?
I, uh...
There is a great pestilence upon this land.
Here he goes.
Or is it a great mortarance?
Oh, Nick Smith again.
There is a great mortar and pestilence
upon the land.
I never let see.
It is a common thing
among our youth today
to become
one with...
the monster predicted in the Bible.
Its core, a seething mass
of lethal radiation.
Its head,
the head of Philodrumon.
Runs its legs
over the brains of the listener.
And with the secondary brain
located at the base of the spine.
There's no brain anywhere around here.
While in its forepaws, it bears a cup
bearing all the abominations
and filthiness of the world.
This hideous creature
shambling around
this shambling mob
is waiting for something to be born.
The basement of my spine.
The basement of your spine, yes.
As Cyclonians 425 tells us,
he was delivered
and eviscerated for our sins
and was regurgitated to live in death
for life that is in him
for the just and only
of our sins.
As we wander
Hey, Dr. Drummond,
do you have a light?
I'm still here, though.
Oh, no cigars for you, Stang.
Have some fresh lemonade.
Okay, that's right.
Okay, goodbye.
Here goes.
Farewell, farewell.
But this I shall see you
at our wedding, yes.
Ah, that felt good.
Evaporated.
I feel like the phylo's gone out of my head.
Every color that is destroyed
gives us terror.
Ah, destroyed.
By the sound.
Though the dear Bob
he made and loved us all.
You can tell it's getting down near the end.
Is that the show deflating?
Have we got a leak in the show?
Man,
we're gonna have to land soon.
Which of which of this
There's plenty of waste gas in the show.
Look at the ozone bubbling up.
In fact, I would say waste gas powers the show.
Look at that spark leap across the gas.
Yeah, don't let it spark across the waste gas.
Don't look directly at that arc.
It can burn out your eyes.
Don't look at the spark in the waste gas.
Show error, one conspiracy per breath.
A penny a puff.
And a pound a poop.
Isn't that the way it is?
You pay more to get rid of it
than you're good to get it.
Is that the way it is in your life, my friend?
Look at this disgusting
organic mess.
You know what this heaving monstrosity is?
It's every piece of meat you ever ate in your life.
Now it's back to us.
The need for one gigantic creature
which we call
the Overslime.
We begin show sequence four.
The Overslime.
Bob stuck new pets
in Overslime maintenance.
Edit show mode seven.
Young Adam Cadman Dobbs
brought home the Overslime one day.
Oh, show deflating.
Two night of slack shooting tape.
As Connie shows support mechanism.
Can I actually do this?
The tapes did not die because he had to.
Wellman chose to kill him
on the stage for unique everyone.
But mainly for his own reasons.
This man was handed over to you
by Dobbs who set purpose and knowledge.
And he, of course,
is the making to the people at Overslime
with the help of Rucos,
Pinkton, Wands,
putting together by nailing him with raw
cat hairs of Wellman's gums.
And who got up in the morning
just to be able to slay him?
This computer is incapable
of saying things like that.
It was impossible to make it so.
Little other computers hurting brain now.
Yes, friends, that's what happens.
That's what the show does to you.
Especially this show in Berkeley.
That was puzzling evidence.
Dr. Howell, the evil Dr. Howell,
Gary Gabrogfran,
and myself for once.
That's it.
On KPFA in Berkeley.
But this is KNON 90.9
in Dallas, Texas in the morning.
And this is what happens to you
when you get too much show here.
Who's that?
Oh, I know, I know.
It was the other one.
You're moving too fast for me.
I'll just sit over here and relax.
Yeah, just relax.
Just relax.
I'm having a good trip.
I'll start again.
I'll talk a little bit slower.
If you start talking slower,
then I'll have to concentrate on what I'm saying
and then I'll start getting into this stream of consciousness
just like it's coming out of my mind as soon as I think it.
I can't think of it anymore.
So just think and just talk slow.
Or else.
Yeah, oh yeah man, I can dig that.
That's cool. That's cool.
Hey, well, uh, not to get too excited or anything,
but, uh, you got any more of those pills?
Oh, you mean those green pills?
Or those, uh...
Actually, the red ones would be really cool.
You don't want to try the red ones.
You see what's happening already.
Oh yeah, the red ones. Those are the good ones.
Yeah, I like the red ones.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You can't have any more red ones.
Give me the bag back.
There's something weird going on.
It's slightly delayed. I can hear a little feedback.
Yeah, do you hear the echo in the room?
It's not an echo.
Let's just take a little more pills.
Oh, you gotta be careful about them pills, friends.
Oh, yeah.
You gotta be real careful.
I want you to write for information
from the Church of the Subgenius.
Free information
in this video.
This outreach...
trying to bring
succor
to the suckers, you might say.
No, no, not really. To the mutants.
Sounds funny to say that.
Sometimes we make it sound like a funny joke.
Ha, ha, ha.
It's not that funny.
Well, what should I get out on? Shoot.
This is the rain.
We got three minutes to go until
Robert Wisdom's
American Music Party.
I think we got into it pretty good.
This is the Rainmakers song.
This is their Bigfoot type song.
I thought about saving it until we did a Bigfoot show,
but it's not really about Bigfoot.
It's really about crazy people.
And that's why you need to write
Bob at P.O. Box 140306
Dallas, Texas.
Oh, yes.
Dallas, Texas 75214.
That's Bob at
P.O. Box 140306
Dallas, Texas 75214.
Thank you.
I'm Bob at P.O. Box 140306
You can find me on
www.daviddick.com
I'll see you next time.
Bye.
There's a wild man
Lives in the woods
Outside of town
Howls at the moon
Listen if you can
You might hear the late view man
. . .
Some say he was a soldier
Who came home from war
All in one piece but with emotional scars
We'll be on the story, argue about the days
Vietnam or the war between the states
And the late new man is a wild man
Lives in the woods outside of town
Bow to the moon, listen if you can
You might hear the late new man
guitar solo
I took the shortcut to the river last night
A beard and a blur in the long mean lights
We drank a few beers, skipped a few stones
And I drove a little faster on the way back home
guitar solo
A dog disappears, a cow is found dead
A chicken is missing, bound missing its head
Shotgun gone, bread in the sand
Two toes shy of the late new man
The late new man is a wild man
Lives in the woods outside of town
Bow to the moon, listen if you can
You might hear the late new man
Cause the late new man is a wild man
Lives in the woods outside of town
Bow to the moon, listen if you can
You might hear the late new man
guitar solo
A dog disappears, a cow is found dead
He lives in the woods outside of town
A chicken is missing, bound missing its head
A dog disappears, a cow is found dead