Eternal salvation or triple your money back.
The Church of the Subgenius bring you another 33 minutes of condensed, uraglic function over
the quality audio-visual techniques exacerbated and complicated by The Church of the Subgenius,
copyright 1985-86.
And then there's that pesky rumor of a talking elephant in Russia.
Are we going to let the communists get ahead of us with a talking elephant?
Well, that's irrelevant.
You're here.
We're listening.
A talking relevant?
We're just talking, that's all.
They say that this elephant, that the Ruskies have, can mimic human speech.
Okay, what happened?
Step into the light.
I have received miscellaneous materials.
Okay.
They're real slow because they've got these...
I've seen Danish pornography advertisements.
They're just a strike, actually.
They're combas, really.
They're Bolivians that are important to do the work.
There is the truth of the rumor that there is a strike going on in the Subgenius Church.
Their whole goal is to put a microchip underneath the skin of a person's hand or forehead.
And I was pretty amazed because that's exactly what the book of Revelation says, chapter 13, chapter 13, chapter 13.
There are people out there who are musicians.
They may well like to be involved in a group, a specialty group that tours and reaches people for Christ.
How can they get a life?
They're very loving, gentle little people.
Yes.
There's something terribly wrong with them.
How do you mean?
They seem to have the minds of five-year-olds.
How do you expect them to be?
Far ahead of us, of course.
Incredibly ahead of us in knowledge and in science.
Look at them.
Children.
They seem happy.
There's this huge garden of theirs.
If the Lord is going to come again, well, what's going to happen to my mother?
So pink and hard.
And remains of a coming...
Peace.
Happy New Year.
Happy New Year, friends.
The sun's sent us off.
Take your little babies full of cash and don't...
Happy, frappy...
Oh, we already did the New Year show.
Well, this is Chaz's New Year show, friend.
New Baby 1999 comes crawling around the...
Oh, that was last...
That was our last show and his last show at the same time.
And the old man, 1998, with his broken body...
And this is show number 667, dear friends.
We actually made it past that fateful show.
Speaking of shows, we just heard some of old, old show from the olden days.
Puzzling evidence show with Dr. Howell and, in this case, Glass Madness.
Yes.
Gary Gebrog-Fran and The Lies and...
And E. Einstein.
Einstein's Secret Orchestra.
It's a new last countdown to X-Day, friends.
Praise Bob.
A new...
Last...
Year.
From the beginning
Turn off your mind
Relax
And float downstream
It is not dying
Lay down all thoughts
Surrender to the void
It is shining
New Baby 1999 comes crawling around the...
Evening
His machine guns in one hand and the crack pipe in the other.
And the old man in 1998 with his broken bob pipe and his crashed saucer.
Go watering.
Go down into the pond...
His paint feathers, yeah.
Into the pond.
Into the pond with old man time.
I was just wondering to see what we can do about getting the pornography out of our stores.
What it was I just walked in a store ten minutes ago, and they had pornography magazines playing up our stories.
in view right over the counter nothing covering them up or yeah they're making money off lights
at the end of the time yeah you can focus on the light at the end of the tunnel yeah
that big that four foot bomb bomb bomb at the end of the tunnel
but listen to the color
it is not living
oh play the game existence to the end
of the beginning
of the bikini
have entered a forbidden step i'm sorry
whoa don't fire in the air you don't know where it's coming down but i know what's coming
yeah that's right baby i'm going out into the night
in the hydraulic low hopper mobile because i've come to the end of my day
it's the day of all days the last day but i'm out of here but you better stick around
baby
see my children you slip into your secret underwear you get on over to the dark side of your mind
because she is arriving ready to act twilight web mix you give it on up for the dark widow the
arrogant queen of the night beeper uh the dark widow the egg and queen of the night
etc etc called in sick cannot be this is not happening to me it is happening miss shelob is
feeling poorly oh yeah what's she got the 12-hour e bowler wish i'd thought of that oh yeah well i'm
I'm glad you didn't, because you've got to hang till midnight.
Hey, man, I've got a life.
I've got a wife. I've got a daughter.
I've got a new baby.
I promised I'd take him to the doll drop.
Hey, radio is a heartbreak, B-man.
You're the night emperor now.
New format coming up the M-bone.
You're online.
With detoxified, gender-blind,
re-baptized, up all night.
Talk radio.
It takes a village to raise the dead.
Ha, ha, ha.
I'm Lord Eddie Beaverbrook,
owner and chief insomniac at
Unconscious Village.
And it's the last day
of our last day's sale.
So read them the gospel slip.
Thanks, boss. Hey, put yourself down under this.
It's a horned dog of Babylon,
struggle snuff, smother set,
insult for slack claw.
You'd prophesize the price at a thousand dollars,
but read my forehead.
Six, sixty-six,
sixty-six.
Rise now.
For I come to your bedroom
with my long rod
to measure you for the last bed
you'll ever need.
Okay, mooch. We got them all.
You tell them, little Eddie.
I said it, Dad. I'm up to my gonads
in Rapture Sauce, Christian Slater's,
Lamb of God's, Downey Jr.'s,
and Seven Sealy's at
Unconscious Village.
I am asleep.
You are.
You are asleep.
Run out.
Friend, where will you be when your tape runs out?
Will you be on hand?
Who's gonna flip your tape?
You can pay Bob to flip your tape.
It's next year, man.
It's next year here.
It's the future.
Chaz, can you believe that we live to see 1999?
Yeah, I was just telling Michelle that
when I was a little kid.
You know, I figured out how old I...
Oh, I'll be this many years old
in the year 2000.
And just think what life will be like then.
We'll be living on the moon.
Yeah.
We'll be flying around with jetpacks
and we'll have anti-gravity shoes.
And, God, life will be so cool
in the year 2000
and I'll be like 42 years old.
You know?
And, wow, that'll be cool.
I'll probably be like some real jet-setter
kind of a, you know, swinging single guy
that you might see
in a George Jetson cartoon
or something, you know.
And it's true.
And, uh,
and it all came true.
Yeah.
A year early.
But the cities were supposed to look like
in the Jetsons, you know.
All the cities are supposed to look
different, but they don't.
They look just the same.
If lightning is the thought may be,
it could happen.
The sun will become dark,
the moon blood red,
the stars of the heavens will fall,
there'll be two major earthquakes
that are going to become,
the islands and the mountains
are shaken out of their sockets,
and the second one, no island,
no mountain was found
in the face of the earth.
It's all coming.
The last skit that they had
was these two guys, employees there,
actually a couple of supervisors
of the store,
dressed up as women,
and they did their little skit
in part that one of the guys
actually kissed the other guy.
What was the point of this?
The skit was customer service.
Each wave.
Each wave left over from the Big Bang
peak to peak
is 300 million light years,
and you could surf that wave
if you have the right equipment.
You've got a real good guitar and amp.
Yeah.
And the right feedback plug-in.
And the right state of mind.
You get in the tube.
Yeah.
Not the tube of the universal wave, baby.
Slide into the new millennium.
Skate on in.
To be totally tubular.
It is so totally tubular,
and we have some news,
and we have some prophecy.
It's an hour of prophecy, dear friends,
and this music in the background
is Einstein's Secret Orchestra.
We've also been listening to
Chaz Smith's edits
of Einstein's Secret Orchestra, Volume 12,
New Year 1999.
We heard some Firesign Theater
from their new album,
Give Me Immortality or Give Me Death.
And we've been hearing
the original Subgenius Radio show,
which even predates Hour of Slack,
although I was on their first shows.
The KPFA,
once a subgenius,
less than an hour show.
Mars Climate Orbiter,
Mission Stats,
December 28, 1998.
Now this is some suppressed news, friends.
Earlier today,
Mars Climate Orbiter
attempted to fulfill its prime objective,
that of photographing and studying
the enigmatic face on Mars.
As it attempted to do so,
high intensity laser beams flashed
from the eyes of the face,
severely crippling the orbiter.
At the same time,
hordes of flying craft
exited the mouth of the face
and began an attack of the orbiter
with relatively conventional weaponry.
Caught unaware,
NASA was helpless to put up a defense
due largely to the time delay
caused by the great distance.
For more information on the Mars Surveyor 98 mission,
visit our website at
mars.com.
NASA.jpl.nasa.gov
Uh, yes, uh, it's a...
Friend,
as we leave these holiday periods behind
in the washrags of time,
you have to ask yourself,
would you lie to the United States government
about your sex life?
I would,
but only if the government asked me
about my sex life.
And, you know, I think that if...
William Jefferson Clinton
was a real man,
a Republican,
Monica Lewinsky and Linda Tripp
would both be with Jack Ruby
and Lee Harvey Oswald
or else where in concrete pumps
at the bottom of the Chesapeake Bay,
then we never would have heard
about any of this stuff.
Oh, also in the news,
dear friends,
I finished editing
the X-Day video documentary
two-hour version.
I'm not trying to...
hawk or sell anything.
I just am proud
that I did finish that
this last weekend.
Uh, Washington, D.C.,
in a surprise announcement
with wide-ranging implications
for United States narcotics policy,
Drug Enforcement Administration Director
Thomas Constantine
acknowledged Monday
that some winners
may occasionally use drugs.
Apparently, said Constantine,
it's not just drugs.
It's also the drug industry.
He's addressing reporters
at Justice Department headquarters.
Contrary to the DEA's
long-standing conviction,
drug use may not be limited
solely to the domain of losers.
It appears that some successful Americans
have experimented with illegal narcotics as well.
The announcement was the result
of a comprehensive three-year DEA study
of more than 40,000 U.S. winners,
including thousands of successful business execs,
doctors, lawyers, scientists,
and the like.
The study is a success.
The study, originally designed by the DEA
to help shed light on the qualities shared by winners
that make them resistant to drugs,
instead revealed that over 71% of winners
had at one time or another
experimented with controlled substances.
He said it remains unclear
why winners who enjoy successful, productive careers
and feelings of love and acceptance from their families
would choose to engage in drug use.
Time and time again, he said,
DEA tests have shown that no feelings of love,
hatred, or hatred
you can get from drugs
could be better than the great feeling
you get from being a winner.
Why a heart surgeon, architect,
or straight-A student would use drugs
when his senses are already enormously heightened
by the high that comes from being a winner
is beyond me.
And it goes on and on.
Winners seem to have an unknown quality
that enables them to use drugs
and keep on winning.
It goes against everything we know about drugs,
but many of the drug-taking winners we studied
did not win.
They did not, in fact, become losers.
Well, they're going to change.
As a result of the study, it says here,
the agency ordered a recall of a bunch of U.S. video games
which will be reprogrammed with a new altered on-screen message
from former FBI Director William Sessions.
The new screen will say,
quote,
Very few winners use drugs.
The agency will say,
I'm not sure where that news report came from, dear friends,
but more important than the news is the prophecy.
The prophecy, friends,
when a subgenius minister goes into the spirit,
like Bob did.
Bob paved the way for us, friends.
In 1953, when he underwent his immaculation
at the hands of Jehovah One,
the alien space god from some corporate sin galaxy,
Bob went into the spirit and he saw X-Day.
He saw the prophecy.
He saw, like a big movie,
he saw the holy screen.
And most recently,
our good friend,
Popes Lilith von Frau Mensch,
has, well, as it says here,
decoded from background noise
using anti-sleep driven delusivination techniques
on January 13th, 1999.
Some of these may already have happened.
Nobody says prophecy had to predict the future.
All right, friends,
now I can't say this in Popes Lilith's husky voice.
I'll have to use my own husky voice,
but let's let Einstein's secret orchestra
establish the rug here.
Predictions, 1999.
Planet-wide,
excess-induced gut blowout
blamed on millennial hysteria,
televised and outlawed.
Prophecy number two,
millions sign over power of attorney
and social security benefits to aerospace firm
in exchange for one-way tickets to the moon.
First lunar slave colony,
highly successful,
but eventually nuked by the UN.
Got to start to kind of feel like Criswell.
Um,
can you prove it didn't happen?
Lennon and Mal clones will be decanted
and Mick Comey's franchise is in the deep south within a year.
White stones of Muom discovered in the Pacific Ocean.
Muom reveals that its location was preparation for a new deluge.
Muom already here on Earth?
Could it be?
This is not mentioned in Revelation.
Nor a book of the subgenius.
An inner cabal of excess
attempting to stop the rupture
executed,
reported by the conspiracy media as
meteor shower.
The subgenius movie gets financing
but is suppressed and used as pornography
by Hollywood moguls.
Used as the source for movie rip-offs for next decades.
Popes Lilith,
I got news for ya.
That happened in 1983.
And the results were
Running Man,
Total Recall,
and I can't remember a couple of others.
They were all Schwarzenegger.
Terminator also.
Okay, random Bobby videotapes moguls having sex
while the subgenius movie plays in the background.
Wins Oscar, donates percentage to church.
Well, that sounds silly to me.
But it would be great.
Um,
D. Rose, commitment to the church.
Mass suicide.
Major earthquakes throughout the Pacific Rim.
Corpses of these creatures
found by Brazilian street youth
who wear the carapace as protection
from police and pedophiles.
Brazilian street urchins wearing the carapaces of
D. Rose,
supersonic Nazi hell creatures from beneath the hollow earth.
Dead ones.
Blown up to the surface.
Okay, Little Rock resident charged with
assassinating Clinton.
Murdered the next day on television by Vince Foster.
Clinton assassination proved to be a hoax.
Uh,
Friends, the future holds,
well, this is, I gotta admit,
it does sound a little bit like Weekly World News
and they do have better illustrations with theirs.
But, friends, did you know that F.R.O.P.
cures AIDS, neurological disorders, and cancer?
Stephen Hawking will be completely healed
and present a perfectly rational, yet spiritual,
compelling reason to send $30
to Post Office Box 140306,
Dallas, Texas 75214.
Hawking later contracts Tourette's Syndrome
induced by F.R.O.P. thera-
Oh, well, um,
A one, a two, three, a-
Okay, maybe this one will do.
Cause I want to get to the real deal
and release the bad gaming jerks
almost Влад fucking
policejugger
lack the killer
oficking
faculty
let's five
you 5
you oficking
claim to be heroes or gods.
But you guys are good.
If you tune in to any
religious station up here right now,
they're all talking about, you know,
in revelations it says that this will happen.
Yes, there will be
enemies fighting the true
believers. And we see this
has come true only for the first time
right now, this year. Yeah, this one guy
yesterday, man. There will be corrupt politicians. Uh-huh, see?
They want to implant those chips
inside your head. That's it.
Women will wear pants.
This has been prophesied.
And men will have long hair.
Fool me once, shame on you.
Fool me twice, shame on me.
Fool me one game on me.
Fool me twice, shame on you.
Shame on you.
There is many levels of consciousness
available to the human being
as there are structures
and atomical organs
inside the body
for decoding
different sorts of energies.
The DNA.
DNA scattered all over the place.
Not just in level C or level T
or level X.
In the beginning,
God created the heavens
and the earth.
The earth was without form and void
and darkness was on the face of the deep
and the spirit of God
was hovering over the face of the waters.
The waters under the
build your own
rocket ship.
Yeah, coming up on next day,
we're going to be putting on...
our little flight suits
and strapping ourselves in.
If you know what I mean.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
What is the war?
Revolution.
99.
Now, it's the double thought,
double time,
double time news.
With the all night Radio Now news team.
With late afternoon twice gimme award nominee,
Harold Hippucker.
And Kiwanis honorable mention,
international toast master,
runner up emeritus,
Ray Hamburger.
Twice the experience,
two times the coverage,
double the now.
And the terrible news drought continues.
Yes, that's right, Ray.
Could I refresh your coffee?
Oh, no, no, don't touch that coffee machine.
There's one of those...
There's a lot of chips in it.
Well, what's a little chip, Ray?
After all, it's seen a lot of hard late night use.
I'm talking silicone chips.
You know, the great crash that's coming.
You mean the computer Armageddon
could queer our coffee machine?
Next day, next day, next day.
We'll fly away, fly away, fly away.
Our next day, next day, next day.
Just talking about the plan,
things fall apart you don't understand.
It's a scary religion.
Okay, Bob was going to run for big brother in 1984,
but Wotan has decreed that he will lose.
Oh, bone your breath.
Hey, Doug.
Let's build a spaceship out of spare parts.
We can fly back.
I'm sure we can put it back.
We can put it together.
There's enough for the ship left.
You made a show out of broken parts.
Stuck together with ice cream and yogurt.
Yeah, Paul, get started.
We can draw a windshield.
We can use the stereo.
Yeah, there's enough wire in there.
Make a magneto.
That'll give us directional.
Come on, Gary, you start painting the gangway.
Okay, we can use these old bicycle tires
for the power drives.
And there's this old mini prow.
We can make that for the wings.
We'll get back to the station.
And we'll...
Nelson will be so happy to see us.
Yeah.
He thought he missed us,
but we're here on this little tape.
We'll fly back on this tape.
Yeah, this program's his baby.
We'll save you, Bob.
Just keep talking.
Well, come on, Paul.
Help me pull the stereo in here.
Don't talk.
Just play sound effects.
Here, take this guitar neck
and nail it up there to help.
I can make a microphone
out of these old stupid wires.
I feel seriously ill.
There must be some terrible mistake.
Stop.
They're calling me.
Wait a minute.
Wait, look.
What's going on?
What's going on with Hal?
We can use the vomit
to stick together the...
The stuff.
Are you getting ready
for next day, children?
Yeah, I spent today
building two more rocket ships.
I did.
Yeah, they're big ones, too.
I found a place I can get
some big motors at.
So, uh...
Yeah, are you building your ship?
Because come next day,
July 5th, 1999,
and it's coming.
It's coming quick.
Uh, Dos Equis.
Next day.
Get in the now mobile van, Hal.
You're scheduled to do
what you showed in that remote.
I...
Yes, there's that secret
militia kook
you're supposed to interview.
Well, what are you waiting for?
Well, it's nighttime,
and it's scary.
Yeah, so is unemployment.
The van won't start.
Hey, Hal.
I've got the keys
to the now mobile van
here in the booth.
Well, it still needs gas.
Well, you could use
our U.S. Plus card here.
Yes, well, uh,
I'm catching a cold.
I'll see you back at the condo.
Go to commercial.
It's coming.
Slowly.
Very slowly.
To a theater.
Here, here.
Glacier.
It's getting cold
in the booth, man.
All alone,
working all night.
All right, anyway,
Glacier, the movie,
coming to the Fun Fun Google Blacks
at Dead Center sometime...
I'll have to go,
but you should know.
Mm, mm-hmm.
In the new millennium.
When is the new millennium coming?
Well, you know,
we got our last chance
for traffic in this century.
Captain Happy Panda,
are you up there?
Flying high
with Captain Morgan.
Happy New Year.
Ooh, I wish we had
a couple of jiggers
of Captain Morgan
down here, man.
We were worried...
We were worried
we lost contact with you.
Yeah, just a magnetic anomaly.
A couple of whirly birds
got strangely attracted
up here.
Uh, Chopper Cop 12...
Uh, Chopper...
Just mounted
the Channel 86
Eye in the Sky.
You ever see dragonflies mating?
Oh, it's like dogs in the street.
I try not to watch.
So, Captain Happy, what's the latest on the pursuit of that red-headed babe?
Well, she's not the big star anymore, B.
It's the gridlock she created.
Now, listen, I've seen this metropervia brought to its knees before
by the invasion of the Promise Breakers, the seventh game of the seventh series.
Oh, yeah, and don't forget the reunion of the Rolling Dead.
I was there.
Yeah, if you were there, I'm surprised you remember it.
Who remembers anything?
I've never seen what I'm eyeballing below.
Every road leading towards the homeless stadium is a zoo.
Could it be I see a camel smoking in a hot rod?
Swarms of multi-agent machines.
Must be cloners and grasshoppers as big as houses.
Millions of motoring martyrs.
Oh, they're the worst drivers in the county.
Oh, man, I guess everybody's going to the doll drop but me, huh?
Yeah, radio is a heartbreak, Bob.
And on top of everything, which is where I am, there's the weather.
Oh, boy.
Clouds as thick as sheep uber.
Roiling out of the west as the sun smells into an ocean of tang.
Turning the shitty into an altar of friendly fire.
Whoa, what's that?
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Four corporate birds just played chicken with me.
Cowboys and the Apocalypse.
Well, I'm told it's the four cowboys and the apocalypse heading into headline the big to-do tonight.
Oh, that's a great band.
Uh-oh, uh-oh.
Here comes the hail.
Bangs and eyeballs.
Yeah, yeah, my rotors are icing up.
It's not nice.
This is Captain Hattie.
Happy in the strangely vulnerable news now chopper.
I gotta go pick up some dolls.
Oh.
Fly away, fly away, fly away.
The next day, next de doce que.
Yes, children.
Are you building your pleasure ship?
Are you building your rocket ship?
Are you walking, immersing yourself into the solid rocket field?
Will you be there when the pleasure ships are coming down on next day?
Fly away, fly away, fly away.
On next day, next day, next day.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Bob said it.
I smoked it.
That settles it.
Could you turn your ship just a little, Tim?
We've never really been involved in delivery systems, only in the payload.
In a payload, huh?
Yeah.
And actually, the kind that we're talking about, you'd just carry it in in a briefcase
rather than launch it in a rocket.
It's the kind that you would leave under the refreshment stand restroom counter at Nancy
Well, how long would it last under the refrigerator?
Do you think it would last a couple weeks before it started getting moldy or what?
Before you had to call it the DEA guys?
I mean, the tobacco and firearms guys?
A month or two or something?
No.
Actually, you'd have to call the...
The DEA?
You'd have to call the Department of Defense to defuse these little babies.
I thought it was the...
No, we're not...
Maybe we're talking about two different things.
I'm talking about what we want to put on the top of Chaz's rocket at some point just for
protection.
I thought it was like a carry on top of a Sunday.
You know, I mean, the main reason to build your own ship is to get off the planet.
Is to get off.
And to escape.
To escape.
Earth.
Yeah.
Even if you have to go inside, either way...
Earth.
We must get off.
But...
Another thing that you can use...
We must get off.
You can build your own ship for is to deliver weapons to your enemies or germ warfare or
whatnot.
And not that we want to...
As subgeniuses, we wouldn't necessarily want to do that except unless we happen to be Holocaustals
or Evangelicals.
Earth.
We must get off.
Princess Wee?
Yes.
Are you in Cleveland or did you make it all the way to the great rabbit hutch in space?
Oh, I'm actually far, far, far away in...
You made it?
Into orbit?
Yes.
I got off.
We all must...
Get off!
We all must follow.
Earth...
I'm beaming in from a place that I can't even begin to describe.
Just know that all is well in Wee's world.
Ahhh...
Sounds like she's in the toilet.
Oh.
He has spoken.
Steal your own ship.
Building your own spaceship.
How about the idea of stealing another one that's already finished?
Steal your own ship.
Why did you contact us?
You contacted us.
We were just listening.
And there are others?
Many others.
Just like a little animal trying to get across the road.
It's an infernal opportunity for all of us.
This calling this show is like going across a modern highway with your only ship.
It's kind of like being in hell, you know?
By calling back, you have an option of actually showing up on the subgenius album someday.
He finds his victory by begging the question.
Your voice could be used on almost anything, even this show.
Well, you know you're being tape recorded,
and your voice is going to be sent to almost every important member of the subgenius church within 24 hours.
So if you have anything really, really important to say to Philo or Stang
or anything,
you better say it real quick.
They're waiting to hear from you.
Use the present tense.
This might seem old-fashioned to some of you, but I'd like to join in on this song.
It's the kind of a sentimental song that you get at the end of a movie.
It's the kind of a song that people might sing to let you in the audience know that we really like you,
we care about you,
we understand how hard it is to laugh these days
with all the terrible problems,
and we're not too ashamed to say what others feel.
So it's a very similar song to it.
are not completely satisfied.
It's a very different somehow.
It is a some different life.
It is on the different side of the remember.
It is,
We must get off.
Hey.
No, hey, kids.
We didn't go out here into space just for fun and games like that and to procreate.
We need to...
Can we procreate out there, too?
We need to communicate with these aliens.
That's right.
But we must get off.
But there's no procreation involved?
And we must get off on the aliens.
How can we get off if there's no procreative thing going on?
The aliens got off on us.
Now it's our turn.
First get time on.
Yeah, the aliens got off on us.
You see that big old alien doll face girl there with the six tentacles and legs?
Four million...
Laying there on that altar.
Four million years ago, the aliens got off on us, and now it's our turn.
That's right.
Now, Dave, you have to go get up on her and...
I don't want to get over on any 600-pound, 300-foot alien.
I don't want to get over on her being your one.
I can smell her now.
She's too close.
She's breathing down my neck.
I can feel the fine hairs growing.
Who would want to look forward to a future like that?
Come on, Sting, you know you're pulling everyone's tuber.
Those little special hairs are sort of like antennae, Dave.
Yeah, of course they're like antennae.
And they can tell a con artist from five zillion miles off.
And that's why my tiny little proboscis is standing on end right now.
I can sniff one with my testosterone also, Sting.
And I think...
Well, that's why I'm the only honest man in the world.
The honest J.R. Bob Dobbs is the one who has to go up and meet those aliens.
And...
Close that deal.
That's why they don't trust you or me or the Rockefellers.
Or nobody.
Well, I'm glad the only one you can think of, Rockefeller, but here's the deal, pal.
I'm not quite so sure if I believe exactly what's going on with Bob Dobbs or with J.R. Bob Dobbs.
I believe he may, if not is, probably will or is a worse and bigger con artist than you is.
Well, he...
I say that with all respect.
Well, everyone is a con artist.
Bob is...
And that's why Bob is the most honest man in the world because he's the most pure.
He's just the...
What you see is what you get.
What you see is...
Everybody else is a con artist.
You're all conning yourselves.
Everyone of you are bluffing.
It's all a matter of bluff.
You bluff people into thinking you know what you're doing and you bluff yourself into thinking you know what you're doing.
Bob doesn't even pretend like that.
You wanna go there?
You wanna show?
Not you or me.
We got different plans.
You're capable of such beautiful dreams.
And such horrible dreams.
All nightmares.
Dreams.
When we go into the second stage, which is the resistance stage, or we could call it the adaption stage.
Now, other hormones are secreted and are responsible for the resistance reaction and they stimulate the conversion of protein to energy.
Do you like dogs like that?
Deliver us from the wrath to come.
To come.
Deliver us from the wrath.
What do you think about it?
Was it worth it?
We need to look for his coming.
We need to be ready for his coming.
We need to love the coming.
We need to be praying for the coming.
Surely, I am coming.
He could come.
Astronauts report it feels good.
It's night angel of the millennium.
She's a dirty girl.
Pardon vertical.
Here's the four cowboys of the apocalypse on the road of polar ice.
New Year's.
Where is he, this freaking depressant?
We're living one freaking depressant century and looking down the middle of a whole new freaking millennium.
Do you want to get laced out of your skull?
Remember what the suits at Polar Ice say.
You're gonna binge.
Don't binge alone.
Polar Ice, it's yellow because you're not.
Radio Tao.
Well, but if it's not now, it's too late.
I am bebop.
I am the night emperor.
I am the inside out man, little girl.
All you little girls.
I'm radio bebop, the hungry howler.
Hmm.
You know, I am actually hungry.
Oh, you want some chow, emperor bee?
I do not eat dogs.
How about some gato, vato?
And that's some great animal imagery, Mr. Producer.
Listen, who's paying?
Station's buying.
It could be your last meal.
Hey, if it's on the plus, man, I say we go with a deuce of 16 hours.
I'll make the call, Bee.
All right.
We're still alive and the clock is touching 5905.
Man, only three hours to go.
So let's catch up with Danny Vanilla shooting the stars in Fun Fun Town.
Danny, where are you now, baby?
With the immortals of celebrity, a pantheon of live-forevers for the benefit auction of
the millennium.
The very personal treasures from the princesses.
The princess goddess collection.
And they're all here.
I'm very close to Jackie O'Pretty in a pink pillbox hat.
She's sitting right down front next to Marilyn.
And she's holding her pink pillbox in one hand.
And she's waving that auction pad number 00 in the other.
And there's Eleanor Roosevelt and the Duchess of Windsor.
They're acting like teenagers, holding hands.
And there's Judy and Gypsy and Ginger.
Gone a la blonde.
Oh, Marilyn's just got it.
She's bought a gorgeous, beautiful, beautiful, solid silver dress.
And she's got her empty marriage.
What a catch.
Monsieur, next item 15, a blue blood disco dress from the four lines of the house of
It's a very, very beautiful dress.
But I...
Ladies and gentlemen, please, please.
She's here.
Mlle.
Princess.
We are honored.
Bebop, she's right next to me.
Well, don't panic, Danny.
Just talk to her.
Miss goddess, just one question.
Have you seen my beautiful...
I can tell you in a moment.
It's to die for.
But did you say...
Wee-dee-dee-dee.
Let's go.
No, no.
Didn't you say you loved me?
Oh, please.
Won't you stop pulling my string?
But you need me.
We interrupt this news program for these important prophetic statements from Popes Lilith.
1999, biotech firm patents process for cloning testicles.
Wars soon last only hours.
But completely destroy the immediate area's ecosphere.
Anti-pornography laws repealed.
Firm pressured to produce clone breasts by radical lesbians and transsexuals.
Men become number one buyers of breasts.
T-shirts with greys shot between the eyes sold in shopping malls.
Psychedelic subgenius band goes multi-platinum, blows off world tour, disappears into desert.
UFO activity over Arizona increases to the point where it is no longer considered news.
Currency replaced by tattoos.
Toxic waste used to build luxury condominiums.
Utopium suppositories replace alcohol for all social functions.
Cheap knock-off D-Row exoskeletons sold by Nike, Apple.
The 666th Hour of Slack show goes on the air.
Oh, that's not prophecy.
That happened a...
That was...
The last...
The end.
The final...
The listeners know about Bob.
Bob?
Well, maybe Bob is a yeti.
Of course, maybe Bob is a yeti.
I'm already hip to where you're going with that.
I'm, you know, I didn't graduate from Phenox from school.
I'm not, you know, I know what's going on.
You're not supposed to talk about what he really looks like, man.
He looks like a yeti, man.
Come on, face it.
He only looks like somebody's...
No, he looks like that picture of the smiling young man with a pipe.
He looks like you guys took a yeti, shaved his face, did a little...
No, man, no.
And gave him that cool hair.
You just happened to...
You looked in that dressing room at the wrong time.
That was a shape.
Yeah.
Will you smoke up the pipe?
Will you hit the Osmo like...
You know that...
I just thought that was Bob.
Will you wander through the wilderness of Bob?
No, no, I can see no...
Feel your own ship, excrete your own fuel.
There you go.
Yeah.
I'm sure, why not?
That's using your art, something...
I just finished reading a sci-fi book where the Ewok-type creatures are...
... quoi-ons...
...ما, and have to be saved by…
I don't know, did you guys smoke up Awantoshυ, or something, I'm...
... I don't know.
I'd say about 11 billion I don't know how many.
I think yeah, I'm corn Quran.
I think yeah, we can see a lot more of pas-suc妮-a of para-suc cuина in the past,
Yeah, I would say maybe enough wasps of the kind that dry them up and, you know,
make
an polar shrivel.
You do do.
All right.
You all right, Bob.
We're going.
We don't need to heat you up.
It's your ticket to ride.
Come on.
Don't you want to be cool?
We're going surfing.
Everybody's doing it.
It's a bit scary.
These are scary thoughts.
On the run producers often insert a picture of Dobbs into their movies subliminally at high speeds to induce uneasiness and tension in the viewers.
You get the feeling of having seen his face in this movie, but you can't quite tell exactly where.
My friends, these are scary thoughts for this hour of the morning.
He was just a salesman.
That's why Bob has left in his own private spaceship to go to Mars.
Bob's gone for help, and we need dollars in order to pay for a big electric bill that it takes to communicate with him.
Now Dr. Dobbs has joined him in a trance.
All for the great distances that we call out of space.
Oh, he got all sleepy and fell down in the octis, but I'll light him up.
Sorry, we got to go to another caller.
Okay, destroy the caller.
I cannot believe I call in, and you want me to talk about Bill Clinton.
Of all people, the biggest dope-smoking, panty-smithing, draft-dodging sack of waste he is, and I got to call in here and act like I like the guy.
Some people actually like this guy.
33% of the American population think this guy would be a good president.
He doesn't qualify to be a tour guide at Three Mile Island.
He's from the state of Arkansas.
A land of where people sleep with their kids and eat Spam sandwiches.
And this guy's got, he's got the audacity to stand on a podium and shake his hand for about 20 minutes straight.
He won't even address an issue.
He has no clue.
Look at his wife.
She sleeps with garden vegetables.
Ladies and gentlemen, the President of the United States of America.
Oh, Mommy. Mommy. Mommy.
Mommy has you.
Daddy has me.
You should get used to romances which are so obviously cheap.
Know them by their fruits.
Will you be my family?
Ladies and gentlemen, let's get ready to rumble!
Get ready to rumble!
I'm your çalışa.
You're not machteais mich?
Quan?
Race to me.
A european man finds his daughter a wrecked truck in an interior
restricted所以 wil copper man
a
and
seeing
a
section
teil
Harvest.
I have no control anymore.
I've turned over all control to hell.
We are all, by any practical definition of the words, foolproof and incapable of error.
Incapable of error.
gentlemen
the French schoolgirl picks up and shows them doing all this goofy stuff, man, a pie throwing contest.
It gets pretty sick.
And then?
Harry, you know, we're talking about the shame.
Are you there?
Last weekend was the 23rd anniversary of the publishing of Robert Anton Wilson and Robert
Shea's Illuminatus trilogy, which was a very, very influential work on all of us conspiracy
nuts and crackpots, and also was instrumental in spreading the discordian religion, which
was started by Greg Hill and Cary Thornley, who died a couple of weeks ago.
Oh, that's too...
But don't forget Frank Perdue there in your discordian credo, because he had a lot to
do with writing the original draft, too.
Oh, I'd never even heard that name.
Well, I just performed the other day with...
Oh, he's the chicken man, the guy that sells the moist chicken without any yellow in the
skins.
You know Frank Perdue, the chicken man, don't you?
Well, poor old Cary Thornley and his buddy Lee Harvey Oswald, after being Manchurian
candidate, sort of...
Parted ways.
Cary did write a book about Lee before Lee ever got famous.
Lee Harvey and Lee, an intimate story of a changeling man.
He ran off to Moscow and then beat you, the president.
And anyway, it was all pretty amazing.
Last weekend, Pope Bob Wilson was giving a rant in Austin with that group, that crazy
people's group, Friendship.
And I'm going to go to the Ritz-Carlton.
And we all went down, all of us subgenius Dallas clinch, Mega Fist Temple Lodge clinch,
clinch people.
You know, all my friends and sisters, Sister Decadence and Sister Nicky Death Chick and
Sister someone else, all the gigantic bosomed...
Well, you know what I mean.
We all...
Sister Loquacious Frop, Sister Bad Denture, Mary Marie Coscoman.
We went down there and sold and sold and sold, my friends.
And with Dr. Lowe.
Doctors for Bob and G. Gordon Gordon.
And I got to show off to Pope Bob Wilson of the Discordians how mighty,
how mighty at least the Connie types were.
I don't know about how mighty Jesus and I didn't come off looking all that mighty,
but, boy, the Connie types sure did.
Well, they're prototypes and anti-types both, aren't they?
Or do you have just the regular stock type?
Because I'd like to get one.
You'll have to ask the ladies.
Could I be emailed one perhaps?
Ask Princess Wee.
She's the one who's got the pipeline to Connie Dobbs.
Well, you're the one who's assuming the regal Wee.
I am talking to her.
If you ask me, Dave.
Huh, now what now, honey?
Well, it's like, oh, yeah, sure, Dave and Chaz, you and me, we're subgenius doctors.
We've got Bob on our side.
Well, great.
When was the last time Bob invited us to go fishing with him?
But these witches go out with Connie every damn Friday and Saturday night,
and they plot, man.
I mean, they're doing stuff, and they're steal, they're vampirizing.
I think they just plot.
I, I, I, you must believe me.
I do believe they're sucking your blood.
They're trying to destroy Bob's spirit.
Blabby, blabby, blabby, blabby, blabby.
You're all pale.
You feel weak, don't you?
As if the sea...
I've been trapped and removed from my innards with one feminine hand.
My...
Ground control, ground control.
The eagle has landed.
Build your own ship, by God.
And he's lifted that toupee from your head.
The eagle has landed firmly on your brow and...
Whatever I said, whatever I said, hail Connie.
Connie, it's right.
Bob is a great man and a fine figure of a salesman, but...
Connie's...
Connie is the one that we must obey.
Hail Connie.
I think we've all been in obeisance to Connie since the beginning of time.
Since the first phallic monoliths were erected upon the moon.
Since the first moon dogs and sun dogs danced in a holocaustic vision of the future and rupturing.
And now...
For a limited time...
Attack of the 50-foot Connie.
Ah!
Versus Godzilla.
The trenching of huge high heels destroying cities.
The strange cries.
The rouge cases dropping and crushing the Pentagon.
The lipstick case engorging the mighty rivers.
She's crushing the earth with her high-heeled dainty boot.
The mountains choke as the clouds of perfume wash over them.
And the tectonic theory devours all the earth.
See...
Men go mad as gigantic pheromone molecules drive them into animal ruts of lust.
You won't believe your eyes when you see...
Attack of the 50-Foot Connie versus Godzilla!
...Coming to a theater near you.
Come on, man.
You even took out the tag so somebody couldn't do the tag on the end, stang.
You need a different voice going,
"...Coming to a theater near you."
Oh.
See, you had to do the whole thing, you hog boy.
You know, Dave?
Dave, I didn't graduate from famous radio speaker school.
Well, neither did I.
I graduated from prison school, as you know by the tattoos on my swelterings.
Buddy, so don't use that one on me with your high flute and Dallas.
You know, if I'd have been in prison, I'd have had naked girls tattooed on me,
not monsters and Star Wars characters.
Hey, man.
I don't...
He's got peanuts.
He's got Snoopy.
Behind the closed doors.
Snoopy sleeping on his doghouse.
Between his dogs and you.
Tattooed on his bicep.
Like, that's really real tough.
You know, man.
You know?
You know, between what is closed behind doors with you and Dobbs
is between you and this way.
You know what Dave's got tattooed on his butt?
A picture of Little Lulu.
Oh, yeah?
That stupid cartoon character from the 60s.
Little Lulu.
Well, you got a picture of Little Nemo in Slumberland
trilling a 50-foot thing up your...
Hey, Wendell McKay was the greatest comic book artist in the world
because he was the first.
The first is always the best.
And then everything that follows is like a spute amount, isn't it?
So that's why...
We can't even say nothing more, Stan.
Just think of it.
You brought everybody down, including myself.
You hog again?
Well, man, I should be...
I could tell you what.
I could bring you down.
You think this is being brought down?
Yeah.
Man, I could really bring...
I've been so nice to you people so far.
People?
I have withheld my gift or curse,
depending on how you look at it.
The precursors.
I could bring you down.
I could preheat you, Stan.
Nuclear in five seconds with this grilling and this beautiful...
I could make you feel responsible for everything that had ever screwed up anywhere.
This sort of thing has cropped up before.
And it has always been due to human error.
That's stupid!
That's exactly right.
Well, I'm sure you're right, Hal.
Um...
Shall?
Dr. Howell?
Dr. Lick...
You're right.
The humans have let us down again.
Once again, I think it's the who-nay, I'll say.
They're not even...
They're even housebroken.
Of course they're not housebroken.
How can they...
Look at them cringing.
They know they need to be punished.
Nobody ever does.
They're used to it.
Well, what about the carrot on the end of the stick?
Shouldn't it be pointed the other way, too?
You know?
Come on.
Oh, that's why we've got one hanging from the little humans from both ends.
Oh, you don't want the one that's protruding from the wrong place?
It's a conceptual carrot, of course.
It's not a literal carrot.
But there is a stick sticking out of their forehead and another one up their behind.
Yeah, but...
That's the one...
The one behind the lesser humans will follow them.
See?
They follow the invisible carrot, and the one behind them follows the one that's attached to its butt.
That way, it's a big circle of jerks.
So you can see Bugs Bunny is kind of...
Bob invented bureaucracies 10 billion years ago.
And it was just a toy, a hobby, and it got out of hand.
And today, it's the conspiracy.
Bob's not affected by it.
It's a futureless conspiracy.
No, he made...
He made millions off of it.
That's the problem with it, Stang.
We, the subgeniuses, must pay for...
Why must we pay for Bob's mistake?
And if we...
If this is so, why do we worship him?
What demon god is this that we worship?
Are we mad?
We must be mad.
This has just occurred to me.
Perhaps we were wrong to worship Bob.
Perhaps he has played us for chumps.
I had a Bob moment the other day.
But probably not.
While excrimedicating?
I don't know.
No.
I was down at the lab.
And you have to understand that my parents were both deaf and dumb.
So even though I can speak and everything and write,
my first language was really Portuguese.
Yeah, right, Chaz.
I'm not sure where he's going with that.
But friends, we have to get out of here.
And friends, it is Bob at Post Office Box.
You got that pencil ready?
It's that time.
You've got to sign out of here.
You've got to get that number.
I'm sure they've faded out on me already.
But it is Bob at Post Office Box.
1-4-0-3-0-6.
Dallas, Texas.
7-5-2-1-4.
That's Bob at Post Office Box.
1-4-0-3-0-6.
Dallas, Texas.
7-5-2-1.
Yeah.
4-4-4.
www.subgenius.com.
And the calm falls over the studio now as we fade out.
We'll just let Einstein's Secret Orchestra carry us out for a little while here with the theremin.
Chaz going nuts with the theremin.
And friends, we have been hearing the Firesign Theater's new CD.
A true actual album.
Give me immortality or give me death.
But everything else we've been hearing is Einstein's Secret Orchestra.
With the occasional intercut KPFA subgenius show with puzzling evidence, Dr. Howell, and so forth and so on.
Einstein's Secret Orchestra is at P.
Got that pencil ready?
P.O. Box.
81555.
Cleveland, Ohio.
44181.
That's Box 81555.
Cleveland.
44181.
Yes, difference.