This is real, isn't it?
I think so.
Real?
I'll check the tape later.
What?
Oh, there we go.
6-6-4, we're checking the park.
Alright, we're checking the park now.
Oh, really?
Is this a real police scanner or something? What is that?
Cool.
I think it's a show.
I'll check the tape later, that one isn't really sure.
...more, she's shot.
Oh, okay.
...from YouTube here on 11-3-6.
Okay.
Our communication system is not functioning properly.
Our transmissions are being blocked.
Oh!
Right.
Right!
...more colors, more grams.
Like a runaway hologram or something.
It's very, very strange.
Are you afraid to die?
Uh-oh.
If you're smart, you'll make opportunities.
Hi, baby.
Some of this, maybe?
...you.
...in this world.
I hope that bus comes soon.
...this is all happening.
What?
What, you mean the show is-
No.
There are people listening, though.
I mean, it's really happening, it's not just telepathic.
Can you look carefully at him?
What, if I- okay, I'm looking and what do I-
What?
You're not here?
You're strapped into an implant chair, and I'm monitoring you from the psychotropic console.
I am?
Oh.
I thought I was doing-
What you're experiencing is a free-form delusion based on our memory tapes.
Now what the hell is that-
You may call.
Welcome to the subgenius radio ministry Hour of Slang.
Sponsored by the Church of the Subgenius.
A haven for the mongrel scum of the earth.
An engorged parasite on the underbelly of the West.
Ten thousand people dead.
Let's talk about love.
Love.
Love everything.
Love the creepy crawlies.
The spiders.
Love all of it.
You are beautiful.
You're beautiful.
than any dream of beauty I've ever known.
What is your point, Mr. Spock?
I love you.
Love!
Jake!
Love! Love!
There's one dark place that we have to be very careful in.
Do you know where that is?
Possible they might have hit the wrong entry point.
Yes.
If you'll excuse the intrusion, Captain.
Help!
Huh?
Calling the engineers.
They must rewire the transmitters and see that those reactors are giving enough voltage.
Yes, sir.
Wait!
First start the low frequency system.
Yes, sir.
Yeah!
B-b-b-bye-ya, dog!
Bad Joke Wednesday.
Not on my radio station.
We'll just go back to the music of Unibrow.
Making the world a better place.
Safe for your brain.
And mine.
Well, we suspect it's a domestic problem.
All right, all right.
Now let's be serious here.
I have arranged all this just to have a moment alone with you.
I prefer a naked microphone.
Come on.
Up to bed.
Here you are!
Here's the phone.
I'll cut you in half.
Forget about it for now.
Fuck!
Yes, sir.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Yeah!
No, don't forget that.
What are you hiding anything from me.
What?
He didn't get through it again.
I'll know when to say that before you take it back to me.
To join this man and these women and their Coca-Cola cans and brass, body parts, car keys and so forth in a temporary but no less virtuous bondage.
Yes, a bondage. A bondage of life.
Holy matrimony. For better or for worse, but not for love.
Praise God.
Do you feel the spirit?
Everybody say praise God.
Praise God.
Okay, now put your hands on each other.
It's mostly, okay, ah, yes.
This is it.
This is a bond of some holy bloodlock.
So no matter what physical position these beloved may take in the next 24 hours, their moral standing will remain upright.
If there were any jealous losers here who feel these men, women, car keys, brass, body parts and so forth should not be joined temporarily,
even for me.
I'm here 24 hours.
Just hold your peace because we don't want to hear about it.
Okay, now hold your hands.
Let your hands on each other.
Hold real tight.
Before we proceed, has the preacher been paid?
You're the preacher.
Oh, yeah, more or less.
More or less, yes.
Paid in slack.
Do you insert name here?
Insert name here.
Take, okay, let's start with the, we'll do the.
Feminine.
The con.
Vex.
The male.
Oh, the yang.
We'll start with the.
The church yang.
The be-dick-ed.
The be-dick-ed or whatever.
Dominant.
Parcel.
Not necessarily.
Yeah.
Dominant.
A prod.
Yeah, well, we'll start with one side.
It could be the concave ones, too.
It's whoever is the main delivery.
Okay.
Dominant.
To, yeah, do you take these things to be your lawful wedded, quote, wife, unquote.
Not necessarily female.
In short duration, subgenius matrimony, to have and behold, in fact, to do just about anything.
Anything you want and hold.
As long as he or she agrees to it, or it agrees to it.
For richer or poorer, in sickness and kinkiness, through any hardship or disaster that may befall it or her or them or whatever in the next 24 hours.
For whatever sick and twisted but no less blessed reasons for the next 24 hours.
Say, I.
I.
Do.
What's wrong?
I don't win.
I trust you.
Okay, now get out your rings.
You do have your rings, don't you?
I got the rings on already.
Oh, she's got her ring.
Well, if you don't have a ring, form your handy sacred temple of, oh, there's a silly putty ring.
Low in the dark silly putty ring.
Or your handy temple of Devo.
As we call it.
And we take this ring as a symbol of the holy estate of marriage and of the shackles, the girdable handcuffs of wedlock, as well as of the pole going deep into the hole.
Repeatedly.
Now, install the ring.
Wahoo!
Yes, baby!
All right.
were you stupid?
We should buy a new guest control Automated aquariums in mad размерsa.
I'minking, why didn't we just sayIC
through
Each year, Chun Sirius has a wide array of
這
What's this?
the Starwood
Festival. This particular
Starwood included
as guests Dr.
Timothy Leary, our old notorious
friend, as well
as Illuminatus
author Bob Shea
and really most spectacularly
of all
Jeff McBride
aka Magnus the Magician
whose magic show is so
cosmic
it really makes me wish this was
a cable TV show just for a week
so I could share that footage with you
and there's always lots of bands
and there's the endless zen
drumming and the dancing
around the bonfire and all the
but I don't want to sound
again like I'm bragging to all of you
stuck in your mundane world
about what a swinging time I had
so
but I did. In the background
I should mention
the background music is by
Zug's Rift and Joe Newman
I told you about what was
coming up on MTV
DK Jones and Huge Voodoo
and their poet friends were going to be on
MTV
Unplugged and they were
and this is
Maggie Estep
with Huge Voodoo
Actually friends I forgot there's a little instrumental piece here at the beginning
and it reminds me that
a Huge Voodoo in this case was joined for their MTV performance by
Brother Cleve Donut Duncan
yes or ah yes
that mighty, mighty gospel keyboard player
heard here in the background
Praise God
Music playing
Applause
Patounts
The stupid jerk I'm obsessed with
stands so close to me
that I can feel his breath on my neck
and smell the way he would smell
if we slept together
because he is the stupid jerk I'm obsessed with
and that is his primary function in life
to be a stupid jerk I can obsess over
and to talk to that dingy bim-bim blonde
as if he really wanted to hear about her
manicures and pedicures
and new age ritualistic enema cures
and truth be known
he probably does want to hear about it
because he is the stupid jerk I'm obsessed with
and he is obsessed with doing anything he can
to lend fuel to my fire
he makes a point of standing
looking over my shoulder
when I'm talking to him
when I'm talking to the guy who adores me
and would bark like a dog
and wave to strangers
if I asked him to bark like a dog
but I wouldn't ask him to bark like a dog
or impersonate any kind of animal at all
because I'm too busy looking at the way
the stupid jerk I'm obsessed with
has pants on that perfectly define his well-shaped ass
to the point where I'm totally frantic
I'm just gonna go home and stick my head in the oven
overdose on it
and not make an aspirin
and sit in the bathtub reading the executioner's song
and being completely confounded by the fact that I can see
the stupid jerk I'm obsessed with's face defining itself
in the peeling plaster of the wall
grinning and winging
and I start to yell
get the hell out of there
you're just a figment of my imagination
just get out of my plaster and pass me the next painful situation please
but he just keeps on grinning and winging
he's the stupid jerk I'm obsessed with
and he's mine in my plaster
and frankly I couldn't be happier
Maggie Estep dear friends
accompanied by huge voodoo
that's DK Jones, Bruce Grant
and in this case
Brother Cleve
Duncan
now
here's the little collector's song
this is last week
Willa Dobbs played a Star Trek edit
was it last week or the week before?
the week before
the amazing Captain's Log
and this is sort of a companion piece to this
to that
this is a song recorded at the Starwood event last week
a song by Reverend Vicki Ganger
unlike any other
this song grew out of a dream that I had
actually it was more like a nightmare for me
a dream of a sexual encounter
with a certain bald headed starship captain
and I'm not sure if that's true
now for some people that may not be a nightmare
there may be some women or men or aliens or things out there
that would find that like you know
an erotic adventure of some sort or another
I prefer my heads full as it were
but anyway I woke up in a cold sweat
and my muse decided to play tricks on me
because the song came through in kind of a
a grunge heavy metal punk sort of version
which I thought was highly amusing since I play acoustic guitar
so just kind of think of C.L. Grunge or something
it's called I Want to Be Jean-Luc's Love Slave
I don't know, give it a whirl
for real, and I said Let's Play
fond of The videos on my channel
First I watched at that far pretty
Once I wanted to be aузing
Well, what did I do?
Take a look and see You're the only one for me
Oh, I want to be Jean-Luc's love slave I want to be Jean-Luc's love slave
Meet me in your ready room at one I'll show you how Warp 17 is done
I want to be your love slave I want to be your love slave, baby
I want to be your love slave I want to be Picard's pet
When I see your hair gleam It just makes me want to scream
Is it real or just a dream? It's anti-matter
You're the only one I see Not that there's much choice for me
Cause George is blind And William Breit is getting fatter
I hear my captain's call All the writers on the wall
Oh, I want to be Jean-Luc's love slave I want to be Jean-Luc's love slave
Meet me on the holiday지가 three
The Captain of the Enterprise and me
Wanna be your love slave Wanna be your love slave
epic
Hello there Oh I want you to hear it
Want to be Jean-Luc's love slave
I want to be Your love slave
I want to be a peacock
Make it so number one
And gay
Now Warfie isn't much for chat
So I can really lay you flat
I think I've had enough of that
It's all so hazy
Well, David's got the proper heart
He's programmed in the pleasing art
Another man without a heart
You must be crazy
Oh, what more can I say?
I read you night and day
Won't you come and play?
Oh, I want to be
John Luke's slave
I want to be
In the shot of bed
But
And when we Gus
His locker
Blind
Won't you tell me
It's me baby.
Are they all my
Oh, I want to be
Als
All right?
Quicker
Start
Oh, I want to see
me all.
Yes, dear friends, Vicki Ganger and her good friend sister Melodious Chalk.
Enjoy the rest of the concert.
Coming up, a series of preachings from the Starwood Subgenius Devival.
I can't exactly remember the order I edited these in, but I believe we have Dr. Legume at first,
and then Sister Mary Squared, au contraire, Reverend Velveteen Sly, and...
Is this a miracle? What kind of a miracle? Is this a parable? What's the point?
Is this a letter? What's the big idea? What's he trying to communicate?
My God's dead!
Sorry about yours!
Ashes to ashes, dust to dust, it is done!
Amen and amen!
Praise Bob! Hell, Connie!
Uh-oh, friends, evil Dr. Legume is back!
The scariest!
What's the subgenius at the Starwood?
I'm here to talk about creationism.
Now, first of all, we have to take on a few of these Christian assumptions.
The first one is that God created the universe.
The second is that God created life on Earth in His image.
And the third is that dinosaurs were around long before us.
So the only thing I could come to the conclusion of is that...
Perhaps God is a big dinosaur.
Maybe he's the King of the Lizards and the Lord of Lords!
It says right in the Bible, in Job,
I am a brother to dragons.
Well...
What happened to the dinosaurs?
Was it this God Rex, this giant God-lizard up in the sky?
Yes!
Come on!
Say what?
all the other dinosaurs and he created man.
Men were created to serve him in his master plan.
When the time came, the god Rex commanded Noah to build an ark.
Take his children and all the animals that were on there.
Everybody but the dinosaurs. Yeah, everybody but the dinosaurs.
They didn't get to go. They just swam. They swam up to the North Pole.
And they all got frozen in the ice.
Now, man also survived this time.
And uh,
since there weren't any big lizards around to eat them no more, they started getting kind of
kind of uppy.
They forgot about the lizards. They declared themselves masters of the earth.
Replacing the god Rex with human gods.
The god Rex was both annoyed and amused at this stuff.
And bestowed upon man the secrets of the atom.
And the means to create pollution. The combination of these
two forces caused global warming. Now there will
come a time when the greenhouse effect will melt down the polar
ice caps. And the dinosaurs shall be
set free from their long sleep.
The radiation, either from the nuclear accidents caused by
the god Rex, or the nuclear winter caused by our
own foolishness, shall cause a change, a mutation
in the dinosaurs. Oh, wait a minute you guys. Hold on
just a second, Dr. Leguien. We have to get out of here in about five minutes. Okay.
Well, I'll just cut the
dinosaurs.
Well, I'll talk a little bit about the conspiracy.
The conspiracy, it poisons our water and it poisons our air.
I mean, ever since I found out what they've been putting in the water,
hell, I can't get enough of it.
But, you know, they poison us with the neurotoxin and the ink in Bibles.
Makes your brain go all stupid. Makes you want to just keep reading the Bible,
reading the Bible, reading the Bible. Every time you read it, you get stupider and stupider
from the neurotoxins. And it dulls your Bob-given powers of crap perception.
You know, when you're born, you have that perception to look for.
You look at crap and see crap.
It's not art. It's not food. You look at it, this is crap.
But the more you read the Bible, the less crap you can see.
And, well, they took over. They're the conspiracy now.
They curse us with hijabs and false prophets.
They imprison us for our use of the sacred herb of the Eucharist.
This is crap. Every single day, the con takes another one of our freedoms away.
What are you going to do about it?
Mutate! Arise, brethren! March proudly into Dobbs Town,
on a highway of golden light, following in the path of the Great Smiling One!
Give me some of that old-time religion! Give me some of them pills!
Open my third nostril wide!
And let all the stench of heaven and earth and hell that's above my psychic senses
help me! I'm a sinner!
I'm hiding behind the first seal!
But I'm not the Antichrist! I'm the anti-Christian!
And all my subgenius brothers and sisters are behind the seal with me!
And I swear to you that the day cometh when we shall rip asunder that seal!
And with Bob by our side, we shall come upon Satan!
And we shall come upon Jesus!
And we shall come upon Buddha!
And Mohammed!
And all others of that ilk!
And lo, they shall leave town by sundown!
Our mighty church!
Praise sundown!
Our mighty church shall be the very knuckles of the stark fist of removal!
And all the false churches shall reap of the ass-whippings that is to come!
Praise Bob!
Don't be caught unaware!
Join our church now!
Salvation only twenty dollars!
Twenty damn dollars!
Get that subgenius membership card!
Get it today!
Don't be caught dead without it!
Praise Bob!
Praise Dr. Le Guillaume!
The savage Dr. Le Guillaume from the savage mind of the country's interior!
The savage!
road Freudius college
сделать
this
frigging
mr
german
と思います
campus
shippment
earth
surff 1992
north
india
I said this is woodstock for nitwits. I mean look at these people. They've got so much
Christian ethic that it's frightening that they deny it so flatly. Kind of like how the
Christians do exactly the same thing when you bring up the dinosaurs. Can I sell you anything?
The latest video perhaps? Club No? Let's just say no. Oh yes, yes. Club No. Yes. Yes.
Force me to buy. Whip me, beat me. Bye boy. Bye boy. Bye boy. Here, take my money please.
See? This is how easy sales can be. Give till it hurts. Take it home.
Bob, son of battle.
Secrets of effective subgenius sales. I don't understand.
Those who know don't say and those who say don't know.
What are you saying?
I don't know.
He carried a machine gun. He kicked in many doors. He hung out in the bars at night with
fishermen and whores. So Jesus, if you're listening, please hear my humble prayer.
Will you talk to your father, that old man in the air? The Christians want to leave here
to share heaven with you. I pray that you will grant their wish. We'd really like that too.
Amen.
Oh, sacred sales, dear friends.
Well, since you're talking about X-Day.
Same with the team Sly here.
Reverend Sly and I have worked all since last year at Starwood
to bring you a product that you are gonna need before X-Day. And we have managed for the one time only to put sex and slack
in a single jar. Yeah, you won't need it afterwards, you'll be lubed up all the time.
But, this is the one and only Sly's Slack Lube, my friends, and this is available at
Starwood over by Creative Realities Tattoo. We even have a tester there for your pleasure.
Something remotely penis-shaped, and it comes in maple, venus vanilla, flowing honey, and cinnamon.
Sly's Slack Lube, the one and only Sly's Slack Lube, my friends.
It's sexy, all natural ingredients, it tastes good, it smells good, and it feels great.
You'll be as a sex god or goddess when you reach for the one and only pure Slack Lube.
It's slippery and won't dry up like most other lubes. It's low fat, no cholesterol, not tested on animals, so far as we know.
Yeah.
I'm leaded.
I'm perfect for all your lubricating needs.
Use Slack Lube and enjoy, really enjoy safer sex. Thank you.
Well, I used to be a sinner, cause I truly did believe that the Virgin married Jesus and me worth the gas thieves.
And I used to give my dough to televangelistic snobs, but then the light had shone upon me and I found J.R. Bob Dobbs.
And now my wallet is empty.
My wallet belongs to Bob.
Yes, my wallet belongs to Bob.
Well, my heart is for my honey and my brain is for my job.
My wallet belongs to Bob.
Well, Bobby goes a frappin' every chance that he can get.
He cannot perform the biggest without even breaking sweat.
So I gave him all my money.
Reverend Stang said it was right.
And for only $20, he did save my soul tonight.
So my wallet belongs to Bob.
Yes, my wallet belongs to Bob.
No more can the conspiracy.
My lowly wages rob.
My wallet belongs to Bob.
So, wha- where's Sister Mary Squared?
Not here!
All I see is Slacko the Clown.
And that's a rather- boy, you look like a little boy.
A pretty little boy.
Well, sting me, stang me, and bend me over and bang me.
No, baby!
I am you!
How you guys doing today, huh?
Whoo!
How are you guys doing today, huh?
All right, friends, I'm here to testify for you today.
I'm here to testify and to tell you who I was before I met the Church of the Subgenius,
because I wasn't always the well-rounded woman that you know today.
Oh, no!
Au contraire!
I was a normal two-boy.
I was a good one, friends.
No!
Yes.
I was pink!
I was so pink because I didn't think that there were other ways of living my life.
I didn't think!
I didn't know!
There was no one to show me the light, so I tried to fit in the circle into the square,
the square into the circle.
Au contraire!
I was twisting myself around and around and around.
I was a circle within a circle.
And it was a pattern that was a bad habit.
Huh!
And I got lots of habits.
You see, I went up on the mountain.
I went up.
I walked up on the mountain on Lookout Mountain, that very same mountain that Martin Luther King went up on,
JFK went up on, that Gandhi and all those cute little bee-dicky deities went up on.
And I looked out, and I saw my vision.
I saw it hanging there, dangling like a carrot to a bunny rabbit, a rabbit to a carrot.
Huh!
And I came back down from the mountain.
I came back down after seeing the way things should have been and could have been and would have been.
Had we all smartened up and started living ourselves, because everybody that goes up there on that mountain dies.
So I came down from the mountain.
You understand what I'm saying, brothers and sisters?
I came down from the mountain, because my demons inside my head, they said,
Oh, Alcatraz, we're not going to do that.
We're going to bring you down.
And friends, I became a member of the Diffie Cult.
Stick myself in the third eye, beat myself into unconsciousness.
I didn't know that.
I didn't know what was up from down and all around.
But as within me, so without.
And I realized I had to name my demons.
I had to get rid of them, because it's time to get rid of our chickens and start to dick it.
Starting and fornicating as if our very lives depended on it.
It does.
I'm not clowning around.
It really does.
I came down from the mountain, and I learned.
I learned that there were things that were not right.
There were things that I was invoking in my life.
I was invoking Bummer Man.
The greatest demon of the Diffie Cult.
Woo!
He's a slippery one.
He'll come into your living room.
He'll smoke all your fop.
He'll drink all your coffee in his little Superman suit.
Oh, yes.
With his little coffee stains and his cigarette holes.
And he'll say, oh, yeah.
I could have been, and I should have been, and I would have been.
But something happened, and I lost control.
And it was a real Bummer Man.
Yeah.
And along with Bummer Man came Ms. Communication.
Woo!
She's a tricky one.
She'll make you think you want one thing when you really want the other.
She'll make you sing one thing when you really want to sing the other.
She'll make you get down on your knees and praise the wrong B. Dicky deity.
A castrated little man hanging on a cross.
Choke my chicken?
No, choke your chicken.
Hey, friends, sexuality was at a loss.
As the choke is to the chicken, so is the veers to the fly trap.
It was tough.
Woo!
Sex hurt had not entered my life.
You mean now that I have entered into the magical community, now that I went up on that
planet.
And I had my vision.
I created all this.
I create my own reality.
And I'm responsible for what I have done and what I have seen.
And now I have to share this with other people?
I came down from the mountain.
And Connie lifted me back up.
Oh, she did.
It was a bumpy ride.
It was up and down.
It was down and up.
I was a driven woman.
And I didn't mind the ride.
It was the jerks that got me.
But I came down from the mountain.
And Connie, she lifted me back up.
And while there may be many crazed and confused things in this world today, there are certain
truths that we can all agree on.
Let me hear you all say yes.
Uh-huh.
That's right.
There is a dark and a light.
Let me hear you say, uh-huh.
Uh-huh.
There's good and the bad.
A wrong and a right.
Uh-huh.
Hail, Connie.
And along with the goddess, I discovered who I truly was.
I discovered who I truly was as a unified self.
Since the Einstein has helped me to realize who I am, I discovered that Betty Page, Mae
West, and Rosie the Riveter all rolled into one.
I'm a woman.
I'm an inquiry for business and their
behavior.
Tantric.
I'm trans, galactic.
Talk to me on about this.
alleviations and alleviations and all kinds of inspirations.
You say that for the bobs, not the dicks.
It's the bobs that we love.
Praise Bob!
He may be dumb, but God, he's cute.
Woo!
Hurt me somebody, my legs are on fire.
Feed me!
Milk me!
Pet me!
Eat me!
Save me!
Sacred cow women arise!
Praise the cows!
Milk the cows!
It is time to stop prohibition and start to bitchin'.
Cause there's a conspiracy, my friends, going out there.
There's a conspiracy.
Oh, yes!
And what is that about Bill Clinton being a liberal, huh?
Okay, sure, he was slick enough to do that.
He was slick enough to get in.
But will he stay hard enough to do the job?
I think not!
It is time to start prohibition and start to bitchin'.
Praise the bitchin'!
Thank you, brothers and sisters.
Praise the blessed bitchin'.
Oh, yes.
Tonight, dear friends,
I'm going to share...
a legend with you.
Or rather, a tape that will become a legend.
A tape of a man who is himself a legend.
And certainly this is a piece,
albeit not a very attractive piece,
of radio history.
And before I play the tape,
I must tell you the story and set the scene.
As you know, tapes of this show,
The Hour of Slack,
are broadcast in...
in some sixteen cities.
Now, about two months ago,
Philadelphia became one of those cities.
But under unusual circumstances.
Of all the Philly subs,
it was dues-paying subgenius Reverend Craig
who secured a time slot for The Hour of Slack on...
well, on the station there.
But it was a three-hour time slot,
so Pastor Craig had to fill two more hours,
besides what we sent him.
This was a bit problematic in the beginning,
in that, let us say,
Pastor Craig was an ambitious,
but not very experienced radio technician
and or public speaker.
That's a diplomatic way of putting it.
In fact, his first several shows terribly alienated
his fellow subgenie-y,
such as Dr. Legume and his rude, rude clench.
And yet,
Pastor Craig's inexperience was exactly what allowed
what you are about to hear to happen.
And now, three weeks ago,
Pastor Craig called up Dr. Legume
and asked him to come be on the show.
Legume couldn't make it,
but he knew someone who could.
Someone so dangerously weird
that even Reverend Legume himself
had been known to flee his presence.
And Dr. Legume,
who is a kind of subgenius who scares other subgeniuses,
kind of like Pope Sternodox,
he's a big muscular guy who fears no death,
and whose a-whore, po-bucker roots
terrify the more e-bookish types.
Well, Legume's friend,
the Sheik,
is even more frightening and crazier.
So when Pastor Craig asked Legume to be on the show,
Legume said he couldn't make it,
but would arrange for the Sheik to come instead.
Now when Legume called the Sheik,
the Sheik was very, very drunk.
And upon being invited to the show that night,
he dutifully downed more Valiums and whiskey.
As soon as he got to the station,
he hurled violently,
and then he got on the mic
and delivered a eulogy
to Gigi Allen,
who had died of a drug overdose that very day.
Now I probably need to explain to most of you
who Gigi Allen was.
Gigi was a punk rocker,
so vile and violent,
that even the Sheik himself
is a pussycat by comparison.
Allen, Gigi Allen,
whose songs are all way too obscene for radio,
has as his main claim to fame
the fact that in his concerts,
he smeared himself with his own excrement,
cut himself with knives,
cut audience members with knives,
and played with himself on stage,
and in fact,
devoured the results of these leakages from his body.
Now he'd always promised to kill himself
and many audience members on stage one day,
but he OD'd instead.
We once got a surprisingly unimaginative news,
a shocking bummer's tale from Gigi Allen.
Anyway, the Sheik was not only a fan,
but a friend of Gigi Allen,
and was stricken with grief
over the great artist's death,
as well as being loaded to the gills
on Central Nervous System, the presses.
And the eulogy rant that he delivered
over the airwaves that night
is the most booze-soaked, cuss-word impregnated thing
I have almost ever heard on any radio tape.
The miracle of all this is that Pastor Craig
somehow was unable to shut off the mic
once the Sheik started,
and it all went out over the air.
Now this could only have happened
in the particular unusual circumstances
that developed that night.
Now I've edited all the profanity from this tape
so that I may share the anguish of the Sheik with you.
Our radio audience.
Now sometimes you'll be able to tell
where I've removed the profanity,
and sometimes you won't.
But take my word for it, there was a lot.
Pastor Craig got suspended
for letting this go out over the air.
But what remains is still one of the most poignant
sermons ever delivered by any subgenius.
Incidentally, when the Sheik was finished ranting,
he threw up again,
and Pastor Craig called a cab.
Praise the Sheik, praise Dr. Legume,
praise G.G. Allen, and yes,
praise poor Pastor Craig,
the most mild-mannered subgenius
at whose expense it all happened.
Yeah, I'm Pastor Craig,
you're listening to Baaah of After Dark,
the Church of the Seemed subgenius show,
and after the little rocky start,
we're back on track here.
And tonight's a very special night,
actually kind of a sad night.
G.G. Allen passed away, and I have with me
someone to give a eulogy for Mr. Allen,
none other than the Sheik.
And welcome.
Thank you, thank you, thank you very much,
Pastor Craig.
And let me say, first of all,
I don't really care what anybody thinks about G.G.
I think what I think,
and I think a god has died!
A god has died!
And you all burned!
Your brains!
And your knees!
You'll go down, and you'll sit,
and you'll think,
everything is wrong,
everything's wrong,
of course everything's wrong,
because G.G.'s dead.
G.G. is dead!
Now, how the f*** do I know he's dead?
Ha ha ha.
Yeah.
You, you, you, you, you look at me,
you look at me, and you talk to me.
Let me tell you something, my friends.
I am not going to play games,
I am not going to mince words.
All I'm going to do
is say the truth.
The truth is, G.G. is dead!
And when G.G. dies,
the whole thing dies, man!
It's like there's no real truth!
Now you can talk about Bob,
and you can talk about the Church of the Subgenius,
and you can talk about everything,
you can talk about all these things,
but there's not one single thing
that will really, really, really,
really, really, really, really, really, really,
really f***ing do!
I'm telling you, it's beautiful.
It's like...
Ahhh!
Mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm.
Very good, very good.
You see?
You see, it ain't, it ain't, it ain't what you think it is!
It's what you think you thought it was!
I, I, I, I, I, I...
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Let me tell you a story.
Let me tell you a story, man.
I'm telling you,
you don't like it,
you can leave, you can leave.
Turn the dial.
Listen, everything is okay.
Everything is okay.
I want you to take your fingers
and I want you to take your fingers
and bring them down between your legs.
I want you to begin to make
to what I have to say.
Because what I have to say is so beautiful
and so unreal
and so, so intense.
I'm telling you!
It's sinful.
And I want you to do it.
I want you to think of God
and I want you to think of Jehovah
and I want you to think of Satan.
I want you to think of every sick thing
you could ever possibly imagine.
You!
You are me
and I am you.
Please do it.
Do it.
Now, I'm going to count to four.
When I count to four,
when I reach four,
you will think of the most dirty,
the dirtiest,
the sickest,
the most perverse sexual experience
you have ever had in your life.
You have probably never experienced
this sexual experience,
this fantasy.
But you will at the count of four experience.
I'm saying,
I'm saying this.
One.
I'll give it another one.
One!
Two!
Thirty.
Four.
I want you to experience orgasm.
I want you to climax.
I want you to climax with my voice
and what I am saying right now.
And the church of the subgenius is dead.
It's dead.
Bob is dead.
The whole church is dead.
It's dead.
Why is it dead?
Oh, you're all crying and weeping
and all this sort of trash.
Oh, it's dead because you've made it dead.
You are a killer.
You're a killer.
Each and every one of you,
you've killed.
You kill so much.
I get, I, I, I masturbate to you.
You're murder.
You are monsters.
And I love it.
And I want you to get,
oh, I want, I, I, I, I want you to guarantee
that you will murder.
Murder Bob.
That's what you gotta do.
I'm telling you.
There's no other way
to really understand the church of the subgenius
is to murder Bob.
Man, I'm telling you,
it took me four years
to understand
that Bob had to be killed.
Well, I certainly killed him.
And, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and,
and, and, and, and.
Oh, you damn people.
My friends,
you don't know how hard it is.
You know what it's like.
You know what it's like to be the Sheik.
The Sheik has many friends.
He has his buddies.
He has his friends.
But he has more.
More.
He has people who care.
And they want his guidance.
And I, I, I swear and I bleed out of my eyes.
That I cannot guide everybody.
Each body must guide itself.
Please.
I have nothing to offer.
Nothing!
You fucked him!
You've stayed like dogs!
And now I give you the ultimate treat.
I give you what you should have gotten long ago.
Five years ago.
I give you your God.
I'll give you your God.
Here he is.
Here he is!
Right.
Nothing.
Be quiet.
Be quiet, my children.
My children.
Be quiet.
Try and be quiet.
Love me.
Love me even though you hate me.
I want your hate.
I want you to hate me.
I want you.
I am the greatest, the most powerful.
You and your kind can never, never see.
Something very strange.
Something very important to happen.
Beginning of this week.
Gigi Allen, the greatest of the great, died.
I want you to bow your heads.
I don't give a if you liked them or you didn't or you won't.
You know, whatever.
You know.
If you didn't, that's too bad.
I'm pretty upset myself.
I want you to bow your heads.
I want you to understand that.
There was a man who did something that nobody else ever did.
He was unique.
And the word unique means original.
And that man was original.
And for him to be dead to me is ultimate tragedy.
Why do you think?
Do you think I want Led Zeppelin?
Those stupid, burned out bastards.
Those uncut mother.
What's that?
You know.
Please give me a break.
It sounds normal, but
I'm sorry.
Please.
I apologize.
I give you something.
I give you something to dwell on.
I give you something to suck on.
I'm sorry.
It hurts.
Gigi Allen was the greatest, he was the greatest rockstar of all time.
If you don't understand or you don't like him, that's your problem.
Why don't you just go like your stupid Led Zeppelin albums, man?
I'm telling you.
The Sheik loves people.
The Sheik loves all the subs.
And the subs know who they are.
And the subs, they know.
They know.
I don't have to tell them.
Man, I don't have to tell them.
The Sheik knows.
And they know who the Sheik is.
Shut down.
Oh, I'm not shut down?
Oh, okay.
No, no, let me, let me, let me, let me, let me go down.
All right.
I know, I know, I like it.
Go on, go on, go on, go on.
I love all of you.
And I thank Pastor Craig, who has made this possible.
He's a hell of a nice guy.
And I thank his wife, because, and Jesus, my wife would never let me do this.
we're going to play some
Gigi and
I hope you like it
and I'm sorry if I
did anything
I'd like
to close with this small
statement
you're listening to the subgenius radio
ministry hour of slack
for free information on Bob
Dobbs and the church of the subgenius
send a self addressed stamped
envelope to got your pencil ready
Bob post office box
Dallas Texas 75214
that's
Bob P.O. box
Dallas Texas 75214
stay tuned
and praise Bob
, Bob, and Bob
Gigi
I love you man
goodbye
alright that's all I have to say
man
okay I'm done