You are about to participate in a great adventure.
You are about to experience the awe and mystery which reaches from the inner mind to...
The Subgenius Hour of Slack!
Ah, yes, dear friends, this time we're really back.
And this is the first show that I've actually sat down and done, as far as being an hour of slack, since X-Day, friends.
The X-Day that, let's face it, didn't happen.
At least, I assume it didn't happen.
I sure hope that this is not my escape vessel.
But, you know, friends, we're crazy and it doesn't bother us to trust in Bob for...
Don't worry, Bob.
X-Day 1999, July 5th.
That's when Nostradamus said it was going to happen anyway.
Friends, and I'm going to attempt...
This is going to be a strange show.
I'm going to attempt to explain to you what happened in the very last minutes before 7 a.m.
I'm going to play the audio from videotapes of the moment at Brushwood, New York, at 7 a.m. on X-Day.
When, yes, it's true.
Yours truly, Reverend Stang, did, in fact, have to face the music.
Well, let's get on with it.
This one's going to be tricky because there's a lot of cussing in these videotapes on this audio.
I'm going to narrate this so that you can sort of see with me what's going on.
But I'm going to have to cut some cuss words majorly, friends.
But, uh...
So let us, uh...
Let us proceed.
All right, then.
Hey, friends!
X-Days are coming!
And the pigs are coming!
This tape starts at midnight the night before.
It is now 12.01.
Half the audience is on the stage.
There's like 200 subgeniuses.
It's the day dawned.
The pre-X-Day.
It's 12.01.
X-Day's here, baby.
And this is what you're doing at midnight.
I'm not kidding.
It looks like a scene from hell, friends.
There's several large women partially dressed in what can only be described as breasts and, uh, uh, butts.
And men are having simulated sex.
Okay, now it's the next morning.
It's 7 o'clock in the morning.
The white...
The huge white stretch limo has pulled up outside the, uh, enclosed pavilion area.
There are 400 subgeniuses standing there.
They're standing around.
Uh, Jesus Christ, Mary Magdalene, myself, and someone else just exited the limousine,
um, carrying a dummy of J.R. Bob Dobbs.
Um, th-th-th-th-and it's-it's...
Things are not too confused, surprisingly.
Don't drink that stuff!
It's unkilled!
Exactly 7 a.m.
I guess the time master is, uh, I hope is still alert.
Um, the lovely Friday Jones is dis...
Dispensing, uh, Kool-Aid.
And, uh, I believe someone else...
...exactly at 7 a.m. will take the hit and say,
Fuck them if they can't take a joke!
You see what I mean about the cuss words, friends?
And hopefully we'll be on the saucers by the time that damn sentence is fitting.
I don't know about you, but...
Friends, the, uh, stage is decorated with huge Dobbs heads.
Jesus is in his robe.
Papa Joe Mama is in a Nazi outfit.
Ten more minutes until...
Until rupture, children.
That's Papa Joe Mama.
He is up on stage helping me to leave.
Ready at 666.
We're trying to, um...
Trying to, we're, we're, we're help...
We're trying to organize dispensing the Kool-Aid.
People are lined up.
The subgeniuses are drinking down...
Well, they haven't drank it yet.
They're getting Kool-Aid in little cups.
Hey, I don't know if y'all heard,
Has there been anything on the news about
cities in Europe being, uh, destroyed or anything?
Has anybody tuned in?
I'm dressed in my trademark quiet preaching suit.
I honestly don't know whether...
We're in the future or the past.
I can't clarify that statement for you.
I brought something with me.
I'm gonna have to shut this up.
I wanted to bring the original...
I'm sorry.
Be quiet. Be quiet. Be quiet.
The sound wasn't working right.
I didn't want to bring the original Dobbs head.
I see.
This is the original handwritten note
in J.R. Bob Dobbs' own hand
written... that he wrote in a bar in 1953
that, uh, that says,
The world ends July 5th, 7 a.m., 1998.
This is the original piece of paper touched by Bob.
That was a pretty awesome thing to hold, friends.
This, this little crumpled note,
like a...
25, 45 years since Bob first received the
immaculation from Jehovah One
that, that the Exodus would come
in, according to my seven minutes...
I suddenly decided to take my watch off
and smashed the hell out of it
against the pulpit.
That was a...
I just didn't... I felt like...
I just didn't need a watch anymore.
Unfortunately, then we didn't have anything to count down with.
Right in the crotch, today!
Right in the crotch, you mother...
There's a lot of really drunk subgeniuses out there.
I'm displaying the original note,
a blow-up of Bob's original note
that said the world ends July 5th, 1998.
7 a.m., July 5th, 1998.
So this is just a few minutes before the end of the world.
Eight minutes?
Eight minutes.
Oh, there we go.
Goddamn!
These things keep flipping up.
So did y'all hear what I said?
Yeah!
Okay.
Fuck out.
Hey, how about this?
It took three days to preach and I'm still talking.
It's a miracle that I didn't lose my voice.
That's Sister Susie the floozy.
She should be up here.
Oh, God.
Susie the floozy comes up and joins the gods.
Where's... where's my doctor?
Dr. Legume and, uh...
She's a god. I just...
Ed Strange and G. Gordon Gordon
were burning their membership cards
and just came up to the pulpit...
Seven minutes?
...giving me the ashes of their membership cards.
How did you know, Dr. Legume?
What'd you find out?
Hell no, I said.
Come back home.
We got seven minutes.
What's... what's that...
Burn my membership card.
They wanted me to burn my membership card.
They were really drunk and they...
None of these people have actually read any of our books.
Legume...
I actually just got a new card on me.
I just saw it.
I suddenly realized I'm glad they did that
because I realized that I was not actually carrying my membership card.
I'd left it in my car.
So I ran away from the stage to go get the membership card.
Um...
Legume thought that he was gonna be trapped on these saucers
with all those nerdy subgeniuses.
He did not read his book very closely.
It's a moot point since the rupture didn't really happen.
This is your last chance.
Burn it. Burn it!
Don't be like me and remember to check your card.
Most of these people had been up all night long.
Well, I'm not going.
But I'll be glad to burn this dollar bill
so the exes will be able to know where to home in on you.
You folks.
Yeah.
Fuck no!
I'm not getting on them saucers with you fucking people.
Dr. Legume does not have as high a regard for the subgeniuses as I do.
As the smoke from this dollar bill is still rising up to heaven,
the invisible space monsters that really are there
know that there's still something down here on Earth worth saving.
I think Dr. Legume and some of the holocaustals wanted to stay behind.
Get the first filled out membership card.
I was displaying my membership card.
It's one of the...
It doesn't even mention my priestesses.
That's how you know I'm not a holocaustal.
A 1980 subgenius membership card.
While you folks are all up here in the attic trying to make sure you get out,
I just saw a subgenius heading to the bathroom to take a shit.
Who's got more faith?
Friends, this roof will be...
This roof is going to be blown off the top of this building.
How long do we have?
How's everybody got their...
Five minutes.
Susie the floozy is looking beautiful.
Children, let's not be rowdy rowdy...
I can't describe the Susie the floozy X-Day outfit.
...dispensing the Kool-Aid.
I've been wanting to say that for years.
If you have perfect trust and faith, you will be ruptured.
Don't worry. Trust us.
They did, too.
The Kool-Aid is just symbolic, friends.
You don't have to worry about it.
You really can't afford the Kool-Aid.
I'd like to point out that that one accident the person had when they touched their tongue to the Kool-Aid,
that was because that person was epileptic.
It had nothing to do with the Kool-Aid.
Popes Lilith is up there on stage.
I mean up at the top.
You can take out that money and burn it now, folks.
There's no more use for it anymore.
Now down to officially three minutes.
In 35 seconds.
Yeah!
Friends, it was exciting.
It was really exciting.
You know, considering that most people had not slept.
Get some sleep.
That was all I wanted to do as soon as I was ruptured.
I wanted to get a bed.
You know, because the moment of rupture, you will become what you want to become.
And I hope you want to become.
Praise God.
Yeah!
Woo!
There may be a few Holocausters out there that want to remember this.
I mean, behind just this kind of mop-up troops.
But we don't want to miss out on all the fun.
So we might kind of have to join, you know, say goodbye to the Evangelicals for a few hours.
Because you want to kind of be involved with the actual...
We're not going to all end up...
This is the last we'll probably see of each other for a few hours.
But hours will be meaningless in a few minutes.
Oh my God.
We need something that we can count down with.
I just smashed mine.
It looks like it's two and a half minutes.
Two and a half minutes.
Work, Willie!
Now, two and a half minutes.
Two and a half minutes as Bob sprawled on his original note.
The world ends July 5th, 7 a.m., 1998.
That was the first time I noticed something odd about that note.
Papa Joe Mama is examining the note at this point.
You can see on his face...
What are you talking about?
What the fuck?
You're not giving stuff back?
Man, oh, by the way, hang on to any Earth artifacts you have.
They will be very rare.
And, uh, important...
Oh, yeah.
We have enough of them to stay in our lives.
We're in the hotline.
Everyone will be back at us.
You don't have a choice.
Like you...
Poor legume.
He's gonna be sitting there trying to stay down here on Earth so he can kill more pigs.
Poor superstitious bastard.
Okay.
One and a half...
Don't give him shit!
Could this really be one and a half minutes?
Where's Jesus?
Man!
Nobody recognized Jesus because his beard was mysteriously removed in the night.
I don't know where...
Like I say, I can't tell you where we've been.
I don't...
Honestly don't know whether it was the future or the past.
Uh, the Lord and I and our wives had disappeared during the night.
The final minute.
The final...
Wow.
There's some good looking women up there on that stage.
And some really ugly guys with cool costumes.
Um...
Wait, now we're down to...
Did everyone sign that last will, by the way?
That's just a joke.
Everyone at the camp...
I don't know.
I don't know, people at the camp had to sign a last will and testament before we gave
them the Kool-Aid.
Everybody got their Kool-Aid!
And we're getting down to 40 seconds.
More Kool-Aid!
Thirty five seconds.
Hey!
Kool-Aid!
Three...
Watch the camera, 30 seconds, 30, 29, 28, 27, 26, 25, 24, 23...
No, it's 20!
21...
I wanted so much for the X machine.
this to rupture us all up to our escape vessels, friends.
30, 12, 11, 10, 9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
Suck up if they can't take a job!
All those subgeniuses have their arms and tape decks raised up waiting to be ruptured and then nothing happens.
10, 9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
Suck up if they can't take a job!
Well, um,
friends, I wish you could see the close-up of my face.
Why has Southport sacked me?
Uh, triple their money back!
And of course they're instantly already calling for triple their money back.
Father Joe Mama just noticed that the 1998 on the note has been taped in and upside down.
It had originally said 86-61.
I'm showing the note.
Papa Joe is questioning the note.
Susie the floozy looks over my shoulder and sees how the year has been taped in upside down and gets the most...
She gets the most horrified look on her face.
What do we miss?
The year 8,861?
The world ends July 5th, 8661.
That's not for sure. That's just a theory, friends.
But, uh, you can see...
I was horribly confused and shocked at this point myself.
Susie is crying. Susie the floozy is crying.
Jesus looks disturbed.
He didn't change the... When we started talking about this, he didn't jump in and mention any changes.
I was getting a little scared at this point, friends, because people were starting to call for my blood.
Maybe swing another needle. I don't know.
I mean, it said he could swing another needle.
Hell, we might have to... Fuck. I don't want to have to do this again next year.
I'm afraid we will have to do it again next year.
There's no reason that we can't keep up the spirit, though, children.
I know that there's a lot of pocket calculators out there. Somebody do the math.
How many more seconds until 8,661?
No, I can't. You're wrong.
The mood of the crowd is turning.
I was wondering what that other apostrophe was doing.
Ed Strange is making a hand-mincemise over on the side.
Let's get around.
Are you... Are...
Are you...
This watch can't be right.
He had a new pamphlet?
Then he meant 707s.
I'm going back to the story that...
I'm just saying, I don't have... I hate to be the one to tell you this, but if some explosions don't start exploding soon,
I have a feeling that somebody up on this stage...
I'm not saying no, no, no, no, no.
Maybe we all better just kind of...
...dance in opposite directions.
You know what?
You know, as far as the eternal salvation goes, that's when you die.
Okay?
We promised two utopias, one before your dead and one after your dead.
You don't get your money back until you, you know, until you can prove you didn't get eternal salvation.
That may take a while.
Uh-oh.
Dr. Legime and the Luciferian Liberation Front just...
...the fucking charlatan!
...suddenly the Luciferian Liberation Front guy, who's like a Green Beret, grabbed me.
And they're physically restraining me, yelling at me.
Gee, Gordon Gordon is helping.
Quick, we need some women up here!
Dr. Legime calls a bunch of women come up happily ripping my clothes off.
Get up! Get up!
Someone else, my wife, Reverend Friday Jones,
the new Christ in a Bucket, or Christy Liv and Christina Bucket,
and Susie Dufluzzi are stripping the clothing off of me, forcibly,
holding me down while they pulled my t-shirt off of my head.
These girls thought this was real fun.
...and never have to pay it back.
I've just worked here my very life.
Oh, and the rabbi is up there helping to strip me.
I've...
Every day, I was stripped and thrown into water by women.
Any last words, Ivy?
Uh, during that weekend.
I'm trying to hide my nakedness behind the pulpit at this point.
There's a man with a Satan mask in the crowd, standing there in the foreground.
And, oh no! This is...
Then they pull out the honey, a big jug of honey.
And Dr. Lagune poured this huge thing of honey over the top of my head.
Joe Mama said it was...
Joe Mama said motor oil, and that's what everyone thought it was.
And then they dumped, friends!
Here I am, stark naked, covered with honey, and they dumped a bag of pink feathers on me.
Bright, day-glow pink feathers.
So that I looked like a little naked chicken.
A little half-foot chicken.
Um, totally humiliated in front of 400 subgeniuses.
All of you shit-or-actions just line up here on the side of the stage.
Hey, stay!
We'll make sure that this world will end with a bang, if not a whimper.
Friday Jones comes up and tries to wipe the honey out of my eyes.
And Jesus wiped his wept.
Oh, and Jesus is helping to wipe my eyes off.
Having honey in your eyes is a strange sensation, friends.
We want our money back!
We want triple one, three, four, and three!
Um, Christina Bucket, Christ in a bucket, I mean, is comforting me.
Beautiful, uh, young lady.
And, uh...
Careful! Careful! Careful! Careful!
I finally... There was nothing to do but cry.
Jesus held the mic up to me and I just bawled like a little baby.
And, uh, everything would have been fine at this point, friends, except that, um...
Go to the showers. Put that in.
I wanted to go to the showers.
But...
My mom! My mom! My asthma has forsaken me!
Um, unfortunately, someone got the bright idea to throw me in the pond.
And that is what subsequently happened, friends.
You know, I was looking for a last minute porno movie.
Poor little naked stang.
I ended up trying to run away to the showers.
I think that's as close as we're gonna get to him volunteering to bend over and take it where it counts.
I'm afraid Bob did that to me some twenty years ago.
I got one request.
Don't throw this piece of shit in the pool. I gotta clean the pool.
Throw this asshole in the pond.
Thanks, Rhino.
It was one of the Brushwood staff suggested throwing me in the pond, and that was it.
I tried to run away, friends, and, uh...
This is Popes Lilli.
...that Bob had that note and was writing it out, and then just got distracted.
The note got turned upside down, and he did write down 1998 upside down!
And monkeys might fly out of my butt!
Listen to this!
Woo!
Ends dateline for dominance.
At the very end, you have the chart of time outlining the events that are going to be occurring in the past and the future of this universe.
And there, it clearly says July 5th, 1998.
Exes arrive underneath.
It says the year 2000.
Exes depart.
As far as we know, the exes are, in fact, here.
They're just not making themselves known to us.
Well, that's a hopeful feeling.
Of course, Jesus...
Ladies and gentlemen...
...happened to be ready.
Not that I was prepared and didn't have faith and, uh...
Yeah, all right.
...was prepared for this in any way.
Of course, down to the wire, I thought we'd be ruptured.
But just in case, we have prepared for you...
I have prepared for you.
Bob has prepared for you...
the new official subgenius sticker.
Only $2.
July 5th, 7 a.m.
It's all purpose.
There, that'll give you some free...
Jesus was selling bumper stickers already...
...with the year removed, friends.
Okay, I give you free.
Now it's $2 a piece.
In all of the subgenius pamphlets where it used to say 1998, it now says...
...soon.
I think nothing should be mentioned that if this man actually winds up in the pond...
If y'all recall, we had a little incident in the whirlpool a few nights ago when someone laid a turd.
Oh, my God.
But that pond, I think, has got more than a lot...
More than just one or two turds in it.
I think that's kind of where the sewage winds up.
Free and safe.
How appropriate.
There's leeches in the pond.
Yes, friends, I spent the next half hour or so start naked with 400 people laughing at me.
You know, it's...
That's what most people would consider a horrible nightmare.
The nightmare of slugging through mud while 400 people point at your nakedness and laugh.
To me, that's just a memory.
Into the pond.
Friends, I tried to run the other way.
And...
Into the pond.
But the girls themselves caught me and dragged me down and the whole crowd just...
He has to go into that pond.
I tried to run.
Friends, I...
Should I continue with this tape and...
And play the humiliation of poor Reverend Stang, the...
The...
The charlatan, the fraud.
Finally, in the end, after they had mocked me and berated me and mocked my nakedness and so forth...
And said, triple your money back a thousand times...
Uh...
The guy in the devil suit, Satan, came down and said...
Stang...
I'm still on your side.
You can come with me.
I'll help you out.
And I was helped up out of the pond finally by Satan himself.
Um, friends...
You know...
The...
Well...
Actually, I guess what I should do now is take this tape over to the subsequent devival.
Believe it or not, two weeks after this terrible failure, this...
This...
Non-rupture...
And humiliation.
Two weeks after that, I was back at Sherman, New York at Brushwood Campground for the giant Starwood Pagan event.
Um...
And did a devival there with Einstein's Secret Orchestra.
And that's where I...
Uh...
Tried to explain our take on...
On this...
This problem.
This X-Day problem.
And, um...
And our faith that...
Sure, if X-Day doesn't happen on...
Double X-Day...
Dos Equis...
In 1999...
Uh...
Perhaps it will happen on Triple X-Day...
Um...
The year 2000.
We may have to have a party every year...
Oh, God...
Friday Jones herself pushed me into the water there.
A poor, pathetic...
It...
The pond was very smelly, friends.
And, in fact, I've had an illness ever since that day.
I didn't get it in the pond.
I had it before then.
But I've been suffering from that.
It's like vertigo.
Quite badly.
I feel like I'm spinning right now.
I'm...
I'm down there in the water trying to wash the honey out of my face using this stinking,
rancid water.
I cried and wept.
Only now in the end do I understand.
I do still believe, friends.
Look, poor little naked stone.
As Father Joe Mama said, it's true, he only has one.
Where the fuck am I?
That's where I used Jayner's one.
I remember us in seventh grade trying marijuana for the first time.
Woo-hoo!
Well, friends, it went on for a while.
There was a...
You know, of course, more movie quotes yelled out from the crowd.
I got mad and yelled at them.
I ended up finally just...
I may be being baptized in shit, but that's nothing compared to what you fuckers are gonna
have to deal with.
Maybe we got the math wrong or something.
I don't know.
Hey, it's not my fault.
I'm not Bob.
Yes, you are.
I just...
You believed in two.
Show us Bob.
I've been placed down with fucking peps.
Where is the Bob?
Bring him before us.
Shoot a wad for Bob.
Feed him to the beast.
Show us Bob.
There is even a model flying saucer burning on the little island in the pond.
Hey, Stag, you're alone in feathers.
Hey, Stag.
I got your saucer right here.
They're in a balsa wood and paper just like the church.
Maybe they're just small.
balsa wood and paper saucer being burned in disappointment.
What goods has sex got us that little?
My dreams of excess escape going up in plums.
I've tried to leave the pond, it was really cold.
This is up in ski country and it's quite cold at night there.
You know the thing is, it was as if Bob never existed.
They took it all out on me as if there were no Bob Dobbs,
as if I was the one who came up with all this crap.
And then triple your money back.
That's uh, that triple your money back is for when you're dead.
I'm trying to get out of the pond and the girls push me back in again.
Is this enough humiliation for you?
Hell no!
I was really getting cold.
Show a handstand!
And looking sad.
Well actually friends, I'm in better shape than most 44 year olds,
so it wasn't that embarrassing.
I don't look too bad.
I'll just rip my clothes off if you don't look at my face.
I still believe it goddammit!
I still believe in Bob!
I still love Bob!
This was just a test!
Bet you had a test!
You just wanted, I'm the only one who passed the goddamn test!
I'll bet you!
I got you Bob!
Here!
You guys fucked it up!
It's sad!
If you had faith!
If you had faith they would come!
This show's your faith!
You fucked it up for me goddammit!
Oh that's so sad.
Did John the Baptist have to go through this?
Did Moses and Jesus have to deal with this kind of crap?
Did Bob ever have to mess with these yo-yos screaming at him like this?
You better hope you don't!
Oh man.
You better hope you spike the fucking Kool-Aid!
There, see?
Where's your Kool-Aid now, Kool-Aid man?
No, you're just on your way!
I transubstantiated your...
Well friends, I...
There, as you can see, I'm a little bit more of a...
I mean as the camera pans over the crowd of all kinds of people.
The subgeniuses are, you know, comprised quite a cross-section of people who...
Some of them even look sort of normal.
Uh.
So, friends, on side two of show we shall now proceed onto the much slicker and better produced subgenius devival at Starwood.
You motherfuckers have me mixed up with Bob fucking Dobbs, don't you?
You motherfuckers never...
You motherfuckers never once believed in Bob!
You fuckers thought Bob was a goddamn piece of clep art and nothing more, right?
Admit it! Admit it!
Subtitles by the Amara.org community
You'd never have believed
in Bob's honest autonomy
Your finger tips set holdin' fire
Everlastin' sweet desire
If you matter what the doctors say
You're a man you steal away
Immortality for two
Miracles, they come for you
Subtitles by the Amara.org community
He can make you understand
All you gotta do is take his hand
Remember what Ivan says
As the man inside the head
Finger drips and hold his fire
Everlastin' sweet desire
The Faith Healer!
You can never escape the eyes
The eyes of God watch you wherever you go
Can I put my hands on you?
making your periodic heartb
Welcome to the revival of Rose Ivan Stone.
Praise Bob!
Let's get right to it.
I want to hear a moment of sacred noise.
Praise Bob! Praise Bob! Praise Bob!
Goddamn Bob.
Oh, and the fucking Bob, too.
We'll praise all of the Bobs.
Friends, I wasn't supposed to be here today.
I was planning, like every other subgenius,
to be on the escape vessels of the sex goddesses.
Don't interrupt.
I know, maybe we are on them.
There are 180 excuses for X-Day on the Internet already.
Personally, I believe that Occam's Razor, usually,
which says that the simplest explanation is usually the best,
Bob fucked up.
I know, I know that it's hard to imagine
that a holy man like J.R. Bob Dobson,
would lie or fuck up.
I know, I can't believe that Bob would fuck up,
but that may be it.
Maybe that's what happened.
Maybe that's why the X-Ess didn't arrive
two weeks ago on X-Day.
I'm not going to explain any of that to you.
You can pick it up from context.
But friends, you know,
remember that little nutty religious cult
in Garland, Texas?
The God Salvation Temple.
Poor little teacher, Chen.
They were from Taiwan.
You've heard about them, I'm sure.
They actually, that silly end of the world cult,
was right down the street
from where our skyscraper office is.
Really is.
And they had been predicting that the world would end March 31st.
I think God was going to be on TV and so forth.
And those poor, silly cultists,
duh, they were so wrong.
And the media laughed at them and made fun of them.
And friends, I remember standing on this very stage
six months ago saying,
well, we don't have to worry about being like those idiots now, do we?
And friends,
two weeks ago,
we did the countdown.
7 a.m., the exes, the aliens,
did not show up.
I'll admit it.
They took it out on me.
People don't believe in Bob.
They have to, you know, kill the messenger.
So they stripped me down
and tarred and feathered me.
Poured motor oil and feathers over me.
Threw me in that pond down there.
Friend, did you ever have that nightmare
where you dream that you're slugging through the mud
and you're naked and everybody's laughing at you?
Well, the next time I have that nightmare,
it'll just bring back fond memories of a fun party, dear friends.
And I'll tell you something.
Sure, our prophecy may not have come true.
Maybe Bob fucked up that one time.
Uh, but you know what?
We're religious nuts!
We don't care if Bob...
Bob could suck up a hundred times
and we'd still show up here at Brushwood
waiting for those blind saucers
and having a hell of a party.
Did Bob...
Did the Jehovah's Witnesses stop coming to your door just because their world didn't end every time?
Last time I noticed, they were still at my door.
Well, are we going to let the Jehovah's Witnesses be bigger religious nuts than us?
Say no!
We are the biggest religious fanatics in the world, and we will wipe out all other religious fanatics.
But, friends, I guess what that brings us to,
I'm afraid that, of course, there are many provisos for why Bob's prophecy might not work out,
if you read the fine print in Revelation X,
but what I think people forget is that, you know, we can make up all these excuses
why we aren't on the saucers of why Bob's prophecy fucked up,
but maybe some of you did not read the very first sentence at the very top of the first pamphlet number one,
Prophetic.
Printed in 1979 in Dallas, Texas, and I don't mean where it says $1, friends.
At the very beginning of the very first pamphlet, does it say the world ends July 5th, 1998 at 7 a.m.?
No, friends.
It says the world ends tomorrow!
Tomorrow!
And you may die!
In fact, I promise that every single person here will die!
Now, are you living your life as if it was the last day on Earth?
Some of you may be!
Some of you probably are living your life like it's the last day on Earth.
How many of you are living your life as if you've got all the time in the world?
Well, that's just as good!
Friends, the point is, you know, sure, Bob Dobbs may have fucked up,
but what does that say about all those other religious leaders?
I mean, if Bob's gonna fuck up, what does that say about...
Well, I don't want to name names.
Jesus, uh, I'm tired of bad-mouthed Jesus, because he works for me now.
Couldn't be here instead of sending his blessings to everyone.
But seriously, friends, obviously, there was, and I've been saying this to subgeniuses for a while now,
the mystery of X-Day may, in fact, be an important lesson that many subgeniuses desperately needed to learn.
That lesson might be, don't believe everything you read.
And don't depend on Bob!
That was his whole point!
He does not want a bunch of cripples leaning on him!
He, he's trying to get you.
It's like, okay, he depended on a holy man.
He fucked up.
So what are you gonna do about your escape vessels now?
I think the message is, build your own ship!
That's what it is!
The X's may show up, uh, in 350 days.
Uh, those X's.
X-Day.
1999.
Like Nostradamus said.
But we can't depend on that!
All of those holy men may be liars and cheaters.
Even Bob!
So therefore, are we gonna sit on our asses and pray for some benevolent aliens to come down and save our butts?
No!
Build your own ship!
And while we're working on that, if you think about it, we're on our own ship right now.
Unfortunately, we're all on the same ship.
And it's not the same ship.
It is badly in need of repairs.
So let's work on the spaceship that we're riding on right now!
Get the motherfucker fixed up.
And then, we shall conquer the universe.
Praise Bob.
But, of course, the conspiracy...
Say, boys...
Maybe we could do some, uh, scary music.
Yeah.
Do you guys know how to play any scary...
We'll work on it right now.
Okay.
Um...
Now, speaking of wishful thinking...
The, uh...
I'd like to share with you something called the keys of magic.
There are a lot of people here that call themselves magicians, right?
I mean, well, maybe they're all the humorless ones that stay away from these.
I don't know.
But, um, you know, I, uh...
Certainly, magic is real, but...
Judging by its practitioners, sometimes I think belief in it maybe defeats the purpose.
And, uh...
You know, we...
There are a lot of, uh, subgeniuses that...
Are sort of, uh...
Pathetic and...
Sad and disgusting and...
But they're not nearly as bad as the Scientologists.
I got hold of the most expensive Scientology newsletter.
The cheaper Scientology newsletter.
I've ripped them off myself quite a bit.
The ones that you get if you're a $15,000 a year Scientologist...
Are written like Dick and Jane books.
Uh, for first graders.
Because that's the kind of person that will spend $15,000 a year on Sci-
On Scientology.
Now, a typical testimonial from the most well-trained Scientologists went like this.
I have a fa-
I had a fancy bicycle that I kept in my garage.
And I was like,
One day someone stole it.
Using the techniques I learned from Scientology...
I drove around my neighborhood and found my bike.
Praise L. Ron Hubbard.
Now friends, that guy spent $15,000 to find out what I'm about to tell you for free!
That guy was using one of King Bob Solomon's keys to magic.
The first key!
And there's only four of them. They're very easy to remember.
The first key to subgenius magic...
Get off your ass.
You wanted a girlfriend?
Talk to a girl.
You hate your job?
Quit your job and get a new one.
Just get off your ass.
That's the very first step, the first key to magic.
Number two key to subgenius magic...
Is bust your ass.
Number three key of subgenius magic...
Is get others to bust their asses for you.
Which we call...
Ass...
I guess we call that assholism.
And uh...
The fourth key...
Watch your ass.
And if you watch your ass, no one will kick...
Oh wait!
There is in fact a fifth key to magic, more important than any of those others,
brought to us by the great Saint Red Fox.
And that is not watch your ass, but friends...
Wash your ass.
That will get you further.
In some cases, some of you lonely people, you'd be surprised what a little effort at personal hygiene would do for you in your life.
Now...
We all uh...
We're always, you know, talking about slack.
This is the church of the subgeniuses devoted...
Of course, everyone knows it's Bob and he teaches slack.
Well...
Well what is this slack stuff, you say?
And you go, oh I know slack isn't that conspiracy bullshit where life is a Miller beer commercial and every...
You have slack if you just drank a 12 pack, your team just won, and all the girls around you look like MTV bimbos and all the guys are buff jock assholes.
Then that's really slack.
Well we know that's bullshit.
Then you go back to your stinking job the next day and it's...
Well we know better than that, but some of us go, yeah man, like slack, that means like uh...
What Beavis and Butthead do, right?
You like get stoned, watch TV and eat all day, right?
Sure!
That may be slack for you, but being cheated out of your life by the conspiracy may be your idea of slack.
The difference between us and them is we won't tell you what it is!
Because it's different for every fucking one of you!
And if we could bottle it and sell it...
We would be the conspiracy and it would be up to you to kill me now!
I am not bottling and selling it!
In fact, if you come up to me after this and say, Reverend Stang, I saw your show, I paid money but I didn't get slack,
I would have to say, sir, you will never get slack because you will never be able to understand Bob's message.
You have to make the slack yourself, build your own ship!
And here's the point, friends, slack is not necessarily laziness.
There are some of us, we call ourselves the emergent tile subgeniuses as opposed to the rewardians.
I love the rewardians, friends, but some of us, some of us get slack when we are working so intensely hard at what we wanted to do!
Not the slave labor, but what we wanted to do.
That you get so into it that you may go without sleep for days.
You may even go without drugs for days.
You may...
You just develop this concentration, right?
You're flying, you're in the zone, you're cruising on what you're doing, you're really into it,
and suddenly you become sort of more smart for a second.
And you realize that you are God, life really is incredible, an amazing miracle,
the rust streaks on the side of your car are prettier than anything hanging in an art museum,
and life really is more psychedelic than that old t-shirt that you can't fit into anymore.
Now, hold that thought!
Hard to do.
Because, uh, the conspiracy has a secret weapon, friends.
The conspiracy has this invisible monster.
Now, polls have been done that indicate that 87% of Americans, this is just in America,
really believe that there is an invisible giant monster in the sky
that will do favors for you if you kiss its ass enough,
and will curse your enemies if you kiss its ass enough, basically.
Now...
Friends, I...
Just because there doesn't happen to be an invisible monster there,
as long as 87% of the dumbasses believe in it,
we still have to deal with it!
And that is why we, the Church of the Subgenius, have decided...
Now, friends, this is kind of harsh,
but we have decided to declare war on God!
War on God, like Jason and the Argonauts did!
By God, we shall...
Because what kind of a God is it that is so weak and so pathetic
that it has to be defended by illiterate little old redneck ladies against assholes like me?
That is a sick God!
A guy can do better with a piece of clipart
than those idiots can do with their so-called God!
Do they have a photograph of him?
Hell, they don't even have clipart.
So...
Friends, if you've obviously...
We're no different from all the other religions.
It's not really that we love Bob all that much,
it's that we love the idea of everybody else burning in hell forever!
That's what religion says!
That's what it's really all about!
Oh, yes!
And friends, we here as subgeniuses, looking around at each other,
hell, you may look at the next one over and go,
God, I don't want to be stuck on a spaceship with that nerd!
Friends, it's true!
Most of us actually have nothing in common,
except that we have nothing in common with the conspiracy of the normals!
And...
You know, sure, I'll admit, maybe we're kind of queer for Bob.
I'm queer for Bob, but...
And this is something many of you may have wondered about.
Yes, many of us in the hierarchy of the Church of the Subgenius are...
Bisexuals.
That means, when you go back there and buy our shit, we come!
You buy, we come!
Thanks, Bob!
Thank you!
Bob, Bob, wherever...
So friends, uh...
You know, what we're offering is the same thing everybody else is offering.
Something for nothing.
But!
Think about it.
Money.
You know, money.
We're getting money from you.
Well, what is money really worth?
Ask Elvis Presley, or Michael Jackson, or Madonna.
It's meaningless to them, you know?
But what they wouldn't give for some slack!
Slack!
Man, now that is something!
Money is nothing but slack!
Slack is something!
And friends, slack is what you need!
Now, there are many people here who are thinking,
Man, Reverend Stang, that's easy for you to say.
You get paid to preach to drunks in nightclubs.
But, believe me, I know how it's like.
Some of you here are, uh...
Funny looking.
Some people here are what you might say...
Too fat!
Or too skinny!
Or have bad teeth!
Or have a mental impairment of some kind.
Some have physical problems.
Some of you, um...
May just simply be socially awkward.
Clumsy.
Not a people person.
Not a team player.
I know because I have been all of those things
and hope to be all of them again all at once someday!
But...
And in your case, many of you may have become so accustomed to solitude
that you don't really...
You know, you don't need an encounter group, support group
for fucking weirdos and Trekkies that read too much.
You really just...
You don't care about your fellow subgeniuses all that much.
You really just want to be left alone.
And here's the miracle of the Church of the Subgenius, friends!
You can be alone...
With Bob!
You think about it!
Every other personal savior...
No, they don't...
Being a short duration personal savior isn't good enough for them.
They've got to be your only personal savior
and they're always leaning over your shoulder, questioning,
Were you cool enough today?
Did you make enough money today?
Did you kiss my ass and pray enough today?
Friends!
Bob Dobbs does not give a shit about any of that stuff!
Not at all!
He does not care about your sins
because he is not equipped to forgive your sins.
He doesn't think you need to be forgiven.
All you ever needed was an excuse!
Bob brings no forgiveness!
But he brings the greatest excuse!
And that excuse is Bob!
Praise Bob! Praise Bob!
Whoo!
And friends, that's why we say...
Sure, we may be drunk or neurotic, brain damaged,
fucked up, funny looking...
But we've got Bob and they don't!
And so that we can hate them!
Hate them!
Hate! Hate! Hate! Hate!
Pretty good!
Come on, man!
I dig the vibes!
Drink the Kool-Aid, children!
All right!
I got 300 people to chant hate at Starwood.
That's not bad.
Two weeks ago we had 400 people line up to drink Kool-Aid at 7 in the morning.
All of them at 7 o'clock.
We did the countdown.
Three, two, one...
Fuck them if they can't take a joke!
And...
I had to prove that I could take a joke.
But, uh...
Friends, the slack is all around you.
You're floating in it.
You're floating in a sea of pills, as Jane or Hyperglyphs used to say.
You're floating in a veritable ocean of Bob's best pills and best smoking admixtures.
But you're just too blind, deaf, and dumb, and taste-dead to know they're there.
Because, hell, for all I know, maybe we are on the escape vessels.
And we're just...
We just don't have faith.
But!
I won't accept that!
I want my escape vessel!
I want my slack!
And I'm willing to wait another...
If I have to, goddammit, I'll wait another 350 days.
And that brings me to a very important point, my friends.
You may be fucked up, ugly, poor, and broke, and hopeless.
But!
You probably only need to hang in there for one more year!
Surely Bob and the escape vessels will be here in a year.
So that's all you have to do for slack.
You're not gonna be able to defeat me.
You're not gonna be able to defeat the conspiracy on your own.
And the whole Church of the Subgenius...
Not this year, I don't think.
But!
Every little decision you make is part of the termite digging away at the foundations,
tying together the shoelaces of the Colossus.
And as much as it would do the Church a lot of good, financially, with publicity,
like everybody here would commit suicide while wearing a Bob t-shirt, or...
If you do what you always wanted to do, take that machine gun to a McDonald's full of schoolchildren...
Don't do it, friends.
As much as that would help our Church...
Don't do it.
Don't go postal.
Don't kill them, and don't kill yourself.
That's all you have to do!
That's all you have to do, friends, is stay alive for another 350 days.
That is the message.
That's more important than getting your idea of slack.
It's more important than quitting your job.
It's more important than any of the other things.
Just hang in there a little bit longer.
You don't know what the future may hold.
It sure as fuck surprised me several times over.
So, friends...
So, friends, we come down near the end of this show, this old show,
and that was the Subgenius Devival at Starwood Festival with Einstein's Secret Orchestra in the background.
That Devival was beautifully recorded and is on a DAT tape,
and we may turn it into a CD at some point.
It goes on for another half hour, so sorry about all the cuss words
and the fact that I'm going to have to remove them for most copies.
Friends, you can get it all, the free information about everything, from Subgenius.
You can write to Bob or the Hour of Slack or Church of the Subgenius at
gotthatpencilreadyfriendspobox140306
That's box140306, Dallas, Texas, 75214.
That zip again, 75214.
Or you can always check out www.subgenius.com.
You can hear the show on the air.
You can also listen to it on the internet, in fact, by hitting there.
You can try to email slack at subgenius.com.
And, friends, this Einstein's Secret Orchestra music in the background is not helping my vertigo.
Seriously, I'm suffering from an inner ear infection or something like that.
It makes me dizzy and vertigious.
I don't know what's going on, man.
I just wish them axes had shown up.
Bob at box140306, Dallas, Texas, 75214.
Praise Bob and thank you.
Thank you, Bob.
Thank you very much in advance.
Mmhm.
Exactly.
Besides us, I'm Joe and Bob not Bob, uh, anymore.
And I just want to remind you that the faith has nothing to do with people anymore.
My priests keep telling me that's all Wayne craft done, over and over again.
Just out all of this pretty good.
So, well, I don't know when to miss one, but it's gonna be the time as it comes.
Be cowboy, Mr. Spock.
Secret Orchestra at P.O. Box 81555. That's a new P.O. Box for them. P.O. Box 81555. Cleveland,
Ohio 44181. That zip code once again 44181. Einstein Secret Orchestra. P.O. Box 81555.
Cleveland, Ohio 44181. And I ate one. If you can't beat them, friends eat them.
P.O. Box 81555.