I am seeking information about Bob. Let us see what is on the radio.
You're listening to PR News.
No, I don't think I can accept that program.
Nor that man.
Yes.
Well, you know what? I'm high. It's simpler than you think.
By the time we finish, you're all going to know everything that you need to know to be able to get high in a flash.
I'm going to show you how to get high with two hands.
I never do because it takes too long.
Tonight at 9.
Let's get high and have fun.
I'm.
Falling.
And I can't give up.
Calling Dr. Howard. Dr. Fine. Dr. Howard.
No, I'm a doctor, not a mechanic.
We're losing potency in our antimatter parts.
My mind is growing.
I can feel it.
You see? You see? You're stupid minds. Stupid. Stupid.
Are you talking about the mind shafting gap?
Where you've been shafted in the mind again?
Right in the gap?
I'm a poor.
What?
It's a beer.
I'm a poor.
Huh?
Being of a blood mind.
I'm a poor.
Is that hurt?
Do
Hereby
Be
Queeth
Benadryl
Eve
Stop!
You're dressed
Way
There's a lord
Tell the lady
I am now
Well, guess why now?
So beware of falsehood.
So you're the man who gets drunk and kills innocent people with his car, are you?
Did you know you were putting a cell phone right into your brain?
That's the truth, and that's why I'd use a cell phone.
But guess what? There's a brain phone called Ray.
That's R-A-Y.
Ray is a small chip that attaches right into your brain, right next to the antenna.
Takes about 20 seconds.
Once in place, Ray's patent-pending subtle energy technology
immediately begins to counter the effects of the government without affecting your brain.
The cost of Rayway? Only $5,444.95.
Order right now.
Now.
Dot.com.
We enjoy the rich flavor of the products we've made with our minds.
The human mind is capable of more than you know in your show,
your dog and pony show, your light.
And dark shadow show.
For one thing, the human brain is fattening.
For another thing, it's fattening so much it's going to take over very soon the rest of the body.
Deep fried.
But it's buttery and sugary.
So, well, some of the human brain.
Other parts are bitter and sour.
Have you ever jacked in?
Have you ever wire tripped?
It was terrible. It was just terrible.
I'll never get over it.
As long as I live.
It was terrible.
It was just terrible.
I'll never get over as long as I live.
It was terrible.
It was just terrible.
I'll never get over as long as I live.
It was terrible.
It was just terrible.
I'll never get over as long as I live.
It's alive.
In the line
Deadly church
Are creaking over the earth
Killing every human in their path
Radioactivity's a constant thing
It's the ride
Phineas Narco
From Midnight
Voice Jail
Did that
And before that we heard some
ESO Swamp Radio
From WCSB Cleveland
Host Chaz Smith
With Lonesome Cowboy Dave
Yours truly Reverend Ivan Stang
And Princess Lear Doe
And friends all hours of slack
It seems are
Lighten and dripping
With collage pieces
By Fernanda Nande
Lee Murr
This
Particular show
Hour of Slack number
Is an educational show
With the subject matter being
Drugs
Yes
It is educational
Now
Well
Now let's go back to ESO
Swamp Radio
About a month ago we had just gotten back
From doing field research
On Entheo Musicology
At a conference of scientists
Who specialize in that
It was a slack filled
Starwood
As such things go
Partly because it rained so much
There wasn't much to do but hide out
With your loved one
Or your right hand
Well Starwood's this outdoor festival
Run by the
Crazy people and crazy people perform
And it's just insanity
In the mud
Late at night you see these neon giants
And they're all like
Stalking the campground
That were actually
Not hallucinations
But giant puppets
Rod puppets
Twice the size of a person
They were kind of tied like Waldo machines
To a human
But you didn't even see the human
Because they'd be in the darkness
The giant puppet is lit up
To freak out those on ketamine
Which was going around that campground
That particular
Now is that a legal or illegal substance?
Ketamine is legal if you're a horse
That needs to be tranquilized
Or if you're a vet who needs to administer
The tranquilization
I didn't touch that stuff
I saw that movie Altered States
It turns you into a caveman
And you run to the zoo and rip up the
Taper throats
Yeah
Crop circle makers were there
Reverend Circle Maker
Was at my house
I just sent him
Back home to Wales
The other day
We had one of the many
Crop circle artists
The people who
Make crop circles for the aliens
We're not saying the aliens
Don't direct the making of the crop circles
Or anything like that
It's just that most of the crop circles
Were made by these
British
Coffee drinkers
Let's say
Who like to stay up real late at night
And make artwork
Out of
Farmer's fields
Illegally
I was talking to one of these
These K people
And they talked all about
Going down the K hole
Yeah the K hole of special K
Ketamine
And they told me it was a club drug
And I couldn't imagine it
Being like a dancey kind of thing
No I've been told just the opposite
Really?
Yeah
That it's a what drug?
Well the guy
Has told me
He took some
He got up about 30 seconds later
And started to change channels on the TV
And fell to the floor
And at that point he said in very slow motion
I don't think this is a club drug
And that was the last thing he was able to say
As he lost contact with his body
But went on to another planet
Inside his own head
Apparently
I don't think this is a club drug
One person said
It's just like being real drunk
It's like drinking a whole lot of vodka
But without swallowing
But the guy who said it
Didn't sound like he was very drunk
When he said it
So I didn't believe that exactly
I think the numbness and disconnection
From your body
Is the vodka like aspect
But then there's some kind of a weird
Interior head trip
That you do
And you know ketamine is classed
As a telepathine
Wow
That is it causes people to
Telepathize
Think that they're experiencing telepathy
Especially with somebody else
Who happens to be on the stuff
Yeah
There's a very interesting article about that
In Paul Craster's new book
Magic Mushrooms and something something
About going to John Lilly's house
And taking ketamine
And getting in the isolation chamber
And freaking out
But then
Hearing John Lilly's mind
Speak to him to calm him down
Which somebody else later said
Well yeah he did go and sit outside
The tank with his hand on it
While tripping
And he didn't say anything
But he looked like he was beaming
Calm down trip guidance
Into the tank
And you picked up on it man
If you believe that sort of thing
You picked up on it
Personally I've found that when people
Get drunk as a lord on psychotomimicry
And they're on drugs
What they want to happen sometimes happen
Like them red lights on that phone
You think that might be Dave?
CSB
Hello
Man
CSB
Hey
That's not Dave
I'm not Dave dude
How you be?
It's Echo Man
Echo Man
Is this the ketamine dude?
You know it's me?
How you doin'?
Is this the disembodied spirit of Sam Phillips?
I don't know
Call back in a few minutes
Hello?
Yes who is it?
From PR News
This is week edition
I'm from Cimarron Kansas
Ha ha ha
And where you from?
Cimarron Kansas
I think you're from
Sssssssss sssssssss
Cimarron
Are you ready to play Let's Play?
Alright today's first word ends in O
Oh?
And the second word starts with O-R
Okay
Right number one is
A floor rug made into something you smoke
You might say
Whoa
Ahhh
Okay
The first word is pipe
Oooh
Oh, fuck.
You might say the first word is James Bond's zits.
Oh, sure.
You might say the first famous broadcaster of Japanese zits.
Nasty mouth.
You might say the first word improves old zits.
I enjoyed the tongue infection.
And your last one, a cry at a Washington Zit Ball game.
Ow!
You're a idiot!
You should have listened to me.
Goodbye.
Oh, thank you.
Watch her carefully.
Don't take your eyes off her.
All right.
Drop the gun.
So, let's look at Bob.
I use it almost every day of my life, even if just for a minute or two.
So, in something like one or two seconds, you've gotten the buzz going with the gentle inner's pure dynamite.
Believe me, you'll know it when you have it.
I don't know.
It might be pretty scary in there.
And you hold on to that as you're Bob.
And pump up that tender feeling coming from that smile until it just becomes.
Take off, joy life.
Do it.
And get that want motor revved up for wanting brings passion.
Passion brings.
Bob.
Brings more wanting, but also stake your claim for universal or intangible things such as.
I'm so sorry.
You're my boy.
Afterward, I knew the rules.
I understood what I was supposed to do, but I didn't.
I couldn't.
I was compelled to stay.
Compelled to disobey.
And now here I am.
I stand because of you.
Bob.
Because of you.
I am no longer an agent of this system.
I've changed.
I'm unplugged.
A new man.
So to speak.
Like you.
Apparently free.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Friends, you're floating in a sea of pills.
A sea of Bob's pills.
But you're just too blind yet to, done to see them.
Oh.
I'm not blind.
Oh, friends.
I know you're not the dumb-asticated type.
I know you're the smart-asticated type.
Oh, but people say, Reverend Stagg, what is slack?
I want you to tell me what slack is.
You know, friends, the television doesn't have to watch you as long as you are watching
the television.
And a lot of people, a lot of people think that slack is that Miller beer commercial
where everybody's good looking and you're rich and your team just won the game and you're
drinking Miller beer and your favorite show is on.
And you know that's bullshit because slack is not laziness, friends.
Slack is getting into the zone.
It's being awake and alert and doing what you wanted to do until your eyes snap open
and you're stuck.
That's good.
That's bad.
That's better than getting too wasted and trying toん going oops!
You know you've been here long enough longer than in my opinion because it's so boring
Mums!
I don't know if I have to say anything to you.
Please be nice.
I am in charge of your children from language and information, but this is fucking begging
It's not the right time to be sober
Now the idiots have taken over
Spreading like a social cancer
Is there an answer?
Mensa membership exceeding
Tell me why in hell are all the stupid people breeding?
Watchin' it's really elementary
The ingestible revolution
Has flipped the bitch on evolution
The benevolent and wise are being wanted out to size
What a bummer
The world keeps getting dumber
It's not the right time to be sober
The insensitivity is standard
And faith is being fancied over reason
It's always rolling over and it's toughening
Cause I think it starts surviving much less often
Now everything seems to be reversing
And it's worsening
Someone plopped a steamer in the gene pool
Now angry my mentality is no longer the exception it's the rule
And I'm starting to feel a lot like a fool now
Strong Heston
Stranded on a private planet
Apes and orangutans that ran into the ground
With generals and the armies that obeyed them
Followers following fables
Philosophies that enable them to rule without regard
There's no point for democracy when ignorance is celebrated
Political scientists get the same one vote as someone can talk in bread
Majority rule
Don't work in mental institutions
Sometimes the smallest, softest voice carries the grand
PG solutions
What are we left with?
A nation of God-fearing pregnant nationalists
Who feel it's their duty to populate the homeland
Pass on traditions
How to get ahead with legions
And prosperity via subaltern culture
The idiots have taken over
The Idiots have Taken Over
Do you want to help?
The Idiots have taken over
The idiots have taken over
The Idiots are takingover
The Idiots are taking over
No FX, friends, was the name of the band that did that.
Before that, me and ESO at XX Day in 1999 in Brushwood
with some clips from my cousin, Agent Smith,
from the Matrix Rebloated.
And the Bob Meditation Collage was by Reverend Jartow.
Now, friends, you understand that Bob, J.R. Bob Dobbs, replaces drugs.
This church is often misunderstood in that respect,
especially by the man and idiots
who glean everything they know only from surface appearances.
But, as you well know,
appearances can be deceiving,
which brings me back to the reason why we're here.
We're not here because we're free.
We're here because we're not free.
There's no escaping reason, no denying purpose,
because as we both know, without purpose, we would not exist.
It is purpose that created us.
Purpose that connects us.
Purpose that pulls us.
That guides us.
That drives us.
It is purpose that defines.
Purpose that binds us.
Can I have some?
Uh, can I get you a cup of coffee?
Yes.
Or, um, some water?
No, no, thank you.
This is good coffee.
It tastes awfully good.
The hot in the world of me?
That's torture.
Yeah.
I mean, you have this totally unbelievable life-altering sex,
and then you just disappear.
I mean, you stop drinking coffee.
I know, I know.
I had to go get coffee.
God!
Is this Johnny Pops?
There's a lot of people who are like,
Oh, there's a new movie about Napoleon.
Oh, wait, no, I thought that was my alter ego.
No!
This new movie about Napoleon.
That's my alter ego.
And he's played by Ian Johnny Potts.
Oh, yeah.
Johnny Potts, from Meet Napoleon.
Wow, cool!
Oh, didn't they already do this in Bill and Ted's, uh,
Excellent Adventure, and, uh, you know, in that Terry Gilliam movie?
Why Johnny can't smoke pot?
Why Johnny Cash smokes pot?
I knew Johnny Cash smoked pot, though.
He doesn't know how to do it.
He's so big.
Um, okay, uh, let's backtrack a little bit and make sure that we're on the same page.
I wouldn't want to be at cross purposes.
Cannabis or us?
You haven't heard of that, no.
Hey, Neil, we're gonna have to kill Johnny Potts, mate.
No.
I want each and every one of you Johnny Potts smokers on air.
Johnny on the spot.
What?
To what?
Or Johnny on the closet.
The call of lost control.
He comes out, and we'll smoke some more.
I'm James Salyer.
I'm the guy that's been working on the briefest of fogs.
I'm going to have to go sit somewhere else.
I'm going to have to go to Harrison.
Yes?
Have a nice day.
Have a new day.
Yes.
Down the road I look, and there runs Mary.
Green, green, pair of black cherries.
It's good to choke the green, green grass of home.
Yes, they're all home.
Farm livin' is the life for me
Land spreadin' out so far and wide
Keep Manhattan, just give me that countryside
guitar solo
The charge
The stars
Fresh air
Times Square
guitar solo
New York is where I'd rather stay
I get allergic smellin' hay
I just adore a penthouse view
guitar solo
Darling, I love you, but give me Park Avenue
You are my way
guitar solo
I said goodbye city life
Green Acres, we are there
Green Chems here tonight
j knew you was a sweet little thing
I always knew
Green Acres, there's no other place
I'd like another getaway
you can be along just hangin' around
Even if you stay out here
together with your cell phone
You're my lass
This and his present always feel in a fizzling.
Hey.
Hey, Andy.
Oh, hi, Goof.
Andy, I've got to talk to you.
We're just having supper.
Would you like something to eat?
Oh, no.
Anything?
No, no, no, thank you.
Well, let's have our certain coffee in the living room.
No, no, I'll get it.
Hey, hey, everybody.
Hi, Goof.
Goof.
You know that's funny.
Well, I'll...
Shows what greed will do.
Oh, yes.
Changes a person completely.
Oh, that makes a lot of sense.
Yep.
Yes.
Shows what greed will do.
Right, Andy?
Yeah, well...
What time you got?
Well, come back.
I'll be going.
Shows what greed will do.
Hey!
If you are a loved one,
have taken my alliance
and have developed
bravo.
Bravo.
You may be entitled
to a potentially fatal
muscle disease.
Call 3966
369-
Thank you for purchasing
your pharmaceuticals.
Is your co-payment ready?
Bob is my co-payment.
We do not accept
Bob as a co-payment.
Will you accept Connie?
No.
I'm sorry.
Well, what will you accept?
We accept
orange plastic dildos.
Damn.
I'm fresh out of dodi.
Do you have any slack tokens?
I have a dead cat.
We do not accept dead cat
as co-payments.
My tumor has gotten bigger.
My best friend is a tumor.
Would you like to touch it?
Well, can I?
That feels good.
It is green.
I am very proud of it.
You should be.
Would you accept a chunk?
As a co-payment?
Yes.
Sure.
Have a nice day.
Thank you very much.
Heart Ignition did that.
The HMO is a great company.
It is called the HMO Fiasco.
A little while before that, Green Haze was by Elvis Hitler.
And everything else around it was cut up by Mr. Fernando Andelemer.
Now a cut up by Baran, whoever that is really.
I got it off of Binary Slack.
Featuring Terence McKenna from the new album Conversations at the Edge of Magic, which
was recorded at Slate.
It is available at Starwood and is available at through www.Rosencomet.com the ACE website.
Oh, I should mention this background music is by Hell Pope Huey.
And now Terence McKenna.
And here is my answer to this riddle.
Where did human consciousness come from?
It began.
It begins like this.
The vacuum, byğim.
And in highly sexed animals small amounts of psilocybin mushrooms would
have naturally been eaten.
And blamed by Extraterrestrial scientific proof.
There are no þo girocephalic anyone was ever exclude.
In small amounts of psilocybin, orarzci走吧 di daetos y enzim preservatives, theynosis
partiasi iq advertisement mosca eae paquial corpati.
ول
And so you see, my young friend, here we have a case where the use of drugs actually introduces
us to a more true vision of reality than if we have avoided the drug.
Some of these we take in highly sexed animals, small amounts of psilocybin mushrooms, and
an exotic pseudo neurotransmitter.
Is that when you take slightly larger doses of psilocybin, and that is the psilocybin containing
mushrooms that grow in the dung of cattle.
Mommy!
Whip me up a plosive bee, I'm about to lose my noodle.
I'm getting spiritual now.
I've taken all the pills I can take.
I feel so relaxed now, but I certainly don't look forward to what I have to do.
And if you don't want to, I'm going to have to go to the hospital.
You can kiss me if you want to.
I just want to do this little thing projects, putting on some clothes and his
my eyes at a track.
You know, my left foot is my pillow.
And I'm a law abider
There's nothing I like more than getting fired up on beer
And when the weekend's here
I exercise my right to get paralytic and fight
Good bloke, fairly
But I get well, Larry, when geezers look at me funny
Bounce them round like bunnies
I'm likely to cause mischief
Good clean grief, you must believe
And I ain't no thief
Law abiding and all, all legal
And who cares about my liver when it feels good
What you need's some real manhood
Rasher, rasher, burning catcher
Putting people's backs up
Public disorder, I'll give you public disorder
A down eight pints and run all over the place
Spit in the face of an officer
See if that bothers ya
Cause I never broke a law in my life
Someday I'm gonna settle down with a wife
Go on lads, let's have another fight
My name's Tim and I'm a criminal
In the eyes of society I need to be in jail
For the choice of herbs I inhale
This ain't no wholesale operation
Just a few eights and some playstations, my vocation
I pose a threat to the nation
And down the station
The police hold no patience
Let's talk space and time
I like to get deep sometimes
And think about Einstein
And Carl Jung
And old kung fu movies I like to see
Pass the hydrator please
Pffft, yeah I'm floating on thin air
Going to Amsterdam in the new year
Top gear there
Cause I take pride in my hobby
I home make bongs using my engineering degree
Dear leaders, please legalise weed for these reasons
Like I was saying to him
I told him
Spock with me and you won't live
So I smacked him in the head and downed an old man's head
Part of the cahling
Badda badda bing
Full of that's like
Mad fight
His face a sad sight
Vodka and snakebite
Going on like a right geez
Ease a twat
Shouldn't have looked at me like that
Anyway
I'm an upstanding citizen
If a war came along I'd be on the front line with em
Can't stand crime either
Them hooligans on heroin
Drugs and criminal
Those thugs are the pinnacle of the downfall of society
I've got all the anger pent up inside of me
No, I don't see why I should be the criminal
How can something we know recorded first
Fatalities be illegal.
And how many deaths are there per year from alcohol?
I just completed Gran Turismo on the hardest setting.
We pose no threat on my settee.
Oh, the pizza's here. Will someone let him in, please?
We didn't order chicken. Not a problem. We'll pick it out.
I doubt they're meant to mess us about.
After all, we're all adults, not louts.
As I was saying, we're friendly, peaceful people.
We're not the ones out there causing trouble.
We just sit in this hazy bubble with our quarters,
discussing how beautiful Gail Porter is.
It's MTV, BBC Two, Channel Four is on until six in the morning.
Then six in the morning, the sun dawns and it's my bedtime.
Causing trouble? You're stinking rabble, boys.
Saying I'm the lad who's spoiling it.
You're on drugs.
Really bugs me when people try and tell me I'm a thug.
Just for getting drunk. I like getting drunk.
Because I'm an upstanding citizen.
If the war came along, I'd be on the front line with them.
Now, Terry, you're repeating yourself.
But that's OK. Drunk people can't help that.
A chemical reaction happening inside your brain
causes you to forget.
What you're saying.
What? I know exactly what I'm saying.
I'm perfectly sane.
You stinking student lame-o.
Go get a job and stop robbing us of our taxes.
Well, actually, according to research,
government funding for further education pales in insignificance
when compared to how much they spend on repairing
a layer of drunk people at the weekend
and casualty wards all over the land.
Why you seeking it? I'm spying. Come here.
I'm going to batter you. Come here.
The irony of it all by The Street's
original pirate material.
And now, a live revival recording
from 5X Day in London, England.
Yes, where Pope David Lee Black
can be heard performing a healing.
Now each, now a sub-genius church service
would not be complete
unless we had a what?
What's that?
We gotta have a healing.
And if we can't have a healing,
we gotta have a sickening.
Is there anybody in the audience
who has a problem, have an ailment?
This, that something bothering you?
Somebody, somebody's gotta...
You, sir.
There must be someone as sick as me.
Yes, sir. We have one.
Sir, sir, tell me.
Tell me, what's ailing you?
At the moment, I've got chronic alcoholism.
Did you hear that?
He has chronic alcoholism.
Well, I've got some good news for you.
We have a, we have a, we have a cure for that.
I want you to close your eyes.
Alcoholism is an ailment.
It's a blessing from God.
We have this holy elixir here.
Fear.
Obstinacy.
I want you to drink it.
When you, when you've had it, come on, drink it.
Drink it all.
Hey, this ain't, this is a, a church of excess,
not a church of obstinacy.
Come on, drink it.
Come on.
Drink it.
Get your fucking neck.
Get your down your fucking neck.
Woo!
I'm drunk.
I'm going through this.
He's an alcoholic, my friends.
Bob has rubber stamped his alcoholism.
Yeah!
This is whiskey for Bob!
Whiskey for Bob.
Whiskey for Bob!
Woo!
I'm not afraid.
I like it out there.
You wouldn't believe me.
No!
He defies all the laws of man and God.
There may be an entirely new set of laws, Jim, that we know nothing about.
Come out and say what you mean.
I'm only guessing.
Sall I sing in my yard.
Come by y'all.
Sawa and Sene Marlon
Kumbaya
Oh Lord Kumbaya
I'll believe the world once paid
With your majestic
It's a New Year cackling hand
Your people I do not understand
So do you my Shambhala
Shambhala
A place we all believe
That someday will take us away
A place of refuge
With every dark feeling
That grows within us
An understanding develops
Someday
In Shambhala
We shall fight them with sticks and toads
We shall bring them down
And squish them with our mighty mortars
We shall pray to them
On altars of cheese and peanuts
And sing while the devils dance
Around us
Ah Shambhala
What was that about fighting them with sticks and toads?
Just exactly what kind of toads are you talking about?
Mystic toads my friend
I am talking about mystic toads
The kind that drip from your cerebellum
When you are stinking in your sleep
Everybody loves the hypno toad
Oh yeah of course
But I don't think that's what you're talking about
No I wasn't talking senor
I was just informing you
How it's going to go down
Over the next 25 years or so
The world's in a collision course
With it's own self see
Prophecy
Obviously
The earth and the moon shall come together
And have unnatural sex
Like a priest and a school boy
Children shall all be born
With a third nostril
Very very visible
To those practitioners of the church
Of the evil Sabianians
This man
Is absolutely dangerous
Do you realize how many children
Are out there probably looking at this program
And you're telling them
It's not dangerous to use drugs
I can name you 15 people
On crack
Crack cocaine alone
And my stepson
Got on it
And he is in prison
The child was a
Good Christian man
And he got on cocaine
And he is in prison
For stealing
Because he's a Christian man
Because he could not
Support his habit
And these children out here
Are listening to you man
Cannot compare alcohol
Alcohol is addictive
Cigarettes are addictive
Nobody should do none of them
Don't compare drugs with alcohol
And say that it's alright
The government sell alcohol
And it's not alright to sell drugs
You're dangerous man
And the fellows that fell down
A double latte
To hell
All the way down to hell
It has milk in it
They bounced on the leaves
The acid
And took the acid
And then fell
Faster faster
Falling freely
Into the abyss
Into the deep deep dark abyss
Into which
The psychedelic
Sounds
The linoleum and fluorescent lights
Make me feel so
Much like sitting down
At this little table
And then there was
Thousands and thousands
Of cockroaches
Swarming
Seeking out the
Female view
While I scope out the action
At this mall
Here in the puzzling
Evidence of states
Stretching and sprawling
Over mile after mile
Of reconquerable hell
They were stolen from them
But Bob
But what happens
When high altitude
Air force planes
Split the sky
With a glowing contrast
Bob paid for the
Return of your orgasm
With his self
With his pain
Oh Bob didn't have anything
To do with that file
88888888888888
Hello you're on
Am I just doing this
For the benefit of
Some other doobie dealer
Well but you're under
No obligation
To go to the dealer
Yeah
I'm asking 170 bucks
Don't forget
That they will
Break things
for free.
Okay.
Alrighty, bye-bye.
Good luck.
Yeah.
Jesus.
What a stupid
f***ing home now.
No.
And speaking of
enjoying things,
who can leave out
the very basis
for our faith?
Our famous,
most holy,
and revered world
without end
reason for life.
The Brinsky's
Nuclear Bear.
It's the same
as the fine amphetamines
you are surely
familiar with.
It allows us to do
our vastly needed work
for the economy
and expands our awareness
that we may fully
appreciate the wonders
that our hard-working
bozo leaders
have provided us.
And we are generously
allowed injections
five times a day.
It helps us
mature faster.
Our eldest citizens
are 25.
Like football?
Well, wait till you see
the war against Mars.
The finest teenage
champions
have been bred
for these gala celebrations
which keep alive
the tradition
of skillful combat.
Colorful but simple,
rugged but rewarding
both to winners
and losers,
it's just like
the good old days.
A grueling test
of stamina
with two entire
players to support.
Watch our Earth team
fight for our
Binsky's
which those
Martians
just can't do without.
Whoops,
looked like that
Martian won't score.
Sorry Mars.
What anti-drug
film are we
in?
I don't know.
I'm not sure.
Which drug?
Which drug are they
trying to warn us against?
That's what I'm...
Dave, are you
handing out...
Those are...
Man, that's not medicine?
Yes, these are.
Or candy?
It's red medicine.
These are communist
medicine.
Those are Martian pellets.
These are...
Oh my God,
these are Martian pellets.
Little red children
orphaned Martian children
from Mars
that came in
after the war.
Oh, wow.
Which war?
The ones that lost
their antenna.
The war against Mars.
The beer war.
Oh, I thought you meant
the dinosaur war.
Remember the sperm for beer
and all that?
Yeah.
See, I totally forgot
about that one.
I remember the dinosaur war.
I used to forget about it.
I remember when Carter
was there, you know,
Carter of Mars.
Yeah, Carter.
Jimmy Carter of Mars.
Those were the days.
Fort of Jupiter.
The really advanced
presidents were
like over men
and they were highly
trained in the mystic arts
and could expel
a pineapple
from their...
The nether regions.
They didn't need armies.
With unchewed
and undigested.
They could swallow it down
and expel it a day later
completely whole.
Bringing the entire village
good luck.
And then they could make...
Garfield could do that.
And making smoothies
for all of them.
In fact, how do you think
Garfield won the 1884
Transcendental Reerections?
Right, right.
Because, you know,
Ohio is the father
and the bad mofo
of presidents.
There was a boy
Very strange and
Chanting
They say
Wonderberry
For
Overland
Sea
A little
Child
And said
I was
Very wise
Was evil
I got an idea
I had a plan
to grow in you
Before the outdoor
was to be recreated
Do you believe
I was implicated
in a grow room
Wanted to produce
the kind of plant
that you could display
up in a showroom
So beautiful but yet
Stinky
Stick to your thumb
Index
Little ring
Pinky
And the brain
So the first thing
was to provide
setting for proper
cultivation
Discrete location
10 by 10 foot spot
Lit up by a thousand
watt lamp
Plus two air vents
for the air to circulate
And um
I calculate
30 gallons of water
Oh we um
Really into this
Now all I need
is some good fertilizer
And some photosynthesis
To proceed
After I choose
The right seeds
It's all in motion
With a little
Love and devotion
I can make
the front cover
of high times
I hope I never get
Busted and have to
pay some fines
For having a
Secret garden
Like Barry White
I must not tell anyone
And keep my lips
still tight
I got the grow
If you ain't never
had the homegrown
It made you choke
Put your hands
in the air
And say no
And if you're high
already
You can't take
another toke
Put your hands
in the air
And say no
I got the grow
During the first
stage of growth
The seeds germinate slow
Start a root system
Sprout up some leaves
And grow
Towards the light
Make sure the temperature's right
I was told by this fun guy
Watch your plants
closely
You're aware of bugs
and fungi
The hurt your garden
They only interfere
with the vegetative growth
That lasts about
two months to a year
When full grown
flowers bloom
Big buds and leaves
Watch out for these
People like to
stash it up their sleeves
It's now been three months
I'm tempted to break off
a piece and roll some blunts
I wonder what it is
Is this some skunk?
I see some purple stems
and orange hairs
Could it be the humble
mixed with Maui?
It's a hybrid
Wow
Look what I did
I got the green thumb
Observe the superb herb
Bushy branches loud
Smell light green pastel
I got it on deck
For a new year
And if anyone asks
it's for medical use
I got the growth
If you ain't never
had a homegrown
that paid you choke
Put your hands
in the air
Zen note
And if you're high already
you can't take another coat
Put your hands
in the air
Zen note
If you ain't never
had a homegrown
that paid you choke
Put your hands
in the air
Zen note
And if you're high already
you can't take another coat
Put your hands
in the air
Zen note
It's been over
four months
Time to get high
Uphroot the plants
and let the
Let them hang dry in a cool room with dry air for two to three weeks.
And I'ma be waiting right here with my loose leaf sheets to lovely harvest.
It came in different amounts.
Four trees, each one just a few grams shorter than ours.
I can't wait to smoke it.
I know this bomb.
Been waiting so long.
Make me want to write a song.
I guess I'll sell two ounces and puff on the rest.
Find a recipe to sprinkle herb on my filet of chicken breast.
Or some tea chalk for the THC.
Hit the bomb.
Cut open and swish it sweet.
Then come off on me.
Man, it's stuck to my fingertips as I try to break it down.
It went limp.
The food is earthy.
The taste is profound.
They have me buzzing for a light here.
And you best believe I'll have some seeds.
And be at it again.
Yes, indeed.
If you ain't ever had a homegrown, they made you choke.
Put your hands in the air and say no.
And if you're high already, you can't take another choke.
If you ain't ever had a homegrown, they made you choke.
Put your hands in the air and say no.
And if you're high already, you can't take another choke.
I got the bull.
Put your hands in the air and say no.
Grow Room by DJ Pooh.
And Mr.
Grim.
And before that, Nature Boy.
That very strange piece was by Artemia Salina.
Hi, this is Jeff.
It won't take the government to interrupt our food supply.
There are scores of other man-made disasters like a comet or an asteroid impact
that will do the job just as quickly.
Are you prepared for relief agencies to get contaminated food and water to you in a major crisis?
One phone call and a food counselor will come right to your face.
You'll be able to save your family in times of disaster.
And by then, it might well be 1953.
Call right now.
Free.
Force Food.
24 hours a day.
The wait. Force Food.
Is over.
Dr. Louis Therese is now available.
Nostradamus gave splints.
You're all ruled by the power of the Truthseeker Company.
24 hours a day.
Alright, go ahead.
Yes, sir.
Oh.
Who's that?
It's Micah, Paul.
That's what I was afraid of.
Micah.
I can smell you.
Well, I haven't had much breakfast.
The years haven't erased your stink.
No, we volunteered to take a bath.
Alright.
Turn around.
Nice and easy.
Oh, go ahead.
Hold it, mister.
Throw that marshal down with your hands up.
Oh, boy, this is awful.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Awful.
Uh, I'll, uh, I'll see you later.
Oh, no.
Don't leave me for so long.
Oh, my dear, a female dear.
Little day.
That you bring us back to norm.
Can you get to it?
Can you get to it, baby?
It's not so far away as the crow flies.
But like a giant bird, it can gulf space like a breath.
Oh, yeah, that'll take you there in no time.
Hyper, hyper, hyperspace.
But the back of your cerebral cortex passing away.
You've taken too much, you've taken too much, you've taken too much.
You sit and watch the evening news in a trance, pissing your pants.
You think there's a man outside with a gun or a knife ready to take your life.
And he sits there waiting for you, behind the wall outside of your view.
Your neighbor hears you screaming tonight that you're too busy.
He's smoking, yes, God.
Too bad your mama found out.
Supposed to be something, not a target for a shot.
Downtown, there's a room upstairs where nobody cares.
You can yell all night.
He got picked up at the bus stop.
Had to get away, they had his DNA.
How many broken bodies fit inside the trolley?
Your baby's mama is...
Crying tonight.
But you're too busy smoking, yes, God.
Too bad the bottom dropped out.
Too bad your mama found out.
Oh!
And that was by CD Truth from the CE Chemically Dependent.
Their name is like the object CD.
And in fact, you can check out www.cdtruth.com.
That's a C and a D and truth, all one word.
And now more no effects.
Thank you.
No second chance.
No guiding light.
I never meant to cause you pain.
I never thought I'd be the one who took the fall.
I got lost in the moment.
Assholes like to test the limit.
Six minutes down.
Breathing machine.
Brain not feel right.
The look on you.
Is killing me.
Drowning in shame.
But don't feel bad.
Cause I never feared consequences.
Hate regrets more than apologies.
A year has passed.
Like photographs.
My life is just.
A scrapbook of.
Old friends and faded memories.
Looks like I pulled the rug from under myself.
The fall's too much for me to recover from.
It's been real fun.
But now I must say goodbye.
I'll see you when I'm gone.
Good riddance, nasally.
I'll make it go.
Oh, he's friends.
Says the hor ere.
I'm going bananas!
Yeah.
We'll have aaya job on.
I don't.
too soon, did he?
I wonder.
Men, friends, you have been listening to
the Hour of Slack from the Church
of the Subgenius. For more information,
see www.subgenius.com
www.subgenius.com
And, or,
you can actually email me,
stang at subgenius.com
Praise
Abe.
Well,
I've told you before that I will not tolerate
brutality in this penitentiary.
Here, here, stop that.
I'm sorry.
Next, ma'am.
Yes.
Oh, I knew there was a catch in it.
One last spurt of cleavage
produces two diploid ribosomes,
each carrying half the plans
for a new worm. Hopefully,
not the same half.
Finally convinced that they are, indeed,
of the same species,
they hesitantly begin pairing.
They combine to become one
single blasphemula,
which makes a last tug of mycotic cell
division, and voila!
There are now two worms where there
once was one.
But, what becomes of them now?
We'll learn not only that,
but also why the peen worm is so
crucial to our nuclear beer,
and even the Martian War
in Series 9.