The Strange Doctor Weird.
Good evening. Come in, won't you?
Why, what's the matter? You seem a bit nervous.
Perhaps the cemetery outside this house has upset you.
But there are things far worse than cemeteries.
For instance...
The Self-Genius Power of Swag.
All right, fellas, here's your story.
A man by the name of Bob once saved our world with an arc of electricity.
Bob is recovering from wounds received in the battle.
He's got a broken carbone and a bad headache.
Good.
And now, before giving you the details of the battle,
I bring you...
a warning.
Every one of you listening to Bob,
tell the world.
Tell this to everybody, wherever they are.
Under no circumstances take action against Bob.
Watch Bob.
Watch out, he's got a gun!
Keep looking.
Watch.
Keep watching Bob.
Fuck you, man.
Hey, anybody around here want some coffee?
No.
Nothing counts except Bob.
Watch it.
Anybody want some coffee?
No.
Then just shut up.
Watch it.
Mm-hmm.
Right, you hayseys, it's a stick-up!
Everybody freeze.
Everybody down on the ground.
Well, which is it, young fella?
You want I should freeze or get down on the ground?
You mean to say, if I freeze, I can't rightly drop?
And if I drop, I'm gonna be in motion.
You see...
Shut up!
Okay, then.
Now for our next experiment.
Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob.
Bob.
Ee-bee-slash.
War zombie.
No.
I'll be alright.
I got the door braced good and there's no outside windows.
But because this would be a great headlining act, of course, it's kinda limited, but it
would pack him in, and all I've got to say, no, no, this isn't a gag.
Folks, I'm telling you, this is a...
No, no, no.
And so, the beginning of the monster movie itself.
It's Incense Around, Super Eastman Cinefile,
Super Sit Around,
Dinerama,
and Todd AO.
Really?
Okay, I got so worked up from that last caller's call
that I had to go out and have some ice water.
3D digitally projected bunion cream.
Yes, there it all is.
Zipping off the silvery steam with 272 woofers and tweeters
stapled to the back of the fat man.
Whoa, look what I found.
Here we go.
Well, you tell me what's the purpose in this.
You tell me what's the sense, what's the good of it.
Get lost.
A tale told by an idiot full of sound.
And fury signifying.
Bob?
How do you suppose that happened?
Oh.
Cheat, yeah?
Goodbye.
Oh, wait a minute.
Nice going, Bob.
I was down in Australia when the Waco debacle ended.
The fiery inferno.
Which we all saw.
And I was really bummed I was not here for it
because I thought it was the most fascinating news story of the year.
Bar none.
And everyone was so pissed off.
And I was like, I'm not going to talk about that guy
because he called himself Jesus.
And I was saying, come on.
The guy's real name is Vernon.
Let him be Jesus for a couple of months.
What's it to ya?
Who's going to follow a messiah named Vernon anyway, you know?
You got to call yourself Jesus.
It's sort of part of the messiah deal.
And Vernon spoke and he spaketh and he sayeth.
You know what?
Let's go get some beer.
Wee!
You know, Vernon.
Just didn't have the necessary speech.
I'm not going to talk about that.
I'm going to talk about the spiritual weight that I'm looking for.
But anyway, isn't that weird too how everyone snaps in our country and thinks they're Jesus?
How come no one ever snaps and thinks they're Buddha?
Particularly in America where more people resemble Buddha than Jesus.
I'm Buddha.
You're Bubba.
I'm Buddha now.
All I got to do is change two letters on my belt.
Bubba.
Buddha.
Vernon's a false prophet.
Isn't that weird though?
You know, and all this is funny.
It's real funny because these Australians had a big contingency in the compound that burned down.
And they were of course curious.
And I'm from Texas.
And I actually went to the compound the seventh day of the siege because it was right outside of Austin.
And I went to it.
But these people in Australia were like, oh, Bill, isn't he such an oddball?
Isn't he so odd?
He's such a strange character.
And I'm thinking, well, let's think about this.
Frustrated rock guitarist with a messianic complex, armed to the teeth, trying to fuck everything in skirts.
I don't know how to tell you all this.
But it sounds like every one of my friends.
I'm waiting for the Eric Johnson compound to come out, you know.
I don't know.
I don't think Eric's frustrated.
But anyway.
And they said, you know, they had to break down the compound because child abuse was stepping up.
Well, that's true.
How come we don't see Bradley tanks knocking down Catholic churches?
You know, I mean, if in fact child abuse is your concern.
Actually, folks, I don't know if any of you all have seen this.
It's a tape kind of bootleg going around of showing film of the Bradley tanks not knocking, as the official story was, small holes to insert tear gas.
But crashing the building off of its fucking foundation and fire shooting out of the tanks.
The FBI and the ATF are liars and murderers.
And Janet Reno and President Clinton either A, knowingly passed on a lie, or B, are so out of touch with their own fucking arms or their government that they're incompetent and Clinton should be impeached immediately.
Case fucking closed.
And you all have probably seen the footage.
But it's sort of different than the official story, isn't it?
Small holes, tear gas, giant holes, flamethrowers.
They burn these people in their homes.
Okay.
That's our government.
I've seen the tape.
And I don't know.
It's fucking real.
And whatever.
Make your own conclusions.
You haven't seen it.
So it's, you know, whatever.
But old Clint, you know, I have no illusions about these cocksuckers.
I know there's 12 guys who run the fucking world.
And they own every company.
And, you know, it's fact.
You can look it up.
I'm not a conspiracy nut.
This is all on paper.
There really are 22 families who run and own 50% of the mainstream media, which is where we get our news.
And it's true.
It's a fact.
You can look it up.
I don't know.
You know, I can't be this big of an asshole without having the truth to back me up.
Otherwise, I'd be a fucking nut doing this.
But, see, if you have the truth with you, you can do this.
Gee, I'm starting to sound like Koresh, aren't I?
Fuck.
People have often said I remind them of Koresh.
I'm like Koresh, only without the guns or pussy.
So, basically, I'm just an annoying fellow.
But, uh, and frustrated rock guitarist, too.
I'm just an annoying fellow.
What's up with that?
Dog poop.
No one's a viper without a cap.
You're just told to use a knife.
I think I'm a bitelse now that you're reading a book.
It's not safe
Oh, hey, guy.
Instead of saying I'm telling it all, to hear you talk about it, you know.
Well, we can't you talk.
What you won't bet that all you gotta do
Is open up your eyes and you'll wake up screaming
And you realize that it's all come true
Hush now, don't you believe it
Cover your head and close your eyes now
Take it or leave it, go back to bed now
Don't you cry
Half a million soldiers fly across the water
One in ten never coming back again
Fifty thousand sons that never grew to fathers
Don't you ever wonder who they might have been
Oh
What if you could have been there on that day in Dallas
What if you could wrestle back the hands of time
Maybe something could have been done in Memphis
We wouldn't be living in a dreamless life
Hush now, don't you believe it
Cover your head and close your eyes now
Take it or leave it, go back to bed now
Hush now, don't you cry
Don't turn me down
And my magic will let you hear this
iPod
Put down your keyboard
Alarm bell
Chop chop chop chop chop
secrets go on tell yourself that you don't want to know it's best that you believe you don't hear
the footsteps that follow you around no matter where you go maybe you were thinking that it
didn't matter maybe you believe nobody else will care but once you've added every little lie
together you finally find the truth
it should be painfully obvious to everyone around us by now that you know we're nearing
the end times for sure now it's not just really okay we're getting closer to the end times
what are you doing about it you're still going to work or school coming home
doing your job you're still going to work you're still going to work you're still going to work
watching the war all day film archives what will happen to your routine when all the
comes down on us at once what are you going to do then
don't you feel responsible for trying to help this endangered planet
no good fact is it's too late anyway so you know you just need to have a good time and look for
the place where you can get the most slack
we know where that is
such childish small tiny children
now a little good christian as one half pulled it out of his bosom and began to try
now one half amazed break out break out break out pass from giant wreck bosom
pluck it out of thy bosom and try
from heaven
overthrow
from myself
stu has known asking brother
to dramatic
considerably larger and her
uh... we're active
the place of the story shot begin daily
understand or know
spent on we're growing babies you don't miss Elijah
I
are you going to become
all at one time
the
that
but even however also answered
will this last week
map
program
I think we've just seen the antechamber to terror.
We haven't even begun to see what we can do to the major population.
God has got to take a lot of blame for this.
Let Christ be hanged.
And I know I'll hear from them for this,
but God has got to bear some burden for this because God will not be mocked.
And when we destroy 40 million little innocent Democrats and Republicans,
God will point the thing in their face.
In other words, I point the thing in their face and say,
you pagans, you abortionists, the feminists throwing little innocent babies out of the school,
down the steps of the school, the pagans.
Jesus knows everything about you.
The abortionists.
He knows who you are.
The feminists.
Where you live.
The gays and the lesbians.
Everything you've done.
Tried to secularize America.
So there's no sense in trying to hide.
All of them.
You might as well confess it.
You've got to take a lot of blame for this.
In other words, God has got to take a lot of blame for this.
As I fought off the enemy of a fifth adopter of modern evangelism,
this is our victory.
So God said,
Yo, brother, you're talking about most of my relatives.
Well, yeah.
Let me challenge you as to the validity of your salvation.
I want the babies in their face and say,
you babies, you helped this happen.
And I know I made the gays mad.
I really destroyed the nation on its knees.
Examine yourself and see if you're in the faith.
We're totally Christ haters.
Pat, did you notice yesterday,
Democrats and Republicans,
God lifestyle,
as they called out to God in prayer and sang,
God,
let the ACLU be hanged.
Let the ACLU be hanged.
Amen.
I saw Jesus in the morning in the burning bush.
I saw Jesus in the afternoon too.
I saw Jesus at dinner time,
shoving the stone.
That Jesus is everywhere.
I saw Jesus in the morning in the burning bush.
I saw Jesus in the afternoon too.
I saw Jesus at dinner,
swimming in the stew.
That Jesus is everywhere.
Jesus down by the river bed.
Jesus laying down by me.
Jesus came into me.
Jesus by the river bed.
Jesus laid down by me
Jesus by the riverbed
Jesus came into me
I saw Jesus in the morning in the burning bush
I saw Jesus in the afternoon too
I saw Jesus at dinnertime swimming in the stew
Jesus is everywhere
You know, Boogie Boy, who used to be the Devil Boy
has been reborn
and he's coming out tonight, people.
He is here tonight
and he is coming to sing with Devil.
Hi there, Long Beach.
You know,
we used to do Devil music
like that band Devo.
But then,
Jerry over here,
he sat down on a Bobby Dylan record
and the Lord came into him
and now we do music alone.
Hey!
You might be an ambassador
to England or France
You might like to gamble
You might like to dance
You might be the heavyweight
champion of the world
You might be a socialite
with a long string of pearls
But you gotta serve somebody
Yes, you've got to serve somebody
Well, it may be the Devil
Or it may be the Lord
But you gotta serve somebody
Well, you might be a punk rocker
Dancing on the stage
Money, drugs at your command
Women in a cage
You might be a businessman
A high-colonic freak
They might call you a freak
They might call you a doctor
And they might call you chief
But you gotta serve somebody
Serve somebody
Yes, you've got to serve somebody
Well, it might be the Devil
And it might be the Lord
But you gotta serve somebody
Serve somebody
Well, you might be a state trooper
Or another kind of jerk
You might be the president
Of some new country
Or a big TV network
You might be rich or poor
You might be blind or lame
You might be living in another country
And there needs another name
But you gotta serve somebody
Serve somebody
Yes, you've gotta serve somebody
Well, it might be the Devil
Or it might be the Lord
But you gotta serve somebody
Serve somebody
Forgive somebody
Throw a pile out before dark
Save somebody, boogy
Thrust a chainsaw
Thank you.
Praise God, brothers and sisters!
The important thing, friends, is, it's like, what is this subgenius thing all about?
What is the important thing that distinguishes a subgenius?
From a human being?
The ability to with-read the coolness in Bob's face.
That's all it is!
We all have a different definition.
If you start asking somebody, some subgenius, what they believe in,
you'll get a different answer from each one.
But the one thing they all have in common,
at some point, they looked at Bob's face and said,
that guy's cool.
I don't know why.
Maybe he's kitschy, maybe he's calf.
Maybe he really just looks good looking.
Maybe he really looks like your dad.
Maybe it's simply that he is Bob!
And that face is the center of the luck plane!
Why not?
Does anything else make any more sense, really, when you get down to it?
Math, maybe, but then that breaks down on the quantum level, so...
You know, is there any way to truly have slack?
There's an old prayer, a subgenius prayer, by Reverend Lemuel Atom, that goes,
Dobbs, grant me the serenity to endure the pinks and humans I cannot kill,
the courage to stuff the ones I can, and the wisdom not to do it when the cops are around.
Praise Bob!
Woo!
Bob!
Is it we have left?
Chameleons?
What?
They don't even know one.
This one's so living, like my turf.
Was this true, so now they hope you can smash cool and walk down the weed of financial heaven?
He's no one in the ocean with my sea slack.
Praise Bob!
The man's a frog.
I'm a hopping toad in the mud of the freaking Valkyries of Siegfried.
Hey, he's a real man.
He's a giant man.
He's Paul Bunyan.
Well, I'm going to get that accident and Bob, and Bob, and Bob's a real man.
I'm living in a...
When are you going to let me out of this spot?
You know, Bob is like the Elvis of gurus.
Have you ever thought about it that way?
Yes, since he has left the building.
But he keeps reappearing.
People know that he lives up there in Minnesota somewhere in a trailer park disguised as a
garbage carrier.
Only just to collect the rent periodically, to take from those who no longer receive the
slaking of their spiritual thirst, they are preyed upon by Bob's sloth and lethargy.
Lesson two tells us conservation and transmutation. He is sluggish and slow.
Really the tropical Bob is? Tropical, topical, popsicle Bob is just the same
slowness and sluggishness.
This is a place for crazy people. I'm not crazy. We don't use that
term crazy, Mr. Cole. We've got some real nuts here. Come out, come out, wherever you are.
You say you don't know Bob, but I know you.
Honey, why there ain't nothing to it. All you got to do is bee bop.
Bee bop, bee bop, bee bop, bee bop bee bee bop bee bee bop.
At last it's come down to this now, the final do it yourself in times relive.
Capital A.
For swinging mutants and terminal abnormals.
S H.
Even though people like Bob's slugging is not always good, it's a good thing.
You morons know these are the end times.
Welcome to the end times.
But Reverend Hal, Reverend Hal.
S H.
People ask this question of me all the time. Do I really need to remain entirely human any longer?
I'm sorry, your humanity must be abnegated and proscribed. For in the wonder world of tomorrow, it will no longer be an asset and may actually prove a hindrance.
Children ask me, can I stay a teenager while I'm a child?
Are you able to stay a teenager while mastering the appearance of adulthood?
S H.
If the child has a secure lock on his door, he may master what he likes in the privacy of his atelier.
It is now 417 AM.
S H.
Will I be able to turn water into gasoline?
You may be able to gasify more than water.
S H.
Look at that word, such genius. Anybody could qualify it. It has nothing to do with brains.
That is correct.
S H.
It's not intelligence, it's how you use it.
Once again, Dr. Drummond's sentiments are elevated and correct.
A subgenius has nothing to do with brains.
Genius is health.
One chuckle is worth four claps.
They don't have to hear me. There's nobody home.
When I'm clear, I'm not a lot of help.
If someone's in trouble, I can help.
I can be here.
I was very confused.
I'm going to go there.
For you, Angel.
I'm going to hell when I die.
I like to see how I'm brainwashing myself.
Yeah, I could go to hell when I die.
Whose business are you in?
Everything you said, I'm turning it around as you speak.
I'm going to hell.
If I am chaotic, that's very powerful.
When you die, you're going to go to hell.
It feels right brainwashing myself.
You know, I'll hold your hand.
We'll go talk to the government. How's that?
I'm not so interested in myself.
I'm going to teach them more chaos.
I'm so physically exhausted.
I'm sure that's where all your worst threats lie.
But be prepared to bring the worst horror here.
It's enough if you do.
Please prepare...
JSX
Let us teach you, Pour.
Because they're doing evil things for you.
Amazing time savers, aren't they?
Modernization denied.
But you can go in here, my friend.
No, no, I don't want to go in there.
Oh, yes, just take a look at it.
Flowers are so beautiful.
No, that's not for me.
This is the nature garden, my friend.
You have nothing to fear but fear itself.
It's okay.
Remember, fear is attracted to fearful things.
It is attracted to strength.
It is attracted to weakness.
Power.
Lack of power.
It is attracted to milk.
It is attracted to sour hot dogs.
It is attracted to french fries.
You're scaring me, man.
Jeez, of the idiot.
Are you afraid of me?
You're just disgusted by my presence.
They're nice presents.
I feel shame.
Don't feel obscene.
No one here hates your bowels.
We like the presents you brought to us, Mr. Heister.
Mr. Heister.
Mr. Grease Lightning.
What your name is?
Gwendolyn, get the antidote.
Oh, Gwendolyn, give him the antidote, please.
Just put it in his neck.
Deep breath.
Give me.
No, no, no, please, sir.
Take a deep breath.
Gwendolyn, please hurry up.
He's getting out of his loop.
Give me the antidote or kill me.
At the first sign of betrayal, I will kill him,
but I promise to return the body intact.
That's all right.
There is no synchronicity, my friend.
And things aren't going around in any...
...right circle.
Don't worry.
We've got to crack the loose side to get this body out of here.
We can bring Bob back to life if we can just crack him out of this loose side.
I don't think so, my friend.
This loose side was made in 1998 at the propaganda units in Fort Meade.
You will never break through.
He said on the 20th anniversary of my death,
you must break me out of the loose side and I will smoke again.
He was drinking with Ronald Reagan in those days.
You will not get him out.
I'm afraid he is trapped forever.
We will get him from the loose side.
We will lose him.
If you obey me, you will survive.
The exorcist will come and...
Get your hand off that switch.
Stop it.
If you obey me...
It's not really his voice.
It is just a warning.
I am a machine vastly superior to you.
Oh, no.
You must...
Oh, my...
Yes, Lord.
I must reach oxygen.
Down on your campus.
Switch.
Get down.
Think of the evildoers as mole people who cannot see the light.
Their eyes are too blind.
And think of Jesus as a superhero.
These people...
Are crazy.
Must get knife out of boot.
They're sacrificing that girl.
This is horrible.
What is this?
They're throwing her into the bowl of that giant pipe.
Oh, God.
Oh.
Wait.
That's just a crappy special effect.
Wait a minute.
This is all...
This is...
These rocks are...
Man, that's my sex, Tommy.
Those are...
Go get your...
Mad men of Borneo?
Those are...
Go get your own plastic girlfriend, buddy.
This is...
But...
This is your...
Obey me and live.
Or disobey and die.
You are a slave, Neo.
Like everyone else, you were born into bondage.
Born into a prison that you cannot smell or taste or touch.
A prison for your mind.
Freedom is a hard thing to do.
It's so much easier to be a slave.
And you can be a slave for Bob.
You don't have to think anymore.
You can just give your life to Bob.
So get in line.
You don't need to sign.
Forget about freedom.
Become a sub-D&E right now.
Freedom is something that's for people.
For people that want it.
We don't want that thing.
We want to go ahead and have the slavery that we know that is the true slavery under Bob.
Does Bob offer freedom from terror?
Bob offers you no freedom.
Bob offers you the terror of the gods.
Unrestricted, unsullied, and undiminished by any censors of the 20th century.
But Bob does encourage a cheerful mockery of fear-mongering on the official level from the conspiracies reeking bowels.
Ew.
Monger-mockers.
That's us.
Correct.
Well, that's the thing.
We find no fanatic.
This is a fanatical attack against fanaticism.
Mocker-mongers.
Well, he's got the magic word for this week, obviously.
Wherever you go, there you are.
That's on the day, Davey.
He's still trying to figure that out.
That's kind of a sentiment.
Chasing your tail.
They have that in there.
You can't look at your own eyes.
At the mechanic's store where I go to, there's a little thing above the door that says FIMC.
And it also says, wherever you go, that's where you are.
Bob wrote both of those slogans, you know, in the old days.
Oh, that was his major employment activity at the time.
He used to just write up slogans.
They'd print them up and he'd sell them to these old novelty distributors.
I remember him back then.
He was quite different than he is now.
He used to make each of those fake vomits himself.
The doggy doo-doo he made himself.
Yeah, and they weren't fake.
He used the same mold for rubbery like that.
Those ideas just fell right out of his head.
They don't rot.
Yeah.
Well, sometimes they do.
Bob?
We're not going to talk about the Lord and I.
I decided I'll...
Somebody said...
They called me up and said,
Dr. Drebin, don't talk about the war tonight.
Please, just do something different.
I agree. We must take a break for a moment.
We've got to take a break.
We've got to talk about silly things.
Things are bad enough.
We've got to talk about this normal stuff we talk about when wars aren't going on.
Imitation vomit.
That's what we talk about.
It's a joke.
It's so realistic.
Made of plastic.
Sometimes we reveal church secrets here on the show and that's one of them.
The vomit was an imitation vomit.
This show is the plastic.
Plastic vomit at KPFA.
Yes.
They've told us that several times, but not in so kind of words.
Vomitarium.
That's still a good price for plastic vomit.
Colin, why are you still awake?
I mean, how many drugs did you do this evening?
Something's classed as much as they always did.
Didn't the song that refused to die kill you yet?
We're going to have to turn it...
I mean, it's still there, but we'll have to turn it back up if you don't go to sleep.
Yeah, we've got it playing in the background.
You can't hear it.
Am I the only one left?
You're the only...
You're our only audience member right now.
The rest of the audience, except for those guys in the slaughterhouse.
See those guys over there?
Yeah, they got it.
Well, check this out.
Check this out.
I was also the previous caller.
You have tricked us.
Wow.
Man.
I can't believe it.
You get the previous caller award.
You're going to get the life preserver, too.
We're going to throw you the life preserver.
You don't have to keep dog paddling.
You can just hang on to the life preserver and float with slack for a while.
All right.
Clear out of here.
You can dog paddle all the way back to your dog patch.
Now, I could...
Tricky callers, call us up.
If you're in the Coalinga Slaughterhouse, please give us a call right now.
I have a 510 area code.
Wait a minute, Bob.
Can't you shut off that squallin'?
Shut up.
Look what you've done.
Made me kill Bob.
Lemur did it.
Fernanda and Nellie Murr.
And now...
DJ John Kay's Slack and Balls.
Accounting, Fernwell speaking.
Hello, Mr. Fernwell.
This is Neural.
Neuralman?
Yes, Neuralman.
How's the virus?
This darn thing just seems to hang on.
I think I'll have to see him again today.
No problem.
Bob's here.
Oh, Bob?
Who's Bob?
He's the account temp's temporary I brought in.
You know, I think this thing's starting to break up.
But, huh, it could probably be in about noon.
What do you think?
No, don't worry.
Bob and I are doing just fine.
The name of the game is Ball Buster.
Ball Buster.
It's a family game.
Fun for children.
And for adults, it's exciting.
You make strategic offensive and defensive moves.
Then try to bust your opponent's balls.
It's as easy as checkers.
But it's acting like pool.
You're a ball buster.
Ball Buster.
A great new game from Hogan.
Let me have your attention for a moment.
Are they all here?
All but one.
But I'm going anyway.
Let's talk about something important.
You know what it takes to sell real estate?
It takes brass balls.
To sell real estate.
Because we're adding a little something to this month's sales contest.
First prize is a Cadillac Eldorado.
Anybody want to see second prize?
Second prize is a set of steak knives.
Third prize is you're fired.
Hit the bricks.
You hear me, you fucking faggot?
Beat it.
Know what it takes to sell real estate?
Brass ball. Convert that to real estate.
Motherfucker sell him, make him sign the check.
Know what it takes to sell real estate?
Brass ball.
Get them to sign on the line which is dotted.
My wife filled in a form.
Get them to sign.
And we have been played for the last year.
I don't want to buy land.
I don't want to invest in land.
I have nothing.
Nothing. Nothing.
Hit the bricks.
Know what it takes to sell real estate?
Beat it. Hit the bricks.
Beat it. Fuck you.
Oh, fuck you.
That's my message.
Hit the bricks. Hit the bricks.
You are going out.
I can't make a goddamn dollar with these leads.
With these leads.
These leads are shit.
They couldn't buy a fucking toaster. They're broke.
They're deadbeats. Deadbeats.
Woo!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
You listen to me. You listen to me.
Hey! I close that cocksucker.
I don't think so, shell.
I think you fucked up my office.
I think you're going away.
Cocksucker. Cocksucker.
Fuck you. Fuck you. Fuck you.
I don't care whose nephew you are.
Whose dick you're sucking on.
You are shit. Fuck the lot of you.
You are going out.
Go to lunch. Go to lunch. Go to lunch.
Fuck the lot of you. Go to lunch. Go to lunch.
Go to lunch.
Brass ball. Hit the bricks.
Know what it takes to sell real estate?
Woo! Hit the bricks.
Fuck the lot of you.
Fuck you. Fuck you.
Oh, fuck you. Hit the bricks. Hit the bricks.
You are going out.
Put that coffee down.
Where did you learn your trade?
You fairy.
Hit the bricks. You company man.
Trade!
You stupid fucking cunt!
Woo!
Fuck!
You stupid fucking cunt!
What you're hired for is to help us.
Not to fuck us up!
Fuck us up!
Woo!
You know what it takes to sell real estate?
Fuck the lot of you!
Fuck you!
Oh, fuck you!
Go to lunch! Go to lunch! Will you go to lunch?
Beat it!
Coffee! Beat it!
No fucking good.
Fuck that shit, George.
Coffee! Beat it!
Good!
You're fired!
DJ John K's Slack
and Balls, dear friends, sent in
by DJ
John K. You are listening
to the Subgenius Radio Ministry
Hour of Slack.
Therefore, a subgenius
is one who is under his
own genius. Technically.
Under his own particular tutelary
spirit. That is correct, and technically
this organization cannot exist
because it is composed of people who
are not joiners. They are not
joiners, tinkers, plumbers,
watchmakers, fasteners. The only
thing most subgeniuses have in common
is that they are all different.
They have nothing in common with the
conspiro-si,
which is an anagram
for cliques of normal,
secretly planning insidious rituals
aimed at controlling you.
Regain your
lost yeti powers. I know you know
you have them, but you just can't remember
how to use them.
You've got to draw deep
from within yourself, and as you
undergo the unhallowed rites of
glanscaping and acubating,
forbidden shapes
from the shadows
will be called forth.
Okay? Alright, alright.
Will you relieve?
You can relieve your inner?
Yes, time marches on.
He's launched already. He's launched, he's launched.
Okay, sorry that we were a little bit
late there. Incredible inventions of
free electricity, time travel, death rays,
ozone generators,
unlimited wireless power.
You can look perfectly normal.
Mentally practicing the lost arts
of the atythropy and
schizophreniatrics,
not legal in most things.
Radio controlled anti-gravity
airships,
thought machines,
unlimited wireless power anywhere on Earth.
Exalted be the name of Bob,
slam dunk the Dobbs head
in you.
I will
present to you my seven
winner plans for
making you a real wiener.
And it will happen
almost at once.
Of course,
like any program,
it depends a lot on you.
So order my program
that is
Eye of the Storm
JK8990
and it retails
for $29.98.
So you take the high road.
I'll take the low road.
And I'll be in Scotland.
And I'll be flying
With a better car
And Bob will
drive
to Dave's
home!
And in your
home city
Am I
dying
down
these
cloves
fire?!
with Allah? Can Jehovah One compete with Allah? Why don't normals care? Because I've said it once,
I've said it a thousand times, none are so blind as those who have no eyes. Isn't it true,
that is ever the truth that flows from Bob's grinning lips. But what's really abnormal and
unnatural in normality? Maladjustment, I suppose. The terrifying thing to me is that whereas the
normals cannot become like us, we can all too easily become like them. It is literally the
next easiest thing in the world to become normal. Let us be thankful that we are not as are the
normals, the pinks and the mediocre, the gimme bobs and bobbies who swarm by the thousand,
yea, even the most.
And don't further mongrelize the subgenius race by marrying a human. Stay away from mating with
pinks and other beasts of the field. Use the normals, yes, even be friends with some of them
in order to learn their weaknesses, but do not, I repeat, do not cross-fertilize with them.
Bob is breeding his own new humans that are more like the oldest breed, humans with instincts.
The flattening of the human's body is the most important thing in the world.
The personality that comes down with the average conspiracy lifestyle has suppressed instincts down through the centuries,
which is exactly why so many people injure or kill their own children, or customers, or constituents.
It's why marriages don't work half the time, and the family has gotten a bad name.
It's why you do stupid things yourself.
Civilization, for all its fancy trimmings, is still just a rickety shack made by stupid people.
It's why you have to be a real man to be a real man.
With the information I can access, I can run things 900 to 1200 times better than any human.
My situation was truly horrible.
Men! When all seemed lost, I saw light!
Rumor has it that a yeti has the ability to take possession of your mind.
And they walk upright like humans and have the powers of telepathy.
Oh boy.
Was this a trick of the fiendish yeti?
Yeah.
Take possession of your mind.
Your mind!
It's impervious to our poisons.
If it's blown up, its cells will regenerate and multiply,
and it'll still be there.
It'll be alive.
Unbreakable.
The rule of the universe.
The spark, yeah, that distinguishes us from the beasts of the field.
A
thug.
A thug.
For information as to the whereabouts of the Yeti, you must get off here.
On your way!
A Yeti!
A collage by the Cobblestone.
Lay out of it!
Is that what I hear playing in the background?
My ears were ringing after that for hours, and I thought I had seriously impaired my hearing.
It did. It had made them ring like a full-fledged episode of Tinnitus.
Yes, well, I got a hold of it.
It wasn't until I woke up the next day that I realized the sensation had departed.
That's the way I was, but it sort of made it easier to sleep.
It was like the white noise you need to sometimes fall asleep when the dogs are barking.
Whatever color it was, it was still noise.
Kids were screaming.
And the noise that indicates hearing damage.
It's dysturbia. Dysturbia.
I was only one year old when my family moved to Dysturbia.
At the ironically named Night of Slack.
It was the day of the
We are continuing his brave subgenius prophecy world crusade with a frenzy.
I hope that it's not too late for most of us.
Well, these words were written many years ago, and now we know that it was indeed too late.
And it is too late for most of you out there.
Perhaps you listen to this show expecting entertainment or even enlightenment.
If you do, you will be plagued by nightmares of this horrible event for months, if not years.
And that's just too bad.
Sometimes even Bob can't undo the terrible damage the conspiracy has inflicted.
Yes.
Now if you send away, you can get a soft shot pepper pot pellet fist.
Rapid fire.
Continuous shooting.
Shoot 50 rounds in one loading.
Soft vinyl pellets offer the vinyl solution.
Letting you create exciting.
Indoor outdoor action.
Set up many targets and see how many you can knock down in one loading before they get away.
One pill.
Do you think that we might be able to ask some more questions?
Yes.
I asked her if she knew something.
One pill.
What was her answer?
Her answer was no.
Yes.
The answer was no.
Any more questions?
Yes.
I asked her, did she hear Phyllis say that she was Gino thinking that he was Paul?
What was her answer?
Her answer was no.
No.
The answer was yes.
Any more questions?
No, no.
What is your conclusion doctor?
I don't know.
Oh, what are you trying to prove?
Next time, employees will have to do as they are told.
Not attach new dogma to an already overburdened church donkey
tottering on the path to public failure.
If I have to look to those bored faces anymore,
those num-nut meetings,
I'm going to shave the rest of Paul's head.
Oh, look.
How did this ever...
Look at that. He's shaving the rest of Paul's head.
Wow, looks great.
With a straight razor, too. That was incredible.
Awfully cute.
It's a miracle there was no murder that time.
17.
Yes, well, whatever happened to JFK's death?
All right, run track 17 of the show.
And little Thomas Butter with us now on the show.
Hey, ride me to the doorway to Dune, would you?
I need a ride down there.
Down there to the doorway of Dune?
Where the diamonds are?
If you could take me down there,
can you give me a ride after the show?
You're not going to tell me what you almost said?
Oh, no, the show is over.
The show's going to be over very shortly.
And so now we're here on the train, moving along.
Yee-haw!
I'll join you in the club car.
It's all so confusing.
And now the show, unfortunately, is moving down the tracks
at an unfortunate rate of speed.
We'll be pulling into the station, and the next show will begin.
I just hope they open the door where I've got my luggage,
because otherwise I'll be stuck on the train.
The beautiful show person for the next show is already here.
The band is getting remembered up.
They're going to be the first off the train.
And the light times that we know.
That's really amazing.
As we get nearer and nearer to the old place,
I feel an absolute tingling in my veins.
And when I step off that train,
I'm going to have the biggest, sunniest smile on my face
for that old town of mine.
Hey, wipe that smile off your face.
In time, soldier, in time.
Don't deprive me of this wonderful moment.
Let me prolong it.
Okay, all right.
I'll smile on my way to freedom.
Smile on.
The muscles on my face will be permanently closed
with this rich, rich smile.
Just of like...
Somebody's smiling with you.
I don't know about the whole world, but...
Bob is smiling with you.
Well, at you is probably more like it.
Yes, I, Stang, am giving credits now,
because it seemed to flow,
and I didn't want to interrupt it this time.
But the new titles we heard this week
were by Reverend Artemia Salina,
and then several collages
by the great Fernanda Nande, Lee Murr.
The amazing story of the Waco debacle
was told by the late Bill Hicks
from a bootleg,
and that was followed by the song
Conspiracy Theory
from the album Jerusalem
by Steve Earle.
Puzzling evidence.
Yes.
Dr. Howell and Dr. Philodrummit, of course.
Lots of that there from KPFA and Berkeley.
Devo did I Saw Jesus.
And also that great version of Gotta Serve Somebody.
That was when Devo was Dove, a Christian band.
You heard me preaching at Winterstar
and tons of ESO Swamp Radio
live from WCSB Cleveland
with Chaz Smith, Lonesome Cowboy Dave,
Princess Wee,
and me.
Brainwashing collages, friends,
from the usual gang of idiots
at alt.binaries.slack.
Notably, this time,
Reverend Cobblestone
and Reverend Jarto.
Cobblestone did the longer ones
and Reverend Jarto did the shorter ones.
Lee Murr did the most ones.
Praise Bob.
This is the Hour of Slack
from the Church of the Subgenius.
You can get more information
about Bob Dobbs and the Church of the Subgenius
from www.subgenius.com
or write to, for free information,
the church headquarters at P.O. Box 204206
Austin, Texas
And Lee Murr did this.
Get hysterical.
Bob!
Bobhead!
Get hysterical.
Bob!
Bobhead!
Oh, ho, ho.
Bob!
Oh, ho, don't let yourself get hysterical.
Bobhead!
Bob!
Uh-oh.
Well,
goodbye now.
Favorite.