We came here, we, we, we came here, we, we, we came here tonight to get started, to call
at hell or get retarded.
Wake up my sweet darlin' and see the light upon your eyes.
Blue light flashin'.
Shadows leapin', church bells ring mad against the night.
Hey my love, please stand up and watch me tonight.
Milfe?
Have you got a hundred.
recognizes as still its own Don't pull the full面 dro acoustic guitar The
floor was of God's grace.
Once you know he's a мeth Legos voir.
check our bank locos at eyecepo.com This is avent GMB Yup, uninstall at home leína olmounucro,
hey this is n shell Open double Bitch ab coisas del Thorn
They say nthin' butايayo and the perfect game.
ne palmenvira eвид I.ncührdaons are now at g1ce I Gar回ha Ibarra per nine că cuando
kean. SG Re dio наш in Dorca Campos viable change the nature for Coo vму.
çünkü weya I notu Easter!
Welcome to the subgenius radio ministry Hour of Slack
Sponsored by the Church of the Subgenius
The subgenius Hour of Slack
Announcing the Los Angeles Uber Devival and Fundraiser in just two weeks
A mere $150 for a weekend seminar and all new Devival
Why save your money?
You won't need it ever again after July 5th, 1998
Sponsored by the Church of the Subgenius
Spend it all now
Attendees will include Robert Williams, Jonathan Demme, and Nina Hagen will be in the strip show
Captain Beefheart will be coming out of retirement for this super event
Devo, all five members, including the original drummer, will be uniting for the Los Angeles Uber Devival
Johnny Cash may attend to do some Bob covers, we hope
The Los Angeles Uber Devival was to star...
...but Dave Brokie, dying in a motorcycle accident this weekend, has kind of screwed that up
Cut it
Let's go start from the beginning
Let me go over this
chi
Austin Plum Monica
Shaxi
Andrade
militarice
Virginia
Patrice
kraarra
There's like no pause.
Announcing the Los Angeles Uber Devival and Fundraiser in just two weeks.
$150 for a weekend seminar and all-new subgenius devival.
Why save your money?
You won't need it ever again after July 5th, 1998.
Spend it all now.
Now. Attendees will include Robert Williams, Jonathan Demme, and Nina Hagen will be there just to be in the strip show.
Captain Beefheart will be coming out of retirement for this mega subgenius event.
All five members of Devo with the original drummer will be reuniting for the Los Angeles Uber Devival.
David Lynch will be doing a documentary about the Church of the Subgenius and starting his filming project with this devival.
Marvel!
Mike Jitlov will be filming a new short at the seminar.
We will be launching the frozen head of Timothy Leary into low Earth orbit with a giant hydraulic cabin from survival research laboratories.
We are hiring an actor to play Legume in Los Angeles because he has been erratic and Jano will be played by his own clone.
Seminar subjects will be sales training, speed typing, and how not to fall for the conspiracies blamelessly.
Send $150 for your ticket to the Subgenius Foundation.
P.O. Box 140306, Dallas, Texas 75214.
Price does not include hotel room, air reservations, food, or oxygen.
We are hiring an actor to play Legume in Los Angeles because he has been erratic and Jano will be played by his own clone.
If you were to land in Bolivia, they'd hand you some sort of metal and...
Naughty, naughty.
Someone's got the bunch to burn.
Someone's breathing church air.
Yes.
Worshipping.
You can worship at the workbench.
You can worship whatever you're doing.
It's a good thing about, you know, the spirituality of all of this.
Is that you don't have to go into a church or anything.
Yeah.
You know, whatever you're doing.
When you're drawing, you're doodling pictures, you know.
Yeah.
You know, whatever.
Yeah, and I know, you know, so many religions, you can work.
You got to worship with certain orifices.
You got to, like, you know, fold your hands and stuff like that and talk in your mouth and your heart.
No, you can pick your nose.
Yeah.
You know, like in this one, you can worship with any organ you want.
You can praise God with your rectum for all we care.
And he cares, really.
Bob.
Or she.
Yep.
Are we talking about Bob?
What did you mean by liquor and religion?
Reality and spirituality or what?
Well, I don't understand your question.
We have 12 steps.
It's a 12-step program for Emotions Anonymous.
What's the first step?
Step number one.
Do they seriously want people who are too emotional?
Yes.
We admitted we were powerless over our emotions, that our lives had become unmanageable.
That's number one.
No!
Can somebody get Edward Munch out of here?
Here's number two.
There he goes.
We came to believe that a power greater than ourselves could restore us to sanity.
Wow.
Sanitation?
Yes, for God is clean.
He beareth not stinky boogers and juices that emit from him like we his foul creation.
Here's a good one.
Number five.
Admitted to God, to ourselves, and to another human being the exact nature of our wrongs.
Louie, Louie.
I'm getting a little bit woozy.
Are you a girl or a girl?
Louie, Louie.
Oh, Dave, man.
Oh, he took a bad one.
I told you not to.
Are you a girl or a girl?
Dave, when I bring up a tank of nitrous oxide like this, you can't hog it all.
You're going to keep falling over and passing out.
What drugs did you use?
And where did you get them?
How much did they cost?
Oh, the sergeant's coming.
That's Bob.
Oh, my God, he's fat.
I never saw him look like that.
The last couple of years have been rough on him.
What's he doing?
Why do I need him?
Praise Bob.
I'll praise Bob.
When he comes to us.
Praise Bob.
No, wait.
Bob.
Praise Bob.
It's that loop again.
Give it up, Dave.
Do you pee?
Then you may be interested.
what I have to say.
Some people,
you'll notice, there are, there's, there's,
I just mentioned two kinds of people.
That was a lie. There's three kinds.
There's those who have presence.
You know what I mean?
Well, that guy there, probably not.
Some people just have, you know,
Santa Claus, Dr. Legume.
I'm probably
a pretty good example.
Some people have no
presence. They have none at all.
I didn't get any presents!
But,
but at least they don't bring you down.
Okay, that's most people.
I guess you call them the Larrys, as opposed
to the Moes and the Curlies.
The third, I guess, actually, I'm probably
a better example of the third type,
which is a sort of an anti-presence
that sucks
slack from you.
You know what I mean?
There's, there's, there's,
well, what we're talking about are
human cartels.
We're talking about subgeniuses.
I'm sitting around, I'm sitting around
backstage looking at my fellow subgeniuses
and I thought, that's what it is.
I'm living in a world of human
cartoons, or
non-human cartoons. They're cartoons.
The humans,
they're full three-dimensional
fleshed-out characters.
Us subgeniuses, praise Bob,
we are two-dimensional characters!
We are cartoons!
We are stereotypes of ourselves!
We just happen to be a subgenius.
be the first example of that particular
stereotype.
So, you know, as we've always said
in this church, the sub-genius,
sub-genius, get that,
it's not the intelligence that counts.
You know, it's the sense.
Common sense, sense of humor,
dollars and cents.
You're only as think
as you smart you are,
I think Bob said at one point.
And the pink,
yes, the human, the pink, the pink boy,
the Barbie Ken, the mediocrity,
the cage dweller,
they tend to imitate
TV. In fact, I mean, it used to
start out where television imitated
them, but now they
imitate TV. You know, TV
is more real than their reality.
They don't feel like they've really
broken up with their girlfriend
until they've done it on open.
You know what I mean?
They seek
to make their lives
into a, they don't seek
slack, they seek the opposite.
They seek what they see on television.
They want to turn their lives into a
perpetual soap opera.
Well, our lives are already
a perpetual
Dr. Bronner's soap
opera.
Praise Dr. Bronner.
And we're trying to escape from it.
So, sure, we're all robots
for our glands, like the
scientists say, but
we sub-geniuses like to break
Asimov's first rule of
robotics every day.
Yeah!
For those of you, I believe that first rule was
don't harm a human.
So,
sub-geniuses.
God damn it, it's
10-20.
Hey,
believe me,
these schedules, these schedules are
the one anchor
of sanity in this
raging ocean.
Practice time control.
Break your watch.
Hey, speak for yourself. You want to bring your watch up here?
Do you have a watch?
I would love to do a time
control ceremony.
Sickness,
healings. Friends,
is there anyone here who's willing to
free themselves? Alright.
Break off. Listen,
check this out, friends.
We will do it. We will destroy
time.
Jesus collected. Wait a minute.
Are you sure? This is not too bad.
It's a Casio.
It's really working.
It's probably at least a $10-$12 watch.
Friends,
this
will be the, because when we
smashed this symbol,
this handcuff, that man just
tore off his handcuff.
He just sawed away
the chain that was
tying into the concern.
And it was tying this revival
to the gospel.
And it was tying this revival to the schedule.
Now, this revival will never end.
Friends, we will give you control
over time.
But only if you let us smash and destroy
Satan's handcuff.
Pray Satan.
No offense,
no offense,
Dark Lord,
that old split foot.
And, um,
yeah, actually, I should, I think I need
to get out of the way and make,
begin to make way for someone else.
And we will later on, friends, have healings
and sickenings, head-launchings,
and a short duration
mass marriage.
So, um,
you know,
what's the most about Bob Armadillo
hair coat?
Yeah, I just want to tell you,
he's got a thing with that hair coat.
We'll get to that.
Um,
oh,
and now,
I introduce, to give the introductions,
Paul Panger!
Oh my goodness, my goodness.
Are you starting to feel
a transformation?
Can I hear a praise
bomb?
Say to yourself, praise
bomb!
Now turn to your neighbor and say,
praise bomb!
Praise bomb!
Or to someone else and say, praise bomb!
Now I want you to meet the man that holds
the secret radio frequency codes
for the weekly show, The Hour of Slack,
Reverend Ed Strange!
Woo!
Ladies and gentlemen,
how many of you came here tonight
to be entertained?
Not me!
I can't even talk!
I can't even talk right now!
I really hope not.
Because you see, I normally preach for free
on a radio show
three hours a week at least.
I was really looking forward to coming down here.
You know, even some time out
in my busy week
to write a whole bunch of
about Bob
to entertain you.
Because I thought,
Texas,
Austin,
just a, what, two hour drive
from what should be the hot bed of slack
in the country, Dallas, Texas.
But to my shock,
to my utter disbelief,
in the $20, 30 minute cab ride
from my hotel room at the airport
to church headquarters,
I got in a little conversation
with the cab driver,
nice enough guy,
shooting a breeze.
He says, well, you know,
what are you doing down there
in Austin heading down there?
I said, well, I'm going to
Subgenius the Bible
to preach to the masses.
He just kind of stopped
and looked back at me and said,
what the hell's the church
of the subgenius?
Can you believe it?
In Dallas, Texas,
with only, what, 295 days
left to X day,
there's a cab driver today
in Dallas, Texas,
who has never heard
of the church of the subgenius.
My fault.
Well, how many
deuce-pain subgeniuses
do we have here?
How many?
Well, I'll tell you what,
you ain't doing good.
You ain't doing good enough
a f***ing job.
I'm sorry to say,
that's why I'm here
to recruit,
to extend a special hand
of friendship to the,
well, the cleverly concealed
and well-disguised members
of the FBI, CIA,
and of course,
the Bureau of Alcohol,
Tobacco, and Firearms
that we know are in the audience
here tonight,
planning to do
God knows what to us
to help keep America safe.
For Christianity.
Please speak into the pen.
Well,
f*** the funny s*** out, Bob.
F*** it.
You know what?
F*** it, Bob.
There's too much killing
left to be done before X day.
You think an alien race
is going to come all this way
to see a bunch of nanny-pandy
do nothing,
sit around on their keisters
watching the X-Files,
just hoping a saucer comes along
to take them to a better place.
Why not?
Huh.
Well, my friends out there
who happen to be working
for the government,
tonight's your chance
at redemption.
We implore you.
I mean, we understand
what you do.
You're actually not that different
from us.
I mean, face it,
you're just doing
what you know is right,
what you believe to be true,
and you're doing
what you know is right
for America.
And, well,
especially the BATF.
The BATF.
I mean, for all the bad press
you guys got down there in Waco,
I mean, personally,
I thought it was a hell of a job.
You just burned the wrong
bunch of pink bastards.
Oh, there are so many millions
and millions of willing targets,
and you have to go
and fly 80 or 90
pretty abnormal folks
who probably could have been
members of Church Subgenius
had we gotten to them,
but no, you had to go and kill them.
That's why, friends,
we need your help.
We need those members
of the FBI, CIA,
because, let's face it,
you already know how to kill.
You're trained in surveillance,
and God knows you're real good
at corrupting the entire morals
of nations across the planet.
The time has come to join us now.
You may not be convinced yet.
You will be by tonight.
Tonight.
Maybe by midnight.
Maybe after you have
a couple more drinks,
it'll all start making sense
after seven or eight shots
of Jagermeister.
You'll start staring
at this banner back here.
Old Bob.
And you'll notice Old Bob,
his whole face,
it's made up these little dots.
If you stare close enough,
you can see there's dots
in the dots.
And if you stare even longer,
you'll find out that
You'll find yourself going in
beyond the dots to the actual
subatomic particles
of those said same dots,
those ink stains on vinyl or paper.
And you may even,
if you're lucky and slackful enough,
see infinite new universes
within those dots.
Worlds coexisting in parallel
and perpendicular universes.
Multi-dimensional life forms
of vast tapestry of creation.
And you may look at it,
and you may think to yourself,
what majesty.
What amazing things there are in the world.
What the beauty of life.
But all you're really gonna notice,
if your eyes are open,
but all those other worlds
are just as as this one.
And it ain't a goddamn thing.
You, me, Stan, or anybody else can do it.
But get right with this man,
J.R. Bob Dobbs.
Get right with this man,
Get right with this man, J.R. Bob Dobbs.
One more!
Hey!
Where are you gonna find the word of Bob?
Are you gonna find the word of Bob in your church?
Are you gonna find the word of Bob in the supermarket?
And you sure as the hell will not find the word of Bob
in your public school systems.
Here is where you will find the word of Bob.
When this is bad,
this is...
...
Gosh, spam sandwich eating man,
it seems like we've been waiting for our kids here forever.
Of course, my nipples are always awfully hard.
Yeah, but they're not very big.
I know, but they're...
Come on now, admit it.
They're dinky.
They're like men's nipples.
Well, they're like raisins.
Of course, they're very small.
I'm not bragging.
I'm just talking...
They're like teats on a hog.
Teats on a hog.
What a...
It's quite poignant, actually.
Hello?
That's a beautiful illusion.
I like teats on a prairie squid.
I think they would be much, much, much, much...
No, because teats on a prairie squid have a function.
Whereas teats on a male hog are useless.
That's the origin of the old southern metaphor.
Now, a prairie squid...
Well, what would you say, a bull hog?
A prairie squid without teats?
I don't know what the hell you do with them.
Millions and thousands of tiny teats,
like little rupturing cups,
surrounding our foreheads in the middle of the night.
Sometimes we can't wake up because of it.
Oh, they'll keep you awake.
What you do is you pet the squid.
You take it, you tickle it, and pet it, and squeeze.
And it starts to ooze from those little tiny teats,
this stuff that looks like rubber cement.
Oh, yeah.
And you take a glass slide or something,
and you scrape it along the little teats.
And you let it dry, like a couple hours.
And then you can roll it up in little balls.
Tasty.
And you put it in the little pipe,
and you can smoke the prairie squid toxic teat secretion.
So the lactic expressions of that squid monster
are actually smokable from?
Mr. Romo, I must admit that I'm puzzled.
You hipsters claim to be such relaxed, free spirits,
yet your rules for social behavior
are even more set, tight, and rigid
than those of square society.
Yeah, well, dig.
If you look on a map,
the counties in Texas and Oklahoma,
the way the counties are laid out,
they outline a swastika.
That's true.
Yeah.
But that was like, you know,
when they did the first crop circles and stuff,
they decided whether they were from the Perseid Galaxy,
the ones that are the real white boys and stuff like that.
Yeah, right.
Those guys said, well...
Those guys landed like four years ago.
Yeah.
Made off with like a number of cows.
Some prairie squids.
Said they'd be back.
Yeah.
Someday.
Yeah, right.
Two hundred and seven...
All it's gotta do is stay alive for 277 more days.
Yep.
And, uh...
And then you get a little, little winky badge.
And then it's all over.
Yes.
You get a little badge you wear,
and you step onto the ship.
Yeah, and it's one of those, you know...
Beep, beep, beep.
I saw one of the badges.
I got to see it because, you know, I'm, you know...
I can imagine you fondling it, too.
Yeah.
You know what they did?
Playing with it and stuff, looking at it in the dark.
It's like those badges that the, the...
Sexual.
That you got to wear when you were in grade school and you were a crossing guard.
Oh, they're real tacked on.
And the belt, too.
Yeah, you get to wear that belt.
Oh, man, you feel like an Ubermage with those clothes on.
A white belt that goes around your waist and then slashes, sashes up over your shoulder.
And then subliminally imprinted, or, you know...
Yeah.
Allowed to crack other children on the head, you know.
Enforcer.
Child enforcer, you know.
Little pipes all around.
Yeah.
And...
Run the belt.
What's so funny about it?
It's almost evil when you think about a, a crossing guard sonder commander like that.
Taking all the little children, letting them go across the street so the cars won't hit
them and then walking them right into a gas chamber.
Get out of here!
You understand what I mean?
You follow the hip commandment.
Thou shalt not bug thy neighbor, which means be cool.
That's all.
Cool.
Cool is a word that's...
It seems to change meaning every time it's used.
Yeah, it does.
That is a cheap shot in the name of Yahweh and Joe Hoover.
Yeah.
Two.
Both of them.
Yep.
Resting in Atlantis now.
With their eyes still open and their nose is still breathing, just dreaming of the days
they're gonna come back here and tell us what to do.
I mean, as if we ain't got enough subliminal messages telling us what to do.
Yeah.
And all's you gotta do is wait 277 more days and...
You'll have...
You'll get all the subliminal messages and...
Good ones.
Everything we'll be telling you what...
Yeah, good ones.
Really good ones.
Not the ones like you get around here.
Like the other day, I was driving through town.
I was going through Euclid and I hallucinated that old big boy.
You know the big boy?
Yeah.
I hallucinated.
Remember the actual fat big boy out there?
Right.
Holding the big boy?
And when I saw that, I got down and worshiped that as an icon.
I knew I was being given subliminal messages by them big boys.
The big boy.
Yeah.
I mean, the other day in the supermarket, a can of them Bush's baked beans done give
me a...
Sometimes told me to do something I couldn't even remember afterwards until I think it
was in the evening sometime I was getting drunk and I remember what the hell was in
that can of beans telling me that stuff.
And beans, talking beans.
Yeah.
It's not, you know, hate Nazi, communism, capitalism, you know, beans.
You know, like a can of beans is giving you orders.
The white men leave talking beans, son.
Don't mess with the talking beans.
Those are the white man's medicine.
That's bad medicine.
The talking beans.
What's coffee?
Coffee, the beans that you roast and then place into your rectum before you're shot
deep into the cans.
Coffee is another form of water.
I'm immortal.
Can you grok that?
Can you grok that, brother?
Who is this guy?
He shall be killed.
Yeah.
Who?
Where is he?
What?
God that made you do this.
Uh, that is, uh, I thought we were talking to Javaro.
Yeah.
Oh.
You did it then.
In your own dreams.
You did it.
You are your own Messiah.
I never did that.
I would never make a peasant do that.
Well, buddy, connect the dot.
Okay.
Connect the dot.
You'll get it.
You really will.
I promise you.
Just connect the dot.
Remember, you are your own Messiah.
Come with me!
Aaaaaaaahhhhhh!
Aaaaaaahhhhhh!
Oh yes!
The friends!
He did it!
He jumped!
Just come over here and sit down in this chair right over here.
I got something to tell you, kid.
That's right.
It's an electric chair.
Ha ha ha.
The Governor never calls.
Yeah, just strap yourself in there.
And we'll let you do all the work.
Yeah.
You get to do it.
You hit the button right there.
Want any special theme music?
Let's see here.
We got theme music.
We can put a video in for you.
And a bar of cartoons.
Huckleberry.
How about Popeye?
Oh, he's done making choices.
Here's Popeye.
I'm Popeye the Sailor.
I'm trying to save the man.
Devil, I'll get you.
They may get me now, but I'll get you.
You'll never take me alive.
See?
It's easy.
And it feels so good.
So if you think some ignorant white boys can do it in the 20th century,
imagine what it was done like when the canoes looked like gleaming vessels of...
Hate.
Burning vesicles of flaming testicles of pie.
M squared.
Cherry pie.
Yep.
The kind Mom used to make when you were a bad little boy.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Drink of my body.
Smoke of my face.
Drop.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Roll up my socks.
Yeah.
I like when they say drink of my sweat.
Drink of my sweat.
The water.
The back to the water.
The bacterial salty water of my extrusion.
That's when we know we're living in an industrial society.
When the preachers come on the television and ask you to drink a tiny small ball of their sweat.
Wrapped in this.
This healing paste.
Yours for only 1795.
And you get a book every month after that for the next year.
With little prayer inscriptions, parts, pieces of the scripture.
And look at this little tiny Madonna you can keep in your wallet or billfold.
Eating the mushroom.
Ooh, more mushrooms.
The misery mushrooms.
The misery mushroom.
I must keep going.
Keep walking.
No, there's nothing to eat.
Someone said she had a dream in Belgium that those huge cathedrals were surrounding her.
She said she was mostly trying to time her Owens Beles.
And buildings and everything.
And books and everything.
And I.
Don't worry, Reverend Shane.
You can trust me.
Oh, gee.
Friend, Dr. Legu pointed out
right in public to many subgenies
he says, yes, on
you spent your $30, bought your membership
card, your ministership, and so
forth. Yeah, on next day,
July 5th, 1998,
7 a.m., you'll no longer have
to worry about the conspiracy
or any of the bad aliens.
You won't have to worry about any of that stuff.
You'll be protected
from the conspiracy.
But Bob didn't say
anything about who was going to protect
you from your fellow subgeniuses.
Kill him!
You'll get your own planet
in 295
days. Oh, yeah.
But so will he.
What
if Dr. Legu
decides his planet
isn't big enough, his planet of
broken glass
isn't big enough, and he
wants to turn your
planet into a planet of broken glass?
You know,
some people say church is subgenius,
so they get involved in it, and they say
after about six or so,
they get real involved. They jump into the
internet intercourse
of the church and so forth. After about
six months, they're going,
God, this is worse than high school!
The popular ones pick on the
wimps even worse than in real life!
Yes, friend,
it is like the high school
from hell.
Praise hell!
Yeah, praise hell. Praise hell and praise the hate,
friends.
Actually, you know,
my own,
I've got teenage kids, believe it or not,
and one of them just
graduated from school, and he was so
glad to get out of high school,
because he thought that people
in high school were so phenol,
full of vanity,
clustering together in cliques
to gang up on others,
afraid of anything different.
And he
was so glad to get out of
high school.
I didn't have
the heart to tell him
what it was going to be like when he got his
first office job.
Friends,
but one thing delivers,
one thing sustains us,
and you've heard this word before tonight,
and that word is hate!
Hate!
Yeah, it's an ugly word.
I've seen all the subgeniuses love hate.
I've seen crowds of them
chanting,
hate, hate, kill them.
It's a beautiful thing to see them like that,
chanting.
And indeed, the creativity
is a wonderful thing.
Our hate is like
a self-fueling,
fusion reactor.
Actually, the conspiracy itself
provides the plutonium
which fuels our hate
dynamos.
It's a great metaphor.
Like I said, it sounds ugly,
doesn't it? But isn't that what
all religions are really all about
is hate? They don't care.
They talk about how they love
God, love Jesus,
love Muhammad. What they really love
is the idea of you
going to hell.
And them not doing it.
That's the kind of hate that we hate.
That's normal hatred.
It's a pathetic little...
They want to destroy anything
they don't have, whether they
want it or not, especially if it's
something that they desperately need
but can't understand.
Like slack.
But our hate is not
wasted on individuals.
No, they're such a nation.
They're such a...
They are crazy.
The song went down.
She got a chili coal thing on the back of her shoe, buddy.
And she thought they was like, you know,
the big cathedral thing
had eyes and they were trying to eat her
and stuff.
Let me suck your rock hard in that...
And there on the side of the building,
King Kong,
King Kong clung
to the pipe.
To the pipe.
The pipe.
King Kong.
Scratching at it with his little
fingernails.
And the pipe.
And the Pharaoh smoke
in the distance.
Frog.
Well, thank God the Indians
had pyramids 5,000 years before
the Mexicans or else we would have
never had them heaping, whomping good tacos
they got down at Taco Jerry's.
Mmm, fishin'.
Mmm.
Nuclear fishin' tacos.
Fishin' tacos.
Mmm.
Nuclear fishin'.
You can get the cold fishin' tacos
and the hot fishin' tacos.
You can actually get one of those rectal jammers.
You can get the fusion taco now, too.
And the cyclotron accelerator.
Or the decelerator.
That is if you don't want to eat as fast.
The accelerator taco is really big, though.
Yeah, but you do get mighty windy afterwards.
It's 30.
It's 30 miles in diameter.
Yeah.
It's the biggest in town.
They claim.
It only costs 99 cents.
Well, that's it.
Well, I'm not sure I can say that.
Well, if you do qualify for the government grant,
it's only 99 cents.
If you're just a regular...
You know, if you walk in off the street
and say, give me one of them...
It costs $4 billion.
Yeah.
So who cares?
They kind of change around with them.
Yeah.
I do sometimes, but it's not the kind of change
you'd want to be around when it was happening.
No.
Okay.
A little psychomomatronity there.
Especially since they got rid of the $1 million bill.
It's not easy to carry around a couple of bill.
Oh, if you want change for salsa, you're out of luck.
You're out of luck.
All right.
Flying saucers never change, though.
Nope.
It's the universal stability principle.
That's the disc.
That's why females have breasts on them
so that we can think about discs and stuff
to remind us that we have to get the hell out of here.
Yeah.
I think.
Bang on a drum.
Yeah, that's an oval-shaped thing, too.
Yeah.
They look just like flying saucers.
Let the prisoner go.
Yeah, feed them on bread and water, but let them go.
Damn you.
I haven't gone in weeks.
Let them drift away.
What's it to you?
What's it three by four you?
Yeah.
You come and you go.
Sometimes you come in your pants
when you're driving in your car and you're confused.
Yeah.
Sometimes you go backwards
and you still forget how it started
so you're left without any contextual framework.
Yeah.
That's bad.
You know, you're twilighted, zoned and stuff, you know,
and things just don't make sense.
Things are like odd little dark currents
that roll around in your mind
like some sort of shining, sparkling drift
in the nucleus of space.
Like a brainstorm, but a bad one.
You know?
Yeah.
It kind of makes your ears flood
and them conduit pipes behind your head
actually light up in the middle of the dark.
Try getting a drink looking like that.
Especially with the specs and shoes I got
and the pair of spats I have to wear
since my increasements.
I had not only a beta increasement,
but I had an oxygen case.
And the oxygen case been going on
for something like 15 years now.
I mean, I wouldn't want to use anybody else's
clothes or anything.
I mean, I wouldn't just,
just wouldn't want to use anybody else's clothes.
I wouldn't want to share like that.
I wasn't born.
I was made.
I was created.
And it wasn't a kind and loving God that fetched me.
It was a pissed off old man.
Some people think that angels
went into the creation of their being
and that angels made the sparks that made them go.
We know what it really was.
Simple toss of a card.
Grumpy,
old,
old fart saying,
here's nothing human being to look at for a while.
I can't believe it.
I,
please,
Roxy.
Let me do it.
Now we've gone too deep.
You can't go back now.
You have to follow the road.
You told us this is what you wanted.
Sin and,
um,
poison.
Too much gas.
No wonder.
Dave's hallucinating again.
Yes,
yes.
We check it out.
I thought that that was the moment.
Hey,
naughty,
naughty.
Someone's got the bus.
Someone's breathing.
Church air.
Hey,
yes.
I want to.
Hey,
you know,
it's bashful.
You know what that means when you're bashful?
Uh,
you have some kind of like an idea of,
you know,
I,
I really.
Ladies and gentlemen,
every year,
thousands of landmines are abandoned by people who just can't care enough to give their landmine the sort of love and attention it needs.
Under the mistaken belief that the landmine can take care of itself,
these poor explosives are left in deserted war zones and along interstate highways.
Most of them desire starvation.
Others are eaten by predatory.
Yeah.
So the conspiracy itself provides the plutonium which fuels our hate dynamos.
Praise the Lord.
And like I said,
it sounds ugly,
doesn't it?
But isn't that what all religions are really all about is hate?
They don't care.
They talk about how they love God.
Love Jesus.
Love Mohammed.
What they really love is the idea of you going to hell.
Yeah.
And then not doing.
But that's the,
that's the kind of hate that we hate.
That's normal hatred.
It's pathetic little.
They want to destroy anything they don't have,
whether they want it or not,
especially if it's something that they desperately need but can't understand.
Like slack.
But our hate is not wasted.
It's not wasted.
It's wasted on individuals.
No,
they're such our nations.
Even such vessels are far too small to contain our great hate.
Copyright 1995.
G Gordon Gordon.
Yes,
friends.
Ours is an all-consuming and all-encompassing and all-pervading hate.
A radioactive hate.
A burning,
scouring,
annihilating hate.
And that's when,
when you build it up that,
pump it up that much,
friends,
that's when you start to become the hate.
But then,
we would,
check it out,
I thought,
I thought that,
roll that back,
roll that back.
That was the moment when the raw eggs were placed under his pillow.
He's still on his way to Alpha Centauri.
Yes.
There we have it.
Now,
now zoom in,
zoom in there.
Look,
the eggs are seeping from around the pillow.
He's rolling in the,
in the flattened,
broken eggs.
He does not even seem to notice.
He's not waking up.
Now,
as the eggs not,
matter,
begins to assimilate into his paws,
things change and take place.
He's only two months from Alpha Centauri.
He's actually entered the Alpha Centauri system.
You want to bring him back?
That's why you're here.
Bring him back.
He starts to hear,
radio signals.
That's a call, Jimmy.
Here he comes.
Take one.
Voices.
He heard voices.
One tree reaches Alpha Centauri.
Oh,
it's in the Pullman car.
It'll be a couple more months.
Pullman.
Or the Orbitz.
Where's my daiquiri and cheese?
And then he'll be a beacon for the pleasure ships.
Don't be reluctant.
Give in.
Come on, Jimmy.
Banzai, it's time.
I'm glad you're load up.
Hold up.
To be continued...
I like the future. I'm in it.
I built it myself and I love it.
I'm not sure.
Personally, I'm very pleased.
I think it's going to be all right.
I can dig in.
How do I like the future?
Well, the future's not here yet, man.
Smaller, but cleaner.
Right on.
I say live it or live with it.
Straight ahead.
Well, I think it has quite a great future in it.
It's electric.
Yes, it's the Honorable Chester Cadiver.
Sure, understanding today's complex world of the future is a little like having bees live in your head.
But there they are.
And like the young lady said...
I said live it or live with it.
What does this mean?
Well, for the straight poop, let's go where I go every morning.
Centrally located and barely a stone's throw from the tomb of the unregistered voter,
downstairs in the historic old grid building.
Hello.
Hello, Clive.
Ah, come on in, Chester.
Thank you very much.
Hey, hey, you're just in time to help me check out this new model government.
Yeah?
Yeah, they just brought it down and they say it explains everything.
Well, you know, it sure is big.
Hey, well, look, look over there on the left end.
That's where you work.
They're in the Bureau of Western Mythology.
By golly, we're a proud service of the Lost Electricity Reclamation Agency, Senator.
Yeah, well, the LAS is under the left...
Well, it's...
I, uh, don't...
I think I'll just plug it in.
Oh, well, listen, I'll just use this little plug.
Right down here.
Not that plug, Choco.
Uh-uh, see?
Oh, that's terrible.
Oh, you've got to plug in the female.
Ah, listen to it.
Teaches you, huh?
Yeah.
Half a watt comes in here.
Ha, must go out there.
Right-o.
Ah, let's see what it does with this fine miniature boxcar of industrial coke.
Okay.
Oh, yeah, look at that.
Ah, turn it up.
That's amazing.
Let's see.
It's pumped from the Veterans Tap Dance Administration.
It goes up here.
To the Assistant Secretary of Leftovers.
Let's plop down to the Secretariat Covers.
Right, right.
Now, watch it go now.
Around the Department of Spies.
And, uh...
Ah, into the office of the Secretary of Failure himself.
Wouldn't you know?
That's shoes for industry, Charlie.
And it's food for thought, you know, Mr. Brown?
Yeah, but we're talking about power, Choco.
Well, I know you are.
You wouldn't be here.
Oh, look at that.
Yes, sirree.
It heard the word power, and it responded just like we do.
Ooh.
And here it comes.
Here comes our ox cart right back to Earth.
Smack dab on the middle of the Small Animal Administration.
Well, I must say, that's the most incredible demonstration.
But where are the humans, officer?
Why, they're right here, son, waiting in the lobby to use the power of that ton of coke.
Oh, then we must be very near the President, Mr. Devis.
Yes, Dagwood.
He's the terminal bus.
The output.
I'll bet you he really puts out.
That's right.
Everyone's always asking him questions.
Oh, well, maybe my friend here will.
I'd like to ask something.
He's been with us since before the beginning, sir.
He must be bursting with a short question about his place in the future.
Oh, is he your friend?
Yes.
Well, I'll ask him his name.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Could you state your name?
Please state your name.
Oh, oh, do you want me to...
Please state your first name.
Uh, Ivan.
Who?
Uh, Clem.
Now we can introduce you and some of your selected neighbors to...
The President.
Thanks.
Step off stopping yellow line.
Okay.
Stand on steady blue lines.
Strobbing.
You are now going to see the President.
Oh, okay.
No flashes, please.
Thank you.
You're not spring-headed.
Here I come.
Yes, dear friends.
That was the Firesign Theater.
Progenitors, you might say.
One of the...
From their album, old album, called, uh, I Think We're All Bozos on This Bus.
Probably one of the most influential, oh, I guess you'd call it a comedy record or, um,
uh, radio play or whatnot of, of, uh, folks like Einstein's Secret Orchestra, um, Lonesome
Cowboy Dave, certainly, and, uh, the, the KPFA subgenius radio show, Mongers, and me.
We're all old Firesign Theater heads.
And friends, I'm about to...
Give you a couple of addresses.
An important one being the address of Einstein's Secret Orchestra, where you can write to them
about, uh, I believe Chaz does, like, a little publication with, uh, sick, perverted artwork
in it, and, and, um, they have tapes.
And the Einstein's Secret Orchestra.
Got that pencil ready?
3-2-2-6, West 99th Street, Cleveland, Ohio.
Once again, and I'll give that zip.
And that's 3-2-2-6, West 99th Street, Cleveland, Ohio.
4-4-1-0-2.
And friends, of course, the subgenius post office box.
The Church of the Subgenius, P.O.
Box 140306, Dallas, Texas 75214.
If you join, I'll let you spank my bottom.
Oh, yeah.
You know you want me.
You want it, friends.
You want it.
It's only Bob at Post Office Box 140306, Dallas, Texas 75214.
What else have we been listening to?
Um, besides the ESO, uh, broadcast with, uh, Dave and Chaz from, uh, from WCSB in Cleveland,
uh, we also heard music.
Music from Ego Plum.
Um, and which you can, uh, you can get information about, um, Ego Plum from www.EbolaMusic.com.
How about that?
And I believe we gave, uh, his address last week.
Also, we were hearing, uh, the, uh, Fringeware-sponsored subgenius devival in Austin, Texas.
Uh, uh.
Uh, yes.
Praise Fringeware.
Um, uh, uh, great preaching there by, uh, Reverend Ed Strange.
And what else?
I guess that's all it's, it's mostly been.
It's been, uh, ESO, Einstein Secret Orchestra, and, uh, subgenius devival.
A little bit of Wendy Carlos, a little bit of Jimmy.
Here's Wendy Carlos in the background and J.S. Bach.
Oops.
Friends, I keep pushing the wrong knobs.
Ahem.
Hey.
Oh, and we heard some Fringeware.
Friday Jones there, I believe, talking about, uh, her landmines.
Uh, friends, it's a beautiful, beautiful thing, this old...
No, it's not.
It's an ugly old thing.
This old church is.
It's an ugly, ugly thing, and I love it.
And good night.