I'll put me through!
Yes, speaking of the body of Paul.
Here it is! Here comes the show! Quiet!
I think I got it.
Right between the walls.
Okay, drag the show over here. Come on, guys.
Come on, guys. We gotta get the show up the stairs.
Check it. See if it's got its wallet.
Let's take it down to the old abandoned warehouse.
Hey, this show's got $500 in its wallet.
This show's got a motor truck. Tie it up.
We'll get its car keys.
I always wanted to get into the show.
Now it's our chance.
You'll never forget, Abel, when I say I get into the damn show!
And he was hopeless.
His legs drew up tight and tense
and withered away to just skin and bones.
Probably would have had to limp.
For a few days because of sore shin.
Don't you see my point?
No, no, no.
Oh, yes, we all love each other.
Well, Bob, I don't know how you feel about matters like this,
but personally, I just don't approve of
the self-genius
power of
watching.
I hardly agree with you.
Oh.
In the next 13 or 14 minutes,
something good,
good, good
is coming.
Your wave.
So don't leave this radio station.
Let's have a good time together.
He's all I need.
Ah, yeah.
Ah, friends, we had so much new stuff to play
that it put us behind.
And the only way to catch up was to blow off the new
and just, uh, well, basically, friends,
what I did was grab one each of all of our subgenius CDs,
the masters of which were right at hand.
And so, uh, what we have are one or two tracks
from each of these various CDs.
We have, uh, Bob's songs, one through six,
media barrages, ten through twelve,
plus zero and five,
and the best of hour of slack.
And so, friends, back to
the good old days.
As soon as you turn your back,
everything in the universe snaps itself inside out
with a hideous sucking motion.
The only reason you cannot call the world impossible
is because it is only through the world
that you know the concept of impossibility.
You have been led to believe that everyone feels
he or she may be the only living consciousness.
But you are in fact the only one for whom this is true.
Oh.
Divine.
The fundamental structure of reality
is totally transformed every instant.
But it provides you with a phony memory
that it has always been the way it is.
Oh.
Since you are always at the exact center of an infinity,
there is no such thing as movement,
location, space, or time.
Oh.
You are a row of electrochemical events
taking place in your cerebrum.
Oh.
Nothing has meaning in itself,
but everything can support any meaning.
Oh.
If you could glimpse for even a moment
the real meaning of existence,
your brain would be neuroanatomically destroyed.
Oh.
You cannot conceive a thing for which you do not have a word.
Everyone's perception is radically unique,
but leads them to believe it is more or less similar
for everyone else.
Oh.
You have always been listening to this tape.
You cannot remember a time before you were born
because there was no such time, nor any other.
It has always been this moment.
Oh.
Death could occur inexplicably any second.
The oddness of the world exceeds the imagination by an infinity.
It has produced this talking about it,
this talker,
this labeling of it,
this labeler,
the concept of labeling,
the concept of oddness,
the word oddness,
the concept of a word,
the word word,
the word concept,
and the concept of a concept.
Oh.
Consciousness is not a continuous state,
but a momentary surfacing for variable periods at random points.
Your next awakening could be 20 years from now.
Nothing can be proven to be true.
Oh.
Because reality is composed of infinitesimally small moments,
there is no such thing as an event.
Oh.
The reason people are untrustworthy
is because their cerebral processes are fundamentally random ones.
Oh.
During the night, every ego in the world changes bodies,
inheriting also the memory.
Oh.
Old age is not a gradual,
but a catastrophic process,
and could strike at any moment.
Oh.
Dreams are the reality for which the real world is a dream.
There has never been a time in history
when men have voluntarily used less than the greatest possible military technology
against their enemy,
and allowed a great technology to fall into disuse and ignorance.
Oh.
Therefore, there will be a full-scale nuclear holocaust.
You are dreaming this moment.
Oh.
The universe will continue to expand
until there is not enough matter per unit space
to provide the gravity necessary for regeneration,
and it will slowly die out.
Oh.
When you finish listening to this,
everything will be different from the way it was when you began.
But, again, your new memory will conceal this from you.
Oh.
All events occur at random.
The universe is one of an infinite number of universes,
the closest of which is undetectable,
being a billion universe lengths away.
Oh.
Only what you are experiencing right now exists.
Love is the feeling that another person
is really yourself.
Oh.
You are about to make the first conscious decision of your life.
Shut up!
Hundreds of New Yorkers at a religious revival
chanting the name of a modern-day prophet, Bob.
Bob's teachings are the foundation of a church
that does little more than parody cults and American consumerism.
It's called the Church of the Subgenius.
Tom Vitale has this report.
You will pay to know what you really think.
But if you give us money,
we will tell you what to think.
And not only have you paid to know what you really think,
but once you will get value for your dollars.
Oh.
Americans will buy anything,
and they're getting sold short.
That's the message of the Church of the Subgenius,
as delivered by the Pope of all New York,
David Meyer, at a recent revival.
Meyer also instructed the enthusiastic crowd
in how to get slack,
how to get right with Bob,
and how to pull the wool over your own eyes.
For they shall see God.
It's still true.
God still speaks in special ways to each of us today.
But my feelings toward him are still so brittle and sour.
I don't care, I don't care, I don't care,
I don't care anymore.
Tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired.
I can't tolerate it.
I can't live with it.
And that's how I became a subgenius.
Children of the great Saint Lenny Bruce said,
American society cripples you and arrests you for limping.
Here in the Church of the Subgenius,
we say, cast off those crutches and crawl with pride.
You can crawl again.
You can crawl again, children.
I may sound like a Bible-beater
yelling up a revival at a river crossing camp meeting,
but that don't change the truth now.
I want to see if one person,
one single person,
will have the courage of their convictions
and come down here and open up to Bob
and give them, give me their wallet.
I don't just want your money.
Don't just want your credit cards.
We want your library cards, your voter registration.
Give it all up now.
Now, now, now.
I'm talking to you tonight about the Holy God,
about the One and Only Bob,
the One and Only Bob,
the Church,
the Subgenius,
the Subgenius.
Praise Bob, praise Bob, praise Bob.
Can I get a witness?
Can I get a Praise Bob?
Thank you, children.
Thank you.
Some of you may not be familiar with the church of the subgenius.
Some of you may not know the heart of the subgenius,
Some of you may not know the purpose,
the divine,
the divine.
What is the purpose of the church?
The purpose of the church is to have what?
Slack!
Can I hear that again?
I need more slack!
Can I get some slack?
Has this ever happened to you?
Why, I should have been there, Ted.
It was great.
There was free booze, great music,
one of the best parties I ever went to.
Where were you that night?
Oh, I just kind of stayed home and watched TV.
I guess I should have gone, huh?
Didn't you feel stupid?
Didn't you wish you could go back to that night, that party?
Well, maybe now there's a way to learn how to do that very thing.
Introducing Bob's School of Time Control.
At Bob's, you'll learn how to speed time,
slow time,
and make time run backwards.
Thank you, Lorenz.
But most importantly,
you'll be learning how to make time work for you.
How, you may ask?
Well, just ask this man here,
an actual graduate of Bob's School of Time Control.
One day, my dog ran out in front of a truck.
Blango.
My dog was dead.
Was I sad till I met Bob.
Bob showed me how I could go back,
get the registration number for the car,
do a slip job on the brakes,
and wouldn't you know it,
that truck went off into a ditch and burst into flames
just exactly a block before he could hit old Booger.
Ain't that right, fella?
Yes, just imagine the horrible things
that could be undone tomorrow
if you had only gone to Bob's School of Time Control today.
Courses start yesterday, but you can catch up.
Ha ha, just right.
Bob's School of Time Control, the universe.
Bob's School of Time Control,
a division of Subgenius Industries Unlimited.
Everybody says I'm paranoid.
They all think I'm crazy.
They all smile to my face.
But they'd like to see me die.
And to attain the slack of Bob,
a subgenius must fight a vast and powerful conspiracy,
what Pope Meyer calls the pinks.
Pink is sort of that ruddy glow in the cheeks you see on people
who want to sell you something you don't really need,
who want to take away that which means the most to you
and give it back to you for a profit.
Reject!
Now!
Who has come along to save us from this conspiracy?
This conspiracy that would feed you this trash?
It's Bob.
J.R. Bob Dobbs was the world's greatest salesman.
He could sell anything to anybody.
He was a foregoing, full-fledged, blue-ribbon member of the conspiracy.
Selling and selling and selling and selling.
And one day he discovered a fantastic secret.
What is it?
A secret that had been hidden.
The secret of slack.
The Church of the Subgenius, a parody of weird cults,
has some 3,000 devoted members who have bought thousands of pamphlets,
stickers, cassettes, and t-shirts,
all bearing the trademark of Bob's smiling face with a pipe stuck in his mouth.
Peek-a-boo!
I can see you!
And I know what you do!
Bob is...
That big, all pervasive figure that encompasses spuddom on planet Earth.
And what is spuddom?
It's the human condition.
It's things falling apart.
It's fat ladies in double-knit jumpsuits beating their kids in Krogers.
We hope to welcome you all tonight to the fervid celestial spouting of the inner epochs and clockwork workings of the Church.
But this task will not be easy.
The fruits of the subgenius plant are not as cordial to the taste as others may be,
kind of mucilaginous paste.
But it's easy to become tangentially twisted along precarious paths that have nothing to do with the straight and true direction of our search.
We are born with the Dobbs nature.
However, only exist technology can complete a subgenius.
The subgenius's transfiguration into over-manhood or over-womanliness.
And so far, Bob has allowed this to happen to one solitary guinea pig.
His friend, Dr. Philodrummond.
What? Goddammit!
Man was born with original slack, yet most civilized people don't believe in it.
And their most learned scholar can't even comprehend it.
Well, I've studied the Saurian stage in human evolution.
As it turns out, many of our ancestors are not the primates as commonly thought, but the theropod line.
The great archosaurs of the Mesozoic.
Oh no, look out!
Get him out of here!
Bob's Saga
Bob is a rock
Bob is a tree
Bob is you and me
Bob is me
Bob is a football
Bob is a basketball
Bob is a rugby ball
Bob is a golf ball
In an order like this, we may have guidelines but you must remember not to be literal minded.
No subgenius follows any two rules exactly.
You must also remember that anything any subgenius says at any time is sacred dogma automatically.
And now the rules of the church of the subgenius.
The first rule of the church of the subgenius is
The subgenius must have
What must he have?
What must the subgenius have?
Doug, what must he have?
He must have slack.
Help me out here, Doug.
The second rule of the church of the subgenius is
too much is always better than not enough.
Can I get a too much?
Can I get another too much?
Oh, but too many of those, children,
it's always better than not enough.
The third rule of the church of the subgenius
is a rule violated every day, everywhere you go.
People say to me, who is a conspiracy?
Look and see who violates this rule,
and you will know them by their actions.
The third rule of the church of the subgenius is
if you don't have a sense of humor,
don't try to be funny.
The fourth rule of the church of the subgenius,
thank you, Buck,
and one of the most important rules
that supersedes all other rules is
fuck them if they can't take a joke.
Fuck them!
You must draw your own conclusions.
But that's the way religion is.
It's been a constant battle since the very beginning.
The first man to try to guess why he climbed out of the slime
was the first man to pick up a stick and hit his brother.
We've been programmed.
Since the very beginning,
our slack was taken away
the moment we entered this room.
This world worries treadmill.
And we've been running like a little rat through a maze.
And the only way you can get away from that
is to deprogram.
Edit your own memory.
Take those bad memories.
Take those horrible training regimens
that you were subjected to as a youth.
Flush them down the toilet as you excremeditate.
Let me ask you.
Yes, sister.
Did you ever own a guinea pig?
I ate my guinea pigs.
I grew them and I ate them.
That's dick, Craig.
They were food.
I'm a carnivore.
I can't help myself.
Thank you.
My every honor says a lie,
including this honeymoon.
I say, fuck them if they can't take a joke.
I got anything for a laugh, I say.
I am the last winning homo correctus.
I am the goddamn man of the future.
I'll drive a mile so as not to walk on foot.
I am a human being of the first goddamn order.
I am too intense to die, for I speak only the fucking truth.
Da-da-da-da-da-da.
Fuck you.
My imagination is a fucking cancer.
And I'll spark it before it sparks me.
I think backwards.
I do it for fun.
I cook and eat my day.
I swam up into the triangle and didn't get wet.
Fuck.
Fuck you.
I'm looking at the future, I'm ransomed into the past.
I wait time, wait up for me.
I'll live forever and remember afterwards.
Yes, I am the purple flower of Hell County.
Give me wild birds.
They say a godzillion is the highest number there is.
Well, by God, I count to a godzillion and one.
I weigh 666 pounds and zero gravity.
Come and get me.
I told Jesus I wouldn't go to church and he shook my head.
I have my own personal saviors.
I change them every hour.
I don't give a fuck if there's life after death.
I want to know if there's even any fucking slack after death.
I am a goddamn visionary.
I see the future and the past in comic books and wine bottles.
I paint my jeans and wear them my DNA with the force of my mighty will.
I steer my own goddamn engine.
Give me slack.
Yeah.
Hey, what's going on here?
Along with Bob, the pursuit of slack, and a conspiracy of pinks,
the subgenious theology includes a vision of the apocalypse.
Accordingly,
According to church doctrine, on July 5th, 1998,
when the television signal of Amos and Andy reaches the men from Planet X,
the aliens will unleash their wrath upon the Earth.
And the men from Planet X are going to come down and take over Earth.
They're going to...
They will put us out of our misery unless Bob can explain to them
in ways that they can understand that there is something on Earth worth saving.
And only the subgenii, the dues-paying, book-buying,
receipt-in-the-pocket, paid in full to the church subgenii,
have the tiniest prayer of survival.
The rest of them? It's a tough world, Jack.
There are people in them, and many of them have already landed on this Earth.
Oh, give me back my lost freedom.
Oh, ye aliens.
Alien stick-men.
Oh, give me back my gone cat.
Oh, great daddy-o from outer space.
Oh, give me warning.
Oh, space creatures.
Ye-i-i.
Give me the signal.
Oh, hideous alien monster creatures from the beyond world.
Oh, the
The message is Mars needs women.
Mars needs...
It's a gag. It's a prank. It's a fake.
I don't think so, sir.
What's gonna happen to your children?
What's gonna happen to you when this society we've created,
when this society we've created,
air conditioners,
are station wagons with wooden sides,
station wagons with wooden sides,
are cautious indeed, are retired actors,
are orange hails, are politicians,
are orange hails,
What happens when that collapses?
What happens when your diary was a damn well?
That's when the man from Planet X-9,
I'm down to save the members of the subgenius church.
But until that day,
the power and wisdom of Bob can help us break their mind control
by activating that mutant gland that we all have within us.
There's a fella down in Texas
They say his name is Bob
He tells me I should slap God
I should quit my job
Well I'm a subgenius
And I must have my slack
If I don't live forever
I get my money back
They said that on July 5th
of 1998
the earth would be
destruction
And I would suffer a deadly fate
That day was long away
Now it has come and gone
There was no fire from heaven
And this old world rolls on
Well I'm a subgenius
And I must have my slack
If I don't live forever
I get my money back
The poor stank was made to suffer
A terrible disgrace
Of such humiliation
He feared to show his face
Now Bob may be laughing
Because we are such chumps
But there is no reason
To be down in the dumps
It'll all still happen
No need to curse or frown
They got all the right numbers
Just got them upside down
Well I'm at some genius
And I must have my slack
If I don't live forever
I get my money back
And I will
back to the office to the meeting the meeting of the other uh new and potentially
significant contributors to the corporal world of communications and uh
the psychological world of how to get ahead by kissing butt but by not actually letting the lips
of the kisser kisser touch the butt of the kissy yes by providing the illusion that the actual
kisser's lips are indeed kissing and touching i mean the molecules themselves are
one on the point of contact with the kiss ease but but in this case we have found how to get ahead
ahead ahead in uh the corporate world by only using the established norms of success climbing
up the ladder and how to use those norms as a uh shall we say skeleton of whose bones you
uh one in that position would act as if they were a ladder or a
some type of stairway yes and advancing up those bones causing the illusion to all other
entities involved in the corporate climb that the feet are actually touching the bones
and the lips are actually touching the butt
but we both know now that that does not necessarily ring true for a oh say a subgenius in that position
and we have found here that the mostiska is the kind of thing that is
allowed to take flight so strategy but then the nangios and the animo have actually never
color coded the way to come up uh wind or conversation checking modern technology
toward lights artoxia so those ».
lorrit per.
how fasting ace with rep AMP
the utmost sincerity,
to use that word again,
and by doing so,
fall into the trap.
Yes.
By following the illusion,
conversely,
one can avoid the trap,
but reap the benefits.
Ha ha.
And so my,
this concludes our topic
of the Zen of butt kissing,
corporate style.
We're all brothers in a perfect world.
There's no need for spontaneity.
Perfect system,
we're all brothers to the end.
I think this is about the sickest,
sickest, sickest thing I've ever heard on KFJZ,
and since I've been listening to it.
It's not just the wars and the awards that win them.
It's not just the dull and empty distaste
for a smothered culture
that expires all around you
and pools,
with its own wastes.
It's not just the terminal folds of Nunu.
It's not just the child zombies
that murdered their mediocrity parents,
and then cruise the streets with bloody feet.
It's not just those starry old vecks
on the park benches
with looks on their faces
like those who shuffled out of the boxcars
of Belsen and Auschwitz.
It's not just the anesthesiologist,
Franigi.
It's not just the heaving pink meat masses
that grope and clutch all around you.
It's not just the dino bones for Wotan.
It's not just the broken headlights,
snapped antennae,
and human excrement on your car hood.
It's not just that the old ways were best.
It's not just the bastardization and perversion
of every honest means of self-expression.
It's not just the killer shit ganja
from the dark side of the bush.
It's not just the penoid snipers
locking and loading on every high-rise rooftop.
It's not just the widescreen,
technicolor corporate daisy chain
that has defiled the entire planet.
It's not just Mongo in the Congo
with fa-fa-fals the size of basketballs.
It's not just the prophets crying lonely
and alone in the wilderness.
It's not just the people who are the most
It's not just the indignity of having to work
for some bland, non-entity son-of-a-bitch
who thinks workers are property.
It's not just the blueness of the womb
cleansed by evil.
It's not just the battling eco-freaks
who want to go back to nature
without realizing that nature
is an open-ditch latrine in midsummer.
It's not just some asshole with a pipe
and a shit-eating I-know-more-than-you-do
dog grin all over his homogenized face.
It's not just the horrible feeling
of being entrapped inside a regimented,
devolving world that you certainly never made.
It's not just the doorway to doom.
It's not just wanting to know
what the hell is really going on.
It's not just the missing H's
or the stolen alpha-beta-max.
No, dear friends, there is more to it all than that.
Bob ain't no nickel-dime bum-show.
I put it to you, he's on the square
and a corking fine business proposition.
He's the grandest thing yet,
and don't you forget it.
Shout salvation and fightin' Jesus,
you'll need to rise precious early,
you sinner there, if you want to diddle the almighty Bob.
Not off.
He's got cough mixture with a punch on it for you, my friend.
In his back pocket.
Just you try it.
I understand them.
They don't understand me.
They are the normals.
They're all that I'm not.
But I'm not the normals.
I am a subgenius,
a whole different species.
If I had my way,
they all would be shot.
For when I was young,
the pigs ruled the world.
Now all that has changed,
cause Bob's flag's unfurled.
I spit on normals,
cause I hate their guts.
I am a subgenius.
They like their jobs,
for all the wrong reasons.
They wear me down
with their false holler smiles.
But my kind triumphed,
and now we will kill them.
Dead normal bodies
for mile after mile.
For when I was young,
the normals held sway.
I'm a subgenius,
a whole different species.
Now all that has changed,
cause Bob has his day.
My shoe will soon kick a hole
in their butts.
I am a subgenius.
I am not bitter
for all they did to me.
They're only humans.
They're deaf, mute, and blind.
But I am a subgenius.
And I have a duty.
The utter destruction
of all humankind.
For when I was young,
the pinks ruled the world.
Now all that has changed,
cause Bob's flag's unfurled.
Cause Bob's flag's unfurled.
Soon I will grind
their face in the dust.
I am a subgenius.
Thank you.
Oh friends,
I just, I can,
the miracle of the Bob world
is unfolding in front of me now.
I can see in the spirit,
through my windshield,
I see superimposed over
this mixmaster
across which I drive.
I can see an ocean
of self-realized subgeniuses
all in one place.
I can see the
the face that can
pile through
eight foot thick
titanium steel conspiracy
fort knocks doors.
The face that can burn
through metal with that mighty pipe.
From across the nation
they came and they saw
a new will begin
in northern Arkansas.
They drove the storms
and heralded night
to their new awakening
and dock docking site.
The cares deep in love
hang through their ties.
The journey was dead
and they were meeting in five.
Bob's flag
was not even there
but they were few.
It was mostly cool guys
like me and you.
And we got high,
so high
on dock dock houses.
Yeah we got high,
so high
on dock dock houses.
We ate lots of mushrooms
to commune with nature.
How are we to know
that the moon
is in nature?
Five hundred colors
flashed into my brain.
My cell division occurred
in three or four planes.
My brain was blasted.
My head feeling fixed.
My eyeballs protruding
but I didn't get sick.
We packed up our tips
but we kept seeing dots.
Yeah we found that the peak
had gotten all the best spots.
So we got high,
so high
on dock dock houses.
Yeah we got high,
so high
on dock dock houses.
The people were happy
they were all having fun.
While doctors for Bob
was farming skulls in the sun.
The corpses were swinging
their love did abound.
The average corpse
floated a foot off the ground.
The band had jammed
and their god was speaking his name.
While the doctors on the plant
cell were swaying their fame.
Farthog explosion
and combo gang fun.
Finish this then,
just in time for lunch.
Yeah we got high,
so high
on dock dock houses.
Yeah we got high,
so high
on dock dock houses.
Yeah we got high,
so high
on dock dock houses.
The people were happy
that was awesome.
we got to get back
to work.
Ah, yes, dear friends, the swinging love corpses.
The swinging love corpses.
The스트bs aye aye villeo.
The steba it revitalize.
That's a proclaim alright yonen
noticed inBeen thought that
the same investor uh oportunisation
ever one is guteer enough to
Sparrows, we need to have our lives doubled by...
Dobstown!
It's where the bad little girls and boys go.
It's where something is happening all the time,
and most of it unsolved.
Some of it is so hard to locate.
Many of the people from the saucer ship emblem itself
have been sucked out and left here.
Dobstown.
I didn't want them to be oblique.
When they strapped me down in a chair
and started asking me questions about Dobstown,
I gave them the location of the website.
Dobstown.
It's Nwatsbod spelled backwards.
It's Brigadoon without the haggis.
It is surrounded by the seven cities of Cibola,
which are its slums,
and it has a ferry to Monster Island.
And what a delightful pair of individuals
you'll never find there.
The ferries of Monster Island.
Tiny little happy people who do things for other people,
who live for other people,
so big are their hearts and so tiny is their stature.
They...
Dobstown!
That's where Amelia Earhart crashed, friends.
It's where the Tunguska meteorite came out
after bouncing around inside the airport.
It's where the Tunguska meteorite was, of course,
as you know from reading your book of the subgenius, Dave,
was a miniature black hole.
It's shot by Dobs,
the young ten-year-old man,
called J.R. Bob Dobs,
from his slingshot,
in a completely by accident.
In a fit of rage?
No, he didn't even know he was doing it.
It was just, you know, I mean, he picked up a...
Other kids might pick up a pebble
or a cat skull for their slingshot.
Yeah, a cat skull.
That makes a lot more sense.
A tiny black hole.
A singularity.
The glowing essence of nothingness
sucking in all that is not Bob.
And that is what he shot into the Tunguska plane,
in the middle of Siberia.
And then, past the event horizon,
the little thing itself went and then became like a bigger thing.
And it went into the Earth, Bob's tiny black hole did,
and it bounced around like a cue ball on a pool table,
back and forth until finally it exited
at the place we now know as Dobstown.
Dobstown, friends!
It is where a thing of beauty is a joy for a while.
It's where you are better than you were then!
It's where you were in high school!
It's where you get all the pets you ever wanted!
It was never a colony of France!
It is where science and magic are the same things!
It is the unfolding of miscalculations.
It is the dawning of the height, weight, hair, and eye color of Aquarius!
It is the fizzling, crackling, ebony...
It is the dissonant fifth vortex,
disrupting the harmonic convergence!
It's where the early worm gets away!
It's where the gravediggers leave their shoes in the middle of the night.
Dobstown!
It's for when you're too lazy to kill yourself!
Where there are no lawyers!
And where the government never tries to be helpful!
Dobstown, friends!
It's where you can make your imaginary friends
fight to the death!
Dobstown!
It's between the dark and daylight,
when the night is beginning to lower!
It is where neither heredity nor environment matter!
It is where the lamb and the lion lay down and have sex together, friends!
Dobstown!
It is proof that hell is full!
And the dead walk the earth!
The fabric is one thing, like yourself,
one thread that could lead to thousands of other threads!
That is our caustic solution for you,
as members of this solemn group gathered together,
squandered and quashed and pushed under heavy stones,
so that you may not know the truth that we speak,
and yet here we are, speaking it to you!
Dobstown is not a place where a man or woman dwells,
but a place in the heart,
as big as that mighty elephant yoke,
and twice as tasty as all the trees that you could imagine!
Now, imagination is not a place you want to stay.
It's not a place you want to bring the kids, grandma,
and ride the ferris wheel with.
It's not the kind of place you want to leave for a better home.
It's a place you visit, over and over again,
with your pants on, your pants off,
and your heart ripped right out, hanging from your chest.
Dobstown!
Where Bob comes home,
after an easy day's work.
And where you can come home too, friends!
Where you'll be home!
Where you'll finally realize why,
why,
and why you can find out more about beautiful Dobstown
when you join the Church of the Subgenius,
the world's only, first, true, last, final,
one, true, religion!
Because it admits it is full of crap,
it is the only one that's not full of crap!
And that's right, and I know it's coming each time,
I can tell it, you tell it,
ah, ah, ah, go!
It's where Ennio Morricone was delivered
of his inspiration for this music in the background.
Huge, huge mandibles,
large, large, fresh, gamy legs.
And now the matador Dobbs steps out
before the enraged triceratops dinosaur,
flashing his red Dobbs-headed cape
in front of the maddened beast,
the furious creature that stomps its feet
and paws at the ground.
Dobbs grins, he smokes,
the creature charges!
Dobbs whips out his pipe
and gives it a little conk on the noggin
as it runs by.
And after that,
it sits and pants like a little puppy dog.
And then he gets up and starts to bark.
My life has changed in many ways
since I first saw this place.
I know that Bob will triumph
with our friends from outer space.
And though we suffer, Niggie,
I know that it's all right
because I know Bob and I.
Tell me what the thing.
The church of the subgenius
will spread across the land.
With pipes in place,
we'll build their place.
They march together and in hand.
The starfish of removal
will strike a mighty blow
and we'll be free
of the noble and the pig.
So give to Bob, Bob, Bob
and you'll feel a whole lot better.
Sir Bob, Bob, Bob
send a dollar and a letter.
He will change all your behavior.
He's your short-duration savior.
He is Bob, Bob, Bob.
Bob!
Friends, this hour of Slack number 984
starred from our old albums
in order of appearance.
St. Palmer Freedies of the Lies Foundation.
Puzzling evidence.
Dr. Howell.
Fernanda Dandy-LeMuir.
Michael Pepe.
Pope David N. Meyer.
Reverend Ivan Stang.
That's me.
Dr. Philo Drummond.
Reverend Bleepo Abernathy.
Reverend Mark Mothersbaugh.
Glass Madness.
Mythical Burrowing Animals.
Doctors for Bob.
Doctors for Wotan.
Orton Nenslow.
With that song, there's a feller.
G. Gordon Gordon.
Dr. Onan Canobite.
The Swinging Love Corpses.
Reverend Gudrun Thompson.
Gary Grogfran.
Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
Pope Sternodox.
And this, that Dobbs, What is Dobbstown thing was written by New Monet.
And now, friends, Brother Cleve.
Well, there once was a man.
The world's greatest salesman.
And he had devised a plan.
To get the shackles from my feet.
Oh yeah, but now he's gone.
A martyr for the cause.
Bob is my lord.
And he's coming again.
Who knew that the first shot.
Was gonna be the last shot.
But he's got a hard driving pipe.
The gas won't go through.
And I'm so much more than I thought.
And although he may be hurting.
The universe will keep on squirting Bob is my lord.
And he's coming again.
Yeah!
The world's greatest salesman.
Robert G. Gordon.
If he's not gonna make history.
Only thing that matters.
If he's gonna make it back.
Austin, tackling.
From the drinking.
Of a referring job.
And my follies.
Every last one of them.
Paide no.
We can only drink and say
Father's my Lord
And he's coming again
I know he can make it
Without him we can't take it
We'll lose the pieces of our minds
To the pink boys and the wimps
Until the day that he comes back
It'll be a world with no slack
Father's my Lord
And he's coming again
If we don't want the answers upon us
Then we need more
To be honest
Father's my Lord
And he's coming again
Great God is on the throne
Right now
Again
This will all come
to an end
To you
If you send a dollar
To the church
Of the subgenius
P.O. Box
Cleveland Heights
Ohio 44118
This will enable us
To continue with the marvelous operations
Which we've known about
And we've tried to spread
Throughout the western hemisphere
And change this
CFR
Triforce
And we've tried mediators
In many ways
To them
We've turned around
And Justin
And lots of other
And as we speak
Know
How we get
To those
Tourneys
So may deeds
Go before
I
Have
B streak
If you
Know
concepts will always be linked in your mind. Sex, money, Bob. Sex, money, Bob. Sex, money,
Bob. Yes, this is a continuation of the flow spew that the doctors of feel-good-ice now
got for us here. You would have been told which Bob to tune to in your area, and this
is not a burned-out, radiance-oriented cult, ladies and gentlemen. This is a spouting spew
and tumping of graven images, spewn-eyed, blun-y-o-ed, nor-deed-y-o-ed.
My mind is my own and nobody's gonna change it. I'm not going into that room! Nobody is,
come on. Break out of that glass bar.
And join the Church of the Subgenius.
You're listening to the Hour of Slack. For more information, check out www.subgenius.com.
And friends, you can write to Bob or the Hour of Slack at Post Office Box 181-417 Cleveland
Heights, Ohio 44118.
After relaxing on the lake, Bob's ready to have a great time entertaining his friends.
Right, Bob? Bob? Bob?
Friends, we're glad you listened to this show, and we're even more glad that some listeners
have donated enough to help us keep on going for another couple of months. And not just
this show, but subgenius.com and all the other articles. We're glad you're here, and we're
glad you've made this possible.
I'm Bob Morin, and I'm the creator of the online blog that you can find on the Subgenius
And if you truly love Bob and want some of that slack back to rebound to you, you should
go to subgenius.com, front page or especially the radio page, or the catalog store pages,
and help out financially as best you can. Now, we know what it's like to be on the brink
of total poverty, and we don't want any subgeniuses to make their own situations worse. But some
of you still have jobs.
Subgenius.com is a free subgenius site, with training and training options to help you
Even $5 makes a big difference, even if it's only once a month from enough of you.
$50 makes an even bigger difference.
All we're saying is that glow jobs could go the way of Steve jobs if you don't pay Dobbs.
We also take checks and money orders to Subgenius Foundation.
P.O. Box 181417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118
Thanks for anything you can do to help Let There Be Slack.