Crash! Down! Destroy!
Destroy!
Show...
Good...
Unsheath the sword.
Praise Bob.
Call forth the death squad.
Let loose the dogs.
Show...
Good...
Make Bob your god.
Blasphemy...
Scream the name.
Stretch forth...
thy rod.
Get on...
your knees.
Make me...
your god.
You are about to...
experience the awe...
and mystery...
which reaches from the inner...
mind to...
the subgenius...
Power of...
SWAT!
Welcome potential initiates...
and remain with us for the next...
30 minutes.
Gosh!
Unbelievable!
It's a giant...
electric... thing.
It eats its way through the earth like a...
huge mole.
There it goes!
Uh, yeah, okay, I'm not... wait a minute.
What was it, honey?
What are we going to do about this dreaded scourge?
This show... this horrible...
This looks like a job for Komode Fran.
From the Komodo Islands.
Komode Fran will save the show.
Little Komode Fran.
Good god, what's that? The ground is shaking.
That's the show.
Komode Fran!
Little Komode Fran.
Cutting through the Scleegers.
Throat smack.
Throat smack?
Yes, they gave him a throat smack because he refused...
to participate in the golfer decapitation...
ceremony here at Doc Stock 73.
The judge said...
it was justified homicide.
Yeah!
It was just a...
pied homicide.
It was just a hat that they...
burned on his homicide.
Which side...
was that?
That's the side that does the blind date show...
Oh, that's the third.
Listen, Es...
Yep, we're almost here.
Pug Girl and Weather Man get together.
But whether this ever happens...
only Dobbs knows.
The Churl...
would never miss out on this incredible date.
He's an unprincipled churl, this Bob Dobbs...
Friends...
I had a revelation...
last night...
Right before...
the World Series number one...
I went to a movie...
The movie sucked.
My wallet...
was gone.
Yes, friends...
when I came from the movie theater...
I lifted up my purse and I noticed...
it was a little bit lighter...
than when I walked in.
Unbeknownst to me...
Bob had reached into...
my life again.
And he had taken...
my credit cards.
He had taken my cash.
He had taken...
my Ohio driver's license.
Praise Bob!
Maybe.
Cause when I went home, friends...
after the movie...
when I called up my credit card friends...
and I said, friends...
my wallet is gone.
They said, Bob...
ran up a $755...
dollar bill...
in the space of two and a half hours.
Crazy!
I thought that was professional...
material.
But it really had been Bob.
Nonetheless...
I've canceled my credit cards.
I have no wallet.
I have no money.
But I do have my faith...
in Bob.
And so, friends...
I will sing to you a song...
that I would hope you would join along with me.
Sing it, Sister Maloney!
It's a song called...
My Wallet Belongs to Bob.
Well I used...
to be a sinner...
cause I truly did believe...
that the Virgin Mary, Jesus...
and me were thick...
as thieves.
And I used to give my dough...
to televangelistic snobs.
But then the light had shone upon me...
and I found J.R. Bob Dobbs.
And now my wallet...
belongs to Bob.
Yes, my wallet belongs to Bob.
Well, my heart is for my honey and my brain is for my job.
My wallet belongs to Bob.
Well, Bobby goes a-froppin' every chance that he can get.
He can outperform the biggest without even breaking sweat.
So I gave him all my money.
Reverend Stang said it was right.
And for only $20, actually it was about $30 or $40 or maybe even $50,
he did save my soul tonight.
And so my wallet belongs to Bob.
Yes, my wallet belongs to Bob.
No more can the kids say,
it's a conspiracy my lowly wages rob.
My wallet belongs to Bob.
Well, Bobby's got a sweetie and Connie is her name.
And her ways could put the sacred whore of Babylon to shame.
She reaches in Bob's pocket, feels around for something hard.
And pulls her hand out holding on to her mighty credit card.
And so my wallet belongs to Bob.
Yes, my wallet belongs to Bob.
And I never have to fear, cause I know Connie's on the job.
My wallet belongs to Bob.
Well, you may have your lady and your horny green man too.
Their existential energy may be what's right for you.
But someday you'll grow weary of those paganistic cults.
Give away your money to the one that gets results.
And then your money will be for Bob.
Yes, your wallet will be for Bob.
And you will be subgenius, not another stupid slob.
And your wallet will be for Bob.
Well, I admit it, and much calmer got the bleeding head of Arnold Palmer
sitting on the dashboard of my car.
Pray.
Praise Bob.
Oh, praise Bob.
Oh, praise Sister Melodious Chops there.
Well, finally, we got a decent recording, live recording of that song
by Sister Melodious Chops.
And she went and flubbed one of the last lines on it.
But, you know,
that's the way of this mighty church, I guess.
Let's see.
Okay.
This mighty church, yes.
This one true religion, the one that was put here for you and you alone, yes.
Only you qualify for the, for membership in the church of the subgenius.
With this record, I have provided you with a record.
With the weapon.
For the love of God, get a copy of it into every American home.
The Xerox 5090 Duplicate.
Powerful, state-of-the-art machine.
Powerful copies are on the way.
.
I'll give you a note for your boss.
It'll prove sins.
I would like to be Pope Reverend Citizen Stoli.
Sure.
Can I be that?
Sure, for that, when that...
I've got the 30 bucks, right here.
All right.
The moment of truth.
I'm passing.
The passing of the green.
Let me hold these dollar bills up against my third nostril.
Okay.
And we'll whiff-read the psychic stench.
Yes, yes, he is a true subgenius.
He is a child of the Yeti.
Yeah.
I detect the, the auraic stench, that particular stench.
Um, I, by the authority invested in me by J.R. Bob Dobbs, uh, Xulu, Quar, and, uh, Connie
Dobbs, and Hercules, I, uh, you may now do anything you want for the rest of your life.
Praise Dobbs.
Praise Bob.
Cool.
Stoli, Reverend, what is it again?
Liberated from that which has enslaved him.
Oh, you're Pope Reverend Citizen Stoli.
Wow.
Pope Reverend Citizen Stoli.
All right, got it.
I've passed the money over.
You're official now, man.
Yeah, man.
But what you need to do now is run out and buy the last New Testament.
Oh, yeah.
The New Testament.
Okay.
Uh, Revelation X, that's the new, for people who loved the book of the subgenius,
uh, you know, that was like the Old Testament.
Now we have the new one.
Oh, okay.
Uh, not to be confused with Generation X or any other X-oriented things.
X, okay.
Revelation.
This, this relates to X-Day, the end of the world on July 5th, 1998.
Okay.
Coming up about two and a half years from now.
Very cool.
I'm, I'm prepared.
I'm gonna bone up.
I'm gonna, I'm gonna be the word of Bob.
Be, be the word.
Let Bob speak through you.
Yes.
Actually, if you let Bob speak through you, you can only get a, you can only channel about
one word at a time before your head burns out like an old flash cube.
We have to go through a heck of a lot of slaves and followers just to get a few sentences
for this book.
Well, maybe I'll just hold off on that until I feel as though I'm a little bit more
powerful.
Oh, you should feel more powerful already.
Yeah.
How do you feel, man?
You've just been ordained.
Oh, I feel, uh, literally electric.
Good.
But yet, just a little bit lazy.
Am I gonna get a receipt for this?
Um.
I'm just asking.
What are you trying to write this off?
I don't know.
I just, I, I, I, you know, I, I just gave up 30 bucks to see Stoli become a minister.
I just, you know.
Wasn't it worth your 30 bucks?
It felt good at the time.
All right.
What I really feel like doing right now is sitting on a big couch and eating peanut butter
right out of the, right out of the jar.
Whoa.
You, you have, you have that, that right.
Okay.
Now, of course, we can't guarantee that the conspiracy won't fire you for doing that.
Oh, really?
Is that against the rules?
Well, uh, it depends on which rules.
Well, there are no rules.
No.
There's only one rule in the Church of the Subgenius, and I have to paraphrase it completely
for radio, but to put it politely, if they canst not take a joke, let them mount up upon
themselves.
Yes.
Mount up upon themselves.
That's a nice way of saying it there, uh, Reverend.
I can live by that.
I can live, I can live completely by that law.
I got no problem.
And we will be watching them mount up upon themselves tonight at the, the gigantic
GWAR Massacre.
Praise Bob.
I got into bad jokes there.
All right.
Praise Bob.
We want to thank both of you guys for coming in.
Absolutely.
Reverend Stang and, uh, the Sexecutioner from GWAR.
Lord Sexecutioner.
I thank you, and, uh, Pope Reverend Stoli, uh, Citizen Stoli.
Citizen Stoli.
Sorry.
Pope Reverend Citizen Stoli.
Thank you.
And Brooke.
Yes, thank you.
We're just normal citizens.
Yeah, and I'm, you know, get Revelation X, man, the New Testament.
I gotta check it out.
Thanks a lot for coming in, guys.
Praise Bob.
Happy Halloween.
See you later.
All right.
We have traffic and weather next.
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to man at home on WTSD Radio at Science Woah.
And the show, in this episode of the show, is brought to you all by粉.
If you wanna be part of the show, кудаortalv
.
A Skype server from Google Home.
Gentlemen, boys and girls, River and Ivan Stang is on the phone with us tonight.
Stuck somewhere.
Oh, listen, man, there's three mafia... Can you hear me?
Yeah.
Okay, now, assuming we're not on the air or anything, there's three mafia guys outside the door.
Yeah, wait, let me get that on tape again.
Business.
Man?
Hello?
Yeah, man, we're here.
We ain't going anywhere.
I mean, the preaching business was a dirty...
was always kind of a dirty business.
But, God, jeez, the music business.
Commercial music business?
Yeah.
These guar guys are afraid that we're going to undersell them.
And they sent some sort of...
They're like mafia tough guys that are supposed to follow us around.
Yeah.
And the other thing is...
Okay, we're not on the air or anything, right?
No.
I think they're...
I don't think that those are rubber suits.
That they're wearing?
Yeah, I know that sounds ridiculous, but I don't think that...
That band, guar...
Yeah.
I don't think that...
I mean, part of it, of course, is costumes, but I...
There's a lot of...
I think they...
I think they really are that way.
Yeah.
Did you ever wonder why they...
I knew that ghost was Lagoon.
I knew that.
Did you ever want to know why you want to figure...
Well, that probably was obvious to lots of people.
The priest with the baseball bat.
Were you there when that happened?
I actually missed the moment of truth.
Like, yeah, like, Dr. Katahdin Lagoon,
materialized in the flesh,
risen from the dead,
just like Jesus,
just like the Son of God.
Dr. Lagoon rose from the dead.
And, I mean, we had...
We had wept over him.
We had done...
I mean, this guy had been dead for a month.
I urinated on his body myself.
Age.
And, boy, were a lot of people mad.
You know, they'd spent money on the funeral arrangements
and having him embalmed and everything.
And here he was prancing around with his baseball bat.
Well...
About three blocks down the street,
I walked out.
I was so nonplussed by watching him walk back up on stage.
He can't hear you.
I think you've got to come sit over here.
I can hear the old sailor.
I can hear the old sailor in the background.
Can you hear the old sailor crying in his mud?
Yeah, there he is.
Poor old peg-legged...
One-eyed juiceberry Frank.
...plopping around on deck.
But you said the Gwarza's not in the rubber suits.
No, I don't think they are rubber.
I mean, part of it's a suit.
The spikes and things and the bear traps and the chainsaws are props.
But their skin...
Their faces are really like that.
Well, I thought you said them three goons which was sent around to follow you
was wearing big rubber suits and maybe that's all it is.
Oh, no, the mafia guys are...
You know, they look like mafia guys in a movie or something.
Oh, that's the rubber suits?
Oh, no, no, those aren't the rubber suits.
No, those guys are in rubber suits, too.
I'm trying to tell you something.
You think I'm misunderstanding.
Oh, you mean the ones that look normal are the ones in the rubber suits?
Yes, and actually those are like very, very skinny bobbies are in those suits.
You think some made men are coming around looking for you guys
because of the Gwar thing and stuff
and because of the penitential results of the annual...
The annual...
The tour you're going to be on.
But there's some weird conspiracy of like three or...
300...
It's scribbled here pretty weird
and they said they're going to go out in rubber suits
like these weird pinstripe things looking like John Gotti and stuff.
Yeah, it was like that.
Oh, I guess it wasn't...
But we can't pay them off.
That's the thing.
Devil Aqua doesn't have the money.
Bobco right now is like insolvent
because of the phases of the moon or some ridiculous thing.
It's like Connie Dobbs gets this advice from an astrologer now.
Yeah, but she...
It's out of the picture.
And the mob has moved in.
It's like we were just playing games with...
Oh, we'd kill a preacher here or a hyena popped there.
Yeah, some of the hyenas got popped by the same time.
Guys are like going,
you don't play that game without our permission.
No, not with...
And we own the contract between both bands.
Yeah, especially with the transdigular arrangement
you both got last week.
Somebody said that his head turned into a whole mountainous
huge amount of cabbage and stuff
and was mowed off by a power mower in the middle of it.
Sorry.
No, no, that was one of your dreams.
One of your dreams.
Like the dream of the tape running out.
Listen to that.
Yes, but the fact is, dear friends,
that really neither preaching nor comedy
have traditionally seemed mixed well with rock and roll concerts.
Not even...
Subgenius preaching with elaborate video backdrops
and taped Doctors for Bob music
and lots of props like flying swords
and bleeding heads that talk
and buckets, whole buckets of pills.
Nope, it don't work.
Not even at a GWAR concert.
Now see, there's this band called GWAR
that we went on tour with, sort of.
Meant to do nine cities,
dropped out after five with no hard feelings.
Um, because the thrash speed metal audience
with, you know, the kids with the rings in their noses
and the highly individualated tattoos and so on.
Well, they were too pink, lame, cowardly, and herd-like
to deal with the word of Bob.
Even, even, friends, the audience of GWAR,
which would surprise you if you knew
what masters of huldada are, in fact, those GWAR beings.
And if you're only passingly familiar,
you're familiar with them, uh, with GWAR,
they seem like just another speed metal band
except that they wear rubber monster suits
and are known for onstage fake disembowelings
and abortions in which fake blood, sperm, and urine
are sprayed all over the teenage audience
of pudgy 15-year-old boys.
But, my friends, if you are in discernment,
if you are truly in the spirit,
you would recognize that GWAR is actually
a vastly unappreciated satire band.
And a pretty proficient one, too.
I mean, they're not entirely divorced
from the beloved approaches of, yes, Devo,
yes, Frank Zappa, yes, Mojo Nixon, et al.,
and the Church of the Subgenius.
And they're almost as blasphemous as Doctors for Bob.
Oh, friends, I could go on and on
about the sights I witnessed in their shows
and the incredibly nervy, anti-conspiracy rudeness
in which they indulge onstage, and maybe I will.
And, in fact, I do on the Subgenius website,
but this is only a one-hour show,
so let it suffice to say
that maybe you ought to catch their act in any way you can.
¶¶
Friends, you ever been to an Aguar concert?
Well, they are kind of like the Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles on acid.
Real good acid, a lot of it.
Kind of like the Power Rangers, but X-rated and totally, totally satanic.
Like a Robert Williams painting brought to life, dear friends.
Plus, they have this great-looking, evil, naked girl dancer that breathes fire
and a 19-foot-tall robot monster on stage.
And in the first five minutes of their Ragnarok End of the World tour,
they decapitate O.J. Simpson and disembowel the resurrected corpse of Jerry Garcia.
Plus, the lead singer gets abducted by aliens and the naked dancer babe gets an abortion
while crucified of her mutant baby,
which baby then bites off the face of the subgenius of the band,
the sadistic, sophisticated Arabian Niner.
And the night's S&M genie called the Sexecutioner.
Friends, it's a hell of a show. It really is.
And I think during this song is when they're fighting Cardinal Sin.
Yes, the rubber monster-suited hideous.
And the...
The thing is, friends, I don't think that those are fake rubber suits.
And I don't think it's all fake blood.
Friends, these masters of Bulldada deserve an audience, shall we say,
a bit more appreciative of their artistry
than can be those slope-headed throwback metalheads
who don't even know when they're being insulted and satirized by the heroes.
An audience like, say, the subgeniuses
who can see visions in comic books and wine bottles.
Yes, friends.
It is time that the church throw its full weight behind
and alongside that of noir,
those lowbrow, disgusting,
completely, utterly un-PC,
mostly must-be-censored-to-play-on-the-radio
top of cool rock and roll party band.
¶¶
I've never been so jealous in my life, honest.
I watched GWAR five nights in a row through a black-and-white handycam viewfinder,
and, oh, it was, I just thought to myself, what a fun job that looks like to me.
But I know that you probably want to hear me talk about the drugs and the groupies,
and, yes, they were far, far better than I ever would have imagined.
It was almost as if they must have been completely imaginary, friends.
It was cooler than being Led Zeppelin.
It was cool more along the lines of Spinal Tap.
That's how it really was.
And, by the way, everything that we've been describing on these shows,
the GWAR tour, the GWAR show, the legume death life rituals,
are reported upon in greatly fictionalized detail
with fun and entertainment.
You can find photos on the Subgenius website at sunsight.unk.edu slash subgenius.
We'll give that address again and our P.O. box and everything else.
Although, you know, half of you are still like my grandpa was about TV,
saying, well, I ain't going to get connected to that Internet
and fall for that conspiracy distraction.
I got all the information I need already from all these punk fanzines
published by, well,
they are published by Time Warner now.
Well, it is true that all radio, TV, and publishing
are now controlled by three huge right-wing companies,
but that Internet stuff,
that's nothing but child porno and viruses and dumb chat lines,
just like the newspaper said.
I ain't going to fall for that conspiracy trick.
Anyway, friends, that Subgenius,
this worldwide website address for those so gullible
as to fall for the conspiracy trick of a totally free-to-anybody,
5,000-page Subgenius magazine in full color
with the uncensored versions of this show
and everything else we ever did,
that web address is
http,
see, it always has the P in it,
slash slash,
that's http colon slash slash
sunsight,
S-U-N-S-I-T-E period,
E-D-U,
Sunsight Unc-Ed-U,
slash,
Subgenius.
And friends,
Subgenius does not have an O in it.
I say that for the benefit of many subgeniuses out there.
And if you can only afford a cheap computer,
the news group called Alt.Slack is just as good,
but in a more interactive way.
Sorry to be so vehement about all this,
but while this church of the subgenius is regarded,
as but a pathetic footnote in the so-called real world,
at least until 1998, that, friends,
on the internet, on the other hand,
the church is famous, respected,
totally uncensored, and financially supported.
The internet is the first medium I've ever dealt with
where it isn't who you know, but what you know.
But, oh, you're probably not interested in that.
No, you probably hate computers
and all those complicated instructions like
on, off, connect to, and disconnect.
No, no.
You're too organic for all that complicated dweeb stuff.
Ah, shut up.
Now, let's get back to this.
Guar versus the church.
We ain't gonna be taking any crap from Guar.
I don't care if they're eight feet,
if they are eight feet tall and got monster faces.
But still, it was kind of cool.
Even though their audiences sort of,
well, they really hated us the first night.
I had to change.
I had to change the,
I had to change the preaching style.
I'll try to give you a little sampling
of just how low I had to prostitute the word of Bob
in order to get these stupid,
I mean, they weren't stupid enough to be subgeniuses, man.
I mean, we're talking bad, bad.
But let's see if we can find,
I had to cuss a lot for one thing.
And so we may have to save this for the X-rated show
that you can't hear.
Thank you.
I bet y'all would love to hear Flora.
Yeah.
You will.
I have some good news, some bad news.
The good news is,
Gwar will play.
They will kill everyone in this entire audience.
The comet Ragnarok shall strike this Earth at 1030 tonight
and destroy all the pink normals and human beings
on this planet, Brave Bucks.
The bad news is,
that the great Sleazy P. Martini could not be here tonight.
Sorry.
Instead, he sent me his personal minister.
Yes, he has some religion, believe it or not.
Don't worry, I'm a preacher.
Yes, I'm a preacher from the church of the subgenius, Brave Bucks.
But I'm not going to preach for long.
In fact, I'm not even going to preach at all
because I know that you people want to rock and roll
and whatever it is, jump up and down, hurt each other,
take drugs.
And we've got to tell you,
man, this is going to be a fast show tonight
because there's a curfew at 1030 tonight.
Because the conspiracy of the normal
does not want you to have the kind of freedom
that you'd like to enjoy.
Anyway, I was just back to say,
quit Gwar.
By the way, if any of you ever wondered,
those are not rubber guns.
They're rubber suits.
I wish to God they were.
If they were rubber suits,
my butt would not be so sore right now.
But I was backstage with a band taking drugs.
I cannot keep up with them.
They take some damn strong drugs.
They start with PMP laced with PCT and crack.
And then they take canisters of mace.
And huff them.
They suck mace out of a can.
I had to cut a really good line right there
about groupies, let's say.
The comfort with their nakedity.
Anyway, friends, you're in for an evening
of glorious hate.
Hate and destruction.
And music for the end of the world, dear friends.
And I'm here to perform the last rite.
For the planet.
Oh, by the way, I was warned
that audiences here in Chicago
are the most violent, mean, depraved audiences in the world.
Yee-ye-ye-ye-ye-ye!
Time for a play, Chicago!
Oh, God.
See, it...
Yeah, it's awful, friends.
That's what it took in order to survive at all
in the seriously demanding,
in some ways, world of heavy metal rock and roll concerts.
What they're demanding of, I think,
is that you be able to play a guitar.
And I can't play a darn guitar.
I can hardly even play a tape, dear friends.
Oh, but that I can do.
The only difference between Church of the Subgenius
and all the other ones is,
at least we admit how full of bulls we are.
And the one thing that the Church of the Subgenius
has in common with GWAR
is that we fuck.
We hate the conspiracy of the normal, ordinary human being.
Hate!
Hate is what it's all about.
The warranty on this planet is about to expire,
and Bob Dobbs is the one who can provide you
the extended service policy.
And Bob Dobbs is the one who's been
holding this all this time.
All right.
We'll see you next time.
Take care.
Bye.
Did you ever feel confused?
All become to their use
You know, hit the gas, the juice
Maybe you should watch the news
We have loyal
We have higher
We ignore you
We were sent here to destroy you
We have loyal
We ignore you
We were sent here to destroy you
We won't have to wait too long
Lots of people making bombs
City bombs
Fertilizer bombs
Yeah
Totally amusing
You wonder why our lives are crumbling
You won't give us any money
Without asking what you get
To give up your fucking sex
But your actions, they shall flow me
They're just waiting for the moment
Now I'm thinking that just me
One day I'll pass on your grave
How do you know?
Stand up and say, I'm not your enemy
One, two, go
We are a race
We'll smash your face
One, two, go
You're a machine
I find obscene
One, two, go
Know what I mean?
You can do something, do nothing
You really fucking think you're something
Hold on, baby, time is coming
Yes!
Yeah, we might be four, you know, I had it.
I had a job at one time.
I had an experience at a job.
I was pulling in good 40 Gs.
Had a car, plenty of credit cards.
And then I found Bob.
Now I'm happy.
Dumbass!
A brief moment there of the sales table
outside the GWAR concert in Chicago or Milwaukee or someplace.
The sacred agent, Steve Devalaqua,
would run the sacred sales table
trying to sell the swag, the Dobbs t-shirt,
the shorts and magnet, you know, fridge magnets and tapes and so forth
to these metalheads who'd never heard of this stuff.
It got into some pretty intense discussions every now and then.
But boy, they didn't want to buy anything
until the very last night that we were on the tour.
Reverend Devalaqua, in desperation, finally,
happened upon the secret sales formula
that would work even for the rock and roll audience.
The kid would come up to Steve and say,
you know, well, like, what's this subgenius thing all about?
And instead of Steve trying to explain how the kid's slack had been robbed away
by the conspiracy, he would say,
Church of the Subgenius?
Oh, it's this thing that started in Texas
and then it became really popular in California.
And now it's what all the kids in Seattle are doing.
And the kid would invariably at that point go,
oh, I'll take one of those shirts.
Oh, man.
My people are destroyed for lack of knowledge, dear friend.
You know, so, but I'm happy.
That's the difference.
That's what really counts.
I freed myself from the shackles of the conspiracy.
Are you guys anti-religion or pro?
Oh, we're pro.
Believe it or not.
It's a disorganization for mutants, misfits, disbelievers,
or anything.
And for those who will believe anything,
the people that definitely wouldn't like it
are the ones who believe one thing.
And they aren't going to be shaken from that no matter what
because it makes them too uncomfortable.
This is for the people who are more comfortable.
Hi, how you doing?
Yeah.
We're kind of checking one thing out after another.
Who's the coolest?
Who's repping stones?
So Bob's been around?
Bob's been around.
Bob's been around, yeah.
I knew Bob a long time ago.
Really?
Did you meet Bob?
Did you ever meet Bob?
I know a lot of Bob's friends.
I saw him get killed once.
I actually did see him.
The one time I saw him in person was the first time he was assassinated.
In San Francisco.
Yeah, it was like 1980.
He gets killed quite a bit.
Yeah, he gets killed by his own followers.
That's not cool.
You know, otherwise it turns into just any old bridge.
So it's like we don't know.
So Bob got killed.
We saw him get killed for the first time.
And he got killed many times.
He was shot, I believe.
Yeah.
I saw the video.
It's on the Rise video, actually.
For $20.
Yeah.
That's that.
No, no, no.
He bounces back.
It's like, you know, when Bugs Bunny gets blown up.
Like Jason Mayer?
He shows up with a bandaid on, you know.
It's fun.
It's fun to, you know, kill your profits.
Right.
He's Bob Dobbs.
Yeah.
You know, he's a horrible fraud.
Bob Dobbs.
Well, is there any way to prove it?
Is there any way to prove it?
The more you struggle against the net, the more enmeshed you become.
We have questions.
You know, what you all need to do is subscribe to my successful course in sex and real estate.
That's right.
You do.
He did it himself, and look what a success he's been just in the last two hours.
That's right.
It's just amazing.
You could be me on my houseboat with two bucks and companions, or my giant mansion with
terrified cowering servants and fleet of luxury automobiles.
But, of course, if you want real happiness, you could own Dockstock Central.
You could own Dockstock Island.
You could own the cliffs of Dockstock right here on the cliffs of Dockstock.
Could you really become a millionaire if you are open to the possibilities?
You can become a millionaire if you are open to the possibilities.
And if you want more than the material wealth offered by this smarmy world, you could be
swimming in a bucket of pills on this show.
And you could be fighting against those little gel capsules washing over your head.
You could be digesting them as we speak at Dockstock.
You could be about to join in on the head launching for today.
Thank you.
You could be attempting to do something with the material wealth of the world.
None of that was funny.
That's not funny.
Then we offer a higher road.
It's up to you to choose.
And it means, you can join us in the future somehow.
And when Dockstock is a little bit safer for people like you and me.
And...
many of our middle-aged female.
You won't have to actually bring your own starter fluid and lubrication.
We've got a whole show to sell you.
Indeed.
So send your DocTalk pre-registration fee.
You can't extrude your own substance.
Yes, but you can excrete.
No, you can't.
Let us draw a curtain over this.
Gentlemen, you can't do that.
We have 11 minutes left of excretion.
Okay, so call us now.
What was that number again?
How are these kids getting it?
Are they Xeroxing it?
They're getting it from Post Office Box 140306 in Dallas, Texas, 75214.
I'm going to give that number again.
This is the address for Bob.
This is the address to write for information about this very thing you're hearing now.
That's Bob.
Bob.
No, you do want to do it.
At Post Office Box 140306, Dallas, Texas, 75214.
This is surface noise in the background.
Long body and a sound bar.
Yeah.
We have you.
Call the police.
Yeah, well, no, my feelings were doing some, were picking up something, but it was just static.
I hope.
Well.
Yeah, no, those guys, the guys in the bear suits were just doing an advertisement.
Do they want money?
Mafia suits and the rubber mafia suits were working for, not, they're not working for Guar.
They're working for Guar's management.
Guar is okay.
Oh, for sleazy.
Don't pay any attention to this.
I want to go down in the other room.
You know, they feed them, and then they let them out of the cage.
They go out, and they do the show, and they go back in the cage.
For the manager, what's his name?
Sleazy or something, right?
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
And he sleazy gives them the pay.
Hey, we're in the middle of our radio sign.
Reach deep, deep, deep, deep into your pocket.
A T-shirt.
A deep pool, a pocket pool.
And grapple with that organ that you feel down there deep in your pocket.
It's called your wallet.
Wallet gland.
Pull it slowly out of its receptacle.
And pop it out.
And de-beak it, whip it open.
Yank out that cash and call 687-6900.
And if you place $25, you get yourself a 95 edition T-shirt.
They will tell you the secret code behind that phone number.
The secret lyrics.
I'm saying that.
When you buy.
When you buy cartel foods, punishments or ointments,
or any kind of luxury entertainment item like a record,
it does not in any way affect the Church of the Subgenius
except for to make Reverend Stang poorer,
unless you buy his or her products.
Oh, that's what I thought you said.
But I didn't want to say it too loud,
just in case, you know, the guys were standing out in front of the door
smoking a cigarette.
No, the communists are out to get us.
And big business is out to get us.
Well, I've talked to a few.
I guess it's a sign.
It's a sign of success to have the mob, you know, trying to bully you.
Well, you know, they kind of make their little statement, you know.
You're not really.
It's like when the government has a dossier.
You haven't really made it until, you know, you've met up with some of the suits, you know.
So if I were to look at it that way, I'd say you're due for some success, buddy.
Maybe somewhere on a lonely road between here and Columbus or something.
But, gee, boy, that sounds.
It sounds.
Show business is really exciting.
It is.
It is, especially when you travel with a band that is named after something which is bad for your teeth.
Jeez, this thing's got stuck right in here.
But I don't even know why or how the increments got involved
or how you managed to play with them so often for the next few months.
Well, I'm only going to play with them until it wears off.
Until it turns black and falls off.
But it could wear on tomorrow night, couldn't it, at the Odeon Theater if you were to go there?
Oh, man.
Oh, the thought is so odious.
But it's actually, tomorrow could be the end of the world.
The band apparently has decided that this is going to be their only performance
because there's not going to be a planet Earth left after tomorrow night.
You mean they already know something we don't know?
Well, there's a comet.
There's a comet that is apparently on the way to Earth.
And the scientists have been, you know, laughing it off because it's, you know,
It's going to blast into the Earth, so I'm sorry.
The medicine worms were not in line.
It wasn't lined up with the medicine worms in such a way that it was going to hit Earth.
But Guar knows better.
Guar knows better.
The idea is that tomorrow night at the Odeon Theater,
they're going to defeat the one bad force so that they can become the other bad force.
And hitch a ride on the comet in some metaphysical sense.
They call this comet Ragnarok.
Well, see, that's what I thought was the ultimate purpose of their organ,
was to ultimately meld or merge with the Ragnarok and the grogs of old,
which came out as some kind of space dummies and beat everybody up.
But that wasn't supposed to happen until way beyond X-Day even.
But so it's happening tomorrow?
Well, that's what they think.
But, you see, here's the thing.
Here's the deal.
If Guar is right and the world ends tomorrow,
then I stand to lose my plane ticket, my plane fare, you know.
But if they're wrong and the world continues to end night after night after night,
then they have to fulfill the contract and I come out ahead.
That's why the mafia is here.
They're kind of like the insurance company.
That's made up of people.
They're making sure that everything works.
They work for the record company.
I mean, the record company is hand in hand.
You know, they're in bed with the shop.
Yeah, we all know that.
We're all conspiracy buffs down here.
We know they're all in with the, yeah.
Poppin'.
They're in with, and Smirsh.
And Smirsh, too.
Yeah.
Yeah, Smirsh and the rest of the underworld.
In fact, there are some underworld groups.
And KGB.
Well, the KGB remnant units?
Or are you talking about the old...
Iron Green Butt.
Oh, I missed that one about Beatrice.
The Foods Corporation.
They have their own hit squads.
And it's all over a lousy potato chip.
Bet you can't eat one.
Bet, you know, better, you better, you know, so on.
Eat a couple thousand or I'll blow off your face.
And speaking of coming out ahead,
how many times have it, has it been in your life
since you, you know, you've always been coming out a big fat head?
And yet, you know, you're not gonna make a single dime off this tour
if these guys rub you, you know, the wrong way and stuff.
Well, get this.
We have to charge as much for our pills
as they charge for their pills.
It's like they throw buckets of pills to the audience.
And we've done that, you know, both.
We've done that for years, too.
Yes.
And it's a good...
Luckily, the pills are completely different.
They're sort of counteract ours.
So you're saying absolutely nothing will happen?
Right.
Ours make you bleed and theirs clot.
Blood clot.
You're listening to WCSB.