The Self Genius Hour of Sack
Pain inside, pain is for you and for me
a good thing we all have a spare.
We're born with a spare. I don't
have a spare. Well, we're all born with
spare parts, but
do we need to use them? We don't need to use
them, then why, well, never mind that.
Evolution has many
tricks up its sleeves,
and we can't,
it is not for us to know. You know,
evolution works in mysterious ways. I've been
thinking about this just recently. I've been thinking
about people with strange mutations on
their bodies, unusual things. Well, they don't
not mutations, they're new things
that happen within a generation
and go away. They're not
transitional, they're
momentary. I had
to have mine removed.
Yeah, but the thing is, once you have them
removed, you have to find a safe spot
to put them. And the insurance
won't pay for that stuff. They consider
it all
cosmetic. Right. It's cosmetic,
so you have
to have it done. And in the fine print,
since it's considered cosmetic and
dangerous, which is another way they get out
of, you know, oh, well, we can use
all the parts from it being dangerous and all the parts,
you know, balancing them against each
other, and you have to pay, and they don't.
That's pretty much what it amounts to. But
it is a dangerous operation, and many people
haven't made it to the other side
of whatever it was they were
on the other side of. Friends, we
hope that whatever side you're trying
to get to, that you make it.
And we have faith
that you will.
We think you have what
it takes, listener.
Young hearts, tiny minds,
and huge vegetable
mastiffs stretching from ear to
ear. It's a cornhead
deluxe, filled with power.
Oh, sorry. Oh, no, I was
just checking to see if Princess We has
returned. Princess We is in
the studio. Is Dr.
Sinister in the building? Actually,
it is Charleston that has
gone to let
him in on the library
level, and yes, everything is handled.
Okay, so it's secure. Charleston is secure.
Thank goodness.
Princess We is going to be famous
tomorrow. She'll be in the St. Patrick's
Day Parade. Now, for those listening
to other stations besides the one
in Cleveland on this moment now today,
the Ides of March,
it's too
late for you. But for the Clevelandites,
the Clevelandians,
Princess We will be in
the St. Patrick's Day Parade
downtown tomorrow.
She'll be doing the
hoop polka, which is a non-existent
dance. No, she'll be
clogging and slap-stepping.
She'll be, um...
She's not going to be dancing.
It's, um... Oh, here it is. Speaking of dancing...
Would you join me
in a minuet, Dave? Oh, I'm much too peculiar.
Would you care to watch me take off
my hat? No, there's too much...
Oh, it's not a real
arrangement there. It's equipment.
Oh, no. Don't mess with the equipment.
You guys are strange.
But look, it works. Twist this
one this way. I have never seen...
seen anything like this in my
life. What in the world?
I love these tights. I just love
prancing in tights. What are they up to?
I've never
seen anything like this. Oh, look, you've stained
them. Are you breathing here hard?
Oh, I'll be breathing.
God.
Oh, look, here comes the king.
Get behind those bushes there. What will become
of the baron?
What will become
of the baron? Well, um,
I have a list of pet peeves.
Oh, no. Another long
litany of pet peeves. Oh, man.
You're gonna get peeve-y on us again? That's two closes in one
word. You're not supposed to... God.
Actually, my list is only one
and I was hoping you guys would have more
pets to peeve off
on than I do. You could say net needs.
I have one, but you go
ahead and I'll chime in with mine later.
People who leave the TV blaring
when visitors come to visit,
especially honored visitors such as
myself, who have come from
miles and yet,
for some reason, people feel that
the TV
like a campfire, as Doc Frop
explained it to me. A loud campfire.
Well, that's the thing. Doc Frop at least turns
the campfire down, so you still
find your eye being drawn over
to the shiny, colorful
box. But there are so
many who choose
when visitors come,
especially deaf ones like me,
to turn the TV up.
Right. So they don't hear you. Not only
do they not turn it off, they turn it up
to make sure everybody can hear it over the
conversation with the visitors. Right, so everything you say
as an honored guest must be greeted with
What? Oh yeah.
I'll admit it. I'm a TV snob.
I look at people. Every time I
walk by TV, I think to myself,
how can people eat that? How can they
put that in their bodies?
What? Nasal drip? I'm a
nasal drip adjudicator. I
got a certification last week.
You have a piece of paper that says your
nasal, your nose can
educate? No, adjudicator.
I actually solve remedy
disputes, or sometimes they call us a crisis
eliminator. Yeah, my dad used to do that.
Adjudicator.
Yeah. Like if you were, what's his name?
Harry Grunt? One of the people from the
old days.
I hear this Brazilian
music and I just want to take off my pants and
dance. Yeah, me too. I know exactly how you
feel. I feel like it's Brazil in São Paulo.
Yeah. Or Rio de Janeiro.
If you take your pants off in Rio de Janeiro,
when you come back, they will be gone.
Well, it's fine and dandy
if you're wearing tights. A little boy will have stolen them
and then that night the little boy will be killed by
right-wing marauding
murderers. Death scrams.
But if you're a woman, you're wearing
tweens anyway, so it doesn't
matter because nothing was being covered by
your pants anyway.
Okay, which peeve pet did you have?
Mine is that when people
say the exact opposite of what
they mean, and I really only have
one good example,
and that's when people say,
I could care...
care less when they mean
I couldn't possibly
care less. That really
bugs me. Irregardless of
what they might say otherwise. Thank you.
Thank you. Exactly. Irregardless
is another perfect example. And then there are
just...
Orientation-wise is one that
bothers me. Unlimited numbers.
When people have... Orientation? Yeah.
We have to get orientated.
What about...
Whatever happened to oriented?
You know,
can't we just be oriented?
No, orientated. Do we have to get orientated?
Are you a dictator who has to
orientator everyone?
Or dictatorate. It would be if they
were dictatorating or something.
That's not a bad dictatorate.
That has a ring to it.
I am the dictatorator.
As long as I'm the dictatorator.
As long as I am the dictatorator.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
I wish we
would suddenly go to this.
Listen to this one.
Come in.
Cigarette.
Did you?
Fellas and girls eat a hearty delicious breakfast this morning
with swell tasting tender guns with lichen and fruit?
Remember Chris. Natural and delicious guns furnish extra food values of swell tasting lichen and nut like iron.
For a hearty breakfast dish you like to eat,
get natural lichen and delicious guns.
Follow all of these rules and you will survive.
To speak properly,
it is necessary to enunciate every syllable.
Enunciate every syllable.
Enunciate.
Hey man, did you see that they have this graphic on the webpage for the show now?
On the KPFA webpage.
Deranged edit segue into a cascade of echoing glossoleliac madness.
I'm going to go to the
boss.
Arr arr arr.
Arrrrr.
It's not about some-
The voicing of lyric ruminations from the free falling brains of disintegrating personalities.
Wanted videotape.
That's what sold me the last two words there.
Disintegrating her- Yeah.
Yeah.
I think that's- I think I'm one of those.
To you!
Wait a minute.
Did they put that down in the right-
Oh no!
It's a little silver box.
I don't know what I- let's open it up and see if anyone-
Don't touch that!
Oh let's just look inside.
Oh, I see.
It has a Dobbs head on the top of it.
There must be something interesting in here.
Oh, okay.
It's the little box full of show with puzzling evidence, which we just heard.
And before that, some cut-ups by Norell Preff.
And mostly, in this case, by Fernandanande Leemur.
Out there in the wilds of Colorado, up in the mountains.
That's where Leemur cuts those sounds up.
In his cabin, deep in the most farthest reaches.
The most farthest reaches of the Rockies.
Now, I heard that he's sexually a Pythagorean.
That he doesn't believe in geometry unless it's with the wrong gender.
No one knows.
It is a mystery.
Leemur is a true mystery man among the subgeni.
In fact, I only know of one.
There is one other subgenius who has met him.
And that is Mr. Sistar.
Who lives around the corner from us.
But Mr. Sistar has a far reach in his vision.
And so he was able to actually go and track down and see Leemur.
What a guy. What a guy.
Who he said was surprisingly serious.
Now, are Pythagoreans a want to seriousness?
Or perhaps is that their lot in life?
To view things on the gray side.
To perhaps make too many.
To make confusing choices.
That later they have to clean up themselves after four.
On it.
Yes.
Well, see, I thought so.
I not only thought.
What you said.
Yeah.
I knew you knew what I was saying.
Times three.
I knew that.
No, I just think that some of them might be seditious.
They might be against the natural laws of God in America.
And, you know, crying out in the wilderness like that is not going to help us.
Right.
And, you know, Plato's cave.
They should have, you know, flamethroned the whole thing.
Gotta be.
I've noticed that God applies different laws to America than he does to other countries.
Seems so.
Such as Texas.
The eyes of Texas are upon us.
I can smell them.
Get back from the way we've been deadlined.
It's a fast-paced environment definitely glowing in the undergear.
You'll...
What?
What the hell are you...
It's Texas.
Look, it's the Longhorns.
Oh, sorry.
I'll gore you.
It's been a tough winter, friends.
And it's only going to get tougher.
I fear.
Or our gas price is going to be going down.
Or will the weather get a lot better?
How about the economy, boy?
I'm sure that'll pick up again.
How about the war?
I'm totally...
I told you it was a comedy show.
Stop, you're killing me.
You're killing me, literally.
Stop it, you're killing me.
Oh, boy.
I wish they killed far less of us and gave more of us decent jobs and housing.
And not here.
Perhaps someplace in outer space.
Perhaps someplace...
Well, you know, there is...
One could actually move.
Were one to find oneself in a...
Just a...
This is a stretch.
I know this is a stretch.
But imagine if you found yourself...
Somehow in this country where...
Things had changed.
And it wasn't really a free democracy anymore.
And in fact, it was almost like what we were raised to think Russia was like.
You had to have permits for everything.
And they wouldn't even let you smoke.
Even in a bar.
I mean, where the things were that totally controlled.
You do have the choice so far still of moving.
Now, where to move to?
I can't tell you.
Some would head south to Mexico.
Well, Reverend Ron...
Some would head north to Canada.
I personally would probably head for the Komodo Islands.
Scandinobria.
That's a place, I think.
Which?
Scandinibria.
Oh, Scandinibria is where Stang would certainly go.
I hear they have really good beer in Scandinibria.
The Scandinibriate beer or something.
No, that was a band.
It was...
Scandinibriational.
Yarn.
Yarnor and the Scandinibriate.
Yarnor.
Yarnor and the Scandinibriate and Octet.
Boy, and they stunk, too.
That's another thing that's going to be happening in the 1984-2008 world of the future.
Is an old factory police force coming around, checking people's armpits in different parts of their bodies.
Uh-oh.
To see if they...
With alacrity and with a smile on their concussion, if they can absolutely enclose the pumpkin, the idea of it.
I mean, you know, to get the whole thing around.
Around it.
You're not allowed to smell anyway, but the way you're allowed to smell.
I know I have to be careful how I smell when I go out.
I have to be careful what I urinate when I go out.
Yeah, it's color.
You have to be color-coded.
Too much red in your urine means that you have to go to a white place to wait in a green zone, I guess they call it.
Too much purple, you have to go to the green zone.
Yeah.
If there's too much...
It's like opposite colors.
Well, the prunes do not help that, though.
They can cloud the operation.
They can make things different.
I forgot the word.
When you get a test and they make it confusing.
I think that's called the conspiracy.
The conspiracy.
They want you to learn math.
They want you to learn aesthetics.
They want you to learn plumbing and geometry.
Actually, I don't...
I'm really teaching you.
It's mind control.
Yeah, I don't think they really do want too many people to learn geometry and trigonometry and so forth.
I think they're trying to let us become more stupid so that we're more easily satisfied and more easily controlled.
I can't wait for that day to come when they finally succeed in making me even more stupid than I am.
As hard as that may be to imagine, even for a subgenius.
That day shall come when even I shall be satisfied with what's on TV.
It is hard to imagine.
Yes, and I'll fix you right if you'll take Jack, my dog.
The sample is not real, nor is the sampler.
Sit back in your easy chair and make things far more difficult.
Thank you.
I understand that you understand me.
Can you hear me?
I'm down here.
Please.
Please let me out.
I can hear the music.
I can see the funny feet dancing overhead.
I know you're having a party.
I see the dog's head and the smiling face.
Let me out.
I'm right above you and you can't see me.
Help!
Help?
Shit!
mantenstensow gap
Don't you think my rigged eyes mightesc benefit you?
Yippie!
Oh, it ain't a biggie!
or something.
I've actually been to an effects world.
On my brief stint as
assistant director of a Devo
music video in Hollywood in
1986,
the Devos and I, or
Jerry and I, went looking for props
and we went into a
prop warehouse
where you could, for instance, there were
bins of chopped
off human limbs
that had been used in horror movies
and war movies. There was, I mean,
separate bins. There was a bin for feet
and legs, a bin for
arms and hands, and a bin
for heads. There was even a torso
bin for babysitters
who had been torso-ized
in the horror movies.
That must have been awfully gruesome.
Hollywood has some
unusual stores, it's true.
It really does. There's a store for the, a special
store for the foam that they
use, well, the different pyrotechnic
foams they use. Well, what they wouldn't,
the store that I, that
people like me and not even
Jerry Casale can get into
are the stores where you buy
the real chopped off
feet. Yeah, the real parts.
Not foam rubber cast and painted, but
actual dead people's parts
for swinging
sexy parties among the really
rich and powerful. Is that how
Sister Decadence did that
Kali that one year?
Because those were awfully realistic. No,
those were false chopped
rubber, they were all alike.
It's weird what the necrotic, the
necrosis of tissue does
to things. It makes it look like
the made-up primavera dance
that you've done with the macrame and
paper mache. Actually, it
looks a lot more lifelike in
death than the actual
removed foot. I can understand
that. See, some of those parts have been prepared
and kept frozen all the way since
the Civil War. Remember the Civil War, they'd give them a hit
at the lot and chop off their leg, you know, even if you got
an ingrown toenail perhaps from marching.
Dave, did you hear the news that there were,
left feet washing up on the shore
in Canada? Did you hear
that? I mean, I'm not making
up a subgenius news story. There's no punchline?
There's no punchline? Yes, there is, but this
was a true story that there were
three different
times recently
men's left feet
chopped off, still in a shoe, have
washed up on the eastern
coast of Canada.
Now, by some coincidence,
I got in the mail
three different times,
right feet, chopped off men's right feet
came to the subgenius post office box,
181417, Cleveland Heights,
Ohio, 44118.
And Nicky Deathchick
informed me that in Wisconsin
they're starting to find chopped off feet.
But they're right feet? I think
we've got a theme on this show, chopped
off feet. She didn't specify
whether they were right or left. Now, all the
ones I've been getting are right feet, and all the
ones that washed up in Canada were left feet.
Is that right? Right. Now, you remember they say
people vote with their feet,
now some of these are actually Malian
votes. Malian. Yeah, Malian
votes. Or Mahler.
Mahler, I mean, well, you know, they're
votes. But, now, see, I forgot
what the hell I was talking about. Did you remember?
No. No, it had something to do
with one was right. Oh, yes, they're sending
you a message. They are sending you a message
because when you chop off
someone's left voting utensil,
that means get the hell out of Dodge.
When they chop off your right
utensil, that means you
get out of Dodge.
They're talking to you. They can cut off both
voting utensils. They're sending you a message,
Dave. Crawl out, yeah.
You're not going to be able to walk anywhere. Crawl out
on your bloody stumps. Crawl on your
bloody stumps. It's hard. I don't know if
there's such a thing as a free erection
in this country anymore, but we're going to find out right
now.
This is, this is how it
works.
Darker and stronger.
Ah, smell it.
It smells, it smells every
time. Subliminal, subliminal, subliminal,
sub, sub, sub. We open the little door,
it goes, ip, ip, ip, ip, ip, ip, ip.
Noisy.
Mmm, solid.
When it comes to crack,
some kids never grow up.
It will beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, make the
rear larger. That's all.
Stop it, stop it. Let yourself
go. Why hold yourself back?
Ask your securities
dealer for a free direction.
Yes.
I am the whistler.
Go ahead, open the door. Go ahead.
Yeah. Alright.
Just a minute. Yeah.
Yeah. Big deal.
Big deal.
Five years.
For a period of two years.
Sixteen.
Head, head, head, head, head, head, head, head, head.
Slick and dangerous.
Rangers.
Allow us to waste precious time given to us.
Loving our own selves.
Welfare.
I, I, I, I, I, I, I, i, i, i, i, i, i, i, i, i, i, i, i, i, i, i, i, i, i, i, i, i, i, i, i, i, i, i, i, i, i, i, I, visible.
We have nothing.
Mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm.
I apologize.
So it doesn't matter.
Tedious.
For the past two years we have had a mess.
You have killed one person
and shot at and wounded another person.
Hehehehe.
This is a whole thing.
What we're finding is we need to teach this earlier
from kindergarten through 12th grade
and embedding it into our current curriculum.
This is bad.
Why?
I seriously doubt it.
They eat, they eat, they gorge themselves.
They're going to be obese.
Get these drugs upstairs.
Get those drugs upstairs.
You can't get the drugs here.
You have to go upstairs to get the drugs.
Drugs?
Yes.
Oh, man.
Get the J2 Paisy.
This show gets into my head.
It's partly because of Norrell Preff.
That was the guy that cut up some of that stuff there.
It's always hurting my brain.
And Lee Murr.
There's a lot of research that goes into that work by Norrell Preff.
In the first place, the guy is a student of the arcane sciences,
and he knows how to grab a person's subconscious
and the inner workings of their mind
and just...
He's peeing poop all over it like a dog.
Yeah, you can just flat out...
He just treats you as if you were like, you know,
his object of insinuation.
Well, it's not like we hide from the listeners
the fact that we're influencing them subliminally.
We use subliminalism and sublimation together
to create an intense frustration in the mind of the listener
to the point where they finally...
It builds up to an explosive point, a mass...
an uber frustration, which finally explodes.
And that is the moment of slack.
We call this the thyroid and the mid-pineal orgasm.
When the pineal gland begins to swell
and various parts of the five and six
and the nectar skin of the enrolled vehicle become collapsed,
the whole brain explodes.
Ow!
Oh, look, see, look, you're turning Princess Wee on with that.
And it was the only fun I had
while I was doing my thing in the stand, man.
Now I...
Ah!
Wait, Dr. Kerstaus.
You forgot what very important thing.
I forgot what you forgot.
Wait, I'll be right back.
Wow.
This is Stephen Kent is the music.
In the background from his album, Oil and Water.
Which do not mix.
Actually, they do if you take them to Brushwood.
He's didgeridooing.
And Brush, the place where X-Day and Starwood are festivals happen.
Water and oil mix.
And you can judge a book by its cover.
And you can look a gift horse right down the goozle.
Squarely in the oculux.
Yeah.
Ah, what a divine place.
Right in the teeth.
How long have you been there, my friend?
You have the gray cast and the white hairs of an elderly gent.
Yet at the same time, you have the spry,
spry nimble step of an awkward young teenager.
What's your secret?
Have you been to this Sherman in the woods long?
Have you been X-ing it for a while?
My secret is I collect subgenius material
every way I can.
And that has given me...
the slack and patience that so few are able to achieve in this day and age.
Now, explain this piece of artifacture here.
Nope.
It's hairy and it's not human hair, is it?
Don't let the listeners see that.
Is this yeti hair?
What kind of hair is this?
Don't let the listeners see that.
Keep that one away from camera three.
Oh, don't worry.
The listeners can't see anything.
They can only hear with their mind's ear.
And their huge third nostril.
Say, I saw an interesting TV program
on the internet
called Life After People.
Not The Future is Wild or Life After Man,
but Life After People.
It was on the History Channel
and it was about how long it would take
for nature to completely reclaim our great cities.
And it was the coolest porno.
It was like...
Sort of like that movie...
I'm the Legend of Zombies.
It was like...
It would show New York as it is now
and then suddenly the grass...
As if by time lapse it showed grass and trees
growing up through the pavement
and cracking the windows out
and the bridges all snapping and falling down.
Man, I felt like to mess up my whole rug
watching that.
I was so turned on.
It was the hottest end of the world pornography.
Too bad no dinosaurs were doing it two on one.
That would be too much.
That would have taken me right over the edge.
You know, I collect end of the world movies
which means that's going to be...
You know, there's one every week now.
You don't need many actors
when you're shooting an end of the world movie.
The world's ended.
Most everybody's dead.
So you get your boy and his dog
and he meets the girl
and then the dog eats the girl.
The end.
It's a beautiful, beautiful story of the end times.
Boy and his dog.
I remember that story.
Yes.
But not very well.
What I remember better
was the time you did in the joint
for what you did to Hilda Bullswine's.
You dirty, rotten...
You...
You flaccid...
You blew it all to hell.
God damn you.
You...
Well, what was the end of the world movie?
We just saw Southland Tales
which I can only recommend
to the most hard-hearted subgeniuses
who might actually like it.
It's hard to like.
But it...
It...
Go over and over again.
You hear the line in that one.
This is the way the world ends.
This is the world...
The way the world ends.
Not with a whimper
but with a bang.
And then they kind of cheat you
because you never get the big bang at the end.
No, you never do.
They just taunt and tease you
all through the movie about it.
But it does fit into the category
of end of the world movies.
And it was one of those movies
that the conspiracy sat on, sort of.
It might have shown at the art house
for a week or two.
Southland Tales.
It was by the guy that did Donnie Darko.
Yeah, and from the smell of it
they did sit on it for quite a long time, too.
By the time it reached
the average distribution house
which is not to say that some aren't average.
That some are...
Yeah.
A little abnormal.
I knew Ab.
I remember Ab.
He usually is at X Day.
Reverend Ab Normal.
And there was Oob,
his younger, unresolved brother.
They all had like Oob type names, didn't they?
Princess, wait.
When we woke up this morning,
I was dreaming that there was a baby's leg
sticking out from between my legs.
I was giving birth
and only this baby,
only the leg of the baby had emerged.
I just suddenly,
that just suddenly came into my head.
That was a most disturbing dream.
It is so disturbing.
It's still disturbing.
Well, you're giving birth to something
and it's taking a long time
and I don't think...
It was coming.
It was a breach, you know.
I mean, it was just one leg.
How do you get one leg out of a guy?
But don't be disappointed
when there's no head connected to the leg.
It was a big leg, though.
No, you transferred the famous story.
Daddy happy.
Right.
Our speaker from last weekend
that was delivering a breach birth,
that was, you transferred that story in your mind.
Ina May Gaskin had to deliver a breach birth
and you see, you just transferred that
combined with the advertisement for the hot dog
that was on the back cover
of the Green Lantern comic book.
Remember?
I chose not to.
Staying where you have earned.
Ha!
The End
Hey, cut it out.
Hey, cut out.
Say, how did you...
I thirst for knowledge.
Huh?
Deep, dumb, and blind.
Beat it, huh?
Beat it, beat it, beat it, beat it, beat it.
You're a fowler-upper.
You know, if I had a glass of beer, I'd cry into it.
Hey!
Hollins, smell up.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Beaten, stabbed, and tortured.
How do I know?
You don't.
You're right.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
I know nothing.
Get down.
You see too much.
You're getting awfully close to a bullet in your head, mister.
Shh.
There's someone at the door.
Yes.
Ow!
Hink, hink, hink.
Ah!
Mrs. Qualley.
Well, what does he want me to do?
Come, go, turn handsprings, quote Shelley, play the bassoon?
Rat that even rats on rat pitch and catch.
What?
Yeah, I pitch like this.
Ow!
Would you mind joining me here in the shaft, please?
And we're right near the top of the shaft.
Yes.
We've got to get off.
Here's news.
You can now get yellow sticks in all states where laws permit.
Yes, sticks.
Already colored a rich golden yellow.
You'll find yellow sticks cost a little more, largely because of the federal stick tax.
But it's a real saving for you in time and trouble.
Remember, where state laws permit, you can buy yellow sticks at the low economy price.
Try the new yellow sticks.
Smoke guns.
Like I said, brains got two sides.
We're on our bed.
You want to fill in the details for me?
I'll tell you this.
The plane switch might now be a coaxing good one.
Yeah.
All right, that's it.
Can't live without it.
Okay.
Well said.
Well put.
Well spoke.
Well spoken by Fernando Nambanin.
Fernando.
The more.
You know, you often can just give up your ideas of sitting down by your old radio and
listening to old radio shows, and you can just listen to Fernandez and get the same
excitement, the same...
Only he had to listen to the whole...
Well, Spotsnick...
He had to listen to the whole show to shorten it.
He didn't have to sit down that much.
Well, you did say he was crazy and lived in a moose or some sort of containing vessel.
No, I said that was you, Dave.
I live in no such animal and no containment vessel.
I'm as free as a Golden Glow Donuts.
Free as a goat.
I'm as free and as happy as a goat.
As brave and clever as a goat.
And do not...
You know, the thing about goat buttocks is not going to be mentioned during this alacritation.
Ha ha!
Oh, you ruined everything.
Fuh, fuh, fuh, fuh, fuh, fuh, fuh, fuh, fuh.
Yaa, yaa, yaa, yaa.
You're a bunch of billy goats.
Try to remain serious for as long as you can.
It is very difficult to do.
Everyone knows being silly comes easy.
Especially to...
To a Laughpire.
A Laughpire is a creature that sucks the laughter out of its victims.
Yes.
A Laughpire may drink your blood after making you laugh.
What about the other forms of vampirism involved in comedy?
Well, dude, I was thinking of a premise one time, and it's like, it's taken me two hours.
Like, I don't know what I was doing wrong or what I was taking.
I was just thinking of the timing, you know what I mean?
And like, I'm trying, you know, people at comedy, they say, you get anything done, you
know?
So like, no, you know?
And next thing you know, I just like, my capillaries and blood vessels just started like totally
popping out, you know?
Like I'm covered with human blood, my own, you know?
Totally.
So here's the premise.
I'm gonna die, you know?
So I gotta go to the hospital.
I dial 911.
Dude, my face is...
My face is...
My finger fell off, man.
I couldn't even dial.
I'm gonna call.
I couldn't even call, so like I had to do it with my elbow, and then we got married,
and that was pretty much in the story.
Wow, that's really not very fat, is it, dog?
No, that's not very p-h-e-t at all, is it, dower girl?
No, dog.
It's kind of thin.
I'm so old.
I'm older.
I'm so old that I was still saying man when dude became cool, and then I finally, by the
time I finally started saying dude instead of man, everybody was saying dog, and I didn't
even notice that until two nights ago.
Well, they're actually going down an anthropological, archeological list from another world.
These are animals, sentient, intelligent animals that exist in other worlds.
The dude, for instance.
The dude has a pyrotechnic range of perhaps 15 to 25 meters.
He likes working with toilet paper, small children, and he enjoys being loved.
Um, a dog?
That's not a real dog.
It's a dog man, a person that's half dog and half human.
Wow.
So man is interchangeable with dog at the end of any given sentence, right?
Dog, man.
Yo, yo.
Man, yeah, dog.
Drew that?
Dude.
Man.
Oh, I did it again.
You guys are so cool.
I'm like so out of it.
I don't know any of your cool jive talk.
I'm just like a little square girl.
You're big, silly.
I think you're kind of round.
There's something wrong with your mind.
It's the inside of my brain that's square, man.
I'm like all nerdified inside of there instead of being all curvy and groovy.
Right.
Yeah.
I mean, dude, uh.
Right.
Okay, then chuh.
Yeah.
Um, that's not the worst part.
Some of them were crawling up on their hands and knees.
We looked out the window and we could see thousands of them.
Their little heads were all bandaged up.
They were cursing and shouting and some were laughing.
They were singing songs to the happy goo goo and the other god dancers.
The god dancers were relentless.
I was like, what?
I E cũng不知道 chat어서 They were singing...
So cool guys just coating each other with dust continue looking like Tool Girl just
Wie to get plenty越
רג
bitch.
And I didn't look around to verify that rope, voice.
I just did it.
the pipe of tobs swirling in the air like an an acronym or perhaps an anagram and we took it down
to our hearts and smoked it and it was good i could tell it was good when they smoked the pipe
it was good unto them you know what though it felt good a minute ago to me to say praise rob
instead of praise bob i think i'm getting tired of bob but rob actually you and rob actually have
kind of a thing going don't you like you praise him and then he prays you and then you praise
each other and there's more plosives than we can stand i'm sorry i i well i'm going home now
well we're both av geeks raise the praises praise and raise and raise and here's the
raising rob oh now here's and here's another rob he's also praiseworthy that wasn't the one i was
thinking of i was thinking of the godlike rob the clip art rob
oh that's is that the formal bob well that's his brother that's his brother rob dobbs oh man
how could i miss that i didn't know there was a rob there was a there was a rob a robert and a bob
in the dobbs family this is very little known if i didn't even know it myself until just now
see i thought maybe it was not nobody's everybody knew about bob's evil twin brother dick but
nobody ever asked i don't think i've ever even been asked
with her we've never questioned whether there were dobbs siblings like a what does bob have a sister
he should it's her name rob everybody has roberta roberta dobbs oh no barbie is his daughter
the barbie doll made by mattel is is based on bob dobbs daughter barbie okay i'm sorry i i can see
the picture in my head and i know it's true i know i know it to be true and it's registering
and he had he had four sons shem who was a sham
shem and and sean and shem jamoke and behope no i know uh and adam cadman adam cadman he was
adam cadman dobbs no he was actually the youngest he's the baby of the family so he was the
naturalist or the procreator you would think he would be the first one but he was actually the
last i thought he was the one who took cain's able the first one now will later be last for
the times they are changing oh you are alfred and he oh megan and alfred and i am the alfred
and the newman
i am both the i have come for i am both the alfred and the newman i am the new man worry me what
that's what dobbs is he is as zachariah was promoted a head of his time well not is for his
bob but not but a head right there's no head but not in any way not anyway body of his time or a
foot there there is a spiritual body his flockern and his
lack of fleshing the body of god he is fl总 like a
when you were in high school Frale was patrician oh Rodney
he are we all Rey cadこんにちは
yes i am Cobes and the word was i found on hickory
i camekost and all started in there and that was that was argued and completely
i i even i think to rob was i i feel this way about his family and that he put the thought
on so many things i come across uh real Espaännese people their mother wanted bullshit and their
He's been obliterated from his brain cells permanently.
Permanently.
We've never been told what Bob's mom and daddy have done for it.
Today I heard his mom was a looker in the day.
And I heard Pappy was quite a fighting man and a lover man.
But I'm not sure because prescriptions does not prescribe.
It only prescribes.
Take two, three, four, however many you can stand.
It proscribes quite a bit.
There are many thou shalt nots involved in the law as handed down by the Dobbs.
But we lost that copy of the law.
So we don't know what we're not supposed to do.
We only know what we're supposed to do, which was question authority.
But where does that get you?
That just means that you shouldn't even do that much.
Right.
Because who told us to question authority?
The authorities.
Right.
Tim Leary, Bob Dobbs, all those guys.
Question authority, question authority.
Why?
Because I said so.
Even the questioning has become a rote, Bobbyistic thing to do.
I stand there at those devivals.
I stand up there and I go, question authority.
And a whole audience out there goes, why?
Because they've been trained to.
They've been trained without questioning.
Then now question authority.
Like a bunch of robots.
Exactly.
A bunch of automatons, they say.
Why?
It's like him.
Why should I question authority, Reverend Stang?
Why?
But they're not really asking that question.
They're just saying it because I told them to.
They're saying it by rote.
Right.
They're posing back at the demagoguery.
And the point and question you make in your flimsy, flaccid arguments are hardly borne out,
I'd say, by the airborne diseases you carry.
You better watch the way you say that word flaccid, buddy.
Oh.
Well, it's coming up near to end of showtime.
And I'm sure that there are many people out there who have cause to celebrate.
We have a little bit of Hungarian in this, don't we?
Is that what tomorrow is?
St. Oro's Day?
Yeah.
Hungarian Day.
It is the anniversary.
St. Vlad the Impaler's Day.
Everybody wear your little white teeth on your lapel.
That's Carpathian.
That's not Hungarian.
No, that's not Hungarian.
Actually, that's Romanian.
I'm sorry.
Terribly, terribly sorry.
Romanian.
I don't want to offend anyone.
I'm sorry.
No, I don't want to start another fight over Carpathia.
No.
Don't get all dracul.
Certainly not.
Okay.
I'm going to let over janitor Philo finish the show off so that the next show can come in and take over.
Is that okay with you guys?
Pirate ships would lower their flags when Puff roared out his name.
Dr. Hal?
That's your statement.
Well, I...
I wish I knew.
I think they're still readying it.
They're primping it and propping it into shape and lightly slapping it and powdering it.
And really, they're doing everything they can.
Clipping its umbilical cord.
Well, they may be buffing its nails.
That works.
That'll wake it up.
That'll devour its placenta.
A complete peanut butter facial.
A lube job and acupuncture.
A double facial.
Rolfing, ralphing, and retching.
But when it's all done, it's not only going to be a radio station, it's going to be a cafe.
Cool.
It's a radio station.
It's a cafe.
Hey, you're both wrong and you're both right.
It's a radio station and a cafe.
So while you're trying to do a show, there's a bunch of geeks googling you.
It's a radio station.
Through a window or a sheet of glass.
And they probably don't have a permit for either one, right?
Yes, they don't realize that they have to...
There's the Brother Hal guy.
They've opened a real mare's nest now.
A can of squirming, hydra-headed, medusa-like worms.
Brother Hal, yeah.
Because they're going to have to run a cafe as well as a radio station.
And to run a cafe, that means you have to have multiple bathrooms and they have to have wheelchair rides.
Captain Stang.
Yes, and wheelchair rides, too, so no one feels left out.
Commissar evidence.
Yeah, okay.
Anyway, Pirate Cat Radio.
And what's Philo?
There's only one more of those shows.
No, he's the overman.
No, no, no, he's like Janitor Overman Philo.
Janitor Hyperthete?
He gets three names.
Over Janitor Philo.
You know, there's...
Oh, well.
I don't care.
All right.
That was a great band, I don't care.
I don't care.
It was a great band.
So vigorous.
I don't cares on fourth.
But who's on first?
What about if you had a guy whose name was...
Your hair's on.
Then you have a mayor of Cleveland.
If his hair actually did catch on fire...
The mayor of...
And you said, hey, your hair's on fire.
He'd go, yeah, so what?
So you're yelling my name at me.
Big deal.
From PR News in Washington, I'm committed to helping PR's reports.
Pentagon officials say that Barack Obama and Hillary Clinton should be totally different,
but they have a high degree of confidence that they should be larger than the size of a football.
But they can't tell for sure just yet.
Barack Obama and Hillary Clinton collided off the Florida Panhandle yesterday.
They crashed into the Gulf of Mexico after a crippling PR News from Washington.
PR News by Lee Moore.
And now to take us out, dear friends, Bob Walkenhorst live at the Record Bar with an old song.
The Record Bar.
It's about recordар norm.
I'd be Conventional on that record.
I'm a football coach, of course and I could be somewhere else.
So here we are.
Morning as my son Dorry writes the super fetish trotters.
Rachel dozen said it's Come On пор Traven.
So Billy smells, NEWS.
ar, let her come over.
See you next week, bye.
Bye.
Take a load off of Manny
Take a load off of me
Manny
You put the load, you put the load right on me
On my big piece of the flag
I went a-lookin' for a place to hide
I went a-saw a-comin' in a hill walkin' side to side
Say, little Dick Thomas
Come on, let's go downtown
Say, I got a boy
But my friend can't stick around
Take a load off of me
Take a load off of Manny
Manny
You put the load, you put the load right on me
Crazy chance to find me
And if I feel like I'm gonna die
I'm gonna call the police
Said, how did you get here?
Said, I'm next to the head
And you can take a check on the file
Said, wait a minute, Chester
You know I'm a piece of the bag
Said, that's okay, boy
Won't you leave him there, you can
Take a load off of Manny
Take a load off of me
Manny
You put the load right on me
Go down to Spores's
There's nothin' you can see
It's just so blue
And it's was waiting on the children's name
The old man with a mouth of brandy
Put a valium in the oven
Said, do me a favor, son
Won't you save me now
Take a load off of me
Take a load off of Manny
Take a load off me
Take a load off Fanny
Fanny
Take a load right off me
Catch a cannonball
Now take me down the line
My bag is stinking low
And I do believe it's time
To get back to Miss Fanny
You know she's in a hurry
To send me in with dirty guards for everyone
Take a load off Fanny
Take a load off me
Take a load right off me
Thank you.