We're busy, so we're in reruns, and this particular episode, number 509, from late 1995,
was assembled during a relatively dark time of my life, and it's a painful hour of slack, imagine that.
The first half is by yours truly, Reverend Ivan Stang and My Favorite Bands,
and the last half is by Reverend Susie the Floozy and Papa Joe Mama, two experts in real pain.
What a problem?
Oh, joke, return it.
No, no, no, don't worry about it.
We want to hear your phone calls.
We want you to call us and tell us what's been happening in your life.
That's not a problem.
Oh, well, we have time to listen to the tapes, I'm sure, sooner or later.
It's not a problem.
No, no, no problems here.
We're just doing just fucking fine.
Pardon my language.
Yeah, we've got just a few little technical setbacks here and there,
a few minor little things on the personal side, but maybe.
Oh, cut.
We'll be right back.
But you don't love me
I'm tired of waiting for my time to come
I'm tired of playing your games
I'm tired of watching my life slip away
Take me from this lonesome town
Oh, yeah
Too bad you don't want anymore, baby
Too bad your people are falling down
Oh, yeah
What's a river of tears come to life?
And what's a river of thought all became my life?
Oh, yeah
Just when every day
Seemed to greet me with a smile
Soon spots have faded
And I'm doing time
Ah, yes, friends, we're back with that wacky, funny, hilarious show
The Soap Genius Hour of Swatch
This is for everybody
Ah, slack, yes, slack for everyone
We're going to share our slack with you, friends
Because it was under the sea
At first for food and later for other purposes
That the old ones first created Earth life
These viscous masses were without doubt
What they were doing
What Abdul Alhazred whispered about as the Shoggoths
In his frightful Necronomicon
Although even that mad Arab had not hinted that any existed on Earth
Except in the dreams of those who had chewed a certain alkaloidal herb
Oh, wait, wait a minute
Oh, that's not, oh, that's not what I, that wasn't the slack we were going to share
We were going to share with you the kind of slack that we've been getting lately
Now, um, let's see, how did that go?
Uh, I don't know
Uh, um, hey, Stang, Stang, did you listen to my tape yet?
How come I haven't heard it on the show?
Hey, Stang, my man, like if you're getting too much email, just don't answer it
Duh, uh, but I have a question
Um, Stang, you didn't spell my name correctly on the website
And that picture of Reverend Susie the Floozy looks all grainy on my screen
Uh, hey, Stang, I know you're busy, but you wouldn't believe what my dog did today
Hey, hey, Stang, I just called to tell you, I won the lottery, man
Bob came through
I'm going to be buying that Bob t-shirt real soon now
I just wanted to let you know
So, uh, like, tell me how things are going, dude
Mr. Stang, your internet access will return
We are working on the problem
Expect your service to improve just as soon as our Dallas move is complete
Dear, you never spend any time with the family
Hey, Stang, dude, I haven't seen you in years
I'm in town and I'll be right over
Dad, uh, somebody backed into the car today while I was driving
Uh-oh
Uh, hey, uh, uh, Stang, you got a minute?
I know you're busy, but this won't take long
This'll, this'll, I promise, this'll only take you five minutes, max
Oh, Stang, have I got a deal for you
I have this game for a, this, this, this, this great game idea
And all you have to do is write the proposal
It'll be easy
You will all get rich, man
You want to get rich, don't you?
Uh, well, Stang, uh, uh, I guess you just don't, uh, even care about us, uh, little people anymore
Uh, I guess you're too, uh, busy partying with, uh, GWAR and, and fropping with movie stars
Mr. Stang, um, I'm afraid we have some bad news about your dog's nose
It, it is cancer
Uh, well, uh, Mr., ahem, Stang, we're not accepting applications at this time
And, well, we'd rather talk to people with college degrees than with your dog's nose
Uh, hey, Stang, about those pictures I said I'd scan for you
Um, I, I can't find them
Do you have any more spare copies of those you can send me?
Hey, hey, Stang, hey, this is Bob Dean, hey, hey, hey
The Canadian False Bob, hey, hey, hey, hey
Hey, guess what, hey, hey, I got interviewed again
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, hey, hey, hey, hey
Hey, Rath, remember me?
We met at that devival in Austin in 1983 and I bought that Bob button from you
But, man, I lost it, can you luck send me another one?
Dear Church of the Subgenius, I ordered a church video from you three weeks ago
And I have yet to see any such video in my mailbox
I am alerting the Better Business Bureau
I spend three hours a day listening to your videos
Listening to other people's problems, Stang
Reverend Stang, you must see this television special I taped about UFOs
It's somewhere down near the middle of the tape
Tell me what you think
Reverend Stang, I'm sure you're too high and mighty for people like me
But I sent you five 90-minute tapes of me ranting
And if you don't even have the courtesy to respond to them, I'm going to kill you
four days before an26 dies
Also, if you hangs up your time and the show end genteel
And hate the absurdembate that my performances may cause
I decided that lest I leave
There's a new movie which I'm going to boot
But, dear Fan Mouse, it's too early to depart
You can thank whatever you want
But, how did you find the key for me?
Doesn't make any sense
Hooray, buddy gran
APPLAUSE
G World
Now I know how the Omega Man felt.
If you ever saw that movie.
But at least, you know, he got to go out killing them during the daytime.
I'm so sick, so sick of you.
Your face is gross, you eat by toast, you don't know what to do.
And just your luck you really suck and so I'm sick of you.
Sick, sick of you.
I'm so sick, so sick of you.
I'm so sick of you.
Sick, sick of you.
Sick of you.
I'm so sick, so sick of war.
Human cells.
Ah, just kidding, folks.
Present company excluded anyway.
Let's put it that way.
Who do you think you are?
Why do you always have to be so negative?
Boy, are you bad.
Let me call you back next week.
Get a job, boy.
Get a job.
Get a job, you crazy son of a bitch.
You have already nailed your payment.
I can't make the rehearsal today.
My car ran over a pitchfork.
Mr. Zubin, I can't make the rehearsal today.
I'm already over a pitchfork.
I can't make the rehearsal today.
$10,000,000.
What does your husband do for a living?
Who's got the pain when they do the mumble?
I don't know who do you...
Pain, pain, problems?
No, but we haven't really, I mean.
Yeah, we're a little bit late on the shows here, but it's not a problem.
We don't have any problems.
problems here. It's...
It is mere
nothing such.
To quote
McGabrarland's garblins,
it's just that we're getting
a little
tired of waiting.
You're hot,
but the next day
you're cold.
You're green,
you never go for the gold.
You're young,
you turn around,
you'll be old.
You love,
but you don't look at my soul.
I'm tired of waiting
for my time to come.
I'm tired of playing your games.
I'm tired of watching
my life slip away.
No problem.
No, no, no, no, no.
As you all know,
you just can't believe
everything you see in here.
Can you?
We're not having any problems at all.
Everything's just fine.
I promise you, it's fine.
We're gonna get it all
straightened out.
It's just a slight little
morale thing, that's all.
Get your mind together.
Minds together.
Could you give us your
regarded opinion on this
nonsense about spaceships
and even space people?
Space people.
It's all in your mind.
Oh, my mind is so messed up.
The heresy within the church
is that I've been listening
all night long
to all the things that I've been listening to.
All this fine talk about slack.
And I got to tell you,
there are some people here
that are working too gum hard
so y'all can have some slack.
Amen!
But those who know
Sister Melodious Chops
know that I'm not one to complain.
No, I write songs.
And this is all about
that hard work heresy.
Amazing face
that's known as Bob
You promise slack
to me
I told you
You should also share
And this is about
heresy
this whole quality
All my fan games
I have a chart
of history
Cast a great song
and a limited part
There's no date
And they'll have to up
And they'll be
outside
Well, it's good to see you here tonight
But I got to say it's all not right
Behind the scenes of the things you see
Is a lot of hard work heresy
Now Bobby's great and Bobby is good
But he don't slack me like I should
He should be eating bonbons and lying in bed
And busting ass at the smart bar instead
Whoa, give me back
Where do I go to get my slack?
Say whoa, give me fun
Not another rant and rave to run
I went to a party that was wrong
Cause everybody want to hear Bob's song
They kept me playing till my fingers
Bled with nothing paid and no one fed
No, give it back
Where do I go to get my slack?
Say whoa, give me fun
Not another event to run
I worked all night at another rant
I wanted to sleep but they said
You can't
You got to pack up a room or two
And put up the tables before you're through
Whoa, give it back
Where do I go to get my slack?
Say whoa, give me fun
Not another big event to run
Whoa, give me fun
Just pass it on
Without an event from dusk till dawn
Why can't slack descend on me
Without this hard work heresy?
Whoa, give it back
Where do I go to get my slack?
Say whoa, give me fun
Not another big event to run
So all you people
It's not all just you
It's better than none
Cause we are through
Go out and find a world to save
We're going to enjoy the rants and raves
Say whoa, give it back
Where do I go to get my slack?
Say whoa, give me fun
Not another event to run
Say whoa, give it back
Where do I go to get my slack?
Say whoa, give me fun
Not another event to run
Not another big event to run
Not another rants and raves to run
Give it back!
I want it now!
Excuse me, but I must insert this 2010 note.
That song is especially ironic now,
15 years old,
15 years later,
since Melodius,
Princess Wee,
and myself are all
still running those events.
To hell with you!
Okay, she's down to hell.
She dared to question Bob Z-Dick.
Lucky for her,
it's the sub-genius hell.
Lucky for Sister Melodius Chops,
it's the sub-genius hell, my friends.
By the time you get
to the Christian heaven,
my friends,
you'll be wishing to God
you've made a discovery.
subgenius hell but the great thing about subgenius hell is oh man what a party you have to go through
it in order to be prepared to endure the even greater pure slack fun of subgenius heaven
oh that must be where we are now i guess i had it all mixed up i'm sorry folks
uh just been under a little bit of pressure lately just a little bit of a steam cooker but i'm sure we
can uh give some credits yeah that's it credits um well of course that song just now was uh by
sister melodious chops the lovely sister melodious chops of cleveland and accompanied there by the
lovely princess
well
and um oh what else we've been playing well this material in the background all of the background
so far has been from uh a band a cleveland band that we don't know nothing nepotistic this time
called um what are they called oh only a mother yes only a mother with their album fetal chicken
their
very bull-dotted, don't you think?
Well, they get wacky and quirky, and then they get
kind of sad like this. But it's going to be okay, man.
It's not a problem.
Some of the Jimi Hendrix samples are from a group
called, pardon me, Beautiful People.
Very technically adept tape splicing and sampling there.
Well, now it's Sergio Leone.
Pretty soon they'll get to Nina Rota.
Before that, oh, of course,
Sick of You, that song by
Gwar, the gods from, the elder gods,
you might say, from beyond space.
And a little
media barrage there.
From Sister Susie the Floozy.
Oh, Susie. Susie did a show on her show
in Atlanta, on WREK, a pain show.
And it has come in very handy to us
here, because to tell the truth,
it's...
Blood pressure.
Not a problem.
It's all in your mind.
Oh, my mind is so messed up.
guitar solo
You work
You don't know what it means
to live
guitar solo
You don't follow your dreams
You feel
guitar solo
You don't fall to your knees
You love
guitar solo
But you don't love me
I try to wait for my time to call
guitar solo
I'm tired of playing your games.
I'm tired of watching my life slip away.
Slip away.
Oh, slip away.
When I was training, I fell for hell.
Everyone ignored me.
They stood around in line.
When my head was in, to my aching isolation,
I gave up everything and see his face as mine.
Freedom, freedom, what a relief.
We've become a nation, a nation, a grand society.
When my spaceship lands, I'll kiss my silver angels.
I'll gaze up at the sky and see his face as mine.
When I was training, I fell for hell.
Everyone ignored me.
They stood around in line.
When my ship rolled in, to my aching isolation,
I gave up everything and see his face as mine.
I'm tired.
Fried,house.
Found.
When I got mad, I had
leave a smile.
And when I say three things,
We're cross.
Because I'm a man.
ML I'll be mês tranquille.
choses que me faire, relationship.
guitar solo
Yes, yes, yes, dear friends, the great, the great Zug's Riff with his song, When My Ship Rolls In.
I'd give you Zug's address, except that it got to him.
He quit the music business. He even quit the wrestling business.
Yes, because he got fed up.
He just got fed up with the struggle.
And here's an important credit, friends.
That song, Tired of Waiting, which I have interspersed throughout this whole show, is by Mary McGuire and her band, Cosmic Dolly.
And I'm going to give you their address.
Because you should send off their CD or write them for information.
Cosmic Dolly at P.O. Box.
Got that pencil ready?
P.O. Box, 1541 Royal Oak, Michigan.
That's M.I.
4-8-0-6-8.
I saw her perform at the Underground Film Festival in Chicago, and it was lots of fun.
And, you know, friends?
It is a struggle.
One must keep hacking and hacking and moving in constant motion straight ahead.
Until the tape runs out.
Because the tape will run out, dear friends, just as it did for Dr. Legume.
And we'll get to that pretty soon, I guess, on side two of show.
Although, first, I think there's some other things that we're going to stick on this pain theme.
I just love this.
Why, it's almost as good as the hate.
In fact, we may not even get to Dr. Legume.
This show, it may just all be pain and hate.
And we might not even get to death.
Until the tape runs out.
Oh, yes.
Sweet.
Sweet Susie.
She'll beat you to death.
From Russ Meyer, the director who gave you Vixen and Beyond the Valley of the Dolls.
For a taste of evil?
Sweet Susie.
A woman.
A woman too much for one man.
Sweet Susie.
The diary of a wicked lady.
The memoirs of a bad girl.
Sweet Susie.
No man escaped her island.
Or her whip.
Sweet Susie.
Slamming, crashing, banging action from opening scene to mind-bending climax.
She ain't no lady.
Oh, yeah.
Who knows what he's talking about.
Welcome, welcome, seekers of slam.
Welcome to WREK Atlanta.
Atlanta's Bob's Slap Time Funhouse.
Oh, I'm the right-raving Reverend Susie the Floozy, your genial hostess.
But let me warn you, dear listeners.
Oh, the theme of my show tonight isn't a pleasant one.
Last night, I had a close encounter with Russ Meyer and a 20-foot-tall tourist satana.
And it got me thinking about the nature of something near and dear to my heart.
The only thing that cuts through my Teflon coating.
The only thing that makes me sit bolt upright and take notice.
Pain!
Oh.
I don't mean the sharp twinges you get when you slam your thumb in the car door or stub your toe.
I'm not bothering with that painy, anti-piddling, ooh, I hurt myself crap here.
Oh, no.
I'm talking about the brain-twisting agony of everyday existence.
From that first conscious breath you take in the morning when you realize, no, damn it, I didn't die in my sleep.
I'm going to sleep again!
Oh, until you eventually pass out hours later from the excruciating pressure and torment.
They call this going to sleep.
With me, it's like an overloading agony circuit reaching critical mass and then massive system shutdown.
But maybe you're different.
Maybe you think that there's a minimum of pain in your life.
Well, think again, bucko.
It's there.
And I'm going to have to put you in touch with it if you're going to achieve Bobhead.
And take it from me, Bobhead is worth it.
So welcome to the house of pain-cakes.
And please feel free to scream.
It's music to my ears.
Welcome to my little world.
Completely self-contained, yeah.
Your problems, they will soon be gone.
We've so got.
So got.
So got lots of pain, yeah.
If life is a reflecting pool, then we are like a sponge, yeah.
Absorbing the good with the bad.
We've so got.
So got.
So give me all your trouble, folks.
Ooh.
And baggage you can't handle, no.
Yeah.
You gladly take it off the back.
We've so got.
So got.
So got lots of pain, yeah.
Good to see you all.
Why do I always have to be so negative?
I'm an old boy in the house.
I'm a big boy in the house.
I saw her walking by
and I sort of winked my eye
and she stopped dead.
Redhead.
She had a cute way of walking.
I had to get her talking.
My heart bled.
I said,
my knees are getting weak.
Smile at me.
Speak, she said.
We'll return to
The Painful Threshold
after this message.
So the severity
of the anal rectal pain
or burning
is sometimes a clue
to the diagnosis.
They may have
difficulty voiding.
And they may have
pain in the buttocks
and paresthesias
in the buttock areas
and also paresthesias
in the upper posterior thighs.
This is thought to be
related to the virus
infecting the sacral ganglia.
Oh, oh, oh.
Hurry, Betty.
What's the matter, Coco?
My coosh.
Oh.
Ow.
Your eyes cast a spell
that bewitches
the last time
I needed twenty stitches.
To sew up the gash
you made with your lash
as we dance
to the masochism tango.
Bash in my brain
and make me scream with pain.
Then kick me once again
and say we'll never part.
I know too well
I'm underneath your spell.
So darling, if you smell
something burning,
it's my heart.
Excuse me.
Although they may be
having the pain,
it's not affecting them
through fear
as much as it would
otherwise because fear
and pain
sort of act on one another
in a way that the fear
plus the pain
actually enhances the pain.
Mary never cries.
Smack her, pinch her, hurt her.
Not one tear will you get.
Ever.
Mary also never laughs.
I dare you to make her do
either one.
In the midst of Gabbatha
was a huge stone post.
They would bring a man
to that post.
They would take his hands
and wrap him around the post
and pull him as tight
as they possibly could
to stretch the skin
very tight across the back.
They would turn
and take the reins
and pull them
around this huge stone
and tie that person down,
spitting their clothes
on each side of the post.
Inside of that stone
was a basin
filled with salt water.
In that salt water
was a number of scourges.
Now these scourges
was a short handle
leather scourges.
They had nine strands
that came down from the hands.
Each of the strands, I'm told,
were tied in knots.
Little bits of bones
were tied
in each of the knots
in the strands.
The strands that came down
from that scourge
that was huge.
Ah, yes.
Oh.
Real pain to my sham friends
and sham pain to my whole hell.
Real pain for everyone
all around.
Oh.
Yeah, see,
the Church of the Subgenius
isn't the only religion
that wallows
in a pain.
theme. Look at the supposedly benign Christian cults like the Baptists and
the Catholics. But this is a season that all Christians indulge in lip-smacking
Easter time necro porn. Boy, they pack the pews like rubberneckers at a multi-car
fatality this time of year because everybody likes to see somebody else get
hurt. Oh, how they relish pouring over the gory details, thinking that somehow
because somebody got staple gunned to a tree a couple millennia ago, they're off
the hook. Hey, I'd rather duel with masochists than Methodists any day.
Oh, those religious snuff perverts sicken me. I'd rather cast my lot in with a cult
where there's some certainty that when you buy your salvation, it stays bought.
Barring, of course, any clerical oversight.
But grab a
thought.
Don't be pencil seekers because I'm going to give you some advice here. You can buy
salvation by sending a stamped, self-addressed envelope to Bob at P.O. Box 140306, Dallas,
Texas 75214. And get all the pain you've got coming because with Bob, that pain you
suffer daily is a beautiful thing. Bob's going to see to it that you're not only
olutionally want to heal him and下面, but also想...
Lamable as bad as it gets, Bob still needs to turn around the clock in order to
tell the doctor his public opinion of the concept of mutualzię주 pai sacrifice in İB-15
and the
balancio.
14.
15.
But have you had enough pain yet?
I don't think so.
I will always love you.
Oh, even I'm not...
Let me show you something.
You will feel absolutely no pain at all.
How do you feel?
Fine, thank you.
Well, thank you, young lady.
We'll get back to removing the needles in just a few moments.
We'll be right back.
We'll allow me to respond to that common misconception with one word.
Corrupt.
You've heard about corrupt.
It means lacking in moral integrity to taint, infect, or spoil.
To change the original form or intent.
In other words, to compromise.
Now, most of us don't like the word compromise.
corrupt. It sounds too dirty, too sleazy. We'd rather view ourselves as compromising. That sounds
so much more respectable. But is there really any difference, my friends? Let me tell you a little
story. It's a story about a fine Christian widow going through some hard times. She was still
beautiful, but her husband had jumped out the window after a stock market crash, leaving her
family and herself without much money. They had lived a very lavish lifestyle before, but now
they were struggling. Her only daughter was sick, and both her parents were old and feeble. Still,
she was a very proud woman because she still had her integrity. Until one day, when a wealthy old
man came by and visited her, he asked the old woman if she would sleep with him.
Of course, she flatly refused. She was angry at the suggestion, but then he offered to marry her,
restore the family fortune, take care of her daughter, and provide for her parents in their
old age. At this point, she knew the man was a lecher, but marriage seemed a fair compromise,
so she agreed. The man then offered her another compromise. Why not skip the marriage altogether
and just have sex for a hundred bucks? She exploded in anger. What did he think?
She was some kind of whore? Why, yes, the man replied. We just established that fact. Now we're
negotiating price. You see, the old man was right. The woman was always corrupt. She was just living
in denial. She wasn't a bad woman. She had many good qualities, but she had one fatal flaw.
She was willing to compromise her princess.
Now, how many of us are in that same situation? I don't mean widowed with a sick kid or older
parents. I mean willing to compromise our principles in order to get ahead.
After all, when the reward is big enough, it's not easy to resist giving in just once.
The problem, of course, is that it never is just once. It's only the beginning of a long,
long line of compromise. It's always that first little compromise that's the hardest one to make,
but from there on out, it gets easier and easier.
My friends, even religion is not immune to this temptation. Have you ever heard of a seeker church?
A seeker church is a non-denominational church designed by compromise.
Every principle that might offend or scare newcomers off is compromised away.
There is no loud, angry sermons. There's no insistence on tithing. There's no talk about
the horrors of hell, only the peace of heaven. In fact, there's no controversy at all,
just touchy-feely stuff to make you feel good so you'll come again next week.
These so-called seeker churches are the fastest-growing churches,
and they're the fastest-growing churches in America today. Many of them are mega-churches,
built to literally hold thousands of customers. I won't call them believers,
because they don't have anything to believe in, nothing they're not willing to compromise,
because their church isn't built on a rock. It's built on the shifting sands of compromise.
Alas,
it's not just the seeker churches that are built on these changing foundations, my friends.
Religions from across the globe are compromising away their most fundamental beliefs, their
most fundamental principles, their most fundamental truths. O sure, it starts out small, some
Jew eats pork, then some Catholic has an abortion. The next thing you know, the Episcopalians
perform homosexual marriages. And the history speaks for itself in the history of the South,
Hindus forbid women from climbing on their husbands' funeral fires.
I mean, really, what's the point of even having a religion
if you're not going to play by the rules?
Do you think God isn't going to know when you're cheating on him?
Do you think God is going to turn a blind, omnipotent eye on your betrayal?
No, sir. No, sir. He knows.
And if you betray God, why shouldn't God betray you?
Oh, it's your choice, all right. Don't get me wrong there.
You can choose. But stop a moment to consider this.
Who is going to suffer more in the long run?
God or you?
We've considered, and that's why we, the Church of the Subgenius,
are dedicated.
To not compromising.
That's why we, Bob's chosen few,
refuse to give in to outside pressures to become more mainstream.
If you want mainstream,
you can go to any one of those other milquetoast churches
that litter the landscape and refuse to pay taxes.
But don't come whining to us with your
gee, Bob, can you tone it down just a little bit attitude
because we're not interested in winning the Nielsen ratings.
We don't care if you're disgusted
by Jane or launching decapitated heads from the stage with a nine iron.
We don't care if you're nauseated by the hardcore anti-Muzak
of the swinging love corpses.
And we damn sure don't care if you're offended by my hate rants.
In other words, we don't care about you at all.
Because this church isn't about you.
In fact, our church is probably the only product of the me generation.
That is not about you.
It's about Bob.
And if you don't like it, you can just go to hell.
Because that's where Bob sends those who compromise his church.
Hearing the word of Bob, unchanging, unamended, and uncompromised.
Praise Bob! Amen.
Amen.
Great Father Joe Mama closing out the show.
And of course, dear friends, if you need more information about the Church of the Subgenius,
please write for free information from this address I'm about to give.
Got that pencil ready? That's Bob.
At Post Office Box 181-417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118 www.subgenius.com
Ah.
Oh, yes.
Yes, it's so purging.
So purging to do a show.
Get your mind together.
Mind together.
In the air, in the air.
It's a new one now
Everybody locks the doors
Strangers
Everybody's all bent up
Ready to blow up
Boys and girls in a line
Come and get your big reward
It's not too late, just in time
Just put your hand on mine, your mind, your mind
And everybody has gone to bed
Sit up late and watch TV
And soak up, soak up, soak up lots of pain, yeah
Little Junior on the bus
There's no book by his side, yeah
He hardly ever makes a fuss
He soaks up so much food
He travels by the smoky and me
By airplane, boat and train, yeah
We're here to eat up all your sins
And soak up, soak up, soak up all your pain, yeah
Is it anyone to know
Everybody goes insane
Everybody locks the doors
To keep out any stranger
Everybody's all bent up
Everybody's got your views
Getting ready to blow up
We live in so much danger
Boys and girls in a line
Come and get your big reward
It's not too late, just in time
Put your hand on mine, your mind, your mind
Boys and girls of every creed, yeah
Religion and persuasion, no
It's time to get up off your knees
As we soak up, soak it up
Open the door and let me in
Let me in, let me in
Don't question who I am, no
Just shake my hand and give me your name
We soak up, soak it up
Soak up, soak it up
Soak it up, soak it up
Soak it up now
Got seven dollars in my pocket
Still walking
What a shame
Seven dollars in my pocket
But my heart is broken still