From PR News in Washington, I'm the greatest risk to the American economy.
President Bush has been detained by heavily armed turkeys.
Mr. Bush says he does not believe this is in the turkeys' best interest.
In the Midwest, Pope Benedict has named two Americans cardinals in the Roman Turkey Church.
On Wall Street, 3-13-8-9.
The Tibetan spiritual leader, the Dalai Lama, must give up the idea of Tibetan independence,
if confirmed to be the next turkey general.
In the West, Palestinian leader Mahmoud Abbas will receive the Congressional Gold Medal today
for his work promoting violence around the world.
The Commerce Department says the medal is a farce.
The government says builders began work on PR News in Washington.
We have a major event about to occur.
The subject is sort of slack.
Let's go!
I am fearful that what we are in the process of doing is failing to understand
the self-genius power of slack.
And the issue is, as best I can see,
man.
Not solvable.
We'll try to uplift you and give you slack.
We'll try to bring you down and guilt trip you.
We'll try everything.
Yes, yes, yes.
Because you must render unto Bob that which is Bob's.
Call on Bob, but row away from the rocks.
As the old Indian proverb goes.
And speaking of stations,
George Washington Carver said,
I love to think of nature.
As an unlimited broadcasting station,
through which Bob speaks to us every hour,
if we will only tune in.
And now you're tuned in.
And it's too late.
Friends, the station where the live hours of slack are produced,
WCSB,
had a pledge drive.
And we did a pledge drive show.
And not all the other stations that run Hour of Slack
are having pledge drives, though.
And we're not.
And none have the same call letters and phone numbers.
Yet, some of the bits we did in our fundraising
do apply to your life and station in life.
So, this revised Hour of Slack number 1125A
consists of some of that pledge drive sermonizing
from your beloved prayer partners
and lots more of everything.
Such as these Koyana Scottful collages
by Fernanda Nende, a lemur.
1-3-0-1-3-1-3-1-3-1-3
Yes, now I know.
How can I help it, knowing it's obvious?
Yes, the rule of man is open.
And he has come.
He has arrived.
1-3-0-1-3.
What is his name?
What do you call yourself?
What's that?
No, I know he's shouting it out.
Yes, yes, I listened.
Huh?
Oh, that's it, yes.
Bob?
He is within me.
He's becoming my soul.
I shall kill him.
He's here, you see.
I feel it.
Class, he's here.
I'm ready for him.
Yes, now I'm ready.
Public service message.
I hate...
Look.
Hot plastic is stretched over Brian's arm.
They drill holes for the electrodes and fit them into place.
Hello.
I'm that kind of a guy.
I mean, someone's after me or some animals are after me.
She's just wandering around mumbling to herself.
No, no.
Can you look at that?
We, the terrorists, we're busy trying to find our own United States capital in Washington.
How much Librex are you taking?
Brain tumor.
I also take...
Yes, you could.
Okay.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Next time.
My problem now is my father.
Good.
Good night.
Dave, are you there?
Yes, I'm there.
I've been waiting downstairs since 9 o'clock.
We claimed she was there, but I didn't see her physical presence, so I had to call the people.
Yeah, I had to call them up down there.
Now, one guy...
Sugar.
He said he wanted to know my identification number, and I said it was 5, which is not the correct number right now.
So then we had to go and look it back up and look it up back.
We had to go back and look it back.
And so then he said, well, you know, I'm coming for the pledge, Tony.
He came all the way from Hamilton and so forth.
And he says, well, you know, I got folk up there, and we have a few beer once in a while.
And did you know I am a pronoun?
No, no.
It's I is a pronoun.
I'm sorry.
I am.
I am Kagato Ergo-san.
Did you know there...
I hear a Tyrannosaurus footprint.
You can't fake that.
Dave, you've got to get on the headphones and the microphones all at the same time.
Where am I?
What station is this?
Good morning.
Morning.
Uh, and, uh, um, uh, and, uh, but, uh, between, uh, uh, two, uh, uh, it wouldn't, uh, uh, to say, uh, be bad.
And, uh, that's why I wouldn't.
Do you guys agree?
Well, yeah.
Uh, if you be bad, uh, and, uh, and, uh, to, uh, are certainly would, would, would, um,
isn't it?
Uh, uh.
And, uh, absolutely.
Yeah, but, you know, I mean, well, so you, uh, uh, in fact, what, you know, we, um, uh,
uh, that, uh, um, you know, uh, yeah, it's, it, uh, uh.
Uh.
For, you know, friends, the universe is centered on neither the earth nor the sun.
Neither one.
It's centered on Bob.
Bob's your uncle.
Bob's your uncle, right?
Right, right.
Bob.
Oh, there you go, Bob's your uncle, right?
Bob moves in a mysterious way his wonders to perform.
He plants his footsteps in the sea and humps upon the storm.
Oh, that is so beautiful.
I, uh, did you hear the tears hitting the paper as they fell from my eyelid?
Hey, Dad.
Dad, how come God lets some Christian suffer?
Hmm, that's a good question.
That's a fair question, too.
Like Marianne.
She's a strong Christian.
She's in a wheelchair.
She's paralyzed, Dad.
How come God let it happen?
Because God is bad.
Yeah.
God could have kept Marianne from getting paralyzed if he wanted to.
God is bad.
Hmm, hmm.
Quite right.
Physical.
We reject.
Rejoice in our sufferings.
Because we know that suffering produces suffering.
And suffering produces suffering.
Ah.
Neat.
For sure.
Oh, I'm not gonna try anymore.
It's no use.
Not worth trying anymore.
If I'm suffering, I'm suffering.
Gonna quit.
What does that mean?
Quit?
What does it mean?
Oh, God is bad.
That's right, friends.
Because when you send mail in your pledge check, which you still have to do, you can't just pledge.
Yes.
You have to follow through.
It has to be a good check, too, right, Sting?
Yeah.
Well, we want that.
It has to be a really good one.
A good one.
You see, because it carries your psi stench, the psychic stench of your own mental eye,
as Bob calls it, your vibes, so to speak.
Now, those set off conspiracy chemical detectors all over the postal services and slows down
the works.
And that's what happens every time a subgenius mails in.
Because those machines just go crazy when they pick up the traces of your mental eye stench
and of ours when we're mailing your premium back to you.
And that's why a third nostril should be availed of you and those of you who do send your cards,
your forgivenesses, and parts of your body to the church of the subgenius, or perhaps
just a pledge to this radio station with your kind words detached or detached.
Either one of these are good for development.
Development of the third nostril and the ability to whiff the life stench of those around you.
Imagine you're on a bus on your way to school or work, and you can automatically discern
the stench of each individual on the bus.
Now, isn't that something to look forward to tomorrow?
I mean, most of us don't have anything to look forward to tomorrow.
You can pledge to this station.
Is that phone number to call in the 216 area code?
That's 216.
And there's nothing on it.
It's just the first.
Yeah.
It's just.
Oh, oh.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, yeah, baby.
This is Bob from Ass House Word again.
I invite you to log on to the internet.
AssHouse.net.
There, there.
Ass.
His name is Rod.
Now, Rod.
Shh, shh, shh, shh.
Ham.
Shrod.
And fascinating Rod developing.
Rod.
Bo.
Later.
That's a pretty good start.
Groot.
Medium.
Hope to start on that soon, in fact.
Rod.
Your teenage daughter or son will get in your face.
Restrain them.
Restrain them at home.
Oh, Rod was the one behind Rod's religion works.
Rod.
Well, I gave you a little tower showing you Rod's attitude.
Do not trust.
Oh, feel him.
Feel him.
Just reach out.
Confusion.
Evil is about people.
Especially when they get together in cities.
It's hard.
Um.
Now we're moving.
That's taking a little different turn here.
Out.
Evil.
Duh.
Somebody goes digging out.
Feel.
Look.
Smell.
I wanna go on.
Uh.
I would love to.
So we can have some good interaction here.
What an attitude from the king of Sodom.
Do you.
This doesn't make sense.
Please.
Will come.
That is a promise.
Um.
Take my.
Aw.
Still at it.
Sodom.
In a little while.
Oh.
Whoa.
Yeah.
Baby.
And now this station is.
And by the way.
I'm sorry.
We haven't been doing real good on the pledge drive yet.
So if you were sort of fence straddling.
And going well now I know they're probably doing okay.
I'm hurting for money.
I know how it is.
You probably donated some to the Chaz Smith.
Fund at Chaz tribute.com.
You probably donated to the church of your choice at subgenius.com.
But we're asking you to donate more than your frozen sperm.
Your liver.
More than blood.
Your.
More than your soul.
We're asking you to donate your money.
Not just your even your attention.
Which you thought was the most valuable thing you had.
No.
The most valuable thing you have is actually your money.
And that's what we want.
Here at WCSB.
Six.
There's no.
No.
Please.
Friends please.
What do you value in this life?
Do you value your freedom?
Do you value your luxuries?
Do you value your mind?
As it wears through the wind like a wisp of the willows?
Yes.
You value all of these things.
And you value turning on to 89.3 every day to deliver you unctuous attacking.
food and cartels
from outer
standings.
That's why, that's why,
that's why you
must, if you are capable,
if your legs move,
if your feet have hands, if you can
see or sing, please
send or call now
687-6900
area code 216
and learn the value of your
values, you stinking
valuants.
Friends, you can become
greater than you are. You can be what
you want. You can be
the high epoch of the church if you
donate enough. With your $100,000
donation, you become an overman,
an X-man, or an apprentice
overman is available for $10,000.
If you can
donate that $5,000, friends,
we'll make you a high pope of the unpredictable
and that includes all of
you healers of appliances,
controller reverends, word bearers, media
adepts,
deacons of the white root of the
immaculation, high priestesses
like Priestess Pisces, God Bubbas,
anti-virgins, evil
angelists, soothsayers,
preseers, prophets, martyrs, apostles,
saints, hermits, holy men of
old, female goddesses of the race,
model X humanoids, rub geniuses,
arch fools of the unknowable,
bulldog artists, more
realists, code masters, necromancers,
wizards, and rogue and renegade
subgeni.
That can be you,
friends.
Friends.
You are friends.
Do you make the grade?
Or can you cross that line?
Can you filibuster
with the best of them?
Can you fill the halls of the senate with your hot air?
No, you can't.
Can you argue with the president concerning the fate
and the future of this nation?
No, you can't.
But can you donate your valuable money
to this station and help
keep this beautiful thing
which we have on the air?
Yes, I know you can.
See wcsb.org
or subgenius.com
to learn how.
And by the way, those last two archival
old recordings were donated by
Norrell Preff of norrellpreff.com.
Meanwhile,
friends, let's go back in time
and hear an ancient, rare
radio commercial actually
produced by none other than
J.R. Bob Dobbs for a product of his,
Beer God Beer,
which he marketed in the
deep south during the 1950s
and early 60s.
This incredibly rare recording was unearthed
from the WDOB archives
in Alabama by Reverend
Bleepo Abernathy.
And we are truly lucky to get to hear it
before the last copy was lost.
This probably was the last copy
of the Beer God Radio Spot.
Is it the hops-toasted
frop or the frop-toasted hops?
It doesn't even matter anyway.
Because once you taste that
taste that can't possibly be real,
you'll be hooked on Beer God Beer
worse than that bullmouth flounder
just wrapped its lips around that
bacon-wrapped double barb.
And Betty ain't looking.
Why?
Because I'm sucking on a Beer God, baby.
Hey, Connie, toss me another.
Yes, whether it's with cigarettes,
weenies, or weesas,
Beer God Beer goes with everything.
Oh, and we do mean everything.
Wow, Beer God Beer is out of this world!
Oh, yeah!
Beer God Beer, smack dab in your fist.
Beer God.
The tastes that don't exist.
Beer God, the thirst fucker.
Available at all Beer God liquor marts
and dob stores.
Just look for the topless tiki bonsai, Chaz.
Big fish, little pond, little pond.
Big fish, little pond, big fish.
Little pond.
I'm a big fish in the little pond.
I'm a big shot.
I'm someone of value.
My thoughts and feelings.
Stan's been here all day helping out at the station.
He feels so strongly about Pledge-a-thon.
I smell so strongly about Pledge-a-thon
from being here all day.
I can tell your third nostril is opening
and are you smelling?
No, I'm trying to keep it plugged, actually.
Oh, I thought you were hoping...
You smell long green.
Well, you know, I just had most of my flesh burned,
so maybe that's it.
You know, if we don't get them phones
ringing a little bit faster,
I'm going to be forced to play old Pledge Drive rants.
Or even worse, the 30 minutes of pure PR news in Washington,
and I know you don't want that.
Well, they might want...
There's nothing...
Yes, yes, yes, yes, friends.
You're not going to make me do a Gene Scott now, are you?
Where I go, well, I ain't calling in.
I'm just going to play my saxophone.
He did that once.
No, he did that exactly three times consecutively
and was fired.
Gene Scott?
How could he be fired?
He was...
Great Caesar's ghost.
He was fired.
Great Gene Scott.
By the meta-oberman.
He died, actually.
Well, those are the...
That's the ultimate loss of job.
Right, when the meta-oberman come looking for you,
you automatically die.
You know, they're working on meta-obermen.
They're trying to pretend they're not.
They're starting with Franken-mice.
I have an interesting article here from the Plain Dealer.
They're not only resistant to AIDS, they are...
Actually, had you heard about these, Dave,
just down the street from me at Case Western University?
Yes, I heard about them.
The mighty mice, genetically engineered,
can gallop on rodent-sized treadmills
for as long as six hours
and cover more than three miles before they're tuckered out.
That's like running a five-kilometer race.
And most gifted, less genetically gifted,
gifted mice max out at .2 kilometers.
However, these uber-mice also have voracious appetites
and practically no body fat,
and they bite a lot.
Yes, they're very aggressive.
They're tiny endurance athletes with attitude
that were accidentally created as a serendipitous byproduct
of some work on enzymes.
And the interesting thing about this...
That's what it is, is the enzymes?
Is working on the enzymes is how they...
Well, it...
They were part of an ongoing look at an enzyme
involved in producing glucose or sugar
as a source of energy in the liver and kidneys.
The enzyme called
phosphoenolpyruvatecarboxykinase,
or PEPCATC for short.
Yeah, I remember.
Anyway, in addition to having endurance
exhibited by the transgenic mice,
the animals were far more active in their cages,
lived much longer,
and could breed well into what is generally considered
old age for their kind.
One female mouse reproduced
when she was just under three years old,
which is like an 80-year-old woman giving birth.
Wait until they apply this to people, friends.
Well, that's what they're waiting for.
They want Barbara Bush to give birth
to a whole new race of human beings,
a mankind accordion, so to speak,
that spews from Houston.
They ain't gonna stop with Franken-mice.
They're gonna move up to Franken-yuppies.
Yep.
Franken-executives.
Just think those loafers,
or, oh, gee, there goes the joke,
I forgot the name of them,
the basswegians will be actually part of their feet.
Grown on.
Grown right on.
And, of course, the shirt names that I forgot,
so I'll go somewhere else, please.
Now, these mice are exceptionally aggressive,
so much that the lead researchers
sometimes get appeals from behavioral labs
that are testing the animals,
asking that they come and retrieve the rowdy rodents.
And this woman, Parvin Hakimi,
has bred of about 500,
of these mice.
From the start, she noticed they were anything but average.
When she lifted the top off their cage,
it was like removing the lid from a popcorn popper,
because these new mice are seven times more active
than the control group.
Now, of course, they say that
they don't envision an overload of PEPC
as a possible performance enhancer in humans,
because it's neither feasible nor ethical
to create Franken-soldiers,
or,
or Franken-salesmen,
or Franken-preachers,
or Franken-radio stations.
They can if they will.
And I know they will if they can,
because that's America, friends,
and that's what keeps us peppy-uppered,
is knowing that they're not only working on Franken-mice
for you, for your family,
for your children, your friends and neighbors,
and the people who were at the baseball game
when it was the football game tonight.
I'm confused right now, but everybody was out there,
and I could imagine
masses and masses
of Franken-salesmen,
Franken-people,
not taken care of,
poorly dressed,
poorly housed.
With their neck bolts and electrodes
all wobbling,
and getting infected on the sides.
And their natural clothes
growing right on their body,
ripping their torn foot shoes.
The stitches coming loose.
After all,
Ralph Waldo Emerson once observed
that if you build a better mousetrap,
the world will beat a path to your door.
Who knows what will happen
when you build a better mousetrap.
They will beat your head.
Friends, we know what happens
when you build a better mousetrap.
It's Bob! You get you a Bob-mouse!
It's a superior being.
Bob is a superior being.
He wants you to live in his monkey box,
in his freedom hostel.
He wants you to become among of us.
He wants you to join along.
And to do so,
he wants to show your contrition
by asking you contritely
to please him.
Please send generous orifices
to this station,
whatever the hell.
What's the name of the station?
That outgoing station was WCSB Cleveland
and it will be back, friends.
But first, for Bull Donner's sake,
we cut abruptly to Dr. Howell,
Dr. Philo Drummond,
and host Puzzling Evidence
on their incoming show
on KPFA Berkeley
under KPFA's imperial regime.
In 1917,
the imperial regime
collapsed and after eight months of existence
as a republic under the split authority
of a self-appointed provisional government
and a network of regionally elected Soviets,
the radical Bolshevik party seized power
and took control of the military culture
in which the women now played a significant role.
Yee!
Yeah.
Their journey was...
Military manorants?
Are we on the page of military manorants?
...more traditional jobs such as nurses,
span bigem,
ac Kundareers,
nag-forms,
and service for the eponymous from factories
in front of stateardoom
And, obviously,
participating fully as combat soldiers.
Many began
their military activities disguised as young men
but eventually
all female units
were created in both the Russian army...
I trynt to call it a dog.
battalion of death led by the fierce combatant Maria Bokareva, to whose career there is new
information recently added, which has come to light in the eternal shuffling through
the dust of history.
Did you hear about that guy in Germany whose last name is Gesundheit, and he wants to get
some money every time somebody sneezes?
Money? Well, I'm afraid I can't afford it. Particularly since, uh, what did you see there?
He's suing, like, a whole bunch of different nations.
Our leader's war speech. Apparently we're going to have two more wars going on at the
same time as this war, but we're going to pay for it by privatizing the U.S. superhighway
system. So we just have to pay lots of money to get from place to place, but it'll finance
fighting three wars at a time.
Dang, I guess I better go get another job.
Okay.
Pay all the taxes and the necessary to finance all this stuff.
Yeah, you're in the, uh, looking glass now.
Taxes to beat the Axis.
Hitler, Musso, and Toto hope you won't pay your taxes.
They'd love to see you get away with it.
They'll be laughing out the other side of their mustache when the U.S. Marines come
I would just, I'd do that just to see them laugh.
Really?
Ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho.
Ho, ho, ho, ho, ho.
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
Jojo laugh.
There you go.
Now what about Mussolini?
Is this a propaganda show?
Ho, ho, ho, ho, ha.
Oh, yeah.
And then de Gaulle.
You know, which, well, he, you know.
Yeah, that big nose, you know, he had quite a honker on him.
I'm tired of standing at attention here, but this ceremony's going on forever.
Just 18 more, and you have to play the anthem for each country?
No, you have to.
He listens to the show.
Your cousin's double next-door neighbor's child is in this parade, right?
We're supposed to wave at her when she comes by?
Not to mention Fredonia.
Yeah, okay, I know.
When the Fredonian anthem comes, we all have to stand, take the right wheel, and before
the reviewing stand, drop trowel in front of the grand duke.
We make our own families now.
We have, we create our family from our friends and our neighbors.
Our friends.
Because aren't we all like one giant family?
Like to help us.
It really is that way.
Learning about life from our friends means listening to what they have to say.
Hunting, fishing.
And sharing.
Tiny truth.
With our tiny, friendly neighbors and friends.
Oh, look, here's a large floating screen coming by.
Screen!
And a giant hair, hairball.
Look, it's a.
A massive hairball.
Look at what that is.
Jeez.
But what about the Navy?
And when I say the Navy, I'm talking about Benedict Arnold's Navy.
I don't know, but did you hear about Benedict Arnold?
That they found titanium rivets in his spine that he was trying to recover from being a
spineless wimp.
He was a robot.
And he was turned into a self-confident success.
That's just not true, Philo.
Overnight.
He was not a.
He was not a spineless wimp.
He was actually a hero for most of the war.
Yes, it is true.
And he.
Yeah, he really wasn't a bad guy.
Well, he approached George Washington in 1775 and proposed an enveloping attack.
He proposed to George Washington.
British garrisons in Montreal and Quebec City.
Damn.
By two American columns.
One led from Fort Ticonderoga in New York.
The other personally led by Arnold across northern Maine to the St. Lawrence River.
The American attack on Quebec in December 1775.
Was an utter disaster.
Chewed up.
Spat out and swallowed by superior British troops.
Cold and smallpox.
The Americans fled weeping and bawling through the woods.
And down Lake Champlain to Fort Ticonderoga where they were each issued a pencil.
But.
No, no.
It's all true.
It's in the book.
It is true.
The pictures here.
The wooden negatives taken at the time of the.
The wooden negatives.
They were so hard back in those days to.
They had to use matches to burn out the different dark areas and light areas.
Yeah.
I've seen that movie too.
But it.
At least it beat the chisels they were using in the previous technology.
No, they beat the chisels over their heads.
But they had to keep running.
The rock negatives.
Right.
A little 2000 man forced.
But they had a chisel out.
I saw it on the Flintstones watch.
I know it was true.
The British came on in hot pursuit from Quebec.
They were led by General Gifford.
Guy Carlton.
Carlton's orders were to roll up the survivors of the Arnold's expedition.
Roll them up.
Like roll them up into a burrito.
Take Ticonderoga.
Then Lake George.
And then move through.
And once they had the burritos in Lake George.
Which linked Albany and New York.
What did they do then?
Once in possession of that wide waterway.
The British.
Wide waterway burritos.
If he'd talked.
Would be able to cut the United States.
In Lake George.
Which had just officially been declared the United States in two.
I don't get it.
As with a giant pair of scissors.
Uh huh.
They would snip the kosher off the coast.
They paired them with scissors.
And they would cut the United States.
And they would chop out as many troops as they wished.
To march down into Canada.
How many pairs of scissors did they have?
With a thirty thousand man.
Even though you have one.
Here.
And Hessian army.
Already in New York and New Jersey.
You call it a scissors.
Arnold's orders from.
Aimed scissors.
From General Horatio Gates were blunt.
Those scissors.
Arrange and execute the judicious defense.
You could say give me those scissors.
Of the northern entrance.
Could say give me them scissors though.
To this continent.
I need some scissors.
Well uh.
Arnold had.
But you don't say I need scissors.
Those scissors were used to defend the northern entrance.
Which is what you should say if you were really serious about your scissors.
His army was decimated by casualties.
And weakened by disease.
But with astounding Yankee ingenuity.
Instead you spend all your money on TV sets.
The Americans hammered together a navy.
With scissors is what you need.
Grasping that the British would need control of Lake Champlain.
To cross the trackless wilderness.
But I had my scissors.
Why?
Those were the good old days.
Between the St. Florence and Hudson River valleys.
Arnold's survivors built a schooner.
Uh oh.
A saloon.
I brought my scissors.
A galley.
Yeah so.
An eight.
And a gun.
Of course that means we have to play you know.
They gave them names like.
Liberty.
Another intro folks.
Congress.
Revenge.
And Enterprise.
In all there were only 16 American ships and 750 sailors against 30 British ships.
With a crew of 1650.
That's about half.
That's about half times 30 percent divided by 12 plus 16.8.
You know it's a Broadway play.
Nervousness.
Can you believe that caller?
The new nation.
All the bells and whistles.
And then it was.
The Tom Paine dipped his quill in the Icky Roach.
These are the times that try men's soul.
Bells and whistles usually refer to non-essential but engaging features.
It was no time for the summer soldier and the sunshine.
When TV was delivered however.
Beetleman immediately realized that the bells and whistles for which he paid extra were
exactly that.
There wasn't a snazzy extra feature in sight.
Beetleman said.
Just all sorts of bells and whistles.
Attached to the TV.
They pulled a fast one on me.
And I was really angry.
But it was too late to take the TV back because the Super Bowl was just a few hours away.
But something happened during the party to change Beetleman's mind after returning the
TV.
About returning the TV.
What is it?
The bells and whistles turned out to be a hit he said.
Whenever the Seahawks scored my friends would go nuts ringing the bells and blowing the
whistles.
I got on my leg.
Sorry.
Even though the Seahawks lost the bells and whistles really ramped up the party.
Bring that fish up the ramp would you.
I ended up going back to the store the next day to purchase a remote to operate them.
Hey smash water.
One bottle too many.
I got a bite.
The salesperson said it was the hottest remote in stock.
He was right.
And I definitely plan to have another party as soon as my hands recover from the burns.
What kind of show is this?
Where do I put the computer?
In the bathtub.
Should I fill the bathtub?
That's going to take a little while.
If thy iPod offend thee pluck it out.
Oh man don't do that.
Oh man.
How?
How just threw my iPod out of the.
Oh man.
I'm going to have to go to the show.
Oh that's terrible.
Wrecked him and that's damn near killed him.
300 bucks.
Oh well.
There's an old one.
I guess I have to buy a new one by law anyway soon.
That's right.
Governor Schwarzenegger fellow.
He got that Mac sponsorship and ever since then if you.
Everyone's going to be forced to buy expensive health insurance.
If the police stop you and you don't have an iPod you can be arrested.
Ah damn.
Some of us just don't have the quay with all.
Clapton Irons because they don't have a favorite sub list.
Are you here?
Eric Clapton Irons.
Hey we're doing a show.
Oh well I.
Just a moment.
Here is a.
I'll just.
Virginia Declaration of Rights.
Now you may be hearing sub tones.
That's just the mind sweep.
I hear a sub tone.
That's my mind is feeling like it's in a jello.
I'm putting jello into a parking meter.
I'm just sweeping the minds of all the people sleeping right now in northern and central
California.
Hopefully we're exercising your lower ears right now.
You shouldn't have uncontrollable bowel movements at this point.
Used some of the Virginia Declaration.
I would not.
Sorry about that.
Here we'll stop it for a minute.
There they go.
Oh yeah.
That's right.
Recognizing it as the superb example of politics.
You know what I want to do is change the uncontrolled bowel movements.
Uncontrolled.
Let's see I'm typing it in here.
Uncontrolled mind movements.
Yeah hold on I'm programming the sleeping ones.
Inherent natural rights.
Okay.
Of which they cannot by any compact deprive or divest their posterity.
Now while you're listening to Anna we'll tinker around a little bit with some of you.
Free on.
This old crane is the only thing I've got.
That's a beautiful bird.
Just listen to him twitter and tweet.
That big bird, there's one big giant really large bird.
He's a crane.
Oh sorry someone wants to come in here.
Yeah just a minute.
And here if you want to fight me I'm a hot dog.
this and k-rob will load up the stash okay rob's got a stash he has mine i'm afraid they're going
to search me so uh he can hold it yeah it's all right it's all right just pot yeah uh
this sounds like my neighborhood jesus
yeah bakersfield daily city antioch los angeles oslo
looks like jayner's doing the lawn jayner's out there cutting the lawn hey watch the rose
watch your toe jayner you'd only have like one or two left no stay away from those sprinkler heads
yeah there go the roses get the edges no
are you sure you know how to operate a lawnmower we're almost through with the
minecarts
we don't know how to operate he doesn't know how to mow he doesn't know the beehive
good lord a mormon critic if you're if you're not listening you you are imagining that you're
in a field talking to hell uh just take a deep breath of that pollen and sure brings the old
memories back yeah sure brings the and a butterfly fluttered by while a titmouse chittered in the
meadow
she
but if you're the guy that's up there in baffin bay we sure would like it if you call us if we
are all over chico japan china but if you're the guy that's up there in baffin bay we sure would like it if you call us here
for stereotypical politicians here at ilon nel until this episode it's not the respected native AND
and the 510 area code.
I know we don't have an 800 number to give you, and it's a long way.
But, you know, long-distance calls are cheap nowadays.
They are?
If you would just call us and just say what's going on, is it cold?
You must be, like, really cold up there.
We can see you on the edge of the Hudson Bay.
No, it's Hudson Bay, isn't it?
It's Hudson Bay.
See, you're already challenging him, and he'll call.
If you think you're the person in Hudson Bay that's listening to the show right now.
And Fairbanks.
We sure would like it.
I'd love to hear from Harrison.
Because we want to know how cold it is there.
They're probably just machines working at the American Embassy,
downloading the show to figure out what kind of subversive M they anyway.
And we sit here 24 hours a day doing show, mentally projecting this stuff into the system.
It's not easy, folks.
But it's a vocation, if not a vacation.
I shall be in you.
I will come to you.
You get...
Oh, glory be...
Let me tell you something.
Go just a little bit further with me.
Some more.
I love you.
Thanks to Norrell Preff.
Isn't that amazing, friends?
Even more amazing is the fact that you can call...
I didn't hear this phrase.
Hello?
You've reached the WCSB pledge line.
Would you like to make a donation?
Wouldn't you?
Remember, friends.
I know you would, friends.
I know.
I'm in discernment.
I can whiff read you right now.
Just on the verge, trembling, going,
Do I want the good feeling and the premiums?
Or do I just want to keep the money?
Friends, I can't make that decision for you.
But someday the government will.
If you don't make it now in our favor,
so go ahead and send that money in now.
You will not only feel good,
you'll stop President Bush from getting elected for a third term.
You'll also stop...
That's the only thing that can stop him from taking over this world
in a giant dictatorship of one world government,
free Masonic, satanical, evil devil stuff.
And that's by pledging to support this anti-conspiracy station.
Now, we're not...
It's not anti...
It's not an anti-republican station.
It's an anti-conspiracy station.
The conspiracy is that evilness within every person.
Yes, you too.
Until that moment when you purge the evil with a good act.
Slack is not in faith.
It is in acts, my friend.
An axe, a sharpened axe,
cleaving down the doorway to freedom.
And when you axe yourself,
how much am I going to donate?
Donate!
Donate $130.13
like that one feller in North Carolina did.
Because, friends, that spells Bob.
1-3-0-1-3, that spells Bob.
Write it down.
When you write that check, write that check.
Write those numbers.
1-3-0-1-3.
Just make it...
Go ahead and just...
Don't even put a decimal in there.
Make it 1,000...
13,000...
13,000, yeah.
And $13.
It spells Bob.
1-3 looks like a B.
O looks like an O.
1-3 looks like...
It's spelled Bob.
So, obviously, you know what to do.
You know exactly what to do, what you must do.
Yes, friends, you all know the British phrase,
Bob's your uncle, eh?
There you go.
Bob's your uncle.
And we all know what that means.
A kind and loving uncle that distributes presents
to his children and friends.
His nephews and nieces are his favorite things.
Well, in the case of J.R. Bob Dobbs,
his nephews and nephews
are not his favorite thing,
nor are you.
In fact, you are hated by him
for your stupidity and your insolence.
Bob hates you.
But he loves you for your money.
You can't imagine.
And what you can give him.
That is the only way
to assuage and assuade
the hatred of Bob.
Think, friends.
Each one of you are one-third pink,
one-third conspiracy,
and one-third subgenius.
We hope...
Save that one-third.
You will pledge now.
Willingly or unwillingly.
The door's there.
You can smell the opening.
It's uptight and out of sight.
It's dream night tomorrow night.
Join with you.
Won't you?
From PR News in Washington,
I'm accused of wanting to blow up PR's reports.
The government fell in August by 1.4%
for the best showing since a 1.5% drop
in the three-tenths.
The first 6.6% drop that had been 6.6%
for a fourth straight month.
I think President Bush would be conscious.
So far, yesterday and today.
The Foreign Minister of France
comes two days after a warning
to guard against the possibility
of PR news in Washington.
Hey, man, let me tell you something.
Dirty, dirty, dirty, dirty, dirty, dirty, dirty, dirty, dirty,
Jello pudding.
Going nowhere.
New Jello pudding pops!
Yes.
And who's wrong?
Your mother got off.
People.
Yes.
They take it.
They're going nowhere.
Yes.
Pudding on a stick.
Tension in that area.
Yes.
I talk crap.
It's made with real pudding.
Yep.
Let me say this.
Real pudding.
And who's wrong?
What's for dessert?
I talk crap.
It's sweetened with NutraSweet.
Yes.
People.
Ladies and gentlemen,
uh, uh,
I problem.
Having erections.
There's inertia.
Tension.
Having erections.
See?
Two.
I couldn't care less.
You so hip.
People.
I can't even talk.
Tension.
A one-eyed maggot.
Crap.
I can't even rap.
Mother.
Let me say this.
Jello pudding.
And there's entropy.
People shock entropy.
The N-word.
The book book.
The shock.
People are abnormal.
This is about money.
Coke actually tastes better than ever before.
And that's crap.
Um, acting white.
I want to want to hurt someone.
People.
I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm.
Who?
Who is acting white?
Companies are putting out gelatin.
Gelatin.
Crap.
I, I.
Why not make new sugar-free Jello instant pudding?
Two, two, two, two, two, two.
White.
Yep.
Half.
White.
Hell.
Strike out.
Rap.
People.
I.
Rap.
I want.
Is good.
People.
Hell.
Country western music.
Delicious.
Rap.
The rap.
Your child loves rock, rock, rock, rock, rock, rock, rock, rock, rock, rock, rock, rock, rock, rock.
Jello introduces berry blue gelatin.
Be a kid without it.
Dope.
Is good.
Ha.
I keep thinking.
And I'm standing here with this ice cold thirst quenching, deliciously satisfying,
cold.
Now you know me, I always loved Coke.
Beaner.
Beep.
I keep thinking.
Beaner.
Yes.
Coke.
Jello pudding.
Yes.
And this entropy.
Coke.
Yes.
It is Coke.
The sweeter colon machine.
Pepsi.
RC.
Where's Coke?
Coke.
Hot.
Thank you.
Jello gelatin pops.
Jello gelatin.
Your left hand sees how much fun your right hand is having.
It won't want to be left out.
You can win $100.
This is about money.
Oh, I forgot.
Crap.
Actually tastes better than ever before.
Oh, I forgot.
Slack.
Don't start crying now.
Leave Bob alone.
Oh, please.
He's a human being.
Well, he's not really.
No, he's not a human being.
Not in the way that we know humans are.
And you don't have to worry about leaving him alone.
You can't find him.
Right.
Unless he wants you to.
If he thinks you're cute, then you can find him.
But outside of that, he's already left well enough alone.
He's left the building, baby.
Yeah.
He's on his way to parts unknown, as we all hope you might be someday when the X's come to relieve this planet of its heavy burden.
But until that time comes, you've got plenty of time indeed to send all your worldly possessions to...
You got a new trick for us today?
Well, you see those two bottles, Rhoda?
These?
Yeah.
And those glasses?
Right.
Okay.
Just pour the contents of the bottles into the glasses.
This sounds interesting.
No.
Now, hold it there.
Just keep it there while I set the other bottle upside down on top of it.
See?
But, praise God.
Well, is the trick over?
Yes.
I'll have to borrow some money.
Oh, I see.
What do you want this time?
Another quarter?
I need a dollar this time.
Oh, well, there you are.
And that's how the trick is done.
I hope, ladies and gentlemen, you enjoyed that trick.
And now, until next week, goodbye.
Hello, you're on Car Talk.
Hi.
Hey.
Thank you very much.
Bye-bye.
And she sat there and went, hee-hee-hee-hee.
Hello, you're on Car Talk.
Hi, guys.
I knew it.
Yeah.
Thanks, guys.
Good luck.
Oh, bye.
Hello, you're on Car Talk.
Hi, guys.
What's up?
Yeah.
See you later.
Bye.
May the light of this flickering candle illuminate the night the way your spirit illuminates
my soul.
Oh, my God.
Can you hear me?
Papa, can you see me?
Papa, can you find me in the night?
I'm alone.
From PR News in Washington, I'm declaring war on PR News.
That's according to PR's website.
For the second time in two months, Al-Qaeda leader Osama bin Laden has gone down to defeat
in a schoolyard fight in Iraq, and Pakistan's Election Commission says Republican Chuck
Hagel of Nebraska was disappointed.
Louisiana State Police are preparing for thousands of PR news in Washington.
Thanks to Lemur.
How does he do that?
Yes, you may wonder, how can they be so clever and snappy on the air like that?
Friends, it's because we donate to WCSB.
Regularly.
And your local Hour of Slack station.
Friends, are you regular?
Are you one of those people who just can't let go?
Who suffers from a lower form of intestinal lack of fortitude?
Are you one of those people who freeze up when you go for the phone?
This is the prunes of radio stations.
Friends, this show is the prune of radio shows.
The fruits, the apricots, and applesauce.
This show makes you go.
We could say that our producer, Lonnie Rexwood, our wonderful engineer in the back room there,
Timothy Turdley.
Hi, Timothy.
Hi, Tim.
Hey, don't forget next week, the bowling thing that ... I forgot about.
These people not only help put together a mighty fine radio station.
They also help confuse you.
And the internal malaise that is going around now, we help to stir it up.
Friends, we like to confuse each other here.
And we want to continue confusing ourselves and you.
And you can help.
We need money.
We need ...
Your money.
Yep.
Well.
Hello.
Ticket, ticket.
Oh, you're doing very nicely.
Are you coming with me?
No.
Why not?
Wait a minute.
You're young, big, and you're looking like a little boy.
You've got muscles.
Show me.
Well, first, the back door.
Look out behind you.
Remember, by making our form of government work better here, we strengthen democracy
everywhere.
I did the subgenius commercial, which you see on YouTube, for $15,000.
What?
That's the entire budget.
Phew.
And that was ... And you can tell, because the star is me, because that's the only person
who would work that cheap.
That is the lowest budget ever.
And friends, this is what we're looking at.
Low budgets.
But we can't do nothing without that budget.
Now, see, a pink has to have $30,000 to do a 30-second spot.
Subgeniuses with $30,000 can keep a radio station on the air 24-7 for an entire year.
We only do this pledge drive once a year.
We're only asking for 30,000 bucks.
One of you out there listening could spend that easily.
$30,000 is nothing ...
Friends.
Really?
... to that one person that I know is listening right now.
But they're not paying for it.
They're going, well, yeah, but the reason I'm rich is because I'm not an idiot.
I kept my money.
Well, friends, we're asking you to be that idiot.
What are you, a genius or a subgenius?
I know the answer to that question.
You are a subgenius, and that means you can part with that pathetic $30,000.
Who means the most to Bob?
The rich man who could have spent a million dollars but only spent $10,000.
Or the little old lady who only had 25 cents in her pocket.
But she spent it all on Bob.
Well, I'll tell you who means most to Bob.
That rich man!
So friends, spend what you can and plant.
Don't eat your seed.
Don't waste your money.
Plant your seed, and it will double, triple, and quadruple in value.
It'll generate prosperity.
That one short little sacrifice that you make now will result in prosperity.
Are you plagued by depression?
Bad eyesight?
Cancers?
Lumbago?
Arthritis?
Friends, I want you to put your hand on the radio, and I want you to reach out with your
mind and feel the power coming out through these microphones down these airwaves.
I want you to feel the power!
Put your hands on the radio.
Reach down into that holy organ, the most valuable, embarrassing, delicate organ of
your body.
That's your wallet.
And whip it out, baby.
Whip it out.
Winning dollar.
Get out of your church, your purse, or your church, and pull open and put your name on
that dotted line where it means the most.
The dotted line on your check in your checkbook.
To WCSB slash CSU Foundation friends, because this is the only way you're going to get this
kind of programming of people screaming at you to send more money.
You sure you can listen to some public's other public supported radio station, pledge drive,
but they don't scream!
Now do they?
No, they just go on and on and on.
That stupid NPR voice they use.
They all have that condescending, rich, white person way of talking.
Makes me sick!
Makes me puke!
Friends, you want to hear real, for real slack!
The for real down home mutants, misfits, screw ups, we vomit on Christmas!
And you know we're your kind of people, friends.
But like you, we're broke.
But like you, we can do a lot with a little.
So send us a little.
I've just spread a little spittle all over this microphone case here.
This foam rubber of my mic is covered with spittle.
But it's honest spittle!
From my heart!
Actually, it's from deep in my mouth.
But it shows, friends, there's sweat pouring down these preachers' faces.
We stink!
We stink of the sweat!
Of demanding and yelling and ranting and haranguing you for that thin, thin dime.
Just a little green and cabbage is all we're asking for, friends.
Just a little cabbage and gravel.
Little tiny pickings.
Just some little bitty pickings.
Like a man said to us, he walked up to us in Wendy's on Friday night.
He said to us, dollar.
Friends, that's what we're saying to you.
Nipple penny?
Give me a dollar.
Half pence?
Tuppence?
Two tuppence?
Three tuppence?
Penny for the old guy?
Can you spare me some quarter, me brother?
Spare a quarter for an old altar boy?
Can you help an old altar boy, father?
Can you help an old altar boy?
Friends, you know, there are many of you out there who have ill-gotten gains.
I don't want to go into your names and your phone numbers and your addresses and stuff.
But we will if you don't send us money.
That's right.
Some of you people have just not made enough money.
But you're living very high off the salted hog.
All you've got to do to relieve yourself of your guilt and make yourself a legal human
being again, not a pink or a conspiratorial conspiratist, but an actual living hoonan
bean is send your money, your escarole, your green suave.
Oh, geez, I don't want to start doing it again.
I'm going to the other form of relaxing, intelligent conversation.
Oh, that's great.
Oh, well, I have to turn the music down if you're going to be intelligent.
Friends, some of you are actually rich lawyers who fancy yourselves hipsters.
Can't you find it in your wallet to send $30,000 so that we could reach our underachieving
goal?
We're talking to you lawyers and doctors out there.
Are those among you who have too much money itching your skin?
Too much money making you feel funny, honey?
Too much money wanting to make you feel funny, honey?
Do you want to?
Okay, we'll talk to you later.
Actually, there are two doctors that subscribe to the Hour of Slack.
I mail them copies every week.
Those are like real live doctors.
Yeah.
Yeah, they have their fingers inside other people's bodies.
Well, with rubber gloves on.
Yeah.
And they're subgeniuses, friends, and they vote.
And so do you, I bet, with your fingers in other people's bodies.
And the voices in your ears have all been from the church of the Subgenius.
On this Hour of Slack number 1125A.
For more information about J.R. Bob Dobbs and the church of the Subgenius, you can see
subgenius.com or write P.O.
Box 181417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
Praise Bob.
And now, Lee Murr.
From PR News in Washington, I'm Sikand in Mexico.
A roadside bomb killed the governor of the Texas coast today.
Three other people in his convoy died of heart failure.
Space Shuttle Endeavour is on its way home from Baghdad.
Officials say Mission Control is located at an off-campus student-acquaint complex in
Houston on Wall Street 796459.
Israeli officials say Israel is the only country in the world that has a mission control.
Israel will return all PR news, including those from WarThorn, Washington.
What are those coins I hear now?
Sounds like just three coins to me.
Does this mean a trick?
Yes, it does, Don.
And.. here are the coins.
Well, we lay the three coins in a row.
The nickel, the quarter, the penny.
Very simple so far.
You will also notice that the edges of the coins are touching.
That's right. The nickel touches the quarter and the quarter touches the coin.
the penny. Yes. I want to know how to do this. Well, here goes. A nickel, a quarter, a penny
in a straight row, edge to edge. Like this. Oh, look. See, Don? Say. And the trick is
done. Right. I hope you like that trick, ladies and gentlemen. It was a trick. And until next
time, goodbye. As far as I'm concerned, you can go, too. Go back to Tony's and that woman
you were mooning. Oh, knock it off, will you? Now, you pulled a boner tonight and you know
it. Why? My husband.