From PR News in Washington, I'm distributed through the internet and viewed by thousands of Russian police.
And now PR's founder has fled the country. He was fired for refusing.
He said he refused to do PR News.
And now the number of Americans falling sharply in March.
Dow is 3, 16, 5, 5, 10, 22, 22, 14 and a half, 41, 7, 84, 39.
The Supreme Court says this is PR News.
And now PR reports reports and dust toughens the lungs and closes lung holes.
Those lung holes are now closed.
The new lung was slashed in half.
The old lung did respond to fraudulent criticism of PR News.
They say federal law limits how much money can be recovered by victims of PR News.
I feel like I'm watching Mondo Connie.
Hey, look, lemur scat. We must be getting close.
Looks like Bob's.
Listen to this music.
Bob, isn't it true that unless you have found your field in life, the thing that you want to do,
isn't it true that you frequently think of what you are best suited for?
And if you could only find out what he's best suited for, he would work 18 hours a day, I assure you.
He would study. He would self-discipline himself.
He'd stop fooling around.
I'm not saying that you are. I'm just using that as an example.
I'll tell you what you're best suited for.
How do you like that?
Now, Bob, if you could ever believe this, you'd just jump out of your skin.
I guess you're jumping now, aren't you?
Bob, you are best fitted for anything you want to do.
Anything. I don't care about your past education. I don't care a thing of your past.
You're best fitted for anything.
You know this theory that's been known since the beginning of time.
That we are what we think.
I'm Bob.
This theory is my play.
Excellent.
Nice.
Ooh, you wanna kill him?
I don't think that's a wise thing.
Not a wise thing to do.
Do you really think that you can't even see him?
You will feel him.
And if you're dreaming that you can take him, I don't think that's a very wise thing to do.
Uh-oh. You know who that is?
That's right. It's your pal, Bobo the Clown. Yay!
Bobo the Clown
Hey, Bobo. Wanna play a game?
Okay. Look up. Look down. Now look at Mr. Frying Pan.
Uh-oh. Bobo, fall down. Go boom.
Oh.
Wake up.
Oh, Bob.
Oh.
Bobo the Clown
Bobo, Bobo.
Joseph's drip back.
Fuck.
Walt Disney quarterback, Mary Jane Monsieur,
Amyράy Popo,
Larissa Adetano.
It's on every station
Get a trace on that signal, now
Let's roll
The other officers quickly take up the slack
That's how big it was
It could be seen for miles and miles around
Here's the king's command
I'm going to command all these musicians
To start playing their musical instruments
And as soon as they start playing the music
You are to fall down and bow down
In front of that great image, 90 feet high
And pray to it
I'm not giving in
To a smile or a grin
On a face I might never see again
I'm not gonna fly
Inside the sky
Of a big, bony sky
On a life that I know
Just can't win
Yes, Bob, you rang?
Am I a lousy flicker?
Whatever
I analyze it and assess it thoroughly
And then I make my prediction on the air
And I pick the opposite
Now there's a guy who knows how to get his point across
I stand on my record
I'm a drunk
I don't know nothing about how I do anything
One thing I shared with you this afternoon
Is that Bobby didn't listen to me
And I'm thankful now that he didn't
And hopefully if you've got a negative spouse
You're not listening to them either
Because he didn't listen to me
And he went about and built the business
Because he saw something in it
A friend of his or an acquaintance of his
Had shown him the plan
And I won't flush his bubble
That's just part of the story
But let us look to the next paragraph of prophecy
Which says
Dateline
Predominance
First paragraph
And I quote
World War III
Church of the subgenius
Shifts into Operation Removal
End quote
Now admittedly, dear friends
That leaves open some room for interpretation
And just what is Operation Removal
Designated to remove?
Well now
Knowing Bob
He'd want to remove
The very concept
Of removal
And Ivan was seen
Leaving shortly thereafter
With this gentleman
We observe Ivan
And this gentleman again
Travel to a country western bar
Bob's country bunker
He said he was going out
Two-stepping with Lisa
Unless his name's Lisa
Doesn't look like a Lisa, I know
We observe Ivan
And this gentleman
As they're walking
Basically fondling one another
On the street
Oh my God
Here we are
Bob's country bunker
We see him
All right, let's go
Well, Mr. Stang
No, we're dead
You've been doing drugs again, Ivan?
Do you know what Jenkins is?
Now there's our
Food, food plant
Hey
If you only have one left
Is it still your left nut?
We shouldn't go there
No
I suppose Bob told you
That his plan is going to prove
Hi, I'm Bob
Hi
Are you famous?
Yeah
See, I saw this program
That I'm talking about tonight
Some seven years ago
Seven years ago
When I saw this program
I folded my arms
Across my chest
I crossed my legs
And then I looked at that guy
That was talking about this program
And I said, no way
Whoever this joker is
Whoever's up there
He's always grinning
I thought, why was he always grinning?
It never dawned on me
Because he is so doggone rich
Being broke's not a good deal
But he looked at me
And he says, Al
Whatever you do
You're going to like Area 3
He says, as a matter of fact
Judging from the first two areas
You'll probably want to be involved
In Area 3
And I was committed and convinced
That Area 3 looked good
And then he spelled it out to me
D-E-A-D
Dead
Fantastic
I'll talk like this
Bob's your uncle, mate
That really doesn't help, Bob
You get the slack in the heart
You get the back slip
Well, that would have to have been
Last Fourth of July
It was very hot out
Oh, so hot
It was just blazing
And I was at the youth group picnic
Minister Bob was there
In his Bermuda pants
They cover more legs
Than his Bermuda shorts, you see
And they're just a little bit tighter
In the back
They just hug as buns
In the cutest way
But anyway
I was slicing
Some Rice Krispie squares
I had made
And Minister Bob
Was filling cups
Of the punch bowl
With his ladle
It was the biggest ladle
I'd ever seen
I wanted to touch it
But I was afraid to
Because it was so abnormally large
And as I watched him
With that ladle
He kept dipping it
Into the bowl
And pouring punch
And dipping
And pouring
Until I saw him
All the cups were filled
And it didn't take long
Because that was
Some big ladle
And then suddenly
Violently
There was a shudder
My buttocks were tingling
I was alone
Lost in space
I saw him toss that ladle aside
His arm exhausted
I must have passed out
Because that's all I remember
So you won't talk to me, huh?
Where'd you get the diamond bracelet, Miss Porter?
You may call me Connie
You did what was doing the storm, remember?
You said, all right, Connie
We might as well go down the street
Down together
I liked the way you said, Connie
It was like a punch in the door
Tell me about the bracelet
That's a dead giveaway
You're wanting us to die together like that
Dying together
Even more personal
Living together
What'd you pay for the bracelet?
Nothing
Pardon?
You're a low person, darling
Obviously out of the gutter
Maybe that's why I'm attracted to you
And maybe that's why you're attracted to me
Now what's gonna happen?
Do you know that's breaking
The second commandment?
Because
Babylon was the head of witchcraft
Sorcery
Horseshell
Notice that
When the music starts playing
You're to bow down and worship
Babylon
Like the beat, beat, beat, beat, beat
Of the tom-tom
When the jungle shadow falls
Like the tick, tick, tock
Of my old grandfather's clock
As it stands up straight against the wall
Like the drip, drip, drop
Drip, drop of the raindrop
When the summer shower is through
So a voice within me
Keeps repeating you
Just you
It's only you
Holy smokes, he exploded
And I won't tell you
I jumped in with both feet
And started listening to tapes
And reading books
Because I didn't
I had to read lots of books
Lots and lots of books
And sometimes you're gonna
to pick up a book in the beginning and you're going to read it and you're going to think,
I can't finish this. This book is too heavy. And you're going to put it down and a couple
of years later, a couple of months later, you're going to pick up that book and all
of a sudden it's going to slap you in the face.
Ow!
Hello, Connie.
Bob! I'm so glad.
You're glad? How do you think I feel? And you're just as good as new again.
Oh, oh!
In high society, I just ain't the type. Folks all look so surprised when I light my pipe.
Yes!
Oh, yeah.
You smoke a pipe, too?
Oh, don't be coy. I like it, too.
What's it going to get you, Connie? All this business of filling my pipe, pouring my drinks,
corned beef and cabbage?
I suppose I should pretend that I don't know what you mean by that, but I won't.
Connie, look, for the past three days, all you've done is...
All I've done is what?
Put down that pipe and get my pipe up.
No!
A partner in sin. Sometimes there is a mood that just... We don't know why.
You wouldn't kid a pal, would you, Connie?
Who are you kidding?
Oh, yourself, maybe.
No!
I don't know yet, Bob.
It's great. Just great.
Hello, children.
Well, here we are, Doc. The two lovebirds, all ready for the wedding. Sit down.
Are we healthy enough to get married?
Yeah, both as solid as a new dollar.
What's that?
This baby didn't hurt you a bit.
You can have a dozen more if you want to.
And, Bob, you'll be pleased to know that there's no trace of your old V.D.
One hundred percent cured.
What did you say about our first baby?
You've been married before?
Doctor, what did you call it?
V.D.?
You mean to say that Bob has actually had one of those horrible diseases?
That isn't true, Doctor.
Is that true, Bob?
All right, if you must know, I did have it.
But it's no worse than having an illegitimate child.
I think it is.
Why, I'd sooner marry a leper.
Thank you for letting me know about this in time, Dr. West.
And now I'm going out into the clean, fresh air.
Well, there went my happy wedding right out the door.
I'm terribly sorry, Bob.
Ah, dear Donald.
Just grabbed by the scalp shaker up and down a bit and choked.
Chub off the slack.
Come on.
Down this streaking out pit, we'll finally blame it on God.
And there'll be some kind of church started called the Streaker's Church.
And boy, they'll just, they'll fall and try to make it religious.
But I want to tell you it's abominable and it's filthy and it's rotten.
And men ought to stand up against it.
Say amen even more so.
The pipes, we need a jolly light, jolly light.
We're free from every demonstrate.
We drink the best of what we drink.
The best of what we drink.
I'm glad that this gay life is mine.
Fear the name of fingers, waters, dirty birdie, Holland, no sterling beef or chemist.
Fear the name of mystic Myron, Tucker, Tolan, Baddus, Sol Ringin, no Georgie III.
Oh, smiling.
No, Nate Bob.
If you understand that we have all had a partner in sin,
you really didn't do anything wrong.
You didn't do it by yourself.
There was an influence there.
Thank you, Bob.
Now we shop at Neiman Marcus instead of K. Martin Sears.
We go to Neiman Marcus and as soon as they spotted us, they said,
Hi, Bob and Bonnie.
Connie.
Ha!
They remembered us.
And so on the back, they take you in the back and they have drinks for you.
Whatever it is, scotch, whiskey, whatever you want.
And I ask for the usual.
Dinkum, dinkum, dinkum.
No, sir.
No, sirree.
Bob, Bob, Bob.
If you drink five gallons of Gatorade, you're going to spend five gallons of Gatorade somewhere
in one of these restaurants.
Good-bye there, right?
Frankly, either way it's .
Hey.
Turns out Connie had a secret of her own.
We went and did some crazy things and I could tell you, in the end, that it was just a
I can remember standing up on stage and putting the microphone up and nothing came out.
They're crying out loud.
And I went, oh my god.
No Connie, no!
I blew a five foot flame out of my butt.
It really isn't all that bad.
Hope you understand that there's nothing more liberating than being able to pee and poop your own diaper.
I love a bob.
Yeah! Yeah!
Come on.
Yeah, what's the matter with that? It's disgusting.
Don't ever ask me to do that again.
You just have to be careful.
You always think about, you know, getting poop on the finger, you know.
And I remember the first time it happened.
I couldn't believe it.
I mean, it's like, oh my god.
I've got poop on my finger.
And then I started thinking to myself, it could be worse.
I could have a job.
I can't even do it anymore.
I don't think I can.
I just can't do it.
And I said, Bobby, please don't ever make me do that again.
John!
Don't call me Bobby.
No Connie, no!
Call me Connie, dear.
I've loved you, loved you so.
Don't ever, ever go
You're my guiding light
Each and every night
You're the one that I adore
For now and evermore
Connie dear
Connie, Connie dear
Oh, Connie, no!
Hey!
From PR News in Washington, I'm unexpected.
In the coming hour, President Obama will end the U.S.
and effectively end more than a decade of PR's reports by the end of this year.
But less than 48 hours after making an unannounced president,
the Obama argue that Obama should be shielded from liability.
According to a senior administration official,
the official says,
says the U.S. will continue a military terrorism operation.
Much like PR News.
Technocrat politicians posed Modi's.
Modi said violence and terrorism must be brought to PR News.
Down is 6266667.
Godzilla drops to second place ahead of the amazing PR News.
Secret protesters say for secret police say
this is an estimated $111 million in domestic.
PR News in Washington.
Oh, yes, dear friends.
That PR News, of course, comes from Leimert.
Fernanda Nendi, Leimert.
And everything else we heard just about was from Reverend Susie the Fluesy's show
from WREK Atlanta.
The show called...
Bob's Slack Time Funhouse.
And I think that's an oldie collage of hers.
Really intense.
Nobody else does what Susie does.
Ever.
That's for sure.
They never did before and they never will again.
And if they do, they will probably be arrested.
Aye, aye, aye, aye, aye, aye.
And friends, we have a new microphone in the station tonight.
Exciting.
We should try to think of a name for it.
It's really sleek and shiny and futuristic.
It's silvery and reflective
and doesn't have the big black foam wind screen on it.
No.
It has a little modern day flat disc of a wind screen
to make the pops, those pops not sound so bad.
And it has an exquisiteness.
It has a geometric sort of artistic balance thing
that holds it just so.
Speaking of artistic bounce,
Lonesome Cowboy Dave should be calling in any minute.
You know, I shouldn't say that
because that would cause some smart aleck to beat him
and call in instead.
You know how they are.
Yes, I know how they are.
You know how the listeners are.
Yes.
Now see, this is probably not Dave.
This is probably some listener.
Our listener.
Do you think that's one of the listeners?
Do I think what?
No, I didn't think it was.
No.
No, it is Dave.
Okay, good.
It's our Dave.
Yeah, we had just mistakenly set up someone besides you
to call line one, but now that can't happen.
But that crapped out?
No.
It's okay.
Everything's fine.
Sure it is.
Thankfully, it's you.
I'm sorry, Dave.
I didn't mean you personally.
Actually, when we came in, our previous DJ, Charleston, said,
everything's good.
It's all good.
Yeah, it's all good.
And I know what he means.
I know what he means, but I still kind of, as sweet a guy as he is,
I still wanted to punch him, too.
I always want to punch everybody who says it's all good.
I can't help it.
I'm the proof that it's not all good.
I'm not all good.
I'm kind of good bad.
Yeah.
What I usually feel at first when I'm confronted with that is like,
yeah, maybe you're right.
Then I feel real guilty because why would I feel like nothing's good?
And then I want to strangle him.
I don't want to punch anybody because my hands are too artistic.
At least the flab handler parts of them, the old ones with the tattoos,
those are, oh, man.
Long story short.
It's not worth doing.
So kids, don't tattoo weird buttock designs on your hands,
especially the part of your palms of your hands,
especially since they tell you to never have a tattoo on the palm of your hand
because it's not only ridiculously painful, it can be dangerous.
Just don't.
Is that true?
I've come to think of it, I can't remember seeing any palm tattoos.
No, you wouldn't want to have those little needles going in there.
But I've seen it.
But think of all the other places that people,
get tattooed.
You know?
That would kind of hurt.
That are even more sensitive, especially because that's what they're made for, yeah?
Yeah.
I don't know why the abjuration would be so strong to avoid the palms of your hands.
Then perhaps it's something religious, you know, for all I could tell.
Dave, you're so old that you don't even have any tattoos, right?
Oh, no.
Only the very, very old and the very old.
Very, very young are tattoo-less now.
Well, the very, very old, some of them have gone through various tattoo phases.
This would probably be my third tattoo phase
because, you know, in the days of punk rock,
a lot of people used to wear tattoos and stuff.
And then there was the second wave of tattoos.
And now there's the, it's very common.
In fact, it's so common, it's like, remember the illustrated man?
Oh, right.
Dr. Legume, yeah, I know him personally.
You know, he's not really illustrated from the waist down, I don't think.
No, he just draws on himself with a big old ink crayon.
Oh, boy, is he fully illustrated from the waist up.
Whoo!
But see, I think if I had a, I don't know, I just don't know.
I don't know because I'm old.
I hate it.
Why do you?
You know, I'll never wear my, and here's another thing.
I try not to be cool, right?
I mean, my hair is real, real long.
That's the least cool thing you can do with your hair
if you're a man or a woman these days.
Yeah, I mean, I try not to be cool, but, you know, I don't have any tattoos.
But every now and then I accidentally do something
that makes it seem like either I'm cool,
or I'm trying to be cool, or something.
Just the fact that I even brought this up is probably a good example.
I'm ashamed of myself now.
I'm going to shut my mouth for two seconds.
Time's up.
Okay, I can talk again now.
What a bizarre sidebar.
Reminds me of like, hey, did you ever see those ramen-style pool noodles?
They're usually not strangled with little orphans and so forth.
Ramen-style pool noodles?
That's a joke.
Oh.
Where am I?
I feel as if there was an ark filled with every type of human two by two,
just like on the North Ark back so many thousands of years ago,
that I would not let you come on my ship unless you did it by following me.
I can't read the rest of it for you because I don't have it in front of me.
You can read it behind you if you change the dialectical approach.
Okay.
You're talking about the ark?
Dave's ark?
As opposed to Noah's ark?
Yeah, Dave's ark would be very profuse with wildebeest and all the hairy children of the jungle
would be there arguing their catapulted songs together, you know, and it would be like yo-ho-ho.
Oh, like a WCSB station meeting.
No, more like a WC Fields irrationality complex.
WC Fields and WCSB.
What is the connection?
Yeah.
It's halfway there.
We almost know.
WC Fields B radio.
The tension lies somewhere in the middle.
Seeing how many dynamic subs diffuse K-5 from that on a pre-cellular level.
You just go down each level and there's like WC Fields and it's like an anagram for CW Sledfire or something like that.
Yeah.
And then you know that's the same.
And then you know that's the same part where the, you know, that bar they destroyed down
the flats because the insane people were.
Did you hear about that?
A bar down in the flats destroyed by insane people?
That one had the last, the last subgenius devival.
That's why we don't do those anymore.
I think that's where it was held and it has kind of a reputation for allowing insane people
to express themselves freely.
And there was some show and somebody, a stink bomb or something in the place.
And started shouting fire in the crowded auditorium.
The police had to come because people were divided into two camps.
There were the elderberries and then there were the stone heads.
And they, I don't know.
I would join the stone heads.
Well, no, they're not like stoners or heads or anything like that.
No, I know they would be hard, more hard headed.
Well, yeah.
You'd be able to use them as battering rams to escape from the non-existent fire in the club.
So.
So this was local.
Was this local news that you're referring to?
Yeah, I guess some of them are neoliberals or whatever they call it nowadays and stuff.
When they, you know, if you don't wear the right uniform, I guess you're, you're arrogant.
Neocoms.
That means neocommies.
Well, I heard that.
Disguised as Republicans, disguised as Christians, disguised as humans.
I want to hear an interesting funny little anecdote about what you just said, which is
actually true.
Sure.
And I heard it on a genuine news source, not the lie I just made up there.
Yeah, man.
Get onto my cloud.
One of the Koch brothers went to Russia under Stalin there and made millions and millions
of dollars rebuilding the Soviet economy.
Then he comes back and starts all these anti-communist organizations like everybody in the world
who is a communist or some or is a Stalinist or something.
Now, wait a minute.
How could the Koch brothers be working for Stalin?
That was Stalin died a long time ago, probably before those guys were born.
No, Pappy.
It's like, you know, Pappy Bush.
Oh, Pappy Koch.
Pappy Koch.
Right.
We're talking about those brothers.
That's how you pronounce their name, right?
It's not?
Pappy Koch and Pappy Bush.
So, I don't know.
You got a point there.
Those two go together, don't they?
Oh, well.
Pappy.
Pappy Koch and Pappy Bush.
Yeah, we don't need to dwell on that, I don't think.
Yeah, I didn't know if I got it yet.
I'm sorry.
Now, back to WC.
Back to WC.
WC is also known as a water closet in England, which is a bathroom.
Yep.
That is also a very important part of the clue.
Yes.
Right there.
The WC clue.
If you don't like it-
Water closet SB in Cleveland.
Now, who are we just that figure out?
We just figure out what SB stands for.
Some bitch.
That's it.
You can say that, right?
Because S-U-M-B-I-T-C-H, that's not a word.
So, you can say it.
If it's not a word, you can say it on the radio, right?
Oh.
Galacondale.
Galafondale.
Pan-ca-ta-ra-pa-da-da-da-da-da.
Talafondale.
Pashna.
Kal-tin-ki.
Sim-pan-de-f-o-na-ya.
Gal-e-s-ma-ta-la-man-gen-ya-o-b-ra-ta-ka-na-s.
So, back to the subject of Africanized killer deer.
Have you had any trouble with those in Ashtabula?
Well, just as out in the lovely metro parks of Cleveland, out here in the sticks, yes,
they had a deer kill, I think it was last Sunday.
Maybe it wasn't a couple weeks ago.
Is that what they call a-
Was it a-
A public hunt.
Can't say that.
Yeah, don't say that fast.
A public hunt.
No, they're not having a deer problem of any kind because the winter apparently killed
a whole lot of everything.
Yeah.
There's articles about the many things that was killed and various new-
Oh, they find old hobo skeletons wrapped up around deer skeletons all mummified and-
Trying to get warm.
What a way to go.
... shooing on twigs.
Yeah.
Having to hug a deer to get a little-
A dead deer.
A deer that starved to death.
Well, wait a minute.
Why didn't he just eat the deer?
See, you made me think of that now, and that is not a very pretty picture to paint.
I have a talent for that, don't I?
No, it is not.
I visualize things and then I share them with people.
And then they feel sicky, sicky in the-
And then all the listeners need buckets, yes.
Yes.
I can see this humor now.
If you were to literally take the dead deer and put it up on your body, kind of a-
Kind of so like the horns and the head were up above your head, maybe perhaps like a mentally
ill native of some tribe that we've never heard of before.
Right.
That was standard procedure, dance around with a deer skull or a bear skull on your
head and represent the spirit of the deer or the bear or the kangaroo or the-
Right, right.
... hobo or whatever.
Yeah.
The spirit guide.
And see, I always mistook that for like the and these other tribes and stuff
like that who were like cargo cults and used to wear like the underwear of Westerners on
their head, like boxer shorts and-
The subgenius tribes would wear the skull of a golfer.
The shamans would wear a witch doctor outfit that had the skull of a World Cup golfer over
their skull, which wasn't hard to do because subgeniuses often have tiny little heads.
Pressing company excluded unfortunately.
Yes, unfortunately.
Unfortunately, some are microcephalic and others just macrocephalic and we're in the macro realm.
Our heads are too big for our feet.
That's right.
Like an old blues song.
Top heavy.
Lord, my head's too big for my feet.
Mm-hmm.
Lord, Lord, Lord.
That's the part I was just like, I'm not saying it's like I'm not.
and little turnarounds and stuff like that.
The guy would take his encrusted claw that I can
and dab it into the interior parts of the round hole guitar.
Sometimes if there was an infall,
it had to be like kind of a kung fu
or some sort of martial arts move.
He usually brought the house down.
Of course, there was construction going on next door
and explosives in the basement.
Who knows how far it really went.
I feel so sorry for the listeners.
Half of them are trying to listen to what,
trying to translate Dave,
and the other half are listening to the elevator music
Rolling Stones in the background.
The Rokeville Orchestra performs the hits of the Rolling Stones
is what's in the background.
It's something, it was a CD that little Pope S. Pantiera
didn't want anymore and donated to the church,
and here it is.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
But I can't even hear what song was playing.
Angie.
Yes, there it is.
There it is.
Manger.
I need to give you a bath.
I think it was Jagger.
It was Jagger.
You're scratching.
Dandruff.
You shouldn't do that.
It is the entropy of Boris now.
It's like when he goes on the next tour,
he's going to be angina.
We started the show with the Muzak version
of Sympathy for the Devil in the background,
and that caused me to remember when
Einstein's Secret Orchestra used to play
Sympathy with the Devil.
Only Dave would invent completely new,
new lyrics.
Oh, please.
You know, like a chorus.
Everybody else would be going,
woo, woo, woo, woo,
and Dave would be coming up with all new things
you didn't know about the devil.
If only we could have understood things.
Yes.
Yeah, and if I could have, too,
I mean, I could have capitalized it
and been on Fox News or something like that
and got a couple availabilities every month
and stuff like that
and moved into the socket.
And then got my check every once in a while
from Root Baby.
That's what we call them here at Fox Central.
We call them Root Baby.
You know, Dave, if you changed your stick,
you could probably be on Fox News
and other Foxy shows, I guess.
You could kind of neocon it a little bit.
Well, maybe, or I don't know.
You could be, they would have,
they'd have like a conservative
and a liberal,
and then they'd have you.
A surrealist.
It's a really great and wonderful place,
and America should really remain true to its ideals
of greed and envy,
and especially of malicious warfare.
And that's the main thing about America,
and I like the way the flag day there.
Of course, I'm not a citizen,
but my voice makes you believe me.
Or something like that.
Yeah, only that wasn't a very American-sounding accent, man.
No, man, I was trying to...
You're supposed to sound...
You're supposed to sound more like an American.
You know, say...
Okay.
And you have to learn to pronounce the word
narcissistic like this.
Narcissistic.
You gotta say it like that real fast.
Me!
Because you know who's...
Everybody knows about Obama.
Yeah, there you go, like that.
Wow.
How would they know that, though?
How would they know if Obama is narcissistic or not?
Unless they were high...
Under his bed sometimes
to see if he was looking at himself in the...
I mean, you know.
Oh, he just looks that way.
I was telling Pappy,
I don't know if I want to move back to Texas.
More than 50% of people there
think Obama's a Muslim from Kenya,
and he said,
well, I think he is Muslim.
I said, why?
He says, it just seems like one.
On the other hand,
I saw a comment yesterday,
you know, that...
that...
the...
the traitorous superhero
that we traded the...
the...
the other superheroes for.
We traded five superheroes
for one traitorous, cowardly superhero.
Well, his parents, right?
Looked like...
kind of like old hippies.
Yeah.
Well, the mom's kind of hot
for an old gal.
And the dad has a long red beard.
I saw some guy comment,
he looks...
see that beard?
He looks like a Muslim to me.
And I thought,
well, what does that say about Duck Dynasty?
Duck Dynasty.
That reveals it.
They're Muslims.
That's why they have those beards.
It's not because they're hillbillies.
It's not because that's how
the super cool people in Arkansas look.
No.
It's because...
Byron.
Fundamental.
No.
It's because they're Muslims.
With a rifle in the back.
They're Muslimics, man.
Copy of the holy book in the car.
That's right.
Duck Dynasty.
And ZZ Top.
They're Muslims, too.
I guess so.
They got that beard.
They got the beard.
And funny hats.
Right.
Sometimes they have a funny hat.
Hey, I'm not wearing my funny hat right now.
I'm no good.
I was afraid I didn't want to get shot.
It's really sick,
especially if you're a Sikh,
which isn't Muslimic in any way, shape, or form,
but they wear kind of a turban.
So they're fair game for mean old redneck ladies
with handguns.
Well, mean old redneck ladies
especially like to blame Christian Arabs
who are right in the middle of everything like that.
Those are the ones you have to...
I don't know.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's sad.
And then there's the poor Nazi, communist, socialist,
pagan Masons
that everybody puts them down,
especially if they're gay.
Well, remember, it is only a social club
and you don't have to wear your party pin
at every meeting and stuff like that.
What, the Masons?
The Masons?
Oh, they've got you so full.
Is that true with the pointed hats
and stuff like that
or is that just kind of like...
Well, they wear those fez.
Hey, there's another thing.
They wear fez like people in Morocco.
You know who lives in Morocco?
Muslims.
Islam, yep.
Islam.
Oh, man.
Mary had a little Islam.
It fleeced us in the know.
Well put, well put.
Yes.
And every time I ate some beans,
I suddenly had to go.
Okay, you're ruining it there.
Okay, I'm sorry.
You're like really deep, man.
I predicted that somebody would say the phrase
I'm sorry during this show.
However, I think I picked the wrong person.
Well, what does the term political paucity mean?
I can't put paucity and political together.
Political paucity?
Give me an example.
The political paucity of the paupers,
of the nimbobs.
Oh, God, I've got a terrible headache now.
Oh, my neck.
It's called the sound of a right-wing radio.
Oh, my God.
I can't stop.
Oh, getting those jowls shaking.
I don't have that much jowl.
And so I have to shake my head really violently.
And now I'm kind of dizzy.
Yes, the poor listeners didn't get to see the performance
that I get to see in this radio station.
Reverend Stagg makes his voice go like this.
Oh, you don't do it.
It'll hurt.
You don't have anywhere near enough cheeks to do that with.
You have to have a big old saggy jowl.
So you can...
It's good to wear like a short sleeve shirt as well
and have like the arms.
They go...
Right along with it.
Hey, I heard a bunch of cats make the subgenie sound
like when they see bugs in mine doors.
Not exactly.
It's not like...
I'm sorry.
You need to change the subject.
No, that's okay.
It can be the funny noise show.
Yeah.
I'm out of funny noises.
I've...
In my head...
No, no.
There's no such thing as being out of funny noises, Stagg.
Not at all.
Sit down and put your feet up on the huff and just relax.
We're going to teach you how funny noises influence our lives
everywhere and every day.
We hear these sounds and many more every day in our lives.
On the way home from school or uptown, it's always...
And all these wonderful noises have meanings
that only the inner ear and the open eye and the third nostril can...
This show's really going downhill.
I'm sure the last few stations that still play this show are probably getting second thoughts.
Hey, Stagg used to edit these things a lot tighter.
Now it seems like he's just trying to get a show done every week.
Yeah, what gives?
He's not spending a week and a half on each show like he used to.
Yeah, what's his emphasis on...
salivary glands and the endocrine
system.
That's what I want to know.
Well, they are
sloppily done now.
It's because, you know why?
You've just said hell with it all.
You've got that right.
That happened
the last pledge drive at WCSB.
That was when I finally said,
that's it, had enough.
I care exactly as much about
those listeners as they care about this
show. However,
outside of the WCSB
pledge drives, the Hour of Slack
does occasionally
get a donation.
And?
Although there haven't been many of those lately,
when they do come in,
that helps me get out of bed.
I feel like I can
afford to get out of bed
once a week or so.
Two very burly gentlemen
from Kingston that
you claim you
met some time ago.
Yeah, that was Dr. Drummond
and his son, Byron.
Byron?
From Kingston.
So he was the famous poet?
Right, Lord Percy Shelley, Lord Byron.
He was married to
Frankenstein's daughter.
Oh.
Mary Shelley Stein.
Did you ever see the movie?
I'm sorry.
Two? I'm sorry so far.
Sorry, go to three.
Okay, go ahead.
You know, I just wondered
about the Lord Byron
thing there, if you've ever seen
the movie Dead Man by Jim Jarmusch.
Yes, I have.
That's right, there's...
Did he think he was Byron
or Coleridge or something?
I wasn't caring about either one.
What about Dead Man?
What about Jim Jarmusch?
That was a great movie.
Well, the hero,
the Indian guy,
thought that the...
the guy who had been wounded
and was traveling around
trying to die and stuff like that,
he said his name was Byron
or Wordsworth or Coleridge.
Oh, no, William Blake.
Blake, yes.
Yeah, William Blake.
The Indian was a big fan of the poet.
No, not William, whatever, Blake.
Yeah.
And Johnny Depp
just happened to have that name.
It was funny because
Johnny Depp's character
originally came from the movie.
He's from Cleveland in that movie.
He goes out west
and has a terrible time
and he's dying.
And the Indian says to him,
Blake, you are about to go
where the souls go
when their life is done.
And Johnny Depp goes,
Cleveland?
That was a very atmospheric
black and white western,
I believe made in 1999,
maybe?
With a beautiful soundtrack
done by, of all people,
Neil Young on a silver-toned guitar
and a silver-toned amp
from the late 1950s.
Was it Neil Young?
I thought it was Ry Cooter.
No, that's Little Big Man, I think.
Yes.
Right.
It was Neil Young.
Okay, yeah, that was a really good,
that had a great score.
And there's a wonderful scene
where Johnny Depp falls in
with three cross-dressing bandits.
Bandits.
Or, you know, it's like
Billy Bob Thornton, Iggy Pop,
and some, who's the other actor?
I can't remember.
And they get all gay over,
Billy Bob Thornton's going,
how do you get your hair like that?
I just can't do anything with my hair.
He's just feeling of Johnny Depp's hair.
He's wearing this stupid wig
and a gingham dress.
I just can't do nothing with my hair.
Did you know it was also
Robert Mitchum?
Was it Mitchum's last movie?
It was.
Yeah.
But just seeing Iggy and...
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Now I can't even remember.
I didn't know.
He was the mean pappy.
He was the mean pappy
who sent for Johnny Depp
and then he screwed him
and Johnny Depp...
Oh, that's right, yeah.
The mean boss man.
Who hires,
just like your jobs, Dave,
where you go all the way
across the country
and he goes,
well, it's going to be,
you know, $2 an hour
and somebody...
We already gave the job
to somebody else.
You're going to have to turn around
and go back to Cleveland.
God.
And that crazy actor guy
that's Steve Siddick's buddy.
What's his name?
Crispin Glover.
Yeah, yeah.
George McFly.
Crispin Glover
had a creepy thing
at the beginning of it.
He's like the coal shoveler
of the train,
so he's in blackface.
Yes.
And he says,
this is where you're going.
Nobody ever comes back from there.
Something like that.
That's a great movie.
I think that was shown at X Day.
I think.
I think it was awesome.
I think Dr. Dark showed that at X Day
and the drive-in.
You know, we have a drive-in
at X Day festivals
when the world's about to end.
For some reason,
at a campground,
people decide,
oh no, let's watch DVDs.
World's about to end.
We're at a beautiful campground.
Let's watch TV.
And although it is,
I got to watch Big Man Japan
laying on the stage.
Watch, you know,
with the screen
gigantically huge in front of me.
That was great.
It really is pretty groovy.
And we'll have the drive-ins this year.
I think Dr. Dark's planning to be there.
And if he doesn't,
which is unthinkable,
hell, I will.
Somehow.
Even if I have to do finger puppet,
shadow puppets on the screen.
We're subgeniuses.
We can do that.
I'll do the finger puppets
and Hal can do the voices.
And if you can,
if we can get you there somehow,
then you can do the strip tease.
Yeah, Dave, and the pole dance.
I could do like a punching Judy thing
with doing all three parts.
Dave can be the pole
and I'll be the pole dancer.
Can you imagine that?
I would look so sleek
in little underwear
like they wear
in those,
those shows.
And Dave would be so upright
and stiff.
And I would just slink around him
and climb up and down him
like a snake.
Princess Wee seems to think
this is a funny thing to envision,
but you can see things like that
at X-Day and at Starwood.
They have,
Princess Wee,
don't laugh into the mic.
Oh, I'm sorry.
There is a,
isn't there a pole dancing thing
at Starwood?
That's the fourth.
I'm sorry, by the way.
There have been pole dancing
events at X,
at Starwood Festival.
Absolutely.
Yes.
Well, see, normally
when we think of pole dancing,
we think of polkas
and mazurkas
and real fast dance music
like that and stuff.
Oh, yeah.
They changed everything.
It's all different now.
Yeah.
One of the most popular dances now
is called the puppy dog.
Think about that.
Well, what does that involve?
Well, you use your hands,
you use your hands,
like little paws up on the door
as you're trying to get into the house
as you're dancing.
Are you serious?
Yes, it's the puppy dog.
I guess I haven't been watching
my YouTube enough lately.
I guess cultural decline
has reached the LCD
in every way possible.
I've seen the puppy dog.
So what is twerking, Princess Wee?
Can you demonstrate that for me?
No, not right here and now,
Reverend Stang.
I don't think that it would be
appropriate at this juncture.
I feel like such an idiot.
I've never seen,
believe me,
believe it or not,
I've never...
I laughed at him.
I've never even seen
child pornography.
Honest to grobs,
I've never laid eyes
on child porno.
I've been cruising the internet
for nigh on to 94.
And yet I still...
In fact, the closest thing
I ever saw was something
my son showed me.
He said,
my buddy got this off
his dad's computer.
His dad's a cop.
Oh, Princess Wee.
Princess Wee was just
kind of twerking.
You were twerking?
Yes.
Well, what is twerking?
Is it just like somebody
talking and they can't
pronounce it right?
I don't know if I can
describe what I just saw.
It's not normal.
It's not something
I see very often.
You twist someone's underwear,
right?
You grab their underwear
from behind.
You twist it?
No, no, no.
Now, that's a wedgie.
That's a wedgie.
Yeah, twerking is a dance
thing that old people
do to make young people laugh.
Isn't there like a
Hillary Clinton twerking YouTube?
John McCain twerking
and all that kind of
whatever twerking means.
Well, Miley entered it
into our vocabularies,
you see.
Who's Miley?
Miss Cyrus.
It started with the Chinese
Communist Party Central Committee.
Huh?
Princess Wee's talking about
modern day youth stars and stuff.
So anyway, we're talking
about that movie
that came out in the 90s.
It just came out.
Dead Man.
Hey, have you seen
the new Godzilla?
Godzilla versus
the Smog Monster?
It's subgenius time control.
Yeah, exactly right.
You even get to walk
in the theater
and it only costs $7.
Actually, yeah.
What did we pay?
We went to a movie theater
this year, didn't we?
I believe it was more
like $11.
$11.
Yeah.
Oh, well.
And that wasn't the 3D style.
No, that was the cheaper version.
Yeah.
Because now you can get
a movie like,
how can you get it?
Normal, flat, 3D,
animal style,
Christmas style,
and what, smothered,
smashed, battered.
They have as many kinds
of movie formats now
as Waffle House has
of hash browns.
And you don't even need
the special glasses.
But they're really expensive.
Yeah.
They have the movies
that you don't need
the special glasses for.
You have to cross your eyes.
Oh.
Hey, it's five minutes
until the end of the show
and I have a five-minute
Susie thing I'm going to play.
So that's the end.
That's the end.
Well, I'll just go
across my eyes
and see everything in 3D
for as long as I possibly can.
That's how the kids do it.
That's how the kids do it, Dave.
Dave, I think we've been cut off.
Reverend Stang is cut off.
He's cutting us off.
No, not yet,
but I'm about to.
Suddenly.
I don't feel bruised,
but I do feel used.
Welcome, welcome, my friend.
On and off the road for fun
We forgot why we came here
We have quit all
All of our jobs
Like a headlight
Friday, dear
He has lit the sacred pipe
And he's smiling at us now
On and off the road
He's gone
We are his town
That hurt, Bob.
Bob, where are you?
Where are you?
Friend of Bob's.
He pointed to an unobtrusive object
the size of a radio.
It had Bob's fingerprints all over it.
I found my fingerprints and not yours.
He and I both agreed
that Bob's not a nice person.
It's funny because it's true.
That was enough for them.
Oh, but you know, you can write for free information from the source itself.
Oh, the memberships have finally notched up to 35 bucks.
You haven't been well-worn for the past couple years, but hey, what price off-planet survival anyway?
But if you're craving enough to be sniffing around for some free information,
grab your pencil.
Just write to Bob.
He's waiting to hear from you at the Subgenius Foundation at P.O. Box 181417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
Or he's as close as your keyboard at subgenius.com.
And hey, admit the truth to yourself now.
You know you'll be coined.
You're going your way to the head of the line to buy a membership when the atomic heat rays are so close they're welding your butt cheeks together.
Oh, but don't come crying to me.
I can't wait for X-Day.
I love the taste of human flesh.
I just haven't had it cooked yet.
We get down and dirty in this church because religion happens to be a dirty, dirty business.
This church is a lot like an old car sometimes.
Isn't it?
But it's the dirt that's the only thing that's holding it all together.
And Bob, Bob is the bondo that keeps our sagging bumpers up.
Isn't that the one thing that we're here for after all, sneakers?
The dirt.
Oh, so let's dig in and dish it up.
It's crammed packed with minerals, too.
So don't settle for the poop du jour.
Excremeditate your troubles away with the armor-piercing slack of J.R. Bob Dobbs.
God almighty, I'm full of it.
But I'm going to let it go.
And you've got to let it go.
Dear friends, just as sure as you can bet it, one of those two greatest guys up there is going to let go just as you is letting go.
Bob, what's Miss Presky's heat?
So far.
Right, Jack?
Yes.
Well, how do you feel, Miss Presky?
Sick.
Oh, well, you can afford it now, love.
But like the good book says, there are bigger deals to come.
Oh, Christ.
OK, thank you, Max.
Oh, come on, now in a brilliant condition.
Look, I have about 22.
That big one of thoseLast somebody brought their little ladies Forbes recently.
AW citizen.
I hope things work out the way you want them to.
Thanks, Bob.
I'm hoping, too.
No, Connie, no!
Oh, crap!
It's on fire!
Great.
Now what?
Good night, Seekers.
Oh, sire, there is no more money.
We gotta get some money.
That dirty, purgish, hark-a-back, flackin' wharton,
fill-a-bunker-burton, purk-a-loom-a-burton,
durk-a-bustin'-a-law!
Friends, we're glad you listened to this show,
and we're even more glad that some listeners have donated enough
to help us keep on going for another couple of months.
And not just this show,
but some genius people,
and all the other archive sites.
But if you truly love Bob,
and want some of that slack back to rebound to you,
you should go to subgenius.com front page,
or especially the radio page,
or the catalog store pages,
and help out financially as best you can.
Now, we know what it's like to be on the brink of total poverty,
and we don't want any subgeniuses to make their own situations worse.
But some of you,
still have jobs.
Even five bucks makes a big difference,
even if it's only once a month,
from enough of you.
Fifty bucks makes an even bigger difference.
All we're saying is that,
blowjobs could go the way of stevejobs,
if you don't pay Dobbs.
We also take checks and money orders to,
Subgenius Foundation.
P.O. Box,
181-416-7177.
Cleveland Heights,
Ohio 44118.
Thanks for anything you can do to help let there be slack.
There is more to help,
you can pay down at TakeTheMoneyPop.com.
Park Farm Road,
Someone you have no idea on.
The American Asylum Association.
Use the emoji RMTV to click on what you want on a weekend.
This video will spark your contracts!
Company name Howard P.
access
MONEYPOP TV
Security Dept
Kill me!