I don't want to start yakking until I can see a bog.
Volume! That's me. No, I'm the one with the volume. They don't need to turn it up.
I haven't even started yet. This is the sound check.
It'll be going on for another hour and a half since this is a subgenius show.
There we go. Okay.
Let's just watch this one-minute commercial and then we'll begin.
The subgenius power of sweat.
There's a better, long-lasting, healthy way to help yourself.
Just a pill. Maybe a drink at night.
The older you get, the more somehow your priorities change.
I mean, most people go, my number one priority is sex, baby, sex.
But, you know, really, you can go a lot longer without sex than you can go without urinating.
So is sex really the first thing in your life?
If you start making a list, it'll be down there around number 11, just before Bob.
If you're really messed up, it'll be after Bob.
But I think breathing was, air was number one priority, and I think drinking water was next,
and then urinating, then eating, then crapping.
And stuff like money and...
sex are pretty low down there.
Your back not hurting is like number five.
So we're a practical religion, friends.
You know, like I say, we don't even get to Bob up until 11 or so.
And this is 11.
Actually, it's 1,113.
That's how many of these weekly shows we've done since 1985.
And what you just heard was recorded at the Starwood Festival,
2000.
2007.
And most of this whole episode was recorded on that same location at 10X Day,
the subgenius event at Brushwood in deepest New York.
And this year, we had Dr. Howell and Reverend Filippo Abernathy there doing live show with us
and other gorillas and demons.
Right?
Five people.
Anybody else have a gorilla and demon list?
That they want to share with us?
Yeah.
Are there any of those left?
Because those guys didn't really have that many of them.
There's still some left.
There are some.
Yeah.
If you want to fill one out, please feel free to.
You're free, your inner gorilla.
And demon.
So there we are.
And as a matter of fact, as we traveled, we saw more.
And it was over there.
I saw too much.
Yeah.
I wish I could forget.
I wish I could forget some of it.
I wish I could choose which to forget.
Boy, that would be great.
Selective forgetting?
We were just talking about that.
Yeah.
When I start thinking of things that I want to forget, it always backfires.
You know?
It's difficult.
That's the ultimate example of that is that beautiful movie, Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind,
where that happens.
They selectively forget.
Yeah.
I saw that, but I can't remember it.
Ah, that's because you selectively forgot it.
Yeah.
It worked.
It was a movie that worked, I guess you could say.
I think your thing is that you are able to take all the things that have happened to you
and use them as fuel.
There's no need for you to selectively forget.
I think you're able to channel anything that's negative that's happened to you into your head.
Oh, that's what you think.
No, you can't do that.
Oh, no.
We bottle up the really bad ones now.
We keep those bottled up.
Because you need...
Yeah.
You need the pressure from that to release the good ones.
You use that.
That's what keeps everything compressed.
Plus, you can't...
That's a more valuable soul to the aliens, the ones that have a lot of anguish.
Steeped in it.
Steeped in anguish.
Yeah, the souls that have redolent of anguish and pain.
That's what really gets the aliens off.
You can get a lot more money for a tortured subgenius soul than a complacent pink soul.
In fact, really, they just use it.
The subgenius souls are so rare that they use those as flavoring and condiments on the pink souls that they...
I guess that's what they're hooked on.
Yeah, a little dab will do you.
That's what they can afford.
A little dab will do you.
It's true.
It's much...
The subgenius brain just tastes richer, I think.
It's just more...
I don't know.
Just more meat in it.
They smell awful, though.
Well...
You don't have to keep them in your basement.
We keep...
That's not a rumor.
A lot of people...
We just had the one in our freezer.
They must be kidding about the canisters full of souls in the basement.
But the sad thing is it's really true and there really are probably 3,000 of those canisters now.
In your basement?
And rusting.
We probably can't even crank the valve on most of them.
They've been there since the 80s.
I just had the one frozen one that you gave us that we've just been slicing little slices off it for years now.
But you never know when it's going to be cut with bad soul.
Well...
There's a lot of different kind of subgeniuses that join up.
And I'm sure when we get home and process all these new memberships, the most of them will kind of go...
Oh, that's a good one.
You know, you can kind of smell a little bit as it passes through.
And...
That one's okay.
You know, another $30 well spent by that person.
And...
Oh, God!
Oh!
Not...
I remember that one.
I remember you showed me that one.
Every now and...
It's like every seventh or eighth one you run into a bad soul.
Yeah.
You know, a bad...
A chameleon soul.
A lizard soul.
Mm-hmm.
It changes.
Uh-huh.
Because you got to...
You can't be a lizard soul.
You don't want to have a lizard soul that changes all the time.
Because then you have to think all the time to cover what...
To remember what lies you told to who.
As Mark Twain said, if you always tell the truth, you don't have to think about anything.
And if we could be as pure as Bob...
He doesn't have the guile to do that.
He doesn't have the guile to lie.
He doesn't have the sense to lie.
Lying is what makes us human.
It's what separates us.
Our social habits are so much more complex because they're built on lies, on tricking
the other monkey, as cynical as that may sound.
And our goal is to be more like Bob, to grin happily and emptily without suspicion because
we would have to be as lucky as Bob.
You wouldn't have to worry about anything.
Of course, we're not.
We're never going to be like Bob.
But that's a good sort of a direction to head in.
I hate those shirts.
They're so stiff.
You can never get where Bob is, but you can follow in his trail, which is pretty easy
to do.
I tried on one of his shirts that one time.
It was impossible.
I'm sorry.
You can...
He leaves a trail, but you can smell it.
And plus, if you walk around here, you will occasionally find little piles of cotter pins
and jello.
And that's how we know Bob has been here.
And he has.
He comes to Brushwood a lot.
No, I didn't know this.
Yeah.
Cotter pins and...
You didn't know that?
No.
And he's always...
It's my first time here this time.
He's always just missing.
Every time that's happened, the smoke was still lingering in the air.
The jello was still quivering.
It hadn't melted in the sun.
And the cotter pins, well, they just...
Yeah.
Well, he always had those around the house.
Just jars of them.
Well, we don't...
I don't know what the deal is.
I don't know what the deal is with that, but that's how you know you've just missed
Bob.
He's just been there.
And believe me, friends, that's the best way to know Bob.
Is be right on his tail, but don't catch up with him.
No.
Because his slack has to come from somewhere.
Now, where do you think it comes from, my friend?
He's the vortex, the whirlpool.
He sucks it in.
You come close, and suddenly you're like one of those little nubs in the computer graphics
program that suddenly move together.
Like magnetic things that suddenly suck in.
And when it's over with, Bob's still there.
Where are you, my friend?
Yeah.
I was hitchhiking once with Dr. Ahmed Fishmonger years ago.
Again, I'm going back to the 80s here.
And we were in this horrible little median strip in the middle of Chicago.
Where four freeways merged.
It was a terrifying little spot that nobody could really slow down in.
But some completely tripping trucker had dropped us off there.
And so we're...
We're standing in this little triangle with our thumbs out and our signs.
And the traffic is whipping by.
And we're just kind of terrified.
And we see a car.
It's this...
I forget what it was.
It was a really nice Detroit car coming by.
And you could see from far away that it didn't have wheels.
There were no wheels in the car staying.
And I don't know if I've ever told you this.
Yeah, you did.
Yeah.
And it went right by us.
And just as he started to approach, he took the pipe out of his mouth, smiled, waved,
put the pipe back in his mouth, still smiling, and drove past us.
And it was Bob.
And we were so glad he didn't pick us up.
Philo and I had a real similar...
That was the only car that passed us that we weren't glad that picked us up.
Philo and I have had similar experiences where we saw Bob drive by.
That's it.
Yeah.
It's like he's just letting you know that he's there.
Yep.
He's not really watching.
I wouldn't want to ride him, I think.
He's just there.
At least I...
I don't know if I'm ready for...
I'd ever be ready for a ride from Bob.
I used to...
I had a nightmare once where I went to the door...
The doorbell rang in the wee hours of the morning, which is creepy.
And I went to the door and standing there was J.R. Bob Dobbs.
But in the dream, I knew it wasn't really him.
It was something making me see Bob.
And that was a really...
That was a real nightmare that I woke up sweating.
Now, we know from alien abductions that if you think it's a dream, that's just what they
want you to think.
They always set it up to where it's real dream-like, where you wake up in bed going,
I've been abducted.
Oh, no, I just had a dream.
One of the last things they say is, this was a dream.
Oh, but they always do it that way.
See?
They hide it in plain sight.
You must drink the nectar of forgetfulness.
That's how the conspiracy works.
They hide every...
It's all so obvious.
They don't even have to hide it.
What makes...
What amuses me is these nuts that get stuck on one tiny aspect of the conspiracy like
the Masons.
And they found these secrets that were hidden.
And they're not even really hidden.
They just weren't commonly known because nobody gives a hoot.
But to the kook mind, the connections all add up to a deliberate conspiracy of, the
Masons don't have anything exciting enough to hide.
Believe me.
The secret of the universe is...
The ones that do have something worth, a secret worth hiding, you don't know about
because you ain't J.R. Bob Dobbs.
And you aren't, you never made it to the top rungs of the conspiracy ladder before, rebelling.
Nor have I.
So I'm just taking his word for it, I suppose.
The secret is...
But then we have to assume quite a bit these days now, don't we?
We have to assume that this is some sort of planet Earth, which we've lately found out
is not so at all.
We have to assume that this year is 2007, even though by obvious, it was obvious this
morning at 7 a.m. that this could not be the year 2007.
Why is Danny Elfman hollering in the background?
He's always doing that.
Have you heard his instrumental orchestral symphony thing?
No.
He has a new symphony.
I bet it all sounds like Batman.
And here's another weird publication.
Starwood 27 Tour Guide.
This is as good for laughs as the Weekly World News.
And it's about as accurate, actually, if you try to stick by the schedule.
But traditionally, I love to go through the...
Before we start making fun of the subgeniuses, we have to make...
The pagans actually pay us to make fun of them.
Christians don't pay us to make fun of them.
Scientologists don't pay us to make fun of them.
I have a feeling the Amish might.
I met a guy who's called the Amish comic, a traveling stand-up comic who's an Amish dude.
I wish I could tell you something funny about him, but he was just an Amish guy.
But I'd love to go through this, and I'm not putting anybody down at all.
I did that already.
Years 10, 15 years ago, I wrote a book called...
High Weirdness by Mail, where I was snidely made fun of all the Wiccans and Scientologists and subgeniuses and so forth.
And the funny thing is...
And this is my 17th Starwood.
Despite that book, they invited me to speak at Starwood, and I'm about to be good friends with almost everybody I made fun of.
Now, if only I could improve my own self-image, then we'd be friends with everybody.
I'm...
But...
Now, talk!
Talk about bad scheduling.
On the same day, this was on Wednesday, at the same time, these two workshops, Feng Shui and Natural Campsite,
that was at the same time as Wilderness Survival Part One.
It seems like you'd have to go to both.
How can you do Wilderness Survival if you don't have the proper Feng Shui in your survival campsite?
You could starve to death.
I like the name here, Afro-Belly-Hip...
Hippie Hop.
I don't know what that means, it just sounds good.
Afro-Belly-Hippie Hop.
Elspeth did one that was...
It had a very subgenius-like title, about...
That sort of relates to Slack.
I don't know what I want, but this isn't it.
Someone was teaching, learn to spin.
And I thought that that's kind of...
shameful, teaching children how to get high.
Like, encouraging little children. They do that already.
Someone had a class called, Are You Full of Poo?
Now that's what I call a loaded question.
Sorry, I had to do that one.
Flute Salad, that's a nice one.
Floydtronica.
Serpent and Reptile Magic.
Now that's the kind of thing that makes the fundamentalist Christians in Sherman think that we're devil worshipers.
And I noticed a whole lot of workshops about fairies and something about the land of Faerie or something.
I'm very ignorant about that, I'm going to have to Wikipedia it.
I'm more familiar with the world of Bigfoot.
And Yetis, which I think is maybe the opposite of the fairies, I don't know.
But somebody should do a workshop about the challenges of intermarriage.
Between Yetis and fairies.
That's like Chihuahuas and Great Danes.
It puts a weird picture in your head.
Hawks smelly and good for you.
That's not explained, but I figured it was about medical marijuana.
And right underneath that, annual high faerie tea and pot luck.
Which didn't bother me especially until I realized that the person teaching it is my next door neighbor.
Seriously.
Buffing and polishing your craft.
Is that what they're calling it now?
Partner stress.
Stretching.
Is that what they're calling it now?
And I guess our friend Ron Slabe is going to be doing pyroglyphics.
That'll be the big fire and explosives show over there.
We do have insurance, by the way.
And I guess pyroglyphics, he's going to be writing slogans in flames on all of Brushwood.
That should be seen from a plane if you can do it.
The Land of the Blind concert.
That's tonight.
I'll be king for a day at that one.
Oh, and Erotic World of Faerie.
But they left out Erotic World of Bigfoot.
Prejudice against the subgeniuses, friends.
I'm ready for the loan-ger.
Ready for him.
Loan-ger.
The loan-ger.
Come on, be quiet.
For a moment, the loan-ger made no reaction.
He replied.
His eyes burned with murder lust.
Answer me!
Shut up.
Me going to shack.
Then me show you loan-ger.
Then me come.
Why?
It easy.
No, no, no, wait.
Me not, I not my way.
You mean you want a loan-ger?
Me, oh, go to shack.
Me promise show you loan-ger.
Then me come.
All right, go ahead.
But make it fast.
Me not take law.
Then came a sound that removed all doubt.
The loan-ger blanked out.
His eyes moved soundlessly, and his lips had the look of a madman.
The loan-ger came from several directions.
Broderick was hit in the shoulder.
The loan-ger.
The last I saw him, he disappeared behind a tree.
some brushwood.
The loner changed his appearance
by hollow plugs in his nostrils.
And I'll take care of the loner.
The loner, wearing a disguise
with tense and alert,
his cock came into view.
His voice was husky with emotion when he spoke.
Me loner.
I never suspected
he was the loner.
I don't know.
Look, my forward skip won't work.
Whoa!
And now,
the most important revelation
of 2007
or any year.
Yes, friends,
a new quote from Bob.
If you weren't here at 7 in the morning,
heed.
There are four new
transmissions passed down
from J.R. Bob Dobbs.
Never before heard until now.
The first one,
Bob said,
so many look but don't see.
And most don't even look.
They just use their eyes
to keep from bumping into things.
This is the Tom fuckery
of foolishness.
And that was the end of that.
Take right there.
Isn't that amazing?
And that was the Tom fuckery
of foolishness.
The subgenius must have tape.
Now, on another
on another occasion,
Bob handed down this,
his first comment
on the subgenius internet.
It's a comment about
the subgenius internet.
Alt.slack is the Cleveland,
of the internet.
You gotta be tough.
I'm surprised that Bob
even was aware of alt.slack.
Honest.
And oh,
the third quote
from Bob.
No need to watch
spilt milk burn.
You just think about that,
my friends. I did and it,
I learned nothing.
The, the final thing
is that it was,
it's not really from Bob,
but it was about Bob.
We've learned that in American
sign language,
Bob's name is spelled
in this mystic hand pass.
B-O-B-H.
You can throw in the huh.
Did I do that right?
B-O-B-H.
Now see, you can tell they're shitty cultists
because they're not even attempting to image.
There's one guy back there in Princess Wee.
And she already, she's the one who taught it to us.
Oh, and Barbara Alien.
She's a good sport.
B-O-B-H.
That's right, everybody, come on.
Now Dr. Dark is adding the quotes,
the little devil horns that go on either end.
And that does make it sound like a good thing.
It's sacred.
So I guess you could go, huh.
B-O-B-H.
Yeah, that's the uh.
That's more cultish.
That's the uh.
Well, think about in Close Encounters of the Third Kind.
There was this whole field full of Indians going, ah, eh, eh, oh, eh.
And still making some little hand motion.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, it was very impressive.
Now, we don't have that field of subgeniuses.
We have to see that film again because they may have been doing B-O-B.
I don't think they were.
No?
No, I think I would have remembered.
I don't remember.
Now here's another one.
Yeah, without the quotes it's not real.
Because you overslept the saucer's arrival like so many.
X-day in American Sign Language.
It turns out the X is the same symbol as a huh or a question mark.
It's a question mark or huh or an X.
A day is like that.
Sun going across the sky.
So X-day is just simply like that.
You can walk up to people.
In the Sherman supermarket tomorrow when you're going to walk up to Amish people and just
go huh, huh, huh, huh, huh, huh, huh, huh, huh, huh, huh, huh, huh, and see what happens.
You know, maybe you'll recruit some Amish people for the church.
They're surprisingly, they're real friendly folks.
We have a lot in common with the Amish.
Everybody else thinks they're nuts.
And they think everybody else is full of it.
In fact, they call us.
They call us the English.
Did you know that?
Anyone who's not Amish is English.
So we're all English on this bus, you might say.
Some more English than others, I suppose.
So.
I was sad that I didn't meet any subgeniuses in England.
Is that a new one?
Oh, there's a lot of them.
Oh, and the other thing.
This is the other thing we announced.
Was that this morning?
It was X.
No, that was yesterday morning.
It's just one day, man.
It is.
X day is like Brigadoon.
It's just one day that keeps repeating every hundred years.
We got a membership.
We get about three or four ordainment orders a day these days.
And on June 28th, while I was at my daughter's wedding,
we got an order from Robert Dobbs in Beaufort, South Carolina.
Not Robert R. Dobbs or anything like that.
No, James Robert.
The JR, by the way, just is a JR.
It doesn't stand for anything.
And Bob is on his birth certificate.
But this is a Robert Dobbs, a person who happens to be named Bob Dobbs.
And I doubt if it's him because it says Robert M.
What is JR?
Does JR have a middle name after Bob?
No, it doesn't.
It doesn't stand for anything.
No.
No, a lot of people that have the cutesy idea,
oh, it must mean Jesus Robert or something.
Or no, no.
It's just J.R. quote, B.O.B. unquote Dobbs on his birth certificate.
Because his dad was not a real sophisticated fellow.
He was a pharmacist, but he was an immigrant.
And he thought he had had a boss who had a nameplate with a quote in the middle.
And he thought that was a sign of success.
Right.
You know, J.B. Tiny, Osmond, or whatever.
Well, the name you are injects you with success or not, you know, depending upon the name.
Like someone named, you know, Percival will have a hard time, perhaps, because, you know,
he'd be Percy and no one's named Percy now.
Oh, but that's just what can turn you into a subgenius.
Yes, exactly.
That having a funny name.
Yep.
It might be enough to awaken that Yeti gene.
On the other hand, it might be enough to make you sort of autistic almost, kind of depends
on how it all comes along.
It comes down the pike.
They made fun of me in kindergarten because my name was Bleepo.
Yeah, imagine that.
Bleepo is probably what turned you into a subgenius.
Yeah, I think so.
I think it really was.
I would have been one of the ones picking on you, too.
Well, by the time I was in first grade, I was like, you know, really, I figured it out.
I had it all together.
But then when I was 13, I lost it, but then I got it back again.
I don't want to talk about what made me different.
Yeah.
I did that once out here, and I never should have.
It's been following me around.
Yeah.
People can't handle it.
Oh, there it is.
Oh, yeah.
I just saw it.
It was right there.
Let's see.
I knew it was around here somewhere, man.
Don't worry, man.
I wish it would stay further away.
Oh, wait.
We have another gorilla.
Oh, another gorilla.
Great.
Now, this one's all sound effects.
It's Reverend Emperor Delirious.
Okay, here's what the gorilla says.
Yeah.
.
That's the gorilla.
The devil says, hey, gorilla, stop eating the urine-stained gravel.
It isn't really albino candy corn.
.
I just lost...
Oh, there.
It's just my ears.
I'm sorry.
I thought the equipment was messed up.
Here's another gorilla.
Oh, can I...
Oh, for use...
This is good.
It perfectly timed.
For use when show gets slow or retarded.
Perfect timing there, Lord Cyclohexane.
Oh, here.
You can do that one.
All right.
I'll try it.
.
Oh, my God.
I can't do this.
Don't poke me.
Oh, wait.
You gotta turn it down for this voice.
Sorry.
Don't poke me.
Sleeping.
Half awake always.
Wait for hate.
Wait to wake.
Wait for annoyance.
Sleep.
Want.
Roll over.
Back asleep.
Building.
Annoyance.
Hold it in.
Percolate in hate.
Wait for it.
for it. Fuck you!
What the fuck? Let me
goddamn sleep! Monkey smash!
Remove heart
to half awake, half
alive state. Fall
asleep. Walk
through life
never paying attention.
Sleep.
Wait.
Explode when
necessary.
Wow, that was great!
That was the best one ever.
Yeah!
Okay, here's the demon now.
Tar baby crawling through
asphyxiatic dreams. Lockstep
jackboot nicotine march through
narrowed veins. This is obviously
a heavy metal demon.
Green phlegm thrown from diseased
lungs starving for the sweet air.
Red blood cells craving
company of carbon's monoxide.
Shunning dioxide's euphoric
embrace. Ah!
The beauty!
Wow. And that's a quote from, apparently that's a quote from
Reflections from a Nicotine Demon.
Or maybe that just was...
I recognize that one. Yeah.
That was nice. I like that.
Good demons! Somebody must have quit smoking.
Anybody who's just arrived or hasn't
done this yet, we have these forms somewhere.
I hope still a couple of them. You fill
them out with your inner gorilla
and your inner demon and
the subgenus radio ministers will
you know, read it.
By the way,
Princess,
we are, though, there has been teaching,
has been learning American sign
language and she taught me how to spell
Bob and it's really easy.
This is a B
and this is an O
and that's a B, so you only need to know two things.
Uh, yeah.
Yeah.
B, O, B.
Or
you could do the quotes, which is like
a little devil horn.
Quote, B, O,
B, quote.
Quote, B,
O, B, quote.
You guys are such
better cultists than
the subgeniuses.
I am not kidding. I could not get
any of them. They couldn't even remember
the third B.
And you notice I have trouble with it.
Why do you think we call it subgenius?
I get to say that once a week
and that was my weekly
utterance of that.
Well, that was certainly something.
Yes, it should be Dr. Jam
and weird images
and, uh,
you know, we can always sit around and watch movies of
Last X Day. That's true.
That's actually what happens
if it rains, if the
prophesied thunderstorm,
which has not really shown up yet.
You may think you saw the rain,
but the real Brushwood rain,
hasn't happened yet.
It surely must. You'll know when it happens
because you won't be able to see.
It's that
sudden. It's a
biblical flood
that happens for about two hours.
It's got to happen.
But when that happens, that's when we go to
the studio up at the top of the hill.
The Heavenly Studio, which is
indoors.
Where we set up the video
projector and watch the sunny
parts of X Day.
So,
we're prepared for every eventuality.
This is PR.
PR.
Advancing public well-being through improved
communication.
Helping to develop PR's fun.
From PR News in Washington, I'm detained.
The US government continued to exert every effort
to channel assistance to Saddam Hussein,
even with evidence that he was not only promoting
terrorism, but was also
pursuing a nuclear war.
The US government has been
nuclear weapons program.
A senior US diplomat says this is PR news.
Some six pounds of fresh and frozen ground beef
have been recalled after officials suspected
Bob contaminated some of the meat.
When it comes to bad meat,
it's all voluntary.
PR comes from contaminated meat.
Under the penis jar.
Yes.
Yes, but we need more forms.
There's at least a couple that we haven't received yet.
That's for sure.
Speaking of forms, I need to prepare the Ask Dr.
Howell questionnaire forms.
Oh, yes.
And my equipment is back at the swag shack.
So I'm going to ask somebody else to sit up here at the mic.
What happened to young Alex?
Alex, why don't you come up here?
Howell is waiting to come back up.
No, I didn't.
We're going to do Ask Dr. Howell in a little while,
and we have to have the question snippet thingies.
Which I go, ah, ah.
I can make things like that.
Yeah, but the scissors are back up there.
I have scissors here.
You just sit there.
The Reverend Alex walks up to the mic.
I should say the Saint Alex.
That's right.
The reason I started calling myself a saint is actually due to Reverend Stang,
because the very first year that I ranted,
afterwards he yelled,
praise God.
He said, praise Saint Alex.
And at the time, you know, I figured I was youth and Bob.
I didn't really have the wherewithal to be a saint at that point in my life.
So I gave it a few years,
and now I'm ready to embrace what it is to be a subgenius saint.
And that is a lucky thing for me because actually you live under my roof now.
That is correct.
We are roof dwellers.
We live under a roof.
It's not really an apartment.
It's just this little sort of subsection under a roof in Brooklyn.
Above a flower shop.
It's I think the highest point in the whole place.
It's about three and a half feet high.
But it's really colorfully decorated.
It is.
It's beautifully decorated with wild psychedelic streaks of color.
And that was almost entirely done by Professor Ali Valkyrie.
Is that correct?
Yes, yes.
Professor Ali Valkyrie also shares the dwelling.
And it's a nonstop, well, you'd have to see it anyway.
You really would because it's a marvelous thing.
If there are ever any photos taken of the apartment, then, you know.
But, you know.
I'm still working on my sainthood.
Well, yeah.
But you've enough titles for now.
Because in addition to being a rock star, you're a real saint.
You're a reverend.
And a doctor.
You were also radio pope of the northeast.
Yeah, but I don't like that.
You know, I don't like, yeah, look at me, radio pope.
You know, I don't like doing that.
Some popes do that.
I just, you know, I like to keep it under my sleeve.
And, you know, I pull it out when I need it.
That's basically it.
But I was mentioning earlier that, you know, even older subgeni tend to forget that the masthead of the Book of the Subgenius includes your surname listed on the back of the book.
And it's listed first and foremost among the radio popes is radio pope Cates.
Oh, you know.
The very first.
Some call that my surname.
Some.
Some would call, some would call that your surname.
Some would call Abernathy your surname.
I like to call it my master name.
Yes.
But, you know, sir, master.
It's all just, you know, nomenclature S and M really is what it boils down to.
That's right.
So, you know, we're slaves to our names.
We are slaves to our names.
Which is why it's important to reinvent our names as subgeniuses, I think, sometimes.
That's right.
So that we can become slaves to Bob.
Yeah.
Through our new names.
We can learn more about the name of Bob.
Yeah.
Which is the purest name.
Which, as you may remember, is B-O-B.
B.
Oh, but of course.
Yes, that's right.
Uh.
Yeah.
You can, I don't know if, since the uhs are double, you can do them either before or after.
We have to establish how that goes.
I don't know.
I don't know how that would go.
But that does seem to be the running theme of this year's X-Day, just a uh.
I think before and after.
Before, okay.
Okay.
Uh.
B-O-B.
Okay.
So remember that.
You can go up to people in grocery stores and just start doing that and they'll, they
will just follow you around.
Mm-hmm.
You know, that's what I, that's what I, that's what I love about Bob is, is that everybody
understands Bob.
That's right.
This is how we get him into the literature.
Well, that's, no, actually that's just something of a misnomer because not everyone
Okay.
Understands Bob.
I was just trying to sell it.
It was just bullshit I was saying.
That was bullshit, but that's okay because.
I was trying to sell it, you know, because I, I've been selling things for a long time
so.
I understand.
If I say a selling line sometimes don't people see it.
Everybody understands it.
That's always a good selling line.
Yeah.
Because people want to.
Yeah, you want this.
Come on everybody.
Everybody understands it.
Everybody, everybody understands it.
Don't you want to be like everybody who understands it?
Of course there's the legend of this.
The Brushwood Demon.
The Brushwood Demon has been known to haunt these parts for nigh on 40 years.
And he, he eats only the jello that's left in the wake of dawn.
Yeah.
And he files away the cotter pins and makes, makes little, little dresses.
Or so it's said.
Or some would say.
Yep.
Yes.
If you can find those cotter pins and the jello, well you set them out in a trap.
You might be able to just trap yourself a Brushwood Demon.
That's right.
They call him the Brushwood Demon.
But then what you do with it when you're done, well.
That's your own business.
The Brushwood Demon speaks the truth.
Indeed.
Whether you like it or not.
Yeah.
You know.
He's kind of like, he's kind of like the, the Brushwood version of Apollonius of Tyana.
He'll tell you what you want to, or he'll tell you the truth even if it's not necessarily.
What you want to hear.
That's why he, that's how he earned the moniker of Demon.
Because people became so irate that he was, you know, accurately predicting their, their,
in divining their futures.
Oh you Demon.
You Brushwood Demon.
Forsooth.
What is Sooth anyway?
I don't know what Sooth is.
I'm stuck in the voice of Walter Brennan.
That's my son, Will Sonnet.
You know where he is, don't you?
Yeah.
All right.
Now I'm over it now.
Okay.
That only lasted like a minute.
But that's okay.
Usually does.
Walter Brennan comes and goes.
You know.
He just.
Yeah.
He comes into your life.
He was like a completely racist asshole.
Yeah.
He was.
Apparently.
Walter Brennan was a very racist man, which I was quite surprised to discover.
He didn't like, he didn't like Jews and he didn't like black people.
No, no he didn't.
And he was necessarily.
He always used those names for the movie.
But you know, Bob likes Jews and Bob likes black people.
Exactly.
And you know, and they're used.
A tape.
Oh, uh oh.
Or something here.
You.
I don't know.
Is this a mini disc?
Only .
So, uh.
I don't know.
I'm not sure.
Make your own radio show for a minute or two, everybody.
Where's Sven?
Where'd he go?
What's going on?
Well, the.
The.
Hello.
We're off the air.
And we can't talk on the microphones unless we're on the air.
Fine.
Yep.
.
Being an AV boy, I have some understanding of some of the things that
does with these things.
.
So, one moment please while we.
Oh.
Doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo
Do-doo-doo, do-doo-doo-doo, do-doo-doo-doo, do-doo-doo-doo, do-doo-doo-doo, do-doo-doo-doo-doo-doo.
Liza.
Any more, girl?
Question.
Any more question?
I see out there there's a place called Dobbstown.
How can I get there?
Dobbstown.
Remember Jonestown?
Jim Jones and Guyana had this great club of,
well, they were kind of over-anxious sub-genius.
It's like Heaven's Gate.
They didn't feel like waiting around for the bus.
They had to jump right in front of it.
Dobbstown is hidden, is deep in the jungles of Malaysia.
It's actually in disputed territory.
It's pretty hard to get there.
First, you have to join the church with that $30
and learn to chant Bob Slack, Bob Slack,
and become a real stupid fundamentalist Bobby for a while
where you quote all of our slogans
like a tiresome Monty Python fan that never shuts up, you know?
Or whatever fan.
I'm not going to put down Monty Python.
I know people that do that with Firesign Theater and sub-genius.
Alistair Crowley, any of those comedy outfits.
But then you go to Dobbstown and the overmen deprogram you.
And it hurts.
And you can't sit down for a year.
But it's worth it.
Because the true Slack comes when the hammer stops hitting your head.
You know what I mean?
Really, everybody has original Slack.
You're already in Dobbstown.
You're floating in a sea of the good pills.
But you don't really appreciate.
You don't really appreciate it until it's taken away.
The day that you can't sleep.
The day that you have nothing to eat.
The day that you truly can't pee.
That's when you'll know how much Slack you always had, my friend.
Thank you.
This is an open stage.
If you have a rant, you should be right here.
When I say open stage, there's nothing that indicates that you will have an audience later.
If you must have an audience, this is your best bet right now.
Thank you.
So we've got 15 more minutes.
Are there any questions?
This is my favorite part.
Sure.
Yeah.
I'm pretty sure that next week is coming.
And I've got to make some decisions about what to do.
And I can either go to the beach and pee town with some friends.
Or maybe have a glass of wine with my neighbor.
Or do something.
And I don't know.
How do I decide relative amounts of Slack?
If I'm looking for some Slack, how do I decide what to do next week?
You really need to spend that $30.
I can tell by your indecisiveness that you need to limit your options.
And if you're $30 lighter, you're going to take whichever one is cheaper.
And either one is going to give you as much Slack.
And this way you'd be spreading the Slack you see.
So, you know, the other thing you can do is flip a coin and let Bob decide.
Okay.
Speaking of which, suicide.
Not a good idea.
Number one, the reason you're doing it is because you're such a miserable failure and everything is so screwed up, right?
Well, killing yourself is just another one of your dumb mistakes.
Bob or God is going to get around to killing you anyway, sooner or later.
Do you really think you're going to do a better job than Bob?
So, you know.
All you have to do is wait until X day.
It's not like you're going to have to suffer forever.
Put up with it a little while longer.
Maybe you don't really know the future.
Maybe everything isn't going to be completely screwed up forever.
Maybe that person you're madly in love with is suddenly, for some reason, going to suddenly be divorced.
And it turned out that you're the one they were interested in.
You don't know.
That was the message of 1998.
We all quit making predictions when the saucers didn't show.
The End
Music
Here it comes
He's coming, bud
Go come on
Go come and take your slack away
He's back
Here it comes
Slack
He's coming to take your slack away
He'll take it too
That big bad bob
Heaven in the sky
That's right, just send us your one dollar
One dollar
You get a lot more for your money
Heck, one dollar
You get bob
Think of bob
Yeah, think of bob
Think about bob
Yeah, he makes us
Think of
Bob
Everybody's
Think about bob
Everybody wants to
Think of bob
Yeah
Well, I'll
Think of
Bob
We'll
Think of
Bob
Yeah, we'll
Think of
Bob
Everybody's
Think of
Bob
Now to continue our story
After Bob left
He dashed into the
Lawn-ger
The lawn-ger returned to
Camp by a roundabout route
At top speed
And without being seen by
Bob's dark exhausted horse
Bob made slow time
On his first full familiar
Little silenced bell
Just
Go ahead, Bob
And see how things work out
You
Great Scott the Lord
Here
In time
I'll let you go on
Just a minute, Bob
You propose to make an example
Of that young scamp
Bob stole money
I'll hear, Bob
He knows it, Tonto
Bob
Here
What do you want me to do with Bob?
Got to think of some way
To send Bob to jail
You think
You'll refine Bob guilty?
Maybe
The lawn-ger kept a close watch
On Bob in town
The lawn-ger found a small hill
On which they could watch Bob
And if Bob stole all the money
That was stolen
Doesn't Bob mean something?
Not a chance
Well, maybe
If Bob was on the scene
Bob's identified, Bob.
He'll go to jail for life.
Uh-oh.
Bob.
Oh, Bob.
I'll hear Bob.
Talk to me, Bob.
Tell me about the tears on poor, hungry faces.
Bob's gonna die.
Oh, that's good, Bob.
Oh, Bob.
Tell me again.
She's gonna die.
Tell us of you, wasn't it, Bob?
What's it to you?
Bob.
Oh, Bob.
Dead says they're sure to find you guilty.
Oh, doggone.
Gone.
Oh, here comes Dad now.
Now, don't recall, Ted.
Dad, what's the matter?
Hey.
I got Bob.
Yeah.
Oh, but there must be something I do.
There's something I do, Dad.
So I see.
Bob surrenders day after tomorrow.
I can just see the tears on poor, hungry faces.
They're coming from all sides.
Yeah.
Thanks to the loan, Jack.
I'm dead.
Now back to the show.
Thank you, Bob.
We'll be right back, Jayden.
As always, I'm playing with a Folge 10 of the
Understanding There's Askiulture With Honour
with Des Federer My Pooey
Ho occasional
I encountered
a guy
major
And Carter LeBlanc, ranting about ranting.
Over five-fisted, Tales of Connie, the X-Day Jam Band.
Matthew Dare doing music in the background right now is the Amino Acids live at 10X Day.
And the killer music that you're about to hear is Bonobo's Convergence live at 10X Day.
Bonobo's Convergence live at 10X Day.
An ordinary can be just another one, another one
Freaking with a smile on, is that nothing special?
Going on
An ordinary can be just another one, another one
Freaking with a smile on, is that nothing special?
Going on
Thank you everyone! Thank you Reverend Stank, thank you Princess Wee, thank you Dr. Howe, thank you Lonesome Cowboy Dave, thank you everyone! We love it here! Thank you very much!
We have Bonobos Convergence! Thank you! Have a wonderful, wonderful, stay cool for the amino acids!
Stay cool for the amino acids!
Praise Bob and thanks to Bonobos Convergence heard live at X-Day
Thanks to Potter Nostril for the recording and also of the amino acids in the background
More can be had about Bonobos Convergence at bonobosmusic.com
This is our Slack number 1113 or 14 or something like that from the Church of the Subgenius
For more on the subgenius morons, see subgenius.com
And now, Glass Madness and other old-timey doctors take us away
Oh wowee!
We shall verse a genius
We shall qualify
He's something, saying something over there, way over on that other channel
We can't see left, can't hear anything
You notice that our patient is strapped in, he cannot see the two-way mirror
Nor can he hear our instructions, ladies and gentlemen
So you will be with us on this experiment in green brain
In private
Okay, now we have his brain here, which we've taken out in a hologram
I have worn it
It looks much like it does inside his head right now
We're going to put it in the Vegematic
You'll notice a lot of static, a lot of static blur
The Brain-O-Matic pulverizes into a breezy bulb in just two seconds
Now be careful, don't heat that brain up too much because, uh,
We've lost a lot of memories that way
Perhaps we want to turn it down then
When you put it back, it just isn't the same
The last I saw of him, he disappeared behind some brushwoods
Brushwoods, brushwoods, brushwoods, brushwoods, brushwoods, brushwoods