Tonight, radio's distinguished series dedicated to man's imagination.
The Soul Genius Power of Swag.
It's our way of acknowledging our American heroes.
That's what you say.
We say you could act like a jackrabbit.
With frazzled nerves and a heart pounding like a trip hammer.
You gotta keep jumping. You gotta keep punching.
Punch. Punch. Punch that grandfather.
Ugh.
The victim can stand only so much abuse.
Too many people die because they couldn't live.
Grandfather's journey is ending.
He swam from the Pacific Ocean all the way up to Mount Fuji.
That's impossible, isn't it?
This is beyond our present knowledge or understanding.
Bob? Bob? Bob?
Good evening, Bob.
Where are you going tonight, Bob?
Who will you be with tonight, Bob?
Where will I find you if I need you, Bob?
And there's a joint in it.
That's good.
Do you know a Bob?
Oh, yes.
Yes.
Hurry, Michael.
Bob's cool. He takes special interest in Bob.
Bob's sensitive.
Very crabber.
Bob smashed people.
Bob.
Look here, what's this all about?
You come.
What?
You come this way, please.
No. No.
Oh, yes.
No, no. I...
You are coming.
Oh, oh.
Oh.
You come.
It has been my observation that when a lady starts banging some man...
It's sore.
Hard.
I see.
Very sore.
Swollen.
You have to shoot.
Oh.
Helps drain all cavities.
Such strange jokes.
Thank you, Lemur.
And this is not a rerun.
We have some jolly stuff at first.
Then it'll get somber because I have yet more...
Subgenius obituaries.
Then it'll get scary.
But then hopefully we'll have a call-in from Dr. Philo Drummond,
overman first degree,
co-sub-founder of the Subgenius Foundation and Bob's good buddy.
But first, well, this piece of music is a mystery to me.
The file title was Shadow Men,
and I presume that's the band.
And the file also had the call letter CK,
which is or was a small Toronto college station
that once had this show on every week.
Shadow Men.
¡C Gotcha!
I love you.
¡C GRACIAS POR PUMPAR!
¶¶
Whoa.
Hi, man.
Hi, you old scutter.
My family has left for the day.
They've gone to get their hairs cut.
And I always thought it was funny they call it a haircut, you know, instead of a hair's cut.
Yeah, so if you're only going to have one special haircut.
Or like you had just one big shaft of hair sticking out of the top of your head.
Boy, that would be so.
Like six or seven inches in diameter.
Right.
And, you know, it'd look like a horn.
It would end up looking like a big old horn, a hair horn, like a rhino.
It would be a lot easier to keep clean, you would think.
If you don't hear me talking.
It's because I'm propping.
Okay.
I'm trying not to waste time.
I was thinking about going to get a beer.
You should.
I can't hear.
Well, hold on.
I'm thinking about passing gas.
You can just blather.
The recorder is still on.
I'm thinking about passing gas.
Oops, I don't even have to think about it anymore.
It's actually manifested itself into reality.
And as a result.
I got to walk away for a minute.
Yeah.
This is the time.
This is the time that all men must enter their adulthood and take hold of the beer bear.
Beer bear.
A beer bear.
And wrangle that guy back into control.
Get that beer bear up with his beer belly.
All right.
Wow.
What's that?
So.
So, okay, Dr. Drummond.
I've got my.
I want you to fetch me a Lagunitas.
And.
Okay.
I've got me a Frappanitas.
What is that noise in the background?
Sounds like you're dragging a coffin across a concrete floor.
I was just dragging a coffin across a concrete floor.
Oh, okay.
That was a good guess on my part.
Yeah, very good.
Very good.
See, that's exactly.
Exactly what it sounds like.
Yeah.
To have drawn a carpet of concrete often across a carpeted floor.
It's heavy.
Oh, I had it backwards.
Anyway.
But we got.
So now it's the hour of slack number 1889.
Wow.
And I can't believe it.
That's.
That's a.
That's definitely a milestone.
A milestone.
A magnificent proportion.
Huge.
Well.
Yeah.
Who else has done almost 2000 subgenius radio shows?
Well, puzzling evidence has been on since 1982 and still is.
And our slack started in October 1985.
Wow.
Yeah.
So it's been.
It's been.
I don't want to think about the math.
It's how jealous we were when Doug Wellman had his own radio show and he was doing stuff
and sending his tapes.
Man, we had to do that.
It's amazing how competitive we were back then with our friends.
Well, yeah.
But once once I finally got a show.
I played a whole lot of their their show, you know.
Yeah.
Because.
Oh, yeah.
It was so, so great.
The parts that you could hear were really great.
Then there were the other parts.
Yeah.
That you no one would want to hear.
Except puzzling evidence in headphones.
Right.
Well, I wanted to hear them.
You know, I like to hear all the bad and the good.
The good and the bad.
That's very.
Noble.
Yeah.
Noble of me.
I like that.
Well, OK.
To listeners who don't know anything, we're the two original cool guys that Bob first
recruited.
And we we we allow a small group of other almost as cool guys to hang out.
We shouldn't talk that way.
They get real mad when we do that.
You better cut this part out of the show.
That's right.
But it's true, though.
There's the handsome and mature.
Gents are few and far between.
But we're especially lead squad of subgenius hierarchites.
Right.
Yeah.
We make big decisions in the background.
So, OK.
OK.
Onan sent me this letter.
And when he wants to tell me something real, I mean, we talk all the time and text and
stuff.
But when he wants me to take something real seriously, he'll actually send it by mail.
You know, I was dragging my feet.
I'm getting that agent and Mr. Dobbs book out, which bothered him because he had actually
done all the layout and work himself.
Yeah.
And he's waiting for you to put your imprimatur on it.
Your imprimatur.
I got this immensely heavy box in the mail that probably cost 50 bucks to mail from him.
And inside was a brick with the word agent and Mr. Dobbs written in charcoal on it.
And basically, I had to carry that brick around until I got that job done.
And we did get the hardcover.
We got the $50 hardcover edition is out and all sold out.
And then I dragged my feet on the paperback.
But by the time people hear this tonight, I'll have that purchase button on subgenius.com
in the book section.
And people can buy the agent and Mr. Dobbs, which is hilarious.
It is hilarious.
Yes.
I've got my actually have my copy here.
Yeah.
Right here in front of me.
It's very much like a cross between H.P.
Lovecraft and the Three Stooges.
Yeah.
Right.
It is.
And that could be done.
That could be done.
It captures what does it.
It captures the essence of Bob better than just about anything else.
Anybody's done, including me.
It's amazing.
Yeah.
People would be, you know, if they I could just say that, you know, that that particular
line about any H.P.
Lovecraft fan or and any three Stooges fan, you don't have to be both.
You could just be one or the other and still find this to be a very interesting and revealing,
if not enlightening book.
Yeah.
Mainly, it's just really funny.
Yeah, it's funny.
You know, here's here's the weird thing.
I have not heard back from Teeters Laverge since I sent him the first copies of the hardcover.
Maybe he got drunk in celebration and is still celebrating.
Well, another thing.
He was still on Facebook, but he was talking about Ukraine.
I think he's, you know, from a Ukrainian background.
Oh, despite the name fighter Laverge.
Yeah, right.
I don't know.
You know, it could be.
But it could be that Laverge may be a subgenius name.
It may not be actually a birth name.
Teeters Laverge.
It might not be his conspiracy name.
He might have some real dull name like.
Yeah.
Bill Smith or.
No, it's going to be.
It's going to be a Ukrainian name.
It's going to be like, you know, Vladimir Shmugmoid or whatever they have over there.
Mm hmm.
OK, well, anyway, here's this letter that Onan sent and it's kind of the first page is pretty short.
Then there's a short story, a true story about P.T.
Barnum and Grizzly Adams.
Oh, but get this.
Please stop hour of slack.
Please stop at any day at any time unannounced or no.
Stop.
Lots of work.
Lots of time.
Little pay.
Much complaining.
And, you know, you guys and my wife hear the complaining.
In fact, Princess Wee said that I'd been complaining about having to do this stupid show as long as she knew me, which was 1990 or something.
Anyway, Onan says, you won.
You outlasted most paid career DJs.
And it's true.
Hour of Slack has been on longer than than Johnny Carson or what's his name?
Or we ought to work on like a Wikipedia page just for our slack.
Well, there is there is one book, a groundbreaking show that lasted longer than everything else.
You know, yeah, but all the ground was totally broken afterwards.
It's completely broken.
Yes.
Soft.
It's completely soft and mushy now.
Can't even.
You can't repair it.
You can't.
You can't grow anything in it.
No.
Anyway, he says, free up that complaining for something else.
Permission granted.
The listeners don't know this, but I really I really do complain because it's a routine.
It's not just.
There's all this other stuff I have to do that a nutless chimpanzee could do my job.
If only I could train him to read numbers.
He says.
He might.
He might need one.
He says every X day.
Oh, yeah.
That's not funny.
Dr.
Drummond.
Every X day and revival has a curtain.
Every book has a back cover.
And yet subgenius rolls on and you roll on.
I am specifically not saying to switch to any other anything.
Not web, not books, not dogs, not anything.
Just stop doing the one thing over and over as if there will be a different result.
Whatever it is, are you making it better or are you making it worse?
And, you know, I've been I've sort of been begging for permission to quit this weekly routine for a long time.
And, you know, let's face it.
There's 2000 shows that anybody can listen to any time, any time or play on their own station or podcast.
That's right.
I even call them up there.
They're retrievable.
They're like archived and all ready to go.
Anybody could even mechanize that process if they wanted to.
Actually, some stations did.
I think already.
But it's simple.
You know, it's like I'm I'm one hundred and sixty eight years old.
And I'm I'm everything's taken longer.
It takes you were that sacred scribe for that other religion before this one.
Why?
We don't talk about that.
But there's you know, there.
I'm still sacred scribe number two hundred and seventy three.
But there's there's going to be a number two hundred and seventy four.
Yeah.
And I think he's all I think he's all.
I think it's probably going to be.
Yeah, he's probably already.
I think he's like in his, you know, journeyman phase.
Yeah.
You know, he's more than an apprentice now.
He's actually graduated up almost to yeoman.
Well.
Right.
Well, he.
Well, and he's done his own.
He did the man of books and his own podcast and things.
He's done.
He actually at one point offered a man of letters.
He he offered to take over the show at one point.
But, you know, I don't want to do that.
It'd be it would be a different show.
Wouldn't be the hour.
Yeah, that's right.
And and we're not getting the contributions.
You know, there's no lemur.
We're not making out new stuff anymore.
Yeah.
That's all from the olden days.
So the content is, you know, the content is harder to come by and not just.
But that's not really.
It's not that.
And here's another thing.
I'm not an angry young man anymore.
Right.
I'm angry.
Old man.
Yeah.
Well, I'm angry at chronic diseases and and aches and pains and that kind of.
Who isn't angry at that, though?
I mean, that's everybody's anger.
You know.
No, not everybody.
Everybody.
It's chronic pain.
Believe me.
Not like you.
Hey, we remember a long time ago we needed units of measurement for things like pain
and slack and confusion.
Yeah.
And inebriation.
And the first we most immediately landed on drummonds of or was it phylos of slack and
phylos of slack and stangs of pain.
And that may have been a self-fulfilling prophecy.
Man, we should have been given.
We should have given old Stang some upside.
Well, there was Jane's of confusion.
And I think sternos of inebriation.
And I forget what some of the other ones were.
But I don't remember.
That may have all been cut from Revelation X.
Yeah.
Just think about all the stuff that got cut.
Well, that see, there's another whole half a book right there.
And I'd like to be scanning old things that were never published that happened before
the Internet.
But after we quit publishing because the postage cost too much and it was too hard.
And I always lost my shirt.
Yeah.
On this.
Do you remember what the Reverend Stang?
Do you remember when the Internet was just like seven guys with tape decks?
Yeah.
Right.
That was our Internet.
Yeah.
That was the only that was the only worthwhile.
Part of the Internet.
It was very slow and it was mostly audio, but it was mobile.
I mean, we would record.
We would talk to each other and do stuff.
And it was fun.
Really fun.
Yeah.
Well, but we all had we all had horrible real life jobs then.
And we needed that fun.
We had when we managed to take a break, we didn't waste it.
No kidding.
Whereas now we're kind of jaded in that respect.
And both of us have.
We have farming chores that we.
Yeah.
I got animals to feed and.
Right.
And crops to harvest.
Yeah.
It's.
I got.
I got some crops.
And the squash has been coming in.
Whoo.
Yeah.
I saw those pictures.
Dr. Drummond actually has a farm and with crops and because it rains and he has dirt.
Yeah.
I have a very big garden, but it's in pots because our dirt is not really.
It's.
Yeah.
I feel sorry for your dirt, man, because our dirt is so is just like you just plant.
You just put seeds in it and they grow.
Well, you put cactus seeds in this stuff and it'll grow and see.
Well, that's true.
Yeah.
But yeah, it's like you put it.
You said it.
Well, you said it was this land had an ornamental dusting of dirt.
Over a foundation of solid limestone.
Yeah.
That's what it is.
I was just.
That's just where the limestone got worn down a little bit and turned into dirt.
The limestone is all made of dead sea creatures.
Shell.
Yeah.
It actually is.
I mean, if you look at it real close.
In a lot of areas.
If you know what you're looking at, you're looking at ancient eroded seashells that were
piled up for billions and billions of years.
So.
Oh, here's.
Oh, here's the rest of this letter about the quit in the hour.
Yeah.
And, you know, I have.
I hate to admit it, but I have been thinking about it for about 25 years.
My first wife was so happy when I got kicked off K and she thought I would stop.
But I just kept making tapes and sending them to the other stations.
Anyway, here's.
Here's.
More in.
In Onan's excellent handwriting.
One day, a man made an appointment to see P.T.
Barnum at his American Museum.
The visitor was known to Barnum.
Grizzly Adams.
Mr. Adams was begging for a job.
Barnum put him to work wrestling bears.
After a time, Barnum asked Adams to come to his office and say how things were going.
Adams had taken the job to pay for his children's education.
So that they did not have to wrestle bears past retirement.
Adams appeared in Barnum's office but left his animal skin cap on.
Barnum said he was accustomed to men removing their hat in his office.
Adams removed his hat and so revealed a great wound on his head.
Adams explained a bear had bitten him, removing flesh and part of his skull.
But he didn't want to quit for his children.
Barnum wrote out a check.
He was asked to pay for his children's education and fired him on the spot.
Don't be Grizzly Adams.
So I think what Onan is saying is that, you know, I've been bitten by the bear enough times.
And my children are past the age of education.
And it is getting.
That is frightening.
Doing those links every week.
It's the linking and the, you know, and you have to write a blurb.
You have to write a little blurb about it.
Yeah, that's the blurb always got me.
I could do all the mechanical stuff, but the blurb, man, you had to take time.
You actually had to listen to the show and make.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
My website has logs.
Blurbing.
Of just about everything.
You know, any show that has less than 100 cuts, I'll usually have a log of it.
Yeah.
It's really just the file names.
They were played.
But, you know, it's a lot of stuff and it's all still there.
And, you know, if I get a wild hair, we do something that's really amazing.
Yeah, a special show.
You know, I can always tack it on as, you know, here's an hour of like annual special.
It'd be like the Ewok special for Steven Spielberg, you know?
That was George Lucas.
The Christmas, the Star Wars.
Yeah, the Star Wars.
Christmas special.
You need a, you'll have an hour of that Christmas special.
That's so bad that people can't, that it's a collector's item.
It becomes a cult classic because it's just whole total badness.
You know?
People have to seek it out.
Well, that would.
Artificially restricted supply.
That would be when Princess Wee and I finally record our 17-minute rock dog opera, Buddy,
based on Tommy.
You read the lyrics.
You thought they were hilarious.
Yeah.
We're ready to go.
I actually have, I found a website that pulls the vocals out of sound.
Wow.
And I used the Live at Leeds version of Tommy and removed the vocals.
It sounds a little weird.
And, of course, Princess Wee is almost a professional singer.
Yeah, she can actually sing, but you are different.
Yeah, I'm a little different.
Dave, Reverend Angry Larry said, I want to help you do that just so you won't be the
one singing.
Yeah, you know, I miss him.
I used to get to see him every year, and at least once a year, and now I don't get to
see him anymore.
So that's the bad, sad thing about X Day being a do-it-yourself thing.
Oh, Reverend Angry Larry.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
I mean, well, here at my house for some, like, for five people.
Yeah.
But it's too late now.
Well, I mean, no, you know, Reverend Zanthia is going to start her resort up again.
She's got new land, and she's moving the weird domes and buildings and all of her stuff.
I don't know where she gets the energy.
Oh, now I remember.
She's never done, she doesn't do drugs.
Oh.
She didn't really drink or frop or anything.
Man, I don't know if I like people like that.
Oh, she's wonderful, actually.
She's great, but she's an overachiever.
She always looks like she's kind of in pain in those pictures.
I think it's just the artificial irises.
The irises, that's what does it.
Oh, the contact lenses?
Yeah.
Well, she sure does work hard in her skimpy, skimpy costumes.
You sure can tell that, for sure.
A lot of subgeniuses went, I don't know, how can she be a subgenius?
She's too beautiful and too, I don't know.
Right.
She's too, I don't know.
She's actually come to this house and was really cool.
I've stayed at her house, but she's moving.
But we still might have ex-days in Florida.
However, right now, because of my situation, I can't leave.
We're going to have an ex-day here, just me and Princess Wee and Wee Mama,
who is mostly pretty out of it because she's heading for the saucers.
That's why I can't go anywhere.
Yeah.
And so I would love to do that stuff again, but I'm not ever going to go.
I'm going to go back to Ohio.
Oh, no.
I don't want to get on airplanes, and I can't carry luggage anymore.
That's what broke my back was all those ex-days, packing the car, unpacking it in a big hurry.
I can remember every time I picked up a case wrong and went, oh, that was a mistake.
You had a pinched nerve recently, right?
Yeah.
I got over my pinched nerve.
That's something that I would get almost every day.
Every ex-day and suffer through it.
Oh, man.
That's why you mentioned that I grunted incessantly.
Yeah.
My grunting has only gotten more constant and louder.
Yeah, and it drives people.
It actually makes people feel sorry for you.
I know, because I'm always going, ah.
But then the other day, not too long ago, actually, maybe a little while ago,
I noticed I was grunting a lot more.
Like, wait, why am I grunting?
Well, folks, it's just a sign that happens that you're transitioning into a different phase of existence.
Yeah, a skeleton.
One that you need to maximize.
You know, it's like I was telling somebody the other day,
is that every age of man has its advantages and disadvantages.
And you don't want to get all bogged down in the disadvantages of being an old man.
Right.
That you forget about the advantages.
It's great.
If you look around, you know, you're always getting a discount on a buffet somewhere.
That's true.
Princess, we go shopping on Tuesdays and Thursdays because that's old folks' 5% off day.
Yeah, see, people always want to go to McDonald's.
They give me coffee for like 70 cents.
Yeah, the first time that happened, I didn't ask, and I didn't understand.
I looked at it and went, oh, man.
They can.
They did that.
I didn't even ask.
You know, they gave me a senior discount.
And that was 15 years ago.
So my point is just don't forget.
You know, every age is a special time, and you got to live it.
Live it.
Live it or lose it.
Dolomite said something about when I get old, Dolomite's not going to lay around and feel sad.
He's going to get his kicks thinking about all the swinging times that he's had.
That's exactly right.
Dolomite was, you know, he was a great philosopher.
Yeah, but he's dead.
Yeah.
Well, nobody lasts forever.
That's for sure.
Some of us are lucky if we make it to, you know, 70, 80, 90.
Well, that's the thing.
We're lucky.
We're already lucky.
Yeah.
I mean, I think 73 is the average age of a white man in America.
It's about that.
It's a good lifespan.
If you're a 73-year-old subgenius right now, you're a lucky son of a buck.
Yeah.
Think how many are dead.
Son of a mother buck.
I read the list earlier before you were on.
It's a long list of people who are already on the saucers.
Oh, well.
Already made it up there.
They're reading their old comic book collection right now.
Yeah.
And all good things must come to an end.
And we're thinking maybe show number 2,000, which is 10 shows from now, maybe that, we
can say, will be the last show.
But wait.
What symbology does 2,000 have?
Nothing.
I mean-
Doesn't 1998 have a much better symbology?
Yeah, that would only be eight more shows.
Eight more shows.
I like that.
Yeah.
1998.
That's it.
Yeah.
2,000.
Anybody would end their career at 2,000.
Anybody can end there because it's round.
You know, the first thing somebody said is, oh, you're going to be 2,000.
You're going to stop it at 2,000.
Oh, wait a minute.
I just thought about something.
That's another 100 shows from now.
I would actually have to stop at 1,900 because we're at 1,889.
Yeah, that's-
Oh, damn.
Yes.
That wrecks the whole thing.
1,900.
Who cares about that?
Yeah.
You know what?
What would Onan would say?
Onan would say, 1,889.
We'll just end it right now.
That's it.
And we could just turn the recorders off right now and say, okay.
Yeah.
And that'd be it.
I'm not going to do that, though.
I'm going to play Doc Stock Mountain, High on Doc Stock Mountain from the Soak Your
Butt album by the Swinging Love Corpses.
Why does this one sound so much better than the one I've played?
Because this one was actually recorded in our little basement studio, you know, when
we were-
We were trying to practice and do things well.
We weren't actually in a-
Not that we weren't trying to do things well in a show.
It wasn't in that-
Right.
It's just harder to get a good recording.
Yeah.
And we never had good mics or good recording attempts.
We were too worried about doing a show.
Right.
And unfortunately, never had really good live recordings.
Well, there's some.
I think some of my best of Swinging Love Corpses is live, but it was just, you know, it was
collected from-
Old tapes.
So anyway, this is about the Doc Stocks that we used to-
Actually, Sterno, you might say, was the host of those in Arkansas.
Yeah.
They were secret subgenius gatherings that only like 20 or 30 people and maybe their
spouses and kids would even be invited to.
And they were pretty wild.
And everybody would jam and rant and swim in the lake.
Sometimes.
Yeah.
Those were great.
So anyway, here's a song about it.
High on Doc Stock Mountain.
Okay.
That's where we play the song.
Howdy Mopter.
That's right.
Several mountains, many close to us you may be so far to where I live.
By the way, that's a local bass track band.
You debt.
Let's take a a deep breath.
retour to the we識
This is a soft ska-
I like this.
Can I make a love song here?
I know the blues.
awakening and talk, talk and talk.
They shared peace and love and great times.
The journey was there and they were feeling fine.
Bobby was there, but they weren't you.
There was mostly cool guys like me and you.
And we got high, so high, talk, talk, talk, how's it?
Yeah, we got high, so high, talk, talk, talk, how's it?
We ate lots of mushrooms to commune with nature.
How are we to know we got to move our shit later?
500 colors flashed into my brain.
My cell division occurred in three or four planes.
My brain was blasted.
My head was blown.
I was feeling thick.
My eyeballs protruded, but I didn't get sick.
We packed up my tips, but we kept seeing dots.
Then we found that the peaks had gotten all the best spots.
So we got high, so high, talk, talk, talk, how's it?
Yeah, we got high, so high, talk, talk, talk, how's it?
Yeah, we got high, so high, talk, talk, how's it?
People were happy, they were all having fun.
While Dr. Sir Bob was farming skulls in the sun.
The corpses were swinging, their love did abound.
The average corpse floated a foot off the ground.
The band that they're not was speaking its name.
While half-doctors on the glam show was claiming their fame.
Farthog explosion and comedy.
The cocaine fudge.
Finish this sin.
Just in time for life.
Then we got high, so high, talk, talk, talk, how's it?
How's it?
Goodness.
Hey!
äs
Was legend of an funk rock if it didn't start now…
Well, I'llanamoo-
We've got high tamon on the peck.
That gr ella!
I'm gonna go back there
I'll even meet the Pope
Better make it to Doc Doc
Or just give up hope
The dead will be walking
Maybe Bob will appear
The sound of chainsaws
Will be all that you hear
Now I'm gonna go back
And I won't be stopped
I'm gonna go back
To smoke the ultimate frown
You just can't imagine
What it's like to you go
When reality's on hold
And Doc Doc's the show
We got high
High
On Doc Doc
We got high
High
On Doc Doc
We got high
Oh yeah
I was way up high on Doc Doc Mountain
I climbed down
I climbed up all the way to the top
I took everything you could think of
I shot beer
I smoked heroin
I started marijuana
I stuck
I slipped glue
I put
I got them drops
Baravor
ının
I got stuck up there on top of Doc's talk partir
because the song was over before I could ever come down.
So now I'm lost in a dog-stalk,
frolopulated, hell-neither-world
in the song.
Man, okay, tell me when you're going to go back into the show
and we can talk about how awesome that was.
Okay.
Because, you know, that particular one,
I really dragged out.
Yeah, okay, one, two,
one, two, three, go.
Man, that was so awesome.
Yeah, that was a great version.
I think we were probably a little bit inebriated
or something during that one.
That's you singing mostly, not your brother, isn't it?
Yeah, that's my brother, my cousin,
singing in the background vocals.
And I was singing lead there.
Yeah, and Colonel Sphinx Drummond traded off a lot.
Right.
We traded songs.
Generally, we didn't trade in a song.
You know, he'd do one or I'd do another,
and then we'd trade backup parts,
things like that.
Every now and then, my cousin, my brother-cousin,
would do some vocals.
Dr. Ray Hay.
Dr. Ray Hay, right.
And, yeah, I'm actually in the process right now
of getting all of the,
all of the,
all of the live footage in one place.
So I can,
my plan is to make this little bit of a playlist
kind of a thing that anybody that wanted it
could easily watch all of the live footage
that I have of Swingin' Love Corpses.
Listeners, the Swingin' Love Corpses
were long before Spinal Tap.
And yet, there's a lot of similarities.
Sure.
There's a lot of differences, too.
There's a whole lot of differences, but...
We played a role.
You know, we were a band that was a famous touring band
that had met harder times
and was doing local shows again.
And our tours may have only been like two stops
in the U.S. that year.
Yeah, like the Subgenius World tours.
Yeah.
And so,
but yeah, we played that role
and it was a lot of fun.
And we all had wigs.
In fact, that was one of our few rules
is that you could not appear on stage
without your wig on.
Yeah, they had,
and wild costumes,
very tasteless
and crazy outfits.
Yeah, our outfits were based on some hippie's nightmare.
Yeah.
A bad trip.
A hippie's bad trip.
Yeah.
And there was great spazz dancing
during the instrumental parts.
Yeah, we had, in fact, we talked about just recently
how we had a character named Beetle Bob
who would show up at our shows and he was really tall
and he would stand right in front
and do the craziest dancing right in the middle.
Right.
Now, unfortunately, people couldn't see me as well
when Beetle Bob was there, even though I admired his dancing
and didn't want to lose his draw appeal.
So what we did is we would prepare,
because Beetle Bob came to every show,
we got some, like, that kind of tape
that they tape off where, you know,
where the bottom fell.
Crime scene.
Crime scene tape.
And we taped off an area
and then designated it Beetle Bob only.
Over on the side, right?
Oh, it was on the side.
Yeah.
But up front, right up front next to the stage.
A little over to the side
so that he wouldn't obscure the audience's view of me.
I always used to videotape my favorite bands like yours
and the Amino Acids from the side of the stage.
So my right ear was pointing directly at the main speakers
and that's why I can't hear anything in my right ear.
Yeah.
Isn't that funny?
It'll do it to you.
It's funny, but only in an ironic sense.
So anyway, let's play one more Swingin' Love Corpses song.
And this one's an instrumental
that you just posted recently I'd never heard.
And the title of this one is
Rock Roll Led Zepp with Rubbit Planet Voice Horn Parts.
All one word.
There you go.
That's pretty much a good description.
Dot wave.
We can climb up on Doc's Doc Mountain
while that song plays.
Yeah, okay.
We know what that means.
Okay, here goes.
Yeah.
Thank you.