I got to thinking about something.
Yes, dear?
A new and wondrous thing.
The finest dignity and elegance.
What is it?
The self-genius power of swat.
What a wonderful idea.
Oh.
Uh, Bob.
Oh, yes.
Right.
I have a feeling there's not going to be all that much happening until the exes get here Friday morning.
Perhaps.
One may hope.
If that doesn't happen, then we're going to be stuck with a baptism in that reeking pond again on Saturday.
Reach must exceed his grasp.
Or what's a heaven for?
Yes, the baptism occurs after ex-day.
It will either occur on the saucers in the careful recreation of the pond there,
or it'll be in the pond itself where they've installed a filter, which filters out all the...
What was the matter?
That's the funniest question.
That's the funniest question I get every ex-day.
What was it?
Do we have an itinerary?
What's the schedule?
What is the schedule?
Well, check your brochure.
I'm going to be asked that all day long.
When is the baptism?
What's the schedule?
Check your brochure.
I think that there was a schedule.
It's in the brochure.
Why don't you check out that...
Pick that brochure up and read it.
I've worked my ass off on that brochure every year, and then no one ever looks at it or even picks it up every...
It's got the last word in there, the wisdom of the ages.
At the end of ex-day, it's like I print up 75...
brochures, and when I'm cleaning up, there's 74 of them left.
Besides, you know you want one as a priceless souvenir of this occasion, full of informative things.
Yeah, it's got the Dobstown nanoheliograph paper.
But look under schedule there, up in the upper left hand of this jazzy document.
Never.
That's the last thing any subgenius looks at is the instructions.
That's... it's um... well, that's one of those distinguishing things between the emergentiles and the rewardius.
Perhaps the instructions are not for them, but for you to indemnify yourself.
You can say that you put out instructions as to what to do, but they did not follow.
The emergent...
Rebellious children...
The emergentiles write the instructions...
...worshipped the golden calf of the conspiracy while you were on the mountain communicating with Dobbs.
Well, did your question get answered, Philo?
I tell thee it is on the day after, uh, X-Day.
After the 5th, it will either be on the holodeck or out in the muck and the tick-infested...
As usual, we'll have either... if we're lucky, it'll be on the holodeck, but we have to be ready for the infested pond.
Yes, so the ticks on the holodeck are augmented special effects, unfortunately.
AR, we call it.
Yes.
But the ones in the pond are the real thing.
Right. Nature in the raw.
Yeah.
And I... so leeches, because I've felt things attach themselves to me while I've been in there.
Uh, but, um, anyway, uh...
Well, the candiru toads are certainly... this isn't really the time of year for them.
You have to stimulate them before they are a problem.
Don't forget the ones that swim up your peace tree.
The ones that swim up your peace tree.
Those are the ones. They are the ones that swim up your urethra, but as I said, you have to...
Dr. Drummond, don't talk unless you have something to say. Into the microphone.
Ah, yes, he's talking.
They swim up your peace dream.
So what is the... what do the instructions say for today?
The instructions for today...
Today's Wednesday.
They say, relax, settle back, and enjoy our featured presentation.
Wednesday says, too hot, wet, stay at cafe.
Stay at cafe, there, that's perfect.
Stay at the Chargers, watch the live radio show.
Yeah, yeah, doing that, yeah.
And or jamming and ranting.
Right. What about the scrapple and stuff? Is that...
That's like everything.
That's not in the schedule because that's... not for us to know yet.
Okay, but aside from that, and if you'll move your eye down the column, you'll see...
Then Thursday, forget what day it is, totally revise schedule, stay up all night, and upset everyone.
Yes, that's what we do.
And then a little bit further...
Further down, past the...
On Friday at July 5th, 7 a.m., we will be exiting with the Exists...
Yes.
And the Sex Goddesses...
Exit only.
In the pleasure saucers.
Next six floors.
So the rest of this is meaningless. What's the point? What is the point?
But it says that the baptism is after...
What is the point?
After the moment of the rupture.
But that doesn't mean anything.
That doesn't mean anything.
Well, it means that the baptism will not take place...
Or...
Before the rupture.
Oh, wait.
Or...
Or everybody goes back to bed for a while, followed by hours of cursing, moaning, and
excuses in the cafe...
See, we have it covered.
Or various camps.
Ask Dr. Howe...
Yeah, come see my show.
...and Bulldog Auction, Rants and Jams...
Rants in your jammies.
...and Saturday...
Bobtism.
...recuperate from Friday the Bobtism in the Pond at 2 p.m.
2 p.m.
Costume or not party...
Be there or be square.
...at 4 p.m., more Bulldog Auctions.
No noise on stage.
Followed by surviving performers and a Bob burning.
Now, costume or not, does that refer to a closed, optional lifestyle?
Yeah.
Costume or not par...
Partay.
Well, all sorts of things are coming up, as...
...as you can see.
So, uh, there's ample reason to fly low.
Sunday, slacking, jamming, last-minute conversions.
Yes.
We're doing, uh...
I don't know, I don't know what to say.
So yeah, see who's carefully prepared
Andrew the Impaled is coming
I don't know about the other clown
But he usually puts on a great show
Or two
One is the disgusting show
The show involving self-mutilation
And trying the flesh
And then his other show is a lovely
Inspired music reminiscent of Tom Lehrer
Quite reminiscent
She said she'd always love me
As long as life goes on
She said she'd keep hold of me
Turns out she was wrong
She called me her one and only
And she said she'd keep hold of me
And my ear, she'd softly sigh
That I'd ne'er again be lonely
That was just a lie
I guess I've been had
And if it wasn't for the cash I spent
Fixing up her car, well
I wouldn't feel so bad
I never saw it coming
I didn't realize we were together
And that I would soon be slumming
Even though I just paid the rent
I thought I made all the right moves
And that things between us were cool
And I thought I might get some good news
Instead I got schooled
I guess I've been had
And if it wasn't for the time I wasted cleaning her garage, well
I guess I've been had I guess I've been had And if it wasn't for the time I wasted cleaning her garage, well
I guess I've been had I guess I've been had And I wouldn't feel so bad
And ain't no euphemism either
We never did fight
We always got along
We'd rock it all night
Oh yeah, our lovin' was strong
We made a good team
At least it's so I thought
But then again, sense of perception
Is something I ain't got
Right?
, L.L.
If you get that seizure
Hard beans break очень Yeah gun dries
Wanna make her happy
But you judge her
Oh off at my door
And then I'd knock her door on the doorstop
She said, oh, that, that's nothing
She said that they're just friends
Turns out that was something
And that something was the end
I guess I've been had
And if it wasn't for the fact he was my roommate
Back in school, well, I wouldn't feel so bad
I guess I've been had
And if it wasn't for the fact I could have been with Cheryl Moore
Wasn't for the fact I just installed a brand new floor
If it wasn't for the fact she stood there grinning at the door
Well, I wouldn't feel so
I wouldn't feel so
I wouldn't feel so bad
Settle down, you dogs, geez
This was recorded at 22X Day last summer
With Dr. Hal, myself, except that I left
And Philo Drummond
But we had a new guest of stars
Mr. Sister and Reverend Crimsoniculus
So let's go back to that live in front of us tiny audience
Oh, wait, I think we turned the audience into the show
Enjoy the day
I'm sick and tired of sitting here
Well, you have to
I need a volunteer
What about the
Come on up, Reverend Crimsoniculus
Come on up, Mr. Sister
You've had enough of that hot wine
Fight citage, live up to your name
And fight boredom with
Oh, wait, that's not what the fight stands for
It's friend them if they can't something
I forget
Flex them
Fark them if they
Fark them if
I can't remember
It's one of those
Finklestein, maybe?
So please, Miss Star, Sister Star
Take a seat and put on the headphones
As you know, and your lips are near the microphone
It's warm and everybody can hear you
Everybody's comfortable
So, as I've been given command of a microphone here
Just put your lips near it and you'll be audible
I would like to put a shout out to Bob Woods on Facebook
Is that a literal shout or are you just going to mention him now?
Woodsy the Mailman
Uh-huh
If you have nothing better to do, subscribe to his posts
He's a mailman, but he also has like a blog?
Is that the story?
I cannot explain it to you
Is that your right wing buddy?
No, no
He's apolitical
Does he put out a post?
Printed hard copy newsletter?
Magazine?
Zine?
Giveaway?
No
Flyer?
He's online
He pretends to be a person
Of interest
Working a cell phone
Uh-huh
And everything he posts is in capital letters
That makes it important
So, yeah, like somebody's grandfather maybe
The bigger the headline, the bigger the story
Yes, and he misspells things and
Why let's not?
Blazers
I know
It's very uncomfortable
18th comes a day
New songs on Thursday
Browns
The costumes
JC
On the Country
I'll say it on
s
Pros
Co bakın
Present
And it won't work
Everything's Fan
It'sin
Par
All
One
etc
Come
The
Show
Catch meека
э
The Church of the Subjects, be chum genius, whatever it is,
being a joke is completely beside the point
because that doesn't have anything to do with the validity of what it asserts.
It's just that we assert it in a comic way.
There's no disproving something just because the element of humor is added.
Indeed, the element of humor demonstrates that there's something there to laugh at.
Deep words, deep words.
The asserted absurdity of the human condition is what creates humor.
Yes, of course, and the sudden incongruity of a slapdown.
It's not what you believe, it's how you believe it.
Seems like what you believe kind of has something to do with it, wouldn't it?
That's what others...
Other people believe suddenly coming in contact with what you believe
that creates the frictive frisson of humor.
People believe about what you believe.
What they believe about what you believe.
What they believe about what you believe represents and reflects their beliefs too,
which become evident during a humorous interchange.
There's too much reflection going on.
Now you're laughing because there's two points of view being simultaneously expressed.
One of them is a surprise that comes at the end.
The fabled punchline.
It's like two radios turned to different stations playing together.
It's like the country music station.
But occasionally there's a mashup.
It's not always on, but it's always in the air.
Some powerful throbbing stations with wide bandwidth overcome little stations
that might have neat stuff on them but are completely crushed by their powerful signal
from right next to them.
On the dial.
It's like that Mexican AM radio station that comes in at night very late.
It really comes pounding in, eh?
Really loud?
Really loud.
Pulsating signal?
Yes.
En Español.
En Español, yes.
Se habla Español.
When Puzzling Evidence and I get off the Puzzling Evidence show,
which is about 5 o'clock on Friday morning,
we tune in.
We try to listen to this show that's broadcast on the Indian reservation.
And it's hard to get to because there's this Jesus station
that's really powerful right next door.
Jesus keeps bleeding over into it.
But then you hear them broadcasting in the Dine language.
And when they're not doing that,
they seem to be playing some kind of countrified country and western music.
Oh, intriguing.
Yeah.
Well, you see, I hail from Cleveland, Ohio,
where there are a lot of Russian and Polish people.
Uh-huh.
And Klezmer music.
One hears a great deal of polka music.
A good polka in the eye with a sharp stick.
A Weird Al's polka?
I like Klezmer music,
and I think that's very au courant among the youths of America today.
Yes.
They go out and they play funny oompa music with their friends
rather than being laid-back, cool disco techno.
Uh-huh.
Very little Klezmer.
Klezmer rap, though.
It's true.
There is some.
There is a chap rap from England by the original gentleman.
Oh, I've heard of that guy.
Yeah.
He's fighting trousers.
Cultivated rap about Guy Debord and all the different types of tea he likes to drink.
So there's that.
There are all sorts of variations.
All forms are permissible.
Everything that could be exploited should be exploited.
And will be exploited.
Nature rushes in to fill a vacuum.
Because it pours it.
Nothing is excerpted.
And pour the vacuum.
Yes.
Those giant underground crystal caverns under Mexico City that they discovered,
and others like those elsewhere,
well, they're not filled.
Oh, yes.
Yes, they are.
Now that they're discovered, our air is rushing in there.
And humans are rubbernecking and breaking off little pieces and checking it out.
Nature vacuums a whore.
And everybody else.
They want to get away with it.
Around the far corner.
We're not putting on the poke.
This isGod.
A either образом
We see every single that makes us hungry.
We turn on our computer.
We can face it with Р.
But the fact is that life ischtal Part of health is being practised every now and again.
We deserve better these days.
As long as gives the rest,
Never affected.
Honestly.
guitar solo
Thank you, and if we pass the audition,
hopefully we'll see you again next year.
Listen, I can tell you're fake clapping.
You're not really clapping because you like it. You're clapping
just because you say, well, good, they're done.
And that was
the Slut Rods.
I've got two dogs here that are just
out of control.
Are you all aware
that everything that's
necessary to destroy this planet
is already here somewhere?
It's already freely available,
and that is a very sad
revelation. If we didn't know, we were going
to lose the planet already. Every time
you go into one grocery
store, that is one of a zillion,
godzillion grocery
stores, and everyone has a long
shelf stretching into the
distance of solvents, soap,
sips, heavy chemical
preparations, insecticides.
You know, this
massive chemical thing that you see
is repeated
everywhere. Where are they going to go?
They're not going to stay on the
shelf of the grocery store.
It's going to go into the water table.
It's going to go right into you
through a million vectors,
and there's no way to
stop it because there's so much. Haven't you
been in the grocery store and looked
and seen how much there
is just in that one grocery
store? Dozens of different types of pesticides.
Just alone. You can get your local
grocery. It doesn't even have
to be the super
strong bad chemicals, although there
are a lot of those. It could
simply be all the salt
that is present because the presence
of salt when it enters the soil
kills all living things.
It used to be the practice in the ancient
world to sow salt in
your enemy's field so they couldn't grow
anything. That was a Roman practice.
From space you see the desert
areas spreading
out in the satellite
photos, and they're spreading out because
of agriculture because every time
that they inundate their
fields, salt flows
in, and you're shortening
the life of that
arable land. But I,
for one, am so thankful
that salt is so much more affordable
in our era. Ooh, it's tasty,
and we've got the big salt
farms over
in California where I am.
The salt flats. You can go out with a
measuring cup and scoop it up.
Good old sea salt.
We don't have to recover...
Or like the cliffs of Dover.
Well, that is calcareous
animalcules creating chalk.
Oh, chalk.
I still pour it on.
Skeletons of zillions of tiny
creatures.
And not only the tiny ones,
the giant ichthyosaurus
is sometimes
found there, and
the shells of grotesque
ammonites, tentacled
beings that have
a large spiral shell like
the horns of the god Ammon.
And wouldn't it be fun to go back
and get one of those just to bring with you?
Oh, you think you could just go back
and get one, huh?
Well, I mean, we kind of invented time control.
You get in the water with that
thing. We've invented time control, so
of course. I mean, once X-Day happens,
we'll just go back in time, go pick up some salt.
Pick some up.
Well, you can go back, but then you can't go forward
because now it's all different because you were there,
you stuck yourself out, and now
probability is all
completely changed.
You cannot travel back,
so you have to go forward.
And if you're lucky
and you have the right type of time machine,
you can go forward fast. Otherwise, you have to
go forward at the same rate as
everybody else.
60 seconds is a low way.
That is a problem.
And they say that although
it is possible to invent time machines,
they couldn't go back to an earlier
period than the time they were created.
Who knows?
Depends on the mythos, for sure.
If we could go back in time, it would
cost a fortune to open up all those
restaurants that closed or bring back
those people that we miss.
Yes, well, you go back and you
get all the rare
collector's comic books when they're
cheap and easy to get off the stand.
Oh, they're one
tiny guy who had
three little pain guys.
Oh, piggy,
see how they run.
Oh, see how
they run.
Oh, they all run
after the bar with me.
Who could have said that we're carving
them? Now I'm the one
of the three little
pig-blivers.
Two piggies, three blind
mice.
Why don't we always go oink,
oink, oink? It's our
tradition to go oink.
Three blind mice.
Pee-wee, pee-wee,
we're skinny and green.
How they run, they will
see how they
rise. For they all
can have fun.
Oink, oink, oink, oink, oink, oink.
Well, we all
are just a little bit
alive. And now we three
blind mice.
Oink, oink, oink, oink, oink.
We're the only
best type of three blind
mice. So don't
ever try to go oink,
oink, oink, oink, oink.
We are the we, we,
we.
Yes, well you go back
and you collect, get all the
rare collector's comic books when
they're cheap and easy to get off
the stand. Which I was fortunate
enough to collect and keep
in my garage all these many years.
That's good, I'm glad you've got yours.
You know, not only were
moms assiduous in junking
comic book collections, but there
was a national movement
to burn them in church
sanctified bonfires.
Terrible. The Kefauver Commission's
investigation into juvenile
delinquency pointed
that comic books were the reason
there were all these scary
kids with ducktail haircuts
and leather jackets and
stilettos, you know. Comic books.
Comic books had to be the reason.
And they were massively
destroyed.
We got rid of the
EC comics line, the
great entertainment comics.
And all that were left were
DC and
the Dimely that became Marvel
and then there was Carlton comics
that were sub-bar. Harvey,
uh,
not many.
And even then, odd one shots
like Carl Anderson's Henry or
the great duck
and mouse epics of
Dale's Disney comic.
I was
a fan of Uncle
Scrooge McDuck myself.
Well written, incredibly well written
stories by one guy who
didn't even get to sign his name,
but people recognized
this is really good, you know.
This is better than any actual Donald
Duck cartoon or anything.
It has tremendous
depth to it and
I ended up
working in a bank
in similar conditions.
Did you, I mean,
Carl Barks was the guy
he eventually did achieve
some fame. His bulldozers
plowing coins
in underground vaults. Paintings of
And then swimming in it.
And swimming in it, yeah. And throwing it up
and letting it fall on his head.
Which I never understood. I've done that once
with small change and it hurt every time.
Yeah, well, you must be
not rich enough to enjoy.
Or have a feathery coat which
will let them
not fall on your exposed
skin. I see.
Well, that's something I'll do the next day then.
Change my body, be a duck so I can swim
in small change.
The duck is an interesting
feature for that matter. I have a few
Mad magazines too, but I consider them
in retrospect prophetic.
Well, the Mad magazines,
but they were an
E.C. comic and the only E.C.
comic that survived was Mad,
which then became a magazine and
stopped being a comic book.
But the early ones
had the great stuff that's reprinted
in the early Mad Ballantine
books. They're parodies of other
comic books which they excelled in
at that time.
It was kind of like the Monty Python of
America.
They were really thought to be evil.
They were denounced because they were
subverting the American
way. In
fact, there also was
Panic in addition to Mad.
Mad was done by Gaines
and Harvey Kurtzman.
Panic was done by Feldstein
and Feldstein never knew how to be
funny. But it was beautifully drawn
and one take
on the night before Christmas
drawn by
one of the great
E.C. guys,
Will Elder, I think, was denounced
on the U.S. Senate floor.
How could anyone create this?
This work of filth.
Think goofing on Santa Claus.
Really, couldn't people be a little
less uptight?
But they weren't.
Gaines went in to testify
for his books but he didn't
make a good impression.
He took too many speed
pills before talking to the
House Un-American Activities
Committee.
He just basically zipped through it.
He defended a horror comic which
showed a woman's severed head being
held up. He said, well, yeah,
this is what we do. You call
this good taste? Yeah, it's
in good taste. The line is
there so you don't see the meat and
things hanging down. That didn't work.
And he also
said that the
stories and the E.C.
comics had an O. Henry
ending and that anyone who
didn't understand this
type of literature was like a
dried up old maid,
claiming to legislate
for everybody else.
Another thing that he regretted saying.
Oh.
So kind of like some of the situations
we have going on now.
Always. The eternal situation
is always going on and it's
going on now. People who just don't know
are trying to write the laws when
they should just be asking.
Well, people who can attack art because
they know it's helpless and it can't attack
that.
Still who's
going to offset these
Secret
Secrets
is
the
native
And his mind was ablaze
Lame situations were his subduesure
We didn't know the maladies that he had come to cure
Well, he got himself a job there right from the start
Help wanted sign in the shape of a heart
He took it inside to Fanny the Forest
Gave him a job cause he lives in the forest
His dad was a tree and his mom was a ranger
We didn't know we were friends until we were strangers
His name was Rusty Cavallaro
And he walked into a town with a heads-on barrel
When he was a kid
He got agitated
Everybody got elevated
We came around when he came around
The Condors, they all came back to stay
Marching bands played downtown every day
The mayor, he stopped wearing a tie
The chief of police got a tattoo on his thigh
Ashtrays killed all the Emerald Beatles
We gave blood without any needle
His name was Rusty Cavallaro
And he walked into a town with a heads-on barrel
When he got agitated
Everybody got elevated
We came around when he came around
And his dad just got seriously hurt
He left a single showumbled
And his dad died
What a live-on
One of the APs once said
We were the verses and he was the chorus
He taught us songs that we already knew
We all sang along and we sang them in tune
He gave us all, he gave us nothing
We were the turkeys and he was the stuffing
His name was Rusty Cavallaro
And he walked into our town with an answer barrel
When he got anticipated, everybody got elevated
We came around when he came around
So your dress lashes out to chastise rivals and subordinates?
Anyone who gets it within three feet, it'll just...
And does it some damage? Does it hurt?
I don't think it's that efficient
Lashes you? It slaps you?
I mean, it is like plastic and silk
It probably does sting a little
It could do some damage
Under the unluckiest circumstances possible
For the most part, it would do nothing but annoy
Yeah
Hey, what's this?
Oh gosh, it's in my eye
Or even dare those who enjoy receiving that form of attention
Well, you know, some people just want you to stay out of their area
I think it's kind of a neat thing
But when you go to a party, oh well
Well, yes, you definitely couldn't wear that at a party
Just every time you're trying to get a beer
Trying to talk
There's the invisibility suit that the CIA was trying to...
To develop
I thought that that was all Photoshop and smoke and mirrors
Well, it was...
It's like mirrors
It's like the garment is covered with cells
And the cells are little cameras and little screens together
So you see what is on the other side
That the camera takes
And then the computer has figured out where it should go
According to your point of view
But there's still...
There's still the problem of the ripple that you see
As the suited person moves across your field of vision
The shadow that he casts
Is still there
Yeah
Because light is still going
Yeah, he's actually there
You're just seeing what's on the other side of him
But you also see his shadow
I imagine you'd probably also see his footprints and such too
Yeah, they're actually there
So you would see them
Unless there was something else
Who knows?
Maybe hard...
Hard-packed dirt
Wouldn't have any
Somebody walking very carefully
Not making the footprints
No, the special invisible operative
And then, of course, they are armed with weapons
Which also have given the invisibility treatment
Well, because it would make no sense to just have a gun sitting there
Floating in mid-air
And then shooting at people
Yeah
The gun shows you what's on the other side of it
But it doesn't show you what's...
Inside it
The bullets which emerge
But too fast to be seen
Into visibility
Indeed
It would be silly to do it otherwise
Is what I was saying
If you had the invisibility suit for yourself
But not for the gun
You'd just have a floating gun
Well, the gun doesn't always have to float
Well, true
You could lie on a shelf
Until needed to be snatched up
By the super invisible agent
Well, then that would just be scary
You're walking into a thing
You think you're trying to find a...
Some kind of agent
And then all of a sudden, bam
Just a gun floating there
Am I dealing with ghosts?
No
Yeah
No, probably not
Time to leave the vicinity
This troubled area likes me little
Let us call the mystery machine
Because, obviously, this is their department
From PR News in Washington
I'm disturbing
The Justice Department's Inspector General
Has rocked the region
More than 20 U.S. attorneys across the country...
Are vacant and empty
On Wall Street 313-8237
A British court has ruled that this is British PR
But behind
Later this hour, congestion and delays
Morons will address concerns about PR News
It sort of brings to mind a fantasy I have about
The next version of cell phone
What would that be like?
Well, that would be a device which
Is constantly transcribing
Everything adheres in text
To a web server
Which may be searched
Well, they might be doing that already
Because...
Well, the idea being that
If you want to talk to someone else now
You have to voluntarily dial them
But in the future, I conceive where
You just say, hey, Bob
I want to talk to you
And they would always be listening
And they would have full video
Well, that would get so, so very hard
To listen to all the time
I mean, you wouldn't even have to call Bob
Because you could see and hear
Everything he was doing
You wouldn't need to communicate with him
Right, well, that works with one person and one person
But what about one person who's friends with ten people?
Or one person who's friends with hundreds of people?
Well, it could work with groups, too
Like, hi, oh my gosh
I can see what Bob's doing and Carl's doing
You get to scan past them
And then when you see something interesting
You can look at that one
Oh, so it's like TV, then?
Yeah
Like having a closed circuit TV
And then you can look at that one
TV everywhere
And some lawn equipment
Well, there's a Grim Reaper
Or the International Harvester
Preparing the killdozers for
When we inevitably change the Earth
To its original primordial state
Indeed
Well, they'll have to do something
With the place for the future tenants
Well, yeah
I mean, that's part of the whole deal, right?
Dues paying?
Get ruptured up?
We terraform back to primordial state
And then we give it to the exes
Right
Brilliant
This writes itself
Has been for the last 20 years
Why change?
I don't even know
Well, I'm happy to sit out here in this heat
To find out
I mean, you know
What becomes
I've been here for the last three years
So I'm waiting for it
And if I have to
I will figure out how to get to it
Well, it's not far
The landing area
Is just down the road a piece
Oh, I didn't know
Been going here three years
And I still don't know where it's at
Don't you get up at seven in the morning
On X-Day
Troop out to the landing field?
Well, yeah
But most of the time
I get accosted by squirrels and raccoons and stuff
Before I even get halfway
And then I have to turn around
Right
They're trying
Warning you
Trying to hold you back
If you ever grow a pend finances
But don't worry
I can jump in the pants
So minimally
Oh, oh, oh
Thank you, Reverend Jimmy Ryan.
Did I hear reference to filtration in the pond?
They have added a filter, and it does supposedly filter the water.
This was what was happening last year here.
So I haven't heard about this year, haven't been there so far, but that's what I hear.
Wow.
That's that.
Progress.
You could ask a wisteria person.
They would know the latest scuttlebutt on that.
The native wisterians.
Yes.
And their mystic knowledge of the clouds.
The wisteria.
The wisterians would eagerly tell us what there was to know.
With their ancient tools.
Otherwise, it may be that they forgot completely about it and haven't even opened up the pond at all,
and that if we went down there, the barbed wire would still be drawn over the entrance,
and the entire thing would have a very unwelcoming, unprepossessing look.
You never know.
Well, until you go down.
So it's Schrodinger's Pond now, then.
The pond will be in use for the baptism, but after the rupture.
Of course.
On next day.
Yes, yes.
I wonder if old Sequa is still there.
Oh, guaranteed.
Supposedly, yes.
There are many snapping turtles in the pond now, and it's been speculated that these are the progeny of old Sequa.
Not the full-grown snapping turtles that they appear to be, but actually the hatchlings of mink.
Is Sequa.
Where's Mr. Sequa?
I've seen them a lot.
You can see them there.
They're there, and they're big.
Their head is here, and then the back of the shell is here, and there's some tail following there.
Those are large snapping turtles.
So like two and a half feet, three feet long?
Longer than that with the length of tail.
The tail extends.
The tail is armored, and it's all armored.
The shell is armored.
But the one I saw had a sort of a gracile look.
Maybe it was a female.
Unless it was long, a snapping turtle, if it is inactive, deactivated, you can hold it by the tail,
and it'll reach down to the ground when you hold your arm straight out from you.
Wow.
Well, I mean.
They can get to be 60-pounders and so forth.
But what we're talking about are the recently hatched progeny.
We have the giant cryptid snapping turtle called Old Sequa.
Long may she reign.
Native Americans built the turtle mound out there,
which has been adorned with goofy beach balls for eyes that was never put there by the tribal culture.
Now we have some beef jerky to eat.
Turkey, jerky, beef jerky.
I understand turtles make excellent soup.
What astonished me about turtles that I learned fairly recently was that they're quite intelligent.
That I wouldn't have thought.
But then I saw that YouTube video of the guy in his backyard playing with his pet dog and his turtle,
and they were playing ball.
And this box turtle is scrambling to push the ball with its head.
It obviously knows what's going on in the realm of play with the dog and is wiggling around pushing the ball
with its head.
Who knew that turtles had a mind which could understand game play and get into the moment
and that a slow reptilian creature would busy itself to hit the ball with its little head,
with the dog pulling it the other way.
An incredible video.
It just takes a trainer that has to...
I expect all animals are more intelligent than we give them credit for being.
Oh, that's definitely true.
I recall seeing a video of a turtle.
Humping a croc shoe.
Well, you know, a lot of the time when you're looking at your turtle or whatever,
you're looking at a captive, a creature that's in jail.
And they evolve pathological methods to deal with captivity.
Do not judge the species by what some poor prisoner may do.
I guess it's like the mafia, you know, when you're in jail, whatever you gotta do to get along.
Well, you could be in rich folks' jail.
Right, where you'll get out after three months.
And while you're in there, you have all the recreational opportunities.
Must be terribly nice.
You can play high lie, that sort of thing.
Is that the one where you have to throw the clay ball?
It's where they put the actual wolf of Wall Street.
High lie is with the big scary hoop thing, isn't it?
The big scoop.
The scoop.
It's the ball.
Scoop ball.
The Aztecs invented the vacation.
It comes from them.
In other parts of Ohio, they're now using drones to drop off things for the prisoners.
It's, of course, not legal, but you never know when a drone is going to come over the jail yard.
Oh, so it literally just comes into the jail yard and gives them a thing?
It drops off some.
Contraband.
Drops off some contraband, yeah.
It was only a while before they figured that out.
Well, I read that Martin Shkreli, while in jail, was operating a cell phone illegally and making financial transactions and sales.
I heard the same thing.
Seems like if they're going to do it, they're going to find a way.
Or if they want to do it well enough, they're going to find a way.
They don't seem to be following the...
The program.
Yeah, the same coda.
They're not acting as if they're rehabilitated.
Just continuing along on the same lines, over and over, as if they didn't...
Not at all.
As if nothing ever happened before.
We're all prisoners.
It's just the distance between us and the prison walls may be greater in some cases.
But all prisoners shall be released, we believe.
We should believe.
Or do we?
Should we?
With subgeniuses, the only ones we worry about.
We don't want everybody, we just want the subgeniuses.
Only the ones with the maxed craziness.
Personality contact?
The ones who can be tolerated.
Who are tolerable, who will tolerate you.
And who are the best for genetic experimentation, of course.
From PR News in Washington, I'm a turkey without explanation.
Trump said turkeys are not good.
President Trump left one turkey dead last summer.
Just last week.
Trump's 4% unfair and 1% unjust for turkeys.
Surprise attack near the fighting.
But the attack suggests fighting.
President Trump accused the governor of Virginia of using turkeys as human shields.
A federal judge in San...
Francisco is deciding whether this is PR News in Washington.
Thank you, Mr. Lemur.
And now, The Psychoskeletons.
Music Playing
I don't know.
Thank you.
Thank you, skeletons.
Psycho, that is.
The psycho skeletons.
And friends, you can learn more information about this show,
the Church of the Subgenius, and the strange bands and music we play,
at subgenius.com.
Or, prisoners may write to P.O. Box 807, Glen Rose, Texas, 76043.
And aren't we all prisoners in one way or another,
either of the conspiracy or of Bob?
And here is Stang once again.
Well, we have Cossack.
Cossack's you guys should go feast and drink in celebration
because Nigel and Joy are here.
Woo!
Oh, yes.
That's not X Day without them.
That's wonderful, isn't it?
Well, there's been some without them,
but they were Nigel-less and Joy-less.
Yes.
X Days.
Now we are infinitely better off.
They've launched many, many fake saucers.
They've fooled Mr. Sister.
What's to eat, then?
Are we having?
Um, tornadoes of beef.
And some fondue to go with that?
I pointed out to them the two new people that are in the room now.
There's one other one that wandered off.
And they're actually not necessarily new.
A couple of those guys were here last year, but I wasn't.
No.
No, I missed the next day.
And we were sad.
We were sad to see that you couldn't make it.
Oh, God.
We all understood.
It had a certain inertia.
I'll tell you this.
something really ironic and kind of sad. As I later put all this together, if you look
at the list of people who actually signed in last year, there's really only 34 of them.
Now, there were some I know were here who didn't sign in, but 34 people.
That number seems low.
On July 5th last year, the exes had taken my niece to the saucers, and there
was a wake at my house. It had 35 people were at my niece's wake, and 34 were at Ex Day.
This was on Ex Day?
Yeah, on July 5th, the year the conspiracy calls 2018. Yeah, right.
Yeah, not 98 yet, though.
No. And yeah, that was sad.
I preach.
But what I basically said was, it's so sad, on this fireplace mantel behind me,
this is my family in Texas, I'm speaking normally.
Right.
So, on this fireplace behind me, we normally have 19 stockings at Christmas, or Exes-less-mas,
and we've lost two. There's only going to be 17 stockings this year. I said, we got to replace our
numbers. There need to always be 19 stockings. So, I looked at my two grandsons who are
eight and 10 years old. I said, that means you boys got to get to work.
Put that responsibility right where it belongs.
Yeah. I said, no hurry. You don't have to start now. They look kind of relieved, you know.
And actually, I think since then, two of my other nephews and nieces, well, my daughter got pregnant,
delivered a third grandson.
Yeah.
There you go.
The snake-killing nephew's wife is going to deliver in September. So, we're going to have 19
stockings on Exes-less-mas.
Okay. There you go.
At Stang Ranch. So, the youngsters are doing their job to make new little subgeniuses.
Well, on that hopeful note, perhaps we should conclude this broadcast and
remark that there is a generation coming into being who may be the
salvation of the world.
Yes.
The Stang DNA continues.
Short version.
Into the universe. And why? Without knowing.
So, yeah.
Because Bob told us to. That's why.
Okay. We are all dismissed.
Hallelujah gobble.
That means there's room for the youths with their loud guitars to come here and...
Yes. I don't see them, but if they wish to come up and give us that...
I'm sure they're having a real ex-day party over in Newtown down the road.
Well, I haven't heard anything from the stage, but then there are other sounds which
might be muffling.
Oh, they're back in the orgy woods where we're not allowed. It's like, no,
you have to be this young to enter here.
And no electric guitars playing?
Oh, there probably are. It's just drowned out by the moaning and groaning of all the
sex they're having. They don't tell us about.
Mm-hmm. Well, then there's a...
I mean, I think we're going to have to get rid of the terrible, terrible acoustics then.
Yeah.
Because guitars should be able to wail much louder than people. Just probably.
Okay. Okay. Okay. All right. Slack. Okay. Okay. Slack. Slack.
Slag on.
Slag on. Slag on. Slag on. Slag on. Slag on. Slag on. Slag on.
But you'll be less of a conspiracy dupe if you contribute to poor old lonesome cowboy
Dave's GoFundMe. He really needs help. Look at the radio section of subgenius.com. There's a link to it.
Because it's too complicated to read on the air.
Thank you.
Oh, I almost forgot. It's Slack Friday all the way through Christmas. From November 30th, which is
over with now, all the way to Existlessnessmas, December 24th or so, you can get two subgenius
memberships for the price of one. Yes. Two for one sale. Slack Friday. Only 35 bucks.
Plus postage and it's a little more postage for two of them and you can ordain yourself and a loved
one or a pet or someone you really hate. Or you can deny a membership to someone you really hate
by buying it and then not giving it to them, giving it to somebody you like.
Seriously. It's our annual sale and it's going on and people are taking advantage of it. It's funny
how they.
They wait for that special.
deal before they spend their precious $35 on J.R. Bob Dobbs and the church that saved them,
or at least saved their sanity, or at least saved some of the money they spent.
Praise Bob. And friends, have you tried Triology Soaps yet from TriologySoaps.com?
They have Dobbs bars. Yes, I'm serious. Triology Soaps, run by our friend Lord Ferg,
manufactures bars of scented soap with Dobbs heads made of other soap embedded in the
translucence. It's like a translucent, in this case, a green bar of soap. You can kind of see
through, and there's a brown,
silhouette Dobbs head inside that is gradually freed as you clean yourself. As none other than
Reverend Ivan Stang said, these are the good stank, and they are. Princess Wee and I have been
using many of their different scents and flavors. These specially blessed soaps might not keep the
conspiracy completely at bay, but at least you'll be smelling fine. These are handmade soaps,
and they do indeed stank, and they have names like New Time Bobber Shop at Dobbs Bar,
FrankenBob Dobbs Bar. If only Boris Karloff could smell this bar, we think he'd enjoy it.
Connie's Suckle Honey Dobbs Bar, Cosmax Select Cedarwood with activated charcoal.
These are all about $6.50 a bar.
Dr. Philo's Frop Brownie 4 oz. Dobbs Bar. St. Joyce's Jasmine Frop Blend. Orange Rose Peony for Wee
Ma Ma. I hadn't seen that one. Wee Ma Ma is my mother-in-law. Fidjuli Dobbs Bar with sorbitol,
sodium chocoite, and artwork by Catfeather. Catfeather Sparkling Barf. Wow. Dragon's Blood
Dobbs Bar. And so forth. And you can see the Triology Soaps catalog, which also includes
t-shirts and unique designs and many other soaps besides Dobbs Bars. Those are at
triologiesoaps.com. One word. Triology is spelled T-R-I-O-L-O-G-Y. So it's tri as in three instead of
as in try as you may. T-R-I-O-L-O-G-Y. Triologiesoaps.com. Praise Ferg.