Please destroy this recording by the usual method.
Sorry, I was giving myself an oil jar.
In any event, please dispose of this tape recording as directed.
Oh Pete's got ideas!
Those that ain't vile are foul!
As usual, this recording will decompose one minute after the breaking of the seal.
You have soft hands for a man, Don.
My micro-mechanism thanks you, my computer tapes thank you, and I thank you.
Come in, come in sergeant. Stop that noise. Come in!
Why do you stand there? What is it? Speak up, you empty head.
Do you keep watching the clock? Do you run down and jittery?
Do you tired? Do you never end?
But that's how you feel.
For your own sake.
I say try Sub-Gideon Meter.
That's right, Sub-Gideon Meter gives you glorious strength, energy, and needed vital substances.
Plus iron. The name is Sub-Gideon Meter.
And now, turn off your radio.
Now.
My pappy said, son, you're gonna drive me to Lincoln.
But you dog
Evans
itu
だから
A
Holy
Someone's Bob
Bob
Bob's own Bob's head
Bob struggled again for air
While smelling his rank body odor
Bob knew it was wrong
Bob
Had a beer and a good laugh
And then a good night's sleep
My bourbon Kentucky
Too much beer
Bob asked, how is your daughter?
I would ask her, but she's still unconscious
Bob
Some big punk
Something out of a nightmare
Fly legs and spider heads through his brain
One sip and I'm gone
Oh my god
Then he got down
Down to it
Bob
Perfect round black hole
Entry positions in the rear
Bob
Bob's
Bob's own Bob's head
Bob
Bob's
Bob's own Bob's head
Oh my god
Bob stayed as calm as he could
But nobody was interested in his strange idea
sin
He proved that in corporateattan
ended up against Bob
Bob's best friend
Bob that's it
Bob's going to shower
Bob's cutest房
Bob left a good helping hand
Oh Thanks Dog
It's 제가
Stop working
chance to go to Vegas and Bob thinks you know possibly a chance we could have been slacking
there. I don't know. I think we did all right but we might have slacked a little. I wanted to get
you these suits because you deserve a little spoiling on this trip and I am just wanting to do
it. From Bob! Lay down with some nice clothes for us to wear on our night out in Vegas courtesy of
Bob. That's Bob, that's the kind of guy Bob is. Bob knows me this is so sick.
Bob knows that this could potentially be a huge distraction. But uh one thing we had
to remind him of- it's like, Bob we just went home.
F1 fogus let's go.
Off camera banana banana!
F1 F1 F1 F2
Again!
Off camera zal Bloeman
One more time, each leg.
Each leg?
Yes sir go.
Off camera fanboy
Followillä dlatego, for suggested text then get ready.
We're having an thanks for each constructions on your side!
This is our last FastFestFestFestFest before Vegas with Bob.
And Bob isn't too happy we're going,
because he thinks that there's a chance we could slack off.
So he is pushing us really hard today.
Two more.
He is killing us.
And it's not too fun.
This trip is coming at the worst possible time.
Last one.
We don't have time to.
The Self Genius Power of Slack.
She keeps Grape, Mogan, David in a Purdy Mason jar.
Got Oprah Winfrey programmed on her VCR, plucking off her goatee.
So her boyfriend won't see any kind of infection on her.
He might surmise Rush Limbaugh on the radio.
Well-versed in fellatio.
Extraordinary nice.
She's a traitor.
Wee!
On racks in Ovaltine,
Kenny Rogers makes her cream.
Krusty Poo on her behind.
Recommended at the price.
Just ignore the pubic lice.
You wanna try some of that?
I have said all along that America is based on Judeo-Christian beliefs.
And our unalienable rights don't come from man, they come from God.
To avoid constipation,
she always took some dung.
milk-a-lax.
In conversation, she spoke just like Ranobulax.
Met a man from Vida, bought a double wider.
Traded in some plasma for some hairspray and wine.
Perfume came naturally from Walmart.
Smelled just like a dog fart.
For stideous and for sash.
Traitor.
Wee!
Unwanted pregnancies.
Reading People magazine.
Krusty Poo on her behind.
And even theFC psychopath.
Oh no, he's got aTERO.
So I'm trying to Bl VIp him.
roots all over me,
Girls I need aетровalk
sports fans sing them songs over my singing rap
CC round 12 mierdy
IÕÕ's1ÕR
Thanksgiving
Dis jumped off a tower
And when she craps, it's as smelly as cattle in an abattoir
Momentarily out of tampons, bloated with digestive gas
She'll absolutely drive you wild, wild
She's a trailer queen
Gland back and Ben's a dream
Snorting methamphetamines
Krusty poo on her behinds
Recommended at the price
Just enjoy the pubic lice
You wanna try?
You wanna try using that?
Smells pretty good
And beats all me
Always good and sweet
Always pretty
And beats all me
Don't panic, but sobering.
Yes, if you ever use the term American.
The gorilla.
Do it.
Same country.
America.
Bad.
From.
All right.
But then.
You know.
Robert.
They look like you and me and everybody else.
God.
,
Green means time to go.
Go.
Move over, bro.
You're moving way too slow.
Maybe you should know.
No.
I'm the leader of the western world.
The big decider in the neighborhood .
I'm floating hope on an ocean of need.
I'm Santa Claus.
So look under your tree.
I got.
Something for everybody.
All right.
Red says time to stop.
We're back.
Stop the giving up.
Run, now ditch the walk.
Next, get back on top.
I'm here to fix it so it runs like new.
But the bankers tell me no can do.
I'm facing problems way beyond control.
I'm talking smooth but I'm deep in the hole.
Now, tell me what I say.
Sounds like a line.
Trust me, every word is true.
Just don't ask me why.
I got something for everybody.
Something for everybody.
All right!
Psychopundits keep on burning the fire.
Spin the story then they call me a liar.
Telling me how I should do my job.
Dropping crumbs for the angry mob.
Al Qaeda and the Taliban.
Fundamentally way out of hand.
I keep trying to turn it all around.
But the new world order wants to take me down.
They got something for everybody.
Something for everybody.
All right!
Something.
What about the pink tool?
Both of which were easy.
And also a joke.
But a neck.
To perform in public.
It was open war in the end.
The eyes fixing the horrified viewer.
In a ghastly glare.
All she'd needed was one man.
And that's what she'd got.
Bob.
Animals twisted everything.
Old age is the blood.
I thought everything you did was glamorous.
A bodiless hand.
Scrolling across a wall.
Maybe God doesn't have a left hand.
I said he got his left hand cut off in a war.
What about the pink tool?
Oh!
Well, now the song is being recorded.
That's right.
You heard a lot tonight on Big Things in Copyright Australia.
You did a real pretty good job today.
The jam band with the amino acid helpers and Dr. Sinister on bass, I believe.
Does anybody want to rant?
And Pope Black is about to rant.
This is an amazing piece here.
Take it away, Pope Black.
Now, I'm looking out here into this terracotta army of overmen, and you look like you're guarding the grave of your emperor, Dobbs.
But I got news for you.
Instead of sitting there on your awarding asses, you should be getting up and jumping and singing and dancing and screaming and praising Lord Dobbs.
Because in a few hours, the skies are going to open up.
And that sweet cherry...
is going to swing down and let us ride.
And take us off into the heavens.
To another place.
To a planet X.
A planet sex.
Where we shall be the love toys.
The chew toys of intergalactic goddesses.
Who will keep us.
And love us.
And catch.
From now.
Until.
The end.
Of time.
That we control.
There'll be no more hate.
There will be no more fear.
There will be no more pain.
And there will be.
A cornucopia.
Of drugs.
And alcohol.
And meatloaf.
And grape jelly.
Because you.
And you.
Believe.
And if you got it right.
Right tonight.
Going into physical madness.
Run through your mind.
Going to the world.
All the time.
Get it right tonight
Right tonight
Great jelly
In the open heavens
All you can eat
It'll be the Wesley Willis
Snorkin' board of
Intergalactic love
Love
In the hot rocks
From outer space
Gonna swing down
And give you a smile at least
They're gonna pick you up
Carry you off to heaven
And give you an intergalactic
7-Eleven
Frame up
Wraith ball
Dr iPod
guitar solo
I got sprayed with mace
In a sacred place
Love got us coming down
Take me off this base
You think it's fair
To live on planet Earth
With loads of bad TV shows
And landmines in the dirt
Well, we're going to play
In outer space
Where there ain't no hurt
Praise God
müsst
And you
Thou
Are
Fed that conspiracy
By the tape of the neck
Shake it like a rag doll
And stomp him to heck
Take that evil conspiracy
Drive him off to hell
We'll go off to space
And eat it like an electric taco bell
Woo!
Woo-hoo!
Ah, yes.
Pope David Lee Black.
Oh, man.
Yeah, Pope David Lee Black there,
recorded by Potter Nostril,
at 13X Day.
And, yes, Pope Black really did get maced
at X Day.
Welcome back to America, Pope Black.
Unbelievable.
Yes, that was a pretty amazing rant there
that was totally spontaneous.
And the music was spontaneous,
and that was Six-Fisted Tales of Connie.
That's the name of the band
that forms once a year at X Day.
It's always different people
on different instruments each song.
But this was more or less, I think,
Reverend Sud Shaw with Monkey Hive
and Reverend Angry Larry,
I think, both playing guitar.
Dr. Sinister played bass
until he had bloody fingers.
He described that on his show last week.
He played drums sometimes, didn't he?
Yeah, and Reverend Phil played drums
and Dr. Philo Drummond.
He played all kinds of things,
but mostly saxophone.
That was recorded a Sunday night
at a time when a Buffalo newspaper
claimed that, quote,
nothing was happening at X Day.
I think they must have been
at the wrong pavilion or something.
Anyway, before that, we had,
well, starting at the beginning,
there was a long string of collages
that were by the great
Fernand and Andy Lemur,
and other ones by The Large
and Mr. Rection,
and other ones by
the great Reverend Hart Ignition,
who is back after some hardship.
He sent a whole bunch of audio cut-ups,
and if you look at the Subgenius Art Mines
at subgenius.com,
you'll see some of the greatest artwork
in the church's long history,
which is kind of equivalent
to the Catholic Church's history of artwork.
The song Trailer Queen
was our friend Reverend Joe Newman
from his band,
the Rudy Schwartz Project.
I'm not sure which DVD or CD,
whatever that was,
the HoloCube that was.
Possibly...
Oh, I can't remember.
And that was Devo
from their new album,
a song called Something,
which I think is about
President Obama
or any president.
That's my theory about that song.
And thanks to Reverend Baz Otherwise,
who loaned us that CD.
And this is some kind of music
from 70s porno movies
in the background.
I've always loved it.
Some of it sounds kind of like
Jefferson Airplane.
Not this one,
but you'll see what I mean later on.
Princess Wee,
is here,
and this is the first time
we've been in the studio
at WCSB here since
before X Day.
This music reminds me
of the Greek band
at the fish fry.
That's right, yeah.
Yeah, the freak fry,
freak fry at the
Greek Orthodox Church.
There's a Greek Orthodox Church
near us,
near the Slacker Mansion
where we go to their
their fish fries.
Yes, very Greek,
Greekly.
That band, that house band
does sound a little like this.
They do a killer Greek version
of Black Magic Woman.
Oh, speaking of killer versions,
would this be Lonesome Cowboy Dave?
Could it be?
On this particular piece,
the armature of the student
should be very firm,
and the lip should be,
the bottom of the lip
should be cemented up
in a kind of a bridge-like motion
so that the teeth
can move.
And the tongue
and other parts of the labial area
can produce the note.
Is that the Dr. Overman's
saxophone lessons?
That is right.
And also, in his lessons,
he includes a brand new reed
for each student.
But it's not the kind
that you would think.
It's an interdimensional transport
of some kind, I believe.
Well, we all believe,
as Pappy said,
I believe what I need to believe.
That's true.
Our needs are based on
what we need to believe
of our needs, our needs.
And that's what the church,
the subgenius, is here for, friends.
Whatever you need to believe,
we'll probably tell you.
Sure, yeah, go ahead, believe it.
Absolutely.
Reinforce them.
Reinforce those beliefs
right up the wazoo,
and start to engender
and create kind of a false,
no, I wouldn't call it false,
but a need for new beliefs
that,
are convenient for us.
Well, as J.R. Bob Dobbs said,
believe me out of it.
And he was believed out of it.
Wasn't he?
I mean, most of the time,
he was still kind of believed out of it.
Is Bob in the station?
Did I hear Bob?
That's Bob.
That's baby Bob.
He's whining.
He's whining?
That's unusual for Bob,
but I guess, you know,
he doesn't like to be in the station.
You need coyotes,
and you need coyote urine,
which you can buy out
in your local,
outside of Cleveland stores,
out in the sticks,
in your feed and grain
and pet supply stores.
You get your coyote repellent,
and you put it around
the WCSB station down there,
the beautiful, beautiful
WCSB station.
And that way,
no wolves or bears
or coyotes come in there.
Oh, because the coyote's
already been there
and staked his claim.
It'll also keep rabbits out,
I would think,
and pussycats.
Well, like Bob will keep rabbits out.
You know, he's got the,
the trickster coyote juice.
Yeah, Bob's urine
will keep almost anything away.
Except customers.
It draws customers.
That's the funny thing about it.
They just want to get close enough
to reach in for their wallet.
That's about it.
Just close enough
to hand him that money and run.
And any closer, P-U.
Hand over the money and run.
Well, every church has its,
every church has its pew, Dave.
And I thought my jokes were bad.
And many jokes have kneelers.
Oh, never mind.
Kneelers.
Um, kneelers.
Kool-Aid Lorraine.
Thanks, Lorraine.
Lorraine?
Her name's Lorraine, too.
We're all Lorraine,
and you will be Todd.
And name choosing,
especially for you,
by Gil.
What does Bill do
with all your stuff?
He's holding it
for us at the car.
Oh, I see.
A compound.
Where's the compound?
I'm not really sure.
In Texas?
Oh, you're not a singing group,
you're a cult.
Are you sure?
Of course we're sure.
We're the Bureau of Alcohol,
Tobacco, and Firearms.
It's our job to know
what these fanatics do.
So you have no ethics at all,
do you, Bob?
Oh, we have a couple of events
to mention
that might be of interest
to the subgenius listening audience,
at least the ones in Cleveland.
On Monday,
August 7th,
the Cleveland Freethinkers
are having their monthly meeting
or whatever,
and they've invited me
to come and speak to them
about how to lose
their free thought,
how to give their thought
over to Bob,
and it will become paid thought.
You'll pay to know
what you really think.
Anyway, that's at Panera Bread
in Rocky River,
Saturday, August 7th,
at 7 p.m.
And I think anybody who wants to
can come in.
It's a...
Oh, what did he say about it?
Reverend Anacron is part of that,
and he said,
the Freethinkers are a group of atheists
who hope to build out
an island of sanity
in the sea of theocratic nutjobs.
I'm sure they'll be receptive to you
in the word of Bob.
And so...
And Princess,
we will be there also.
Isn't that what atheists
always do, though?
Yeah.
Oh, they're such a bring-down.
I mean, you know,
they can't believe in Bob,
for one thing.
And they also falsely
and indeterminately believe
that Bob will bring them down.
Maybe atheists can believe in Bob,
because he's not God.
Sure they can.
They don't think that Bob
is a nutjob, though,
unlike, you know,
the Christians and the...
Are you making fun of me again?
No.
Oh, no, no, go on.
I'm trying, but I can't.
That's an inside joke,
an inside joke.
The scrotal area joke.
A nutjob.
Now, why would you want
to expose the insides
of scrotal areas?
For laughs.
For cheap laughs.
That's a simple answer.
Sophomore humor.
I will...
If people look at the events
part of subgenius.com
tomorrow night,
they will see information
about that Freethinkers show.
I didn't get that on there today.
And also tomorrow night,
hopefully they'll be able
to see our photographs
from X Day, 13X Day.
But they won't be able
to see the photos
from the devotional for Devo,
which is coming up
August 27th and 28th.
It's two days this time.
Wow.
At the Beachland Tavern
here in beautiful Cleveland.
Actually, that's over
in Collinswood, right?
North Collinwood.
Or...
Where we used to live there.
The Waterloo Arts Area.
Yes, David.
We used to live there once.
Well, I was like
a part-time liver.
Yeah.
Just like many of us
have in the church.
One that works
once in a while.
I would go there
and spend the night
many nights in a row.
Wow.
Like four or five.
And it's not important
how many nights
you would spend there
in a row.
But I often spent
summer afternoons
gazing out at the lake
from a fifth floor window.
And then below me,
all around,
there was just natural beauty
and there was squalor
like gunshots
and bullets.
Yeah, right.
I was gonna say.
hoes and mofos
and different kinds
of words like that.
Yeah, that's actually
a pretty rough neighborhood
over there.
A steady in contrast.
But the Devo fans
will all cluster
at the nice, secure
Beachland Tavern.
Oh, it's wonderful there.
On August 27th and 28th.
Oh, yes.
That part of the neighborhood
is lovely.
Plenty of security.
Oh, it's all
gentrified now.
It's all...
There's like
five art galleries
in one 20-yard area.
Oh, yeah.
Nice place to eat.
And all kinds of things
are in there.
Shoot, rich people.
I hate them.
People without goatees
are fined $25.
That's right.
Princess Wee,
you better have that 25 bucks
ever since you shaved.
I've got my goatee.
I get made fun of
from having a goatee
by, I don't know,
these subgenius haters
who think that, you know,
the goatee is supposed
to be devilish or something.
Well, I just thought
it was supposed
to be goatish.
I just thought it was
goulardish.
I'm not from...
I'll start with the
guh sound,
which makes me, you know,
goatee, goulardy,
goat...
Ghosts.
Goot, goot, goot.
It's, um, I wonder
what the phonetic
relationship is there
between, you know,
the mind sound,
like if we were
ancient Aborigines
about 12 million years ago
and we would look at a box
and everybody at the same time
would go,
gah-gah,
or something, you know.
And that would be
the word for
box.
Maybe.
Well, actually,
you know, probably
if they looked at a box,
a perfectly squared-off shape,
that would freak them out.
They might worship it
like Bob does.
If you were from
a Stone Age kind of a culture,
a cardboard box would be
something of a marvel
because of the straightness
and evenness of it.
That 90-degree angle,
squared-off blockhead,
that's unique to you.
It's unique to people
who build square houses,
squares.
Only the square culture
builds square things.
Round cultures like to have
round living areas,
like teepees
or little yurts
and such like.
Domes.
We're the box dwellers,
the caged people.
Sebaceous dwarves.
What?
Sebaceous dwarves?
Are you kidding me?
Are you making fun of me again?
You are, aren't you?
You just came quick
picking on me.
If there's something to pick on,
I say get out the needle and thread
and pick on it.
Wow.
Bob knows
that picking is good
in Mr. Rogers' neighborhood.
Oh, well.
Hey, next.
Bob knows it's no fun
to think of, about, of, about.
so we are
um
I'm
Bob Head
we're not perfect
Bob must die
internet porn
prostitution
sex trafficking
what did he mean by that
down down down
8-06
why
hierarchical
we have the power
click
well Dave
you were at
X Day
for one day
that was my
briefest time ever
in the history of humanity
well
but it was brilliant
I don't know
that it was
I haven't heard
the recordings yet
for all I know
it could be awful
but it was Dave
come on
well there were
a few titters
of laughter there
but there were
more titters
than there were laughers
there was Dave
and Dr. Hal
and Susie
the floozy
and I remember
oh yeah
we have pictures
Susie the floozy
got bored
with the boy talk
and took her shirt off
and smoked a fake
smoked a cigarette
but it's a fake cigarette
you see her all the time
with this
it actually smokes
smoke comes out
of the end of it
but it's not a real cigarette
she just
she just smoked
but uses it
to look slutty
in keeping with the name
Reverend Sue
Susie the floozy
just a prop
just another prop
she did some
wonderful preaching
we'll be hearing
all of that preaching
on future
I mean hours of slack
whatever this is
oh god
and then there was
Starwood
and I
we're still dizzy
we're trying to
grasp our bearings
but
yeah we've had
actually that was
in the land
of round places
and now we're back
in the world
of square
in fact on the way
back from Starwood
we and our past
and your Reverend
Baz otherwise
stopped at a
like a family restaurant
Laurie's family restaurant
just inside the Ohio border
across from West Virginia
what a memory
West by God Virginia
Mr. Sister knew
what town it was
it's like Crawford
or something
not that's where
President Bush
used to live
Crawford
but it's
something with a C
anyway
we had been
okay at X Day
which is pretty
there's some weirdos
but we had been
and then we were
at Starwood
which is all different
kind of weirdos
and then suddenly
here we were
in Laurie's family restaurant
in off the highway Ohio
and Baz drew our attention
to the fact
that everything was
white
and clean
and smooth
and square
straight
flat
all of
and including
the people
and just as
who obviously
had just
gone to the
church
most of them
and here's the funny thing
just as we were sitting there
thinking about how pink
all these people must be
suddenly
this old feller
who looked like
Abe Lincoln
crossed with Uncle Sam
quite a courtly old gent
a real old gent
like in his 80s
he did have the facial hair
to create those illusions
yes he did
he had a long white beard
and he looked like
Uncle Sam
out of his costume
and he was with his family
and he suddenly stopped
by our table
and looked at me
and he goes
excuse me
fella
I need to ask you a question
now
you're sitting here
and you're not all that good
looking of a fella
but you've got these
two beautiful women
sitting here with you
I want to know your secret
I know you must have a trick
he said that to you?
yes
and I
and I witnessed it
now you can see why
that part of my family
that lives down there
in the hillish area
that did
I
think they're crazy
well they're not
this guy
my father
and they'll just walk up to you
and say these really weird
things sometimes
that's not that
I've been
it was so much like
something my father would do
that I knew exactly
how to handle it
you know
he sort of insulted me
by saying
you're not so good looking
and you're sitting there
with these beautiful women
what's your secret
and I said to him
I'm rich
and the whole place
cracked up
and he said
I thought you had a trick
because I got one too
and he
you know
kind of
motioned to the ladies
he was with
and did the balloon animals
routine work?
yeah
for two and a half hours
so you see
there's
the moral of the story
is we're sitting there going
god
we're these weirdo subgeniuses
and everybody around us
is oh so pink
oh god
and suddenly
this local guy
walks up
and proves he's as big
a subgenius as anybody
so it just goes to show
you can't
only
only J.R. Bob Dobbs
can judge a book
by its cover
he's the only one
who can do that
truthfully
I've always believed
that what I said about
the other side
of my family
is not correct
I
speed
up
my
oh you know
like hula ladies
those ceramic
hula ladies
that have the name
of a ship
from world war 2
or Korea
underneath them
and stuff
and that sort of thing
and I forgot
where that was
you were telling us
that your family
are a bunch
of characters
Dave
Lonesome
Cowboy
Dave
northeastern
perspective
I remember going to a place and asking for some eggs and toast and the lady went you don't want no meat with that
meaning pig meat
Yeah, I was automatically felt very outcast just just because of the huge volume of pork consumed
in those areas
Well, you know when in Rome
Eat pork. Yep. Everything's better with bacon. Don't you think that your relatives from down there might occasionally say
Yeah, we've got we've got a relative up north names a lonesome cowboy Dave. He's a bit of a character
Oh, of course, they would of course they would he reads then stuff. I
Seen him read a book one time. I
Don't even think it was upside down
But I couldn't
take
a look at the
No, it was pretty good at reading and writing but
Those are kind of Bob Dobbs is rich in a strange way
Even though they're all gnarled and twisted and kind of connected to everything every group of people if there were
Excellent group. Well, jr. Bob Dobbs himself was raised in a small town. I
Will reveal that it was not in Texas. It was in Kansas
Fairly small town
and although he
He grew he kind of he moved to Texas and developed he had to just kind of a general
Midwestern accent a tornado picked him up and dropped him off in Texas. I would suppose a Kansas
Actually
You're thinking of Bob's attempt the attempted abortion of jr. Bob Dobbs his mom for reasons
Wanted to abort the infant Dobbs before he was born but
He could yank him out of there because of his magic power and they finally strapped her down in a Kansas wheat field and
Tornado came and that managed to suck the fetus Bob out. But as soon as she saw the little
preemie Bob she like everyone else she loved him and
Was sorry that she had attempted to abort him and so they they raised him and I don't think mr
Dobbs ever really was had a clue about any of that or
the stories about the real father
The different colors of hair on his neck and stuff. Why they don't matter. Yeah. Well, mr. Dobbs was a
One of the few American Mayans. He was Mayan American and and Bob obviously doesn't really resemble
I mean, he's like a
he's so
Caucasian he's
Almost alien looking I'm speaking of which I read in the news today that the aliens are fleeing
Arizona and selling their disintegrators
Well, that's not the Martian community. I guess the Martian community is selling of CDs to world beat guys
I guess their music is really really bizarre
It's like elements of Martian disco mixed with afropop mixed with
you know country music just everything thrown in there and
It's hard for some to understand but it's an experience
You know what?
I mean people buy the CD to have the some of them vomit some of them cry
But it sounds like some genius music. Yeah
Purgative in some ways and an animatic in other ways
Oh we next next day we're thinking of changing the name of it to love parade
I thought that might be a
Kind of a draw and in some ways it'd be more accurate. I
Could just see though like huge ants on a screen with a bunch of subgenie around it and where the
Huge ants are like eating the heads off of regular people running down the street and Kansas or some
It just kind of puts an unusual perspective to it. That is an unusual perspective
I'm not sure where that came from. Well, everything is so smooth and flat and suddenly there's huge ants
Oh or little crabs or whatever they are
right
I'm just I'm just a little slow today. The heat's been getting to us. Mm-hmm me too. It's me for
I guess our north up in Canada and you know around the northern Great Lakes from Minnesota and so forth
it was even hotter than down here for some weird reason and
Many hundreds were recorded and whatever that is in Canadian talk 30 something whatever
Yeah, yeah, that's uh 40 maybe it's kind of brutal. Oh, it's probably snowing in Texas now
I
Heard it's raining and I'm very lush in Texas right now
Have any thoughts?
Yeah, but it's that spent that new methane rain coming in from the Gulf
Now that the hurricane sees the storm season is coming in the it's the the the new chemicals are wafting into the heartland
Soon soon my brother's goats will all have oil
wads
Like those pelicans. Yeah, you'll be wearing gas masks
I did goats with a gas mask
That's a strange image, you know goats can handle almost anything if a goat has to have a gas mask
And that's a bad
Yeah, I remember seeing early military training films and stuff and they put gas masks on the poor little coach and then
Pump whatever kind of gas and if the goat was still working, I mean goats still standing that meant the mask was working
Oh, there was one military then there was the military
experiment where they killed goats just by staring at him because they
were Jedi's
the new earth army
And then they made a lot of money off of a movie and then there were yeah
Oh, and then there was the people who killed goats by cussing at them. It was called men who swear at goats
That was in it was in Arabic originally was this I should
I
Should take over dr. Dark's job as awfulest punster
Actually, they're I couldn't hold a candle to him. I
Put me in front of the radio. I don't do this all the time. Do I princess way? Yeah, you do
The point is yes, she
One point and now I'm a punnery
fellow
Also, I used to talking puns constantly, and he would never quit
We make you cry sometimes
I'm sorry
I could
I could swear I heard the Devo song I played today, I could swear I heard him say,
Psychopath Finders in the lyrics.
But that can't be. I must have just imagined that.
I actually read the lyrics online before I played it on the radio,
because, you know, I'm deaf. I can't actually hear anything.
So, like, for instance, what you're saying now, I had to look it up on the internet
so I'd know what to say, you know, on cue.
Thank goodness it's all there on Google.
Everything you're going to say is right there.
What would we do without that safety net?
Talk about stealing people's dreams. I think that's what Google's all about.
They wanted to steal every author's book and make it free.
Oh, we've decided your book is free now.
Well, then they'll write it for you and charge you.
So we finished those last four chapters.
We knew what you were going to say anyway.
Here's an invoice for...
Reverend Stang, we improved your subgenius book.
It wasn't very good.
It's gone.
It's called... It's Praise Bill now, the Book of Bill.
That'll be $5,000.
Well, no, they'll just won't pay me any royalties until that $5,000 has been accrued by sales, advanced sales.
They'll be like, you know, potty chairs with lots of fur and any of your favorite...
I know you're into sodomizing animals, so, you know...
What?
Those magazines and stuff will provide it for you.
No, I only do that for on stage.
That's just a stage.
Okay.
It's just wild vegan food to be commenced today.
And it's... I'm sorry, I forgot.
Ay yi yi.
I didn't mean to interrupt with that.
Mm-mm-mm.
What did you interrupt?
I don't remember even that.
Me neither.
I think he interrupted himself.
We better Google it.
Wait a minute.
Oh, no.
Here, let me Google that for you.
Yeah.
Well, I made the mistake of looking at the news again today or yesterday.
Well, it had this funny headline that said,
Is Pakistan During...
directing Afghanistan insurgents.
It was implying this fantastic, horrible secret
that the CIA knew but didn't want to admit,
that the Taliban had actually been being supplied
and advised by the Pakistanis.
And then I remembered, wait a minute,
we used to supply and guide the Taliban
when they were fighting the Ruskies.
Yeah, they're still using them stingers on us.
So what's the difference?
I mean, what did not seem like, it's just a horrible...
Talk about dog eat dog.
Yep, that's what's bad about the WikiLeaks.
Talk about bog sucking in bog.
Yep.
Bog is my favorite character on the Dead Dave show.
Bog?
Yeah, that's Reverend Angry Larry's new TV show,
the Dead Dave show, you should look that up.
I knew that part, I'm glad you repeated it for the airtime.
Yeah, and bog is this...
brainless swamp thing
that talks kind of like a cross between Zippy the Pinhead and Bob Dobbs.
He gets a lot of the best lines, and Dead Dave is the straight man.
It's a sitcom about what zombies do when they're not eating your brain.
Like what?
It's all pretty mundane.
He celebrates Halloween in one episode,
and they have Christmas in another episode.
Then there's an episode...
It's like a making of the Dead Dave show that's behind the scenes
that shows their effete director, Colin Dewar,
engaging in all kinds of lascivious movie director type stuff.
Sometimes referred to as Colin Dower.
What else is in the news here?
U.S. holds drills off Korea as Pyongyang talks war.
I thought,
Oh, if those drills are deep sea oil drills,
that'll sure show those North Koreans.
Yeah, why don't we just light up North Korea with a nuclear device or...
Just send BP there or any of those guys.
It didn't have to be BP.
It could be any drilling company.
Caliburton will be right behind them.
When I think of drills and, you know, destroying the Gulf and so forth,
and then I think of the drills that the Pakistani secret police are doing,
which are just, you know, drilling like,
Okay, how can we kill a bunch of Americans?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And when I think of all the other drills they're having,
and there's never going to be a war between North...
Nuclear war between North and South Korea.
I mean, why would Americans even believe that?
I mean, would there be a nuclear war between Ohio and Pennsylvania?
Why would they use any of those drills when they could go to the X-Day drill?
Yeah.
Or they could just use a good old dental drill
that kind of makes people flap around on their seats and scream.
Yeah, some people pay extra for that, I've heard.
Yeah.
Some people make a living out of it.
Yeah, I've actually paid quite a bit of money
to have somebody do that to somebody else.
It was my kids, in fact.
I paid a dentist a lot of money
to torture my children's mouths.
And they all have...
They have all their teeth now, you'd think.
I mean, they look just like they have all their teeth.
Beautiful.
In any second, I could be...
We could be grandparents, too.
Any second now.
Any moment.
My daughter is scheduled to thwelp a new stang child.
Actually, its name won't be stang
because she's married to somebody whose name is not stang.
But think of the horrible visit you've created in the mind's eye
of so many listeners out there.
A little teeny beautiful baby girl with a stang head on it.
She looks just like you exactly.
You're not a very good-looking guy.
What are you doing?
What's your head doing on this beautiful woman's body?
You're not that good-looking.
That body's real good-looking.
What's your secret?
Get me the hell out of here.
Hmm.
Yeah.
Oh, hi.
I think all subgeniuses who enlist, re-enlist,
or co-opt themselves today
really ought to consider the fact
that they could instantly become
a sort of conceptual grandpa or grandma
if they want to.
Even if they're not old enough,
they're not old enough to have a child of their own.
I would just make that offer as a statement
just to flip it out in the air
and hope that it never comes back.
Now, what?
Did you say you're offering to be the grandchild
of any subgenius?
No, I was just saying that any subgenius...
Any person...
Come here, little Davey Wavey.
Sit on my lap.
Let me spoil you.
You've got some toys.
Bounce a baby.
Bounce a bounce a baby.
I'm going to show you how to play the accordion, child.
When's our new grandchild Dave here
going to start growing some hair?
Yeah.
His teeth have come in.
Well, some of them.
And now he's growing hair on his mouth
and teeth on his head.
And that's the way things should be.
They could...
I was horrified to learn that hair
had begun to grow inside my ears.
I didn't know.
There are tools, aren't there?
My friends told me.
Yeah, there are tools.
And I had to start, you know,
learning.
Learning to use them.
Old, old, old.
As a youth, I once mocked a man
for looking like a man,
except for the fact you could tell
he was getting old because
he had a mustache on his nose.
On his nose.
And I thought,
he picked that.
And I realized after a while,
who cares, you know?
Just get out a can opener
and remove as much extra wind as you can
and scoop it up
and hope it never,
uh,
gets in your way.
I'm gonna go to the toilet.
But we don't have to worry about that.
We'll never get old.
Because any minute now,
Bob and the aliens will come and save us.
Because X-Day could be any moment.
That was Bob's point
in making us wait at 7 o'clock
on every July 5th
for the last 13 years.
That's a magic number, too,
in your holy masonic rituals.
Well, and some.
Well, no, I mean...
A lot of good it did us.
24 or something, but...
Yeah, no, it's a magic number, too.
It's gonna be lucky 14.
That's...
I'm sure that'll work.
Yeah, well...
Double sevens.
Hey, speaking of the world ending any second,
which it could,
this show is also ending any second,
or actually in a couple of minutes.
And, uh, I'm just warning you,
because I'm gonna turn...
I'm gonna hang you up
and get off the mic in about a minute
and play something.
I can't remember what is next.
Right, that was a big deal.
Because, uh...
I was going to call late,
so I could talk all the way until 12 o'clock.
No, until, uh...
Until 10 o'clock.
12 o'clock.
You can, actually.
Dr. Sinister's show starts in...
Yes.
He usually starts taking calls about 11 o'clock.
You can call in and...
Perhaps we could do that, too, isn't it?
Commiserate with Rock Gnar and...
Eviscerate.
Yeah, eviscerate Bernie and all the regulars.
And then with that,
I think it is just about time
to let this, uh,
to give me some scissor space.
Friends, you've been listening to the Hour of Slack
number 1,267.
Oh.
On this July 25th, 2010,
which, the rest of you,
it won't be that date anymore.
That's what we call time control.
And if you want to know more about
the Church of the Subgenius Hour of Slack
or anything that we've been playing,
you can look at subgenius.com.
And in the radio section,
if you click on the number of a radio show
that's stored in there,
you can see the log of everything that was on there.
Again, that's subgenius.com.
And if you really...
For those of you in prison,
my prisoners out there
who aren't on the internet,
that would be post office box.
What is it now?
How can I possibly...
It's been...
I didn't get very...
I didn't sleep well last night.
I should forget your post office box.
Was it 181-417?
Yes.
181-417.
Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
You see, too many X days,
too many Starwoods.
Too many ones and eights.
Too much slack.
And...
Too much crumbly brain.
Too much is always better.
Too much spontaneous breast enlargement.
And...
So let's see what comes next here.
Here with my Bob,
I feel safest of all.
I can light up my pipe.
It's the only way to live.
Praise Bob.
Here with my Bob,
I receive lots of slack.
I can listen to stang
and keep me stable for a day.
Praise Bob.
Here with my Bob,
where my brain cells break down.
Will you visit me please,
If I give you some frappres, Bob
Here with my Bob
I just stare at his face
My brain in deep outer space
I can feel alone with Bob
Here, here, here
dot com
praise Bob