I and only I will decide when and how much we eat. Any argument about that, I
settle it with this. Oh, you're a tough man, all right, packing that gun. Just don't let
go of it. I don't intend to.
I haven't had time for your kind of woman. Don't touch me. I can't stand you.
Now the world don't move to the beat of just one drum. What might be right for you may
not be right for some. A man is born. He's a man of need.
They're not wrong from you. They got nothing in their genes.
They take different strokes. They take different strokes.
They take different strokes to move the world.
Everybody's got a special kind of story. Everybody's got a way to shine.
But no matter what they got, not a lot. So what?
They're all theirs. You'll have yours and I'll have mine.
And together we'll be fine.
Take a different stroke.
It takes a different stroke.
It takes a different stroke to move the world.
Yes, it does.
This is not true.
No, this is not important either.
It's not important to know whether a dog gets your command or is commanded by you or gives
you rhetorical questions about existence.
I.
I can picture in my mind an ancient sage, perhaps 5,000 years BC, walking across the
desert, carrying a pipe in one hand and wearing a little funny tie in the other hand.
Yes, as he crosses the hot sands and the blisters grow in both his brain and on his feet.
This is so unimportant.
His fever is going.
People say my dog looks like Toto.
Yes, it does.
I'm the Wizard of Oz.
I tell you one thing.
My dog is always with me.
Don't tell Bob.
I won't tell Bob.
Fuck that guy.
Come and listen to a story about a man named Jed.
The poor mountaineer barely kept his family from bullying crude black tea.
Well,
the first time he was born,
California is up the truck of swimming stars.
The Billy.
The Hillbilly.
Bar-
Billy.
Hilly.
Oh, what the what?
All right, now everybody just act cool.
I don't think so.
Bob.
Goddamn Bob.
No.
I just want to Bob rat face Bob.
Asshole.
Look at me.
I'm a kid.
Wow.
We're back with a.
What were you saying about the Moose Patrol?
The organization's first meeting.
And after that little encore in the back room, I hope you're all feeling an awful lot better.
Know that the vents have been closed and it looks like only three or four people are going
to have any permanent brain damage.
So let's get on.
We want to.
I think it's Father Winkley as it's his turn to speak on ecumen and then I don't know if
I'm saying this right in the new century and slack.
So if you'd like to give a warm pair of hands and just put them right here where I can feel
it.
Thank you.
And we'll.
Are you pulled out?
I'm sorry.
That's not the only one.
That's not the only one we need to talk to.
Is it too Meghan?
Yes, it is.
She called me last night and said, can I get a text message to it?
I don't think so but I want to about what you said about you calling me out.
Yeah, sure that you wanted to interrupt me as I was CE.
I forgot to mention that, you hate the marriage okay?
G send off an admin to watch over and over again and play a quarrel with the
reac
Thanks Hold on, whose is that?
Damn it.
You're-
if you will, the global overmind is somehow lapsing into a coma.
And we think that perhaps in each country there are maybe a few avatars,
a few saviors, if you will, a few people willing to raise the rod of slack
and place it where the sun don't shine and continue the struggle
if we are indeed struggling with something here.
I hope, at least I hope, I hope, that we can all contribute in some small way
and I can't go on.
That was the voice of the under-mook,
unable to express the lofty thoughts of the overmind.
The poor under-mook is reduced to sobbing and mewling and puking on college radio.
I look up and I see thoughts, I smell them and there they are and yet I can't touch them.
Ice cream tastes like laughter.
But feel like it's slack.
In the...
This life or another one.
Who knows?
Who cares?
Does the universe...
Why should the universe care about you and your slack?
That's right.
Why should the universe care if you have anything at all?
Let alone that little, little, teeny, tiny dandelion you're holding in your pocket.
Walk on, friend.
You're penniless and you get nothing.
Except slack.
Loads and loads.
If you sign...
And here.
There you go.
Thank you.
And here.
Don't forget to...
Don't make no sense and it's not supposed to.
The nights are gay and the sun...
This won't make too much sense but it's not intended to.
Well, well, well, that's our excuse anyway.
It has been since 1979.
Well, we welcome you to Hour of Slack.
Number...
828.
Using bits of other shows such as Chaz Smith's ESO Swamp Radio on WCSB Cleveland
with Lonesome Cowboy Dave, which we heard just then.
And before that, the Beverly Pillbillies cut up by Fernandanande Limur,
who will also be doing the weather.
And other clips coming up on the show.
Different strokes there.
The TV show theme, which we're still doing a bit of.
That was by Todd Bridges.
And...
And, uh...
The music in the background here is Einstein's Secret Orchestra with Ron Slabe,
recorded at Winterstar 2001.
Here in Dobstown, friends, it's Malaysian junkies.
Meanwhile, an area of low coast.
It could be tonight, maybe early in the morning.
And Cape Clip Coastal's just fine.
41, 39, and 39 up in Wappentrees Falls up here on the Hudson River.
Boston, near from the Cape.
Outlook for the Midwest, more and more low.
Here's Christina.
And in the south, we're going to see most of the south,
but parts of southern Florida, maybe around Miami by the afternoon.
But we think into the evening hours in Orlando and Miami tomorrow.
Let's take a look at wet weather.
Wet weather.
Wetter weather lingering in the area.
Now, in the west, for you, expect a high.
Paul, please tell us your high.
Oh!
Yeah, my friend.
I won't forget it.
I'm hungry.
I need food, meat, red meat.
Nearly raw.
I don't know why, but it'll do me good.
And so, here's the meat men.
GIVE ME THAT COUNTRYSIDE
Green Acres is the place to be Farm livin' is the life for me
Land stretching out so far and wide Keep Manhattan, just give me that countryside
XT
I get a magic-smelling hang.
I just adore the penthouse view.
Darling, I love you, but give me Park Avenue.
The chores.
The stores.
Fresh air.
Times Square.
You are my wife.
Goodbye, city life.
Green Acres, we are there.
Did you hear about the new gorilla that they found in the condo?
These are the gorilla-like creatures that raised Tarzan.
Tarzan was not raised by gorillas or orangutans or normal primate apes.
He's raised by these mutants.
Well, by yeti.
Full-blood yeti.
By yetis.
That explains everything.
That explains his lisp.
That explains the weird cranial dents.
That explains the hairy orifices on the side of him.
That explains everything.
That explains why he was so sexy.
Tarzan was sexy because he learned that from the yetis who raised him.
This is the kind of music Americans need to listen to as they march to war against these strange mutant gorillas.
You know, a lot of kids today don't know that Tarzan was based on a real god.
That there really was a Lord Greystoke who was raised by these Bigfoot creatures.
In the old days, we called him Lord Greatstumper for the amount of wanking he did in a short period of time.
Well, that was why they had to change it.
They had to change it in the novels because that's about all he really did.
The mind of an ancient oriental dog.
Insert transition here.
Do you know your daughter well?
Do you know she's dreaming?
Talk to her soon.
Do you know your daughter well?
And do you know she's dreaming?
You know as well as I, she stays higher than the moon.
And do you know your sister well?
And did you know she's drinking?
Do you know your sister well?
Talk to her soon.
Boy, do you know your sister well?
You know I think she's losing.
You know as well as I, she stays higher than the moon.
Thanks for the information.
Thanks for no thanks for the information.
Cause information's got your number two.
And do you know your brother well?
And the company he's keeping?
Do you know your brother well?
Talk to him tonight.
Or do you know your brother well?
He's very, very well.
Very, very strange, they tell.
Probably he'll go to hell.
Unless you steer him right.
Thanks for the information.
Thanks for no thanks for the information.
Cause information's got your number two.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Woo!
Well, yes, I know my daughter well.
And yes, I know she's dreaming.
Yes, I know my sister well.
That's the way it goes.
I know my sister all too well.
Yes, I know she's drinking.
How do I pigeon her for something she already knows?
And yes, I know my brother well and the company he's keeping.
Yes, I know my brother well.
He sings a different tune.
Oh, yes, I know my brother well.
I've heard it said he's queer as hell.
Pray that he's in love as well.
Fire's on the moon.
pérennés
Don't relatively eat or drink.
Let's rap your
began
Information.
Thanks for the information.
Cause information's got your number too.
Oh, it's me, dude.
Ask yourself, have you gotten right with Bob lately?
Or are you living and backsliding life of sin?
Or sinlessness, as the case may be.
It's just as bad.
All we care about is slack.
Sin is, that's to the eye of the beholder.
You know, that's a pluck it out yourself thing.
It's slack.
Slack is what Bob is interested in.
He don't care whether you've got some negative problem with sin.
He wants to know whether you are getting slack in a positive way.
Real positive.
Positive, self-actualized, prosperity-oriented slack.
Now, boys and girls.
Can you describe the event yourself as a moment of slack?
Is it in your own personality?
Say, this is slack.
That's how we judge, friends.
We judge if a person says, hey, this is happening for me.
This is slack.
It is slack.
We don't care if somebody's sticking up the weird and clad to watch your ass again.
But we're not worried about people who do have slack tonight, Dave.
Dave, tonight, we're on an evangelical, deviable witch hunt.
We want the people who don't have.
We want the people who don't have slack tonight.
We want to reach out.
To listen in.
We want to reach out to you.
We're not preaching to the choir tonight.
We're reaching out to the people who don't have any slack in their lives.
I'm in the spirit.
I can feel this man out there.
He's saying, my God, these people are out.
That's worse than a sin.
It sounds crazy.
It sounds crazy, but it's true.
The arguments we've gotten with the Blackbirds.
Sometimes when we're out in the field by ourselves, people recognize us.
My God.
You know, this is a sheer sign that slack is not a part of everyone's life.
Before.
It should be.
Slack is missing in this land of 911 and other emergencies.
Dave, can I offer a testimonial here?
You can put your, every testicle you got right there and we'll follow you.
Testimonial.
Here's my testimonial.
Boys and girls, a few years back, I was a hard-ass motorcycle riding road with a bad-ass gang.
Amen.
Lived in the bars at night.
I slept with anything that moved in the bar.
I'd go home with anything.
I ran drugs.
That's right.
I did LSD and I did heroin.
I did LSD and heroin together.
I looked terrible.
I wouldn't even go home because I didn't want my family to see how bad I'd become.
And I was living it alive and I was living it with all these people who didn't care a damn about life.
And we just lived on our motorcycles and rode from town to town.
Raping women.
Murdering.
Robbing people.
Robbing stores whenever we needed.
We just, if we wanted something, we just plucked it off the tree and we had it.
Lord have mercy.
God have mercy.
And I thought that was what life was about.
I thought I was living good.
I thought I was on top of the world.
Nobody could topple me.
But I'll tell you one thing.
Bob toppled me.
I realized one day I was slackless.
I was working too hard for all this money and whores.
And drugs.
Why should I have to pull out a gun and shoot somebody?
That's too much work.
That ain't no slack.
I found Bob.
I found real slack.
I don't have to rob the stores anymore.
I own the store.
What a, oh, what a poison.
Oh my God, what a testimonial.
What a poison testimonial.
Bob has come down into this man's life.
Can you feel how this man's life has been changed?
The sincerity.
The sincerity is flowing out of him like a river.
Oh my God, look at the car.
Say amen, brother.
It's just like the green oily pores in the back of his neck opening up to let the slack out.
Only this way they actually return to his body and come back and give him more slack.
And it was a bad night when I realized that I was slackless.
I was having a good night.
I'd murdered three store clerks.
I'd screwed 14 hookers.
I was having so much dope in my blood veins.
I was on top of the world.
It was a great night.
But I sat down.
Sat down on the curb right next to my bike.
Started laughing.
I couldn't stop laughing.
I laughed and I laughed until my heart hurt.
And then finally my heart stopped hurting and it felt great.
I just kept laughing and laughing at the world.
This form of laughter is a form of spiritual release.
And I heard the sirens in the distance.
I hopped on my bike.
I got the hell out of there.
That's what slack can do for you kids.
Slack can pull you out of that gun-toting, drug-doing, horror-messing lifestyle you got going there.
There was a day when slack for me was the realization.
Oh my God.
It's just that I'm insane.
Oh thank God.
It's not what I thought.
I was just crazy.
Yeah.
It's merely my mind is gone.
What an incredible relief.
You see all those judges sitting up in tribunal amongst you and then looking down at you and
suddenly you realize it's your own self saying, Stang, I am crazy.
You are.
We both.
You is.
I am you.
And the worst thing.
And you know that slack has saved you again.
The worst thing is that the judges, they're French.
I said to myself, well.
They have the little belt to ring.
They go ding-a-ling-a-ling.
If we don't want to get down to it, you finally have to remind yourself, if my baby don't
love me no more, I know good and well that her sister will.
And after that, sit down and think about this.
You'll never hear surf again.
What the hell are you talking about?
You just confused me.
Well, never hear.
After you hear.
Never hear.
Never hear surf music.
After these people.
Dave.
Dave, listen to me now.
And then you should hear it.
Dave, just listen.
Shut up and listen.
Okay, okay.
After these people come to that revival on March 15th at the Beecham Ballroom here,
Einstein's Secret Orchestra play a surf rock version of Britney Spears' Oops, I Did It Again.
In military uniform.
In military garb.
With the anti-girls.
With the incredible background videos.
I think it is safe then to say, you will never hear surf again.
Well.
I thought, you know, I was amidst this pool of slack.
This whirling, gathering pool of slack.
And suddenly I could see these waves cresting and breaking over my flow field tubes and so forth.
And I knew that was, you know, surf, man.
You know.
You were surfing.
You were surfing the luck plane.
And then suddenly you wiped out.
Get on that stream, baby.
Suddenly we wiped you out.
Because we pulled the rug out from any, right?
We weren't talking about what you thought.
But I look down on myself and I say, it's slack, right, Dave?
And Dave says, yeah.
It's like, so we say, not guilty, huh?
Surfing the stream of consciousness.
The fish judges.
Uh-oh.
Surfing your stream of consciousness.
Make sure you've got enough wax on that board when you surf your stream of consciousness.
But don't wipe out when you surf in the stream of consciousness.
Because there's a danger on the tube.
And don't get caught in the tube, either.
A very dangerous on the tube.
You get stuck.
And if that pipeline collapses on you when you're surfing your stream of consciousness.
Forget it.
You ain't coming back.
Don't surf like a French judge, my friend.
No.
You don't want to be a French judge.
Come on.
Grow up.
Don't be a French judge.
Yeah.
What kind of a hoedaddy are you anyway?
Into Uranus.
All the new world wonders me.
With your majestic, subdued, cackling hand.
Your people I do not understand.
So do you.
You must have put it for you.
Never hear surf music again.
Ah, some Hendrix.
And some ESO Swamp Radio.
And before that, the Rainmakers.
Rainmakers from their first album, that song, Information.
And here's some.
The Church of the Subgenius was co-founded under Bob by Dr. Philo Drummond.
And yours truly, Reverend Ivan Stank.
Dr. Drummond, Philo Drummond, the overman of church legend, is also a church doctor,
which means that he makes music which cuts into you.
And then sews you back up.
And so, let us briefly, and then again at the end of the show, enter Philo.
Excuse me, sir.
There's a call for you.
Hello, Becky.
It's your time.
Zach, I got a sporting event laid out for this Saturday.
A fire eater named Philo.
Philo, never heard of him.
I know nothing.
Nothing.
Lord, you have to be careful.
I've given me these crosses to bear, and I will carry them all the way from Jerusalem to Jackson, whichever's closer.
But hear me, Lord.
Though I walk through the valley of the shadow of death, I will choose on Philo's ass for my last supper.
Oh, oh, oh.
You know I'm covered in blood.
Oh
Oh.
Malas Shittas, Son of a Ass!
Oh, oh, oh.
You know I'm covered in blood.
Oh
Malas Shittas, Son of a Ass!
Oh.
Oh, oh, oh.
You know I'm covered in blood.
Oh
Malas Shittas, Son of a Ass!
Or is it...
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh, oh, oh, you know what I'm talking about.
Oh.
I don't need that.
Oh, oh, oh, you know what I'm talking about.
Oh.
I don't need that.
Son of a, son of a.
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh, oh, oh, you know what I'm talking about.
Motherfucker.
Oh.
Oh, oh, oh, you know what I'm talking about.
Motherfucker.
Thank you.
Cocktails, darling?
Well, maybe some fruit cocktail, then.
Milk? Hot chocolate?
Do you have any of that punch?
Punch?
Let me see now.
Oh, I'll have a martini, please.
Oh, say, isn't that a pretty little drink?
And what a cute little tiny olive.
Hello, little tiny olive.
All gone.
Well, just one more martini, then.
Oh, my goodness, another drinky.
Boy, they sure slide down, don't they?
And with two cute little olives.
Hi, little olives.
Oh, my, that was goody good good.
Oh, but I never drink three martinis.
Whee!
Oh, another rinky dinky drinky.
Dance?
I thought we were dancing.
Oh, boy, those olives are strong.
No more timonis for me.
Whee!
Who are you?
Cocktails, darling?
By somebody named Gordo.
From a collection called Frolic Diner.
We've got some more of that coming up.
I got that off of...
Some news group, probably, all.binary slack.
And speaking of which, I should do better credits.
I muffed up or wronged some credits in previous shows,
such as the El Queso All-Stars,
who are also now known as Interbulator 009,
had to, because of their comedy about the Church of Scientology,
they were banned.
And from mp3.com.
But there's another place called stationmp3.com.
Here's the URL for Interbulator 009,
which also used to be El Queso All-Stars.
That's...
Got that pencil ready?
www.stationmp3.com
Station MP3 is the one big word in the middle.
Um,
Phineas Narco and the National Cynical Network,
which did such great recent hour of slack hits
as Chap in the Hood, Mentally Deranged,
and All the Stupid People.
I gave his URL wrong.
It's actually
i.am
slash
dapper
d-a-p-p-e-r
i.am
slash
dapper
You don't have to type anything else in.
Similarly, his other URL is
listen.to
slash
voicejail
listen.to
slash
voicejail
as in
jail for voices.
Now,
into
a live subgenius revival
recorded last year or two
in Cleveland, Ohio.
Yeah!
My subgenius brothers and sisters,
I, like you, have been
saying
every time
I've seen the
broken circle
God,
believe us, man!
I, like you, have been
saying
personal saviors
D-L-O-S-N-D
Praise the
King of God
and good luck
to poor old Jesus.
Now, let's text
the praise ball.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hoo!
There's a rock and roll
Jesus, friends.
Don't you get hung up
on that
poor little old
there's so many Jesuses.
The busy buddy
school mom Jesus.
That's only one of them.
You've got to
mend as many
Jesuses as you've got
yourselves inside
of your head.
The hot rod!
There's a surfing
Jesus, friends.
There's a hot rod
Jesus.
There's a football
playing Jesus.
There's a muscle
builder Jesus
that can tear
phone books in half.
There's a
there's a
transvestite
Jesus
that you think
was a woman.
And there's a real
woman Jesus.
There's a
transsexual
Jesus
that puts a
male Jesus
that wanted to be
a woman
and then vice versa.
And there's a
lesbian Jesus
that was born man.
And there's a
Jesus that's a
veterinarian
and a Jesus
that's a
that just cleans up
after the elephants
that were served.
Friends,
there's a
corporate
CEO
fat cat
greedy Jesus.
He's a
president of the
board of heaven
incorporating
there's a
janitor Jesus
that works for him
and makes his guts
round.
There's a
Jesus for everybody.
hooker Jesus
that you pay
any amount of money
to get with.
And there's a
John Jesus
who's after her
right now.
And there's a
guilty Jesus
that feels bad
for what he did.
And there's a
happy Jesus
that's proud
of doing the
very same thing.
And friends,
there's bound to be
a Jesus for you
that's probably
weirder than anything
I could ever imagine.
And I can imagine
a lot, friends.
So,
you just be ready
because you never know
when that Jesus
is going to stand
up behind you.
You don't know
when Bob's looking
and you don't know
when Jesus is looking.
I wouldn't worry
too much about Bob.
He ain't that well connected.
He ain't even
forgiving sins.
forgetting his sins.
The big word,
forgiving.
Besides,
he brings excuses,
not forgiveness.
But Jesus,
friends,
he will forgive.
I guess he
believes in sin.
Some of them
depends on
the Jesus
depends on you,
friends.
And the Jesus
that I heard about
never said
that you had to
go through
some middleman
to talk to him.
As a matter of fact,
the original Jesus
warned him,
said,
don't go
telling everybody
about this shit
because they'll
misunderstand it
completely
and try to get
everybody to believe.
That's the book
from the original
Jesus,
friends.
Praise God,
Jesus.
Praise God.
Open some
of us,
people.
Let's pray.
Praise God.
Praise your money
and praise your
price of five women
and the five
sacrifice men
love déjà vies
and the five
beer
air we still
have to breathe.
Right, Bob?
Happy Sunday.
God Micheal
and Paul伝
Whoo!
Yeah.
Oh, yes, dear friends.
A little bit of a broken circle gospel deluxe playing there at the, where was it?
The Blind Lemon Tavern here in Cleveland about a year ago.
Thank goodness there's this different kind of dinner roll.
The subgenius agenda.
Through the leadership of J.R. Bob Dobbs, his vision of a 22nd century America where subgeniosity is the subgenius lifestyle.
Dobbs has repeatedly addressed subgeniuses saying,
I have a vision.
And you are part of it.
It's lovely.
It's too many.
They're all right.
I'm moving on.
Oh, no.
Took me some.
Don't think about the part in this guy.
Move on, move on to the job.
We finally got a piece of the pie.
Yeah.
Oh, boy.
Oh, my God.
Remember me?
Say, how about a little...
Oops.
I'll get it.
Don't worry.
I got it.
I'll have a drink.
Thank you.
Oh, boy.
Oh, my God.
It feels like the top of my head is coming off.
Say, tell me, what time does flow come on?
See?
Oh, she does?
Oh, I wish I'd have been here last night.
Boy, oh, boy.
That was a good one.
How about a glass of...
Wait.
Hold my seat.
I don't want the water at all.
I'll be right back.
I'm back.
Oh.
I'll have the water now.
Thank you.
That's better.
I feel better now.
I mean you.
Thank you.
This is disgusting.
It's so wonderful here.
And you've joined us here in the beautiful world.
Here at the base of the beautiful world.
I was up at that time.
God, it was terrible.
But don't you feel cleansed?
The 1934 four-door automobile.
It just opens up your pores.
And your birth of...
And Clyde Barrow.
Inspire all over you.
Ah, yes.
Echo now.
Obviously, those girls were just brainwashed idiots.
Yep, it's true.
We're just brainwashed idiots.
But isn't that true of most of them?
Most of them, yes.
And it always is us or them.
If you listen to the earlier shows, I mean, I'm talking 15 years ago.
It's always us or them.
We brought it up all the time.
It's us or them.
And I know you're one of us.
Yeah.
And we aren't them.
And I haven't heard your voice before.
I haven't heard my voice before either.
But what difference does it make?
What voice is this?
Oh, this is tape number 643 voice.
You know this subgenius stuff?
Do I?
Yeah.
And I love you.
Are you asleep now?
I love you too.
Love you too.
Yeah.
You love me too.
She loves both of us.
Love you.
I'm like subgenius.
Thanks.
You are subgenius?
You're up my handle.
I don't know if she knew you did.
But you can make it.
Messages are erased after 48 hours.
Okay, thanks, thanks.
That is crime.
Yeah.
Crime must be dealt with forcefully.
Stop!
Yeah, we're getting ready to fold the show up and put it in a little drawer.
Until next week.
We have it.
We still have 12 minutes.
Of show last.
Part of the show usually comes in the last 30 seconds.
Continue listening.
That's why you have to hang on to the bitter end.
Copy the show.
It's actually posted on the internet in several places.
I found a site out there that has copies of this show in real audio format.
I'm trying to remember the site name.
I should be able to say that.
We can every show.
We can tag that site.
During this show.
Yeah.
Oh, but I know a place.
If you go to www.subgenius.com,
at subgenius.com, there is a link for the sounds.
So you choose sounds, and that takes you to the area for the hour of slack.
And at the bottom of the hour of slack, there is something called Subgenius Web Ring.
Subgenius Web Ring.
And you click to the right of the web ring, and it takes you.
The first site it takes you to is a site where a guy stores a whole bunch of puzzling evidence radio shows on real audio format.
And he has lots of them with Dr. Philo Drummond, who is his favorite character, I understand.
And he has collected all of those out there.
And his website.
Because of his strange affection for Dr. Drummond, for whatever that may be.
We'll have to send him the video of the desert, in which he can see the overman in various incarnations.
In fact, I need to borrow that mask from you so he can keep showing up, keep showing up, keep showing up everywhere for no reason at all.
And then a music video would happen.
Yeah.
There's got to be a music video.
For each character.
Leave a trace.
I like the clocks out, man.
And you can get more information about the Church of the Subgenius.
Yes, you can.
I appreciate that, man.
Yeah.
Okay, now we're getting on down.
That's the Puzzling Evidence Show.
Friday in the wee hours of the morning on KPFA Berkeley.
Uh-huh.
We'll be right back.
Make a lot of noise.
Yeah.
The earth is big.
Suddenly, there was no more oxygen in the water.
When you're dead, you shut up like hell.
When you make a lot of noise.
You make a hell of a lot of noise.
Because when you die.
When you die, my friend, you shut up.
Like hell.
In the house of the sick.
It's because of Dante.
I want to be saved.
No, no, no.
I just got back from the writers' meeting.
Settle down, everybody.
I just got back from the writers' meeting, okay?
Hey.
You're the man with the changes?
We're going to reformat the whole show.
The bleep all methane all methane show?
I know.
Look.
Uh, here's the story.
Uh, wait.
Who's here, first of all?
Oh, everybody.
Don't worry about that part.
All day in church.
It's just like one address.
Nonca Dave.
Pop Bull Davina.
Chaz and Chasmina.
Nikki and Nick.
Papa Gano and Papa Gano.
Okay.
We and her consort.
And the guy who make the sandwich for me.
Oh, jeez.
And me.
All of us.
And, and, and.
Filippo, you have a lovely singing voice.
I think he's.
His name is Luigi.
Legu, thanks for the music.
And Chaz, thanks for the show.
Ahuga.
Do we have the changes for the bleep all module?
We'll be back to pick you up later.
But, uh, I guess, uh, so we're all making what?
$640,000 an episode now, right?
That's right.
Okay.
The thing is, uh, the commercial people, the people downtown, you know, the people who
were, uh, talking fast and thinking large.
I am fearless.
And I think we all want to think that way.
And, uh, you know, go in a progressive fashion, uh, from now on.
Uh, we're going to get a more traditional format.
Uh, first of all, I think this whole set has to be replaced by, uh, uh, you know, like
a neighbor's kitchen set, let's say.
Okay.
You're talking about a lot of carpentry there.
You're talking about union guys.
This already looks like my neighbor's kitchen.
Is that a gym neighbor set now?
Is that a gym neighbor set from Andy Griffith or a gym neighbor set from, uh, from Gomer
Pyle USMC?
Yeah.
What about that?
I think more of that line, but, but, but, but.
Think of that.
Like, is it the gas station?
A bus station.
A gas station or a barracks?
Everybody at the table at the same time for the wacky comedy.
I go for the barracks.
Bus station, luncheon.
That's what I think he's thinking.
A bus station, luncheon, and everybody meet everybody five times.
Nobody know anybody.
Oh, and Dave, don't worry.
We will bring in the bear on a regular basis because the demographics reveal that the bear
has gotten actually, uh, geez, he's gotten 10 times more ratings than even Julia Roberts.
Wait, I actually like the bear a little more than you, Dave.
Can Dave play Sergeant Carter?
Oh, boy.
Yes.
In fact, uh, we were thinking of that.
Uh, good thing you brought that up, Chaz.
I like your thinking.
You're thinking on your feet.
I think that caused a lot of damage.
Even though you're a drummer.
I'm still taking him.
Do you use your feet to drum, uh, Chaz?
I don't know.
No, you're a keyboard guy, I guess, more than that.
I'm more of a self-flagellator.
By the way, which one of you guys is pink?
Oh, three of us.
We're all standing here right now.
We've got the changes, and it looks like the first scene is out.
It looks like part of the second page here on the bottom where you use the word asshole
is out.
And I think in the bottom of 92 here, I think the end of the...
Episode where you have the luncheon blow up, I think we need to replace that idea.
Well, the thing is that that was written, of course, before the big tragic, uh, evidence
of, uh...
This sounds like they're planning the last episode of Twin Peaks.
Yeah, yeah.
They were sure they'd get funding for another season.
You know, it's a new attitude, of course.
There's only a course to get that kind of regulation.
That's showbiz!
Until next week!
Keep your head on time!
Thanks, Nicky, for coming!
And for two drinks this week!
Back in the way!
Commercial show!
I'm so glad everybody's wetting themselves together.
And you're sacking the saddle!
Wetting themselves together?
Yes.
I feel better, don't you?
You realize that I'm only talking like this, you know, for commercial consideration.
Well, when you consider all the spots for a bit, all the bad news we're gonna have,
it looks like we're gonna be, like, short 35 seconds.
How are we gonna clear this?
What are we gonna do with 35 seconds of dead air?
Insert transition here.
Well, they had it coming to him. He was crazy.
Never hear surf music again.
tu tu tu tu tu tu tu tu
to tu tu tu tu tu tu tu to
by, by, by, by by my side
Positively disgusting!