Like to drop by the fantastic bag. Well, welcome to the hour of slack.
Brady, Bob, Gold, and Connie drag. Yes, welcome to the hour of slack.
Ah, yes, dear friends. Because we're in the middle of a cross-country trip,
using the iVan as a recording studio, this hour of slack, number 1,311, will actually be a glorious
rerun of one of the greatest episodes of Bob's Slack Time Funhouse from WREK Atlanta,
Reverend Susie the Flusie's incredible apocalypse special. Prepare to have everything blown.
Susie the Flusie.
Susie's amazing collage should get believers all pumped up for X-Day, July 5th, when everyone else
will be destroyed, along with every other thing on earth that subgeniuses don't keep for their
collections. Speaking of which, I personally have dibs on Wisteria, the campground in southern Ohio,
where both X-Day and Starwood are now held. In fact, we just stayed at Wisteria,
Wisteria.org.
By the way, to finalize plans for our July 5th weekend festival and subgenius mating event.
And it all looks as great as Susie's X-Day special show sounds as heard here. Praise Bob.
I just want to start a flame in your heart.
Oh, in my heart, I have but one desire.
And that one is you.
No other will do.
I've lost all ambition for worldly acclaim. I just want to be the one you love.
And with your admission that you feel the same, I'll have reached the goal I'm dreaming of.
Believe.
Believe me.
I don't want to set the world on fire.
I just want to start a flame in your heart.
I've lost all ambition for worldly acclaim.
I just want to be the one you love.
And with your admission that you feel the same, I'll have reached the goal I'm dreaming of.
Believe me.
I don't want to set the world on fire.
I just want to start a flame in your heart.
A flame in your home
Oh, no.
Help us.
Help us now.
No.
Tomstown.
Crap.
I'm still in Tomstown.
How is this world never going to end?
I want my apocalypse now.
This old earth ain't gonna stop rolling.
No.
Round the sun, boy.
This old earth ain't gonna stop rolling.
No.
Just because you're gone, boy.
Oh.
All the winds are gonna keep on blowing.
Rivers gonna keep on flowing.
Grass is gonna keep on growing, too.
And I'll be loving someone new.
This old earth ain't gonna stop rolling.
No.
Through the sky, boy.
This old earth ain't gonna stop rolling.
No.
Or just say goodbye, boy.
All the birds are gonna keep on singing.
No.
The bells are gonna keep on ringing.
The love is gonna keep on swinging, too.
And I'll be loving someone new.
The final hour is approaching for the people of Earth.
Hear this.
You are to command the forces that pop up.
No one must survive.
That's the farthest it's done the boat since Betty.
The love must survive.
The love must be mad for sure this morning.
I wonder where Eddie's pitching them.
Every one of them is bound for the earth.
You mean that little old dream in place?
Carrie, don't you know the earth is a new scandal?
Everybody's talking about it.
The Lord is mad as can be at that measly little planet.
Or I should say the scum that's on it.
That's mankind down there.
They must be scum, too, to get the Lord so walked up.
He's certainly letting them feel the wrath.
Ain't it a shame to plague the Lord that way?
They've been begging for what they're getting.
My brother flew down to bring up a saint the other day.
And he said from what he can see, most of the population down there's done made the devil their king.
And they're working in three shifts for him.
Don't make me come over there.
Listen not to the devil, for he makes his life with the truth and for moose.
You promised me no one would get hurt.
Forget it.
When may I want a horse?
Oh, God, I've been misinformed.
Maybe you just better forget the whole thing.
Get your smarts.
Smart?
Oh, my.
Anyway.
No one could have believed that human affairs were being watched from the timeless worlds of space.
No one could have dreamed we were being scrutinized as someone with a microscope studies creatures that swarm and multiply in a drop of water.
Few men even considered the possibility of life on other planets.
And yet, across the gulf of space, minds immeasurably superior to ours regarded this earth with envious eyes.
And slowly and surely, they drew their plans against us.
Are you serious, sir?
I mean, do you really think the world's going to end this afternoon?
Yes, in just over one minute and 35 seconds.
Isn't there anything we can do?
No, nothing.
Well, I always thought we were meant to lie down or put a paper bag over our head or something.
If you like, yes.
Will that help?
No.
I've been hearing something on the streets the last couple of weeks.
Weird stuff.
Some sort of epidemic of violence, what they've been saying.
I was talking to one old boy.
He told me they got some sort of cult up there.
End of the world kind of stuff.
I mean, the cults – your college, the church, yeah, whatever, doesn't matter.
It's like the drake, because they're saying, there's a name to the word that we aunque
they may call it the impầnant malayo, it's no longer the same a there.
Looking at this video, I think just at half an hour for it.
Don't need a brain cause you got a G
And it keeps you in line
And it makes you divine
Wake up, get up
Who's gonna save the world?
Wake up, I'm better
Who's gonna save us?
Could it be somebody famous?
Or just a regular joke?
Tell me where I hear about
Who will protect us?
And who's gonna save the world?
We are going to save the universe
Goodbye
We are full of ground
We are grown up men
We are all happy
We've made some reasons
It is our mission
It is our task
It's all beyond
The future
We are gone
Inside the universe
Inside
Tradition
We are born and From this perspective
We are born of light
We are away, from where place
Inside the universe
Inside
both
Well, maybe next time.
Take heed that no man deceive you,
for many shall come in my name,
saying, I am Christ,
and shall deceive many,
and ye shall hear of wars
and rumors of wars.
See that ye be not troubled,
for all these things must come to pass,
but the end is not yet.
Now I'll be the first to admit
that the odds of actually encountering
an aberrant phenomenon are infinitesimal.
But if you've been listening at all,
you've come to realize
that statistics dictate
that all of the weirdest events
will take place in the end times,
i.e. tonight.
So if you want to be a survivor,
you will prepare for the impossible.
And there shall be famines
and pestilences
and earthquakes in diverse places.
All these are the beginning of sorrows.
If these things that we're seeing in our day
are merely the beginning of sorrows,
think what it's going to be
when the end time is really upon us.
The sky,
the sky is red,
but the sun,
the sun is red,
but the sun is red,
because you too
discovered
and found
the treasure
of the world.
Therefore,
ulating
your field
theVES
then killed.
he came based
story
his boss,
We're down!
How many years, Lord?
How many days?
Can the world go on this way?
How many trials, Lord?
How many tears?
Cause we always live in fear
Oh, there'll come a day when
Hatred will cease
And all the world will have peace, Lord
A flare spurting out from Mars
Bright green
Drawing a green mist behind it
A beautiful, but somehow disturbing sight
Ogilvy, the astronomer
Assuredly, we were in no danger
He was convinced
There could be no living thing
On that remote, forbidding planet
The chances of anything coming from Mars
Are a million to one, he said
Are a million to one
But still, there he comes
Drink up
Why three pints?
Muscle relaxant
You'll need it
Did I do something wrong today?
Or has the world always been like this
And I've been too wrapped up in myself to notice?
I'll try to explain
Drink up
How long have we known each other?
Five years, maybe six
Most of it seemed to make some kind of sense at the time
All right
How would you react if I said that I'm not from Guildford after all
But from a small planet somewhere in the vicinity of Betelgeuse?
I don't know
Why, do you think it's the sort of thing you feel you're likely to say?
Drink up, the world's about to end
This must be Thursday
I never could get the hang of Thursdays
On this particular Thursday
Things were moving quietly through the ionosphere
Many miles above the surface of the planet
Several huge, yellow, slab-like somethings
Huge as office blocks
Silent as birds
Which hung in the air exactly the same way that bricks don't
The planet was almost totally unaware of their presence
They went unnoticed at Goonhilly
They passed over Cape Canaveral without a blip
And Woomera and Jodrell Bank looked straight through them
Which was a pity because it was exactly the sort of thing they'd been looking for all these years
Arthur, of course, was totally unaware of them
He was only aware of a sudden
Terrible, crashing noise
This displeases me greatly
What's the total?
18,960 for the morning
And that's including the village with the fortune tellers
They certainly can breathe fast
Look at them there
Squirming and fighting and bearing false witness
Why did I ever make them?
Should I get some more thunderbolt?
No, they don't do no good
There's gotta be something else
Oh, how about this?
What would it be if you was to doom them all again
Like that time you sent down the flood?
I bet that would make them mine
You know how much good the flood did?
How about cleaning up the whole mess up
And starting all over again with some new kind of animal?
And admit that I'm licking?
Oh, no, of course not, Lord
Bitch, I'll f*** your ass up
Run, run, run, but you shouldn't leave her alone
And I'll pour it on, a tooth for a tooth
Both for me and I'll set you free
Raccoon, brother, raccoon
Well, the back of your face in the middle is
A provision to our nature
All the children
People are stunned, confused
They stagger about the malls
My gosh, it's like seeing
Truth
In advertising
Is this the apocalypse?
I don't know
Six pints
Right, keep the change
From a five, I thank you, sir
You've only got seven minutes left to spend it
Four, would you please tell me what the hell is going on?
Drink up, you've got three pints to get through
Three at lunchtime
Time is an illusion
Lunchtime doubly served
Drink up
So, you're confronting some shimmering crap
That your hypothalamus can't put into a category
And you've got about five minutes before your mind implodes permanent like
What do you do?
Well, since you've approached it with no basis other than some half-assed so-called objective perspective, you're dead
Try begging it for mercy
It never works, but it's worth a try
You've got nothing better to do while you die, so give it a shot
Hey, instead of writhing around and being a snob, you've got a chance to show your
in your own excrement wishing you'd paid attention,
why don't you pay attention right now
and enjoy writhing in your own excrement
by memorizing the following indirect observation technique.
They took me off! They got my truck!
It's all over, people!
We don't have a prayer!
Oh, man, yeah.
So, here we find ourselves
standing at the cosmic crossroads again.
Thumbs out expectantly as our eyes search the heavens
for the supernova light of the oncoming exosplea
and wishing with every fiber of our beings
that this time it will work!
This time we shall escape!
This time!
Oh!
Bob!
Please make it work!
This time I can't take it anymore!
July 5th at 7 a.m., Bob.
I'll be there.
Will you?
Have you seen Bob?
He ought to be here soon.
Yeah? Well, maybe.
Yeah, maybe.
Bob, you are testing my patience.
Oh, you're telling me.
If he doesn't get me off the planet this time,
I'm gonna rip his half-toed ass to shreds
and get me a decent savior.
Oh, my God!
Okay.
Girl, what have you done?
Beth?
She's dead!
Buried under the rubble!
Why?
Satan!
Why did you take one of your own?
Oh!
Doomed!
Thank you.
throughout the day. I rate editors from all over the country were insistently
demanding more specific information. Newsman from the wire services, reporters
from local and out-of-town newspapers were hemming me in, he laboring me with
questions for which I had no answers. For the first couple of hours we at the
press desk had a terrible time getting the story straight ourselves, but bit by
bit I managed to piece it together. There had been both visual and radar contacts.
Andrews Field, the Air Force installation, had radar returns similar
to those on the CAA radar. Jets had been scrambled in an attempt to make an
intercept of the UFOs, but they had not been successful.
Yes, yes, but can you see the saucers? They should be there.
What's that? What's that? Suicidal impulses and remission? Doctor, another
patient cured. I'll say. Is he gone? Oh yeah.
Oh yeah.
He was over one attack. Now he's still alive. Still alive. Screaming in the streets.
But he was still alive. He's back to his place. He's okay.
He was over one attack. Now he's still alive.
Still alive. Screaming in the streets. But he was over one attack.
But he was over one attack. He was over one attack.
Still alive.
Still alive and screaming.
This is all TV stuff.
This is all radio stuff.
Still watching too.
Outlandish! Sal
still alive! It's screaming in the streets. What is it about!
They're frustration they didn't be coming.
Hauling! Sal
still alive! Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Sal I you talk to him, he kicks himself behind.
If OK…
.
. . . . . . . get this thing over here, and finish the job right here, if you want to.
Sal . If you will put this down here, that's the only solution.
Assignment, come, you smack bastard!
Oh, you know.
He's a f***er, that fella.
The hammering from the pit and the pounding of guns grew louder.
My fear rose at the sound of someone creeping into the house.
Then I saw it was a young artilleryman, weary, streaked with blood and dirt.
Anyone here?
Come in.
Here, drink this.
Thank you.
What's happened?
They wiped us out.
Hundreds dead.
Maybe thousands.
The heatwave.
The Martians.
They were inside the hoods of machines they'd made.
Massive metal things on legs.
Giant machines that walked.
They attacked us.
They wiped us out.
Machines?
Fighting machines.
Picking up men and bashing them against trees.
Just hunks of metal.
But they knew exactly what they were doing.
Hmm.
There was another cylinder game last night.
Yes.
As it looked bound for London.
London?
Carrie.
I hadn't dreamed there could be danger to Carrie and her father so many miles away.
I must go to London at once.
They're made.
Got to report to headquarters.
If there's anything left of it.
They're money because it's true.
It will be the end.
The apocalypse.
We're doomed.
Doomed.
It's all over, people.
Ah!
This party is over.
The apocalypse.
Great.
And I ain't begging.
I got a whole lot of shaking going on.
Well, I did shake.
I beg you to shake it.
I did shake it.
Beg you to shake it.
I did shake.
Don't you let it break now.
Shake it.
I'm a roll.
A whole lot of shaking going on.
Whoa!
There was a meltdown
happened last Tuesday
Now it's second chance to lose
It's just me and the jukebox
And it's playing a mournful tune
Just keeps on playing
those radiation blues
When the sun went down last Wednesday
I went walking in the park
Didn't mind there were no street lights
I was blowing in the dark
Just call me Glower
Got radiation blues
They had a wake for Jake LaBarber
One long drink and one short breath
He went and shot himself this morning
Cause the whole town lost its hair
Came out in handfuls
Got radiation blues
Ain't no use in going no place
Home and town is just like here
Boss man really fixed us this time
Think I'll have another beer
Ain't no use singing
Those radiation blues
the way of the world
Is it just me
Or am I picking up
Some negative vibes out there?
I saw the earth
Turn brown and die
I saw
But I couldn't cry
Everything I knew so well
Disappeared
Before
I knew
I was calling out your name.
Calling out your name.
Bob!
That's what the world is today
The South wherein an all time high
You're both walking round with your heads in the sky
Cities aflame in a summertime
So our feet goes
F-o-l-u-tion.
Revolution down control the size of soul
Shooting rockets to the moon
Kids going up to zoom
There's not enough wire to open that door
Politicians say more taxes will solve everything
And the band played on
So I'm going to never, ever be alone
When I get to the bottom, I go back to the top of the slide
When I stop and I turn and I couldn't go right
Till I get to the bottom and I sing again
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah
Oh, do you think you want me to love you?
Coming down faster, miles above you
Come on, tell me, tell me, tell me
Come on, tell me the answer
Will you make me a lover, but you ain't no answer
Oh, do you think you want me to love you?
Come on, tell me, tell me, tell me
Catched with burning sunlight
On the inside of my eye
Will I burst into oblivion?
Burn in Armageddon
Will I
Flaming ashes
Light the sky
Oh, where will I be?
Where will I be?
Where?
When darkness descends on me?
Where will I be?
So we're living in a real crazy world, my friends.
We're living in a world where everyone is crying out for deliverance.
Now, many times you will see the president standing there in the Rose Garden with two of these smiling men from the East on each side.
One has got a tablecloth on his head, and he poses, they smile, and then they put there in the newspaper, uh, a priest.
I've got no problem with the peace treaties that they sign.
I have a problem with the people who signed the peace treaties.
Uh, that's, that's reality.
George, you should be ashamed of yourself.
And how.
Recently, another 400 scientists, scholars, businessmen, and politically-democratic leaders have been in the same situation.
They've met in Texas to ponder the problems facing mankind.
They said, it is a gloomy world indeed.
The energy crisis, famine, the financial problems of New York City, drug abuse, and other unrelated problems are all portents of the present darkness.
And the Bible says...
I am the God of Hellfire, and I bring you fire.
...woven destruction cometh upon them and they shall not escape.
That's what the Bible says here.
There shall be famine, pestilences in different places.
And I don't have to tell you these things.
You know, if there ever is a time that Bible prophecy is confirmed right before our eyes
is now, place, pestilences, and things like that.
Yeah, now the boss says this is a very bad thing for the country, because this contract
starts after the war.
And the boss has got an idea with all this Nazi and Jap money that, well, I haven't got
it quite straight, but anyway, the boss says it's a bad thing for the country.
So far you've told me what the boss has found out.
What did you find out?
I don't need the terrorists.
Boy, you're hotter than a firecracker on the 5th of July.
Who is it?
All right, listen up, everyone.
I want you to calmly file towards the exit.
That's it.
Everybody run.
Just walk.
Now if we just stay calm, no one's going to be harmed by the huge bomb that's going to
explode any minute.
LUCAS!
Here's the car!
It's、
PREVIOUS HARM,
BY LUCAS!
THIS WAS THE ARMS AND SHOT'S PROTEIN WHbrush Crime.
We have no alternative.
We must use all our nuclear weapons.
May I suggest we join in prayer?
I can't see how prayers will help.
Oh, yes. We can at least save our souls.
We must either attack them now or surrender to them.
Some more trouble.
The military men want to use all our nuclear weapons
and then resist them to the bitter end.
We'll be wiped out by the radioactivity.
We have a tiger at the front door and a wolf at the back.
What is that supposed to mean?
With the temptation, not in place of the temptation,
but with the temptation,
also make a way to escape
that you may be able to bear it.
See, lest the demons come on you,
oh, I mean, they've got power as you find out.
They can really come upon you.
But in order that you may be able to bear
the amount of temptation that he allows to come upon you,
he's made an escape route.
But if you don't climb in the capsule
and fire the thing off,
you won't escape.
And to many of us,
refuse to pull the D-ring,
that's what they call it when the ejection seat
blows you out of the canopy.
When your plane's on fire,
you've got to blow the ejection seat.
When it gets too hot,
you've got to pull the D-ring, as they say,
and blow it out, get out of there.
When these fiery trials are upon us
and the devil is tempting hot,
you can't stay in the middle of all the environment
of the demons and the temptations.
And wallowing the thing,
you've got to take the escape route.
Hey, what about Major Kong?
On the way!
I like the view!
Basic instructions before leaving Earth.
Hey, hey, hey!
That's what you teach those kids.
Basic instructions before leaving Earth.
Are you there?
If you have any red pills left,
take them now.
Stay out of our medicine cabinet!
I'm sorry.
Yes, very much.
Thanks.
Setonium, polonium, and thallium,
and gallium, and bismuth, two-eleven.
We've got some carbon-14,
and astatine, and larynxium, two-five-seven.
Kerbelium, brachylium, and strontium-90,
and iodine-131.
We've got some technetium,
plutetium, brantium, radon,
and a little bit of radium.
Someday I'm gonna blow you up!
Get outta here.
I'm taking the freeway on my way home
Bringing my money, clothes and all my charm
Going to take freeway won't take very long
You know I'm going home today
Something that I have to say
I've been gone too long
And the people who came may be gone
I just have to say
Play the violin for me
So I'm taking the freeway
Gotta find my way back home
Use the right lane now
Soon I'll be home
I'm taking the freeway on my way home
You know I'm going home today
Something that I have to say
I've been gone too long
And the people who came may be gone
I just have to say
Play the violin for me
You know I'm going home today
Something that I have to say
I'm taking the freeway on my way home
Use the right lane now
Soon I'll be home
When I was young I used to dream of other worlds up there
I thought the god who made us all surely made others somewhere
I closed my eyes as I stared at the sky
Let my mind take leave of this body and fly
Over the yards and roofs of my small hometown
Up higher I'd go and from the clouds look down
To see the small spot of the earth that was mine
The street where I lived was but a thin line
And in those moments of fantasy I recall
How I realized my place in the scheme of things was small
A fifth machine appeared on the far bank
It raised itself to full height
Flourished the funnel high in the air
And the ghostly terrible wind blew it away
A terrible heat ray struck the town
Look!
My god, what's that I see just there?
Swirling and turning in the one-night air
Those lights keep on flashing me
They paralyze me
I can't seem to move but
I still can see
I'm going much lighter, but
I'm a heater off the ground
I'm being pulled toward the ship
Whirling round and round
I'm drawn to an opening by a powerful beam
This can't be happening
It must be a dream
A dream!
Ahhh!
This ain't right, Bob.
Nothing's right anymore.
Go on.
Go on, get going.
Didn't I warn them?
Pray I said.
Destroy the devil, I said.
They wouldn't listen.
I could have saved the world.
But now it's too late.
Too late.
Me!
I'm a rocket.
Like a Saturn 5.
Like Apollo 9.
I'm a rocket.
Ready to rock.
Ready to roll.
Come on, come on.
Give me mission control.
I said I'm ready to rock.
Ready to roll.
Come on, come on.
Give me mission control.
Rock!
Go!
Like a spaceship
Going in the sky
Like a sun and sleep
On a mountain top
I'm ready to rock
Ready to rock
Ready to roll
Come on, come on
Give me the control
I said I'm ready to rock
Ready to roll
Come on, come on
Come on
Baby, I'm ready to rock
I said I'm ready to rock
Ready to roll
Come on, come on
Let the ghost walk upon me
Baby, I'm ready to rock
I said I'm ready to rock
I'm ready to rock
Because of my previous experience,
I was assigned to unidentified flying objects.
I was back in the flying saucer business.
Space cowboys
Flying up into the sky
Well, I'm flying up into the sky
Space cowboys
Bet you never thought I'd resign
Good lord, I'm rocking
Do the
Finally, the hot лиш, girls
Ready to roll
Get up and down
Ready to rock
To sleep
פ
It helped
What do you say?
Awoo
Till we meet again.
Good night.
Happy dreams to you.
May they all come true.
Till our next canoe.
Sleep tight.
As each day goes by.
Keep your wishes.
Look out of your pipe and smoke it, whore.
I don't know why I feel this way.
As though someone should pay.
For I'm so lonely.
I'm so empty.
I too am dead.
Bitch, bitch, bitch.
Don't come crying to me, lady.
You should have spent that membership money while you had the chance.
Oh, but I have a feeling nothing could have persuaded you
to come over to the subgenius side of the force.
Not even listening to things like,
we heard tonight, like Jeff Wayne's War of the Worlds rock opera
with that narration by Richard Burton.
The BBC radio version of Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy.
The A's asking us who's gonna save the world.
And the swingin' love corpses telling us that they're going to save the universe.
This time, maybe.
Oh, maybes.
I wanna have Dr. P. Ellis of the lymph nodes.
Institute destroying the world.
Too bad that didn't take.
Mofongo jumped in with the end of the world.
And a little bit of the temptations of ball confusion.
Some Ruby 3.
A little bit of the tinklers.
Talking about those link rays.
And then that creepy Wayne Williams era darkness over Atlanta number was by Dave Barton.
Followed by BGK.
A Dutch hardcore band with no limbs.
And then a little speeded up Jerry Lee lunatic.
Survival Alliance came in with radiation blues.
And then a little bit of Zeta Reticuli.
A love story.
Oh, man.
You're so lucky you're only going to die July 5th.
You didn't have to listen to that whole thing.
And then that was a Don Harrison version of Helter Skelter.
Don Barnett was this strange lisping creature talking about Bob and his escape hatch.
A little more Survival Alliance.
Oh, some Noel Coward telling us the party was over.
The Griffin was trying to take the freeway.
Spin Out came on like a rocket.
And Space Cowboy 2.
And then there was a little Doris Day.
Oh, I can smell it.
And the air seekers.
And it smells like breakfast.
Oh, the lure of galactic destruction is enough to break even me out of my usual reclusive shell.
To my total astonishment, I find myself looking forward to the festivities.
Oh, yes, at the Gathering of the Tribes.
Oops, somewhere in South Ohio now.
Subgenius.com has details.
We will enact the beautiful and glorious.
Rituals and traditions of the Yeti people.
And prepare for our deliverance in the stars.
Oh, it's probably too late to write for free information.
But you can check out Subgenius.com for a listing of all the events.
Yeah, that's Subgenius throwing another I'm the richest man in the universe party.
I knew that son of a bitch was alive.
Oh, yeah, and there will be the usual blood wrestling and hellish human sacrifices.
Plus all the nudity and frappy we've come to expect from this church.
So, seekers, good night.
For the path is over now.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Let's get the hell out of here.