Achtung! Achtung! All cruise cars be on the lookout for strange invaders
believed to have landed from outer space somewhere in the vicinity of Berlin.
Car input, computers, tapes, all go.
Place of the encycling normal cryogenic systems go.
Cathodes at 67,000 volts and steady.
Time selector set at present.
All set, Al. Stand by for a time synchronization.
Standing by.
Date, 5 July, 64.
Time, 11 hours, 14 minutes.
Counting.
5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
Mark.
Right.
And by to activate image stabilizer switch.
Ready.
Switch on.
This is an hour that comes to all,
except in states that don't have daylight saving.
I, sir, was referring to your...
So genius.
Power of...
The dead.
Kill me.
Never laugh.
I heard there's a man down there.
He pays folks money, singing to his cane.
They say he pays next year.
If you play real good.
Join us now for the Bob Hour, coming to you from the campus of Bob.
Join us now for the Bob Hour, coming to you from the campus of Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
Study the essence of Bob, which, by the way, is the official name of our savior, according to the flesh.
You've been listening to Bob onvenue,
coming to you from the campus of Bob.
Spirit preferably the lion.
Send a check, send a.
Manly take me easy.
All, until death I fall apart.
Bob's skin.
Bob.
Just blows me away.
Bob's skin.
Bob.
Just blows me away.
All night and day.
Join us now for the Bob Hour coming to you from the campus of Bob.
Our speaker today is Bob.
What the hell is going on?
Join us now for the Bob Hour coming to you from the campus of Bob.
Our speaker today is Bob.
Sponsored by Bob.
Why, this is bigger than the Whispering Steeple in Kansas City.
It's bigger than the Headless Ballet Dancer in Dublin, Ireland.
And it's even bigger than the day our dear Teresa received that personal message from Rudolph Valentino in Toledo.
Cool!
What is it?
To steer, you gotta turn the handlebars.
Break if you must.
Do it!
Okay, here we go.
Ten, nine, eight...
Wait a minute!
What are you doing?
I'm putting a frog in the room!
Rock it!
Is that a good idea?
It is if you want to be the owner of a frog that breaks the world record for traveling in space!
Is the frog gonna be okay?
I guess so.
This is just a test anyway.
Besides, he has a space suit!
It looks like he's just wrapped in tinfoil.
That is correct!
Let the countdown continue!
Eight!
Seven!
Five!
Wait!
Seven!
Five!
No, wait!
Stop!
I don't like this.
I didn't build this rocket just so you could send some poor little defenseless frog into outer space.
Well, that's why I bought it!
Besides, this is just a test!
The real launch comes later!
And then my little frog will break a world record!
For being the only frog to fly!
Into outer space!
Then I'll be even more famous than I am now!
You're famous now?
I thought you were just kidding.
But it doesn't matter!
I still don't like this.
Five, four, three, two, one, blast off!
Wow!
Look how powerful that engine is!
This is a great rocket engine you've built for me!
It pushed so much air!
It knocked that statue right over!
Unbelievable!
Look at this frog!
He's scared to death!
Beware the Beast-Man, for he is the Devil's Pawn.
Alone among God's primates, he kills for sport, or lust, or greed.
Yea, he will murder his brother to possess his brother's land.
Let him not breed in great numbers,
for he will make a desert of his home and yours.
Shun him.
Drive him back into his jungle lair,
for he is the harbinger of death.
Oh, look.
I appear to be lying at the bottom of a very deep, dark hole.
That seems a familiar concept.
What does it remind me of?
Ah, I remember.
Life.
Yep.
I said it before and I'll say it again.
Life moves pretty fast.
You don't stop and look around once in a while.
You could miss it.
So very wise.
Well, we missed it, because it was cancelled.
Uh, that Cytopia doping festival in Jamaica, that is.
Gee, I wonder how that happened.
But friends, we vacated anyway.
We're going to the next festival.
Also, we got to attend the annual Devotional in Akron,
and a Devo concert, which will inform our shows as they come along.
And we slaked our slack-off need.
But L'Emoire didn't, nor Norell.
Norell Preff did some of our openings, as did, as always,
Mr. F. L'Emoire, and also Puzzling Evidence.
And, um...
We have a lot of wonderful movie clips for this and upcoming shows
from various movies that came in from a new member,
Reverend Jacques Patti, a W.O.R.T. listener
in, uh, around Madison, Wisconsin.
Praise W.O.R.T.
He sent this huge stash of audio and notions.
And in general, friends, there's going to be lots of music
in this all-around hour.
And, uh, in the course of the last hour of Slack Number 1010,
the background music is by Hell Pope Huey.
Uh, but now, here's my dad.
Well, well.
If it isn't the square bookworm we laughingly refer to as our son.
Ha, ha, ha, ha!
Hey, ya square bookworm!
Have a cigar!
Yeah.
Go ahead, go on.
Pure Havana, straight from Havana, yeah.
As one who has traveled back in time, Commissioner,
let me tell you, it was an interesting experience.
Where did you plant that terranium bomb, eh?
Where did you bury it?
Slack.
Try to find slack.
In this house.
Mmm, popcorn, peanuts, and real buttery slack.
It sure tastes good right now.
See what I mean?
Why not? I see it coming.
Slack, slack, slack, slack.
See it coming.
No!
Slack!
For many generations,
men have spoken and sung of the romantic, queenly, banjo-plunking negro.
They simply put their children to bed and waited for them to die.
Help!
Send us help!
Send us a man to work in his government lab.
To him, the message that assigned him to spend the rest of the day in ignorance and starvation
goes south at once.
Blood from the bodies of dying hog butts and masses.
What if this thing is simply a butt?
But one butt.
Why?
Like a good doctor laughing at the fact that he knew that the man would die insane.
What butt behind him?
The Man Who Died Insane
www.pазifagenew polishingissacres.com
Extent Non-initiative
www.p بالpr 얘기를
www.pbalaidinsane.com
www.pBasicR44.fi
www.PASIFease lessons
www. jutbat guarding brand
www.just nenny.com
www.justnenny.com
and go grooving out someplace,
just remember, somebody in an office someplace
is rubbing his hands together
and saying what a wonderful thing it is
that you're so tore up that you'll never be able
to think your way out of the stuff that they lay on you.
Well, the first thing that you ought to do
is stop using drugs
and start paying attention to what's really going on
and stop believing what everybody tells you
in the newspapers and on television
and read between the lines
and get it through your head
that the best thing that you can be
if you want to stay alert as an American today
is be cynical.
Cynicism is a positive value
and the more cynical you are,
the better off you're going to be.
We as a nation have decided to choose cheese
as a way of life
and we always seem to opt for the cheesiest
of whatever is available
because we now believe thoroughly
whatever the accountants tell us
and all of our decisions that relate to the quality of our lives
are based on the bottom line
and that's the big mistake
and it's those plastic people that you're thinking about
are the ones that have bought that idea
and live by it
and if you can just remember
that you're going to have a better life
with more beautiful things in it,
if you realize that the best things
that you can consume
are not necessarily the things that you have to buy.
You hear that, man?
That's pretty.
You hear it, man?
I'm going to go.
But when my pace has fallen slack, I catch myself thinking back.
A certain night, a certain summer, long gone long.
August, she was swinging low, town of about a thousand.
So out of school, ready to get out of here.
Off to farm, off to state, each going our separate ways.
Graduation message still sweet in our ears.
Whoa, come singing now, man these clocks are slowing.
Heart beat on and on and long gone long.
Got into a car that night, drove out past the street.
Signal light, past the city limits, guess it wasn't that far.
Stopped out on a rural route, Gooch got out his 22.
Shooting at a freight train that was hauling new cars.
Drinking underneath the stars, watching counting meteors.
Robert said, you know those fell a hundred years ago.
The light is just now reaching earth.
I said, man.
For what it's worth, I think you were wrong.
And you really don't know.
Whoa, come singing now, clocks are slowing.
Heart beat on and on and long gone long.
There's something going on.
I tell you now.
Nothing's going on.
Going on, going on.
There's something going on.
I tell you nothing's going on.
Nothing's going on.
Going on.
Goodbye to the home team, goodbye to the rinky dinks.
Goodbye to a girl down my street heading home, she stepped out from behind me.
And a tree tears are running down her cheeks
Goodbye to more than either of us could have known
La la la la la la la la la la la la
La la la la la la la la la la la la la
La la la la la la la la la la la
Some apes it seems are more equal than others
Ridiculous! Tell us bright eyes
Why do men have no souls?
What is the proof that a divine spark exists
in the simian brain?
Ah!
Oh well he's very popular Ed
The sportos, the motorheads, geeks, sluts,
bloods, wastoids, dweebies, dickheads
They all adore him
They think he's a righteous dude
Cigarette butts on the ground
Just like the sky, the sun, my slack
Goes on and on and on
Just like the sun, the sky, my slack
And on
Praise Bob!
Just like the sky, the sun, my slack
Goes on and on and on
And on
Praise Bob!
Yeah yeah yeah yeah
común
mix of Frank Zappa giving some advice, a
lemur butt, some norelpref.com
communications. This is Helpo Huey
playing in the background. Oh, Psycho
Skeletons. You can download a lot more
of their material at this URL.
Soundclick.com slash the Psycho
Skeletons. Actually, Helpo Huey has a
download site which you can find on
alt.slack. It's not right in front of me.
Friends, alt.slack on Usenet is where all
the latest news is happening and
alt.binaries.slack is where we get such
lovely contributions as these.
Okay, well, all right. So we will ask one
more question.
Okay, so we will ask one more question
from this stack of questions and I hope
that for your sake. Do them fast. Do a speed
round. Okay, here we go. Speed round of
questions. You get a one, you get a one
sentence answer for each of these
questions. Ready? Here we go. Dr. Howell,
one. Why can't white people dance? They're
too worried about it. What does Bob's
wafer taste like? Like a hostess Twinkie.
What is the singular of feces? Sterkos.
My seven-year-old nephew keeps asking
about Bob. What should I tell him? Wait
till you're older, dear. Okay, so much for
deep throat, but who is deep pipe? You're
looking at him. If we get bodily fluids
on our clothing, does it get ruptured
during the rupture or does it just stay
on our clothes? You shall have new
arraignment in a new heaven and a new
earth and don't you dare get those dirty.
And oh, one more question, Dr. Howell.
Better. Charged up. And this, the final
question, the one that you've all been
waiting all night for, the one we've left
for last because of its great
significance, particularly in a
philosophical mode relative to these
times and this evening. Now you shall
find out the most significant question
this evening. All right, let's have it.
And that question is... Please hold the music,
Reverend Stang. What would that question
be now? Is the chupacabra more of a threat
than the Jersey devil? And especially at
these latitudes. Is the chupacabra more
of a threat than the Jersey devil
at these latitudes? And of course, let's
also throw in Mothman and whatever lake
monster may inhabit our local pond. We
tend to think of all these as threats
and menaces and indeed they are unknown
quantities that lurk just beyond the
firelight of our comfortable and
familiar circle. But let's put the shoe
on the other foot. You know, do they...
You're the monster. Yeah? Everything about
that? Yeah? It's a cliche. But in fact, they
have far more to fear from us than we
would ever, ever, under any circumstances,
have to fear from them.
Do you think chupacabra, a shy being which
hardly ever shows itself is really going
to put itself at risk to go after the
dh screenshots, which you stamp one down
and six more spring up in their place?
If they're wise and they are because
they've done this so far, they will
retreat their dens, their fortresses of
solitudes, their remote quietness in the
distance and at the margins, and hope that
that we get ourselves out of the way sooner rather than later.
Eh, jackalopes.
Do you remember the Delmar Bandit?
Dr. Howell, the Delmar Bandit?
The guy with the carrot top hair that stuck out sort of like carrot top,
but more like pointy out the top.
And he didn't have any feet.
He just had these stumps, and on the end of his stumps he had these pads.
And he would run around outside people's houses late at night
when it was really quiet.
And he would go up to the windows at night and he would say,
la, la, la, la, la, la.
And he'd do this because he was sad,
because he was deserving of our pity.
And if we could, deserving of our...
You didn't even know why he did it.
Because he was lonely, because he was an outcast.
But we are subgeniuses, and he is not outcast.
As long as he comes around our campfire.
We will high him into the circle.
We will make him one of us.
And he will ascend with us into the glowing, churning, burning wheel of the saucers.
In fact, he can go before me.
The first time I heard those sounds outside my campsite
just flipped me out completely.
I was just completely shit-faced, first of all.
But he...
I'm just totally out of my mind.
No harm was done to you.
And then the next thing I know, there's these...
La, la, la, la, la, la.
But you were made better for the experience.
Well, sure, yeah.
You are refined and purified.
Thank God I was made better.
That was the easy part, was making me better.
But I mean, the shock, the pure horror, the pain, the suffering.
These are all good things.
Well, it's good from a transitionary, transitory...
We need shock, horror.
We need...
We need to be jolted.
We need to be waked up.
We need to see lots of monster movies.
La, la, la, la, la.
And we need this because it's an essential part of our development.
La, la, la, la, la, la.
There's no growth.
There's no development in experiencing blandness and monotony.
Although this is, of course, what we cultivate and love.
It creeped the fuck out of me, man.
I heard it.
We need the jagged, unsuspected incursion.
Sure, yeah.
Jolt, yeah.
An unknown way.
People, yeah.
Sure, sure.
To stay healthy.
To stay alive.
This is different.
No, you say people, but it could be anything.
This is the damnedest thing I ever heard on KFJC.
Both hell and heaven are other people, you know.
But people aren't all of what we think about.
There's more than people.
It's important to remember.
People are only a piece.
This would be a hell of a place if it wasn't for all these people.
But think of how many other people might be here that you wouldn't care to...
Meet.
That's true.
I mean, these people, these are my favorite people in the world.
I mean, I feel closer to these people than anybody.
I mean, you're camping with your friends.
We're like this, you know, every night.
What's wrong with that? It's good.
In my bunk together.
All of us.
It's crazy.
It's just crazy.
He's inviting you folks, though.
And the Miracle Whip and the...
I'm going to have to get a new bunk.
And the Zola Oil.
I mean, it's just wild.
Mine is collapsed in the middle.
It's sagging towards the top.
Yeah, I noticed yours was collapsing last night under the weight of all those...
Masses of people.
There's another one available in the trailer where we are.
Well, folks, I guess that about wraps it up.
And I hope you have taken advantage of our snack bar and the cheeseburgers and other...
Fifteen minutes left for snack time.
Fifteen minutes left for a delicious trans-fat saturated repast,
which shall remain with you for quite a while
and influence your thinking to a certain degree,
as everything which we take...
invariably does.
But it will precipitate a delightful bowel movement tomorrow morning.
Or not.
We prefer to say excremeditation, Dr. Drummond,
although that's not always the same thing as...
Because at these private moments, often...
Take advantage of it.
Great thoughts are birthed as well.
Surely Beethoven's quartets and other things
were the product of meditation behind that little door with the moon.
A sacred place where...
Well, even the basal pleasures of just defecation can't be discounted,
but added to that, excremeditation will then...
You elevate it to a plane of one that we can all agree would be...
Yeah, you just don't want to stay in there too long.
You also want to agree with that.
It takes the time to...
Yeah, you stay in there too long, and then that can cause other problems.
Yes.
You know, emotions.
Emotions too long.
Change your scene.
Change your path.
Yeah.
Change your underwear.
Change.
It's important.
Forget about it.
Yeah.
It's about почему your a lunatic.
But nobody cares,
without your heart.
This is the kind of missions youvre doing,
and pioniures during,
like,
there's no why.
Closed to your face,
tonight,
in your room of a damn doubt,
IT'S SO Rifiord.
Shall we go there again?
That's simply,
None of you would help me when I bake my bread
Not all of you would help me eat it
I can see that you are very well fed
This indicates that you don't need it
Enough said
Stop and let me tell you what tomorrow holds for you
Stop and let me tell you about a plan I have for you
Take all the leaders from around the world
Put them together in a great big ring
Televise it at the lowest show on earth
And let them fight like hell to see who's king
Oh
Hey
Gather up the people when the fight is done
Then you'll find out living really can be fun
The next thing I say to you will be true
The last thing I said was both
Remember to do nothing when you don't know what to do
guitar solo
You want a world you could figure out
But something happened while you were asleep
You wanted a good life you could brag about
Too badly to had the time
of what you wanted to keep
Enough said
Stop and let me tell you
what tomorrow holds for you
about a plan I have for you
Take all the leaders
from around the world
Put them together
in a great big ring
Tell the lies
and let them know
it's your honor
And let them fight like hell
to see who's king
Oh
Yeah
Gather up your pieces
when the fight is done
Then you'll find out
that it really can be fun
Enough said
Devo
And before that
Dr. Howell and Dr. Philodrum
and at 8X Day on the stage
and now
via Norrell Preff
Reverend Pat Robertson
Assassination
We really ought to go ahead and do it
all over the continent
Assassinate it
Go ahead and do it
We have the Monroe Doctrine
We have other doctrines
that we have announced
or take him out
because I think the time has come
Come
Assassinate him
Get it over with
Assassination
We really ought to go ahead and do it
Do it
I don't think
Exercise assassination
Exercise nothing
I don't think
We now present
Bob DeFounder of
Bob Universal Studios
who during his earthly ministry
was one of Bob's great warriors
My head
The devil will get you
But don't let him stop you
He may make it hard for you
Don't stop
Wicked tongues
Now don't get shocked
Now wait a minute
I need protection from the fellow behind you
There isn't a living man big enough
I want to tell you something
Wait a minute
At the right moment
when he finishes his job
Don't let me soften up
Don't let me pull back
Never mind
You know
Now wait a minute
But the big gun
If the big guns
The omnipotent guns
The high explosive
The guns mounted high
Are no gun equal to his gun
You have just heard
Bob Founder of Bob's University
Bob Bob Bob Bob
There was a farmer had
V-O V-O V-O
And Bob
Was his name-o
Bob's friend
In supposed to be80
In supposed to be a
Bob's neighbor
in his talking
była
Danny
the 10th straight time. Investors were relieved today when oil prices rose after tomorrow.
On Wall Street, 710.610.14.4. The Environmental Protection Agency today proposed radiation
exposure for PR News in Washington.
Sure. On Monday, and we get more Tuesday. Wednesday, making its way into Thursday, finally
moving on down towards Friday, right into the early part of next week. Notice that we've
got a slightly more concentrated area of southeast as that northwest begins to lift
a little farther northward across the southeast, right back into the southwest here in the
Midwest and the Northeast.
Sure.
A long stretch of Lemurian news just then, and now more Norell also.
I mean, what do you think you're doing? That's something special for the Baron's birthday.
Let me tell you.
Let me tell you, toy maker. This news of mine has never failed me. And if there are
children here, my friend, you will die.
Talk about contempt. Just throw the cards out on the table, let the chips fall where
they may.
Dark, foreboding, almost evil. I took a bunch of Black Sabbath. Evil, killer kangaroo
out to take vengeance on people. Like a pink thumb thumb piece and a love Black Sabbath.
They're playing thump thump and making lasciviousness.
I personally don't believe
in
the
But when you go down into it, if you go down, sexual churches, fanatical illusion, you can't even think, you can't even hear.
Good song for you.
It's me, Bob.
Your current wait time is, your call is very important to us.
Your call is very important to us.
There is no one to take your call right now.
Thanks for listening.
How are you, Bob?
Better than I've ever been in my whole life.
It's me, Bob.
Have you heard about the guy that invented this thing?
Well, yeah, actually.
There are all kinds of things.
Yeah.
Supposedly, he was born in a mental institution, and he sleeps only one hour a night.
He's a great man.
Oh.
Wow.
Jehovah.
Feed me.
Oh, oh.
Jehovah.
And the videos this year are only $15.
We're not five bucks off of them just because the world is ending.
Why would we need them?
So we're practically giving this stuff away, friends.
You can say shit.
Call us crazy.
Call us insane.
Call us subgeniuses.
It's an insane giveaway.
But it's yours for only $15.
And you're in it.
Wait a minute.
You're probably saying, say, Reverend Stang, if I'm in it, shouldn't you be giving me $15?
Praise Bob.
This is the church of the subgenius.
We don't do things like those normals.
We'll do them the way Bob said to do them.
The way that will benefit Bob.
That's right.
It's all about Bob.
It is.
All about.
And, you know, we can sit up here and talk and talk and talk about the facts of Bob and the doctrine of erasability.
The doctrine of erasability.
And the show and all that bullshit.
But all that really matters is that face.
That face is the key to everything.
Either you instantly see that face and know that it is the coolest face, or it's just another face to you.
Really, you know.
That's the test.
That's what it comes down to.
The coolest face you've ever seen or not.
The inherent coolness of the Dobbs head.
That is the test as to whether you're a yeti or just one of us.
If those others.
If the blood of the yeti, even the tiniest smidgen of that code, courses through your genetic history.
Then you saw that Bob head and went, what is that?
And that's why you're here, friends.
Yes, you said, what the?
Giggling insanely.
What the?
That's why I'm here.
That's why Dr. Drummond and I were here.
And I remember the day you and I first saw that particular picture of Bob.
Layed eyes upon it.
This is getting scary, ladies and gentlemen.
Well, it scarred Philo for a while.
He used to have to wear a mask.
Well, I actually saw him in the flesh.
Yeah, but Dr. Drummond at times played with the young Bob as a kid.
And later in high school.
I mean, not played with him like in the sexual sense.
No, Bob was much older.
It was the other way around.
Be careful here.
Bob played with Philo.
Bob played with Philo throughout Philo's life.
Game balls.
You might say.
Philo is Bob's main toy.
Many kids when they grow up play with fire.
But Bob.
He's not dittling me or anything.
Played with Philo.
The sense of dittling toys or things.
Well, don't be embarrassed, Philo.
We've all taught.
We've taught for years that if it's Bob, it's not queer.
It's nothing to worry about.
And even there's nothing wrong.
Not that there's anything wrong with that.
But really, boys, you know, when you have those thoughts about Bob,
that's nothing to worry about.
There's nothing unusual about it.
It is natural to want to have sex with cuddly cartoon characters.
And some people think that Bob Dobbs is one of these.
One of the cuddliest of all cartoon characters.
Remember, I think it was Gore Vidal who recently said,
there are no such things as homosexuals or lesbians.
There are only homosexual and lesbian acts.
And there are certainly subgenius acts.
Individual forms of expression.
Perhaps taking a sexual dimension.
Only a subgenius could or would want to perform.
These.
Are you talking about those sex acts?
What is the Latin name for the kissing of the devil's fundament?
That's called the osculus infandum.
Ostrus infandum?
Osculus infandum.
The kissing of the devil on his anus.
That was required of witches.
But it's not required here in the Church of the Subgenius.
In fact, I'd like to be called that.
What do you think?
I won't fly.
Will we go there again?
That's any good?
Would you like to see Bob evenly?
Could it be knightly-looking, or cheaply pretty, and yet left pouty like a rocking horse?
so fast
and it's one
more day up in
the saucer
and it's one more night
in the brushwood
if a Friday
Jones could be my
island
I wish she
would
na na na na
na na na
yeah
the smell of the boys
and of normals
and the feeling that
they all can't help
but sit in my
face
with my third eye I look
across the mill
no way to see
he exists
I
not
lamp
and
the
me
I
could
through
Na-na-na-na-na-na-na, na-na-na-na-na-na-na-na-na-na.
I'd cruise this laddered mansion sometime after 2 a.m.
And talk a little while about the church
But the conspiracy makes you move a little slower
Makes you talk a little lower
About the day that we take over
It's been a while since next day
And I guess I will believe
Maybe next year will be better than the last
I can't remember all the times I played the hour of slack
And wished my wish would make it come to pass
So it's 6.59 on Gordon's Saucer
Yeah
But it said no one in Marshwood
I have never made it to a next day
I guess I should
Na na na na na na na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na na na na
Yeah
Na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na
Na no dot Com- shooter
uh Namun no do
It did
Uh
The
It did
Oh
Uh
Here
Yeah.
of the CDs. We did like
ten collections
on cassette tape before those.
But now let us hear some
Phineas Narco with
National Cynical Radio.
I just couldn't
take it anymore.
This is better.
So much better.
Hey!
You wanted me.
And here I am.
It's hard, I guess,
if you figure
I'm experiencing
the reason, I suppose.
Except
you would do this.
You would simply
I
guess that's okay,
but
I
How?
Here it is.
Okay.
Enough of that.
I was really running
on fumes, I guess.
I get dependent
on what other people think.
What's his name?
He's
becoming a butterfly.
I was mesmerized.
I sometimes regret
all that nonsense
floundering in this
holding pattern.
We're just here
to play.
I can see the bliss
in what you surrender to.
Not knowing.
Stop now.
I'm going
back in
the Garden of Eden
for a short while,
anyway.
Okay.
A National Cynical Radio
dot com.
And now some remix of
Norell Pref by
Joe at com.com.
.
しっ
Russian
皇 12
Three guys, they're all packing.
It's too crowded.
There are too many people.
FBI!
Hold your fire!
Stop!
Use the firepower rather than judgment.
Stop, stop, stop, stop.
Everyone's going to be happy.
Come on.
There are shallow rollers and there are deep rollers.
It'll be short.
Thinking about the others?
No, he's speaking of the others.
What kind of doctor are you, by the way, sweetie?
Sawbones, is that the idea?
Or a head shrinker?
I went to them once.
Head shrinker.
Told me he had a dual personality.
You know, split, schizo, and all that jazz.
Then he lays an $82 tab on me,
so I give him $41, and I said,
get the other $41 from the other guy.
Ha!
Is Commander Gilmore U.S. Strategic Command
and General Bolshevsky Russian Intelligence?
Russian Intelligence?
Are you mad?
A lot's happened since you were frozen.
The Cold War's over.
Well, finally those capitalist pigs
will pay for their crimes, eh?
Hey, comrades, eh?
Austin, we won.
Oh, groovy, smashing.
Yay, capitalism.
Hello.
Well, that was some fun, though, wasn't it, George?
Yeah.
Almost makes me wish I hadn't have been saved.
Jacking up banks.
I can see how a fella'd derive a whole lot of pleasure
and satisfaction out of it.
I'm so infuriated by what I'm refusing to do.
I know I'll have a mission here,
and it's more than just promoting X-Day.
I want to get people to join up and enlist.
Well, I'm proud to salute
old Gory.
Old Gory.
And the colors for which she sighs.
She sighs.
There's some red for the blood.
Choo-choo-choo-choo!
White for the guts.
Choo-choo-choo-choo-choo!
Blue for the people.
Bye.
Zip.
Oh!
And I'm proud to tell the story.
The story.
Of the United Snakes of old.
Cha-ching.
With a buck for a back tail.
Mobile X on a unicow.
Cha-ching.
A buck for Halliburton.
Halliburton.
Cha-ching.
Game awardated.
Cheep ken-ditch the
Oh, drake myself off.
All nation's way.
Wave it all over our head.
We're gonna tell the story.
Something can forward back town,
We're gonna fuck for a back towel,
I feel right for a Halloway town
Albert!
I'm about time to salute an old girl
For the reeds
And the colors for which she sang
She sang
Red for the black
White for the black
White for the blue
I'm about to use a sip
Oh!
Oh, don't let she wait
Oh, don't let her swing
No one makes you wait
I'm coming home, mama
Coming home on the big jet plane
I'm coming home to Andrews Air Force Base
Yeah, it's gonna be great
But you better cancel my bowling
My soccer league
My soccer league too
And I ain't only got a
A finger or two
Oh yeah, but think of the why
Why I ain't got no legs
What about tomorrow?
No, I can't be that day
I'm fucking dead
That's a Maverick
John Osprey
Tommy Batter
California
Mmm, smell that bacon.
Paper Action.
From PR News in Washington, I'm the man who pleaded guilty to committing PR News.
Israeli forces have now raided President Bush's Texas ranch.
The U.S. military says the trip will include outreach to Jews limbs as well as Europe.
Ohio's in Columbus today.
Ohio State criminal forms in Columbus.
The Vatican says four American soldiers are demanding a meeting with Pope Benedict XVI, first foreign pope.
Hundreds of anti-PR candlelight vigils were staged last night in support of an anti-PR protest being held near PR News.
Reminds me of the Bobby Girls.
Never was my hobby girls.
Can full of worms and a pole fishing.
Cork bobbing like a hot red bulb.
And a blue jay squeaks his beak open an inch above the creek.
Gone fishing for a week.
Well I put down my pole and I dropped my pants and felt free.
Breeze blowing up me and up the canyon far as I can see.
It's night now and the moon looks like a dandelion.
It's black now and the black bird is feeding on lice and his red wings look like diamonds and rice.
I can hear the mice toes scampering.
Gophers rumbling in pile crater rock holes.
One red bean stuck in the bottom of a tin bowl.
Hot coffee from a crimped up can.
Me and my girl named Bimbo.
Limbo.
Spam.
Captain Beefheart, thank you.
Thank you, thank you.
It's the only poem I know.
Yes, the only poem I ever memorized.
That was some live eight.
X-Day stuff.
We all were getting up and doing poems.
Wait until you hear what Hal did.
But now, uh, uh, let, well no.
Now let me give the URL of the Church of the Subgenius.
That's subgenius.com.
There, now you got it.
Because you're listening to the Hour of Slack from the Church of the Subgenius.
The one world religion preaching the slack of J.R. Bob Dobbs.
And, uh, as I said, subgenius.com has all of that.
You can download everything, including entire DVDs, at alt.binaries.multimedia.slack.
And now, let's catch that Norell Prev.
Surprising, you bet.
Shocking?
Of course.
Because nothing in the whole spectrum of American life is so emotionally charged as marital responsibility.
Nothing as socially stigmatized, legally entangled, morally mixed up.
Surely no drive so basic in mankind, so potently felt and widely exploited in modern life, has ever been so little understood.
Thus so fraught with fear and venom, passion and prejudice.
A much higher percentage is attracted and aroused.
No one knows with any certainty its cause or its cure.
They cannot possibly enjoy heterosexuality.
Surprising, you bet.
Shocking?
Of course.
I am a big, fat Muslim.
I am a feminized, homosexualized, savage nation.
Crip, crip, crip, crippled.
Uh, reaching out, mental disorder.
Savage nation.
Mental disorder.
Sounds good, right?
Savage nation.
Crip, crip, crip, crippled.
Mental disorder.
Savage nation.
Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, demeanor.
Here is the, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh.
insanity insanity racial profiling but listen to this here's the punchline i am a big fat muslim
i am a feminized homosexualized nation government got what they deserved did you hear what i just
said yeah mr magic fully adjustable pole it comes with a flexible head and two hard to reach
areas mr magic fully adjustable pole with a flexible head it comes it comes and more
universe i cannot gain with this my brain recorder
brain
analysis