PR news in Washington. Unclutching pillows loaded on buses.
Lance Armstrong has been charged in connection with the killings of Shiite Muslims in Mexico.
Hundreds of Jewish settlers in Cancun alone were ordered to evacuate hotels and other residences.
Many were hanged, others were shot.
The BBC's bad.
Saddam Hussein has added more than a minute to his overall Tour de France lead during a difficult mountain stage in southern Niger.
He says children in Niger died before reaching PR news.
There's just a week to go in the race and Saddam now leads his nearest rival by two minutes and 46 seconds.
A criminal case has been filed against PR news, Washington.
You can kill a man by shoving an ice pick into the base of his...
Now, break it up.
I've been afraid a lot of times in my life.
Good, but I didn't know the real meaning of fear.
Until...
Until I kissed...
The self-genius.
Power of...
What?
Oh, no.
The hospice of St. Bernard stands beat up on the Alpine Italy.
Famed for their keen monastery, St. Bernard dogs lose their way through the path.
Sheriff, come on.
Opie!
You wouldn't chew my paw?
Oh, don't worry, Opie.
I don't need any other...
Welcome to Monsanto's plastic future.
Constructed entirely of plastic.
Made of plastic.
Hardly unnatural material appears in anything.
The future.
Financed by Monsanto.
The almost unlimited flexibility of plastic.
Gracious living and convenience.
And convenience.
The future.
Welcome to Thot.
Thot.
Thought at www.thought.org. I'm a young shepherd, a charmer, and a warrior, a scheming, vengeful
murderer. Welcome to Thought. My pleasure. And the rest is history. I want the whole world listening
to a grinning imbecile that comes at you and will say anything and do anything and smile anything to
get your money. And I talk about money. Maybe you can understand people that don't get it. People
that don't get it. Idiots out there with your mentality that's been sucked on. And I'm not
gonna bother to say it again. You're an expert. I didn't do a PhD at Stanford University. I'm
addressing my remarks and have a worldwide network to talk to morons. Now all you that love me get
on love me love me love me love me. Ladies and gentlemen, here is something you should know if
you ever suffer from the sudden pain of pain. Don't miss out on a big turd full of flavor.
An exciting treat to eat every morning.
In 1953,
while working on amateur experimental television of building yourself a TV,
he stepped into a puddle of water and suddenly was transported into a spiritual realm.
what we call his immaculation, The divine immaculation of Bob.
At which point the spirit of this alien space god, millions of years old, calling himself Jehovah 1,
entered Bob and took him on as his own descendant.
and informed Bob as his new prophet that for thousands of years,
this monster alien had been masquerading as the one true God,
causing people to do all kinds of ridiculous things
just to win a bet with some other God it was dealing with.
And it was time to really cash in on all this.
And he told Bob that since time began, there has been a conspiracy,
a conspiracy not of clever, manipulating rich guys,
although there are enough of those as well,
but a conspiracy of the plain, ordinary, garden-variety, normal people
against all weirdos.
And I don't mean just the weirdos that wear antlers on their heads at Starwood.
I'm talking about anybody who's slightly weird
is facing a conspiracy of the normals.
And the sad thing about that is, it's not even a clever,
if it was a clever conspiracy, maybe we could fight it.
But it doesn't even matter.
No, it is a conspiracy.
Dear Mother, I am writing you this letter on the 5th of May.
I know that you're so confused with every habit.
Please do not heart to surviving.
Mama, America is a trash or nothing.
For besides homomikas, they also mass-produce automobiles and radios and your son, Bob.
The drive and the dream has become a reality.
He has turned plastic into concert homikas and claritinas.
And though it sounds unbelievable,
Bob
makes almost half the harmonic mangas in the world.
Ah, yes, dear friends, and praise that man Bob and his great harmonikies.
This is Hour of Slack, number 1059.
With a lot of...
This is one of those shows that...
We've been really busy, and I gotta admit, I just threw it together.
And often, those are the best.
There's a lot of Fernanda Nende-Lee-Murr, which we have already just heard.
And a lot of Reverend Norell Preff's cut-ups.
Those two cut-ups.
There's some recordings from Starwood Festival of 2005,
and I think Winterstar of this year.
And a little bit of Radio Synesthesia, but mostly...
Oh!
Oh, and some puzzling evidence radio show from KPFA in San Francisco.
Praise Bob.
And, oh, also we have a little bit of music from an ancient subgenius album
called The Hairs in Bob's Ears.
And I think we'll start off with this song called Slack Talk by Cud.
Cud.
Cud. Cud.
People say slack and I guess that's true
The best thing probably isn't just this good news
If all my eyes are just my eyes
Don't mean I'm meaning a snuggly
I'm not a snuggly
Slack time
There's a time to be tight
There's a time to be slack
And that's the time tonight
There's a time to be tight
There's a time to be slack
And that's the time tonight
Slack time
Let him in, Archie
Would you like some beer?
Well, I had planned to wait until the morning
But if you insist
Here you are
You know, the most significant
Proposed national legislation
Is representative Rush Holt
Who is a Democrat from New Jersey
His voter confidence
And his accessibility
Bill HR 550
Would require the use
Of voter verified paper records
And audits
Would also prohibit
The use of under-
Or dance like a chick
Software, flatware, and tableware
And wireless communication devices
Used in today's high-tech
Republican-hacked voting system
What was that?
Working for Satan
Working for Satan again?
What?
Satan?
No
Oh, no
Not working for Satan
Yeah, what happened is
You've invoked the spirit of Aunt Bertha
Who will always be around
If Satan is around
She's right behind him
With a rolling pin
Running after him
When you play with Satan
You play with fire
Man, shut up, you old bag
Oh, Billy
How can you say that?
It makes Jesus' heart
Weep tears of blood
Grandma, slow it
Can't get up when you can't get up
Jesus' heart
I ripped Jesus' heart
Out of his bloody chest
It was only a harmless seance
You say
A fun game at the Ouija board
Or a harmless party
That's what it starts at
It's just a fun Ouija board
Game
And then all of a sudden
Somebody loses an eye
And
Billy
Thousands of people
Innocently play
With occult fire
Having no idea
How badly
They can
Wait, I had to work hard
For that eye
Nine months of preparation
Now I want you
To sit down on the porch
And learn the multiplication table
While I rummage
Through my retina
And I'm insecure
For those
One Jesus
Three Jesus
Four Jesus
Help me Jesus
Help me soff through this wooden leg
Jesus
Help me Jesus
I gotta leg by leg
I gotta burn it
Cause it's not on fire
My petal of contagious
And you gotta saw this leg right off Jesus
Saw the leg
Suffering the state of combustion
Saw the leg Jesus
Someone give me assistance
Hey, this sounds like geek love
Jesus is sawing assistance right now
He's sawing logs
Jesus, get up off the couch
Which dog is this?
I'm a bee
I've got it
Just throw thevid
This, this is no us
I've got no
Batch several
Gogos
V night
The cadets with the animals back.
What's happening?
That's right, gonna hit them.
That's, that's a huge hole.
Transcendent is the word I'm looking for, yes.
I'm going to make you a proposition.
You'll be fed, clothed, and housed.
A show to gratify your curiosity.
Ladies and gentlemen, look at Baltimore.
Baltimore, the eighth wonder of the world.
Okay, we do have to go with the first one we heard, which was a letter that was called.
Sorry, Connie.
Congratulations, Connie, you're a winner.
You have 24 hours from now to play your incredible creamery.
Connie, experience Ireland, Connie, you're a winner.
Yeah, 4,550.
No, we're not sending you there.
We're sending you to this beautiful dead kelp.
Kelp Beach.
Yeah, you're welcome.
Spin, Connie.
Well, you got a bankrupt, so.
We're paying no attention to what you're saying either.
Sorry.
Oh, sorry.
Sorry, Connie.
Friends, that was a little cut-up there by Reverend Maynard Brainard.
Before that, we heard lots of cut-ups by Fernanda Nandy-Lemur.
And some show from Puzzling Evidence.
At KPFA Berkeley with Dr. Howell and Dr. Philo Drummond.
Going on there about Aunt Bertha versus Jesus.
A little bit more of that coming up.
I wanted to mention, however, that there is a new subgenius magazine out.
I wanted to do a quick review.
It's from the Cuigibo Adult Library.
Actually, you could say this was the 30th issue of Cuigibo.
The Great Subgenius.
The Great Subgenius zine.
An actual printed zine.
Although this issue, which came out just for X-Day.
It was a nine X-Day memorial issue.
This has the title of The Southpaw Self-Pleasure.
Now, Princess Wee, settle down there.
Editor Chris Lee put this thing together with the help of the other Cuigibians.
Michael.
The Dark Angel and so forth.
It has a preview of our new book, The Bobliographon.
Page 3 Girl is always featured.
This issue, Page 3 Girl, is Priestess Pisces.
We got a lot of attention on Hour of Slack number 1057.
And rightfully so.
There was this one spoilsport who just thought she was terrible.
Because she wasn't exactly on.
On key, I guess.
Sometimes with the musicians.
They were all guessing each other's key.
Considering that they were improvising.
It was great.
Anyway, friends.
There's some news about the devotionals.
X-Day eyewitness materials here.
A lot of photos.
And for people who are interested in the behind the scenes.
Not just the dogma of the subgenius church.
Which is described in our books and online.
But this is more like the gossip mag.
And there's even some poetry in here.
Poetry about X-Day by Reverend Magdalene.
Reverend Magdalene, by the way, is in financial straits.
And you might want to look at the information on subgenius.com.
About Reverend Magdalene's ongoing custody case problems.
If you look at the news part.
Or my old.
News.
Blog thing.
Anyway.
Let's.
Enough.
I should.
I should give the address.
I suppose.
If one needed to.
Get more information about the South.
How would I get one?
The South.
Self.
Reverend Stang.
Pleasure.
You would.
Would be to check out.
Cuijibo Cartel.
At.
This is a short address.
18 West Main.
Greenfield.
Indiana.
That's 18 West Main.
Greenfield.
Indiana.
I've been there.
And the zip is 46140.
That is the address friends of one of the coolest subgenius bachelor pads.
That I've ever been.
Has its own brewery.
And the world's largest collection of Simpsons toys and memorabilia.
Just close your eyes.
And imagine.
Being.
In the coolest geek out.
Bachelor pad.
You can imagine.
That's the Cuijibo Cartel Clinch.
They're in beautiful Greenfield.
Indiana.
Oh yes.
Well anyway.
Back to.
Did you have anything to add about that?
No.
I think you really covered it very, very well.
Reverend Stang.
Friends.
We're still recovering from Starwood and the big pagan festival.
That.
That happens around here.
And also X-Day.
We'll have more X-Day shows coming up.
But we thought we'd take a break with this particular divine madness.
Oh yes.
Yeah.
Yes, I said.
Yes.
Oh yes.
You know Robert Philpin has a weird Bible.
Yeah.
He's making fun.
Ever known of that?
Does it sit by the Bible?
It's kind of a weird looking Bible.
Yeah, it's got a zipper around it.
And apparently he's editing it.
Yeah.
Like he's been through the process of editing the Bible since his show started.
Bob's Bible.
Bitch.
Let me say right here that it is even dangerous to ask a Holy Spirit filled person to prophesy over you.
It is?
But why?
Because this reduces the gifts of the Spirit to private fortune telling.
And however sincere the child of God may be, they may attract to themselves another spirit if they disobey God in the proper use of the gifts of the Holy Spirit.
The church is here.
I want to show you the way.
Here comes a train load of the Holy Spirit into our giant depot.
What holy alliances.
The elders of Mary.
Moab and Midian approached Balaam with the reward of the divination.
A likely story.
And that can be found in Numbers 22.
Chapter 22.
Wasn't Balaam the prophet who spoke with his ass?
Balaam's ass was the most prolific of all speaking asses.
The Lord allowed the ass of Balaam to speak.
As it were.
They were not.
But Balaam was the most prolific of all speaking asses.
And the same way that Little Big Man's horse spoke to him on the morning of the Custer Massacre.
I am the prophet.
The anti-massacre by Arlo Guthrie?
No, this was the Washtenaw River Massacre of the Indians by the 7th Cavalry under General Custer.
Well, this fellow said that his horse turned around and spoke to him and said,
Get the hell out of here.
And he rode out.
And he was not massacred with the rest.
That horse got wise at the right moment.
Well, if it happens to the Christian Balaam and his ass, why can't it happen to an Injun with his gods and a horse?
Yes, why not?
That's what I want to know.
Why not an African Yoruba cult?
Well, you see, because Jesus is the one true Lord.
That's not the only incident of animals talking to people in times of stress.
Their heathen gods are sacrilegious enemies.
During World War I.
Whichcraft.
There was a similar incident.
Power of the Devil.
Where animals spoke to soldiers before a parade.
And all of his enemies were hurt.
Lay it on down.
Yeah.
But why go into it?
Let's just say that Fido sitting by the doggy door is smarter than you think.
Is Puzzler intentionally only taunting me with his antipodes?
Did you say Filo was sitting by the doggy door?
No, Fido, not Filo.
Filo means love.
Is there even a guy in that room?
But Fido means faithfulness.
Yes.
Sometimes I wonder if all this election is just a joke.
You know what, do you think that these electronic equipment doesn't, like, cause our humanity
to deteriorate?
Too late?
Or are we done?
Yeah, it is too late.
But, I mean, you know, it's still something to wonder about.
Not that I'm going to quit, but, you know, it does make you think, well maybe I should
go out and take a walk.
I remember trees.
It's actually psic...
Dirt and trees are psychedelic enough.
If you've either developed this proto-awareness or if you've developed this psychological
killed enough brain cells.
Either one. Hardly any
difference really at that level.
Give thanks to Bob
our eternal
hope and praise me
to Irwin, New Jersey's
Pope. We're fickle
and free and we
don't make no fuss
at the Church of the
Subgenius.
Bob, hear our plea.
We beseech
thee, help us
be free from
normalcy. We're
dumb, devoted
and dumb, talk back.
Please give us an
hour of slack.
J.R.
Bob Dobbs never
fails. He's the living
slack master of
mystic sales.
All you conspiracy doofs,
just you wait
till July the 5th
19...
1998.
Invaders will come
from Planet X
bringing gifts of money,
time control and great sex.
A new age will dawn
and we'll never look back.
We'll be busy
enjoying our slack.
Everybody now.
Bob, hear our plea.
We beseech thee,
help us be free
from normalcy.
We're dumb, devoted
and dumb, talk back.
Please give us an hour
of slack.
He's the bridge between
heaven and earth
and hell.
He's the Patriot
Saint of Sales.
Yeah, he's doing well.
Mediareten's are normal,
send things beware.
The slack master
sells everywhere.
Give thanks to Bob.
Our eternal hope.
And praise me to her
when you jersey's go.
We're fickle and free
and we don't make no fuss
at the church of the subgenius.
Everybody now.
Give thanks to Bob.
Our eternal hope.
And praise me to her
when you jersey's go.
We're fickle and free
and we don't make no fuss.
At the church of the subgenius.
Give thanks to Bob.
Our eternal hope.
And praise me to her
when you jersey's go.
We're fickle and free
and we don't make no fuss
at the church of the subgenius.
Give thanks to Bob.
Our eternal hope.
And praise me to her
when you jersey's go.
We're fickle and free
and we don't make no fuss.
At the church of the subgenius.
It's Peki modify
Don't doubt on me
Down on me
On me
Going down on me
Go down on me
Down on me
To make every day more enjoyable, make every day more enjoyable.
To make every day refreshing, delicious, lively, and long-lasting,
make every day full-bodied, healthful, refreshing, and delicious.
Dysfunctional homes.
Loss of dysfunctional homes.
Loss of our dysfunctional homes.
Let me give you a hyphen, hyphen, hyphen, hyphen, hyphen, hyphen, hyphen sample.
Let me below you, below you.
Coming down.
And you feel the earth shake.
And you see the body parts vibrating, vibrating.
Da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da.
Caverns open up and body parts open up.
What's going on here, brother?
I don't mind, actually.
Idiot.
Yeah, Albert E. Moove-o.
I'll be back, I'll be back.
Typical subgenius behavior is defined as anything other than typical subgenius behavior.
Pinkness.
Normality, however, reveals.
It reveals itself.
Like a scorpion under a black light.
Whereas subgenius genes tend to remain hidden.
They have to remain hidden.
Because of centuries of oppression.
Real oppression by real normals.
And there are those subgeniuses who could, number one, acknowledge that they are an endangered species.
And number two, recognize that discretion is the better part of valor.
And hiding is smart.
And the ones who didn't hide their subgenitals simply were killed or died.
And my subgenius friends out here, you do not have to be on all the time.
You do not have to be a weirdo and expressing your abnormality every minute.
In fact, the ones that are doing that may not be subgeniuses at all.
You have to get into the upper secret hierarchy where we have the good drugs.
You have to be able to shut up.
You don't have to be able to talk real good, Bob.
You have to be able to shut up and do the non-glamorous stuff.
Not as an act of submission to the chosen ones like me who would really appreciate it anyway.
But as proof that when the hammer comes down, you won't blab.
Like the subgenius who wants to be weird and do like, be a good proud subgenius or pagan or whatever.
And goes up to the cop and goes,
Officer, I'm not a good subgenius.
No, sir, I'm in a mail-order mind-control sex UFO cult.
Would you like to smoke some Tibetan Habifrock Zimpilops with me?
Well, that officer might be a fellow subgenius, but he'll probably arrest you anyway to protect the church.
Constipation can be a problem for anyone, even doctors.
Well, a majority of the doctors we heard from had this to say.
Have a real cigarette.
Have a real cigarette
a real cigarette
All right.
Hi.
What?
Ever have some monkeys?
Yeah.
I did.
That's right.
Pardon me.
What is it, please?
There was a dead monkey.
Thank you.
So long.
Yeah.
Thanks.
Are we, then, but parasites on the skin of the...
Is the human race a virus?
A lot of people think maybe we should just quit reproducing this.
The human race is an infestation of the planet Earth.
Well, will our host soon be dipped?
That is exactly what we think is coming.
But I have hope, friends, along with the sacred hate of the church.
I don't trust the conspiracy or the conspiracy theorists.
I only trust Bob and his revealed truth, no matter how stupid it is.
If you see a red light and Bob says it's green, thwart, man.
Don't trust yourself.
Trust Bob.
Now, the way we've dealt with this political problem, you know, we really don't want to...
We want the Republicans' money, too.
It's that simple.
And they...
As Bob said...
They may be pink, but their money is green.
Actually, L. Ron Hubbard said that to Bob, but Bob took credit for it.
Bob hates the silly pink scissors.
But what Bob created was a political party, so to speak, called patriopsychotic anarcho-materialism.
Which is summed up in that every yard is a kingdom.
Every child and dog a serf.
Every checkbook a queendom.
And the idea is that you rise above the conspiracy's news.
That's one thing you can do is quit watching the news.
You inflate.
Rise up.
Blow yourself up and float high above the middle of the road so you can look down on all of them
and see how silly they all look.
If you study chimpanzees or teach kindergarten for a week, suddenly politics will all make sense.
お願いします
You're gonna make those kids do Hmph.
You're gonna make those kids do Hmph behind closed doors without people's permission.
That's what the police do, right?
We're doing that right now.
That's why I said this.
You still don't understand?
I already ended up with fouricia in 2014.
I think I play with my Skills squirrels.
I care about what the hell I sing.
I love singing.
Doing what?
don't i i i i i i i i i would not argue for the pro-life position
because you don't know i mean because you freaking don't know
i mean it freaking freaking freaking don't know well
well well there's just too much that you don't that you don't know there's just
too much that you don't don't know don't know don't know don't know
abort every black baby in this country abort every black baby in this country
abort every black baby and morally reprehensible tricky tricky tricky
tricky abort the national media
The blackness comes forward.
It stares straight into my face.
It smothers me with its ugliness.
It blinds my whole white maze.
And then it goes away, and it's just another day.
And I smile at everyone.
But I have to go.
I have little to say.
The blackness is powerful.
It cannot be stopped.
More slow.
As the futility.
Because born.
More evident.
My will to resist.
The tact of the road.
But no one seems to know.
And no one seems to care.
And I want to tell them all.
But I know I mustn't dare.
I know I just have to say it once.
I know of the times.
That have come and gone.
As the conditioning Charles Mama starts.
And it's coffee break at ten
And the Broncos got lucky again
And Elway should know the ball more
But it's really all such a bore
The blackness is honest
And as sure as the statist
It takes my pristine illusions
Leaves them tarnished, stale, and dull
I know the arguments are good and long
Showing how all it is
I do is wrong
I want to put them out of my mind
For I know what I will find
And every one of your goodness
Is until date
And it's just not stuff
You would put on
Well, it was possible
That this wall had something
Between my eyes
So let me tell you
The blackness takes over
It embeds itself deep in my soul
There's nothing left for me to do
Except acknowledge its complete control
And the hospital bed is flat
And I see the world from my back
And I smile at everyone
At last I finally can laugh
At last I finally can bet
At last I finally can clean
At last I finally can Axx
At last I finally can play
I rejoin the spirit of family
I go home a tattoo fromband
beaches
How was that ether fraught, Dr. Drummond?
It was like the void of Moab.
Were you linked to the 80 million tribes of the blood of the Lamb of Moab?
Yes, I was spiritually and psychically linked.
Did you forthwith launch that Especial Head?
That Especilene. The head Especilene.
Was it coated with Especilene before you launched it?
It was coated with Vaseline to give it that quick lift off.
Well, I don't know about you, but I use Especilene.
Should I answer this line?
Go right ahead.
We have another call. Hopefully they're calling to apply for the free Eternal Salvation Certificates we have to offer you tonight.
Tonight only?
Here on KNO-IN. Tonight only. Just call us here at KNO-IN.
Or if you don't happen to be listening to KNO-IN, if you happen to be watching television,
it's the same thing.
If you happen to be driving in your car and you don't have a radio, then please stop.
...of the church of the wretched excess.
Does that have to do with... that doesn't have anything to do with retching, does it?
Good. Could well.
I hate to retch. If you've ever done it, it's really...
It's sort of like squirting upside down.
It's kind of a Shakespearean wretched, he said.
I feel that way sometimes myself.
So, kind of wretched.
That's the hour of slack. We listen to one side of the phone conversation.
I can understand why retching was derived. You know retching was derived from wretched, right?
So anyway, the fourth caller will receive, free, at no additional charge, the Bleeding Head of Arnold Palmer Disco Soccer Kit,
the Certificate of Absolution from the Church of the Subgenius.
This caller makes an excellent point, is that redneck, jello-headed, limey...
Bleep!
I guess, can we say bastard?
Sure, we can say bastard on the phone.
That redneck, low-liming, limey bastard.
Low-liming?
Low-liming, yeah. He's not even a full-blown limey.
And what did you say? What was your excellent point?
He has no yet to send DNA or RNA...
He doesn't have Hello Kitty in his heart.
Yeah.
I'm gonna cry. I'm gonna cry right here on the air.
Somebody who doesn't have Hello Kitty in his heart...
I don't know if I can go on.
That was an excellent point, though.
I'm gonna let you go now.
Thank you.
Thanks for your excellent point.
And, uh...
We have another caller.
Call you later. Bye.
That's right, dear friend.
And, uh, Sterno will take this call.
Uh, unfortunately, we can't, uh, tap the phone callers in.
Most of them are so foul-mouthed that it would be against the law to have them tapped in, so...
That's why we don't take our callers.
But, uh, some of them are... have some grain of humanity and...
Oh, they do. Yeah.
Not humanity. Not in the... not in the negative sense. Only in the... in the philosophical sense.
Yes.
And, uh, we... we wouldn't like to imply that any of our listeners were human.
Nor should it be inferred.
That's right. Or... or implicated in any...
So, Dr. Drummond...
Yes... yes, sir.
You would know better than any man here. What... what was Dobbs like before his immaculation?
We had a caller ask me that last week, and I... not knowing you were going to be here...
Well, like, in what context? Uh, what was he like?
I mean, that's a fairly broad topic.
He was like, uh, like, uh... like a man, and yet like a bear.
Or a bear slapping fish in a stream.
So that was... that was Dobbs.
In the winter, or in the summer.
He was sort of a sea... a man for all seasons. A bear for all seasons.
And... but... but that's a really, uh, uh, philosophical bent on...
...on what Dobbs was like.
Not anything like...
...that the Limey interpreter...
Another... another comment on the Limey interpreters.
...that he can put his lips on her buttocks.
Okay.
And she gives him permission to do that.
And makes smooching sounds.
And makes smacking... smooching sounds.
While... while the entire Church of the Subgenius hierarchy stands around...
...gawking and laughing...
...having their way with deep... deep-deep-deep prairie squids...
...pointing their fingers...
...gawking and laughing...
...and pointing their fingers...
...and laughing...
...and gawking...
...well, it's...
...Englishter.
Well, he's got a lot of gall in him...
...in that letter...
GALL.
...in that company.
This country...
Yeah.
This company...
We were hoping that...
This company of countries...
This grand, very bad...
This grand, very bad boy...
...can, uh...
...can deliver...
That was Karen, who lives in Dallas.
And Karen says that he can plant his limey lips right on her buttocks...
...for sending us that despicable, childish, puerile, adolescent...
Lettuce letters.
But I hope that he wipes his lips off since that lime juice may sting a little.
I was hoping that when you hear Dr. Drummond, we could talk about a certain amount of butt kissing.
Because there's no...
That is one of the most requested cuts that we play on.
Is that a normal butt kissing?
Yep.
It's a very difficult art to master.
One that I've spent years and years to find just the exact distance.
The approved distance that would allow you to manifest that butt kissing viewpoint.
Which is so strongly required of American management.
We'll interrupt this diatribe for another comment on the limey bastard.
That the limey bastard has already paid his $20 for salvation and is receiving the material.
Our caller.
Wants to know what the cost will be so that we won't send him any more material.
We'll save money.
Just think.
Think of what a wonderful thing he's done.
But it's not just money.
I mean it's the cost.
It's the cost.
It's the cost of his slack.
Yeah.
That too.
And so we put a little bit more slack back in the cosmic slack pool.
You know as far as I'm concerned.
We gave it to him.
He rejected it.
And so now he's taunting us.
Instead of giving us the benefit of the doubt.
And realizing up front.
That there was no possible way.
In heck.
That we would ever publish such a horrible.
Infantile.
That's the word I'm looking for.
Pure isle.
Horrible adolescent.
Sexually fantastic.
Whatever those other things are.
We wouldn't be doing those.
These bestial.
The bestial.
It's a bestial damn magazine.
It's the best you'll get around here.
I'll tell you.
You'd better.
I'm there, but.
That's the Pauwbucker.
That's the Pauwbucker coming out in me.
Because you know I'm an ascended Pauwbucker.
And that what should give all you Pauwbuckers part.
That even you two.
Could possibly become an overman.
From your lowly status of Pauwbucker.
Inside the foot of every Pauwbucker.
Beats the gland of a subgenius.
Only weighting to be.
Stifle that radiating.
Massage.
Overman aura there.
Follow it.
Burning me.
Huh.
Uh huh.
Oh, yes.
It could be a headache.
Oh, thanks, Dr. Drummond.
Anybody got any aspirin?
A beer?
A pill?
We were looking for pills all the way up here.
How much is a bucket of pills in Dallas, anyway?
They're pretty high in Little Rock.
Well, if you get the kind that have the stuff inside, it's a little bit more than the kind
that don't have any of the stuff inside.
Oh, the claw-legged, ball-peen, anti-bathtub is full of pills that used to sell down on
Greenville Avenue, I believe.
Yeah.
I like Greenville Avenue.
I like the burlap sign.
They were cheap several years ago.
On the north side of the south part of East End there.
It's kind of on the back side of the west side of that grocery store.
They closed it down now because it got out of hand, especially when they started pushing
those wigs.
You know who came in to buy the wigs?
Those insidious gasket wigs that tighten down.
I got it.
I killed it.
Killed it with my breath.
That's why I don't brush my teeth.
A lot of people have asked me,
Fido, why don't you brush your teeth?
It's those wigs.
You never know.
They're going to come crawling across a floor, a desk, or whatever,
and you've got this built-in power that you can utilize.
It works.
There's living, dead proof of it right there.
Living, dead proof.
Blackboard.
There's a pool of it right there in my hair.
Adults in hand.
You'd like that.
If you're like Bill Clinton, you won't engage in life.
You'd like to receive something.
I never engage.
Laugh, work, vomit.
I don't even hang on what I breathe.
I'll sum up.
Certified pure by the Church of the Subgenius.
Just send 1295 to Post Office Box 140306, Dallas, Texas.
People tell me, how's it going?
7-5-2-1-4.
I say, what?
How's what going?
What is it?
You know, what is the it?
People say, how you doing?
Well, I never really thought about how I did it.
How am I doing it?
You know, I just did it.
It just came kind of natural.
Lightning erupted.
Dobstown shut down for a weekend when Philo did it.
Let me tell you a little bit about what happens when Philo does it.
People say, Philo, how are you?
You're free by the millions when Philo does it.
Vinyl melts by the time when Philo does it.
People say, speakers crackle.
Old women's beehives melt.
Checked out.
You just left.
Grocery stores.
Cut out.
You hit the road.
You just beat feet.
You just packed it on down the highway.
You packed it up.
Rolled it down and shoved it on down the road.
Rolling the long.
Kitten natividad squirm.
Philo does that.
Yeah, I do a little kitty.
Yeah, I called her kitty.
She just knocked P. Wadden out of me one time.
Now, as we go back to the phone, we find that we have a caller who's ready to pledge.
She'd like to pledge.
She'd like to do phylo.
I can understand that.
I like to do phylo.
And I am phylo.
But it's a hard thing.
It's a very hard thing to do phylo the right way.
I've tried it myself.
I've done it.
And I've been there.
And when I got there, I didn't know what the heck was happening.
And we're speaking literally, friends.
So geniuses and geniuses are not innuendo or spouting.
Dear friends, you may be wondering, what the hell?
What the hell was all that?
That was old, old, old stuff from the old, old show.
Will you play any?
What was that?
Eventually, we will.
Increase 31% by just 20%.
What?
Happy birthday, Joe.
Yes, friends.
What we were hearing there was from the old, old, old hour slack in the olden days on the K&ON station in Dallas.
Apparently, that was some weekend when I was...
I was out of town and Will O'Dobbs, who handled the phone and the mail order back then, took over as host.
And Dr. Philo Drummond and Sterno Keekhaver were around for some reason.
And that was a pretty good example of old doctor, the old doctor talking.
Who says the Church of the Subgenius isn't totally relevant to important issues today?
If that wasn't it, that wasn't it.
And this, friends, is it.
The Hour of Slack.
If you want more information about the Church of the Subgenius, the religion of which this program is one of the outreaches,
you can check out subgenius.com.
Or you can write for free information.
We'll send you a little booklet or a catalog or something, maybe.
You can write to Hour of Slack at Post Office Box 181.
Or you can write to us at 417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio.
44118.
Friends, this show has featured a lot of editing by Norel Preff.
You can get more of his at norelpreff.com.
That's N-O-R-E-L-P-R-E-F.
And other editing, a lot of other editing was by...
Fernande Limar.
The great...
cut-up of Idaho Springs, Colorado.
And so, friends, stay tuned for more.
And possibly better.
As Dr. Sinister or somebody...
More. Better.
Comes in and...
Takes over.
Price Bob.
Swipe, wipe, wipe out.
What?
Oh, it's...
Oh, oh, oh.
Those were...
Neat.
Guy.
Of.
No.
What?
Increased 20% by just 31%.
Hey, toss the phone.
I want to order a pizza.
You're high.
Yeah.
You're high 24 hours a day.
Nice.
All the time.
Really?
Yep.
Yeah, you poor jockster.
Sit down.
I'll tell you about it.
Yeah, I got six.
It's pork chops.
Hmm, that's funny.
Oh, seven pork chops.
Hey, where's that pork chop?
That's what I came up here to look at.
Yeah, back there on the bench.
Well, I'll have a look at it.
Well...
I'm just gonna look at it.
Boy.
Funny about that pork chop.
Okay, here goes the doorbell.
Better begin to look shy.
Shut up.
What?
Nothing.
Not the greatest show on earth.
Will you play any sound?