Well, we don't try to make people feel better.
In fact, we hope people feel worse.
They feel so bad that they decide to regurgitate.
And what the prophets were doing back then was saying,
nothing's going to change if you vomit.
And we want to send that to you if you'll support this ministry.
The Self Genius Power of Swag.
Hi, I'm Bob.
I'll tell you.
I'm Bob and I've discovered a fuel burned in your engine can choke off its fuel.
The fuel removes harmful power and mileage.
So did, did, hey, where did, uh, did 420 guy leave already?
Yeah, yeah, it's after 420 and so he, uh, well, he's...
So that's what you mean by 420 guy.
There he goes in his own spaceship flying along Highway 1.
So, uh, 101.
It's not after 420.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
He's wobbling.
He's going to hit that building.
Don't do it.
Oh, man.
The old green silo on the edge of town.
That's terrible.
No, he's okay.
See, he went right through it.
It's a virtual highway.
Man, I should have known in San Francisco.
See, in Cleveland, man, everything's real, baby.
All too real.
You know, their city slogan used to be Cleveland, you gotta be tough.
That was when they were at their very lowest.
Lowest, yeah.
Which was pretty damn low.
When the river was burning.
Yeah.
His hair caught on fire.
Long before Michael Jackson.
Both of these happened more than once.
That was used to be a requirement.
Yeah.
To be a city mayor.
In Cleveland, you had to set your hair on fire.
And people wouldn't tell him either.
They wouldn't even tell him who to set it on fire.
At an amateur hour.
Yeah, sure, she wasn't wearing clothes, but that was part of the point.
So, how long was his hair on fire before they extinguished the mayoral duty?
Oh, you know, I don't know.
I wasn't there.
It was before my time.
I just heard about it.
It's legendary.
I think the length was...
You can wick me at, I'm sure.
One click.
Cleveland Mayor hair fire.
So, Michael Jackson was a Johnny come lately.
Michael Jackson was the mayor of Cleveland at one time.
He, uh...
I should shut up now.
Careful.
Remember these politically incorrect asides.
Like...
Some episodes of Tourette's syndrome.
Though possibly excusable.
Bad Tourette's.
Well, how come the South Park guys can get away with that stuff?
And we can't.
Because this is the capital of free speech radio.
No, but I can't get away with it even...
Hail Fredonia.
Even up in Imus land in the northeast, I can't get away with anything.
They arrest me for everything I say on the radio.
And, get this.
I have to call the police.
I have to call the police to let me into the station.
How do you think that feels?
So, you broadcast by their suffra...
Especially when they pat you down and do the cavity search.
They have all the keys.
I thought you kind of liked that.
I used to, sure.
I think I might have some cavities.
No, it's cold.
They have all the keys, man.
They got all the keys, though.
That's the thing.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Now, seriously.
When you do a subgenius show in Cleveland, Ohio.
I don't know.
You have to wait outside in 10 degree below zero weather until the policeman comes to let you into the building.
And that's all because of Osama Bin Bush and his henchmen.
Oh, man.
Oh, my goodness.
Osama Bin Babin.
It used to be that anybody could walk into any radio station and take over any show.
Watching the swinging love corpses right now.
And now, nobody can do any of that.
Look.
This guy's a funny.
He's got a nuclear pad or whatever.
You know what?
I guess Bob Nelson got out while the going was good.
Isn't Bob Nelson still tunneling towards the D-Rows?
Yes, he's still performing his experiments.
Digging deeper and deeper into the Nevada desert until sooner or later he breaks through to the inner earth.
The hollow earth in which the Nazi hell creatures dwell.
And other dwellers in the abyss.
Sometimes he's right below your feet.
See that trap door on the floor?
Don't open it.
Just look at it.
Don't even look at it.
Forget it.
Whatever you do, kids, don't knock three times on that trap door and say,
Yard sub thog.
Yeah, don't do it.
Copyright 1952.
Sterno.
Keycaver.
Right.
Well, that's true.
You know, I mean, you were bad to your bone at the time.
Oh, I'm very bad to my bones.
You know, I don't get enough calcium and I keep bumping into things and cracking them.
Yeah, I have that problem.
I think that's a subgenius thing, too, by the way.
I think that when you when you when Dobbs becomes part of you in his way and he does
it to each of us differently, some more painful than others, that it sort of causes a problem
with perception that makes you trip over the cat or run into the wall a lot.
It's psychic vampirism.
Bob's a psychic vampire.
Psychic vampires.
Oh, man.
That's one of my favorite subjects, actually.
You know, there's there's actually a psychic vampire cult.
Yeah.
Located in the greater Cleveland area.
Yes, there is.
There is.
Yes.
Cool.
I just I just talked about Bob making me trip over the cat.
Now the cat's got an air ball.
Well, is that the time when you're supposed to go, oh, I can't make a lot of meetings,
but I'd like to at least meet some people.
Now, you said there's a there's a slack vampire cult in Cleveland.
No, a psychic vampire.
Well, yeah, not.
Yeah, I guess they they kind of do steal slack from people.
Or maybe I don't know.
Look it up online.
There's there's a few articles about them.
I'm not going to talk too much about them, but they they trace their spiritual heritage
back to some ancient Egyptian thing.
Oh, the Mayans, of course.
No, not really.
That's just the Egyptian lodge.
You see, I heard psychic vampire and I sort of trace their heritage to an ancient Nixon.
These guys actually also make fun of other like vampire people.
They actually make fun of people who call themselves vampires who are not them.
They're particularly ones who actually drink blood in rituals and wear the white face,
smell like clowns.
Do they do that, too?
Do they do not like blood here on one cheek and stuff and a red nose and stuff?
Well, no, just the goth.
The goth.
They don't have the red.
Otherwise, they wear a lot of rubber and vinyl.
Well, when they get old, their noses kind of turn red, you know, from the rosacea or
whatever.
Well, that's a problem that you could just easily fix by removing your face.
You know, that's all you got to do is just like make the incision lines in the right
place and just rip it off and start a new face.
They've already done face transplants.
Well, what a wonderful thing for a psychic vampire to do to have his face constantly
transplanted so that so that so that there's a French woman who was mauled by a dog.
Dog tore her face off and they got her a transplant.
Yeah.
Right.
A dog face like on the island of Dr. Moreau.
Yeah.
They actually transplant the dog's face onto her.
It's like.
Yeah, it serves that dog right.
Yeah.
And the dog got mauled.
She's naturally she's actually now worshipped by by a small number of homeless schizophrenics.
Plus she has a great gig in the circus.
What makes you think all homeless are schizophrenics?
I didn't say that all homeless are schizophrenic.
I said she was being worshipped by a small band of homeless schizophrenics.
Who, you know, once you get back to that ancient Egyptian thing, you know, they think
she's Anubis now that she's got this dog face.
The homeless people are like.
I'm making this up.
In one year in the United States, half a million who look for lifelong happiness admit that
they had not found it.
It means that with every passing year, failure, bad luck.
They had to shoot a man to start a graveyard.
And inexpensive, too.
Yeah.
I really think the constitute the affirmers of transforms.
Do you believe your razor blades lying around?
Do you like babies?
I hadn't thought of it.
No, why?
I'm awful hungry right now.
I wanted to stay this way forever and ever.
I have all the faith in the world.
And, you know, I wanted to have.
The Ether, I kill you.
I might lose my hand.
That could happen to anybody.
I want to die.
If that's what you want, sure, why not?
There's no greater thrill in the world.
Plate, as usual.
To arrive.
But he was very popular and nobody-minded, of course.
Doomed to fail.
Well, it's certainly a good thing when we're going up to DEFCON Blue again.
Hey, you know, that reminds me.
There's actually a cool post-apocalyptic movie.
I think, Stang, you've got to have seen this.
It's called DEFCON 4.
Oh, that's an oldie.
Yeah, that's an oldie, but good me.
It's a B movie that actually rates like an A.
There is a wonderful History Channel special going around called Life After People,
which shows what would happen to the planet if all the people suddenly disappeared
and they conveniently don't leave corpses.
Oh, that's also a National Geographic channel, The Day After Humans.
Basically, as soon as 85 minutes after humans are off the planet,
There's a lot of subgenius porn on television.
Subgenius porn?
Yeah, end-of-the-world movies.
Time lapses of forests growing in the middle of Dallas.
You know, can I mention a website on the air that I found the other day
that's a pretty cool Cold War website?
It gives, like, the history of all things Cold War.
It's called ConnellRad.com.
ConnellRad?
Yes, ConnellRad is in the old civil defense, control,
electronic radiation acronym.
I thought he was the former Prime Minister of Germany during the 19...
When I was a little kid, I thought he was, like, the king of the United States.
Yeah, we all have...
This is a ConnellRad warning.
Yeah, they used to have...
This is only a test.
Yeah, a ConnellRad warning, remember?
The little cuddly doll they had?
Hide under your desk.
Cover your head with newspaper.
And funnel your ConnellRad dolly.
Yeah, and at ConnellRad.com, they have a history.
about the duck and cover movie.
And it's like the Citizen Kane of disaster preparedness movies.
Well, ConnellRad himself was portrayed by William Wildburn, Van Heerden.
No, he was...
Cornell Wilde played ConnellRad.
Oh.
Yeah.
ConnellRad?
That sounds like a G.I. Joe character or something.
Colonel Radical versus G.I. Joe.
Oh.
They're making a...
G.I. Joe movie.
Of course.
Yeah.
Of course, because...
We've done everything else.
You know, this is what they do.
Yes.
Every 20 years, they run out of ideas, and they just start...
Go back to the cool things I played with as a kid.
I tell you what.
Now, this is...
You know, there's an awful lot of...
Dropout.
Useless memorization.
Ignorance.
Nazis.
I don't know what it is you're slapping around that makes you so happy.
It can't be much of anything, quite frankly, which is why you try to reach for the phone
and get all the information.
Get off on the receiver.
Get some help.
The real.
Okay.
You could be...
Maintain an erection.
Go on.
Big sticks.
Long and hard.
The Limbaugh, Hannity, O'Reilly, and Savage, and Ingram, all off the air.
All off the air.
Yeah.
Yep.
I'm paranoid.
Yeah, I understand.
Yeah.
I went on the internet tonight, and I got some information.
When you're on the internet, you can get information.
Mm-hmm.
Incredible.
K.I. Joe.
K.I.
Mm-hmm.
What do you think a dick is?
Dick?
Yeah.
I'm illiterate.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Uh, let's go to Bob.
Bob.
Good morning.
Mr. Dobbs.
Well.
I'll wait.
We've just recently had a giant sinkhole open up in downtown Cleveland, right underneath
a bunch of lawyers.
Hmm.
Well, that explains much.
Where was that?
I feel like God was getting a little bit of revenge.
Right.
That's what I was thinking.
It sounds like divine providence.
Where was that?
Somewhere downtown, one of the big office buildings, they had to close off a street
or something.
Sure.
It wasn't just a pothole.
It's kind of hard to tell the difference sometimes.
It was underneath a building.
It was like a month ago.
It caused a whole lot of damage.
Which building?
I impaled an alien at the solar...
I think it was the soldiers and sailors monument as a part of an art school video project once.
I just thought I'd mention that.
Oh, okay.
Well, I understand that as we suck water out of the earth underneath our fair cities,
the hollows left where the water once was eventually sort of cave in and houses get
swallowed up.
It happens all the time where I'm from, actually.
All those limestone caves full of water.
We take all the water out of them.
Hmm.
And giant sinkholes engulf major interstate.
One day you're going to be driving home from wherever you're going and all of a sudden
the I-80 will turn into a giant sinkhole.
That's funny.
You'll wonder why.
Yeah, my route over to I-90 caved in.
Really?
Over on Coit Road.
Oh, is that why it's closed now?
It's been repaired since then, but I started to head in.
Yeah, I tried to take that route a few weeks ago.
It was blocked off.
There was just part of the street just dropped into the ground.
Well, the Native Americans had a tunnel network that stretched somewhere from around here
where the Hopewell culture remains are to all the way to the center of Tennessee.
You could go like hundreds of miles underground, supposedly.
Well, and of course they were in league with Sightings and his imps so that they were able
to get into the caves that lead to the literal hell, which is around the center of Tennessee.
Yeah.
And it's kind of like a real place with troglodytes who are experts at torturing you and yet keeping
you alive.
Do they have like white hair and like kind of reddish eyes and stuff?
No, you're thinking of that movie The Time Machine.
That's in the future.
That's yet to come.
Okay.
That's when they emerge and rule the earth.
I always step another time again.
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
And we got about...
Every time you mention an alternate future, that opens up yet another alternate...
Scientology is...
An internet.
An industry of death.
It's a Nazi pseudoscience.
Euthanasia campaign.
Scientology was designed for you.
A piece of mud.
Scientology is...
Adventure.
Mystery.
Western.
Tech to spy.
Science fiction.
Fantasy.
Romance.
Where does the money go?
Gays.
Mind control.
To bend men's minds and brainwash them.
Mind control program.
That's a lot of riches.
Dianetics.
It's outmoded Scientology.
Sellout.
Ah, yes.
Ah.
Church of Scientology.
Gay.
Like you.
Man.
I started playing with it.
As a kid, I always wanted to be a Scientologist.
Uncomfortable experiences.
All ass.
Fun.
To tell you the honest to God truth, I would be dead.
Scientology hasn't helped.
What do I do now?
My answer is to buy.
Buy.
And get help.
So genius.
A better call.
A better call over this call decay.
If you cooperate, we could make you more cheerful.
Shivering.
Agonized darkness.
The choice is yours.
Slam tomorrow.
Shot in your own face.
I'm sorry.
Barbaric.
Gay.
Never mention Scientology again.
Religious oppression.
Injecting.
Yes.
But you don't sit.
Don't sit.
Sit.
Not a head.
Member.
Zero.
I know.
Gay.
Toxic exposure.
In the world.
Doesn't get any.
Who's.
Gay.
I'm a Scientologist.
I'm gay.
Gay.
Stupid.
Scientologist.
Reduce.
Scientology.
Man is.
A.
Piece of flesh.
They've left me to die.
It's not a religion at all.
Interested.
Only in money making.
Which brainwashes its members.
And then bankrupts them.
All.
True.
Say its leaders.
The church is an evil and dangerous cult.
Y'all take folks' money.
Y'all brainwash people.
Science fiction.
That.
That's.
That's trouble.
Trouble.
Brain damage.
Scientology.
That.
That's terrible.
That's bad manners.
You know.
Insane.
Or something like that.
This is wrong.
Something.
Something needs to be done about it.
Furious.
Hubbard.
L. Ron Hubbard feels the heat.
We live in a world where.
Where.
Uh.
We have.
Mud.
And uh.
Therefore.
Uh.
I.
Cheating.
Lying.
To killing.
Deception.
Frankly.
We all thought it was pretty amusing.
Freak out.
Pretty stupid.
Hubbard knew nothing.
Cult.
Weird gang that was.
Uh.
You know.
Just being invented.
By uh.
Johnny come lately.
Cult.
Scientology.
Dangerous cult.
Demon cult.
I just don't see.
Uh.
Dirty tricks.
Penis.
Is that Ron Hubbard?
You betcha lie.
Battlefield Earth.
We will become aberrated.
We will not change.
I don't care.
I really don't care.
And I mean that.
I actually don't care.
Cult of.
Lead.
Obsessed with making money.
Demonic organization.
Greedy.
Three headed babies.
Out of space.
UFO aliens.
The more you know.
The less you know.
You know.
You sort of.
Twitch.
Sweat.
I didn't realize.
And I said whoa.
Real weird.
You know and I was.
And then I was just.
You know.
It really lets you know what it's like to live with a Gestapo.
Scientology has the most debilitating set of rituals of any cult in America.
Get off.
Freak out.
PR flat.
Wasted.
Church waste.
Church of Scientology.
Fascistic.
Totalistic.
The Church of Scientology.
They have hate at the core of this cult.
I think there will be more drugs.
Easy access to heroin.
Drug technology.
Murderers and rapists and criminals.
Fill my church up with um.
You know.
No.
Freedom to spread.
Like.
You know.
Insanity and.
Like.
Jamming.
Some airy fairy way.
Airy fairy way.
Scientologists are.
Nothing.
Weak.
Good.
Loosen up.
I'm getting you to do all this.
Exciting day.
I'm about to fill your exciting day.
Too much?
Are you ready for that?
I've checked my zipper.
I've checked my zipper about ten times today.
Well today we are learning about a really exciting thing.
Scientology.
Doesn't that sound like fun?
I'm pretty excited about that.
Thank you very much.
Scientologist leads to teenage girls.
Scientologists are a little off.
You see.
L. Ron Hubbard was a little off.
We're all a little off aren't we?
Hang the rest.
Cult.
Make a lot of money like crazy.
Pass it up.
Up.
Supernatural.
Commodore.
Teenage girls.
Hot pants.
Scream.
Brutal punishment.
Do it just with men.
Men.
Women.
Dude.
Is a little off.
Bunk.
Trick.
Lied.
Dropping out.
Who made it up?
Comatose.
Severely dehydrated and covered in cockroach bites.
Good.
Okay.
Hold on.
Dog.
Dogma.
Baptist and Catholics and Pagans and Hindus and Buddhists and Muslims.
You are born and you die.
Until you achieve.
Born and you die.
You are born and you die.
Until you achieve.
But.
This is going to sound a little redundant.
Dianetics.
The control of the mind.
Again.
Dianetics.
Neurosis.
Psychosis.
To get.
Again.
It sounds a little redundant.
Dianetics.
Good.
Doing alright.
Again.
Move up and move up and move up.
Not exciting.
Dianetics.
We're getting really deep.
Things are going bad.
I have pain.
I am unconscious.
I don't.
I don't think well.
Good.
Little spaceships break your leg.
Rock.
Broke.
Trip.
Rock.
Wrong.
I do the wrong thing again.
But I do the wrong thing.
Good.
Zap.
Fault.
False.
Thayton.
You are Thayton.
Thayton brand new.
Thayton.
Here it is.
Sound crazy.
Zip zip Thayton.
Tom Cruise is Thayton.
Psychotic.
Thousands of aliens from all over the universe fighting for control of your body.
Thayton let Tom Cruise go.
Isn't it sad?
Woo!
Aren't we all a little off?
Because you're off and I'm off.
Thayton.
Maybe you're a little off.
I love this.
Have you had fun today or what?
What?
Six.
My life just changed.
I thought it would be hard.
It would be hard.
Congratulations.
Six.
Stress.
Anxiety.
Depression.
Negative thinking.
Irrational behavior.
Unwanted aches and pains.
Painful experiences.
Dianetics.
The cause of what's wrong in your life.
You're going to learn how to get rid of it.
We go through life.
What are we doing?
And why are we doing it?
Primitive.
Pleasure.
In a very irrational way.
Problems.
Feeling depressed.
Anxiety.
Panic attacks.
But why?
Pain.
Have anesthesia.
Sick.
Drunk.
Drugged.
Think negatively.
And irrationally.
Now.
Dianetics.
Controlling the way you think.
The way you act.
And the way you feel.
The way you whack.
Whack.
The hit.
The pain.
The feel of the bass.
Watch what you're doing.
Get out.
You can't breathe.
Very deep.
Why don't you watch what you're doing?
Look at what you've done.
Get out.
Get out of here.
Completely irrational.
Fears.
Insecurities.
Irrationalities.
Stress and depression.
You crash into a tree.
Oh, oh, oh, oh my god.
Yeah.
Stress is killing me.
Life is short, you know?
Yeah, I hear you, man.
You know?
Dressed out.
Sick.
It won't stop hurting.
A mother.
Allergies.
Ulcers.
Migraine headaches.
Unexplained aches and pains.
And so forth.
Can be traced back to the harmful effect of Dianetics.
You can get rid of Dianetics.
In Dianetics, the little man in your mind handing out data.
With Dianetics.
You don't like it.
Cancel this.
K. K. K.
Stressed out.
I'm killing me.
Good.
Do you smell?
Yeah.
All right.
Duh.
Very good.
Good.
I can't see.
Dumb.
Good.
Continue.
Dumb.
Feel there.
This, this stress is killing me.
Well, you know.
Okay.
Good.
I see how it's going to go Healthcare, Graduate School Now.
Why, why why toward take you to work to become a
No faith society.
Financial dealings.
The source of what my values really are.
Creator, cult, creator, cult.
That is just not relevant.
They said, then they said, then they said, then they said.
Give me an illustration.
Proceed, proceed, read.
On a regular basis, literally every day,
I think it was a lot to do with ignorance pulling the wool over our eyes.
That was sad.
Give people.
Scientologists don't feel they have to have a dual personality.
In the whole of my career, for profit.
Too filthy, too filthy.
No, I mean.
Good move, good move.
Head, I think, is irrelevant.
I mean.
It's it, it's it, it's it, it's it, it's it, it, it, it, it.
Cut my hair.
Cut, cut.
Deeply.
Fish, it's absurd.
We must bring this discussion to an end.
Scarf.
Fish, it's absurd.
When I got the feeling to start for myself,
I went to a damn Scientology meeting.
Jumping on all the furniture.
Then I went and got that L-Ron.
Hubman built on Scientology called Dianetics.
Dianetics, Dianetics.
I walked in this damn place and this woman comes over and says,
Hello, I'm a Satan.
I said, what?
She said, I'm a minister for Scientology Church.
I'm a Scientologist.
They took me in this room and hooked me up to an e-meter.
They started asking me all these questions about my life.
That little needle on that thing kept going up and up and up.
They said, Betty, you have all kinds of engrams in your head.
And we can cure all that.
Ain't no way in hell I'm giving that woman $5,000.
I said, I heard y'all could audition this shit for free.
And she said, see, I've come and talked to you for an hour.
And they kept asking me all these questions about my life.
And it was real personal.
I didn't like it.
I got up and said, I'm going to leave.
I'm going to leave.
You know what?
They say all these celebrities are into Scientology.
I've done some research on the internet.
It's a cult.
Go take all your money.
I'm a Scientologist.
You are a Scientologist.
It's a cult.
Go take all your money.
Thanks for listening to all these podcasts.
Podcast.
Today is Bob.
Now, we have Bob.
Bob's on the show.
And he was so popular, I asked him to come back.
If you're not familiar with Bob, his history is that he was a professional.
Hi, Bob.
How are you doing?
You know, I don't know.
I wasn't there.
And a lot of people were.
Interviewed some PRs to find out what this was all about.
I take an incredible amount of meat.
Incredible amount of meat.
TV tabloid shows.
Over and over and over again.
White PR.
The church.
Over and over and over again.
Thousands of times.
Yeah.
Promise never to go to bed.
Before your head.
Head.
And I could see that BD made sense.
Duh.
I was involved with several.
Shooting.
We have a party.
It's quite poetic.
Very touching.
Very moving.
Tom and Katie use drugs.
Simple.
White PR.
Crack a joke.
Crack a joke hole.
So, it was all over the place.
I mean, it was all over.
Yeah.
It's a major piece.
All you have is a godless society that's materialistic.
And let me tell you.
Suppressive governments.
You know, mental illnesses.
Or every human.
Behavior and motion and action is in itself the basis of a mental illness.
Of course, the value of Scientology.
They're there.
They're ruining their lives.
And it's okay.
And say, hey.
Killing my wife.
Drugs.
I found a gun in my son's drawer.
The cult.
The cult Scientology.
You know, our cult got some serious situations going on.
Crimer.
Murders and things of that nature.
So, don't know what they're doing.
And we.
Because we've got a cult.
Wherever there's a lot of people living.
Problems.
It doesn't take much.
90 murders.
90 people were murdered.
Killed in church Scientology.
Which is lots of fun.
And very exciting.
They love it.
Get going.
Yeah.
Scientology.
It doesn't take much.
Well, Bob, I want to thank you.
I really love it.
I'm very interested in you.
So, I'm now.
Big.
Tom Cruise on.
Tom Cruise.
Scientologist.
Being a Scientologist.
When you drive past an accident.
It's not like anyone else.
As you drive past.
You know you have to do something about it.
Because.
You know.
You're the only one that can really help.
We are the authorities on getting people off drugs.
We are the authorities on the mind.
We are the authorities on improving conditions.
Criminon.
We can rehabilitate criminals.
Way to happiness.
We can bring peace.
And unite cultures.
It is.
Being a Scientologist.
People are turning to you.
So, you better know it.
You better know it.
And if you don't.
You know.
Go and learn it.
I mean if you're a Scientologist.
You see life.
You see things.
The way they are.
And I thought.
Oh what a beautiful thing.
Because maybe one day.
It'll be like that.
You know what I'm saying.
Maybe one day.
It will be.
Wow.
SP.
He's like.
They'll just read about those in the history books.
You know.
The thing is.
I just go through that tech.
And it's.
It's literally.
It's.
It's not.
How to run from an SP.
It's PTSD.
How to shatter suppression.
Confront shatter suppression.
You apply it.
It's like boom.
Look.
I wish the world was a different place.
I'd like to go on vacation.
And go.
And romp.
And play.
And just.
Do that.
You know what I mean.
I mean.
That's what I want it to be.
Okay.
That's how.
I would.
You know.
There's times.
I'd like to do that.
But.
But I can't.
Because.
I know.
So.
I have to do something.
Don't I?
Yeah.
I really have to do it.
Because I can't live with myself.
If I don't.
And it's.
And that really is it.
So it's our responsibility to.
Educate.
And.
Create the new reality.
You know.
We have that responsibility to say.
Hey.
This is the way it should be done.
I have to tell you something.
I really.
It.
It is.
You know.
It's rough and tumble.
And it's.
Wild and wooly.
And it's a blast.
It's a blast.
When I think about those people out there.
Who.
Are depending on.
Us.
And.
I think about that.
I do what I can.
And I do it.
The way I do everything.
There's nothing.
Part of the way.
For me.
It's just.
A Scientologist can be defined by a single question.
The question.
Would you want others to achieve the knowledge you now have.
In answering that question.
Tom Cruise has introduced LRH technology.
To over 1 million people of Earth.
And that's only the first wave he's unleashed.
Which is why the story of Tom Cruise Scientologist.
Has only just begun.
We of the church believe.
That all men have inalienable rights.
To destroy their own lives.
To destroy their sanity.
And to destroy the opinions of others.
That all men have inalienable rights.
To destroy their own kind.
That the souls of men.
Have the rights to destroy.
The study of the mind.
And the healing of mentally caused ills.
Should be alienated from religion.
Not condoned in non-religious.
Fields.
And that no agency less than.
We of the church.
Has the power to suspend.
Or set aside these rights.
Overtly or covertly.
And we of the church believe.
That man is seeking to destroy.
That his survival depends upon himself.
To destroy his fellows.
And to destroy brotherhood.
With the universe.
And we of the church believe.
That the laws of the church condoned man.
To destroy his own kind.
To destroy the sanity of another.
To destroy or enslave another's soul.
Yes dear friends it does appear.
That this episode of the hour of slack number 1157.
Ended up being the repository.
For many of the Scientology bashing clips.
Mostly edited by Reverend Norrell Preff.
That have been stacking up around here like cord wood.
I personally don't have any more against Scientology.
Than I do against all rival cults.
Such as Christianity or Mohammedism.
And I'm not particularly into the anonymous anti-cult cult.
Mainly because it seems like just another rival cult itself.
But hey what you gonna do.
Invite them all to X-Day I guess friends.
And X-Day is coming up.
The world ends July 5th.
And we're having a hell of a party to prove it.
Like we do every year.
Also it's subgenius mating season.
If you are interested.
And if you think you have what it takes.
Such as no fear of the outdoors.
You can look at the events section of our website.
At subgenius.com
There are many naughty pictures.
Because our X-Day drills take place.
At a clothing optional campground in New York State.
Called Brushwood.
Our mating grounds.
Anyway before the slew of Scientologisms.
We played some live radio recordings.
From Dr. Sinister's radio synesthesia show.
On WCSB Cleveland.
Which follows our slack in that noble city.
With guests Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
Priestess Pisces.
Rocknar and No Money Mark.
And yours truly.
We also heard early on some puzzling evidence.
From KPFA Berkeley.
The oldest living subgenius show.
With host puzzling evidence.
Subgenius Church co-sub founder Dr. Philo Drummond.
Dr. Howell.
Gary Gavro-Trend and so many others.
Our titles and a few other clips and claps.
Were by Mr. Lee Murr.
And no he has no website.
The background music right now.
Is from the new CD called.
Totality.
By the Flyin' Ryan Brothers.
With Reverend Jimmy Ryan.
For more on their fine music.
You'll like this.
See.
Ryanetics.com.
R-Y-A-N-etics.com.
Well let's cut the yakking now.
For some more music.
Which like Scientology and subgenius.
In this case is mostly about money.
First up is from one of our chicken head friends.
Kid Whatever.
Well it's one for the money.
Two for the money.
Twos for the money.
Three for the money.
Goals.
James Archie Davis.
ranea.com.
Ocho xum.
Everything that I got and isn't.
Double sobriety.
James Elian.
Was working.
Esgrafopi Lajinder.
Dave Pinkney.
What's real when he stans it's real when they don't start it at all?
No.
I'll try to do that one thing before this one gets cut.
Go over money
You're so money and you don't even know it
You're so money
The greatest thing on earth
Is love of money
We thank our lucky stars
And money
I treasure each account with loving care
I guess from the deep inside us
There's a touch of all-king Midas
Hey!
To the king!
Thank you
Not at all
The greatest thing on earth
Is love of money
Jed, ain't you lucky to have friends
Who take such interest in your money?
My doggie granny, you're right
We are looking into studies
You got to work atos
And have nothing to talk about
And see if you ever have
I can pray
That the one in
Hand in hands
To our neighbors
And alabaster
Oh Jesus...
I do!
Me a man who threw away the key
And set the speed to barely playing
For thirty days, thirty days
There was a time when I could believe that
I could recall every day I had lived
And that joyride, it came like a slide
And I got very a little out of hand
I used to wake up anxious each morning
Time it was coming, I didn't want to kill
But now the first day of every month's just
Another day to share in a bunch of guilt
But thirty days, I am a prisoner
Thirty days out in the sea
I shall tunnel out of all this trouble
I will be free in thirty days
Well, it's been a bad month, my friend
And last month, it was a bad one
And the time was not so bad either
No wind got knocked out of my life
No, I don't want to fight
I just want to breathe
Yeah, yeah, yeah
So God created better than heaven
And only seven days they say
But on that seventh day he rested
Oh, but I heard it another way
I heard that he died drunk and lonely
Created trouble in town alone
These thirty days he shoots out the bullet
And the whole moon just to remind us
We're on a roll
But thirty days, hell, September
And I could use a day or two
For lots of mystery, I will remember
But thirty days, thirty days
There's lots of mystery, I will remember
But thirty days, thirty days, thirty days
Thirty days, thirty days
Thirty days, thirty days, thirty days
The CEO of the former CEO of the CEO of and the CFO of
Business is business
There's no question on my mind
None, no question in my mind
Check it, check it
Rejection, rejection
Right now I happen to be a CEO, EO, EO, EOO and follower
is too much.
Take advantage of.
9-11. I don't think
it doesn't matter. Fairy tales
in the form of science fiction.
Too far-fetched. Hardcore.
Hardcore. If you want information about
lower forces, you can find it at our site on the
internet. www.allmormons.com
Business is business.
I, the, the, the
Mormon needed to be restored.
Um, but um, well he
wasn't telling the truth.
I just want to uh, make a quick comment about those two Mormons.
Make a quick comment about those two Mormons.
Sure. Corrupted.
That was quick. It's, it's old.
Yeah.
Old like me.
I had to, I want to, you know,
I hear all the subgeniuses complaining about getting old
and I went to get my eyes checked
and it, right after my birthday.
About a, a
week after and went in there and found
out that I had to get bifocals.
Uh-huh.
Well what about straight focals?
Yeah, Stan, what about the congenital
glaucoma and leprosy?
Oh, that's just part of the satire.
Huh? That's part of the joke.
Right. Don't you get it, man?
We have to do about it until we start laughing, you know?
But apparently I have a mutant spot on the back of my
eyeball that they,
it kind of looks a little bit like a
Dobbs head in the retinal photography.
So it's... Which is why they keep bringing me
in, but it's apparently now I have
to get bifocals so I can sort of
split the retinal spot that looks like
Bob into two
visual
You're about to learn why old people kind of
tilt their head back when they read the newspaper.
Because they have three ovaries.
Yeah. Or not
frozen ones, I mean three, not
free.
No, I have free ovaries. I try to
give them away all the time, but nobody will take them.
Well that's like the spot behind your eye.
It is not a mutation.
It is perfectly normal and natural, especially
if it's a scroll down Bob's head.
It makes it even all the more
natural and organic.
Maybe it is exactly a Dobbs head.
Maybe a Dobbs head somehow
burned itself onto the inside of one of your
eyeballs. Or has chosen you.
It has, yeah. You've been chosen.
Well, and they thought it was a cancer at first.
And they said, well of course that's what they're going to think it is.
They're going to think it's cancer because
of the growth of Bob tissue in you.
Right, right. So apparently
one of my eyes,
this would be the left eye,
is an eye of
Bob. Well the left eye
is the path to the right mind. That's true
because Dobbs heads see,
I mean Bob can see out of every
Dobbs head.
And if there's one at the back of your eyeball
that means he's, you're one of his
main spy cameras, you might say.
And I've got to tell you there's something
really creepy about it. The girl I met
in the Waffle House, when they
first found this, it was actually
shortly after
I talked to the girl who said I saw
Bob here and he stiffed me.
So,
apparently
there's something wrong or
right with this Waffle House.
That's when the Dobbs head
marked.
Well now you know there are a lot of false Bobs
and Bob robots
walking the streets
these days. Yeah, sometimes the pipe
doesn't dangle the right way. The pipe should
dangle to the left. Or am I seeing it mirror
image? Should it, is it pointed
to his right
or your, the camera left?
The camera left, facing left, yeah.
Yeah.
Absolutely.
So you know they could have that wrong by
different degrees and still be selling you
a line of stuff.
Oh sure.
Speaking of selling you a line of stuff as Lunsum
just was, you can learn more about everything
at subgenius.com or by writing
to us, subgenius
P.O. Box 181
Cleveland Heights
Ohio
Before the radiosynesthesia
just then and after the Beverly Hillbillies
we heard Bob Walkenhorst
performing his song 30 Days
solo at the Record Bar in Kansas City.
I downloaded those
by the way, they aren't on any album that I know of
although Bob does have a new album
out called The Beginner.
Almost all of the collages in this episode were by
Norrell Preff of norrellpreff.com
who seems like
one of the people put in this country
just to cut audio clips.
He has cut up a whole lot of audio clips.
Thousands of them.
There are some people put in this country just to kill Americans.
George Bush is one of them.
He has killed a whole lot of Americans.
Thousands of them.
And he has crippled hundreds
of thousands of them.
The devils
would love very much to do away with democracy.
We are not a great nation.
You have this silly little woman out of
I don't know, where the hell is she from?
Arkansas?
This white
stupid looking, ugly,
vile, racist
stupid.
Sometimes it's true.
Reality sucks.
Not a law is applied, licensed by the Department of
Corporations Equal Housing Law.
Erectile dysfunction.
Can't maintain an erection.
Send John McCain into retirement.
President Bush and the Pope share a lot of common values.
Terrorism and extremism.
Walmart guns falling into the wrong hands.
And you're not doing anything about it.
You're just like me.
Guns and God completely burned out.
Most people in America feel
exactly as you do.
That's how they do it.
You know, I mean, you live around all those places like
Langley and Fort Meade and you probably
hang out there too.
I'm actually right now really close to NIH.
The National Institutes of Health.
And that's an interesting
maze of a place.
I'm sure there's something weird
going on there. There's always weird stuff going on.
Well, you're putting
Dobbs heads in all the medical books, right?
Pardon?
You're putting Dobbs heads in all the medical books, right?
No, I haven't
gotten that far yet.
Right now, I also work
with a funeral
service group and I'm working my way
into them because funeral
people really do have a very subgenius
line in them.
Yeah, and they're experts
at getting lots of money for
doing stuff
that's totally unnecessary.
Well, and there are, we have a lot of
ministers who are embalmers
and so forth.
Reverend Sifu. Yeah, and they're the only people
that are happy when your relatives die.
I mean, you naturally gravitate to them because you're smiling
and stuff. Didn't people drop
as much money on a casket as they would on
like a car, a luxury car?
Yeah, a yacht. So it can be buried
in the ground. Well, if you're really cool, you're buried in your
car. Right. Oh, yeah.
And sometimes the cars are hand-closed.
Unless you're in France right now.
And there's a town in France where the mayor,
because they have no more room in the cemetery,
They made it a crime to die.
It's criminal to die.
So I'm betting that that's where Bob
is right now. So when you croak, they put you
in jail instead of in a cemetery.
Well, no, you just can't die.
It's illegal. Now, what's the name of
this town? I need to call my dad real
soon.
It's a little
province, and I can't remember the name right now, but it was in
the news and I remember reading about it and I
passed it along to a couple of people.
Death took a vacation.
Death was outlawed.
I'm telling you, as much
as we kill Bob, I'm going to bet you
that Bob's there right now. That's what I
think. I think the pipe is barking into your
pineal gland right there, baby. That's what's
really going on there, and you're just
doing as you're told.
Well, did Bob keep coming back because of the
stem cells that were being drawn from the
stem of the pipe?
Yeah, think of it. I mean, well, how could
you? You know, you're having thoughts of someone else.
But I mean, whoever's thinking, think of it.
Well, you have to remember that
as people have seen me, I don't, when I
talk about Bob or Connie, I
usually don't have any idea what I'm saying.
See? It's like
channeling. Yeah. It is channeling.
Only you're channeling yourself.
Yeah, you're the fish on the hook, and you're the one who
baited it. And the, yeah, right, the fisherman
and the fish. Yeah. And it's
amazing. I get, I would
get on stage at things like, and
it comes out of my mouth. I don't
prepare. I just let that
spot, apparently, in my eyeball.
Like, simultaneously
being the mouth and
anus of Bob. Talk about your
alpha and omega. Yeah. Absolutely.
That little spot in my
eyeball just tells my brain what to say.
What goes in must come
out. Absolutely.
Better out than in. Think of it,
you're a perfect person then, even though you're not
really in on it anymore.
You know, everything that goes in does
come out perfectly, and you're, you're
a witness. You're a perfect witness
to a perfect crime. What comes
up must go down.
And that's why I'm always glad that someone records
stuff, because I don't know what happened.
Well, it's all being recorded around you. I have to look at the foot later.
You're one of the main features.
Right. And all you gotta do is just, like,
Well, but see,
she doesn't have the thing that'll play back
what her, Dob's eyeball is
seeing. Right, I depend on staying
for that. I wait. And then,
We need to, we need to figure out where
that Dob's head in your
eye is transmitting to.
And, uh. Besides your brain. I mean,
Is it upside down? In other words,
did the, uh, Dob's head
kind of invert itself
to where he's
upside down on your eyeball? Right.
No, you know, he is, he is right side
up. Um, and
Well, you see, that's the danger of staring
at a Dob's head upside down.
Yeah, it's like early
telescope. You can't, you know, the squares
start going into your skull. Well, this thing
is probably an implantation.
Like the pipe itself.
Right. Uh, uh, an
exist, uh, technological,
uh, advanced landing, you might say,
inside of Pisces
retina. So,
what we need to do now is
trace the signal
that's going from that. Right.
I mean, and then we can figure out who placed
the Dob's head, or what. It's a signal.
Maybe we can triangulate on some distant
star. It's a signal. Or
nearby federal office building.
I don't know. I, I, well,
you know, and I, apparently it's been there since
I, before I lived in D.C.
I was in there when I was in Georgia.
Well, that's where you picked it up then, probably.
In the Cracker Woods somewhere.
Well, you know, or...
One of those guys out of deliverance jumped up and gave you your
med-vain. I remember after several, two
X days in a row, after both X days,
I ended up having a major
surgery.
So, there's something going on there. That's pretty common.
Yeah, that is. That does happen.
But, uh, because the, I, you know, as
we've suggested, some, maybe we're being
ruptured up into the escape
vessels of the sex goddesses.
One organ at a time.
Right. Or a few cells at a time.
Or, you know, part of your
DNA gets taken.
I, I don't know. Hair.
Look at Dave. Yeah, it could be like a
bad, you know, like, trans... Memory. Look at hearing.
...mit or what thing, like in
old Star Trek. What was that? The transducer
responder? You know, and it's fouling
up. We don't know. It's, it's,
but it clearly is like taking one or two
organs at a time instead of the whole body
and the whole psyche and everything at once.
Well, let's see. It's taken my...
They, they messed up my kidneys
once and then they took my gallbladder.
Did they ever take away
your love? Yeah, did they
go after your shoes or any other, you know, like,
parts of your, you know, like, clothing that we might
want to look at? Well, somebody took
a corset from me at
Brushwood one year. And it was
a male. That was Bob. And I never
have gotten it back. That was Bob.
It was. It was Bob. He needs
that. He took my black lace up corset.
...to the picture that he's wearing.
He has to wear that as a headdress
sometimes because he is, his brain is
literally exploding, but Stang doesn't want you to know
Well, he might have needed it for some kind
of Masonic treasure hunt. Now, we
don't have to jump to conclusions. Yeah, well...
It may have been something simple.
Y'all know me. It's a big corset.
I can't imagine. You would have to stuff it
quite a bit. You know, uh, do you know
who this is? What, what actually did
the system here?
You make it sound like you know who took it.
There's a, like, a pot... Yeah, Bob!
...or a Mooney sign or a
Quark or something. Bob took it. But, you know,
I don't, I, Bob's, I mean...
There is a rascally raccoon
out there at Brushwood that's known to steal
corsets and ladies'
intimates. A cross-dressing
raccoon? Right. A transvestite raccoon.
I mean... Well, I don't know.
He may just collect them like my collection
of shoes and sweaters.
The Betty Paid shoes and the
Hammer Film sweaters with the
bloodstains? You're talking about collecting shoes.
Now, if it was Kirstie Alley's
corset, you'd want that, wouldn't you
Stang? Kirstie Alley corset?
Yeah. Actually, my friend Mr. Sister
is the Kirstie Alley collector.
Oh. Although,
you know, she's definitely... I, I
was, uh, I appreciated
Kirstie Alley's
um,
representation in the, uh, National
Enquirer, which would always make
fun of her whenever she
gained weight.
And, uh,
because she was a Scientologist, and
therefore it was okay... Well, Scientologists
are chubby people anyway. You know,
to, to make fun of somebody who's
weight, just because they're a Scientologist.
But, uh,
I actually did think she was kinda hot.
For once...
At every stage. At all
of her stages. You know, there's
there is, there's lucrative
money in
certain types of films
involving larger women. Oh.
Okay. And
on that note, uh,
it looks like, uh, Clark is running down
here, actually. We're down to the last couple minutes
of the program. Oh, that's right. We had time
control this weekend.
And, uh, by the way, just for the record, just for the
record, uh, you know, I, I think it's high time
we abolish daylight savings time.
I think it's the biggest waste of time ever.
I say it's time we abolish time
itself. Yeah. I mean, it, it does not do
what it... Well, actually, the good news is, the good news
is that extra hour of daylight did help
the snow melt a little better. My, my
savings have already been abolished. You only
think that it helped the snow melt better.
We got an extra hour of daylight today
so the snow could melt. Like, oh, look at this.
No, no more light was created.
That was a joke, man.
Come on. I know you knew it was.
I didn't think you felt it
though, you know? Yeah. It's important.
So, yeah, as, uh, as
Al Ducey would say, it's getting near
the hour. Alright. So, um...
Have fun, kids. It was good
talking to all of y'all. I, I have enjoyed talking to
all of you as well. Enjoying WCF.
Y'all have a good evening.
With that, I shall take my leave. I will smell the
salchow. Me as well.
Hasta luego. Hasta luego a todos.
You're on the air. Make it quick.
Just wanna say, I thought it was a really good show tonight
and, uh, Pisces is awesome.
She, she, uh, is...
Yeah, she's one of the best callers to the station. I mean, her
stories are funny. She's really witty.
She should have her own show.
Seriously.
You know, that wouldn't be, uh, half bad.
That wouldn't be a bad show at all.
A Pisces show. That'd be, uh...
That'd be fun. Yeah, too bad for us she lives
in Washington.
Too bad for us that anyone
lives in Washington.