The Self-Genius Power of Swag
Why is it always, always so costly for man to move from the present to the future?
So, so, that night I didn't get much sleep.
Today it's Bob!
In the locker room yesterday, after he thought everybody had gone, I saw Bob take something from Ben's pants.
Bob! I can't believe it!
Bob, where will we be without Bob?
Terry, there's nothing for you to do but tell Mr. Barker about Bob.
It's the same thing!
Well, and it did seem dishonest to conceal it anyway.
Anyway?
I did what was the obvious thing for me to do.
I questioned Bob.
Well, that's not always easy.
I saw Bob.
That's right.
Is it logical to think that Bob would steal?
Does it jive with your past experience of the way Bob operates?
Sometimes it takes a lot of testing to find Bob.
I guess I wasn't thinking very deep.
Maybe, maybe inside, I didn't really believe Bob was inside.
I think that's the clue to this bigger thing we're seeking.
Know yourself.
Yes, this is the time for me to explain myself.
I'm not saying anything.
I'm just saying that I have a sense of hypocrisy.
When I came in to tell Mr. Barker about Bob, I started by saying certain things.
But I want to be sure that you find out about Bob.
And when you do, all he needs is a chance.
Now I'm catching on to why that's so.
Now, Bob, tell us the truth.
Well?
Well, it was this way.
That's all?
Harness!
Bark, bark, bark, bark.
Now with today's mess, here is Pastor Stink Rap getting bent out of shape.
And that is basic to human existence.
Put on a woman's garment, the human race continues to be interested in cross-dressing.
I go back and I see pictures of a lot of men.
And they were men, male and female.
And I want my hair in this way, and I want my hair that way.
I know it can be very stylish sometimes and is not a bad idea.
My wife liked it, but I eventually cut it off.
I found it rather irritating.
I guess I didn't keep it long enough.
And I actually like men on men.
And I encourage them because it's obvious to me that that's part of the picture.
That helps.
Man, man.
How long is long and how short is short?
Laying all that aside, the general principle is slack.
So, slack is taking that too far.
But the general principle is this.
The general principle still remains.
Slack.
The land has changed.
The biosphere turned.
Become unfamiliar and erratic.
I would say vengeful that nature is indifferent to us.
We fight for our survival, not nature's.
There's a fierceness in the wind I've never felt before.
Something is being unleashed.
A new form of self.
and the softening permafrost.
Why do we despise the world that gave us life?
Why so alienated?
Why wouldn't the wilderness fight us,
like any organism would fend off a virus?
The world we grew up in is changed forever.
There is no way home.
Is there something beyond science that is happening out here?
What if the very thing we were here to pull out of the ground were to rise willingly?
What would that look like?
This is the last winter.
Total collapse.
Hope dies.
And Bob.
Lives.
Friends, we're live tonight with recorded Norrell Preff and Fernanda Nandy Lee Marr,
but it's so cold.
There's been a weird, some sort of anomaly in the weather here along the Great Lakes.
It was like 83 today, and tonight it's like, what, 23 right now?
This summer must be like the last winter.
I think the global coolness deficit is catching up with us, man.
I think what's going to happen is they're going to try and kill us in the winter with cold and in the summer with heat.
And these ghosts, mammoths and mastodons and prehistoric reindeer keep running around us in circles.
But then they go again.
Did you see that?
Oh, yeah, of course.
I saw it and I smelled it too.
The smell is onerous, like the puffy foot.
It's grossly onerous.
It's grossly over exaggerated.
And some, look, some of the mammary glands are expanded.
Oh, man, they're going to have more of them.
It's a Neander man.
A Neander man ghost.
You smelled that?
That's why I left the room.
Jeez.
That was an...
It's so cold and spooky.
They're already breeding new humans now.
I need a blanket.
Neander man might be the only thing that works.
I don't like it, Loose Bob.
Look, there's somebody coming by with mushrooms growing out of their head.
Multicolored mushrooms.
Look, they're luminous.
They're numinous.
They're like little...
Oh, they smell good.
Yep, they're...
Don't get close to that.
They smell excellent.
Hello.
Hi.
I'd like you to stroke my mushrooms.
These, as you stroke them...
Oh, that feels weird.
The juices from my head will go into the palms of your hand.
Be reabsorbed into your body's cyclophymic personality.
It's weirdling, babe.
He's such a fun guy.
I'm getting all slacked up.
Just line up.
Don't, don't...
Fun guy.
Don't let those knees wobble.
Oh, it feels good.
It's a hard floor down there.
Ah, it feels great.
Yeah, see?
Oh, so this is slack.
Or is this the frop?
I can't remember, but it's good.
It's good.
You can't let him know this is the...
More.
This is not real slack.
More, Bob.
More.
This is the beginning.
This is the first part.
He's not ready for it.
He's not acclimating.
You've got to help him.
More than kind pills.
No one can ever help him.
No, never, never.
Oh, yes.
The kind pills can help you.
More of them kind pills.
The unkind pills.
The cruelty pills.
The blasé pills.
What is it?
The ill-willed pills.
The forgotten pills.
What can it be that has done this to us?
What has changed us?
What has made us into these things?
It's just Bob is what it is.
It's just, it's literally Bob.
The demaculation of J.R. Bob.
It's Bob.
Bob.
Yeah.
on at least a daily or weekly basis, depending on their situation in the church,
to wear these alacrid lucid underpants.
Some of them haven't been tested.
Clean those pants, man.
Oh, my God.
The pants are getting away.
The pants are huge.
Oh, my God.
Who would have thought it of Bob's pants that they could do that?
Okay, dude, let me end here.
I'm a situationist, so I could probably handle this situation.
Okay, as the situation is, it looks like some of the guys wearing the Bob underpants are exploding.
Thank you.
I'll be back.
I'm doing the Catskills thing.
Oh, my God.
I feel so alone now.
Why, you're not alone.
You're here with us in Blunderland.
All of us.
All of us in Blunderland.
So pleasant here.
With the psychoskeletons.
Oh, yes.
They're not so bad.
Psychoskeletons aren't nearly as bad as so many people say.
They get the drift of things.
They can be shaven.
They can be worn, really.
And they can be crunched up into a fine powder and reused by these extraterrestrial vessels.
And, friends, that's what this show is all about.
The Hour of Slack is about turning you into a psychoskeleton.
Actually, psychoskeletons are playing a...
Captain Beefheart tune in the background.
This particular time.
Ah, yes.
Don, do you remember the Exoskeletons?
A band that was kind of capitalizing on both nihilism and having skeletons.
That was one chitinous band.
That was chitinous, man.
What does chitinous mean?
That's what bugs' outer skeletons are made of.
Chitin.
Oh, the bugs.
They have a chitinous exoskeleton.
If you're ever feeling really chitty, that's because you're an insect-man.
Or because your exoskeleton is rotting away from your inards.
Princess, we had that problem with one of her exoskeletal fingernails there.
Her integument there, that rind on the end of her finger, if you notice, is rotting off.
Oh, I always thought you were noting the spur on her heel area, which looked kind of like...
What were the names of those flies?
Turns me on.
Wow.
They can do some damage.
Tobson flies.
Hmm.
My favorite.
Covered with rich milk chocolate.
Smothered in peanuts and raisins.
And shoved down the children's throats at Dobbs Town!
Yes, baby!
At Dobbs Town!
Where you can rock out and pile on and cool in and groove.
Cop a groove go.
Pile on day and night.
And the all night, all day mosh pit in Dobbs Town.
You'll never experiencing anything like it before, Nemzes.
We have been in Dobbs Town for so long that the radio station here seems quite unfamiliar.
We can barely see!
We've been swinging through the jungles, friends.
Actually, it's been...
The out-of-Cleveland people have already heard the recordings from X-Day.
And some even from Starwood.
Some even rumbled in the jungle.
But here in Cleveland, friends, we're on hour of slack number 1,167.
Yes, indeed.
But this is a live one now, so that...
It's alive.
It's alive!
The show is alive!
You don't understand!
It's not just the people.
The show itself is alive.
It's the people.
It has cavalieries and it has aortas and it has the veins.
The veins?
And it has brains?
It has a brain, all right!
Wait a minute.
Well, if you want to call it a brain...
What to call it a brain?
The show has a brain after a fashion.
After a fashion, yes.
It has background music by the Flying Ryan Brothers.
That's what this is.
A very fashionable brain with a good background.
He went to school all over the place.
I'm flying with the Ryan Brothers.
He actually fly high with the Ryan Brothers.
Yeah.
He wrote the book on Ryanetics.com.
Now, is this similar to the Bob Leografon or any other works of the subgenius?
Is it like, say, for instance, any of the Scientology books, even?
Or is it just a rancid piece of pulp that should be thrown in the toilet?
L. Ron Hubbard stole all that stuff from J.R. Bob Dobbs.
Wait a minute.
Who stole what?
L. Ron Hubbard stole all that Dianetics stuff from J.R. Bob Dobbs.
And then the Flying...
The Flying Brothers stole the Ryanetics stuff from themselves.
From each other, actually.
They were very competitive twins.
Okay, I want to change characters now and become an interview guy just to get this straight.
Everyone I've been staying has just told us that Scientology is not a ripoff of Scientology.
It's a ripoff of the church.
It's a satire, actually.
It's a satire of the church of the subgenius.
That's what Scientology is.
Oh, that is...
I'd never heard that before.
It was a takeoff on the church.
Because, you know, they were like a rebellious new...
group back in the 50s.
And the church of the subgenius, of course, had been around for a long time by the time
L. Ron decided to get off his tookus or toughus or whatever they...
Wow, that is totally amazing.
Now, one tender fish I'd like to ignore you, if you possibly could, without getting too
remaindering or having any feisty feelings towards that urchin over there.
What really happened?
I hadn't even noticed that urchin.
Well, just don't get too responsive because we're on...
Look at those spines.
Right.
Man.
I bet you could...
You could really get poked with that urchin.
That's why we do have Zilly as an urchin intern here.
And beautiful Kay Watt.
And so that's why I'd like to ask you, without getting too excited, what happened, the massacre
after X-Day?
I mean, is this a rumor going around?
Well, it wasn't really a massacre.
It was the opposite.
It was the dead were brought back to life and shuffled to the music of...
That they...
Friends of Chaz Smith Band.
Remember that?
Right.
Oh, no.
Except that you were rained out of that one.
Well, what the hell were they called?
That was not under the reign of Dave.
The French Davidian reign.
It was under the Wearden reign.
I did witness them try to bring back the muscular Chaz of E. Smith back into existence with
the rampant thoughts of their minds.
Well, that happened...
What the hell?
That happened at X-Day.
They didn't dare to do that at Starwood because...
Well, you know, people are a little bit...
They're a little bit more sensitive there.
They've got some explosive personalities.
At Rumble in the Jungle, Chaz came back as a powerful rainstorm, almost powerful enough
to put out the gigantic funeral pyre.
Yes.
Actually, somebody asked the other day about subgenius funerals.
It came up on Alt.Slack.
Somebody said, has there ever been a subgenius funeral?
And it's like, well, several months after Chaz died and after his normal funeral...
Which was kind of weird with drummers and people like me talking and so forth, the bongos
and everything.
Then there was the X-Day...
There was the first Rumble in the Jungle.
The baptism of the dead at X-Day.
And then at Starwood, there was a concert for the friends of the Tiki Banzai.
His old campground was brought back to life with light shows.
With exhibits showing lots of really great photographs.
Graphs of him and all of his artwork.
And beautiful naked women raping young, shy subgeniuses like Reverend Steve Sinek, who
actually was literally, as part of the Rumble in the Jungle at Starwood, Reverend Steve
Sinek was not raped exactly because he wasn't resisting that much.
But you know those dames out there at Brushwood, those wooden sprites?
They can be a bit forward, hey?
Dames.
Yeah.
I know how they are.
I ended up having...
Having to baptize Reverend Allison as a subgenius just in order to make it no longer be bestiality.
Now, does she have money on both sides?
Otherwise, Steve would have been literally having some sort of social intercourse with
a beast.
A beast.
A human.
A mere hume, as we call them.
A normworm.
A pink girl.
You're like the goat with a thousand breasts.
Do you understand?
Listen to them squealing.
You call yourself human?
Like little piglets.
Sit down, you pig.
You're not a human being.
The fools.
And so we made...
We changed her...
We changed her species from human to subgenius simply by giving her an honorary subgenius
membership pack.
And so that was packed well.
It was an exciting...
I would say she's a well-stuffed pack.
It was exciting.
It was very exciting.
For everyone involved.
Yes, for the voyeurs.
Now, do some subgenius women after their abacrombation or near their courageous muscle tubes, do
they actually grow different glandular orifices like new breasts on their back?
No, it's mostly hidden.
They have barbs on the inside so that once you get in, you can't get out.
Oh.
They'll clench you there and hold you there until they've got all your money.
They must have come through here.
They must have come just through here.
I didn't even see them.
My money's gone.
And I've got these scars all over my attachment.
I've got nothing at all.
I'm holding a piece of...
I have barb scars all over me.
I'm holding a piece of breechies and a half-drunk glass of wine.
What happened?
Bob must have been here.
He did something to us and...
But what?
Look.
Wait.
Was that him?
Look, there he goes.
Let's go after him, then.
Get the torches.
No, that's just a figure.
That's just a solitary figure.
Oh, okay.
That was a scarecrow.
No, no, no.
It is him.
Somebody get a pipe.
A torch.
A lighter.
Somebody get a gun.
A time machine.
We'll blow him up.
We'll use the time machine to explode Bob.
Well, here we are.
Oh, no.
No, he's coming.
I think we angered him.
No, he's in front of us now.
He's coming.
Bob.
Wow.
Yes.
Where'd you get those new shoes?
Where did I get them?
Where did you sell them to me?
New shoes?
Oh.
Bob, I thought you were going to kill me.
I make my own shoes.
How much can I give you for those shoes, man?
Stang, I'm the world's greatest salesman, but I'm not the world's stupidest salesman.
I've been around the block a few times, as you happen to know and have capitalized on.
You're a good salesman.
Just sit back in your seat and listen to me, buddy.
You've taken over, see?
You forgot who the main man was.
You forgot who this church was all about.
It ain't about you, you scrawny runt.
Look into my face.
No, don't hit me, Bob.
Don't hit me.
Look into these eyes.
No.
Don't hurt Princess Weed.
Take it like I'm man.
Oh.
Princess Weed likes it.
Come on over there, baby.
What happened in here?
It looks like there's been an explosion of some kind.
Everything...
What are those clowns doing here?
What's...
There's blood on the wall and clowns with...
Bloody clowns everywhere.
Oh my God.
You, sir.
What...
What happened?
I...
I was doing the Ripple Temple routine.
And the big cat just...
I don't know.
We saw this face with a pipe in it.
And then they...
It was supposed to be a Bigfoot corpse.
Yeah, yeah.
But it wasn't.
It wasn't.
It was some kind of explosion...
Exploding thing.
And we think the Bob guy took off that way.
And...
Oh, man.
I've got to get to triage.
My foot's falling off.
Thanks.
Oh, yeah.
And don't forget, next week it's about...
Friends, speaking of clowns, the devotional is coming up.
For those here in the Cleveland-Akron area, you'll be interested to know, possibly, that
on August 30th...
At the Beachland Ballroom, the devotional returns.
Now, if you were...
If you're ready for the truth, and if you know the truth of Devo, I forget who all's
going to be there.
Last time, Jerry Casale of the Devos.
He could put you, like, square on about the, what do you call it, bloody clowns and so
forth.
And General Boy, the father of the Devos.
Boogie Boys' dad, himself.
Yeah.
And KRK Ryden, the artist of the Devos.
He's blind now, in both ears.
And a bunch of really great bands are always there.
The term Nordic American Bund was my favorite.
But that's August 30th at the Beachland Ballroom.
And to get more information, well, you could look at subgenius.com events, and then go
to boogieboysbasement.com.
Boogieboysbasement.com.
Boogie being spelled B-O-O-J-I.
Boys' basement.
Boogieboysbasement.com.
But it's not like boys were...
But a Y-Z, you say.
It's just like a Boogie Boys.
And then, isn't there like, D-Voieoke or something, where people sing?
Oh yeah, right.
It's gonna be a whole karaoke thing.
Well now, but before that...
For the limbless people...
That's on a Saturday.
That's on the day of Saturn.
Oh yes, but...
But on Friday, Frius Day...
Friaste.
There is an art show called the Jocko Domo at Asterix Gallery in Cleveland, Ohio.
Would that be the...
Would that be on 185th Street or someplace where that'd be?
No, actually it's on 2393 Professor Avenue, Professor.
Oh, Professor.
That's delightful.
Oddly enough.
Over in Tremont.
We were just talking about Professor Chaz, and here it's Professor Ave, 2393.
But it's an art show of the...
You know that dome hat, the pyramid stepped red hat of the Devos?
Some call it a flowerpot hat.
Yeah, the flowerpot hat, or the power dome is actually the way they like to call it.
Well, you can buy those.
It's the power dome.
Little plastic ones.
And Reverend Bruce Perry...
Monkey Boy.
Monkey Boy bought many and offered them to artistes such as ourselves, Reverend Susie
the Floozy, and much more famous ones like K.R.K.
Ryden, and said, make this dome hat into art and people who can come to the show.
And it's a benefit also for Magdalene's...
Reverend Magdalene and Jesus.
And the subgeniuses' legal costs.
You know, the subgeniuses whose child was taken away by the conspiracy because of their
religion, and then...
And it was given back.
And they only got it back because the bio dad screwed up so badly.
So there's lots of money that needs to be...
But their legal costs are beyond imagining, and even...and Bob ain't helping them out.
So, it's a benefit for the baby, Conbo, and...who actually is a teenager now.
I thought he was 43 years old, but...
But we have a...Princess, we and I have an entry in that...actually, our entry is by...
It's not for sale.
It's by us, Jerry Casale, who designed the Devo hat dome, dome hat, power dome.
St. Joe Riley, who made the mask from the bust of Bob made by Hel Swami Satellite Weavers,
and that's all you need to know right there.
It was made by us.
It was made by a consortium of subgeniuses.
You will...if you go...if you go to the Jocko Domo art show, you will see Bob.
You will see Bob.
If you come to that show...if you come, you'll see Bob.
I can honestly say that, my friend.
Look at these people are all clamoring.
No, they don't know that Bob has never...
You can't listen to that clamoring.
...never seen Bob yet.
That's a bunch of hooey.
He's never gonna show up, see?
Listen, I've been following this Church of the Subgenius for the last 45 weeks.
I've been around the block a few times, and believe me, my arm's at tire.
And I'm telling you once, and I'm telling you twice.
If I could tell you three times in all, I'm telling you, there is no Bob.
You understand?
It's a joke.
It's like an inside satirical...
I don't hear you.
I don't hear anything.
La-La-La-La-La-La-La-La-la-la-la-ma.
Listen, Bobby.
La-La-La-La-La-La-La-La-La-la-la-la-la...
La-La-La-La-No-Ta-La...
Listen, Bobby.
It's a joke.
I don't want to hear your...
W-what... that's not all it is, though.
Sure, it's a joke.
But is Bob only a joke, my friends?
Is he not a man? Does he not bleed?
Does his pipe not smoke frop?
What?
Oh my god, apparently his pipe is smoking frop!
Oh no, that's clean!
The clouds!
I can't breathe!
Oh my god!
Reach! Oxygen switch!
Oh doctor, this is some of the best times I've ever had.
Taking the body of Bob Dobbs apart and selling to different organs was gonna make us a million bucks.
Uh, Doc? Doc, you look sleepy.
Grumpy?
Hey! Wake up!
Listen!
Oh, it's just so exciting. This show is just so exciting I got to carry it away.
I'm selling the organs of Bob Dobbs at a fraction of the cost.
The origins of Bob are swathed in mystery and toilet paper.
By pranksters. Teenagers.
A thin tissue of...
Showed up at night and, yes, a tissue of lies surrounds Bob's body as he lays in state.
The Turin toilet paper has picked up a radioactive image of Bob.
We'll sell that later along with the 080808 water.
We have vials of water from 08... from August 8th, 2008.
From August 8th, 2008.
Right, the date, 80808.
Which is like if 8-0 looks like B-O and O-B smells like B-O.
Or 08.
So it's like 0808 means oh Bob.
Anyway, friends, we have to pause, unfortunately, for a...
Well, it's not a station ID, but it's a...
Theoretically, a public service announcement.
We're being thrown out for a few minutes.
This program is presented by the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.
Sometimes small turtles, meaning those with a shell of four inches long or less,
still turn up as household pets in the United States.
Unfortunately, the degree of an animal's cuteness doesn't have any relationship to whether it's healthy or infected with rabies.
Turtles can cause serious illness with diarrhea, fever, and vomiting.
The best way is to have pet turtles in your house.
And to teach children to touch turtles.
And get sick from turtles.
Members of several girls' softball teams bit at least two people.
And tested positive for rabies.
Rather than pick them up, call Animal Control.
What do you think, Bob? Would hand grenades force it out?
I don't know. I can't tell what that thing will do or where it will do it.
Start blasting it, Bob. We're moving up with another unit.
Yes, sir.
Anything there, Bob? Hello, Bob?
Can you hear me?
Can you hear me, Bob?
Come in, Bob.
It's easy and it's free.
Government health experts taking a bribe.
Pimples.
Fatal pneumonia.
Healthy cigarettes in New York City.
I tried to quit, but I'm addicted.
I'm addicted.
Come November.
Incumbent.
If you're looking for a job, do not look.
But if you're looking for a career.
Aura? That all of.
Oh, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Wait! Wait! Wait! Wait!
Let me chew my nails. Let me chew my nails.
Climaxes.
Don't miss this 4-hour do-it-yourself festival.
And much more.
Be cheap.
So, here's the bottom line.
Here's the bottom line.
Harmful chemicals.
What do you get for that hard man?
I don't want Hillary on his stick.
Mm-hmm.
Last week, you may remember, we told you good news for cat lovers.
I've always known cat was good.
Yes, cat made with vinegar.
Vinegar?
Cat experts say vinegar is the secret of cat's marvelous flavor.
I never tasted such marvelous flavor.
Nobody could miss the way it brings out the best in cat flavor.
So next time you make up your shopping list, you'll say,
Cat is wonderful.
And best of all,
Gold.
I recommend gold.
Gold, gold, gold, gold, gold, gold, gold, gold, gold, gold.
Gold, it's free, and there's gold, gold, gold, gold, gold, gold, gold now.
Gold today.
Gold, that's gold.
My machine.
My...
This is the thought of my reaction.
Conviction, confusion, suspicion
What a long reaccusation
With a face of opposition to it
I am a machine
With the fruit of my endeavors
Hates the bitter and the sweet
Too intense to pour my efforts
No submission, taste the sweetness
I am a machine
My machine
Hats it!
Conviction, confusion, suspicion
Thank you.
accompanied students at the Chilswood
ElMME and Gie frost rented back
They had not discovered the seki
SeekiSneJah,
stick to achieve shelter,
fire, and
fertility.
As we see here in Diorama
15, all of the
people of the village have converged
upon a pyramid-looking
monument of some kind.
The Pyramid of Bob, they call it.
And there's the face on the top of the
pyramid, and we notice that
the artist here... There's a broken stump
where the pipe once
jutted out from the mighty face.
That's correct, sir. A pipe has
been jutting out of the noisy face.
10,000 slaves died to
carry the lintel of that great pipe.
Yes, sir. 10,000 slaves did
indeed carry the lintel all the way up
to the top of the pyramid, and by
use of some mysterious technology
which we yet cannot... More slaves,
I think, is what that mysterious
technology... Probably, sir. There were more slaves
than were needed, but the point is
this technology still eludes
us today, and look at what a miracle
it's created.
Gaze upon these mighty
works, ye pathetic
bobbies, and tremble,
for such is the might
of Bob.
Bob is as
Pharaoh, as Pharaoh
is as gods, Bob
is as the gods.
Isis, Osiris, Horus,
all are the denizens
of his domain.
Look out over the window.
This only shines through
on the fortnight of the
Beezlewhip. On this
night and this night only,
the face is seen over the vast
desert and creation.
Look.
That's the wrong face.
The other gods had to sit in the
waiting room of the great
god, Bob, the
over-god, or the
over-mind of all
souled and insolent
beings. Believe me,
it ain't no fun being an elder
god. When I was
a younger god,
I could move
mountains from old as my mind
did my better.
Wait a minute.
When I was a...
I am civilized, man.
Using the power of the weak,
I built the pyramids.
Copyrighted. 1969.
The Fireside Theater.
Thanks for mentioning that part.
I had to be an old man and quote...
At least I'm not quoting Monty Python or
The Simpsons.
Now I'm thinking about...
George Tirebiter.
Good news, everyone.
George Tirebiter contemplating the nature of Bob.
And that is a silly, silly
position to put yourself in.
It's much worse than the yoga pose
they call the Cobra Dog.
Have you ever seen anybody do that?
They have to wrap their anus around their...
Well, you have to actually...
The meaty part of your ear
has to go in the
encephalitis organ of the...
I don't know.
Somebody told me about it.
I'm not...
I'm not really sure about all the details.
Sounds like quite a dangerous pose.
It is not something that should be taken up
by the weak at heart and the inexperienced.
Only those who know these old manner of yoga
and different asanas can permit it
to try the Cobra Dog thing,
whatever was described earlier.
Only those who are allowed into the temple
of the Dobbs
may learn such...
such...
tricky sex moves,
such as this one.
The monkey proffers a peach.
The monkey...
A big favorite of Connie's,
discovered by the monk Bob.
This is also in the Chinese
Kamikaze also.
It tickles me so much.
That's why the monkey proffers...
That's why the monkey is supposed to tickle you
like a monkey.
He's a very ticklish profferer,
that little monkey is, isn't he?
That's what we're looking for, my lad.
That apple at the end of his little skinny arm.
That's what we're looking for.
I mean a peach.
Ticklish monkeys who like the peach.
Ah, the ticklish monkey.
That's what we've been breeding for.
Unfortunately, humans resulted.
The Yetis were trying to breed a ticklish monkey,
and what they came up with was a hairless ape,
which now is called a human being
by other human beings who are just hairless apes.
Right. And we're trying to breed a human being, by other human beings who are just hairless apes.
As opposed to us, who are hairless Yetis.
It's different.
It's vastly different.
The organs are even arranged differently.
People just don't understand that there are those among them
who are not among them.
Can we... must we...
How can we reiterate this?
How can we make this clear to people?
There are the people next to you in the bus.
Don't even try. Don't even try.
Don't gaze into their eyes.
They're not even really eyes you're gazing into.
They have too much intelligence to be able to understand Bob's word.
They're too, quote, smart.
To even begin to comprehend the simplicity,
the perfect clarity,
the single note that Bob is playing of slack,
the note of slack.
Each person hears it differently in the distance.
I hear it as A-flat, tired.
I hear it as B-flat, on top of yourself.
And some feel it rising up from between their legs.
Like the condolini smiling through the organs of the earth.
And others have a C-flat.
Acidly flux.
Don't try that again, you'll hurt me.
But friends, even though you may want to choke it up and spit it out,
no, you must swallow the word of Bob.
Hook, line, and sinker.
For is he not the salesman?
The man of sales who came
and continues to for you.
Thank you. Thank you.
I'd just like to thank the other sales managers
for allowing the Reverend Ivan Stang
of the Church of the Subgenius,
the foundation church for all of us here at the Subgenius Seminar,
for that wonderful prep.
And the steak and beans philosophy behind it's going to put a lot of you and your in on the map.
So don't forget to make one right up.
I'm your cartographer for tonight.
Step right up in the book.
The bonds are loaded.
We've got factory direct refreshments.
And some of the kids aren't even from this planet.
So let's just respect each other as long as we can because it's going to be over soon.
Let's get out the cell, cell, cell, cell.
Just like Bob would. Cell, cell.
You, you in the back. You're not...
Put him in a cell.
Throw him in the sales cell.
Not the sales cell.
The poor sales. The cell for the poor sales.
No, no, no. He's not. He's not.
No, not the...
I'm not going to throw out. I ain't doing anything wrong.
I'm afraid you have done something wrong.
You've interrupted a Church of the Subgenius Sales Seminar meeting.
I'm sorry.
And now it's time for you to take a brief relapse in the sales cell.
Hey, have either one of you guys seen the Bigfoot corpse photo?
From Soviet Georgia.
Yeah, yeah, that's right. That's why the Russians are invading Georgia.
Right, that's what...
Because the Georgians found the Atlanteans out there.
The Atlanteans actually of Georgia found the corpse of a Bigfoot.
Well, they said it was the Lemurians.
Real Yeti?
Either that or they rented a costume and put some possum guts across the top of it.
Right, or the decorum. It might have been the actual corpse.
That was the sad thing is that the DNA tests on the recently found Bigfoot corpse revealed only the DNA of Hugh Mann and Opossum.
Yes. Is it true? Is Bigfoot not a Yeti or a Sasquatch actually, but a possum man?
Perhaps somebody who played dead all the way from the island of Dr. Moreau?
Good Lord, man.
Maybe it was playing dead to begin with as it lay there.
Right, and it's still playing dead. That never occurred to me.
Man!
That thing could be crawling out of that freezer of those poe buckers in Atlantean Georgia any second now.
Yeah.
It had perfect teeth.
Wake up, Lembo.
There was a close-up of the creature's mouth with its tongue poking out.
The tongue looked like a cow's tongue from the store and the teeth were perfect.
Well, that's what they did.
The whitest, smoothest, most unmarked wild animal teeth you ever saw in your life. In the photo I saw.
Probably.
Of course, it could have been touched and touched and touched and retouched.
Well, it certainly was touched as well.
Somebody was touched. I was touched when I heard the news that us another Bigfoot had died.
I wept like a hirsute baby woman.
I couldn't control myself.
I didn't even know if they were my tears. I had the feeling that one of the obelisks was beaming tears into my eyes.
Like, I'm for the Earthmen to cry. And then we all cry in unison.
There are so few yetis left.
Well.
In Georgia, in Soviet Georgia.
But what if they are not only part Russian but part opossum and part plosive?
Then you really don't know when they're dead or when they're just drunk.
Right. They're just lying around and stuff. But you don't want to make them mad, I guess.
I guess that's the lesson as the lexicon actually we should do.
Well, I live over in Cleveland Bluffs. There's a lot of old Russian ladies that remind me of Bigfoot.
I don't mean to be ethnically snorish like that.
But come on. They really actually do.
Well, my ancestors wore babooskas. And yet none of them were familiar with the saints or hollow beings or the exoskeletons of weird beings.
Bags?
I thought your ancestors were Urovians.
Oh, yeah. That's right. They're from south central eastern southern part.
Dave-mania.
Those women in our neighborhood are not yetinsins. They're just Russian women.
Old.
Oy, oy, oy, oy, oy, oy.
Sturdy. Of sturdy stock.
Oy, oy, oy, oy, oy, oy. Come here 1922.
Fierce looking. They have an expression like a yeti.
1907.
Have you ever seen a Russian woman?
Have you ever tried smiling at them?
Only once.
And what happened?
I can see the scar. You don't have to tell me what happened.
It moved down.
It would be better for the show if you did.
Oh, no, no.
Tell us what happened. Is that a wind socket or is that actually your colostomy bagger?
Come on.
I'm forgetting something. There's something really important that we're supposed to say on this show.
Well, number one, you're not wearing headphones. It looks like you're wearing one of those balloon hats.
Oh, my grandbaby is due in a second. This is actually as we do this show on August 17th of this time, not your time, listener.
My daughter, my dafter, Sivit, is due to throw or whelp her first litter of little stangies.
Whelplings.
Little teeny stang grandchild.
Yeah.
Stang.
And that's supposedly due any second now. Princess Wee's cell phone, there's that word again, cell, should ring in the prison of her mind.
And then we'll know.
We'll know if it's a boy or a girl. Or a man or beast.
Not man! Not beast! But thing! Thing!
What if she were to give birth to perhaps two strapping young lads she'd love?
She wanted to call them Romulus and Remus. And then suddenly, as their grandfather, you would become Saturn, the mighty emissary of the sun.
The progenitor.
Not crows. The progenitor. And then they would start a noble city on seven hills. And then they would...
They shall call me Dad. No, actually, they shall call me D-Doll.
D-Doll and Weemo.
D-Doll.
Oh, you shall.
You shall.
No doubt we'll end up being called whatever that first child can pronounce.
And that'll be the name that sticks.
I was the first grandchild on either side in my family, and I got to name one set of grandparents Noon and Nunk.
And the other set was called Mamu and Papu.
And all of the cousins and siblings that followed all used those same names.
I called my grandpa Bursar.
And my grandmother Reprobate.
And I also... There was a curmudgeonly Stinquistle, and there was one guy, Cornucopius.
You've had a good diction as a child, because all I could say was Noon and Nunk.
Well, I stuck out my tongue the same way you did like that, but I have a split in my tongue.
Papu.
Weemo.
This is why I'm gifted with language.
I love you, Weemo.
I'm part snake. You don't know until you look deep into my...
Sorry.
Dave the Snake Man.
You know, I was thinking about that show Lost, and if Dave...
If Subgenius was Lost, or Lost Island was X-Day...
Yes, yes, yes.
Dave would be Locke, because he's a man of faith.
And I would, of course, be represented by Jack Shepard, man of science.
And also because I look so much like Matthew Fox.
Especially when he's a degenerate in the flash-forwards.
When he has the beard and is doing all the drugs.
I really look a lot like Matthew Fox in Lost.
But, yeah, Dave, you're probably not familiar with that show.
No, I'm an extreme intellectual type person.
I don't watch television.
It's against my religious self-awareness.
We don't watch television.
We only download.
See, we download.
That's different.
We download television.
Right, right, right.
So then, yeah, you're not a boob dude, you're a vidiot guy.
Yeah, we are.
We just had to skip the commercials.
Just don't watch broadcast.
So do you like make decisions in your normal, everyday, earthly man and wifely life based upon if Jack, you know, bungles his way through the dinosaur necks?
On that show.
In fact, that show can be used like the I Ching.
And if you refer to the blast-proof door map, you can actually have your own life guided by the, wherever you spin the map and where it lands.
The blast door map that I'm talking about.
It only shows up under black light.
So are you spurted out into the cartological design of this map area?
I mean, you're just instantly teleported there?
Only if you enter the numbers on time.
Oh.
4, 8, 15, 16, 23, 42.
On what kind of time frame?
You can tell we got really nerded out.
For three months, all Princess Wee and I did was watch one episode of that show every night.
And we finally got through.
I'm soaking it.
Now we're going to watch it.
Now we're caught up to where everybody else is.
And it's back to being a complete mystery.
And thank God it's not on anymore because we've been watching other things instead.
The last time.
What did we see last night?
The 400 Follies of Satan by Georges Melies.
Yeah.
Hand-colored 1906 film.
Yeah, that was cool.
Piano accompaniment.
In which Satan and his imps hopped around and did little acrobat tricks.
They were rollick and flock.
Appeared and disappeared in puffs of smoke.
That was like the Star Wars of its day.
And the color comes and goes.
And the voice box breaks.
Was it like the first film by Lex Cargo or whatever his name of train arriving at a station?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Well, it's almost time to.
Yeah, we have to move into collage and fade out time.
Plus, I wanted to get in just before we leave the recordings from Bob Bob Day from 80808.
Oh, yes.
With Ms. Star Sistar.
And if you listen real carefully, you can hear little Mr. Sistar ask if it's going to
rain.
And we wanted to make an announcement.
But we should have to play that now.
It's been edited today.
Connie's Ovaries.
Some sort of holy pronouncement about Connie's Ovaries.
And Connie's Ovaries.
Today is the day.
Today is the day of, yeah, Connie's Ovaries.
So fry them up, friends.
Ovariesy, scrambled omelet, wherever you want to do it.
Slice it as a piece of paper delicious anyway.
And if you need more information about the Hour of Slack and the Church of the Subgenius,
you can certainly check our website at www.thehourofslack.com.
And now, thanks to Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
Thank you.
And Princess Wee Ardo, queen of all the UFOs.
We now go to our prepared, prepared, prepared ending for this show.
We now go to our prepared ending.
This is our Astrid Ask.
Often urged us to live each moment with great ask in view.
But the women who flourish most, who delight most in that calling and are best at it, these
are women who are the best at it.
Women who are aware of the world.
They're aware.
The mom who is home.
I think the moms to be mom.
They're aware of things.
So this woman will delight most.
Big enough to say in front of him, probably going to shrivel up on her and she's going
to feel that it's small and constraining.
My mind wasn't well done and my mind was small and constraining.
All right, friends, we're here at where it is.
We're here at the
Rarities on Probability Pasture Road in Cleveland.
Reporting to you on the hour of slack that as we record this with Mr. Arsistar, Princess
Wee and little Mr. Arsistar, this is the day, the day of, yes?
It's Bob-Ob Day.
It's Obob Day.
Obob or Bob-Ob.
August 8th, 2008.
Or Spirit.
Or Zub.
Zub, as we would say.
Yeah, H-O-A-Zub.
It's Zub.
A blessed date because it's a Bob date.
And we are cognizant of that.
Very cognizant.
And so cognizant that we're bearing down on 8.08 p.m. according to my watch.
Yes, it's...
Which is fixed to French Mean Time.
It's 8.08 somewhere.
Bob o'clock.
That's right.
Technically not right here in Cleveland.
It's Obob.
It's actually 6.08.
Obob.
But it's in the middle of the Atlantic Ocean.
Obobob.
It's already 8.08.
People in Newfoundland are joyous.
Yes.
They're shouting it is now the moment.
It is not just the day of Bob.
Eh?
But the very minute of Bob.
The second of Bob.
Man, these wereby fries.
8.08 and 8 seconds.
Oh, man, we missed that one.
Oh, yeah.
8.08.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
That would be Bob-Bob-Bob.
Bob-Bob-Bob.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Meanwhile, the hundreds of people in line are trying to ignore us as we.
That is good.
As we can arf down our sandwiches.
No, no.
And I keep the hand away from the food.
The hand.
Wow.
Rain?
No, it's not going to rain.
Well, maybe it will rain on the Bob-Bob Day.
You know, if you save the rain on Bob-Bob Day in a vial, you can cure things later.
You better have a vial later today.
For the next hundred years.
Save the rain from tonight and sell it on the internet.
Drops in little tiny vials.
Lucky Bob water that heals.
Two drops on my windshield already.
Lucky healing Bob power water.
But I must finish my chili because, according to my calculations,
that the real 808, it will cause me to produce an erectation at precisely the right moment.
Ah, there you go.
You're timing your pyroflaculation perfectly.
Mmm.