I think...
I think we got it.
I think she's a brawn.
I think...
Before the sermon,
a message concerning
for Bob-Bots,
living avatars,
in seconds.
You have to
love Bob.
He loves you, but
you love Bob.
You have to.
Or else what happens if you don't love Bob?
He'll kill you.
He'll rob you out.
And I guess that was a big deal back in them days.
Back in them days.
Go back in them day.
We're now deep inside the brain cavity of Doug Smith.
As you can see all around you,
there are sparky-
There's a short circuit.
...seem to have recovered.
Now, there are sparking energy,
thoughts all around us.
Far more than the normal human brain.
But as we know, another misfire, we know Doug Smith is not a normal human.
No, and here inside the brain of Doug Smith, we can observe some of the differences that
make this man a unique leader among men.
Over here is the main printout.
This is the sub-channel of Global Women's Week.
I run it like Uncle Graze Bob.
To be a good man.
Turn on the machine.
This is three.
And this is three.
And this is a new one.
Oh, no, it's not.
But it is a new one.
It is the...
It's the hippie redneck nerds that hate everybody's show.
That's what kind of a show it is.
It is dark now.
And if you want to see the real news, come and see Doug Smith.
I've got a little piece of the story here.
And I'm going to tell you a story that I've written a couple of times.
This is the...
As I sit here and watch the mist rise from the bottom of the earth, a new light shines
upon this rock where I was born.
I watch myself step out and find a new beginning.
Ah yes, dear friends, and that new beginning, that new light is
here.
Partly this new album in progress by the Southland Corporation, the new band with
Jayner Hyperkleets in Little Rock, Arkansas.
Baba, Baba doesn't live here.
Anymore.
Baba, Baba...
Baba doesn't live here anymore
My little tiny little creature of the planet
Because you are very different
I can tell you have some special needs
Baba!
Sometimes I can tell that you want to be my little friend
Alright, if you can tell me something that I can learn for someone like yourself
Because you're
Baba!
I thought I could look into my mind
And find some way I can communicate with other people like my kind
That's...
I have some things I can think about sometimes when I'm sitting here
Because I'm a very special person
I'm...
Baba!
Babe!
And now...
The Soft Meer.
I...
I can't stand...
The subgenius hour of slack that you are about to listen to
is specially designed only to be played on radio station...
Right here.
And only in the city of...
This place.
Should any other shows be heard from or contacted in the course of this show,
the listener is advised to remain calm and only contact listed or unlisted officials
in the event of any material from this radio or other listening device being inhaled during broadcast.
Thank you.
It's summertime here in Dallas, Texas, yes.
We had to turn the air conditioning off, you know, in order to do this show.
So it's hot.
It's really hot.
And it's the year of the itch, it seems.
These days, you're the jiggers.
I mean, it's that season when things hurt you.
The mosquitoes, the zits, both blackheads and whiteheads,
the fleas, the poison ivy, the sunburn, the dry skin,
the allergies, the hives, the scabs, the nicoderm patches,
the cutaneous discoid lupus, the heat rash, the ringworm,
the eczema, the psoriasis, the diaper rash, the mites,
the body lice, the head lice, the bed bugs, the scabies,
the crab lice, the impetigo.
The hemorrhoids, the yeast infections, the poison oak,
the athlete's foot, the pinworms, the chicken pox,
the antabuse reaction, and worst of all,
the itch inside your ear that nothing can reach.
And the only way you can scratch that itch inside your ear
is to go...
And, uh, dear friends, uh, your host here with the nerve bumps,
the red bump syndrome, the king of scurf himself,
your host and prayer partner, Reverend Ivan Stang,
is, uh, so, so itchy.
But yet, but yet, dear friends, uh, it is, after all, a show of hope.
Yes.
Let's get some hopeful sort of music on in the background here.
Eh?
There we go.
Eh, there we go.
See, we can get this stuff to work.
Eh, eh.
Uh, thanks to the, uh, thanks to the listeners
in, uh, many, many different towns.
Those who donated, dear friends,
who donated either equipment or money to help us out
in our time of need.
And, uh, oh, we do have some...
Eh, some needs.
Oh, by the way, before I forget,
this music in the background is, uh,
by our good friend, uh, Dr. Kyle Cossop
and, uh, his band, uh, Severe Tire Damage.
Little piece in the background here called Psycho Bebop.
But I wanted to take this, uh, before we get on with the show,
which in this case is a...
Well, it's a Lonesome Cowboy Dave
version of...
Versus Janer type of show.
Uh, and also in this show,
we'll begin our Kooks profile series.
All taken from, uh, Donna Causey's new book, Kooks.
But first, I have to thank, uh, the, the donators.
And because this is gonna be a show of hope,
and it's, it's thanks to those who helped us out.
I've got a, a nice, uh, uh, TX,
six track here, uh, in conjunction with the Radio Shack deck.
Well, I could mix, I could be mixing eight things at once.
Now, I'm not gonna do that to you.
Don't you worry.
But, uh, I could.
And that's, we have to have that option, you know?
I gotta be able to have all the, what, the old beat-up turntable,
the destroyed CD player, everything.
And, uh, and the new, the new...
Oh, I just realized, I got another, another, uh...
Uh, another name to add here for our...
New tape deck.
Okay, here's, here's the donators that I must thank on the air.
Reverend Gary Ingram.
The great, the beyond great, the, the...
The Jim Hoffwood.
The Dave Santovan.
I hope that I'm pronouncing that name right.
Dave Santovan.
There in the, or Santovine.
Uh, he's...
He's a saint of Veen.
Uh, Bob Payne, who has actually reduced our Bob Payne by quite a bit.
The fine Nathan Vincent of Dallas, who helped us out so much.
The great Reverend Zafod Rakitansky.
Uh, yes, he is a relation.
Uh, the anonymous 7177.
111st Street.
But I better not tell you what town it's in.
Uh, but we, we do appreciate.
Uh, and, and, uh, Reverend Mike Cole.
Uh, there in WCSB in Cleveland.
And, uh, uh, friends.
You know, who, whoever else helps us out in between then and now.
Uh, we hope to present to you proof tonight.
Uh, that it, it does indeed make a difference.
And, uh,
I hope to present to you proof tonight.
But before we go even any further than that, there's one other thing that I think you have to know first.
Hello, everyone.
This is Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
For Brain Rot Radio Theater here on ESO Radio in Cleveland on WCSB.
And I'd like to speak to you tonight about how I found Bob.
Tonight's moist sermonette is entitled simply, How I Found Bob.
And not the position I found him in, bent over a lightning struck stump brain in Arabic.
No, I found him in a spiritual sense.
I found him on a slack way wall in Chinatown.
But it was not the hate.
Poisoned, idiot-faced, graphic vestal wound, which I found him in the spiritual sense.
I found him in Cleveland, the shoreway.
In the twisted grimaces of Russians driving by in 78 Chryslers, masturbating and arguing, gesturing wildly.
I found him in a bad onion breath in a bodega in New York.
In a rancid po-boy in New Orleans.
So, you see, I truly found him.
In a spiritual sense.
The sixth sense, if you will.
And the seventh, performing seal in the zoo, if you won't.
And only those with ears who may hear their own ears have ears to hear what their own ears have.
And I say to them, I have been called a moron, moron, more than once.
I've been called a fool.
But I know in my heart what I found.
Phony letters indeed.
There are resonances.
There are phrases in the alphabet which only Bob can pronounce.
And these are startling, fearful letters.
And they don't pronounce themselves dead or ended with Z.
But they have the power to make you commit treason.
To inspire you to acts of heroic ugliness and abstruse martyrdom.
But only Bob knows the keys.
Bob called you on the psychic hotline.
And as you know, in any professional life,
in any...
In any...
There are good and bad psychics.
Hi, Stephanie.
I see you coming into your life now in the...
But will I ever go to the bathroom again?
The psychic hotline of Bob and the psychic salmon spread opened doors for me.
Why not you?
There are so many little fat cells in the life of any tumorous macro-organism.
Twice a day, the captains of the corner area...
I've heard voices.
How it happens.
We're still positive.
Messages from the stale fries and handy-packed ketchup stick.
Don't carminate or change your mind.
Stop working.
Give up your job.
You'll never get another chance to be a troubleshooter.
Or a headcat, for that matter.
I see you will be doing something on the stage in the future.
Maybe...
Behind a chicken coop, perhaps in this lifetime.
But I predict that this will make a lot of people...
If you can call them that...
Very, very...
Very happy.
Hear that sizzling sound?
That's...
That's my...
Baby angst.
Nauseous to be.
I'm much more depressed now than I ever was,
thanks to that hateful grimace on that slack-away wall.
Give me some article of your personality.
That's right.
A bag of vomit.
A phony eyeball in the glass.
A flying in an ice cube.
A plastic doggy do-do-will-do.
Anything will do.
Just an article to hold.
I am getting a feeling now.
Of Bob as a hot, spicy, southwestern chili kind of guy.
Weird.
Because when I thought of the ham fest, I knew he would be there.
I'm getting messages now from...
All the diseased recipe.
Let's watch.
That feels so good.
Call the psychic hotline and...
And send the pants back.
Spray it on your bald spot.
An eight-and-a-half-foot jam sauce.
Ten-foot sandwich.
A deep-groove fasting belt and hamster holster
with wide-rimmed individually-squat square pendant
of the living fun god-da-da-ba-ba-da.
Da-da-bull.
It won't be long.
But I won't be attending.
I won't be there.
No Calumet City blues for me.
No Missouri mud flat plains rising the distance
or prairie dogs mushing up the feet of the little children.
Which I specifically, scientifically despoiled
in the name of Bob Dobbs in my errant dreams.
We all put on so many...
Masks.
And so many different soiled lingeries.
Imagine if your hair could look like this.
Well, it can.
Now if the world were truly your brooding, breeding,
brooding beauty playground.
But the hammy butt, the virgin of Guadalcanal wept,
the angels wept,
in Westro Senora de los...
De los 20 Terres.
En...
Es...
Pero para ti que...
Usted no vive con un higgy no más.
Tu madre y tu padre están muy triste.
Y abuela Laura is ahora completamente loco.
Pero mientras toda la oscuridad...
Tenemos esta esperanza que...
Hijo, ven a casa y...
Sincerely, your sterilized mother.
Another psychic message.
And finally, in concluding this moist sermonette,
I would like to say that the time you take
in reexamining each and every little layered word,
bringing deep, crunchy fish from the subconscious
to your plate so that you may eat.
Remember that Bob Dobbs worked on six days
and then the seventh he was a loafer.
And he gave fish so that you might eat and bite it.
The End
Subtitles by the Amara.org community
Angela Smith ESO Radio
and it is a beautiful thing.
I have to thank once again with Grand Funk Railroad.
And how heavy this is.
The grand cause of heavy metal.
I must once again thank Gary Ingram, Jim Hopwood,
and he would have us...
hopping, I'll tell you. Dave Santofin, Bob Payne, Nathan Vincent, 717 17th Street, Mike
Cole, and the Lonesome Cowboy Dave. And coming up, Janger Hypercleeps and Sterno Keycaver,
Sterno Docs, with a new tape that's sort of like the Beatles getting back together again,
as it turns out. They were, actually, they were sitting around in Little Rock in this
a young Reverend Andrew of the Ogre Network came to visit them, and they just, somehow
they reacted to the presence of that youthful subgenius fan in the, it's the Beatles getting
back together again. Here it is.
But, but can't you see what's driving him into this cult in the first place? I don't
know if it was the Palmer head, or the Trevino head, or the Sam Snead head he's been smoking.
But Ben, can't you see it's, it's not the head at all? Well, I don't know, it just,
it makes me mad, ma'am. It, it makes me pee. I know. Well, there was eight boys in Immokalee,
Florida. They were theorizing about the effect of insecticides on their, their bell pepper
crop.
What is the 12th one?
But Bob came over, just in the nick of time, and then...
Well, you see, Bob just took that pipe into his mouth, and he took down the
prop for a while, and he sat there looking at them, and he said...
I have to rectify the situation.
But how are you going to smoke their soul, he said. He quoted, he quoted thusly,
O yea, verily, ye unto ye, the smiling pink false prophets. And then Jaynor spake thusly...
A prayer to Bob, be speaking, O Bob, please, I humbly, be speaking, O Bob, please,
piously grant, request that ye, in your righteousness, might grant mine humble request that I might
be allowed to wield infinite power over all other living...
And suddenly, Prince Yesoplavsky burst in upon the scene. Rasputin was eating the poisoned
cakes. O yea, the poison was imbued upon the wine. It had been dissolved, but yet it was
weak. The arsenic had lost all its power. The czar, we know, had been so much more powerful
than he had yet lived. But how are we to find this out? Tune in next time. Same bad time,
same bad channel.
Craigorfrans said, then that means I must kill you. Then your mother was the
czar's great aunt, which means that you were the aborted fetus of Adolf Hitler and not
Ava Braun, but Ava Braun's sister.
And in 1898, the protoplastic foot covering factory was founded in Moscow. And yea, verily,
they said...
If you'd like to see the real thing, you can fly across the railroad tracks, across
the railroad tracks to the hamburger store.
But don't forget the Stompenboot, who was suddenly...
Next is the hamburger store.
Finally...
Enough said. Enough said. Said, said, said. Said, said, said.
But I probably...
Oh, you thought you're going to do some acid and listen to us?
of genius tape, huh?
Well.
Thought he was going to hang a damn
pack up his ass.
I didn't know where that pack was.
But Gaprobe friend said.
I'm saying that you're from
ABC Electrical. Wherever you go,
defects are going, too.
If you're defective while you're going,
it can be very, very implausible.
Wherever you go. Or painful.
Sometimes it's colostomic,
which is like catastrophic in an imploding sense.
Colostomy?
That's classic.
That's colossal cold and imploding.
Yes, it does have a rather
yuck quality.
It does have a little ring of the thing, doesn't it?
It has a little twang of dang.
It's reeks of...
Well, let's turn
to another
concept.
If you have another concept.
Anyway, keep up the good work and remember.
Gaprobe friend said.
I'm from ABC Electrical.
I'm saying that you're from ABC Electrical.
And I'm saying that you're from ABC Electrical.
Yeah, I think there's a little bit of Russian mixed in there.
I certainly hope so.
I was not at Auschwitz.
I did not perform the experiments on the twins.
They danced on me.
I beg your pardon?
The twins. They were my dance partners.
Really, Dan?
Yeah, man.
That's all right.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
Are you trying to tell me you're in some sort of sealed vesicle
where phlegm floats around in the air as if it were like
tiny little snakes corrupting our brains?
Exactly.
Oh, man.
Once those snakes crawl in, they can't come out.
I've had...
Our parents are to blame for that.
Well, our parents are to blame.
Who else said it better than your own self when you just said it
just right in there?
I'm sorry.
Well, you don't have to apologize for saying the truth.
Yes, I do.
We're being watched.
Okay.
Well, then apologize for all of us here, too.
Thank you.
Okay.
Now, I just wanted to say that when the corrupting snakes come into the brain of any vital organ,
asthma, ismism, or any other organ, it's not just the brain.
It's the brain.
It's the organism, as it is.
Right?
Why do you keep tittering in my direction?
I could see if there was a nipple at the end of it or something else, but this is nothing
more than explosion...
Oh, thank God for small favors.
Anyway, from our progalactic point of view, we think that it's very important to understand
that understanding is very important.
I'm glad you're not cyclical in your talk.
I'm glad you're not one of those people who just talks around in big, fat, stinking like
Indian wagon train circles.
You're welcome.
Oh, well, think nothing of it, you cynical boob.
What am I saying? No, I think you're actually a caller.
I beg your pardon?
I think you're actually a caller, aren't you?
Well, actually, I think you're a caller.
You mean this is not a tape loop?
I thought the voices were talking.
I thought we had a tape loop going the whole time.
Oh, I thought the little thing in my...
I hate using control like that.
Oh, yeah.
So this guy's real then, right?
Yeah.
Oh, I thought I was hallucinating.
Oh, great. This is great.
Then I've been interacting with another, well, in your case being.
I don't want to make my voice do that.
How do you make your voice do that?
Well, I think what you do is you just...
A little testicular spandex always helps.
It kind of, like, brings things down into a narrow focus.
Ah.
Now, that's what I like to hear.
Class 12.
Somebody said...
Submolecularly expanding and contracting like molten lava from...
Boobla.
Boobalo.
Boobala and boychick.
The old guys in the neighborhood used to say in Yiddish, they'd say,
boychick and boobala.
And the guy they called Boobala had a huge wart in the middle of his forehead.
And he used to argue vociferously about the most inane, absolutely absurd,
non-sequitur, totally stupid, psychical,
mean,
actions and action morons you could imagine.
Just back and forth,
yammy-yammering about this and that,
as if it all made a hell of a lot of sense.
And believe me,
to some of us down at the old,
the arm pit lunch diner,
the counter was always greasy and stained from his remarks.
He couldn't let up for a minute,
and therefore,
he spilled his ketchup.
He couldn't let up for a minute,
therefore,
the coffee hit the table as it drew,
and he pulled from his mouth as he splattered it endlessly skyward,
screaming these epithets over and over again.
Oh, boy, those were the days.
I can't remember anything about it right now.
Oh, I just, I just trespassed in that teeny tiny little zone where no one goes,
where you're not permitted to be.
That little teeny barbed wire unit,
that little mapped off area that everybody says is taboo-boo.
Well, I'm going there, pal.
I'm going there on a big, fat old jammin' wind surfer.
Surfer, surfer, surfer.
I'm going in a motorboat with all my friends.
No theory of origins can be considered a scientific theory in a strict sense.
Creation and evolution are inferences based on circumstantial evidence,
and predictions based on each model can be tested and compared with that circumstantial evidence.
Among creationists,
among those of almost all,
religious persuasions,
except atheists.
And among ev-
just are found those of almost all persuasions,
including atheists.
However,
since evolution is a mechanistic,
atheistic theory,
it is a basic dogma of agnosticism,
humanism,
and atheism in general.
The one-sided indoctrination of our students in this materialistic philosophy,
in the tax-supported public school,
in our pluralistic democratic society,
is a violation
of academic and religious freedoms.
Furthermore, it is poor science and poor education.
Come on everyone, join the fun.
We've got thinking on the run.
The Earth is circled by the sun.
Creation science polka.
Science classes in our schools taught by superstitious fools.
Jerry Fowell sets the rules.
Creation science polka.
The universe was fabricated in six letters.
The world is a virtual paradise.
The humans and the dinosaurs shared a condo in L.A.
Carbon dating makes us cringe.
We're the right-wing lunatic fringe.
Jesus died for our sins.
Creation science polka.
The Earth is circled by the sun.
Science classes in our schools taught by superstitious fools.
¶¶
According to the Big Bang Theory of the Origin of the Universe,
about 10 to 20 billion years ago,
all the energy and matter of this entire universe
were crammed into a cosmic egg of subatomic particles and radiation.
Of course, no one has the foggiest notion where this cosmic egg came from
or how it got there.
Zap! There it was.
Then, for some equally inexplicable reason, this cosmic egg exploded.
And out of this initial chaos,
our marvelously complex universe somehow created itself.
A relatively short time after this explosion, we are told,
the universe consisted of an expanding cloud of hydrogen
with a minor amount of helium.
The late Professor Harlow Shapley of Harvard University stated
that some people piously proclaim,
in the beginning, God.
I say, in the beginning, hydrogen.
He went on to say that starting with hydrogen,
natural laws in time,
one could explain the origin of the universe.
Of course, he could do no such thing.
But the idea was consistent with his philosophy.
This reminds me that someone has said
that hydrogen is an odorless, tasteless, invisible gas,
which, if given enough time, becomes people.
And, of course, that is exactly what evolutionists do believe.
In other words, some Christians think that it is just prayer
and just preaching that solves this problem.
It is prayer and preaching and picketing and petitions
and other forms of public outrage
that show that Christians are united
in our biblical commitment to stop the spread of homosexuality,
pornography, abortion, and so forth.
Now, we don't like to do that
because, as normal human beings, we like to be popular.
We like to be comfortable.
According to Evolution,
theory then, disorder spontaneously generated order.
Complexity arose from simplicity.
Chaos created the cosmos,
all by a process of self-transformation.
According to this theory,
the universe is an isolated system
which began in a state of disorder
and spontaneously transformed itself
into the present highly ordered and complex universe.
Now,
I,
yes,
dear friends,
and that reminds us of
something that was told to one of our friends
by a fundamentalist co-worker
about the Big Bang Theory.
He said,
he said to her,
you know, this Big Bang Theory,
that would be like this.
If I were to take this watch here
and take it into,
take it apart
into all its many, many tiny little gears and things,
then throw them up in the air,
and if they accidentally,
all came back together into a watch,
why then,
that's the Big Bang Theory.
Uh-huh.
Well, you know, friends,
if one could actually understand
what five billion years was,
you could, you know,
that watch would actually,
if you jumbled it around for five billion years,
it probably would turn back into a working wristwatch.
You know,
we've got all those monkeys
and all those typewriters
working away here,
friends,
and some of the,
oh, the results of some of the things
done by monkeys with typewriters,
glorious things,
which can be learned about
in this brand new book
from which we're going to be reading
for the next several shows,
Kooks,
A Guide to the Outer Limits of Human Belief
by Donna Cossey.
And today's reading will start
with this,
uh,
well, the Kooks book
is broken down into so many wonderful categories.
We've got the, uh,
oh,
Anglo-Israelites,
Black Messiahs,
conspiracy theories,
and you name it,
but this is one of my very favorite sections.
We'll be reading directly from her book,
which then quotes the Kook books,
and this one is called
The Devil is...
A Dinosaur.
The scene could be taken from a Godzilla movie
or Journey to the Center of the Earth.
Two gigantic reptilian monsters,
Predator and Prey,
claw for their lives
in the steamy primordial jungle.
Blood disperse from powerful limbs
and furious, shrieking heads.
An armored tail whips out,
gutting,
and exposed,
torso.
Absorbed in the fight,
neither of the doomed creatures realize
until it's too late
that they've begun to sink
ever so slowly into quicksand.
As they go down,
their shrieks become deafening
and fury turns to panic.
Swallowed up by the earth,
their frames are locked in eternal combat,
suggesting an unholy suicide pact.
The scene, however,
is not from a Godzilla movie or any movie.
It really,
really happened.
The bones of the two unfortunate dinosaurs
were discovered in 1991.
Scientists tell us that the battle
between the carnivorous velociraptor
and its intended prey,
the herbivorous protoceratops,
took place approximately 75 million years ago.
Only 10 million years before the creation
of our ancestors, the Yeti, dear friend.
We might think that the world is a cruel place
now, but these two dinosaurs
lived in a world without mercy.
Quote,
a freakish hellish nightmare world
drenched in the blood and gore of violence,
death and destruction inhabited by abnormal,
grotesque creatures and monstrosities,
hell bent on destruction.
It was a world invented by the devil himself.
According to Damon Royce and Jason Zolot,
hmm,
the authors of this book,
Did God Destroy the Dinosaurs?
While millions of dinosaur lovers everywhere
delight in their gigantic proportions
and sometimes comic physiognomies,
Royce and Zolot are deeply disturbed by them.
Quote, even a cursory examination of the facts they write
produces the distinct feeling that something
was just not right with the dinosaurs
and the related reptiles of the air and sea.
It is as if they were not of this world
and did not belong in it.
It is as if they were travesties of nature,
monstrous caricatures of other creatures
and of life itself,
the result of some obscene joke played
by some perverted prankster.
They assert that it was the most perverted prankster of all,
Satan, who created these travesties, the dinosaurs,
and in his insatiable perversity became one, him.
Quote, even a cursory examination of the facts they write
results in a more pleasant conclusion.
Where the world's largest and most important
monster lives in this world,
there lies the skeleton of the giant multi-headed winged sea dragon.
For millions of years, it was the terror of the land, sea, and air
of the primordial world over which it reigned
as the bloodthirsty lord and master.
This monster, unlike anything the world had ever seen before or since,
was the physical manifestation.
of Satan.
So,
friends, sincerely horrified
by this bizarre scenario,
the authors are more than
sorophobic Satan bashers.
They are theologians
who carefully argue their case with due
consideration for science and religious history.
Their inevitable conclusion
that Satan created the
dinosaurs and that God destroyed
them brings together, they claim,
science and the Bible.
With greater sophistication than most
evangelicals, Royce
and Zollett borrow freely from
Gnosticism, Zoroastrianism, and
Paganism to form a Christian
heresy that features an obsession
with dinosaurs.
What are today's creationists
supposed to make of these creatures
who missed boarding the ark
and who didn't warrant so much as a phrase
in the Bible? Some of them
say that God actually
planted dinosaur bones
to test the faith
of believers.
Royce and Zollett rush
to the rescue, pointing out
that the dinosaurs did indeed exist.
And, uh, let's see.
This is quite
detailed and long. We'll skip to the
good bloody parts.
They're talking about how
God had delegated the overall
responsibility for the
administration and care
of all creation under his direction.
The universe which God had created
was to be brought to completion.
One might say that Lucifer
became a kind of subcontractor
for creation.
God's mistake was to give Lucifer
the exclusive power to create
life. It was only a matter of time
before Lucifer got a big head
and became Satan the rebel
and creator of dinosaurs.
Royce and Zollett,
let's switch over
to this.
Ah, Royce and Zollett,
quoted here,
the universe
must have teemed with
life, wondrous and beautiful
in its many varieties.
But then Lucifer began turning into
Satan by beginning to tamper with
the creation of life. Perhaps
it started initially as an amusement
or a prank or diversion for himself
or perhaps to impress
or to entertain the lesser
angelic beings who lacked his
power to create life.
What Satan had realized was that
not only could he create life,
he could also destroy it.
For his amusement, Lucifer
turned Satan, introduced the reality
and the curse of death to the
living, something God had
never intended. Satan turned
Earth into a freakish, hellish
nightmare world, drenched
in blood and
violence and gore, death and destruction,
an obscene parody
of what God had intended.
His blood,
lost, became
insatiable.
Lucifer abused his creative
powers by creating a planet with
steamy, wet, tropical climate,
a planet populated by dinosaurs,
sea reptiles,
flying serpents and other abnormal,
grotesque creatures
and monstrosities.
And, uh, let's see,
it goes on to say here,
uh,
God, after stalling,
so long, had an answer
to Satan's fun and games.
The heavens were completely
cleansed, at least for a while,
of the rebellious, demonic
host. God cast
Satan down to Earth, then destroyed
the dinosaurs and set about the renewal
of the world. Satan was
deprived of his power to create in the
physical realm, but he retained his power
to manipulate life.
Not all of Satan's creation
was destroyed at this time.
Certain areas were permitted to
retain their hot, steamy
climate, and certain abnormal
creatures, like
sharks and crocodiles,
were permitted either to
exist or to arise through
his genetic engineering.
God then pursued
Satan into the solar system.
Evidence of the battle can be found
on the pockmarked surfaces of
Mars, Mercury,
and the Moon.
And, uh, anyway, it turned out,
uh, that, uh, a book of Revelation
can be, uh, described as a graphic
depiction of this chaos and confusion,
although it's supposed to take place in the future,
I thought. And he opened
the bottomless pit, and there arose
a smoke out of the pit
as the smoke of a great
furnace. And the
sun and the air were darkened by
reason of the smoke of the pit.
And there came out of the smoke locusts
upon the Earth. Revelation
9, 13. Thus,
dear friends,
the great comet,
or, wait, where's my background?
Oh, the most horrible
Jurassic Park. What?
What, what, what, what, what, what, what, what?
There we go.
Thus,
the great comet, or meteor,
which devastated Earth 65
million years ago and put an end to all dinosaurs,
they write, was none
other than Satan himself,
being thunderously
hurled towards,
earth, confounding,
and destroying the whole ecosystem
of the planet.
The perfection,
beauty, and harmony
in Eden notwithstanding,
this was still a planet
with the remnants of Satan's
earlier creation. The once
planet-wide tropical ecosystem still
existed, but confined to the planet's
equatorial belt region.
In these tropical and
semi-tropical regions, there
still live such vile and
savage creatures like crocodiles
and alligators, puny cousins
of the dinosaurs and sea
reptiles, but no less
deadly and bloodthirsty.
Other vile creatures of the land and
sea also either survived
the metamorphosis or were
biologically engineered by
Satan afterwards.
And yes,
friends, even after his vile creations were
destroyed, Satan still wouldn't give up.
He sabotaged Eden
and continues to wage war with God,
even to this day. Satan,
after all, holds dominion over Earth,
can genetically engineer
evil versions of
already extant plants and
animals. Poison ivy,
venomous snakes,
saber-toothed tigers and vampire bats,
as well as harmful bacteria
and viruses such as syphilis,
AIDS, smallpox,
and polio are just a few
examples. But Satan is
not satisfied with this mischief.
He wants his old,
power back.
The proof that Satan
still desperately tries to create
is provided by the accounts of
sightings of strange creatures
or huge specimens of
known creatures.
Of all the creatures of Satan's
menagerie, his most favored
were and remain the dinosaurs.
Satan has persistently
tried to recreate dinosaurs.
All such attempts at creation have failed.
His most persistent attempt
to recreate his old brood,
has been at Loch Ness,
Scotland.
But the specimens
are doomed due to the
waning of Satan's power.
This accounts for the repeated vanishing
acts performed by Nessie
and her ilk.
Although Satan's attempts at creation
remain comical and pathetic,
less so are his weapons of mass
destruction. However, even the plan
to get humans to blow themselves
off the earth could backfire.
Uh...
The modern science and weapons
of destruction are double-edged swords.
Satan would like to beguile man
into unleashing mass destruction weapons
upon himself, but he fears
that man might unleash these very same
weapons against his brood.
Man already has the potential
to eradicate all crocodiles
and alligators from the wild, and indeed
from existence!
And man can already launch the
expurgatory war against
sharks, piranhas, lamprey eels,
and other vile creatures of
Satan's menagerie!
To date, man has chosen
to eradicate from the wild only
one member of Satan's brood,
smallpox.
Under the guise of the generally laudable
and beneficial conservation mentality
of maintaining the balance of nature,
man has unwittingly included
conservation of Satan's
life forms.
Royce and, uh,
Zollet finally warn about those
who take pity on crocodiles
and wolves, for they are dupes of Satan!
God is destined to wrest
the earth from Satan's grip,
destroying his seed
in the process.
Nuclear holocaust will
be the fulfillment
of God's will!
And, uh,
yes indeed.
Hoooooo!
And, uh,
that reading
there was from this wonderful
new book, Kook's Guide
to the Outer Limits of Human
Belief. Anybody who, uh,
has been complaining to us about
when you gonna do another high weirdness
by mail? Well, you don't need one now.
Uh, I'm gonna give the address
of the publishers of Kook's.
Uh, it's
like a $17 book.
And you can get that, uh,
right for information
from Ferral House.
F-E-R-A-L
Ferral
House.
P.O. Box
Portland,
Oregon
That's, uh,
P.O. Box 3466
Portland 97208
or you can call them at
503-236-8375
And, uh,
uh,
and, uh, that music, uh, in the background
was by Kyle Kossop
and Severe Tire Damage.
Um, other background music
there was from Miko,
uh, Ultimate Bad Disco
sound effects, uh,
Jurassic Park,
partly as performed by
Zandy. And, uh,
oh yeah, Creation Science Polka
there was by, uh,
Joe Newman, uh,
Rudy Schwartz Project.
Hey, uh, speaking of Portland
as we were just a little
while ago, uh, oh,
by the time you hear this
I will be, uh,
attending the
single most astonishing event
in world history before
X-Day. The Universal Subgenius
Portland Pilgrimage.
Uh, which we've given you plenty of, uh,
warning about on this show, so you
know, anybody who listens to this show should know about it.
We just did a mailing.
All subgeniuses will be getting the mailing.
We just knocked ourselves out
to finish. And, uh,
eh,
but here's what you're gonna be
missing, dear friends. This is from the
flyer here.
It's what I'm looking forward to.
Luxurious accommodations for all pilgrims
in one of beautiful Portland,
Oregon's finest luxury motor
hotels. Free all you
can force yourself to eat
gourmet champagne brunch
all day, every day
for the entire week of pilgrimage
events. Free airfare
and lodging for all major church
hierarchites, ranters and rantresses,
except Janeer.
Unlimited safe sex and
drugs for all participants
who desire them. Total
fulfillment of every attendee's
wildest dreams of attention,
adulation, worship, and acclaim
from the highest ranking members of the
subgenius hierarchy. Public
humiliation of stupid, ugly,
horny college boy bobbies
who publish stupid, insulting, would-be
church material,
unaware that they are only making an
embarrassing spectacle of their inherent
and inescapable inferiority
to even the so-called
pinks whom they despise
but whose low level of wit and creativity
they can never hope to attain.
Free 24-hour
strippograms of all genders.
Climactic fireworks
and laser rock for Bob
as the smashing conclusion to the most
world-smashing revival of all past
or future times before X-Day.
Sexy naked men and women
everywhere. No
hangovers for anyone,
no matter how much
hideously excessive
partying they do.
Free immortality pills at
the door. Global,
total global dictatorship
for him, Nenslow,
who wrote this and is
organizing this thing in perpetuity.
Now wait a minute.
Yes, as it
says here, absolute unquestioning
obedience to all my whims,
however trivial, instantly before
I even speak. The planet
is in the way? Yes, sir.
We'll see to it, sir. That pop star's
voice too shrill? Consider
her killed to death by mile-long
pink horseshoe crabs, sir.
That jerk who tormented you in
fourth grade? Here are his genitals,
sir. Universe
bothering you, sir? We'll have
it crushed into a tiny
crumbled wad in just a moment, sir.
Please forgive the delay!
Yes, dear friends,
Nenslow's big party, and it does
sound like it's going to be great, although, as
Nenslow himself said in a
subsequent newsletter, as quoted
here, the only difficult part
of the entire conference, this is the
pre-party conference,
was refusing the constant
offers of sex and drugs
from persons of all genders and
social classes. Thanks,
but besides being a happily
married man, we feel that
one moment of pleasure, which
is unearned by hours of
arduous labor or meaningless
suffering, would take the fine
edge of hatred off our
worldview and lull us into
the belief that life is good
and worth living.
Then what would happen when it's time
to die? We'd be screwed, that's what.
No, we're, we save
enjoying life,
that most subtle of
addictions, for our evil enemies
or those who show by their blatant
displays of stupidity that they truly
deserve to be cruelly deceived
for our sport.
Paul Mervridis, bon mot,
in regard to the frightening
drug we know as hope,
deserves to be run down
the halls of posterity
to the sagely nods
of future philosophers.
As Paul Mervridis said about hope,
a killer
high, but
what a crash.
And, well friends, I think it's time now
to teach you
the post office box number to write to for free
information from the Church of the Subgenius.
Yes, this mighty Church
can tell you about everything.
You got that pencil ready, my friend?
Do you have that pencil ready?
Uh,
mmm, I want you
to write that, just a
self-dressed stamped envelope to Bob
at post office box
That's box
in lovely
Dallas, Texas
uh,
7-5-2-1-4
Ah, yes,
and uh
...
A prayer
to J.R. Bob Dobbs
O Dobbs,
canst thou not
hear my plea
in my
utter humbleness
For lo, Dobbs, I'm nothing but a loathsome
lowly piece of
before thy
ultimate and divine power
thy
who smoketh the pipe
of infinity, the pipe
of the universe, yea
can I not be washed
in the smoke of the pipe
Heareth my
request
that lo
I humbly
beseech thee, Dobbs
that in thy justice
in thy infinite
mercy and righteousness
that thy might allow me
infinite
power over all other living
beings in the universe
and Dobbs that
I humbly beseech that I might
be allowed to control
the food source
for all nations on earth
in order that
every person of every
country, of every city
of every town, of every
neighborhood
might find it necessary
to kiss my ass
in order to obtain
food
their
minimum daily requirements
for nutrition for that day
and Dobbs
from the beginning of time
mankind has had a vision
a vision of
all men, of all
nationalities, of all races, of all
four sexes coming together
and joining hands
and
singing together in harmony
and Dobbs I humbly
request that you
just totally ignore this vision
because it really has no interest to me whatsoever
and Dobbs I selflessly
humbly request
that you
instead by
ignoring this vision you will be able to
channel more of your psychic and spiritual
energy into myself
and I will be able to
fulfill all of your selfish requests
and Dobbs if I had but one wish
for mankind it would be this
that I would be able to just blow off
the whole one wish fairy tale
syndrome and that instead I might have
an infinity
of wishes
and I'd never have to exist
in some kind of storybook reality
where a guy gets a pudding
stuck on his nose or something like that
Dobbs
furthermore
I request that
humbly Dobbs
I beseech thee
on bended knee
looking up unto you as the
true and one and only source of wisdom
I do humbly request
thy humble servant
I request that
I be allowed to replace ye
Dobbs
and that it shall be me that
smoketh the pipe of knowledge
and in fact ye that
stand on bended knee
before me
begging
mercy before me
in which case
I will just laugh in your face
Dobbs and turn you
down even though it was ye
ye
who granted me this power in the first
place and lo Dobbs
I request that
I might be able to
merge with the concept
of hate that I might
in fact be able to
become one with
hate and lo Dobbs
that the concept of
conscience might be
strucken from my mind that I would
never again be able to
feel guilt and lo
the word guilt could be
struck from my very vocabulary
so that I could in fact
never feel guilt
for demanding
any of these selfish things
oh just little
things Dobbs such as
power over all life in the universe
and lo Dobbs
I request that
ahahaha
hahaha
praise
Saint Jainer
Hyperclites and
thank you