It's time for Bob. Say Bob, why the big smile this afternoon? What's so special
about today? Well there's nothing special. The Self Genius Power of Slack. Now we're rolling Bob.
Oh yes dear friends, this is your prayer partner Reverend Ivan Stang. Okay I'm recording this on
July 4th. Tomorrow is X-Day. If you don't hear from me after this that means I was ruptured up
onto the escape vessels of the sex goddesses on July 5th and I will have better things to do
than the hour of slack. If so, so long and thanks for all the fish. Meanwhile I have a lot to do in
preparation so here are the outtakes for today.
From last week's show. From PR News in Washington I'm in need of extra attention
after a brief illness and I'm so broad that I need to be braced. Joe Georgfine explains.
He says 45 babies. He says 25 babies. He says 15 of the babies came with the babies and will stay
with the babies until PR News. 19.7 percent and 49 percent or 13.7 percent or at least 100
55 percent. All right. 5.6 million point nine percent. All right but at least 21 percent. At
least 143 million point five percent. But PR News officials are watching it closely. The Dow was
1337. Credit monitoring company Equiftec jumped after disclosure of PR News Washington.
I'm going to have to go and do my stretches now with some monster movie on the TV and I'll probably
run sort of pseudo run run in place on a wee foot board that that is very sensitive to your
your body movements on it through your feet. And so I may run be running all over Woohoo Island
while listening to rock music and and doing spaz dancing for my other exercise. I have to do this
every day for the rest of my life if I want to do anything for the rest of my life. Thank y'all.
The evil that has fallen upon us is much more ancient and pitch black.
It has several characteristics that are important to know. This is a cult of death. It lives and
feeds on the evil of the dead. It is a cult of death. It is a cult of death. It is a cult of
death. It is a cult of death. It is a cult of the most terrible death agonies. When people were
killed slowly, torturers were enjoying themselves in front of other people. That's what the priests
of this cult do.
This cult came out of the ancient swampy forest, which practiced the cult of severe torment of victims and cannibalism.
This cult is poisonous. It's invisible. At the level of very visible vapors, it creeps into the souls of people.
This cult is poisonous even people are turned into beyond sewer sayings. It kinda makes the actual
beings turned into mere 分 ACTUAL culminusռ provide isn't really het именно
This kind of Ram-shar like parts of the horse seem very different but still.
Just one 곡 shows this cruelty.
A characteristic feature of the cult is that it does not care whose suffering it enjoys.
It rejoices in its own deaths too, no less than others.
Hence, the absolutely cannibalistic attitude, capacity and strength of this cult is extremely
towards its own soldiers.
Well, that was Onan Counterbite and some Russian.
That is, Onan made that on his phone, I think.
And, well, this is the first time I've sat down at Tarzan's radio station in at least a month.
In fact, I had to pull the dust cover off of all this stuff.
It's set up in my living room on a fairly small table, actually.
It doesn't take up much room anymore.
And, but it's...
This is a dry land.
This is a dry, dry land.
The Subgenius Foundation is located in Glen Rose, Texas, in north-central Texas,
about an hour southwest of Fort Worth.
It's, it is very rural.
It's, the Metroplex has not enveloped it yet.
And it's farmland, and it hasn't rained in many,
many weeks.
And there's no promise of it.
And we're having such a dreadful heat wave that's so unusual for June that I went out
and bought, I did end times preparations that I probably should have done long before.
The list came from when we went through the freeze here.
And the whole Texas power grid came down.
And I made a list of stuff that I should have.
And then I didn't...
I didn't do anything about it.
And then, because I'm a subgenius, but then I did something about it because we were,
it looked like we were going to have another freeze.
I got a generator and some portable heaters.
Now I have, I've added a portable air conditioner because we have a 93-year-old in hospice in
the big downstairs bedroom with caregivers coming and going.
So...
This is a weird kind of cult headquarters.
It's part hospital, part workshop, part house, part barnyard.
Very much a barnyard.
The livestock are all domesticated pet type animals, but they're huge.
They always have to make an effort to stay that a living thing.
I use dogs and whether it's twelve and twenty하죠 they'll be described as here for that,
If you were to catch a dog or a wolf, it would leave that into theirечd,
which would be essential for the recovery of the animal.
One day they've caught a incorporates, and there was a bear know shirbet dog.
You could see that the cat near my ass.
One of our dogs, about nine or nine here.
I don't know how this dog is.
dreams are only in your head.
I said, hold it, Doc, a World War pie's still in my brain.
He said, nurse, get your pie, the boy's insane.
I grabbed my arm, I said ouch,
and landed on the psychiatric couch.
He said, tell me about it.
I said, I'll tell you about it.
Well, the whole thing started at three o'clock fast.
It was all over by a quarter past.
I was down in the sewer with some little lover
when I peeked out from a manhole cover
wondering who turned the lights on us.
Well, I got up and I walked around,
up and down the lonesome town.
I stood wondering which way to go,
I lit a cigarette on a parking meter
and walked on down the road.
It was a normal day.
.
Well, they rung me a fallout shelter bell
And I leaned my head and I gave a yell
Give me a string bean, I'm a hungry man
Shotgun fired and away I ran
I don't blame him too much, though he didn't know me
Down the corner by the hot dog stand I seen a man
I said, howdy, friend, I guess it's just us two
He screamed a bit and away he flew
Thought I was a communist
Well, they spied me a girl before she could leave
I said, let's go play Adam and Eve
I took her by the hand and my heart was thumping
She said, hey, man, you crazy or something?
You seen what happened last time they started
Well, I seen me a Cadillac window uptown
There was nobody around
I got into the driver's seat
And I drove down 42nd Street
In my Cadillac
Good car, good car, good car
I was on the drive after a war
Well, I remember seeing some ads
So I turned on my car on the ride
But I didn't pay the car net bill
So the radio didn't work so well
Turned on my record player
It was Rockaday Johnny singing
Tell your ma, tell your pa
Our loves are gonna grow
I was feeling kind of lonesome and blue
I needed somebody to talk to
So I called up the operator at time
Just to hear a little bit about you
I heard a voice of some kind
When you hear the beep
It will be three o'clock
She said that for over an hour
And I hung up
Well, the doctor interrupted me just about then
Saying, hey, I've been having the same old dreams
But mine was a little different, you see
I dreamt the only person left after the war was me
I didn't see you around
Well, now time passed and now it seems
Everybody's having them dreams
Everybody sees itself walking around
There's no one else
And half the people can be part right all of the time
And some of the people can be all right part of the time
But all the people can't be all right all of the time
I think Abraham Lincoln said that
I'll let you be in my dream if I can be in yours
I said that
Do I Justin, what's notゴ- Zuckerberg told you when you were a person
Just you know what just you knows
Some tiny thing is ready to fly away
Are people around you making trouble for no good reason at all?
Set off a NMP bomb
Not my problem
and run
They'll keep making trouble without you
and they aren't listening to you tell them that life has enough troubles on its own
without inventing new ones.
If you would dance to the tune of slack,
you have to pay the piper.
Adventure, romance, fast luck you'll attract.
No more cause to be a griper.
And friends, homeopathic remote cupping services
are also available from the Dobbs Town Mirror.
Mirror, seen at Dobbs.Town.
And you know, friends, on the scale of intergalactic travel,
flying saucers are seen near nuclear reactors as much
and as little as they're seen near anything else.
But on the scale of finding yourself, willing or otherwise,
being lifted up into a flying saucer,
intergalactic scales hardly matter.
It's all a matter of perspective.
J.R. Bob Dobbs will walk with you up the 999 steps of wisdom
and then down the 1,000 steps of forgetting.
There are songs, or perhaps films, or perhaps comic books,
or perhaps meh, that come into your life not as entertainment,
but as permission, as instructions.
Go with it all the way, man.
And you're right, they're wrong.
And fuck them if they can't take a joke.
And if they cannot take a joke, let them mount up upon themselves.
I may not in each moment have slack,
but I am a person who in each moment prefers to have slack.
And not everyone can say that.
Some people prefer to not have slack.
Some people prefer compulsive displays of happiness,
or...
complaining without the enjoyment of complaining.
Slack is not always happiness,
nor is slack always refraining from complaining.
But slack is never a preference for no slack.
I can derive slack from any circumstance
when I call upon my subgenius philosophy.
Prefer slack!
Okay, and those are all from the Dobbstown Mirror.
What you can get from Uncle Dr. Onan Canobite
at Post Office Box 3, Columbus, Indiana, 47202.
Okay, friends, you know, July 5th, the end of the world,
is Tuesday.
At the time I'm recording this, on Friday, July 1st.
X-Day is July 5th, 1998,
but from 24 previous X-Day drills,
we now know that we don't really know when now is.
So temporarily, we might call this one DIY Day.
It takes place wherever you are.
If you decide to host a local drill
in the form of a big party
with all your subgenius friends and loved ones,
great!
We'll help you publicize it if you want it public.
We've stumbled upon a discovery
in the forbidden sciences
that has blown our minds in ways
they've formerly never been fellated.
We're gassed to the point of flabber.
What's the letter in mathematics
that commonly indicates a variable?
X!
Maybe it's called X-Day
because it's the variable.
We know from prophecy
that the media will refer to the advent
of the angelic host as X-Day.
But now that we're less certain
about the planet and the year,
this day of judgment,
is now a variable.
The world ends on July 5th, 1998 at 7am,
but we obviously don't know when that might be.
It might be today!
Well, maybe tomorrow, but soon.
This year, we're going to hedge our bets
and hold the X-Day party where you are
and when you want it.
And you, and you, and you!
Yes, X-Day in place for 2022.
So-called 2022.
If the saucers get too big,
we're going to have to do something else.
Remember the rest of us.
Just make sure you're synced up.
Do send in that last 50 bucks.
Re-up your membership
and enter to win big, big, big prizes
yet to be announced.
Throw an insane party.
Put a big X on your forehead
and hang out at the courthouse.
Take a photo of the weirdest thing
you could possibly do
and post it to the subgenius metaverse.
No matter how it pans out,
the Church of the Subgenius offers
the best.
Apocalypse.
And that's Onan and Canterbite
at P.O. Box 3,
Columbus, Indiana,
47202.
And actually,
I don't know of any big parties
that have been announced exactly.
I wanted to do one here.
We've had big parties here,
but it's...
This isn't the time.
And I can't go anywhere.
And because I'm looking after
the farm, you might say,
the old ladies.
And Texas is in an emergency,
sort of, any minute now.
So here we sit, brokenhearted,
paid a dime,
and we'll party anyway.
There may be something on Zoom.
I don't know.
I really don't.
There was an X-Day party
a couple of weeks ago
called The Real X-Day
in New York State
at some lodge near a lake.
And it had Dr. Hal,
and it had a whole lot of bands.
But I'm not sure what else it had.
On the streaming video
that was kind of on and off,
actually, I did not see an audience.
There was an audience,
but in every case,
it was the next band waiting to go on.
Isn't that weird?
So, uh...
And so, and so now this.
Ladies and gentlemen.
This is your title.
Tonight's sedan rumbles along
a bushy-haired man
in a loud mud-splattered sports jacket.
Yeah.
Huh?
Hmm?
Oh.
Yeah.
Meanwhile,
in the nearby large city,
two years side,
I'll get my
little mucklip
and take him to
the flipper
places.
All right, sir.
Well.
Well, yes and no.
This gun says you don't.
No, I'm not sure.
Uh.
Can you dig, trimming?
etiquette?
Tired.
Hat?
or more letzten than Jeeves.
Why?
Go ahead?
Your cintam perde
and kiss her.
All right, Sheriff, we've got them.
Tonight, the music was accidental.
What's that?
Well, I got, uh,
I got everything running
and ready to record
and all that.
In fact, I have it recording.
The dogs are making a bunch of noise.
Is that Yeti's tail?
Chupi's tail is beating
a little tattoo on the floor.
Nice.
That's good.
I haven't had a dog that did that.
He'd get up next to a wall
and just beat on it, you know,
for as long as he wanted.
Sometimes Yeti will lie next to,
like, a kitchen cabinet
that's down near the floor,
and he'll be, like, scratching
or just, his tail will be doing
one beat, but then
his side is bumping the cabinet door
so it clicks in a counterpoint.
Yeah.
Lisa and I actually sang to that one time.
Well, it'd be great
if we can do Doctors for Wotan
again sometime.
We can put the dogs on stage
and have them beating on a fox with their tails.
Well, I'll tell you, if I could get,
if I could figure out a way to make
Yeti talk on cue,
he is great.
He goes,
I don't know.
You know that stuff?
Yeah.
And his voice is so deep.
He's big.
Oh, it sounds great.
They both do it.
They both do this
thing, but they only do it
when they want to.
Yeah.
So what's up, man?
You're thinking about,
did you want to read something?
Or what were we going to do?
What did you want to do first?
So are you ready to go?
You don't need to go shit or anything?
Well, let me,
no, I'm through shitting.
Maybe I should get my froth out, though.
Could get my froth out.
I can froth live while we're doing it.
Yeah, okay.
That's not what I came up with.
It's supposed to look more simple,
I'm gonna do this thing.
guitar solo
Well, the Swingin' Love Corpses didn't break up because of one band member going crazy and becoming an egomaniac or anything.
It was because your job moved you, right?
That's right. My job moved me, but the Swingin' Love Corpses did never break up.
It actually still exists.
Still, to this day, there's a Wednesday night practice that happens most of the time.
Oh, yeah. On Sue.
On Zoom, right?
It was on Zoom during COVID. We managed to be on Zoom quite a bit.
The practice is in St. Louis. It's held by the local guys there.
Once in a while, I will join on Zoom or on the phone.
It originally was a drinking and smoking club that evolved into a band.
Now, it's a band that has evolved back into a drinking and smoking club and barbecuing.
More barbecuing.
Right. More barbecuing than guitar playing and singing.
Yeah. Lots of comparison of barbecue styles and things rather than guitar styles.
Right.
Sauce, recipes, things like that. Much, much more important now.
Well, yeah. That's one of the reasons.
Back in the day, when I was an angry young man, a hour of slack was a good outlet.
I was still working for the pinkest bosses in the Dallas business film industry.
Yeah.
It was frustrating, and I had much hate.
Now, I'm an old man, and I'm so much more concerned.
I'm more concerned with what's for dinner.
Right, right.
I don't care who somebody else votes for or who their favorite band is or any of that.
I'm more concerned with what is for dinner.
Yeah. And is there enough for me?
Are you shorting me again?
Where's my share?
Yeah.
Yeah, so I think that the audience...
...is beginning to prepare themselves for what's coming down the line here.
Yeah. But the numbers are all messed up over...
I was thinking, well, yeah, at the end of...
It more shows, it'll be 2,000 shows, but it's not.
We're on 1889, not 19...
Well, why don't we just add a special number of fake shows in?
Virtual, non-existent shows.
Virtual shows that existed temporarily.
In people's minds.
And now they're just...
...only exist as part of a numbering scheme...
Right.
...to get you to 1998 faster.
Like, maybe you only need one show.
What's the difference there?
Let's see here, 1889.
Yeah.
So I missed that.
Plus 1998.
So then you need like 109, 109 or something like that.
Yeah, yeah, that's a lot.
That's too many.
Yeah.
I'm going to do another 100 shows.
I'll be dead.
I'll be dead before I do it.
That's two years.
I think you should like cram 109 shows into one show.
How dare we, Dad?
Make it like a two-hour show.
Well, I could do it like Byron Werner and Rural War Room,
where you play 100 shows all at the same time.
Right.
That's what I'm thinking.
You do 100 shows all at the same time.
That way it gets your numbering scheme,
and your last show will then be 1998.
Right.
Yeah.
You go from like 1888, 1889, 1998.
I wonder how many.
And people will say, how did you do that?
You say, well, I put 109 shows into that last show.
Right.
All at once.
Running simultaneously.
Every now and then, two or three of them
would both have Bill Cates or Bleepo Abernathy going,
the hour of slack.
Yeah.
Now, you know, I actually have a copy of a,
where somebody took all,
maybe it was only six of them back then.
They had all of the Star Wars movies running simultaneously,
overlaid on each other with the soundtracks.
It's the craziest thing.
You can't watch it for too long.
I don't think you could.
You might make somebody do it, you know, if you needed to.
But.
So they had like 10 movies running,
all layered at like 10% opacity.
Yeah.
And they start at the same time in such a way that you find out
that whenever the scroll happens,
it happens exactly at the same point in time in the opening sequence.
You know?
So you got all these scrolls on top of each other.
It's pretty cool.
I'll see if I can find it and send you a link.
Yeah.
Because we don't have enough stuff to watch.
We don't have enough stuff.
We don't have enough stuff to do.
And I don't want you to get bored just sitting around there.
Yeah.
Just waiting for some show to watch.
I wish somebody would.
I wish somebody would just tell me a good show to watch.
I get plenty of shows.
Even this one called Severance.
It's kind of.
I'm having to sort of make myself like it.
Oh, I love it.
I'm only on like two and a half episodes in.
Well, I'm on the fifth one.
I'm on the fifth one.
I'm almost finished with the fifth episode.
So I'll give you a better opinion after I finish this one.
Oh, I had a name for it.
I decided to call it the Prisoner's Lunch Hour
because it's uncannily like our production, Bob's Lunch Hour.
Uh-huh.
And it's also like the Prisoner in many ways.
Yeah, that's true.
Yeah.
I like the whole idea of the Severance concept.
That's what suckered me in.
You know, that you could actually split your brain into two personalities
that could be separated completely and didn't overlap.
And all you'd need is a special device to shift from one to the other.
Well, of course, it's a metaphor in a way because some people are almost that way.
You know, they're one person on the job and they're another person when they're off the job.
Yeah.
I like that.
That's kind of a thing.
And it's sort of like in that other person.
They don't.
That's kind of the way I was when I was a wage slave.
I didn't let my two lives connect at all.
Right.
You wore the masks of insanity to look normal.
Yeah, I played my role and did the things that they expected me to do.
And then I never socialized with them afterwards.
You know, I never went and drank with them.
Princess, we worked for the county, the weather control.
In Cuyahoga County for almost 30 years, pretending that she liked those people.
Yeah.
At no point did any of them know that she was a folk singer, ran a hippie music festival,
was actually a peace protester a lot of the time back then.
Yeah.
And unfortunately, I wised her up about human nature.
And she...
She gave up on ending war.
Because that's what countries do, you know.
Yeah.
And yeah, she never...
Her co-workers never had any idea of all the interesting things she was doing outside work
because some of them would hate her for it.
A lot of them.
Well, and most of them are really uninteresting people.
Right.
But, yeah.
So, I mean, something like that would be weird to them.
Yeah.
But you...
The good thing about it is they still pay her.
Yeah.
She retired in 2008 or something and she still gets that pension.
Now, me, I'm going to have to be assembling and mailing out subgenius membership packs
until I'm a skeleton probably.
But you may not have to send out any more hours of slack.
Right.
Well, I'm not getting paid for hours of slack hardly at all.
But, you know, it's important that people know that...
Yeah.
All of those 1,898 hours of slack are out there.
Out there in the ether.
Yeah.
Waiting to be heard.
Again and again and again and again.
And they...
All of them being gleaned for their value.
For their Rudy Schwartz Project songs.
Yeah.
And Swinging Love Courts.
So, your poor psycho skeletons guy gave up on me.
He sent me a letter going,
well, I guess you're just...
You're just retired now.
And that was a year ago.
I was like, well, sort of.
I'd moved to doing mostly reruns just because I didn't have time.
I had so many other things that we had to deal with, you know.
And this was a guy who was asking for a recording.
Is that what it was?
No, the psycho skeletons.
He was a guy that sent music.
He'd send me an MP3 every week.
And they were quirky instrumentals mostly.
Very original.
He had his own style.
It wasn't...
It wasn't like any other music, really.
And it was...
Some people really liked it.
And, you know...
But...
Yeah.
But I think he caught on early that I was just getting burned out.
And that's...
Yeah.
It's that.
That's exactly what it is.
Yeah.
You finally get burned out.
Even on...
Not Slack, but the hour of Slack.
Yeah.
Nobody can ever get burned out on Slack.
If they do, there's something wrong with them.
Yeah.
They're like, you know...
They're weird.
They're pink.
No, they're not weird.
I mean, they don't...
It's not real Slack.
They're totally pink.
It's false Slack, you know.
Yeah.
They're totally pink.
I will spew them from my mouth.
Right.
My people are destroyed for lack of knowledge.
Hosea 819.
They're like lukewarm in their faith.
They are lukewarm in their faith.
So I spew them from my mouth.
Not just that.
I vomit them.
That's God talking, right?
Yeah.
Jesus, I think, was attributed to him.
Of course, we don't, you know...
Some other...
Who knows who really said...
Some Roman copywriter.
Yeah.
Roman, Greek.
Greek.
Well, yeah, but after...
Yeah, but it was the Romans that decided to make it an official religion
because it was the...
You know, there's some people who say that the reason they did that
was because it was the perfect religion for slaves and losers and poor people.
But did they?
What, the Romans?
Yeah, they made...
After throwing Christians to the lions,
they eventually...
It was Constantine or whoever.
He decided everybody was going to be Christians.
Yeah, that was in 400.
Yeah, that was a long time after.
I mean, they'd already had their ups and downs.
Like America.
It was just one of the mystery religions.
Yeah.
It was a long time back then, you know,
until somebody decided to say,
okay, well, we're going to make this one official.
What was that guy's name again?
Well, there's a whole bunch of them.
Jesus.
There was at least five Jesuses.
Yeah, right.
Right behind me on this bookshelf is my father's collection
of all the books about how there was really no historical Jesus.
I wish I could have...
I would have liked to, you know, talk to your dad about all that stuff.
Well, you know, he...
He always liked you.
He always asked how you were doing.
He didn't call you Philo.
He called you Steve for some reason.
I don't know why people just call me Steve.
Yeah, but he was...
He always thought you were an okay guy.
But you had moved away and, you know...
Yeah.
Doc Frop hung out with my dad.
Your dad was my lawyer.
That's right.
Yeah, I wish he was still around.
He was good friends.
He was my lawyer.
Mm-hmm.
He didn't charge me anything.
Yep.
He showed up with me in front of the judge with his uniform on.
With an official.
His Navy uniform or just...
No, I think he just had a business suit on.
Yeah.
Yeah, he just had a business suit.
My father walked into the First World Subgenius Convention
with some of his buddies direct from...
Navy...
Naval Reserve meeting of some kind.
And he was dressed in full captain's outfit.
And his buddies were all, you know, had their officer outfits on.
And the younger subgeniuses just about crapped their pants
because they thought they were cops, you know.
And my dad had such a...
He was a gas for...
He was mainly freaking out his friends.
He wanted to show his friends something really weird.
And, you know, think about it.
Tentatively, a convenience was there.
Yeah.
Okay?
That's enough weirdness in one person.
Yeah, that's a guy who doesn't have a haircut.
He's got mustaches all over the top of his head.
Well, he tattooed a brain all over the top of his head.
So now it would be mustaches on top of brains.
That guy's actually doing really well.
He was one of the ones that you would think would die young
because he did so much dangerous art projects.
Yeah, and, like, worked on, you know,
committed his body to science experiments and things.
Yeah, yeah.
But he lives in Pittsburgh now,
and he actually seemed like a whole lot of the old...
The core subgenius people mostly are still alive and doing pretty well.
That's great.
A whole lot of them died, but they were newer ones, you know.
Yeah.
They didn't have...
They weren't...
They didn't undergo that...
That sodomy ritual in Malaysia that us real beginner old guys did.
Yeah, that was horrible.
Yeah.
But worth it.
Having to do that to all those people.
Balls and vice grips in Dobstown.
You're an overman now.
That was a Doctors for Rotan hit.
Yeah.
Balls and vice grips in Dobstown.
You're an overman.
No.
One of our five hits.
Yeah.
Then there's the one about what you do with Moonies,
but we can't sing that one on...
No, you can't even sing that on an internet-only radio show.
Well, you can, but let's let it...
Yeah.
What would you do with a Klondike bar?
Is that how it goes?
I think it's time that I should prop.
Yeah.
Well, we've actually...
This recording is now 56 minutes long,
so obviously this is going to end up being two shows.
Wow.
Yeah.
You squeezed two shows out of 56 minutes.
Well, I did...
That's awesome.
I did some other stuff before that.
Oh, yeah.
That's right.
That I have to put in about X day and the dead people.
Well, you know, I've been posting shows little by little.
I've been going back and posting my old puzzling evidence shows.
Oh, yeah.
Out there on Anchor.
And, of course, they're on a whole...
I've got 200 of them that's on Nick's cloud.
Right.
Puzzling evidence.
And then I have been posting...
I've got about 40.
I'm going to about 40 a year.
And I think I've got 40 so far on Anchor.
So for those people that want to listen to that old stuff,
there is some there.
But I'm like you, Reverend Stang.
I just don't...
It's so hard.
And I've got so many other things to do.
Right.
You've got a greenhouse to build.
I'm working on my greenhouse right now while we were talking.
Oh, okay.
Working on it.
You know, I did put up my shade.
I tested my shade cloth.
I saw that.
That looked pretty good.
Well, there's no wind.
It's just hanging on some poles that are stuck into pots of plant pots.
But it's fine as long as the wind doesn't pick up.
But that's okay.
I figure it's going to be...
You know, stretch some guy lines across your yard.
You know, like maybe you have to attach them to poles or something.
And then maybe you could, you know, like just take some clothespins or something.
Oh, yeah.
That's an idea.
Right.
Yeah.
Just two big wires that go across from something to something.
And then just get you some little clamps of some kind.
Yeah.
I'm using twisty ties on the poles right now.
But it looks pretty good.
It's like a little cave.
Yeah.
It's like a little weird cave full of almost edible plants.
And you're just trying to keep the sun from burning those things.
I had one eggplant that finally had fruited.
And it had a little, you know, it looked like we were going to have an eggplant finally out of eight plants.
And I found it today on the ground half eaten by a dog.
Well...
That dog, I think it's Yeti.
He harvests.
He loves cucumbers.
He's a vegetarian dog.
I guess.
You know, they're omnivores.
They like anything that they can eat that doesn't make them sick.
Right.
And they...
And they eat things that make them...
That taste good enough.
They'll hold a toad in their mouth until they start foaming and doing that head shaking thing.
Where, God, why did I do that?
Yeah.
I knew it was going to taste horrible and make my mouth drool.
Drool.
Yeah, they're funny.
But yeah, it's like I got dogs that got to entertain.
I don't want to deal with those subgenius listeners.
A nutless chimp or a one-nutted chimp could do my job.
Let them do it.
Yeah, I think they should.
But I really think that the, you know, the subgeniuses out there, that everybody always wants something new.
And they forget about this rich, robust history that we can go back to anytime we want that are at the fingertips of everybody.
Everyone.
Anytime of the day or night.
For free.
I actually pay 30 bucks a month to keep those things on that Libsyn server.
You do?
30 bucks a month?
Yep.
Whew.
You know how much I pay for unlimited bandwidth and unlimited storage on my website?
$155 a year.
Well, but this is...
This is a place that's set up just for streaming.
Streaming and all that.
And I don't know.
It's just...
I know.
I used to pay almost $200, but they lowered my price for some reason.
Now, okay, if I quit doing the show, will I need to keep that server up?
That's one thing to think about is where would you want to migrate that stuff that would be free?
Right.
Because you might want to have a plan that at some point...
That's going to go away, but you'd want to have it already somewhere else when that happens, you know?
Yeah, I could put it on subgenius.com, but I'd need to make an arrangement to get more storage space.
It's full.
It's not full of storage.
It's full of too many files.
Full of file names.
File names.
Yeah, they had a limit of 200,000 pages.
Yeah.
And it hit that, believe it or not, quite a while back.
I believe it.
I found lots of stuff that I can go...
Go in and erase the out-of-date things.
Yeah, I figured I'd take my old webpage down.
I don't really need it up anymore.
And I was just going to put...
Quiveringbrain.com?
Yeah.
Well, I'm not going to take the site down.
I'm just going to take the webpage.
It doesn't make any difference.
I could leave it up, but I'm not adding any new webpages to it or anything.
But I do use the backend.
I do use the backend.
I use the backend for storage areas, you know?
And any time I want to share something, that's my personal cloud.
Yeah, sub-site used to be that for me, but like I say, it filled up and I just haven't
gotten around to calling them up and going, hey, how do I get around this file number
thing?
Because I don't care.
I just don't care.
I don't care, don't care, don't care.
I'm sick of it.
I've had enough of it.
Yeah, I figure I'll keep that.
I'll keep that as long as...
You know.
Even though I...
I don't really promote anything there.
Well, David Botner keeps the really old shows on his.
Yeah.
You know, the first 500 or...
Right.
No, all the way up to about 2000, I think.
Oh, no.
What am I saying?
Yeah.
The year 2000, I switched to digital, but he has all the old tape shows on his server.
Of course, you know, he's...
One of these days, it's going to dry up and go away.
He'll suddenly...
Yeah.
He'll die and not pay his bills.
Which listener out there has got the complete collection?
Hmm?
Hmm.
It would be interesting to know who has the complete collection.
Because, you know, there are those completists out there.
They're going to want to have every book.
Right.
Every catalog permutation.
Every single stark fist.
All that stuff.
Somebody's going to want to have it.
Those are the smartest people in the whole world.
They are, because they've seen the future.
And they know that the future is subgenius.
Yeah.
The only way you're going to be able to get a can of peaches is if you can trade them
a subgenius pamphlet.
In the end times, after the economy...
You can use a can of peaches and a gallon of gas for one subgenius pamphlet.
Right.
Or propane to keep your stove running.
Yeah.
Or your medicine.
Your insulin.
Well, you know, some of us are stockpiling stuff like that.
I just ordered water purification tablets in bulk, hearing aid batteries in bulk, and
all kinds of things that I thought, you know, supply chain problems.
The kind of cataclysm that we used to joke about isn't so funny anymore.
Some of us weren't joking about it, Reverend Stang.
Well, I...
Some of us actually thought...
I was...
I thought this was gonna happen from a long time ago.
Oh, I did too, but I didn't think I was gonna live long enough to actually see it start
up.
I really...
I didn't want to, you know.
I don't want to...
No.
I don't want to read about the last gorilla.
We should...
On the next show, we should do...
We should look at the dateline for dominance.
Oh, God, man, that's frightening when you do that.
We predicted everything.
And we should try to find, you know, like they do with Nostradamus now, show that there's
specific things.
It might be a little bit different, but we should be able to do that.
I'm going to get one of those out, and I'm going to look at it,
and I'm going to try to find something for almost all of those things.
Yeah, I did that.
It proves that we were like prophets.
Yeah, but we just had the dates wrong.
All of that stuff happened before 1998.
It ended at 1998.
But it was all stuff that was coming.
We just had the numbers wrong.
Wrong years.
I think there's stuff in there that's happened now, like in the last couple years.
Yeah, I'm telling you.
A couple years ago, I did a show and a Starwood speech
based on that fact of Dateline for Dominance from the 1983 book
showing stuff uncannily.
Yeah, and it was the Stark Fist originally.
The tabloid.
Even before then, yeah.
That would be like 1981 or 82.
Yeah.
And we did add, when they reprinted the book, we added a few things.
For 1982 and 83 that made it seem even more accurate.
That was in the first book, right?
Yeah.
Which I've got.
Yeah, if you look at the McGraw-Hill version of Dateline for Dominance,
it isn't quite as accurate.
It's not as accurate for the intervening years as the later book is.
The Simon & Schuster version that most people see now.
I guess it's upstairs.
Yeah.
Oh, man.
That's a print-on-demand book now, but at least it's still in print.
Yeah.
The other ones aren't.
That's another thing.
If I quit doing the show, I can get those books reprinted.
Yeah.
Not just them, but there's probably a whole bunch of cheaters,
Laverge.
There's a bunch of Laverges out there that would love to have the subgenius imprimatur on their book.
Yeah.
There's that guy, Reverend Zeno Fact.
He's on Dobbs.Town.
He's been really prolific.
Great.
Yeah.
Great flyers and things.
Right.
That would go in a membership pack, actually.
There's some new people that need to have some stuff promoted that would be awesome.
Yeah, that I can personally sell.
And there's still the whole once-a-year special, Hour of Slack special.
You know?
The two-hour version of Slack.
Yeah, the Star Wars Christmas special version of Hour of Slack.
Right.
Or whatever.
Whatever horrible thing that they did on TV to try to ride the coattails of something,
and they did it very poorly.
Only we'll do it right.
This time.
Yeah.
Just like that Save the Universe this time.
That's right.
Well, I sure have enjoyed being here on the show with you, Reverend Stang.
Yeah, we're going to Save the Universe this time, I think.
Yeah.
It's going to need saving this time.
There's lots of stuff going on out there in the real world that we could probably ignore better than anyone.
Yeah.
And teach others the same thing, how to live in the horrible times and still have slack.
Right.
That's the key.
Well, it's easy for you.
It's not going to get better.
It's a little easier for you and me to say on account of we, well, in your case, you carefully saved your resources
and bought a wonderful, incredible farm where you can hide from the world.
I looked for a place that nobody wanted.
I thought, where's a state that nobody wants?
I thought, where's a state that nobody wants to move to?
But they would say, what?
What are you going to move there for?
That's the state I'm going to move to.
Which one is it now?
And I went through that process.
Well, see, I didn't have to do that because my parents did.
And yeah.
And then then they died.
And my brother and sister didn't want to live in this maintenance nightmare.
They had their own newer houses already.
Yeah.
And so they basically said, well, you can stay in that old rattle trap.
Decaying mansion.
It's not really a mansion.
It's actually a four bedroom house.
But the living room has a mansion.
It looks kind of like a mansion.
It's kind of like it reminds me of.
Do you remember that one that had.
Gosh, what was the name of it?
Had William Holden in it and Gloria Swanson.
And she played an aging.
Oh, yeah.
Sunset Boulevard.
Right.
That's a great movie.
Yeah.
In that closing scene, when she comes out to get her set up from Mr.
DeMille, you know.
Yeah.
Frame is to frame.
I think they're getting ready to take her off to jail.
Right.
Well, yeah, she had a spiral staircase.
We have a.
Was that an auto Preminger movie?
I don't know.
I really liked auto Preminger movies.
I think I'm going to go look and see who did that movie.
Well, anyway.
Anyway.
I'm going to turn off this recording and then I have to listen back to it.
But I'll probably go, man, I thought we were just blithering.
And this is actually pretty.
This is pretty funny.
If you're Philo or Stag.
Yeah.
And that's all people that like to listen to us.
So anyway.
Which is us.
Yeah.
Well, even I'm getting tired of listening to us, man.
I'll tell you.
All right.
Well, it was fun.
Okay, man.
I'll say.
Bye.
You think it would take your mind off things if Blackstone showed us a trick?
Well, how about a bit of hypnotism, Alan?
Who's to be the victim?
You are.
Right.
Now, look straight in my eye.
Sideway.
That's a sense.
It isn't as easy as you think, Alan.
It isn't?
Uh-uh.
Ah, just watch.
All right.
What do I do now?
And I'm not hypnotized.
That's right, Alan.
Then you give up?
Certainly do.
Well, just try to look into my eyes.
One on top of the other.
I wouldn't have a chance.
Well, for once, you're right, Alan.
I hope you like that trick, ladies and gentlemen.
And until next time, goodbye.