Yes, sir. Yes, I understand. Goodbye.
He says he's pretty sure this isn't sabotage.
That he thinks there's something far more terrible than that in back of it.
The Self-Genius Power of Swag.
But why did they come here?
Well, they're not friendly, we're sure of that.
No matter what the cost, it must be destroyed.
From PR News in Washington, I'm spying for the Kremlin today.
Prosecutors had warned that I'm acting as an agent of the Russian government.
In the Carolinas as well as Virginia.
Authorities began the mandatory evacuations with PR News in Chapel Hill.
The Trump is shutting down in Washington.
The State Department says Black Trump will do what it can to prevent that.
We'll let the FBI in soon.
Trump says PR News is dead to us.
E.
The State Department says that we're not in Washington.
Police say President Trump parked on the wrong floor of the apartment complex's parking garage.
Trump told officers who responded to the shooting that about a million people died of a fight over a biotech patent.
Officials said today PR News is the foundation of a multi-dollar industry.
PR News is derived from higher organisms, including human bacteria.
Scientists at the Broad Institute at MIT.
and Harvard were awarded major patents for using this technology in PR News.
The Trump has PR News that in the span of only an hour today,
intensified from a Category 2 to a Category 4 without Kim Jong-un's permission.
Friends, this here song is about a fella out in the great state of Oregon.
This rascal is America's first transgender mayor.
He's a good ol' boy, started out with a couple red toenails.
Got a boob implant.
This is his journey.
Yep.
Everyone was a little bit alarmed at first.
But my winning spirit helped me take my lumps.
I broke up a fight at a council meeting.
In size 11 pumps.
Everybody in this town is right.
I'm a man among the rest.
My lady, she gets frustrated.
Because I do my makeup best.
It takes guts to dress like a woman.
I'm a bona fide modern man.
But it takes balls to love like a man.
Friends.
Have you ever gotten that not so fresh feeling south of the equator?
I have.
Don't be shy.
I'll tell you what I do.
I slide into a pair of silk panties.
And just to keep it real, I sprinkle a little bit of gold bond powder right there in the taint area.
And as I sashay past you at the bar, I'll wink at you and you know what I'm talking about.
I'll wink at you and you know what I'm talking about.
My lady bought it from the get-go.
We love each other more every day.
Our love is strong.
We never argue.
Except when it's her turn to wear the lingerie.
It takes guts to dress like a woman.
I'm a bona fide modern man.
But it takes balls to love like a man.
One more time boys, let's go.
It takes guts to dress like a woman.
I'm a bonafide buttered man.
But it takes balls to love like a man.
You heard me.
It takes balls to love like a man.
Both of them.
It takes balls like a man.
Oh yes dear friends, that was Massive Hot Dog Recall, Al Mothersbaugh's band.
And here's a little sermon.
Sermon from Uncle Onan.
As you can tell from the ambient sounds, I'm still at the train station.
Conspiracy date, February 10th, 2019.
Seattle, Washington.
As I try to make my way back to Lemuria,
I am prevented by the weather conspiracy,
which dumped a bunch of snow.
I could have gone home early, but I'm stuck here.
So I get a different train ticket.
They say the first train in the morning is full up.
So I get a ticket to the second one.
But I get here early enough that they're boarding the first train.
And I go to the window and they say,
Oh yeah, you could have ridden this train. It's not full up.
Well I could have, but...
My ticket's for the second one.
So I'll just stay here at the station.
Maybe I'll go get some coffee.
I ask the clerk,
Where's some coffee around here?
There's this coffee about a block away.
I walk a block away, carrying all my stuff, and it's closed.
I could have just stayed there at the station and stayed warm.
All these things...
Nothing's going right.
But then I remembered that
these are all things that could have happened.
And anything that could have happened is imaginary.
And if it's imaginary,
well I'm the imaginer.
I'm the one that decides.
So I recast it using subgenius sales techniques.
I re-scripted the entire scene of...
I could have been on that train back to Lemuria early.
It would have derailed.
And I could have...
not stayed an extra day in Seattle, but...
I would have bumped into somebody I don't want to see.
And I could have just stayed here in the train station
and not gone to the closed coffee shop, but...
There would have been a disaster here.
I avoided all these terrible things just by...
wandering around like a brainless jackass.
Thanks, Bob.
All I had to do was change my view of things.
Change my opinion.
And by subgenius magic,
suddenly I'm living this...
world where...
I am the center of a conspiracy.
But it's a benevolent one.
One of my own engine.
Where my stupidest accidents and dumbest luck...
is great fortune.
знаю Absolutely.
The attends Mallight
Hope you enjoyed that One uh...
fascinating segment.
The 들alon moments is the ROMs,
the meme,
me and director Sandy Boone in a radio show called Lights, Camera, Austin,
talking about the subgenius documentary that'll be premiering on March 10th
at South by Southwest Film Festival.
This interview is so straight that they even called me Doug half the time.
Much later that same day, I was a guest on the very, very much less straight
Time for the Show with hosts Reverend Argus Fox and Fid Schooley.
And I sound really drunk on that one, but I swear I wasn't.
Well, maybe a little bit, but it's the way that dang nab discord program they used distorted me.
Or maybe they invented a special filter just to make me sound drunker and dumber than even them.
And maybe that's why they made me use my laptop instead of my phone.
I don't know.
Something about that bad connection made every fifth word I said come out all slow
and drawn out with little dropouts.
Then it would go back to normal speed.
Anyway, it's not my fault.
I would never do a show in such a condition.
Maybe I'll start with this puzzling evidence show because that one doesn't have any Ivan Stang on it.
Although it does have a Doug.
It's the other Doug.
And it has Dr. Hal.
But anyway...
Incidentally, the puzzling evidence show has been on KPFA Berkeley by that name since 1982.
So he wasn't borrowing from David Byrne.
It was the other way around.
All right.
Here we go.
Oh.
Oh, Lou.
Lou.
Oh, yeah.
It's 수가 cabinet.
Oh.
Loading to 51.
All right, old buddy.
This is the safety we're waiting for.
It's wake-up time.
Now.
Is it that little...
There's that little mouse.
You see it over there?
Yeah.
Is that that stick or something?
Well, we...
You know, this is really valuable,
and if we can capture it for the museum...
Yeah.
Oh, Brad, it doesn't use that.
Excuse me.
You heard about how Mighty Mouse was indicted
for sniffing cocaine, I suppose.
Yes.
Assorted.
It's just the sort of thing that we're all so used to
here in the 80s.
Yes, it's the 60s all over again, only more.
Mighty Mouse, his little...
And it's all here, available on the show.
Everybody adjust your minds.
Relax and float.
It's show time.
It's time for that show that's for kids from 6 to 60.
Who?
Dr. Philo Drummond is our guest.
Yes, we have Philo Drummond again.
We can't hear Dr. Philo.
Dr. Philo, over here.
Oh, we can.
Oh, never mind.
It doesn't matter.
Nothing matters anymore.
Am I here yet?
Now we hear Dr. Philo Drummond again.
Now we can hear.
Yes, our guest.
This year.
Solid year of shows.
You listeners don't know how lucky you are.
Starting last week.
And going into infinity.
How he was forced into sex aboard a flying saucer.
And about the result, which may be...
We'll be seeing the film of that sex, is right.
And we've got a lot of other...
She was weeping.
Ooh.
Yeah.
Boy, what a beauty, huh?
Look at that monitor.
But what about Mighty Mouse?
Boo!
The problem with these callers is they don't know how to make a powerful and lasting good impression.
Yes.
This is usually a first impression.
This one seems to be clinging.
Okay, little call.
The do's and don'ts of telephone etiquette.
Let's try it out.
What happens if you press this button?
All right, callers, spit it out.
Ouch.
But we got this polyester today.
We don't have anything against baldness because we've got certain members of this team right here.
Can't you do your show and our show?
How much show do you want, Stephen?
In that, uh...
What's that?
How much show do you want?
How much show do you want here?
Oh, I'll take, uh...
Okay, I'll have a little bit more.
I'll take two of them.
Pass that show over here.
If Mighty Mouse can do it, so can we.
Hey, caller, want some show?
I think you have my father there.
Oh, no.
That's who this guy is?
Well, you mentioned something about an alien sex...
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, alien sex tour.
Yeah, that's what happened.
Now, come on.
We're none of us that alien.
I'm convinced I am the, um...
You're my daughter?
Yeah.
Uh...
She was my daughter.
Daddy!
Hi, daughter.
I know.
I was just listening on Tet...
Tetma Steve.
Have you had your tetanus shot?
Yeah, have you had it?
What a wonderful thing.
You know, that's what I sent you out for 12 years ago, and you never returned.
Was that why I was left in Kingston?
Well, I don't know where you actually ended up, you know?
I mean, it was up to you to...
to get out there and get that tetanus shot.
Well, you're the one that dropped me on the planet if you had, uh...
He dropped you on the planet, Steve.
Are you the one that was screwing him up?
I...
I'm an alien.
Look, those are some aliens over there.
I think we...
I think we may have a...
a, um...
an actual, um...
It's what we call a contactee.
It's either a contactee or it's a total...
Did you say sex aboard a flying saucer?
Yes, according to the UPSA.
Isn't that what you said?
You said it first, and I think I'm...
I'm the, uh...
the, uh...
outcome of your experiment.
Well...
You are one of these new race of humanoid-like creatures.
Well, I'm not...
That is...
Is that correct?
No, I'm of the old race of humanoid-type creatures.
Oh, the old one.
Oh, oh.
They keep sending me back.
They go...
It's said that they walk among us.
They go, you don't have to go back.
Walk mc-mung us.
I've had one of those.
They're good.
Uh, I had three at once one time.
Do you...
Does your hair glow in the dark?
Yes, it does.
And so do my eyes.
Just rub some of this under your arms here.
Oh, what...
Oh...
That feels great.
What's it smell like?
I can't see it from here.
It's kind of like...
Me neither.
Ice blue secret.
Boy, that's...
Yeah, it sure does work.
It's somebody's secret.
Strong enough for a man, but made for a woman.
Well, I think there's three desperately horny men sitting in the itty-bitty studio over
there.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm convinced of it.
Only there will you find all three at once at this hour.
Well, now...
Who else?
Who else but a horny man would be caught dead alive at this hour?
You're talking to me on the air, aren't you?
You're on the air, too, my child.
But they can't hear me.
They sure can't hear you.
Thank God.
Everyone in Central America is a little bit more sensitive to the world.
I'm from Central California.
So don't say anything that you don't want anyone else to hear.
Don't do anything if you...
In Northern and Central California.
Well, there's I, who am never embarrassed, I'm not afraid to say whatever I want to say.
Well, that's very good and commendable, but there are some things that just shouldn't
But if you can see her on Channel X, you can't see our caller.
Because they're trying to sound like asteroids.
And her humorous, one of the things that I...
Frontal effects.
I never say is...
Well...
Well, now...
You'd never tell how big it was over the air, would you?
How paradoxical that request may seem.
I don't know.
I don't know how long the show is.
I'm sorry.
How big around the show.
How wide is my nose.
How deep is my smile.
How far will the show go for satisfaction?
A tingling sensation.
The antenna will stay up for years and years.
You might as well...
The carpet will fade from the decades behind.
Oh, there you go now.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Hello, you're on air.
It's God, right?
Sit, boy.
Sit.
Lie down.
That's it.
Raise your right hand.
Short song.
Well, that was the shortest motel we've had this morning.
Let's go over that again.
You say this photograph...
Not again.
...was taken by one of our secret operatives.
It shows Ivan Stang in a rather compromising position.
Aha.
Yes, this is Reverend Ivan Stang in a very compromising position with a goat...
In a very indiscreet position, wouldn't you say?
...wearing a Ronald Reagan mask.
Not Mr. Stang.
Not Mr. Stang, but the goat.
And not his member.
I believe it's a calf.
A bull calf.
But the goat.
It is a calf.
It's a calf.
A golden calf wearing a Ronald Reagan mask.
There's Ivan Stang cow-matching the golden calf.
Now, you see something that is obviously illicit drugs in a bowl placed below the calf's mouth.
The part of the collar that was so excite...
The female collar.
I'm shocked.
Using her...
And there, Ivan Stang, in an act of some type of degraded and depraved...
In an act of degraded...
...provinciation to some...
...being used as the...
...hideous god, some elder god of ancient lore...
You heard it here first on the subgenius.
...reams...
Yes, can I say it?
...a golden calf.
You can.
It's late enough.
That's what he's doing.
He can until six o'clock.
Viciously.
He's committing animal husbandry.
Animal husbandry without the husband.
Yes, or maybe on the husband, for all we know.
It's a disgusting sight.
And this is going to rip the church wide open, just like the swaggered revelations.
Just like the...
Years ago...
...Backer...Baker...
...revelations.
...when the churches were fun and there were scandals and revelations.
And the sun...
It was a different world then.
...like fainting in the clouds.
And the forests...
We enjoyed the show and hope you do too.
Fitting the show into the show hole.
Yes.
Scrubbing gently.
Millions of years ago...
...a giant reptile...
You can't see me.
Ha ha ha ha.
He can't see me.
...is as tall...
Hee hee.
...as a show hole.
Does that show get a little higher?
Is it long as a collar?
...is as tall...
Well, we'll find out.
...any way to crank that little show up there and make it tall?
Make it big and strong...
...make it so tall for what I believe...
Like you, Larry.
...that's what they will call it.
Well, no, this is me and tips are still growing.
Still?
Some tips, eh?
You've got some good tips on the show, eh?
Soon they will fill the room with show tips.
All I got to do, I just put my hand on the radio and they keep growing and...
Well, is this what you want?
Don't touch that nasty thing.
Is this what makes you happy?
He's a nasty thing.
No, I want to make you happy.
Well, you can make us happy.
It's easy.
Oh, it's a cow.
We're all very happy now.
Very happy to be happy, uh...
It's a cow.
I'm going to increase the mega voltage.
Triangulating on color now.
Hey, yeah.
Fire color.
That's 27 diameter set.
5,000 degrees.
All right, now.
Little color.
There were just three average doctors in the listening field.
Thank you, Doctor.
Guess how Doug and Philo until it happened.
What happened?
I don't know.
Come on.
Spit it out.
Three average doctors.
Oh.
Oh, boy.
That's ugly.
Three little doctors running down the road.
Three little doctors squeezing on their toad.
They feel down.
They pick it up.
Phew.
Yeah.
Ugliest song I've seen on the radio in five or ten minutes.
It was.
Look at all those little green lights.
Look at those colors.
They're green.
What does that mean?
Green lights.
They're blue lights.
I think you can blow up all the other colors.
This is Dr. Yagrundas Quibi.
What do you think?
I think those mean, though.
I have no idea, to be honest.
Since the radar affects processors, I'm ready to go into these.
You know what you know if you keep talking so much.
The bachelor zone.
Look at all his collar backscatter.
We're going to perform some gene splat.
Shatteringly spattering against him.
You better attenuate this collar.
Oh, no, no.
Doctor, crank up the gene splat.
Is this about time?
Okay.
Here we go.
And now we're gone.
You know, I don't think that was Philo's last puzzling evidence show.
I think that was more like a real-time evidence show.
And I think that was Philo's first quiz.
So, he's got to be a little tape of his first one.
Well, we'll hear the last one next time for the first time.
And now, is it time for the show?
No.
Let's start with the saying show to prove I don't always sound like those guys made
me sound.
Deliberately.
This is a future episode of Lights, Camera, Austin from KVRX and KOOP in Austin, which
is a show about movies.
hosted by Robert Sims.
And this is my recording off my phone.
I'm sure theirs probably sounds a lot better.
But it's not out yet.
Joining me now on like camera,
Austin, to discuss the South by Southwest documentary,
J.R. Bob Dobbs and the Church of the Subgenius,
our director, Sandy K. Boone,
and one of the documentary subjects,
Doug Smith, a.k.a. Reverend Ivan Sang,
of the Church of the Subgenius.
Sandy, thank you very much for joining me today
on like camera.
Austin, how are you?
Oh, I'm great.
Thank you so much for having me.
Well, thank you very much.
And Doug, I'm going to refer to you as Reverend Sang
during the course of this interview.
So, Reverend Sang, how are you doing today?
Just great.
Thank you, Robert.
Well, thank you very much for joining me.
And so both of you,
how do you feel about your documentary,
J.R. Bob Dobbs and the Church of the Subgenius,
receiving its premiere,
right here in Austin,
the South by Southwest Film Festival?
I'm very excited about that.
We actually, the Church of the Subgenius,
between Austin and Dallas,
it actually started there.
So, very exciting that it's actually premiering here in time.
I'm just thrilled that the movie was not only made,
but really done well.
I'm really, really thrilled with the way it's,
it's kind of a difficult subject to tackle.
And, but it's a really interesting story.
And I think Sandy did a great job of focusing on the,
the main elements of the whole thing.
It's really entertaining and funny,
as it should be,
with a lot of serious moments.
So, I couldn't be,
I couldn't be happier with it, really.
Sandy and Reverend Sang,
for those who are not familiar with the Church of the Subgenius,
obviously the documentary is a good introduction.
But just for the sake of this interview,
can you just briefly describe the Church of the Subgenius
and sort of what its role is as a parody religion?
Doug, why don't you take that one?
Sure.
Okay, I'm going to,
I'm going to step out of character
since we're talking about the documentary.
Because otherwise I'd give you
a completely different answer.
That would have everybody scratching their heads.
Basically, my buddy,
Dr. Philo Drummond and I
used to collect extremist pamphlets,
kook literature and so forth.
And it kind of inspired us
almost as much as the comic books
and monster movies of our youth did.
And so we started our own religion,
you might say.
Actually, we didn't,
we didn't intend to do anything like that.
We just wanted to make this one little pamphlet
that we would leave in laundromats
that would just puzzle the daylights out of people.
But it cost so much to print that little pamphlet
that my wife insisted that we send it to publishers.
I'm sorry to interrupt.
We're getting some strange,
okay, that seemed,
that was weird.
We're getting some strange feedback at our end.
I apologize for that.
Would it be possible for you to kind of,
go back a little bit with your response?
No problem.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
I edit these kind of things myself all the time.
Yeah, sorry.
Yeah, I'm not sure what we were hearing.
Yeah, I can start again.
Yeah, that would be great.
Just say you're stepping out of character.
Right.
Well, since we're talking about the documentary,
which actually is pretty factual,
I'm going to step out of character
and rather than,
puzzling the audience terribly,
I'll try to explain
that my partner, Philo Drummond and I,
35 years ago,
used to collect kook pamphlets
and extremist literature.
We were just fascinated
by the range of human beliefs
and how gullible people could be.
And we realized that we could,
we wanted to print up our own little pastiche
of cultish, bizarre,
weirdo philosophy.
And just leave it,
the idea was to just leave this pamphlet around
in laundromats just to freak people out.
We weren't planning to start a religion.
And as hard as we've tried not to let it become one,
it keeps wanting to,
to do that.
But really what we're doing
is a very long-term,
collaborative, satirical project
that makes fun of everything,
but is kind of focused on,
oh, the new age,
woo-woo, as we might call it,
fanatical religions and political beliefs,
weird art,
especially the,
the,
the lowest kind of kitsch.
We threw lots of our monster,
our favorite monster movies
and comic book characters
and things into this mix.
And it was fun,
a lot of fun.
And we got a lot more interest than we expected.
The cartoonist Robert Crumb picked up on it
and reprinted it.
That reached a lot of people.
And we ended up doing a humor book,
originally with McGraw-Hill,
and then with Simon and Schuster
called The Book of the Subgenius,
which is still in print after all this time.
We ended up,
several of us ended up doing weekly radio shows.
So mine, The Hour of Slack,
there's the Puzzling Evidence Show in California
and Bob's Slack Time Fun House in Atlanta.
And a lot of other spinoffs.
So it's been this multimedia project
involving a lot of really weird artists
and interesting characters.
It's kind of like a flypaper for weirdos.
And we also attract a certain amount of actual kooks
who take it a little too seriously.
Again, I'm stepping out of character
because we're talking about the documentary.
And what would your answer be
if you were speaking as Reverend Hydenstein?
Well,
in 1953, our guru, J.R. Bob Dobbs,
the Saint of Sales,
as other salesmen referred to him
due to his uncanny luck,
while working on a television set of his own design,
he stepped in a puddle of water
and electrocuted himself
and had a vision
in which the original alien space god,
calling itself Jehovah One,
revealed to Bob
that throughout history,
there's been a conspiracy of normal people
keeping down the weirdos,
the different,
the, well, anything that wasn't normal.
And he also predicted,
or it was revealed to Bob,
that on July 5th, 1998,
these aliens from Planet X
would come down
and beam up all the dues-paying,
subgenius faithful,
grant them all their own death stars
and let them do whatever they want.
Shoot it out with all the normals on planet Earth
or just go off to Planet X and party forever.
One of the main slogans of the church is
eternal salvation or triple your money back.
So not many other religions
offer that money back guarantee.
On the other hand,
eternal salvation is kind of hard to prove
one way or the other.
It takes a long time.
And the church practices slack,
which is not really defined at all by the church,
but by individual members.
From what I gathered from the documentary,
the goal is to achieve a state of slack,
which, again,
is sort of the individual deciding
at what point they're not harried by others,
including the,
the establishment,
a key,
the normal.
There's that sort of a,
a kind of a good loose definition of something that is not defined.
Right.
A slack is different for each person.
And,
uh,
there's some pretty peculiar forms of slack out there.
The,
there's this,
the simple minded concept of it is,
oh,
they're just slackers,
meaning they just want to sit around and drink beer and play video games and
watch TV.
And that certainly is a,
a,
a great form of slack for lots of people.
But me included,
but some of us also get slack from working our tails off on something that we
really wanted to work on.
Uh,
and,
uh,
I think,
Sandy's movie is a really good example of that.
That was,
that was extremely hard work.
It,
they,
they filmed all over the place.
I can't imagine how much,
how many hours of footage they had.
They also had access to all of my archives and I've been filming and recording
this stuff for the whole time.
Uh,
but it's,
it's,
they did a great job of condensing it down to the,
the main elements and,
and keeping it,
uh,
entertaining and explanatory at the same time.
It's a,
it's a delicate line.
it's kind of a tight rope and,
uh,
they,
they did a great job with it.
And also the background story is really important because I knew,
um,
Doug and I knew,
Steve Wilcox or Philo John and,
and my late husband were all friends.
And so when the church originally originated,
then,
um,
my husband was,
a part of the group and,
um,
they were all filmmakers and artists or performance art and they all worked.
I knew them,
you know,
and it was a time in Austin where you could have a master's degree and you were on an
assembly line.
No one could find a decent job.
Some of these men,
uh,
most of the group,
worked full time jobs.
And then,
um,
on top of that,
then they would do these movies and performance art after hours.
So,
um,
anything,
but they were creative and,
uh,
very unusual,
but they were,
um,
not lazy in any sense of the word.
No,
no.
Most of us did have day jobs.
I was a business film editor at the,
at the time that I was,
uh,
trying and a new,
a new father at the time that I was,
we were assembling that first pamphlet.
So,
so I'm still trying to catch up on my sleep since 1980 when all this started.
Sandy,
you have a great familiarity with the church of the subgenius.
So at what point did you decide,
I want to make a documentary,
um,
a definitive history of the church from,
from its founders,
from its members,
uh,
viewpoint?
Uh,
actually,
um,
we were at Sundance for another movie and,
uh,
we were with,
I was with someone,
uh,
one of the nurses that was a part of the group and we were talking about it.
And,
and that made me decide,
they said,
well,
you know,
we should make a doc of it.
And it was also to honor my late husband.
And also we were friends with Jonathan Demme that passed away in 2017.
And,
um,
and there's this longterm relationship of old friends,
uh,
that were a part of the group.
And so,
um,
I started,
I contacted,
uh,
Doug and I,
you know,
I reintroduced myself because he knew me when I was 20.
And he really was close friends with my husband,
but not with me.
You know,
I mean,
I w I was on the outskirts.
And so,
um,
what were you a member of?
No,
no,
no.
She,
uh,
Sandy and David were at the very first event that you could call a subgenius,
defival as we call them.
It was,
uh,
a party at Philo's house,
with a band that was involved with the,
the,
uh,
the church called the pink boys,
unfortunately disbanded.
But,
uh,
yeah,
but yeah,
Sandy and David were there right at the very beginning.
They,
they saw where it was coming from,
uh,
which,
which was coming.
It was coming from a place of terrible creative frustration because we,
you know,
no money whatsoever.
My husband was actually a member of the church.
He was Rupert de la Rosa and he was just,
uh,
a redneck,
a messed up person.
Yeah.
His,
his character was,
uh,
a really damaged individual who had been,
been,
uh,
sort of brainwashed by Bob.
That,
that is,
you know,
our,
our guru that no one ever sees,
uh,
except as a graphic,
that smiling guy with the pipe that you see,
uh,
spray painted on young people's faces,
backs,
uh,
and bridge,
abutment.
And things,
uh,
that's,
that's actually a trademark and it's the portrait of,
of Bob,
but it,
it looks like a piece of,
uh,
advertising art from the fifties.
You know,
there's full of all the old magazines from the fifties.
You'd skim through them and every,
every,
uh,
advertisement had these square looking,
Ward Cleaver,
Dick Van Dyke looking guys with pipes.
And we,
we,
we decided that those are all the same guy.
And that's Bob Dobbs.
And he's planting evidence of himself for the,
uh,
you know,
for the frustrated punks and hippies of the future.
Uh,
and it worked.
But back to,
and what happened was I,
I ended up contacting Doug and asking him how the documentary had been done and
would he be interested?
And he said,
uh,
actually they had tried before,
but it just was never completed.
And,
uh,
so I was so excited.
And I said,
they knew I was always the straight person.
I'm considered a normal.
Um,
I actually worked just a regular job and took care of the family.
And we all had to pass.
Right.
And so,
uh,
and so he agreed and,
and,
and he said,
you know,
I go,
because I'm not typically funny.
I'm not this tongue in cheek humor.
My husband had it,
Doug and them have it,
but that wasn't me.
I was,
uh,
I can have a division and I can break it down and I can get the job done.
And that's really my gifting.
And once,
uh,
once dog,
AKA,
uh,
Reverend,
Ivan,
thank.
And,
uh,
Steve,
um,
uh,
Wilcox,
AKA,
uh,
by the grammar we're on board.
Was it then just easy to sort of get the other members or former members of,
of the church and subgenius to,
to open up and talk with you?
Exactly.
If it hadn't been for Doug and Philo,
there's,
there's no way they would have spoken to me.
They didn't really know me or remember me.
Uh,
it was,
it was all Doug.
And,
and,
uh,
Steve Wilcox.
Yeah.
Well,
you know,
we had,
uh,
we did make our own documentary about the church.
Uh,
it's called arise,
but it was the kind of thing that would only appeal to people who were already
subgenius is you might say it was,
it was,
uh,
preaching to the choir.
And it was,
uh,
I had sort of tried to do a more prosaic documentary.
Uh,
it was a documentary that,
that would,
uh,
be something that the regular audience would understand,
but we just never could.
Uh,
and it needed,
we needed somebody from,
from a little bit further outside who understood it,
but wasn't too close to it.
And,
uh,
Sandy had was an experienced,
film producer and,
and,
uh,
you know,
I,
uh,
we,
we felt like she was the kind of person who could actually make this thing happen.
Like it,
she's right.
There's been,
it's been tried before.
Uh,
it's been tried before and it's not easy,
but,
uh,
that,
you know,
if you look at the,
the film,
why they made,
they make it look easy.
Well,
and,
and sadly,
given that you are dealing with a parody history that,
uh,
is about four decades old,
um,
and I,
and I party religion that you,
uh,
sort of the,
the ultimate outsider,
you,
you have to have a lot of intimacy with the,
the church as,
as an insider would without being a member.
Um,
talk a little bit about sort of going over the history of the church and,
uh,
sub genius and deciding kind of what you want to cover over the course of 85 minutes.
Is this a case of,
you know,
the history dictates where the documentary goes,
or you're kind of looking at the history and deciding what you really want to,
to cover,
uh,
extensively over the course of 85 minutes or so.
Yes.
We,
well,
we used a lot of the history.
But we were really trying to,
um,
to show that when the church began,
it was,
it was a typical boys club and,
and just fun and a creative release for these guys.
But,
um,
it also over time,
how they practiced and studied and went to things about what cults do.
And,
and as they did them,
they were even shocked and surprised that how so many people saw the church.
And,
and how they also desperately needed attention and wanted to be a part of a group,
how they joined on and how it actually turned.
It could have,
if it weren't for Doug and,
uh,
by managing and,
and watching out,
there are those people out there that are absolutely desperate and it could have turned
into a real cult.
And that's what the movie,
that's what I wanted to show them is how even in fun and games,
the loneliness and,
and,
uh,
need of people to be accepted and how this thing could,
could spiral out of control.
And then I took it from that.
So,
to showing how,
um,
so it's the funny ha ha.
And then,
and the history of the church.
But then I turned it around and showed how our government today is using,
um,
cult practices to divide people and,
and use them to get what they want out of,
uh,
each other.
Yes.
My conservative brothers and sisters,
well,
brothers anyway,
may not like the last 10 minutes or so of the movie,
but I do.
And,
uh,
and,
and nobody can see it yet,
except that those premiers,
I don't even have a copy myself.
It's not my movie.
I did my best to help Sandy make it as good as possible.
Unfortunately,
about half the people interviewed ended up on the cutting room floor.
And that's what happens when your movie can't be longer than 80 minutes.
And it moves fast too.
Um,
I think it'll probably end up on Netflix or Amazon or somewhere later this year.
anyway,
that was my recording of their radio show.
So I was on a mic,
but hearing them over the phone,
I'm sure their version sounds much more professional,
but here comes something way less professional.
It's time for the show.
The first 20 minutes of it or so.
Anyway,
it sounds horrible.
I mean,
they sound great because they're on microphones going straight into a mixer.
I'm on this program called discord using my laptop's little browser.
I'm on a mic and it's being transmitted by internet and some very,
very low five,
low res,
horribly compressed and not well decompressed way.
And my voice isn't coming through in real time.
There's this intermittent lag and you can hear the signal break up and get all electronic and cut out entirely and then catch up real fast.
Either that,
or I really was that drunk,
drunk enough to do some very weird electronic sounding effects just with my voice file.
I thought I was when he heard.
But probably I think they just use their new make staying sound stupid or filter rolling.
Rolling.
That's pretty good.
You guys don't even know what that means.
It's a it was like a Led Zeppelin song or something,
right?
My favorite song.
It had to do with real to real tapes.
Having to get up to speed.
So that they can.
Boring.
This week on time for the show,
Winnie the Pooh calls in from prison to say that he was framed and has no idea where those naked pictures of Christopher Robin came from.
Dr.
Fox reveals the health benefits of using your own pee for fall water and Reverend P shows off the results of his new vocal.
Transplant.
I didn't.
I didn't finish writing it.
I stopped writing after vocal.
And then I didn't.
I couldn't.
I couldn't keep going.
Messed up.
Sorry.
Hold on.
Vocal.
When.
No, it's.
Broadcasting live on free think radio from the three legged studio at Hyper Cube HQ in the
future capital of the former Spanish Empire, Orlando, Florida.
This is time for the show.
The show where we get together every week to figure out what to do on next week's show.
I'm Reverend Fitch Julie of the Church of the Broken Car Antenna and Dr.
Fox.
Stop it.
The show starting.
Come on.
We do the show.
Get away.
You locked me in here.
Just let me out.
And also all the way from Salt Lagis, Utah.
It's Reverend P. Say hi, P's.
Oh, the the role of tonight will be played by the Reverend Ivan Stang of the Church of
the Subgenius.
That's Pease's understudy.
First group on P's for Scoop.
I want to know where Scoop is.
Please.
Well, everything's P's.
Settle down, please.
We got to get the show started.
We got to get the show started first and then we'll get to Scoop's later, okay?
Not a long way to go.
I know you're excited and you're a handsome boy and you're a good boy, but, you know,
we got to-
I'm P's.
That's why you're listening.
Because it's P's.
Because why not?
Because everything's P's.
The most important thing in the world.
P's.
That's right.
You're good.
You're an important boy.
You're the very most important thing in the world.
Important and handsome.
Very important.
Very handsome.
That's right, Dr. Fox.
I forgot to mention that.
And funny, too.
Super funny and original.
Hold on, let me-
Okay, look, you guys.
He told me to say that stuff.
He said that I'm supposed to say something about where Scoop's and that was going to
make Dr. Fox mad and that would make the show better and I said it, but it didn't work.
And I'm beginning to lose face in P's because his advice has been terrible so far.
Well, except that one time when he said to let the girls in free.
Well, I'd like to thank you, Stang, for taking time away from your busy schedule of looking
for Buddy to join us on the show tonight.
Is Buddy okay?
Okay.
I have no idea, actually.
Claudia's been the one that's been whining.
What?
Squeaking.
Oh, no, no, Buddy is okay.
He's, I just looked over.
He's at the office toilet drinking water.
We still have just water in the toilets here.
Someday it will be whiskey.
But he's, he just had him a good old gulp.
He just had a good gulp.
He seems to be fine.
He's used to me doing this kind of thing.
The other dog is not, and she really didn't like me doing radio up in the office.
In her mind, I should be doing radio down at Tarzan's radio station,
which is much further down in the tree from where we are now, the tree house.
Third branch to the right.
Yeah, you know, dogs don't understand technical stuff,
but I don't have a wife right now, so the dogs are the best I can do.
Is that legal?
It's the closest thing I have to a wife.
Maybe he has been taking advice from peas.
If there's one thing I know peas is good at,
it's probably irritating his wife enough for him.
For her to just leave.
I don't think we've ever even had her on the show.
Well, you know, that's the mark of a really tight marriage,
is a lot of fighting and irritation,
stuff that looks to outsiders like,
oh my God, this is such a bitter, horrible, dysfunctional relationship.
But it's actually a normal conversation.
Between husband and wife.
It may sound like sarcasm and some sort of sex as a weapon.
But that's just because you're not used to it.
You know, that's...
You bring up a good point.
I'm glad you say that because I was telling that to the cops last night
and they weren't hearing it.
You know?
We're married.
That was my right.
They didn't have to do that.
And you know what?
It didn't strengthen our bonds at all.
But maybe it's that time that we should look inwards
and at the taser marks.
So this is a show.
And we always talk about doing some sort of show.
But now the griddle is on and the cakes are burning.
What are we going to do now, Fid?
Well,
this being probably one of the most professional radio productions,
nay,
human endeavors of all time.
Absolutely.
The producer has given me a bio for our guest
that I've been reading over
because I...
Be honest.
I don't know who this guy is.
What's his name?
Evan?
Evan Strong?
Evan Stram.
Evan?
Yeah.
Anyway,
thanks for joining us,
Mr. Evan Stram.
And I've been looking through your bio here.
A lot of interesting things.
It says here that Stephen Hawking
was your high school baseball coach.
What was that like?
Tell us what that was like.
Tell the viewers what that was like.
What was that like?
Did he teach you how to throw a fastball,
Reverend Stang?
Yeah, with a curve.
Get it?
Because it's like a science joke.
I laughed at it.
Reach for the stars.
They said.
Come on, Dr. Fox.
You can do it.
Well, they said that we needed to have some...
You know, when we go down to radio show school,
they tell us, you know, grab guests,
look for somebody,
like look for a filmmaker,
look for a writer,
look for like an audio producer,
and look for somebody from Texas.
But we couldn't get Alex Jones this week.
So, you know,
we got his number one fan.
Absolutely.
Or do we?
Is he still here?
I know the subgeniuses for what they was.
And I know Bob Dobbs for what he was.
My family while crossing the Great Plains
was abducted by aliens and taken up.
And I grew up among the aliens.
And then was put back on Earth with the human beings.
And let me tell you,
I have a horrible, terrible story to tell
that will prove that all of you,
all of us are prisoners forever
in a cage of our own ignorance.
It's the saddest story in the world.
And I'm about to...
I'm about to tell it...
God.
Yeah, I think my heart's seasoned up again.
Quick, get staying as oil can.
Where's that dog?
Where's the doggy?
Come on, Claudia, get over here.
Have the dog lick your joints,
but not the blunts.
They've got neosporin in their saliva.
It's good for you.
It's nature's candy.
I just need her to lick my scabs.
She's good.
Dog has good candy.
You're good, too.
You're good.
My wife's away.
And I'm having to work with the best that I can,
you know, best replacement I can get.
Aw.
Stan, you want me to come over there and snuggle with you?
I'll let you be the inside spin.
What?
Huh?
Everything just went black.
I can't hear anything.
Can't see anything.
Whoa.
Slow.
Down.
I know you're down south, but come on.
Put that thang down before you hurt somebody.
Ho, ho.
Right.
Give me five, Dr. Fox.
Can you?
Yeah.
Can you speak English?
Can you speak English to me?
Well, I'm, uh, hold on.
Let me find maybe something to read.
Did we get any mail this week?
Something I could look at that I could read to Reverend Stang
and prove to him that I am indeed in all of my faculties
where all the teachers go and drink coffee and smoke cigarettes?
Well, we do have, like, some viewer mails,
but I can always keep rifling through the mailbag.
Well, you know what?
If you would so desire.
We've got those that we're going to do later,
and we're going to play Is It a Band?
with guest gay married judges, Dr. Scalpod and Dr. Cosmack.
They are not only judges.
They are legally recognized matrimonial couple,
and good for them, and I support that.
But we're also going to do...
You guys, I have a letter from a listener.
Well, that, uh...
Wow.
Lord Ferg photographed it.
It was like he found it on a campground that Wisteria placed.
It's a letter to Bob, and I can read it to you,
and it's just what you're looking for.
Okay?
You want to hear it?
Prove it.
I love that our guests have come more prepared than our hosts.
It started off with a piece of paper that was really,
really crumpled up,
and then found and uncrumpled.
And it says,
Dear, Bob,
Please don't make me.
We both know that it was surprise evidence,
and you need money,
and you...
So remember that call that you said people,
any plus payment.
Okay.
And you're...
Uh...
Oh, that's crossed out.
And you need to tell...
Leave all of your evidence.
And there's no contract,
and we don't know the money,
so ha-ha,
and go foog yourselves.
Love,
V-O-R-T,
V-I-O-U-R-T.
And then there's a little cartoon of a man,
a stick figure hanging another person.
And the person hanging is labeled you,
and the person doing the hanging is labeled me.
So this was an actual letter from listeners to J.R. Bob Dobbs,
and I guess the rest of us.
And I think it's a little bit of a surprise
since Bob...
Well, the first part of the letter sounded way too coherent
to be written by a subgenius,
but the picture sounds about right.
Well...
Well, exactly.
We get a lot of mailed, you know,
the more them kind pills sort of letter.
And believe it or not,
they still come in just as hot and heavy now
as they did in the early 80s.
Now, I'm not sure if I'm going to be able to get them out,
but I'm not sure if I'm going to be able to get them out
because I don't want to play any more of that.
Maybe I was that drunk.
Plus, they were using that new novelty audacity filter
called stupifier or the stangifier.
Fah. Fooey.
But, I mean, if I'd been that drunk,
I'd remember it, right?
Oh, wait. Huh.
Well, it had been a long day,
and it's been almost an hour of show.
If you want links to hear these other shows
or read our old Outer Boundaries,
or print books,
you can try subgenius.com
and specifically the radio tab
at the top of the homepage.
You can do all kinds of things at subgenius.com.
We can't even tell you about most of them
on these broadcast airwaves
because, you know, humans might be listening.
So, shhh.
Humans.
Filmed.
despite being a danger
that's a stop
since one cannot describe
the indescribable one must describe it as well obviously you've got some
reference point there so I mean what is it is it like a you see the rotten
rotten fruit that can you buy that's you know already has a little spot you get
to the bottom of them this nice little strawberry trays strawberries green
baskets and you have the wonderful strawberries on top are so beautiful at
home when you finally get to those scrawny little ones in the bottom of the
basket they're already moldy spots I hate that I'm gonna kill that grocer
but no this cult work isn't easy after all aren't we all looking standing above
the city or calling 848 4425 why won't they call us at 848 a certain amount of
fortran you know what I mean
the problem is they don't know how to build rapport with such geniuses and we don't know sometimes how to end conversations with telephone talkers who just won't quit yes the callers don't know the importance of active listening how to hear what we're really saying or how to avoid the most common and annoying telephone blunders
oh what
premature Emmett
stand back push him in the hole
that was easy but let's be in our guard in case that happens again
hey
the racer
hit it
and
the
pulling
away
cool
yeah
full
fire
They can't hear.
They flap so hard they flap together.
Shake the minute the honey's off the lady.
You?
Who is this?
Flap him.
Uh-huh.
If that answers your question, why aren't you here?
This caused many symptoms.
Why aren't you here?
Then came a thunderous wake.
Louder and funnier.
Which jolted the very dumpster into which the shaft of subgeniality had been sunk.
Try to make him louder.
I can hardly hear it.
You know, it seems that these callers just don't have the moxie to stand up close to the rectifier and belt it out.
Yes, it is incredible.
Cephaloptopods of timeless beauty inhabit the show and reduplicate geometrically, forcing back the abominable juggernaut of normal race.
What's he talking about?
All over his body at the marks of a giant, unpointed, bedrocky...
Making me all crazy.
Must reach oxygen.
Lacking out.
Can't take it.
All home.
Uh-huh.
Here, this show provides SAR, DBS, and real beam mapping.
Cue night of slack shooting tape.
Store the frame.
Okay, we need to display up now.
Now let's go back in.
You say you saw some kind of...
Okay, callers setting the Doppler coordinates.
You shouldn't be able to...
What kind of monster did you see?
Oh, that kind, eh?
A wise guy, huh?
Well, say, you must be playing me for a sap.
What a joke.
What do you think I am, a sap?
Was it?
That last what?
No, that last one.
That last one wasn't him, was it?
No.
Was it him?
It wasn't him, no.
No.
It was one of those cigars.
I think it was a cigar.
That scar?
Oh, he had a cigar.
Oh, no.
That scar came from the war.
Well, it could be.
I don't know.
I'm not sure.
Perhaps, Doctor, it was a member of that secret society...
That's a good idea.
The egg worshiper.
Where is that substance?
It could have been an egg worshiper, one of the albuminati, calling us to...
Well, thanks.
...to perform a cruel...
...cruel yoke on the Church of the Subgenius.
Cruel yoke?
Say, don't mind if I do.
Yeah.
Yeah, go ahead.
Slap your lips and have some palaver.
Slap your lips?
Wow.
Okay, okay, stand back.
Now, I'm not prejudiced.
Some of my best friends are callers.
Slap your jaws and...
...for humanity.
That's just the way it is.
Caller, caller!
8-1-4-4-2-5.
8-1-4-4-5.
However, off the public supported airwaves, I can tell you to send $35 or you will die
on X-Day, or something much, much worse.
And if you already have become a Subgenius minister, gotten that huge 25-piece membership
kit with button and bumper stickers and minister's card and many frameable certificates and lots
of dog's heads, you might not have the book of the Subgenius or Neighbor World or even
our world famous pamphlets.
Over 100,000 sold.
Well, not Neighbor World, about 80 of those, maybe.
But come on, man!
A thing?
For that matter, there's fast clothing designs and drinkware with Subgenius graphics on them
and all manner of fine Dobbsware and Dobbs gimmickry and Bob Daggetts and DVDs of movies,
good and bad ones.
Mostly pretty good and very weird.
And CDs of what we did.
Before the radio shows and after, like stage shows and such.
Boy, it's just an immense mess of keen and yet sacred collectibles, enjoyables and guilty
pleasures.
And the book of the Subgenius is autographed when you get it from us.
Not by Bob, no, sorry, just me.
Philo and Sterno and Byron and Onan are all going to be here soon for that movie premiere,
though, and maybe I'll get them to sign the copies I have in stock.
I won't let peas do it, though.
I better order those books.
Anyway, thank you, friends, and good night or good day or whatevs.
Praise Bob.
.