It seems to me that from the newspaper and magazine articles I've been reading,
all the hype building up to the new Twin Peaks season,
that the critics and the regular TV people are just dying to see Twin Peaks die.
They really want the mass TV audience to get fed up with that weird stuff.
It's so confusing.
I don't know whether it's over my head or maybe I'm missing something,
but it's about the dumbest thing I ever saw.
And the reason I think these critics and regular TV people want to see Twin Peaks go down
is because if that show stays popular,
then that would imply that those critics and regular producers and technicians and stars and writers,
it would imply that those people had spent their entire lives being wimpy, cowardly, conspiracy pink boys.
And I hate to hear pinks talk about,
who they think killed Laura Palmer.
It's like they don't even watch the show, you know.
They'll throw out all these ridiculous ideas.
Oh, Leland did it.
Oh, it's really Madeline.
She's really Laura.
And all this kind of...
What they never seem to mention is the element of the supernatural,
which was sort of carefully thread throughout the first season.
And now, of course, it's come to the fore.
The supernatural aspect.
The...
The owls are not what they seem, dear friends.
And Bob killed Laura Palmer.
I'll bet you.
In the end, Bob killed...
Now, of course, Bob was Laura Palmer.
But Killer Bob, as Laura Palmer, said,
kill me.
And that's the way it is, dear friends.
That's the way it works.
And that's the way it's going to be tonight.
You are about to participate in a great adventure.
You are about to experience the awe and mystery
which reaches from the inner mind to...
The subgenius hour of slack.
Eternal salvation.
Or triple your money back.
Just let the show flow right over you
like warm honey as you sleep.
It runs down your forehead into your ear.
Feel it? You feel it? You feel it?
That's right.
Ah, relax.
Go with it. Go with it. That's right.
Are you going to stay?
Well, uh...
Well, um...
Whip it up.
Well, uh...
You're so sexy!
Whip it up!
It's no laughing matter!
That's as if I'm willing to make value judgments,
which I'm not!
It certainly ain't no permanent solution!
Who knows when another one makes...
Wait, you don't know what's going on?
I can't stop dying!
You're the master of my...
I'll make that man of you!
Take it!
I don't care anymore!
You make me...
Be run...
Call it all human.
Come to the war.
You mean I should volunteer?
You're drafted.
Now come.
You mean I don't even have a chance to volunteer?
You have a chance to come as a draftee.
Are you calling in everyone my age?
Not everyone.
Only the boys?
Girls, too.
Which boys?
Which ones?
The ones drafted.