Brace pop.
Ladies and gentlemen, may I have your attention please.
When we leave this area in a moment, be sure to take along all your belongings.
Including your imagination.
Beaver!
You were calling to him in the dark?
Where is Bob?
What are you gonna do to him?
I'll ask the questions.
Where is Bob?
ünkü
B-Hit to believer!
Barbara's fever.
What are you doing?
I'm not doing nothing.
The
S.O.S.
G.E.F.
The Hour of Slack.
There is truth
and there is untruth.
Freedom
is the freedom to say
two plus two equals four.
If that is granted,
all else follows.
And I saw an airplane hit the classroom.
Uh, uh, uh,
one terrible day.
Terrible day.
And I saw an airplane hit the classroom.
Uh, uh, uh,
one terrible day.
TV was obviously terrible.
The Matrix is everywhere.
It is all around us.
Even now in this very room.
You can see it
when you look out your window
or when you turn on your television.
You can feel it.
When you go to work.
When you go to church.
When you pay your taxes.
It is the world
that has been pulled over your eyes
to blind you from the truth.
My truth.
That you are a slave.
I confess to spreading the rumor
on orders from Groves' team
that the war is not ready with you.
Eurasia.
That for years,
in fact since the days of our glorious revolution,
I had no faith in our future.
I forged government announcements
and falsified figures
voting for agricultural and industrial
As a result of mental disturbance
dating from my experiences during the atomic wars,
I was a willing subject of Goldstein's influence.
I was stubborn and egocentric.
When own life thoughts occurred to me, I reveled in them.
I went into the proletarian zones.
I had sex with prostitutes.
I deliberately contracted syphilis.
Yes, dear friends, Norrell Preff did that one.
The preferable Norrell Preff.
Enter.
I'm trading for a second.
Okay, you can trade because trading is always a good thing.
Yes, Norrell Preff of heavyconfetti.com is gone.
But Lonesome Cowboy...
Cowboy Dave, princess.
We are dough.
A few heavy confetti.
Queen of all the UFOs.
Actually, Norrell Preff is still here because he's in the background.
He's that background music.
All of the background music tonight will be Norrell Preff's steaming, sizzling guitar work.
And or Lonesome Cowboy Dave on the accordion as heard here.
Well, we could do live.
We could do a live rug.
Can you talk and play that at the same time?
I can't do neither.
No, I think perhaps...
What the hell is that?
Dave, Lonesome Cowboy Dave has entered the studio wearing an antique accordion.
I mean, a giant keyboard.
Oh, no, the bellows are blowed.
So now I have to maybe put it down or something.
It'll only add the kind of ambience like this.
Well, that sounds horrible, so put it down and shut it off.
No, that's enough, Dave.
Okay.
I thought you could really play it.
I thought I could, too.
Oh, you can eventually.
See, you don't want to waste a whole program waiting for me to get warmed up.
Have I a day?
Hold on just a second and let me read this news.
Okay, everyone's holding something, but it doesn't really...
There was this news thing that came down the pike last week and nobody said anything about it.
The sub-DMEs didn't say anything about it.
Well, the...
They're rather recalcitrant and uneager to speak their own pieces.
No, just the opposite.
And they still didn't say anything about this mass extinction in process.
Now, this won't be news to everybody, but...
Is this actually true?
Is this a true thing?
This is a true thing that I am...
Well, I mean...
I don't understand.
It was on CNN, so no.
With your little saucy-shaped shovel.
The answer is no.
It was on CNN.
Okay.
It said that a survey of birds and butterflies in Great Britain shows a population decline
of up to 71%.
Yes.
A finding that suggests the world may be undergoing another major extinction.
Mm-hmm.
Uh, the, uh, supports the theory that the sixth big extinction in Earth's history is
underway.
And this one caused by humans.
Because for over 40 years, more than 20,000 volunteers counted each bird, butterfly, and
native plant that they could find in beautiful Mariola.
Oh, man.
The bird population has declined by about 54%.
Native plant species, a decrease of 28% in only 40 years.
Oh, man.
Quote,
The bird population extinctions were recorded in all main ecosystems of Britain.
The authors report in Science Magazine, and a biologist with Smithsonian National Museum
and blah, blah, blah.
Sam Gornian.
They may not be representative of the world as a whole, but they have the best data.
The data supports the idea that the rise of humans over tens of thousands of years, along
with climate changes, are bringing an extinction of many species and reshaping the world in
ways that aren't.
Some are not so far from being totally, utterly and utterly understood.
Some are not so far from being totally, utterly understood.
Okay, now, wait a minute.
As a small bit of human interjection, just like I would like to relax your
lubritator, or just perhaps, you know, like if I was to pull on the top of your
pituitary gland or something.
Ooh, that feels good.
You like that tickling motion?
I like that.
Okay, now listen to this.
I've actually made observations because, you know, sono osopetoric.
I mean, I am an assyrup runner.
And I do watch things very carefully.
Have you noticed?
You don't notice because you're from Texas.
Peepers.
Too early, man.
Too early for peepers.
Way too early.
way, way, way too early for them weird southern birds.
Like when you're down south, those birds that go,
those ones that have that nauseating,
that voice,
way too early for the birds.
You go,
like that.
Way too early.
Red-winged blackbirds.
Everything is kind of way screwed up right now.
Way, way, way.
I went past a microwave tower the other day,
and I saw birds incessantly going back and forth,
east and west, east and west,
almost banging against two groves of trees,
coming back together.
There was like a silence for a second.
Then as they were gaining momentum,
they started roaring of birds.
What the hell were they doing?
They were confused.
This is a migration pattern,
and everyone is confused.
Mom nature.
Mom nature has had enough.
Mom nature is shrugging.
First hurricane in the South Atlantic.
What's up with that?
The sun is going down in different places.
If you say that, they think you're nuts.
And the...
Now what?
The sun is not really going down the way it usually does.
It seems to go down,
and then all of a sudden, a couple days later,
it's going down a little wester.
It's supposed to be going, moving more easter.
I mean, norther.
Actually, Dave, the sunlight...
Is not real?
...is decreasing from the last...
has decreased slightly over the last decade or so.
I'm telling people the dark...
Often people I have known, I have said,
the darkness is growing.
And they think I'm trying to be poetic.
What I mean is there's an actual substantial darkness,
almost similar to dark material,
which is sucking on our gonads and ripping our flesh and...
No, don't worry, Dave.
See, the Earth is slowly passing out of a cloud
that has prevented our intelligence from developing.
And soon, we'll all go insane.
That's...
However, now get this.
You know, there have been five extinction events
in Earth's history.
With some so severe that more than 90% of all life forms were killed off.
90%.
The largest one was when the Permian period...
The Permian period.
...ended some 250 million years ago
when all but 4% of all species disappeared.
Another famous one was the Devonian period.
Yes.
From Akron.
Yeah.
And almost 35% of the hipsters were extinct in one final moment
when their entourage moved to the harvest country or the October...
We are in the middle of a sixth extinction event
that began about 50,000 years ago
with the expanding role of...
in the world of human beings.
We have likely underestimated the magnitude of the pending extinctions.
But nothing less than the enormity of the whole event.
You think your peepers are all messed up.
We looked out the window and...
And you do need new glasses.
But the fossil record shows that the disappearance of many animals
in Australia, Madagascar, and North America
started about the same time that humans arrived at those sites.
Mmm, who'd have thunk it?
And gone, therefore,
from our beautiful North American environment
are such beautiful animals as the mammoth,
the camel,
the giant sloth,
and the Dave-raping taper.
The face...
The giant face-raping bat
has all but vanished.
The corpulation...
Giving us no longer any excuse for the...
The, uh...
Face-sucking?
Bat sperm antidote.
Oh, you mean the bat...
The bat...
Copulating.
Yes.
The face-copulating bat.
The face-abusing bats of the...
The face...
In northern Ohio.
The face-copulating bat does exist, still.
They're already gone.
I have seen them.
I've seen their migration patterns.
I've noticed their toot-whistle, the way they sing.
And I've even interviewed a few of them for various stories.
Well, the good news is...
Lies, of course, all lies.
The good news is,
this wave of extinction caused by humans
could come to an end with the extinction of the humans.
And there's another interesting little bit of factual mail
that came down the pike, or news, last week,
which was that...
A hundred-foot asteroid hurtled past the Earth,
only 26,000 miles away,
the closest asteroid ever detected by astronomers
before it made its approach.
Now, they said here, friends,
that anything 130 to 165 feet across
would probably make it to the Earth's surface.
This one was only 100 feet across.
It'd probably burn up, maybe break a few windows.
As it tore in.
It was the closest recorded encounter
between Earth and an asteroid,
says Stephen...
who also said,
there certainly have been closer encounters
that we didn't know about.
And those are the ones I like to think of,
you know, late at night.
The asteroid was close enough to Earth on Thursday
to be visible through binoculars.
If it had hit Earth,
it would likely have broken up in the atmosphere.
Here.
And it was only discovered last Monday.
So what if...
Now, this one was small.
Stank.
What if it had been the size of a football field?
We'd have had three days to kiss our butts goodbye.
This is the voice of your alter credo.
Don't you know your religion is based on this folk science?
This is folk science.
You just...
Hey, Dave.
You can't be heard.
You just stepped on my punchline.
Oh, punchline.
Yes, and I just turned your...
I'm setting up...
I know.
He was punching me with it.
I'm showing...
I'm showing you...
I'm demonstrating something for you.
I can turn...
I'm turning...
See this little knob?
As I turn it down, you disappear.
Yes.
Now, see, you've got to watch for my punchlines.
When my eyes light up...
See that gleam coming out of Reverend Stank's eye?
You know it's not time to pounce out with a new line.
But...
And it's a big atmosphere that almost butted its...
I mean, a big asteroid that almost butted its...
It's way into our atmosphere.
And it just barely went by.
And then it's like, oh, gosh, wasn't that wonderful?
We saw an asteroid.
It almost hit us, but it didn't.
Isn't that cute?
In 2002, only 1.8 million years ago, on June 21st,
an asteroid the size of a football field passed extremely close to Earth,
but remained undetected until days later.
This one came 75,000 miles close.
Would have...
Would have packed some major firepower had this big boulder struck,
comparable perhaps to the Tunguska asteroid or UFO crash,
which flattened 77 square miles in 1908.
This bare mess happened to be kind of a lightweight among asteroids
and wouldn't have wiped us out like the big one did, the dinosaurs.
We wouldn't have known what hit us.
But, well, the funny thing is people say...
That is the basis of your religion.
Well, now, see...
The nice thing is now here it's the 2,000 and millions of the future,
and we could just nuke it out of space.
See, if our astronomers saw this thing coming, we'd send some brave Americans up...
What's that waiting for?
And they'd nuke it out of space.
It's a much larger object than the ones you've referred to,
and this is the basis of your religion.
And, no, we're waiting for aliens to come and do all of that stuff.
Well, they think a bunch of alien ancestors are going to come and save them
when Punga smacks into the hard cakes.
And they also think that...
What's it called?
Lunga?
Limpelotomy?
The bowling lane area and stuff?
They think everything's going to have to be recreated.
You know, not incestually or ancestrally.
I mean, incestually.
You know, if...
Use the same chromosomes over and over.
No, we won't do that.
If one of them big rocks did hit and didn't kill us all,
the insurance companies would have a hell of a time covering the damages, you know.
Well, why do you think the insurance companies are recovering all their assuragements
and all these things that are going on in the banking world?
Why do you think the Bilderbergers and the Schmelweifers
and all these different groups are coming together?
Why do you think the secret societies are fomenting so strongly?
Well, what I'm saying is the good news is
if one of those asteroids were to hit,
it would kill them too.
They, even the Bilder...
Even your buddies, the Bilderbergers
and the guys that run the world secretly from the mountains in Switzerland,
deep underground,
even they would be wrecked.
There's a thing going on in the sausage oil industry.
Because...
Because, friends, it's hard to...
Even if we had a rocket ready to launch when the thing was coming three days from now,
it's kind of hard to hit something going six miles per second with a rocket.
And it's very easy for something going six miles per second.
It's very easy for something to hit all kinds of stuff.
If you were going six miles per second,
you'd probably have to catch up with your own thinking.
That's the robust idea being passed around in the great channels of thought nowadays.
This is what's coming down from the elder ones.
Oh, they've already made documentaries about the animals that will replace us
100 million, 200 million years from now.
Well, we've all got replacement animals right now.
That's the problem with everything.
At the end of the future...
It's too easy to make them.
At the end of the future news report that we saw,
the future is wild.
After 200 million years, after humans are removed,
giant land squids will migrate across a new pangea
and tool-using squid monkeys will...
Yeah, now that makes sense.
...swing through the trees.
...swing through the trees,
prompting a new future, we can imagine,
with these squibbons evolving up through...
The only culture.
...squidus erectus primos quidthropocus,
becoming squavemen and finally the squen and squimen...
The squenettes.
...who will build a new civilization after we, the humans, screw up.
We'll never build any culture beyond that which can be built in a petri dish.
And you want to know why?
Because the very nature of their midbrain itself,
which is what...
...gives them their raison d'etre's and, you know,
the other things you can put in your cereal.
What kind of raisins?
The midbrain?
Raisin d'etre's.
And that's why they think they're in their midbrain,
but actually they're floating around somewhere way, way south of there and stuff.
Mm-hmm.
That's very scientific.
America's new condom, condominium.
Any hypotenuse?
Pineal sands.
For those of you scratching the exterior.
Like, like that.
Okay, I'm gonna...
It's very, very, very new.
I do a lot of...
You want to try one little lick on the side.
If you lick both sides of it,
your head begins to...
I can't lick that flat.
...fabric, yeah?
Mm-hmm.
Dave, have you ever heard of Alex Jones?
Oh, yes, of course.
I met Alex Jones at the brewery the other night.
He passed me some documents,
and I passed him some information.
Here he is driving around Texas.
I didn't even get a moment.
Texas.
No talk about politics or religion.
This is all the involvement of enemy propaganda
rolling across the picket line.
Lay down!
Lay down, G.I.
We saw it all through the 20th century.
And now in the 21st century, it's time to stand up and realize
that we should not allow ourselves to be crammed into this rat maze.
We should not submit to dehumanization.
I don't know about you, but I'm concerned with what's happening in this world.
I'm concerned with the structure.
I'm concerned with the systems of control.
Those that control my life and those that seek to control it even more!
I want freedom!
That's what I want, and that's what Jason wants!
It's up to each and every one of us to decide.
It's up to each and every one of us to turn loose of just some of the greed,
the hatred, the envy, and yes, the insecurities.
Because that is the central mode of control.
Make us feel pathetic, small, so we'll willingly give up our sovereignty,
our liberty, our destiny.
We have got to realize that we're being conditioned on a mass scale.
Start challenging this corporate slave state.
The 21st century is going to be a new century.
Not the century of slavery, not the century of lies and issues of no significance
and classism and statism and all the rest of the modes of control.
It's going to be the age of humankind standing up for something pure and something right.
What a bunch of garbage, liberal, democrat, conservative, republican.
It's all there to control you, two sides of the same coin.
Two management teams bidding for control, the CEO job, a sh**y of lies.
I'm sick of it, and I'm not going to take a bite out of it.
Do you got me?
Resistance is not futile.
We're going to win this thing.
Humankind is too good.
We're not a bunch of underachievers.
We're going to stand up, and we're going to be human beings.
We're going to get fired up about the real things, the things that matter.
Creativity and the dynamic human spirit that refuses to submit.
Well, that's it. That's all I got to say.
It's in your court.
It's in your court, baby.
It's in all of our courts.
And we're all playing left-handed baseball, dynamites.
The entire fabric of our culture is...
It's been dismissed and refabricated.
The front court.
The place is very, very far.
Blimper court.
Labor court.
Labor court?
No, there's no more labor court.
Blinky court.
There's nothing but corporeal disenfranchisement.
People leaving their bodies for no apparent reason.
People reappearing for no apparent reason.
Bodies forming. Bodies reforming.
Psychic entities growing their own bodies.
New psychic entities growing new psychic entities growing more bodies.
A long silver thread.
Hey, speaking of new bodies, have you seen how fat Kirstie Alley has gotten on the cover of the Star magazine?
I can't believe it.
I can certainly believe it.
Kirstie Alley and I, boy, we had a thing going, I think it was in 1979.
Was she a Scientologist then?
Or were you a Scientologist?
She was modeling neck braces at the Land Down Under Stars Cafe.
It was a convention for the new neck braces.
There are also psychic implants and transceivers.
Right, right.
We've marketed for a while, none of them sold.
And now she's Old Navy in it or whatever it is.
I don't know, perhaps she's...
Her bloomers look like they would be much...
Elephantine.
Elephantine is a way of putting it.
She was perfect about 40 pounds ago.
She was diagrostic.
Back around 180, when she was about 180 or so.
That's probably just right.
Well, they say once you start accumulating all that detritus in your brain,
it makes your body want to jump out of its flesh.
Well, I don't know if they say that.
I've said that a couple of times.
Can you really blame the body?
I mean...
With so much detritus floating around in the immune system.
Exactly.
I don't know, it doesn't have to do with the church though, I guess.
Well, she was really hot back when she was a subgenius in the early days.
Was she originally a subgenius?
Yeah.
And then Bob...
See, what happens to you?
You know, let her down and L. Ron picked her up and now nobody can pick her up.
For another face of the church.
The price of the crowd.
The price of slack.
It's often like somebody's cheeks in a different way, if you know what I'm saying.
Her face looks like a butt.
I'm sorry.
She very seldom can pick herself up.
When pinks are slack-jawed, it is with bovinity and boredom.
Yes.
When we are slack-jawed, it's with slack slaked with fully sated lusts.
A happy talker.
Enlisting the smiles of everyone around.
Some of their brains are on slant style.
Look at the delightful carvings in this one's head.
I can smell my spine, Dr. Rowlett.
I can smell my own spine.
It's the fluids.
The fluids to be sucked.
There will be new cerebral fluids going around on next day.
Suckle of them.
Don't expect your old cerebral fluids to get you through that magnetic door, pal.
You're going to have to have a brain made of bubbles and feisty-ness.
You're going to have to have the mega-anche in the top of your pants.
But friends, you can have that slack.
That you so desire, so easily, by just, well, tuning in to this radio station.
The subgenius radio ministry, our of slack.
Twist that tepid torpor into a mynapis dynamic.
Dynamic dynamo of superhuman emotions and thoughts and beliefs.
Jump right out into the new negative world with your own pair of socks directly forced onto your body by one of the eliminator monitors.
Look at the hair grow on the back of your neck as you continue to repeat, repeat, lie after lie.
Or join.
Or die.
Join us, humans, before it's too late.
We're authorized to blaspheme by the gods themselves.
Run it, baby.
Well, now there's some serious umbrage.
There's some serious umbrage being taken by thousands.
Umbrige!
Not only what you say, Dr. Reverend Ivan Stang.
And Princess, we are Doe Connie of People.
People. Yeah, people, sure.
Sure, but this.
But this.
This is ten times worse.
Ten times worse.
There was a time in South Africa that people would put flaming tires around people's necks if they dissented.
And in some ways, the fear is that you'll be necklaced here.
You'll have a flaming tire of lack of patriotism put around your neck.
Now, it's that fear that keeps journalists from asking the toughest of the tough questions and to continue to bore in on the tough questions so often.
And again, I'm humbled to say I do not accept myself for this criticism.
A war is real mud, real blood, real screams of the dying and real death.
That's war.
Well, what's going on to a very large extent, I'm sorry to say, is a belief that the public doesn't need to know.
Limiting access, limiting information to cover the backsides of those who are in charge of the war is extremely dangerous and cannot and should be accepted.
And I'm sorry to say that up to and including the moment of this interview.
That overwhelmingly it has been accepted by the American people.
And the current administration revels in that.
They relish that and they take refuge in that.
The belief went so strong in both the political and military leadership in the current war effort that those who control the images will control public opinion.
They realize.
They realize what an entertainment-oriented society ours has become.
Therefore, in one way of looking at it, it's quite natural that they would say to themselves,
Hey, we've had the Hollywoodization of the news.
We've had the Hollywoodization of almost everything else in society.
Why not the Hollywoodization of the war?
The war is a war.
It's a war.
We don't know if that's going to be the Crow dominant.
The things that we think have been somewhat well-thought-out have been theTrue Crisis.
And if it's the war then I feel, I could write a hundred more of these operations.
How many Hannah give when you kill three weapons in your first go to tet which clearly was this Pinocchio project in the country we lived in, angry own comrade Shakti,
people caЙed talka outward from puppet forbade statement in his manifest to you he is going to work without everyone.
How much did you fail to stop him?
How did you create a war if you didn't have face of those...
He played bad.
Real mud, real blood.
Real screams of the dying and real death.
That's war.
That's Amore.
Actually, that was Norrell Preff.
Actually, that was Dan Rather.
Rather and a Lather, it was called.
The music was by Norrell.
Rather and a Lather.
Are you related to that royal blood?
Do you have the Sangreal, my friend?
I have the blood of the Yeti coursing through my brains.
Do you have the royal purple blood of Jesus cracks in your veins?
The blood of the Jesus of the Himalayan mountains, yes.
The Jesus of the abominable Jesus.
What about the Jesus born in Mount, I mean, buried on Mount in France?
The name of the Mount Shasta, the Bigfoot Jesus.
So you were related to the Jesus born on Mount?
I read that.
He's on Mount Shasta?
The Mount Shasta Jesus.
Sanguine McGuire.
Just call me Sanguine McGuire.
Call me Sanguine, baby.
I'm bloody and ready to fight.
Hey, look at my eye.
Cut my eye, will you, Rocky?
I mean, Snocky, whatever your name is.
Just you there.
Come over there and suck my eye.
Okay, okay, okay.
Okay.
Hey, it's going to puff up pretty bad here if you don't get a razor blade in there.
Here, here, here.
Oh, feel free to go right into the eye socket there.
That's right.
Now, just remove the old occipital gland there.
Burn out the gland at the end of the year.
What do they call the occipital gland?
Yeah, just take off that whole area there.
You don't need the brain cells anymore.
Keep on digging past the skeletal sinus thing.
You're both the members of Skull and Bones, a secret society of the air.
What does that tell us?
Not much, because it's a secret.
Is there a secret handshake?
Is there a secret code?
I wish there were something secret I could manifest.
322, secret number?
There are all kinds of secrets, Stimple.
It's a secret.
There are all kinds of secrets.
Completely alienated.
All this dread.
Purely symbolic.
The powers that be want us to be passive observers.
And they haven't given us any other options
outside the occasional, purely symbolic participatory act of voting.
You want the puppet on the right or the puppet on the left?
What a bunch of garbage.
Liberal, Democrat, conservative, Republican.
It's all there to control you.
You can't control me.
We're all the same size and the same coin.
Two management means.
Bidding for control.
The CEO job of Slavery Incorporated.
No.
It's an acumen.
It's very, very an acumen.
Oh, look, the children are coming up with the flowers now.
They've got their red bandanas on and they're waving the red carnations.
I don't know if it's time to make some more milk or time to fight for a workers' republic
where everyone shares everything except for the sausage.
I'm just going to shake this little fly.
I'm going to shake it up in the air.
Oh, that's not the real flag.
You've got to remember to keep the real flag high.
The secret flag, wear it in your pants.
That's right, in the crack of your underwear.
What about this pom-pon?
Would that be okay?
Well, you can stuff that into your knee socket
and make it look like you've got a very, very puffy ship sitting there.
Okay.
You're fine.
Keep those high steppings going.
I don't want the baton to drop.
Once again, I'm the least bit.
I'm the least bit.
Huh?
Something must have lost the translation.
Somebody must have made a terrible mistake.
I don't know what to do now.
Oh, my God.
I look out on my window, and it looks like the sky is filled with ships.
Large, large ships.
Huge.
I don't know what to say.
Does somebody help?
I'll put a note or something back.
I don't know.
I'm looking at water skiing.
I...
Subgeniuses are spiritual gypsies
discovering new short-duration personal saviors
constantly enforcing them down the throats of other subgeniuses.
Wide-brimmed.
Their philosophical journey will take them in and out of many religions and sciences.
Too tolerant.
One day, they may be undergoing water baptism
at the good old whitewashed rural primitive Baptist church
and the next night, drinking goat's blood at a black mass for...
Hell.
...13 years.
But all the while, they know it was not the Baptist church that saved them.
It was not the Scientology church.
Nor was it him.
It was, friends.
Nor was it even the church of the subgenius that saved them.
Because it was Bob.
Bob alone that saves you.
It is he that walked that hot pavement,
sweat streaming down his face,
his neck tied too tight,
his briefcase too heavy,
that whosoever believe it, then him.
And Bob, not the subgenius church,
and him.
Whosoever believe it, then Bob.
Should not go through
and should have everlasting slack.
Praise Bob.
My God.
My God, man.
Bob is back again.
After another, another long journey into abstract night.
After another journey into forceful self-rejection.
Denial of his own mind.
Denial of his own powers.
Bob has resurrected himself like that salivary Jesus you wear on your sink.
Are you related to the real blood?
The royal blood?
The holy blood?
The sangreal?
No?
Are you related to Bob?
He's like a goat with many breasts, you know.
He is very, very friendly.
I think is the way you put it.
He is friendly.
It's not the word for him.
He's not the way you talk.
You little swine.
You're all gonna have to work for it.
You're down there in front.
The one with the droopy eyelids.
I'm up here now.
Let me see the palms of your hands.
Okay.
Yes.
You do not bear the mark, my child.
Have you done your exercises?
Yes.
Have you repeated your credo night and day?
Every day.
Have you flagellated freely?
Yes.
Let me see the marks.
There's no marks on you.
In fact, it looks like those fake tattoos.
Get down on your knees and pray to the place.
Oh, Bob.
I believe in a world created...
You both were members of Skull and Bones, a secret society at Yale.
What does that tell us?
Yeah.
What does that tell you, buddy?
What does that tell you, huh?
Yeah.
What can it tell you?
They're both members of the Skull and Bones.
Yeah.
They're all thick as steams.
You know, like two fingers stuck together, one on each different eyeball.
You know what I mean?
They're all one.
They're both connected.
Far, far too connected.
Yeah, it's a deep...
Jesus takes a throne and he turns it upside down.
And oops, there comes a smile.
He making me laugh now.
Look, he's wearing clown slippers.
I can't believe our Lord looks so good in those things.
Man, look, he can make his smile go all the way from his ear to ear, literally.
Hey, son of God, son of man, you can't believe that.
Jesus takes a throne.
He makes a lot of stuff, right?
Oh, look, man.
He turns it upside down.
He's making all kinds of lights come out of the top of his head.
Oops.
There comes a smile.
They look like highway patrol lights or the police cars that are coming every day.
They'll send those things to Jesus and then he smiles.
Calm down, Terry.
I can't because I'm thinking all about how we can make Jesus smile.
Jesus has to go to the bathroom now.
Can't you leave the poor guy alone for a second?
He's still part human.
Just sit down for a second and stop tugging on his pants.
He takes care of things.
But, my child, I really have to go, literally.
Well, you can go if you have to go.
I may make you go with me if you know what I mean.
Oh, I don't know about that.
He has to go.
He's making a snowman.
He's going to the bathroom.
My mother has a bit of laptops growing on it.
It's time for Elmo's Salivating in the Hour of...
Slack!
Lots of it going on.
Lots and lots and lots of slacking.
It is possible that there may eventually be slack.
There may be a new thyroid gland built into you.
There may be a new heart muscle.
Sitting out utopia in a world without slack.
Is that what you're doing, friends?
That's right.
Have we finally reached, you know, I mean, this is the best of all possible worlds.
And yet there's no slack.
Yeah, there's no button to push to end it either.
And we're trying as hard as we can.
Thanks to unlimited food supplies,
artificially shortened jams,
gestation periods,
and the perfect religion,
the Earth, only 50 years after X-Day,
will house 100 billion human bodies,
plus almost 1 billion unruptured subgeni.
Quite a healthy soul harvest for the Elder Gods,
don't you think, boys and girls?
Yeah, I see them now.
All over again, five times as big,
like a diamond man taking up continents,
you know, rolling back like the carpet on your front lawn
when the landscaper comes,
and now...
Friends, if you believers aren't giving money,
all you're doing is believing.
Oh, we get it.
First, you want to see the eternal salvation.
Then you'll pay.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, you'll end up with that excuse nailed to your back
with a sharpened telephone pole in normal hell.
My friend, and when you yank that off,
they'll just hammer it in with a bigger nail.
Are you going to yank off with Bob, friend?
You're going to allow the nails to be driven into your skull
at that last final moment.
The passion of Bob, indeed.
You know what they did to Bob?
You know what they actually did to him?
The blood was on the floor.
He was cursing an ancient Aramaic.
They tried to nail him.
But Bob was the Jesus that didn't get nailed, my friend.
That is the miracle of it.
The beautiful miracle.
Beautiful, beautiful.
Friends, when you line Bob's pocket with love offerings,
that helps you to...
to slide between the power sanders of justice and karma.
It greases you up for a faster skid
straight through that chute of white light
and into the before life itself.
So you just kind of pop right out
rather than having to squeeze through.
Limestone pockets getting puffy.
Pop or not.
Friends, that plunge to subgenius heaven
is going to be just like a water slide at the wet and wild.
Pull the lever.
Down you go.
At first, ass guard might seem kind of hot and stuffy.
What with all the flames around you.
Fellas with tails.
But those are angels in uniform.
You know, that's a big joke they have down there.
Yeah, they're fallopian tubes with wings.
They're chasing you, man.
Human, human looking, human looking.
Yeah, they have faces.
They're like, they want to bring you in.
Make a new...
Friends, there are plenty of quality souls
frying in normal hell right now
because they can't do it.
They couldn't follow the goose-stepping guidelines
of their gods,
but they thought that they should.
Untold billions.
Horribly tortured for no greater sin
than that they wanted slack
but didn't believe they were supposed to get it.
If getting slack is a sin, my friend,
then you better pray that someday
we all become mortal sinners.
Mortal as we all are.
Yes, here we are.
Okay.
How can you give?
We are ready and waiting for your question.
Because we are subgenius,
we do go very low.
Well, I'm not actually a member, but they are.
How low can you go is a question
that's never been fully explored.
Yeah, if you've been through basic,
then you can understand the show.
What is the subgenius?
Or what does it mean?
What does it mean?
I gotta tell you, then, you know...
I almost started talking...
I can't see on the babies behind.
It means it's the same as having a
baseball glove radar strapped to your butt.
I think you got it.
It's like, Bob Dobbs, huh?
Just remember, the one thing that's most important
to subgeniuses everywhere,
the one thing you can't forget,
a subgenius must have slack.
Of all other things,
That is the motivator.
Here for the subgenius.
So if you're one that has felt like you needed this thing,
that you didn't know how to explain what it was,
and yet there it was...
Because of the subgenius, huh?
...grabbing, completing you.
What is that?
Well, it makes you jump five or ten inches higher,
that's for sure.
A subgenius must have slack,
but in order to get the slack...
So clip those coupons.
...the subgenius must disengage from the conspiracy
and be under his own genius.
So you're saying that you're not sure
Well, that's what I'm saying.
Well, let's see right here, Dr. Shlaker-Laker,
where you're moving the top of the skull with the...
Do you have the right saw?
That doesn't even look like a saw to me.
It looks like a nail file.
I don't see how we're gonna get much done here.
It's gonna take a half an hour to remove the top of this guy's skull
if we're gonna find anything out.
Oh.
Ah! Ah!
Oh, my God, the patient is still, uh...
He's not anesthetized or...
Hey, man, what...
What are you doing to my head?
You wouldn't put a nail file on my head, man!
Well, that was a memory you didn't want to have, wasn't it?
Do you remember the third time they tried to make the implant?
The third time.
Yes, they were using a different kind of material.
It was... What was it?
Laser-sort of thing, yes. No.
No, it doesn't work anymore.
I'm cultivating a dog's head on my vulva.
That's right, you're cultivating a dog's head on your vulva.
That's what we're trying to create here.
Think. Think.
You can use your mind.
This is the voice of the Inceptor Locutor.
I'm speaking to the top of your neck.
I mean, I'm speaking through your skull.
Your skull is actually now a magnifying membrane, an amplifier, if you will.
A speaker, a great, great speaker.
Speakers.
Make the naps at vulva with your mind.
This here is the quiet part.
That was a terrible dream.
I don't ever want to dream anything like that again.
I was in a laboratory and you were there.
It's all right. It's all right.
And you had a saw.
It's all right.
And then it was a nail file.
Yes, yes, yes, I know.
And they were trying to extract the royal parts of my jelly, you know, in my brain.
It's going to be all right.
But you promised me he'd come.
With a tenon and a ram.
I'm on the receiving end alone.
You said she was on the receiving end and she wasn't kidding.
Yes.
Don't you think we'd both be a little more comfortable without that gun in your hands?
I'm perfectly relaxed.
I can feel the tension mounting like the approach of an electrical storm.
Now just raise your hands above your shoulders, sweetheart, like a good little man.
Was the late Melvin Bishop an amateur Martian picture fan?
It's already answered.
That movie picture film, The Medium News, belonged to Melvin Bishop.
His wife was in bed, wrapped up on a couple of pillows with a 10-inch stiletto stuck in her back.
Right behind.
I knew you were a private det...
Pick up.
She knew.
We both knew.
Pick up.
They were all...
...private detectives.
Where can the Dobstown beat every night from Tuesday to Wednesday?
And where can the Dobson's be?
The following week, one day off for bad behavior, a couple of gags of sauce.
Head down to the old bowling alley and see what's shaking, but I'm still wearing my badge and I still got my gun.
Ay-yi-yi-yi-yi-yi-yi-yi.
It's been a long time waiting here, man.
There's like about 400 people outside of the door.
Ahem.
I...
I actually had reservations.
Not about, you know, coming here, but I had reservations to go here.
Yeah, well, I was waiting a long time, too, you know.
Well, they started a riot and then they had to call the Black Force police.
Yeah, I know.
They cracked some heads.
They also cut some spines and eliminated some...
Oh, really?
Yeah, that vestigial thing back there that...
Ah.
...they don't want to get too magnetic.
You don't have it, do you?
I...
Do you?
Of course I don't have a vestigial tail.
I have one.
I have a four-foot-long vestigial tail, which I have to hide in the bottom of my shirt,
my Oxford slippers.
It's very sexy.
I tie it up with twine.
Very interesting.
Why, well, it actually hurts when I ride the public services.
Oh, I can imagine.
Yeah.
Yeah, of course.
It takes me a half an hour to get to work.
Of course.
You don't want that special tailored clothes, do you?
No fair, baby.
You know the rules.
Go, baby.
Nice shot.
Hmm.
Ping Pong.
Ping pong. Yeah.
He's got to be kidding me.
Time. The holidays. Time. Time. The holidays.
A bug house. A bug house. A bug house. A bug house.
Me too. Everything's so mixed up.
These buildings. I'll never get out.
Oh my God. Oh my God.
What will happen?
Deterioration. Chronic conditions. Limit hope for some.
Others may go home tomorrow.
Modern mental institution. The therapy of busy hands.
First step. Power is so important.
The sick. The sick. Heat. Heat. Heat. Heat. Heat. Heat.
And lower the mentally ill. Life became too much for them.
They just left me alone. I'm going to send you to the hospital.
I think they'll be able to do you...
Why do you think they're going you this way?
The patient's mental disorder.
Well?
Schizophrenia. Paranoid склад.
Schizophrenia. Paranoid struggle.
Paranoid sleep. Paranoidpool.
Insulin shock.
Schizophrenia.
Electro shock.
Loss of contact with reality.
Disordered minds.
Reinforced shock treatment move closer to reality.
Boredom is always an enemy of the mentally ill.
Ping-pong is always fun.
Books mean so much to so many.
Religious services in the chapel offer reinforced shock treatment.
Well learned.
What a difference it makes.
And George comes too.
A cigarette from the doctor.
And Fred's hand is steady.
So this is it.
Sick, sick, sick, sick, sick, sick fear.
Not wrong.
Sick, sick, sick, sick, sick, sick, sick.
But I am well and I know it.
And most of them are happy.
I'm home.
All the time.
Rejected.
He finally really did it.
You maniac!
Rejected.
You blew it up!
I'll damn you!
Rejected.
God damn you all to hell!
The alternative, flee!
Flee America!
The Americans are coming!
are coming. George Bush
had an answer to that and he said,
screw voting, let's roll.
What was the phrase?
He volunteered to go on a beer run
and ended up president
of the United States.
Man.
Some people have all the connections.
Even that spaceship,
Pioneer 10,
fled America. It fled
the whole damn solar system.
I was glad to see somebody finally get off.
But now
it's alone, flying
through the void, no doubt
to be found a billion years
from now by some robot
who'll make a fortune selling it on
eBay as the last thing
handmade by living
creatures, the extinct human
race. It does
get depressing and I'm at the point
where I didn't pay any attention. I avoided
the news for three years
until 9-11 because I
decided that the news was either
evil or
a sin.
It's a slight difference,
but we don't know which one it is yet.
We do know that the news is
surrealism
and we have to get used
to the idea that at any moment
anything can
happen, both the
imaginable and the
unimaginable. Sometimes
the impossible, but more
often the unlikely.
Both are
uncertain.
I don't know.
Yeah, and we're going to be discussing this.
Were we in the middle of a discussion before this?
Yes. What exactly
were we talking about? Chocolate.
And Bob Dobbs?
This is terrible.
katjav designed
很
man
senor
four
to
d
Great Acres is the place to be
Farm livin' is the life for me
Land spreadin' out so far and wide
Keep Manhattan, just give me that countryside
The charge
The stars
Fresh air
Times Square
Elvis... Elvis Hitler, friends.
Elvis had sangria. He was related to Jesus Christ.
That's the thing nowadays, Stang, is to be related to Jesus Christ.
Elvis Hitler, friends. We've also been listening to a whole lot of Nora Lowe.
Nora L. Preff tonight. You can download Nora L. Preff's killer guitar work and cut-ups from heavyconfetti.com.
The general subgenius doctrine is accessible at www.subgenius.com.
Quite accessible to the masses, unfortunately.
You can also, for those without access to the internet, you can write for free information
from this post office box number I'm about to give you.
That's post office box 204206, Austin, Texas 78720.
That's Elvis coming at you!
That's box 204206, Austin, Texas 78720.
You can write to me, Stang, at subgenius.com.
But why would anybody want to do such a thing?
Why would anybody want to do such a thing as write the last of the diamond stags?
Actually, you'd be surprised.
It's a sick man.
It's about Bob.
He's very vindictive.
They said he did his politics.
Bob loves you.
Just sit right back and you'll hear a tale, a tale of a fateful trip
That started from this tropic port aboard this tiny ship
The main was a mighty sailing man, the other was a mighty sailor,
The skipper brave and sure,
Five passengers set sail that day for a three hour tour,
A three hour tour.
Ah, it makes me wonder.
Now the ship's aground on the shore of this uncharted desert isle
With Gilligan,
The skipper too,
A millionaire and his wife,
The movie star,
Oh, and the rest,
They're here on Gilligan's Island.
The skipper too,
Oh, and the rest of them are here on Gilligan's Island.
And they're here on Gilligan's Island.
And, friends, that was, in fact, Little Roger and the Goosebumps doing Stairway to Gilligan's Island.
Before that, Elvis Hitler did Green Haze.
We heard some recordings of yours truly, Reverend Ivan Stang, preaching at last Starwood.
You might check out Rosencomet.com for information on that.
In the background and around the edges, we heard lots of bits by Fernand and Anderly Murr,
and New Monet, Ed Fred, Matt Hive, Heart Ignition, and everything else was by Norrell Preff.
You are Bob.