That's true.
We could stick around for synesthesia, but for right now, I'm going to put on this.
Dave, you could probably call back later.
Dr. Sinister will be here.
But I, in the meantime, have to take us out with some sort of music.
And I'm playing this one just for our friend, Reverend Abnorm Nihil, from the latest Monster High movie, Freaky Fusion.
Thank you, Dave.
Bye, Dave.
We'll see you soon.
Bye.
Bye-bye.
I can't believe how quickly you learned to control your hybrid bodies.
Well, it's like that old saying goes, hybrids make the best teachers.
That's not an old saying.
Oh, well, it should be.
Oops.
Damn.
Okay.
This conclusion
Of freaky science
Rules and defiance
And we're out of sync, yeah
Of freaky fusion
And welcome, welcome, welcome
A very special edition of Synesthesia here on WCSB Cleveland at 9.3 FM
I'm your host, Dr. Sinister
And we are pleased to have my special guest in the studio here
Reverend Ivan Stang, Sacred Scribe No. 1
What? Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah
273, that is
That's right, and Princess Wee Ardo, you hear here?
And as well, Reverend Baby Bear
Hello, hi, hi
First time here at CSB, right?
Hi, yes
Welcome, welcome
So, I never have anything to talk about
Even though I do something that tries to pass for a talk show
And I rely on people who call in at 216-687-3515
To say something
And get the ball rolling
But now I have people in here with me
And we could
Bounce jokes about how idiotic this whole thing is off each other
How come they don't say
Get the balls rolling
Are you making fun of me?
Well, you know, between the two of us
There might be two
I don't know
Now I can say all the things that I didn't have time to say on our Slack
I have so many things to say
So much things to say
But now you can't remember them
I can't remember any of them
Oh, they'll come back when you're not home yet
I'm not thinking about them
They'll just all come back
No, they'll come back when Dave's talking
We've got
Actually, we do have a caller here
I believe this is the Buddha
Hello, you're on the air
Oh, hey
How you guys doing?
Good evening, Buddha
Yeah, uh
Actually, I'm getting some thought
God damn, you're right, doctor
Jesus was a lich
Yeah, he was not a zombie
He was a lich, alright
Because he was not a devoid of personality
There's that front line thing again
No, he was not completely devoid of personality
He wasn't all about eating brains
And he wasn't about drinking people's blood
Or eating their flesh
He would tell people to eat his flesh and drink his blood
But he wasn't doing it to other people
And he brought people back from the dead
And his wounds were still there
That's the crucial point
Yeah, exactly
That's so cool
I was going to ask you this
But kind of narrow casting here
If you don't mind
One thing about
Leaving the station
I do miss
Seeing the Reverend Stang and Princess Wee
You know, at meetings
You guys are missed
We still do have to go to meetings
That's true
Yeah
But it's not court appointed
So it's not too bad
Not yet
We just had a station meeting last week
The pizza was good
We might see you at the Halloween party though
Hopefully, yeah
I would like to
Get together and have some chow with you guys sometime
Just to
You know, it's old farts
Just talk about stuff
But you can't tell who you're meeting
At the Halloween masquerade box
They're raising heavy disguise or masks
My number's still up there
Your number's up, buddy
You know, please
You know, please write it down
You know, I think
I'm pretty sure
That
Dr. Sinister knows my last name
Yeah, I
We
If you want me to give them
Your number
I will do that
Oh, of course
He's got it right here
He's got your address
He's got your social security number
We know what you need
We're gonna read all that, right?
Other than social security number, no
But, uh
No, I'm a semi-hermit in Euclid, Ohio, but
Favorite pizza topping
We know all of it
If you'd join the church
Of the subgenius
I'd have your
Your human street name
Your address
Your credit card number
Birthday
Shoes size
Mother's maiden name
Mother's bra size
Favorite dog
And childhood
Oh, God
Favorite teacher
We know all that stuff
About every subgenius
Baby bear is sick
What?
Has baby bear had her shots?
No, I'm a rabid bear
Yeah
His temper shots are definitely
In the, uh
Hey, I'm fine
I'm
My temper's fine
What do you guys say about it?
Bud?
You know what?
I just now remembered
A nightmare I woke up from
It was either this morning
Or yesterday morning
I had a terrible nightmare
That I had to kill a bear
And it didn't go down easy
I was beating it with a rotten log
And it was a sick bear
Why would you do that?
I don't know
But you'll like this part
Right when I finally thought
I'd killed the bear
And it was a big one
A big brown bear, I guess
You killed him a bar
When he was only three
A smaller bear
A baby bear came crawling out
And I went, oh no, he's still alive
Oh no, that's a different one
Oh, well
And it was scared
The baby bear was scared
And I was
So you killed a mama bear
And orphaned her cub
Apparently I did
In this dream, yeah
You're a monster
Yeah
I did
I felt terrible about it
Someone in armor
Is gonna hunt you
In a video game
That's a video game carryover
It's bleeding over
The baby bear liked cats
What?
Cats?
You like cats?
Yeah, of course
Cats are awesome
Okay, cool
If you didn't know
I was gonna have to
Stand and kill you
Right then and there
You're safe
No, they're delicious
Yeah
Stop
They're great fricasseed
Oh, PETA, listen
PETA, PETA
Who was I?
I think this one comedian
Said, yeah, I
I kill a parrot
And feed it to a cat
Just need the cat
To piss off PETA
That's not very nice
No, that's not nice
No, no
Angering
The PETA is nice
That's okay
That doesn't bother me
Hopefully she was facetious
I think they're meaner
I think this talk
Has scared the hell out of my cat
Because she's nowhere to be found
Well, if you have any bears
Coming around
Give me a call
I know how to handle it now
I won't kill the babies
Oh, so you're not responsible
For the bear cub
That they found in New York?
That's right
Somebody mugged a bear cub
In New York
Right
Oh, that's right
I saw that
I saw that headline
And posted it
On the Scrub Genius Forum
Yeah, someone posted it
In reference to me
Right
On Facebook somewhere
I said, oh, no
And then I posted that link
Because baby bear
Mugged and, you know
Beaten to within
An inch of its life
And what was it doing
Running around loose
In Central Park
In the first place?
Hey, man, you know
Things happen
No, things don't happen
Sometimes you just
Get in the wrong cab
Those cabbies let bears in
You just get out
At the wrong stop
They just let you out
All drunk
And too much honey
Too much mead
I mean, seriously
If a bear actually
Got into the cab
You know, with a fistful
Of dollars
To pay its fare
Like, would you really say
Like, I'm sorry
I don't give rides to bears
Like, would you
Would you really do that
If you were a cabbie?
No bears can ride
No, they'd probably
Take the money
That's discrimination
Not only is it discrimination
But, you know
It's a bear
If a bear walks up to me
With a fistful of dollars
And hands it to me
I'm
I'm just gonna take him
I'm not gonna do anything
I'm gonna hang out
With that bear
That has all the money
That's what I'm gonna do
What a bad influence
If a bear walked into a cab
That's barely possible
I mean, that's
You gotta think
That's New York
That's the big apple for you
Yeah
Well, critters are
Wandering into cities
More and more
Oh, yeah
Deer walk up and down
Our suburban street
Constantly
And coyotes have learned
That kitty cats taste good
And chihuahuas
And even mountain lions
Are, their habitat is spreading
So why not bears?
They've also learned
That American trash cans
And dumpsters
Are just filled with food
That we just throw out
Yeah
There's actually
A problem
There's a problem
With black vultures
In southern Ohio
Where they've become
Acclimated to people
And they just swarm
All over dumpsters
And black vultures
Are much more aggressive
Than turkey vultures
And they are not afraid
Of people at all
And they hang out
In huge roosts
At dumpsters
And they are
Kind of terrifying
That's been going on
For so long
Actually, Charles Manson
Recorded a song about it
Well, it didn't used to be
A problem
It didn't used to be
A problem in southern Ohio
Actually, I was in a
Black vultures are pretty rare
In Ohio at all
But they've been going
Farther north
And getting all tough
I've seen them
Flocking around my neighborhood
A couple of times
They mean mugging?
Just
I don't know
What the heck they're doing
They don't
Migrate, do they?
It's just
Starting to get back
To wildlife
Black vultures
Don't really
But they also
Usually only stay
In places where
They don't have to migrate
But I'm assuming
The ones that come
As far north in Ohio
Probably are migrating
Like turkey vultures
Turkey vultures
Do migrate
From the north
Back down to the south
But black vultures
Usually only stay
In an area where
They can live year round
Oh, okay
If you were a supervillain
Would you be
A buzzard woman
Or a bear woman?
I'm the queen
Of the vultures
Oh, that's right
You're on a comic book cover
I'm on a comic book cover
Your leg doesn't look right
In that drawing
What?
Why?
There's something weird
About your leg
On that drawing
Most of those
Now I'm not going to be able
To stop seeing it
When you put that
In my head
Well, that's my problem
That's why I told you
To leave my head
That weird leg
On that drawn
Fictitious baby bear
Many subgeniuses
Have had their portraits
Drawn by Reverend
Suds Pasha
In the form of
Comic book covers
Bobco comic book covers
If you've been
Made into a comic book
Hero by Suds
You know you're really cool
Which, sorry Dr. Sinister
Yeah, it's okay
I'm actually very hard to draw
I had to pay for mine
If it makes you feel any better
People tell me
You draw flies really well
I do draw flies, yes
It's a dot
With a couple of wings
They're pretty easy
Philo taught me
How to draw flies
Oh, you meant
Draw them on paper
I'm sorry
Yeah, Philo taught me
How to draw flies
You draw a little piece of poop
And then you draw flies around it
And you draw stink lines
In fact
In subgenius pamphlet number one
That drawing lesson
Is on the page about
Bull Dada
If you really look at that
That page
It is a lesson in cartooning
It shows action lines
Stink lines
Surprise lines
And flies
And sweat
Sweat drops flying off
You know it's like a lesson
Philo was teaching me
How to draw
And it was like
Oh good
Well now we have some art
For our pamphlet
Stan, what kind of critters
Have you seen in your neighborhood?
Fort Leggett I'm talking
Um
So
ライ
It's
Do I have this back?
It's Steve
That's good
Yay
Hi again
Keeps him off the street
Keeps him out of trouble
Unless we know where he is
That's all I gotta add
I'll talk to you later
Remember to pass that on to Stan
Will do
Okay
Alright
See ya
Bye
Alright
Sue
Welcome back, Dave
Poor Ned
Is it a picco-yoon voice
A teeny tiny little
Monstral
More like a picaresque
It's more like a cigarette?
No, no
But
Not pika-yoon, pikaresque.
Oh, pikaresque.
Yes.
Like your life, Dave.
The story of your life.
I forgot the meaning of that word.
Pikaresque.
That means there's no plot.
It's just a whole bunch of kids.
A series of misadventures of a character known as a picaro.
Ah.
Like Don Quixote?
Sure.
Yeah.
What the hell not?
Okay.
Well, I feel like Manuel Cervasio or whatever his name was.
I think I've realized there's a way to name my donks, so to speak.
Or so to bark.
Bark, bark, bark, bark, bark.
Oh, I thought you were going to bark.
I keep thinking of our barks.
It is the season for howling.
Yes.
I can imagine people's Adam's apples.
We're snuggling and throbbing like snakes and rioting like...
Never mind.
I was just like...
I used to think that in order to make the subgenius salute,
that you kind of needed an Adam's apple.
But Princess Wee and my daughter both proved that wrong.
You can kind of force it.
How about playing the William Teller picture on your neck?
You need to...
I'm sorry.
You need to abuse your larynx.
Oh.
I never was able to do that.
You learned that from Curly Howard, right?
The Three Stooges?
No.
He'd click his neck like that and make that little noise.
No, that's not where I learned it.
I have never seen anyone do that before.
I'm sorry the radio audience don't see Dr. Sinister.
Dr. Sinister just played his neck and head.
Every subgenius has a certain superpower.
A useless superpower.
And now we know Dr. Sinister's useless superpower.
One of my useless superpowers, yes.
He can do that.
We're all gifted with a useless superpower.
It's like the people who have the memories,
like they can remember like 3,000 digits in a row
after one second of seeing it in perfect order.
They used to call them idiot savages.
Yeah.
But yeah, every subgenius has some power like that.
My daughter, for instance, could send a fax through a phone line
just using her voice.
Like that.
And it would come out the way she wanted.
My superpower is I can type really fast with just two fingers.
My useless superpower is I have super belching skills.
No way.
Really?
Yeah.
My other niece has that power.
Oh.
I taught it to her.
I can do it on command, but it's not very good on command.
Do it, do it, do it.
It's better if you have beer.
You can't tell which one of us is doing it.
I can do that all day.
All day long.
Well, hang on.
You can't come to that skill because it gets weaker with age.
No, I thought you were going to say it becomes more valuable as you eat.
You inhale into your stomach and then they won't come out.
Oh, no.
Yeah.
You don't want that to happen.
So you can't have food or drink in here.
If I had a beer in here, I could really show you guys.
Oh, yeah.
My skills.
My niece, the only goth in Stangville, Texas,
she actually would sit in school.
She would emit these giant belches just to be disruptive.
And she told the teacher that it was a condition she had.
A disorder.
Yeah.
My sister went to open house or something.
And the teacher goes, oh, you know, she's doing very well despite her condition.
My sister goes, what?
Of course, the kid leaves the room real fast because she's about to get busted.
Well, you're not hurting him.
If I know my sister, though, she's not hurting him.
She probably backed her up and said, oh, yeah, it's really sad.
She just can't stop burping really loud.
Can you, honey?
No.
Burping Tourette's.
Yeah.
Right.
She hadn't convinced her it was involuntary.
No, it's not involuntary.
It's a cute thing they learn from their pappies or their uncles.
And they do it and they walk.
And when they see him, it's a funny thing to do.
Oh, yeah.
And they burp back and forth to each other.
And their mothers and fathers are the real people who count in their existence.
Come out and they start beating the hell out of them with these big sharpened sticks.
Like, you know, the Pound Gang and those different tribes in Melanesia and so forth.
In my family, it's all the women that can burp really well, actually.
Hmm.
I didn't learn it from my uncle.
I learned it from my aunt, who's about my size.
You learned it from your aunt?
She's like 110 pounds.
And we both just burp like disgusting old rednecks.
Oh, my God.
Goddamn.
See, that one got stuck.
Can you make it through the whole alphabet?
Yes, but it's really boring.
Can you make it through the Greek alphabet, too?
I don't remember it anymore.
Alpha.
There you go.
Hey, that's good.
I memorized it when I was a kid so I could write secret notes to my friends, except for none of them memorized it.
So it didn't work.
Isn't that the worst?
When you're smart enough to come up with secret codes to write messages to your friends,
but you don't have any friends.
You have to send them messages, too.
They wouldn't learn it.
I tried.
My daughter went to an elementary school that was half deaf kids, and everybody learned American Sign Language.
I thought that was normal.
When I was a mother and father, my daughter and her kids would sit there and talk about us.
They'd be naughty silently to each other.
I don't know that.
I just learned the alphabet.
I had to wear a pig mask when they were making me do their all-day drills.
And stuff like that.
Well, Dave, you were special.
Yeah, I certainly...
I think they had a pig mask last night.
Well, we lost him.
I did.
He'll be back.
Now we need pig man to call in.
That pig mask is pretty terrifying, actually.
It is.
I don't even like looking at myself in the mirror.
Whatever happened to pig man?
Whatever indeed.
He used a blowtorch to burn the hair off of a hog carcass.
Pig man.
Pig man did.
I just love the way pig man talked.
You hear him on station.
Listen to the 50,000 pound monster in my pants.
WCSB.
I love you.
I love you, pig man.
This is a fake pig man.
When I'm out slinging mud, I listen to 89.3 WCSB.
Cleveland.
Praise pig man.
Even the fake pig man.
And praise fake pig man.
That was the fake pig man?
The second one was the fake pig man.
I could do a better pig man than that.
So is that just his on-air voice?
Or did he sound that all the time?
The problem is if he talks like that, he gets stuck that way.
No, he doesn't.
Did he talk like that all the time?
Or was that an on-air voice?
I think that was the way the guy talked.
Was it like a Wolfman Jack thing?
No.
It wasn't Wolfman.
It was pig man.
No, lots of people talk that way.
If they're pig men.
No, that's a monster movie we haven't seen much of.
Pig men.
Definitely the tastiest monsters ever.
I had an attractive four-teated pig woman who kind of makes out with Val Kilmer in one scene briefly.
He's giving her drugs and kind of taking on her little, what you call, trotters.
And, oh, she's hideous.
You can almost smell her.
Makeup jobs are good in that movie.
Island of Dr. Moreau.
You know, the funny thing is Val Kilmer now looks like one of those actors.
He's one of the most animal people in real life.
I haven't seen him in forever.
Because of plastic surgery?
No.
I don't think I've seen him since he was Batman.
Right.
He has a...
He had to stop acting after that.
They revoked his license.
They pulled him out of the guild.
They were like, nope.
No more.
Michael Keaton played Batman in that first Tim Burton movie.
And he's kind of...
There's a new...
He's way too old.
Too short to be Batman.
I just read about today that...
It doesn't matter how short you are in the movies.
Look at Tom Cruise.
He's really four feet tall.
Yeah, he's as tall as me.
There's a...
Yeah, there's a new movie where Michael Keaton plays a has-been actor who once played Birdman.
A superhero named Birdman.
That must be so hard for him to get into character.
The Onion thought he did a great job and kind of rescued his career by acknowledging
that he was, in fact, a washed-up guy who once played a superhero.
A lot of people are doing that.
John Clive Van Damme did that with JCVD.
You know what?
Actually, yeah.
Okay, so Michael Keaton was too short to play Batman, but you know what?
Hugh Jackman is too tall to play Wolverine.
That is accurate.
Way too tall.
Also...
Well, I don't even want to go into that.
Wolverine is a small guy in the comics?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Small and very hairy.
I quit reading X-Men after they went...
I don't know if I'm above 10 cents.
I don't know that you're really missing much.
Wolverine had not appeared when I quit reading X-Men.
The Beast was the closest thing to that.
I love Beast.
Your parents' generation came up during the Golden Age of comics, and your generation
came up during the Silver Age of comics.
My generation came up during the Lead Age of comics.
Wah, wah.
Yeah, that one went over like a lead comic book.
I led you right to the slaughter.
I liked...
I liked Michael Keaton as Batman.
Honestly, if I had to pick a favorite Batman of all the movie Batmans, I think I would
pick Michael Keaton.
I got sick of the Christian Bale thing really fast.
I couldn't handle the voice.
Michael Keaton could have played a great Joker, actually.
He could have played the Joker just as well, I think.
That's true.
And it's not that I didn't like...
I didn't like...
You know, it's not that I didn't like Jack Nicholson's performance.
It was just...
It was a different kind of Joker.
Oh, I didn't like it.
There's different kinds of Jokers.
That might be true.
That movie had a lot of problems.
I liked it when it first came out.
And I thought Michael Keaton did a real good job as Batman.
But that whole series of Batman movies kind of don't...
They don't hold up for me.
No.
I really like the Christopher Nolan ones.
Christian Bale notwithstanding.
He's fine as Bruce Wayne.
I mean, he's okay as playing the suave...
Well, he has to change his voice to be Batman.
Oh, God.
It's so obnoxious, though.
Well, it's kind of like...
It's a Clint Eastwood voice, really.
Who are you working for?
Yeah.
Swear to me.
Hockey pants.
He says that.
That's a line in the second one.
That's when you know that they just...
I like the way Bane talks.
They just didn't care any...
Oh, Bane.
Oh, God.
I love the Bane voice.
Yeah.
What's funny is in the movie, he had a British accent.
And in the comic books, he has a Cuban accent.
Yeah.
He was actually like a luchador in the comic books.
He was of Hispanic descent.
But I really like...
I like his silly accent in the movie.
Although, only three-fourths of that movie is good in the second quarter.
I disavow.
And I won't like it.
I just can't.
I hate it.
But everything with Bane is great.
Well, and I guess Superman versus Batman is coming up.
I was born in the darkness.
You do a pretty good Bane for a very small person.
I'm trying to remember my favorite Bane quote, and I can't even...
I wondered what would break first, your spirit or your body?
It would be extremely painful for you.
What would happen if I turned that...
Poured that mask off your face?
It would be most painful for you.
Yeah.
Do you feel in control?
Wow.
We are making some...
Some great radio, aren't we?
Yeah.
Well, it's...
Bane impressions.
Nerd radio.
This is...
We're scraping the bottom of the nerd barrel now.
Oh, give me a break.
That's all people talk about is movies and TV shows.
This is probably the most interesting thing they've ever heard us say on this stage, because
we're talking about some movie they've all seen, instead of the usual obscure stuff that
nobody knows what the hell.
But what they...
Go ahead.
No, you kind of...
No, I'm saying?
No, no.
No, she's saying.
No, I'm saying?
No?
No.
Maybe we just found the secret to marketability.
We now have 40 listeners instead of 39.
Ooh.
See?
I'm telling you.
You talk about movies and comic books, and that's all anybody's interested in.
Now, I...
Speaking of the golden...
Well, silver age of comic books, I did honestly quit buying comic books when they hit, like,
40 cents, and they kind of sucked anyway.
It was all ads.
Well, yeah, it happened at the same time as the oil shocks.
You know, suddenly gas went to a dollar a gallon, and suddenly comic books are 40 cents.
Well, I came upon a huge stash of comic books, of old comic books lately, and I cleaned
them up and started reading them.
And, well, they came from the late Jeff Rosenbaum's collection, and they were just laying around
a store that we just cleaned out, and there was a lot of 1980s Marvel and DC.
I never used to read DC, because I thought they were for girls, to put it, you know.
Hey.
I don't know how else to put it.
And...
You mean, like, for boy scouts?
So I've been reading a bunch of those real quickly, and Superman comic books, and they
are messed up.
They are tripping ball.
They are...
Tripping the life fantastic.
Yeah, they're silly and dumb, and they are...
But they were obviously trying for real heavy, mind-blowing sci-fi concepts, but the writers
weren't exactly up for it.
So they're just triply idiotic, which isn't necessarily bad.
I've been really enjoying them.
Almost all of them have Superman...
God, the...
Superman and Superboy trade brains, because one was flying from the future to the past,
and one was flying to the past to the future, and they bumped heads.
Okay.
And suddenly, Superboy is in 1980s Metropolis, and Lois Lane's wondering why he's not interested
in her.
And he's panting over the grown-up Lana Lang, who was his girlfriend back when he was a
teenager.
Meanwhile, God only knows what the grown-up Superman is getting away with back in Smallville,
an adult Kryptonian mind in a teenage Kryptonian body.
I have to imagine that Superman must be a hard...
It must be hard to write stories for Superman, because he's Superman.
Like, what's the challenge for him?
How do you...
Sneak the Kryptonite in.
Exactly.
That's what about half of them were about, sneaking the Kryptonite into the story one
way or another, or some long-lost Kryptonian that wasn't destroyed with the planet, and...
Yeah.
And I've heard role-playing game fans say before that, you know, if you're running a
campaign where your characters are all at too high a level, then it just ruins the game.
Right.
I'm a fan of Superman as the disapproving father of the Justice League, who's constantly wagging
his finger at everybody who is...
Isn't doing what he wants them to do.
That's all after my time.
Justice League.
That's like the bad company of comic books.
Super group.
The only thing that really...
Well, I shouldn't say the only thing.
That's one of the things that bothers me about the Justice League, especially the animated
stuff, is that it's always Batman saving the day, and it makes me furious.
You have, like, Hawkgirl and Martian Manhunter, who are awesome, and you have one of them
getting thrown into the other one helplessly.
And they, like, knock down, like, you might as well just have, like, a bowling pin sound
effect.
Like, oh, they can't do anything.
And then all of a sudden, Batman swoops in and saves both of them.
The one guy without superpowers.
Yep.
And he's saving Hawkgirl.
This is an example of how the 1% are taking over.
Is it racism and sexism?
All the veterans go to the rich.
Martian Manhunter.
This is discrimination against Martians.
Yeah.
He has cool powers.
Well, you can't trust a Martian, you know.
Whoa, hey.
Hey.
I'm sorry.
I'm, like, 116th Martian on my grandma's side.
Well, we're all Martians.
I'm a Martian octagon.
According to subgenus doctrine, because this planet is Mars, and they switched place with
the one that used to be called Mars.
Well, it gets pretty complicated, but they used World War II as a cover for the planetary
switching, because they used up the first Earth and turned it into a lifeless planet.
And they brought the first one out from the sun, and they brought the pristine, original
Mars to this orbit, and started all over again.
Is the messed up Earth being cleaned up by all the cute little wallies?
No.
Well, then I don't like this fantasy.
No, there's just two, those two robots are crawling around on the surface.
I guess they're about to be joined by a robot from India or something.
Yeah, there's not many people left on the original Earth, which we now call Mars.
Even the robots are getting outsourced to India.
You know, there's babies inside those robots, and they're probably about five years old
by now.
In fact, I wonder if they've met.
The idea was they put these two fetuses in those, I don't know, the spirit and the, I
can't remember the name of the other robot, but there were fetuses in those who were literally
born on Mars.
And the idea is to get them adjusted to the thin, thin atmosphere, and then let them,
there's, one's a male and one's a female, and then let them meet.
It'd be like that movie Blue Lagoon, where these two kids grow up in an alarm with no
adults in a, you know, an isolated place.
You just referenced a movie that's like older than 25 years old, so we're going to start
losing listeners now.
Thanks.
You, um, you underestimate the average age of our listeners.
You might be.
You're the youngest person in the world who listens to the radio.
That's not true.
I'm exaggerating.
Yeah, she doesn't listen to the radio.
She listens to the download podcast.
I listen to the podcast on the internet.
Right.
Who listens to the radio?
I mean, if I had, if this station came through in Columbus, I would listen.
In fact, we're probably being heard in Germany right now.
Hi, Bucky.
Hi, Tanya.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Their flags are still on the machine.
They are.
This is, this is not, not exactly prime time for them.
I think, what, it must be like 14.
I think it's like 14 in the morning over there or something.
They have hours.
They have their all-night marathons at times.
Yeah, they very often sit up and lift up.
Rob, they, I mean, that other guy.
They were gonna, they're big fans of this show.
We know they're up real late.
Yes.
Or up first.
There's no accounting for taste.
Obviously, we know they're brain damaged and some kind of messed up hippies because they
listen to Hour of Slack and Radio Sinistria and all the other shows on WSB.
They're even worse.
Some of them.
I was totally normal until I started listening to these shows.
Messed me all up, man.
Yeah.
Right.
Sure.
That's real convincing, baby.
That's what I'm gonna tell the jury anyway.
No, actually, my WCSB story is like I came for the Spanish language stuff and I stayed
for the death metal.
Yeah.
That's a good description.
That is a good description.
Sounds good to me.
I'm gonna go ahead and do the next one.
Okay.
I don't actually listen to much of anything on the radio anymore.
Actually, it's really ironic now that I've lost my conspiracy job, I can't listen to
any of my radio shows like I used to.
All right.
Because I would just sit there all day and listen to the most weird subversive stuff
and all my coworkers would pass by me and I'd feel like I had some secret where it's
just like, you don't know.
You don't know.
Now that that's gone, I don't have the time.
It could be worse.
What if you worked for subgenius foundation?
No.
You'd have to listen to this stupid radio show.
It's not something you do to escape your job and cheat the boss.
It's something you have to do for your job because the boss said so.
It's a nightmarish hellscape.
I don't want to go there.
Yeah.
That's exactly right.
Don't make me look at Bob anymore.
I'm tired of it.
Get this.
I'll have to listen back to every word of this show.
It's some of the best I've ever heard in the previous hour.
You have to.
That's part of my job.
If I listen back to it, I even make notes on them.
I have these handwritten logs of what, in case anybody says something funny, that I
could copy, cop and use again, and I do.
Hey, a funny thought occurred to me today.
I was at a diner having breakfast today and I see the packet of Sweet and Low and I realized
there's a treble clef on there and if it's Sweet and Low, there should be a bass clef
on there.
That occurred to me today.
Does it sound like that?
idle minds are the devil's playground exactly
yeah listener are you one of those people who has to read every bit of print that appears in
front of your eyes compulsively like an ocd idiot sometimes i said listeners not talkers
i'm listening to it's compulsive it doesn't work if it's sometimes i don't know how many times i've
read this sign saying no food or drink in main air just in the last half hour when there's nothing
else to look at there's at least writing you can you can read the writing on the wall right or the
label of the ketchup bottle yeah whenever i ate cereal when i was a kid i would always leave the
box out because i would just read the box over and over again a lot of that's pretty mysterious
to a kid yeah and what is that it prompted me to learn what uh they put what's pat pending all that
weird stuff
you
A.I.
it prompted me to learn what all those words were like thiamine mononitrate and bhc
well some people get curious and learn and others just kind of go well i don't know what that means
oh well that was me hmm oh well i'm somewhere in between there i got a kook letter once from
a person who had discovered the meaning of those little c's in a circle that you see on
cds and record albums and little tms
and this c.c. meant it was against jesus and the tm I forget how it meant it was satanic but
it had something to with satan and the illuminati
yes this person had
never i mean i guess they assumed that no one knew what the copyright or trademark or registered
symbols were so it was up to him to deduce this because obviously it must be nefarious or evil if it
It was, you know, something that was for sale.
Maybe TM stood for the mark.
I've got a good one for you, actually.
There was a guy who called in.
Trey Mark.
I got one for you.
There was a guy who called in a few years ago asking the question, why is Texas the king?
Why is Texas the king?
I'm going to pass around this dollar bill until you hear it.
Okay.
Why is Texas the king?
See the K on there?
On that dollar bill?
Uh, yes.
Okay.
Yeah.
See.
Read more closely.
Federal Reserve Bank of Dallas, Texas.
That's where it was issued.
I just happened to, I just had a bunch of singles in my pocket and one of them just coincidentally had to have the K on it.
Why is, why is Texas the king?
This guy called up asking.
Because he thought there was some kind of a...
He deduced the code on the dollar bill.
Yes, he deduced the code on the dollar bill.
Okay.
It's, it's because...
I don't know.
It's because there's a, there's a black seal with the letter K in the middle and it says Dallas, Texas on there.
And like, if you're playing, if you have playing, if you have playing cards, K is king.
Well, yeah, but K's a lot of things.
K can mean a lot of things.
Yes, indeed.
So I told him that actually it's because there's 12 Federal Reserve districts and they're alphabetical and Dallas is the 11th district.
No, that dollar's not for you, Sting.
Every dollar isn't for you.
I'm looking at my own dollar.
But then the next thing that came up is I said, well, why?
Well, you know, L is San Francisco.
That's the 12th Fed district.
Because L is the same as the recolateral lambda.
And lambda is the symbol for gay rights.
Right.
It's like, you can, if you're, if you're delusional enough, you can make any of this stuff up.
And when you hear one person say something crazy like that, then it's easy to come up with something crazy in response to it.
And it's the, it's the frat from Revenge of the Nerds.
Lambda, lambda, lambda.
That's it.
Wow.
That's between my time.
I don't know why I remember that.
Too bad Mr. Sister isn't here.
He could make jokes about the Federal Reserve.
He was forcing me to watch the Catholic Channel on his TV.
I used to watch the Catholic Channel when I was younger.
Well, as his son watches that, actually, that's his son, that's, uh, he, he associates that with his late mom.
That's a scary channel.
To him, that's, uh, his... Okay, see, see.
That's a channel from heaven.
You just made it, you made it not, not funny.
I'm just trying to make a joke.
You know how many, uh...
I mean, you just ruin it with all this reality.
Hey, you know how many, uh...
It's a shared reality.
You know how many Catholics it takes to change a light bulb?
No, how many Catholics does it take to change a light bulb?
Three.
But they're really one.
Ah.
Or Trinitarians in general.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Now you understand.
The mystery has been solved.
I wanna cause, but...
We have not solved the mystery of how many Catholics it takes to change a light bulb.
Oh, I still have a radio show, though.
That's one mystery we haven't solved.
I made up a joke that I won a prize on a radio station for.
It was how many subgeniuses does it take to screw in a light bulb?
And the answer was like 982,082.
982,080 to build the mass clustering shrinking device and two to climb inside the light bulb.
And...
Yes.
Got that problem.
That was...
Classic.
I actually got a joke, a little prize on that, except that somebody else told it and
they got the prize.
Oh.
And that's why Buck Naked is not in the Church of the Subgenius anymore.
Hey, we've got a new caller.
He took credit for my joke.
We've been told.
On the other hand, he coined the term devival, not that I ever was that fond of it.
And I think he invented the short duration marriage.
Hmm.
And he named the Hour of Slack.
It was originally a little newsletter that he used to send out.
Yeah.
And then when I got a show, I called it the Hour of Slack and he thought that automatically
made him a co-host.
Well, let's not forget the fact that the whole story of Bob Dobbs...
That lasted for the first 30 shows and that was it.
Hmm.
Let's not forget that the whole story of Bob Dobbs was stolen.
The story of Bob Dobbs was stolen?
Oh, yeah.
Well, what wasn't of Bob?
Everything Bob has was stolen, some way or another.
See.
See, Bob is the kind of guy who can steal from you and make you feel good about it.
I mean, he can do that.
He can do that.
Well, I always...
My experience with Bob, which has been mostly indirect, thank goodness, is that he steals
from you and makes you feel like you were so smart to pull one over on him like that.
Exactly.
Everybody goes away feeling happy about the whole thing, but Bob is way richer and you're
way poorer.
Yeah.
You know, I am not one to say praise Bob.
I am one to say kill Bob.
Well, you kind of have to do both.
You can't say kill Bob until you praise him in the first place.
Why would you care about killing him if he wasn't somebody you had originally thought
of as being praiseworthy and then got disappointed?
You let me down, man.
Boy, have I heard that enough times.
I used to practically worship you, man, but you let me down.
Some people get their slank from mayhem.
I'm sure you've encountered a few of those.
Some men just want to watch the world burn.
I'd rather be slaying great jazz.
I'd rather be slaying the Aggies.
Yeah, I understand that.
And, uh...
And, indeed.
Yeah.
Yes, and, and, and, and.
And, and, and, and.
In fact, we could just go home and do that.
You could go home and and?
Yes, we could go home and and.
Well, we wanted to give Baby Bear a tour of the Slacker Mansion before she has to leave
town.
She's not staying at our house.
You're gonna make me watch you play?
You're gonna play Monster Hunter?
No, I'm not gonna do that.
I'm not gonna do that.
I don't want to be a part of your sick fetish.
No, no, I understand.
I'm not going to, yeah, and I'm not gonna, I'm not gonna let you show me how to finish
Portal either.
Oh, why not?
You haven't yet?
What?
Of course.
I played halfway through Portal.
Well, you haven't finished it, I mean.
No, I literally got about halfway through.
It was 17 or something like that.
Dang.
It was too tricky.
I couldn't, it took, it made my head hurt.
Use the internet.
I did.
Oh, okay.
It was still, it was still too tricky.
I used the internet for, I have cheat sheets for all the main games that came out in 2013,
because I have most of those games, used.
It's just puzzle, it's a puzzle game.
I know.
Hurts my head.
The whole life is a puzzle.
That's why I didn't play video games until the last three years.
The Spanish word for puzzle is head breaker.
Right.
.
The life is enough of a puzzle.
I just want, I'm into the ones that are just pure, mindless, reflexive.
I just want to get rid of the reflex and make you feel like you've been hitting things
for a long time and finally they die and carve them up, and that's it.
That's the whole thing.
It's like how hard are they to kill?
But the, like the writing and the setting and the, it's so good and it's so awesome.
Oh, I know, I know.
But well, Skyrim is really fun and interesting too.
I played that for a while.
Oh God, I couldn't stop.
But it's like full of soap operas and dialogue and humans and I'm trying to get away from
all that.
So go hang out with the, if you're sick of the humans, then go hang out with the Khajiit
and the Argonians.
Yeah.
I love the Khajiit.
The cat people.
Argonians are lizard people.
Ah, sweet moon, Skyrim.
I couldn't remember their names.
Jesus, this is horrible.
This is the nerd show.
It's a nerd out.
But you notice that at X Day, we do hour of slack on stage for like two hours.
Towards the end, it always degenerates into talk and it's like, oh, I'm going to die.
But by the end it's like there are no other videos that are but verses and things that
Like he knew by survive.
And then we would get over that.
Yeah, that's burning.
Have a good fundamental email address.
He's got his own shout out here.
Well, I love their content.
This can't be blocked.
Yeah, the out of size format has never been so strong and so matchable.
Right, like he said, I mean, that was ice high up.
The different levels here, it was pretty pesar não.
Plenty like that.
Don't get me wrong.
I think there have been Bento's jokes kissed something down there before.
Yeah.
It's a hell of a bento Job.
Oh, obviously.
Really?
It's only like 30 seconds.
Yeah.
I hear it right now.
Can't do it on the radio.
No.
That was why Bob lost, that was the one business that Bob did that he lost money on, Beer God and Burger God.
Burger God.
Both of them, because he used profanity in the ad, the main logo.
Like, I can't, even though we're in safe harbor, I'm trying not to utter certain words.
Technically, we're going to start our safe harbor for another three minutes.
Right, and that's when we're going to leave.
Right.
Because my last blank is out.
Can't you just auto bleep yourself?
I do, all the time.
So wait, in three minutes I can yell profanities?
Yeah.
Well.
Only if they have, okay.
Oh, there's a bunch of rules.
What's the rule?
The Miller test.
It would have to be, for it to count as obscenity, it would have to be appealing to the prurient interest.
It would have to be offensive to contemporary community standards.
And it would have to be completely lacking in any sort of artistic or literary or scientific merit.
It has to meet all three of those points for it to be considered obscenity.
Boy, that's his whole show.
Hey, I like to throw in educational and artistic and literary stuff from time to time.
Yeah.
Rules, man.
The merit of it is a subjective judgment.
That's your excuse.
Yeah, we all do that.
We all use that excuse.
That's right.
I'm an artist.
We just really like to hear the sound of ourselves.
Yeah.
On and on and on and on and on.
I didn't know that I liked to do that, but now that I've been on like 10 plus hours of show, it turns out that if you put a microphone in front of me, I'll just.
I'll just start talking to my own whatever.
Yeah, you'll have that.
Sad, but true.
Oh, well.
Now I'm addicted to show.
I'm sorry, listeners.
Now you know.
You guys got me addicted to show.
That's not nice.
Well.
Just bad subgeniuses.
The good thing is most people hate the sound of their own voice.
They're scared of talking in public and for good reason.
Well, yeah, sure.
And I'm glad.
Yeah.
But this.
We are not those kinds of people.
People.
Yeah, people.
Sure.
But this.
Well, I think that.
You know what the significance of that is?
That was the first comment on the Church of the Subgenius uttered by a caller on our first appearance on radio.
Yeah.
It's like the greatest thing that anyone could have said.
That was the first reaction.
Philo and I had been invited onto a talk show in Dallas and unexpectedly, I mean, we just sent the pamphlet out for the first time to public.
And we ended up on this talk show.
We had to come up with names, too, because we didn't want our human street names, you know, bad mouthing churches in Dallas, even indirectly.
And we were very indirect in those days.
But, yeah, the very first caller, after we'd been talking, being funny or whatever for a while, this guy calls in just.
I'm never going to listen to KPFA again.
Well, you don't think people should invent their own religion?
People.
Yeah, people.
Sure.
But this.
Oh, yes.
So we it's not like we fixate on criticism and repeat it over and over again.
But we do.
Well, I guess now that we're leaving, it can be revealed that this was not just nerd radio, but it was nude nerd radio.
Now, we don't have to go on about that.
I just thought I would mention that.
I haven't worn pants on the air in all the 11 years I've been doing the show.
So, yeah, you are listening to WCSB Cleveland 89.3 FM.
And this is synesthesia.
You have been listening to for the past hour.
I will be here till midnight.
But portions of the following broadcast will be objectionable to some members of the audience.
Therefore, WCSB advises listener discretion.
Views and opinions expressed on this program are not necessarily those of WCSB or Cleveland State University or anybody with their head screwed on straight for that matter.
Special thanks here to my guests in the studio tonight.
Reverend Stang, Princess Wee and Baby Bear.
Yay.
Isn't he slick the way he does that?
Uh-huh.
You'd think he's been doing it every week for 15 years.
Yeah.
You'd think he had no life at all.
You might be right.
Thank you.
Well, thank you.
The pleasure has been all mine, actually.
Praise Dr. Sinister.
You just took care of an hour of my two hours a week that I work on this.
So, thank you for doing half my job for me.
Wrecked my hour.
Our pleasure.