And now, the subgenius hour of SWACK!
I, Stang, am in a big, bobbly hurry,
and so tonight's show is a re-re-re-run,
but not of an hour of SLACK,
not even of a minute of SLACK, nay,
but rather of Bob's Slacktime Funhouse
from WREK Atlanta.
And not this time won by the good Reverend Susie the Floozy,
but a mental classic.
By her co-pod was the Lymph Node Institute.
You are listening to Bob's Slacktime Funhouse,
the Lymph Node Institute edition.
I'm Doc.
And...
I'm Bugsy.
We're going to discuss the brain this evening
in the interest of the magic dancing giants above us.
It's funny, because your brain will fill in gaps as needed,
especially when you're receiving everything through your earholes.
So if you hear any extra noises, it's just the...
it's the dancing giants.
The subliminal dancing giant.
We're not really, as far as you know,
hammering anything into your brain.
It's for your benefit, Atlanta and places beyond.
Your brain squishes.
little monkey man. Let's go.
Let's go.
Good evening, outpatients.
I know it has been some time since I've donned the blood-spattered lab coat of healing,
and it is possible that some of you listening have suffered mightily at the withdrawal of your coded programming.
Some of those not listening may be, in fact, deceased.
But let me make my position clear.
We don't need you anymore.
We're so deep in our endgame model that we don't have the time or resources to even look around,
much less worry about you.
We've got all the human pincushions we need since our rapture-has-passed recruiting drive.
I tell ya.
Global anxiety equals multiple international revenue streams.
But on to business.
One of the last remaining uneaten helper monkeys reminded me
of some damn thing.
I am funding technicality community outreach bullsh-
So, here we are, at or around the point.
Now, more than ever, your mind is a battleground.
The invading armies of normalcy have already dug in on the beachhead of your desire for acceptance,
which is, not coincidentally, perilously close to your slack reserves.
No, please.
I hear your protests.
I understand the reflex to automatically attest your rugged individualism.
But this is not a cigarette ad.
You damn well better take a passing interest in the opinions of others.
I should not have to remind you that our kind has a poor track record when it comes to frenzied pink mobs.
So, you desire that they accept you, at least to the point of keeping your guts off their pitchforks.
You know, all I have ever asked of you is one simple thing.
Make the simple decision that it is the world that is insane, not you.
Just acknowledge that somehow a system of techno-feudalism in which blind slaves squirm at the feet of sad, sadistic, repressed yetis clamoring for crumbs and passing up rumors on their farts
has somehow failed.
No problem, right?
Plain as the scabs on my nose, you say.
But, tomorrow, or the next day, you'll be back at the table, playing their comfortingly stupid shell game.
The world hovers on the edge of rebirth and I'll bet you still have a damn job,
still standing at the answer table in the back of their seedy opium den of lies.
Oh, don't get me wrong.
I'm not here to run the moneylenders out of the temple.
Just think of me as the guy in the next cell who won't stop whispering dangerous bull-dish through the cinderblocks.
But it's not because I'm trying to get you in trouble, although that would be funny.
I just don't want you to forget the present that history has bought for you.
See you in the Gulag.
Good night.
And now, the parts of the train, performed by...the train!
Yes.
Neocortex frontal lobe.
Brainstorm! Brainstorm!
Hippocampus neural node.
Right hemisphere.
Ponson cortex visual.
Brainstorm! Brainstorm!
Sylvian fissure pineal.
Left hemisphere.
Cerebellum left.
Cerebellum right.
Synapse hypothalamus.
Striatum dendrite.
Neocortex frontal lobe.
Axon fibers matter gray.
Brainstorm! Brainstorm!
Central tegmental pathway.
Temporal lobe.
White core matter.
Four brain cells.
Plexus! Plexus!
Central fissure chord spinal.
Parietal.
Piameter.
Meningeal vein.
Medulla longata and lobe limbic.
Microelectrodes.
Hormones.
The brain!
One is moral, one is not.
It's super ego and idbot.
Do you have any idea how frustrating it is to be a robot personification of the human id?
I never should have given you a penis.
That's what she said.
Oh idbot.
Well come on, let's sit down at this all you can eat buffet.
Oh boy, I want all of it. Now.
Now now idbot.
No, out of my way.
Only eat what you need.
Cuff you, you big queer.
Gluttony is a sin idbot.
And you're a pansy, get out of my way.
All things in moderation.
I gots to have it.
No you don't, you're a robot.
As a personification of the human id, I must have all of it.
I gots to have it, I gots to have it.
Gimme gimme, get out of my way.
You're incorrigible idbot.
That's it, I'm waiting in the car.
Get out of my way, other patrons.
Nom nom nom.
Nom nom nom nom.
One is moral, one is not.
It's super ego and idbot.
Did you read Brave New World by Aldous Huxley?
Laugh riot.
It's pretty funny for a book that's not supposed to be funny.
I mean, he was not a swift.
No, but orgy porgy until I started seeing a lot of rap videos.
Really struck me as comical.
Well they got the JC character in there and that wasn't so funny.
And the savage.
It's the same with 1984, there's always a heretic, a Satan figure.
Or Jesus, depending on which side you're looking at him from.
But me mum smoked when she was having me and I got okay with brackish amniocytic fluid.
But it wasn't quite poo poo.
No, in Brave New World they just deprived some of the oxygen of the fetus.
Yeah.
And it's amazing how that really stunts development.
Funny that.
Let's say things go Brave New World and they start doing all the alterations of fetuses to make sure they end up in certain positions in society.
Yes.
Because you know the society, the needs of the society are paramount to the society.
It really messes up the whole mother nature curve if you start dumbing down some and smartening up others.
I'm not the world's most intelligent guy.
Sometimes I just sit and wonder why.
It takes a lot of money and a telephone.
Rock me baby, rock me baby all night long.
On the mark I swear to get this thing done.
Rock me baby!
Someone save me!
Tell me something that I'm still good at.
Thank you earths 아주 use you.
Oh thank you.
Rock me babe.
It's so free and easy.
Yeah.
Fuck you little prick.
Rock me babe.
I forgot to tell her anything about the타慵 периnylЦیx tsé Northern evaluated
En inches sounds like you don't belong there, no mine?
What are you haking for?
I'm not the world's most incredible man
But I just can't seem to understand
If it weren't for all the people I'd be all alone
Rock me baby, rock me baby all night long
Bring us and we will not fade
Kill us and we will return
Drink us and we will not shun
Shock us and we will die
They were doing what I was doing
When lightning hit the street
A bar of soap, a pint of scope
Was all they'd had to eat
Look at there, some macaroni
Had happened to his hair
He had a shirt, but it was hurt
And sadness filled the air
Rock me baby, rock me baby all night long
Now I'm not the world's most incredible man
I never can quite seem to understand
If it weren't for all the people I'd be all alone
Rock me baby, rock me baby all night long
It takes a lot of money
I let you down
Teach em how to talk
Come on pretty baby
Rock, rock, rock
Yeah
One is moral, one is not
It's super ego and it bot
Ah, now for some fine adult entertainment
Remember, no touching
Cuff that noise, I gots to have it
It bot, I can't take you anywhere
You're embarrassing me in front of the ladies
Cuff you pansy, give me a dollar
Well, all I've got are these sack of joeas
Look at the ladies, I gots to have it
It bot, no!
Ladies, I have attachments
I have special attachments
Please, you have to respect these people
They're just working a job like anyone else
Cuff you, give me a ten spot
I wish I had a lap
Oh, I need to have a lap dance
It bot, retract that tentacle
Bouncer, you better step off
Excuse my friend, sir
He's a little bit of a robot
I'll drink all the liquor and have all the fun
I'll have all the booty in this sh-hole
It bot, moderate, you're embarrassing me
People are looking at us, the Japanese businessmen
Moderation is for pussies
Seriously, it bot, I can't take you anywhere
Ah ha ha ha ha, nom nom nom
It bot, that's murder
One is moral, one is not
It's super ego and it bot
Oh, you heard the disclaimer, you know the deal
If you, if you take any of this seriously
Then you have a real problem
Well, you sure are talking serious, doc
About all his cognition processes
Well, hell, I don't know
The brain is funny, too
Actually, the appreciation of humor
Probably is just as important as having the gullies of depression
So all you people who are leveled out, mostly
From the pills you take
You're missing most of the ride
Your rollercoaster's pretty straight
Hunter S. Thompson said that the first sign of insanity
Is the loss of the sense of humor
But what about people who never had one?
Born crazy
The bland, Blanco
The bland
Deaf, dumb, and bland
Hey now, momma, let's go downtown
Flyin' high and gettin' down
Gonzo, hyper, sirenade
Jump in the air and levitate
You are blurred, I hold on tight
Old damn town for rockin' life
Rockin' life, rockin' life
Blast your booty, bust a move
Marsh your mind and ride the groove
Do your part to make a wish
Let's all do the boogal fit
You are blurred
You are blurred, I hold on tight
Old damn town for rockin' life
Rockin' life, rockin' life
One thing except that
overlap
Rollin'
Inside, outside, outside, in
Right brain, left brain, let us spin
Cyber-Zoo and Shimmy-Jimmy
Party on down with Dr. Timmy
You want love, hold on tight
Hold on tight, we're rockin' tonight
Rockin' tonight, rockin' tonight
Music is a strange function of the human mind.
It's not necessarily a function of the mind.
The mind does determine patterns,
but when the music's presented, those are predetermined patterns.
You may interpret them differently,
but it's not like you're making music out of randomness.
You're being presented with patterns already.
But if you go back, I mean way back, to the advent of music,
one can only assume that it was organic sounds.
A couple of stone cavemen sitting somewhere listening to bugs.
Probably hitting rocks and skulls and sticks.
Yeah.
On the sand.
Sixth day of God time, the mastodon went away.
From far beyond the galaxies, I've journeyed to this place
to study the behavior patterns of the human race.
And I find them highly illogical.
Girl meets boy.
They fall in love.
She says he's everything she's dreamed of.
But when they get married, before he's aware,
she changes his habits, the way he combs his hair.
She changes him to someone he's never been,
and then complains he's not like other men.
Now really, I find this most illogical.
Take the case of your automobiles.
Greatest invention.
Since man discovered wheels.
High dramatic overdrive.
Floor on the floor.
Push button windows.
Push button doors.
Double barrel carburetors rush you any place.
But you never can find a parking space.
Highly illogical.
Take the case of modern man.
He works all his life.
Gives it all he can.
Saves all his money.
Works overtime.
Picks up a new car.
Inches every penny.
Banks every dime.
All he can think about is money.
But you know that he can't take it with him where he's going to go.
Now I find that fascinatingly illogical.
Now is the time to journey home.
To tell of what I've learned.
My people, I believe, have every right to be concerned.
For in spite of computers and advanced psychology,
behavior patterns are still a mystery.
I predict the future of this earthly human race
is that having made a mess of Earth,
they'll move to outer space.
Well, there goes the neighborhood.
Totally.
Completely.
Absolutely.
Irrevocably.
Highly illogical.
One is moral, one is not.
It's superego and it bought.
Ah, it bought.
It's been such a long time since I couldn't take you anywhere.
Remember when we first used to go to the candy shack
when we were young boys?
Shut your wet human mouth.
You're making me hungry.
I want sweets and I need them.
Yesterday.
That's exactly what you used to say.
Searching that great bay.
Hey, can I help youse?
Yes, I'd like a modicum of moderately priced chocolate.
Give me everything in the counter.
Open up the counter.
Move out of the way, old fellow.
I will have you from behind.
It bought.
No, you're embarrassing me in front of the old man.
I don't even know who you are.
Don't touch me.
What the hell is he doing?
Never mind my friend, sir.
He's a little excitable for the sugar.
But don't worry, he's a robot.
Put candy in my orifice now.
Put it in.
Nom, nom, nom, nom.
It bought wants more candy.
It bought.
No, that's his head.
Ah, yes, those were the days.
One is moral, one is not.
It's super ego and it bought.
We'll have to wait until the terrorists kidnap Ronald Reagan to do that.
What terrorists?
The terrorists.
What?
The terrorists that...
Don't you remember any of this, man?
No.
The terrorists that escaped from Guantanamo Bay, invaded the country, just like that
Chuck Norris movie, and then freaking kidnapped Ronald...
That hadn't happened yet.
It hasn't.
Well, he's Alzheimer's boy, so we can't very well ask him.
He's so retold.
Oh, I believe it.
He was Alzheimer's boy when he was in office.
No, I have read the script as it is going to be executed.
Right.
The terrorists will escape from Guantanamo and they will kidnap Ronald Reagan and I think
they do something terrible to the state of Texas.
I think Negative Land pulled off the whole time trials better.
Hell yes.
Let's play a little Negative Land.
They've done everything better than we have.
Fine.
Okay, fine.
Let's play some Negative Land.
Yes, let's.
You're the Pepsi generation.
Open it!
Pepsi, Pepsi today!
With a slurp, I can say Pepsi!
I don't know what else to say.
But I need a Pepsi, need a Pepsi, need a Pepsi today!
I need a Pepsi!
Right away!
Open it, I tell you!
I need a Pepsi!
Show my brand loyalty to feel good about me!
I don't know what else to say, but I need Pepsi!
Heads up, you need a Pepsi!
Heads up, you need a Pepsi today!
Heads up!
So I can play basketball!
I don't need Coca-Cola at all!
Show my brand loyalty to feel good about me!
I don't know what else to say!
Open it!
Pepsi, Pepsi, Pepsi, Pepsi today!
Pepsi, Pepsi today!
Pepsi, Pepsi, Pepsi today!
It's pretty good.
Easy!
I need Pepsi sometimes and I don't know why!
There's a voice inside my head that makes me go out and buy!
I need Pepsi!
I buy a Pepsi, buy a Pepsi, buy a Pepsi after drinking some beer!
Buy a Pepsi, buy a Pepsi, buy a Pepsi after eating a Pepsi!
Try me, I need Pepsi right away!
Pepsi now, I need a Pepsi, Pepsi now!
They might as well come right out with it!
All flavors have that Peppy potatoes and I don't know why!
Except Sarsaparilla.
There's a host inside my head that makes me go out and buy a allen that my mosque will
give me when I threatening to B boats, because I want to get it to the there and then get
Bushes on your trzeba!
There's a voice inside my head.
Now please don't misunderstand.
I need a Pepsi.
Our sarsaparilla is absolutely dependable.
I need a Pepsi today.
It's trustworthy.
It's loyal.
Right away.
And many fine, upstanding citizens love it.
Pepsi.
A really good mix.
I need a Pepsi.
But it just isn't what we call happy.
Pepsi.
A really good mix.
Pepsi today.
You take our orange.
It's absolutely rollicky.
Fountain Pepsi.
Our lemon is almost giggling.
Maybe a 12 ounce Pepsi.
Our black cherry and black raspberry are so bubbling with happiness, they dance in the
glass.
Maybe a 16 ounce Pepsi.
We're sorry about sarsaparilla.
Pepsi.
We're really happy.
Why isn't it happy?
Pet opener.
See?
There are illusions inside my head.
Pet opener.
See?
There are illusions inside my head.
Pet opener, I tell you.
See?
Well, let me ask you.
I don't like Coke or RC.
I only like Pepsi.
Or Mountain Dew is better.
With the cool, smooth Mountain Dew.
Pepsi, which makes Mountain Dew.
Yeah.
I love negative playing.
That was great.
It was.
Everything they do.
You know what they call it when they're starting a marketing campaign and the first wave is
just to get you to be aware that the product is out there?
Foreplay?
Basically.
It's called establishing a mindset.
Mindshare.
Isn't that a Queensryche album?
Operation Mindshare?
Operation Mindslime.
Operation Daddy Did Me.
Showload.
It's like Showboat, but loady.
Well, Jack, it's great to see you again.
Hey, thanks.
You folks, have you been making remarkable progress?
Yeah.
I hope the antidepressants have helped.
Yeah?
You look good.
Thanks.
You look real good.
Well, thanks.
I think we should start today's session with a little word association.
You know.
Actually, you do.
You've been remanded to my care by the courts.
Whatever.
So, just clear your mind.
Shouldn't be that hard to do.
I'd say the first thing that comes to mind.
Chocolate.
Let us begin.
Razor wire.
No, see, I will say the word you will respond to, and that's the association by which I'll
make judgments on how normal you are.
Fava bean.
No.
Razor wire.
Are you ready?
Wealthy.
Poor.
Octogenarian.
Octopus.
Pheromones.
My friend's got some ferrets.
They're funny.
Family values.
Family.
Funny ferrets.
Subwoofer.
Pass.
Authority figures.
Mom.
Dad.
Teachers.
Cops.
Ass.
Cryptophane.
Samba resume.
That is…
And I also!
And I also feel sorry.
You won't get away this simple.
Now, don't you know how much money you can earn if you do that?
I do.
I share the money with John, and I tiene millones in my pocket.
And the plastic's all melted and so is the chrome
Who are the brain police?
What will you do when the label comes up?
And the plastic's all melted and the chrome is too soft
Who are the brain police?
What will you do if the people you knew
Who are the plastic that melted and the chromium too?
Who are the brain police?
What will you do if the people you knew
Hormones squeeze in through your various sense organs.
They run through something called the hypothalamus, which is a little squirting gland in your brain.
The hypothalamus is kind of in charge of deciding what is important and what is not.
So it's like Charlie for your brain.
Yes, basically it is your brain's secretary.
It operates basically under four prerogatives, which is fight, flight, feed, and puff.
And if something you see is important to one of those four poles, I guess,
then the hypothalamus kind of gives a little extra squirt,
which is why you might drive off the road looking at some chickies behind
because your hypothalamus is chanting, well, you know.
Get you some. Get you some.
Get it, get it, get it.
And then when you look back to the road and you're about three feet from the bumper of the car in front of you,
that's when your hypothalamus once again kicks in with your fight or flight.
And there's really nothing you can do.
At the three seconds from the truck collision, then you get the whole flash before your eyes,
read the whole of your existence, which has to do with, I guess, the memory.
All your face for me, you love me so
Hold my head, hold my head
You want all I can, but my head, all my head
Is permanent damage
Hey!
You got this for me, sweet and fair
You got this for me, shit to impale
My head on my head, you are all I got
All my head on my head, my mind's going down
Head, head, head, head, head
Did you breathe?
You got this for me, sweet and fair
You got this for me, shit to impale
My head on my head, your words are like arrows
My head on my head, my mind's going down
You got this for me, it hits me hard
Head, you got this for me, you love me so
All my head on my head, you are all I got
All my head on my head, my mind's going down
Chicken, chicken, chicken, chicken
chicken, chicken, chicken, chicken
Head, head, head, head, head, head, head, hey, hey. If you strike me it'll roll in целк
We're all the same
20 eyes in my head
They're all the same
When you're feeling 20 things at a time
You just can't slow things down
When you're feeling 20 things in your mind
We're all the same
This is the crowding of your human face
20 eyes in my head
They're all the same
When you're feeling 20 things at a time
You just can't slow things down
When you're feeling 20 things in your mind
We're all the same
20 eyes in my head
They're all the same
When you're feeling 20 things at a time
20 eyes in my head
They're all the same
When you're feeling 20 things at a time
n
in my head
they're all the same
funny eyes
in my head
they're all
the same
we were going to talk about memory
well that's because your life flashed before your eyes
it seemed like an appropriate segue
yes
and memory is very important
because basically the memories of who you are
and what you've done
sort of make who you are
in the present
let's say you're reading a book that's like 5th in a series
I think you would enjoy the subtleties
of the main character you're supposed to relate to
much more if you'd already been with that character
on several other adventures
with different input
and if you're the character in your own story
which you really should be
then you're going to have a much more
rich existence one thinks
if you can relate everything that's currently happening
to what's happened in your past
but don't live in the past
because that's a Jethro Stoll song
that stangs job to play
Jethro Stoll
we don't do that
yeah so memory is important
when you lack memory
you start to lose your definition of who you are
I think
you look at these Alzheimer people
look at them
I don't want to
I know not a pretty sight
could happen to you
don't drink your cola out of cans kids
they say that
I guess you can't use deodorant either
with all that alum
that's what they say
that's what's said
you can't be what you were
so you're messed up being
just what you are
you can't be what you were
the time and now
is running out
is running running running out
you can't be what you were
so you better start living the life
that you're talking about
you can't be what you were
the normal man
and the new batman
is Patatge of Batman
the normal man
and the new batman
is Patatge of Batman
the normal man
The number man
Never ever
Take a bad
Mind
You're always talking, talking, talking, talking, talking this now
But you will talk yourself down
You're going down
One is moral, one is not
It's surreal
Super ego and idbot
Well idbot, here we are at yet another Woodstock
I smell cannabis
They are illegal and we wouldn't want to do anything wrong or get in trouble
Get out of my way, patrooli makes me crazy
I do what he says folks
I'm caught in the mud, help, I've got to get some of that sex, drugs and rock and roll
Well, maybe two out of three
If it's too loud then you are too old
Well it's not too loud, I've got my ear plugs in
You are such a pansy panty waste
You want me to do it?
I'm going to damage my hearing, that would make you happy
Why don't you hold that girl down while I set fire to this tower
No, we need that tower
For observation and filming
I like to watch, I like to watch
Give it to idbot
Idbot, no!
Let me at it, I gots to have it
Alright, you just retract those tentacles mister, we've got to get out of here, you've gotten us in trouble again
Woodstock, woo, party till you puke
That piece of paper I put in my mouth is making me feel awful funny
I love that J-Tab, I love that
Woah
One is moral, one is not, it's super ego and idbot
What's the difference between the mind and the brain? The brain is the organ and the mind is the part we like to think that we are
Is the mind the soul?
Probably, our consciousness and personality sure as hell don't live in the brain
If you want to test that, just give someone's brain a good whack and watch their personality change
You know, you wipe out one part of the brain and some other part of the brain
starts kicking in
I think the mind is like a modem, the brain itself is like the piece of equipment that we used to call a modem
A modulator demodulator
That's correct
It connects with the outside world
And not only does it connect with the outside world, but the whole part that makes it, I think, the seat of the soul is its connection to things that the rest of your senses can't really get at
And so you have to intuit
So what else does the mind really make you decide you need?
Clothes
Clothes, hey, actually, and again, if the mind is the seat of the soul, then all those big corporations trying to get you and get that mind share that we talked about
Are actually after your soul
Trying to redefine who you think you are so you give them money
It's amazing how people just sort of intuitively understand that companies are after their brains
Right
And that they don't seem to mind, but when you mention the soul, they pucker up
That's why we've got the invisible monster
He's the great Connie in the sky
One is moral, one is not, it's super ego and it bought
Well, it bought
Now that we're in Hawaii, I hope you don't choose to embarrass me here, too
Come on, get out of my way
I need to get out of here
I'm going to get laid
That wasn't funny at the airport either
Now, are you going to sit down and enjoy the luau or not?
You know very well that I can't sit
Are you making fun of me?
Don't put a chip on your shoulder there
Get it, chip robot
I think you are making fun of me
Of course I'm not, I'm just happy
I want the pig
The pig is for everyone, idbot
I will not share, the pig will be mine
I'm cutting you off, I'm sick of this, I can't take you anywhere
Move these damn foreigners out of my way
Move, move, move, move
Now idbot, this is a foreign country, we are all foreigners here
Now, now, now, now
That's it, this is the last time
You, me, edge of the volcano, now
Alright, super ego, have it your way
Just carry me safely to the left of the volcano
Meanwhile, at the top of the volcano
You have had this coming for years
Mom always liked you better, I'm sick of this
I'm a robot personification of your id
You made me vomit all over my prom date
You turned me into a cybernetic organism.
You made me gain 50 pounds when I broke my leg and started smoking pot!
Ahh!
Ah, you never lubricate me properly.
I built you!
You have a point.
I do.
Let's not fight.
No.
Ah, I tricked you!
Oh!
AHHHHHHHHH!
One is moral, one is not.
It's Super Ego and it's BOT!
Tonight the city is full of morgues
And all the toilets are overflowing
There's shopping malls coming out of the walls
As we walk out among the manure
And after a while
That's why
I pay no mind
Give the finger to the rock and roll singer
As you walk out among the morgues
He's dancing upon your paycheck
The sails climb high through the garbage pale sky
Like a giant dildo crushing the sun
That's why
I pay no mind
Sleep in slime
I just got signed
So get out your lead pipe pipe drains
Get out your ten foot flags
The insects are huge and the poison's all been used
And the drugs won't kill your day job honey
Honey
That's why
I pay no mind
I
pay no
mind
I
pay no
mind
I
pay no
mind
I
pay no
mind
I
pay no
mind
I
pay no
mind
If you'd like to learn more about the Church of the Subgenius,
drop them a load at P.O. Box 140306 Dallas, Texas 75214.
My dog, what are you waiting for?
Or just go to www.subgenius.com.
Another fine lymph node production!
Contact us at P.O. Box 670541 Marietta, Georgia 30066-0126
or www.alternategroove.com slash lymph node.
Listen to Bob's Slack Time Funhouse at WREK.org.
91.1 FM, WREK Atlanta.
Your brain has decoded the following audio stimuli in the following order.
Swelling Itching Brain by Devo.
The Mind Lecture by LNI.
Brain Stem by Pinky and the Brain.
Super Ego and Idbot at the All-You-Can-Eat Buffet by LNI.
The Butthole Surfers with Intelligent Guy.
Super Ego and Idbot at the Strip Club by LNI.
Fugu Fish by the very late Dr. Timothy Leary.
Leonard Nimoy with Highly Illogical.
Super Ego and Idbot at the Candy Store by LNI.
Voice Inside My Head by Negative Land.
The Old Word Association Skit by LNI.
Who Are the Brain Police by Frank Zappa.
And the...
Head Injury by Soundgarden.
20 Eyes by The Misfits.
Bad Mouth by Fugazi.
Super Ego and Idbot at Woodstock by LNI.
Super Ego and Idbot in Hawaii by the Lymph Node Institute.
Pay No Mind by Beck.
And in case you feel oddly empty this evening,
like there's something missing from this show,
then just lean back and listen.
To the dulcet tones of Queensryche.
Rockin' you live with Operation Mindcrime.
Oh Dallas, this is Operation Mindcrime.
Mindcrime.
Oh, it just takes a minute to feel the pain.
You gotta make something of your life.
Give me one more thing.
You've come to see that I'll never sell you the year.
I'm gonna take away the questions.
I'm gonna make you shine.
Yeah.
I wanna hit man for the order.
We're gonna go to school.
I had a skin shot for a head use.
Yeah, it looks pretty cool.
I had a, had a do it me night.
I don't want to drag this bird.
No request to God.
No, no, it's nothing for you.
Now I know you won't make me lose.
I know you won't.
Just give me so much to do.
We've been so far.
You've got to make more.
You've got to make me lose.
So take my hand for a hug.
I'm gonna make you shine.
This is Operation Mindcrime.
We were on the ground.
The revolution was in overtime.
Operation Mindcrime.
This is a job for you.
You're the sister of your God.
Just be the son.
I'm gonna make you shine.
Let's open up the good house.
Let me know if it's true.
Open it up now.
Open it up.
Open it all up.
Hey, hey, hey, you know everything
Now there is to do
Now here's my gun, oh
Take it home, we've got a phone
I'm gonna send someone over
Who's gonna give you what you need
You're a war man, death is easy
You gotta make me a city man
I don't know who you are, but you knew
Why do you want to steal?
So what is to do?
We've got so much to do
So take my number
So you have to reach it
My heart
We're gonna walk
Revolutionary
Love and time
Our world ain't just mine
It's a time of week
And a sister will cry
The fear is gone
Our world ain't just mine
We're gonna walk
Revolutionary
Love and time
Our world ain't just mine
You can probably see
The back of the eye
We're gonna walk
If you don't care
I've got a vision in my mind
You gotta make yourself a little alive
Let it sink to your mind
I've got a vision in my mind
It's a job for you
The system you've got
The thing
You've got a finger sign
You've got a fuerte
Get rid of all your fear
Then make good use of it
La, la, la, la...
Waiting, waiting on your...
What are the fears in a life
You gotta stop
Don't get lost
And you can have ausge
And break free
Screams
sobre los ojos
Don't let it concern yourself
Remember to think fast
Be sure that memory
No escaping
Remember to break free
I don't know.
Is that too far out?
Not for me, it's not.
One is moral, one is not.
It's super ego and it bought.
Mertz makes up your mind.
Take only as directed.
Bipolar curiosity.
Hyper-onanism.
Nerdism.
Blue balls.
OCD, OCD, OCD.
If so, you need Bob's Slacktime Funhouse.
Tune in at 1 a.m. Saturday night for your weekly inoculation.
And a dose of Bob's own medicine.
Bob's own medicine.
The preceding claims have not been certified by any reputable medical organization.
Bob's Slacktime Funhouse may cause smallpox, rash, discharge, recidivism, colorblindness, seizure, monobrowism, synchronicities,
Dobbs syndrome, caboose loosening, morning wood, rosetta stones,
dying buttresses, or death.
Your local subgenius radio ministry.
Bob's Slacktime Funhouse.
Saturday night at 1 a.m.
WREK Atlanta, 91.1 FM.