They're here!
One minute.
Ja, it is the hour of penultimate power before the awakening day.
Now it's the turn of the mind to adjourn,
and let that radio play.
The horrible, hideous torrent of noise
that occasionally mars our discourse,
though often a foe is quite often a friend
and scarcely a cause for remorse.
If you don't like our patented radio show
and object to its babbling din,
we respect your objection,
but why not, you know, change your habit of listening in?
The boings and the burps and the babies that cry
overwhelming our well-meaning show,
though always...
The nuisances are in great supply.
It seems we may never run low.
The temple of Bob is a back-breaking job.
It's more work than digging a ditch.
Though we have our supplies of gobofram and lies,
we smell tar and the sun on the pitch.
So I'll say this to Stang and the rest of his gang
and the collars that lurk in the dark.
Though the pace is uphill,
it still gives us a thrill.
So prepare one and all.
To embark.
Baba!
Welcome to Subgenius Radio Ministry.
Hour of Slack.
Sponsored by the Church of the Subgenius.
Out here, it's an incredibly different picture.
While you sit back at home listening to the radio show,
you can't imagine the terror.
These unfortunates are experiencing out here
at Ground Zero in the center of the show zone.
Huge mutant slugs lurch through the underbrush
as a damp, drizzly rain coats us all
with a mucilaginous, acidic slime.
Giant frogs bong like a thronging gong
in the swamp under us,
while slithering snakes depend from the trees,
sleazily sneezing on us snottily as we pass.
BONG!
Knee high in the damp grass.
registers shall vampires
This next record is dedicated to
some personal friends of mine.
registers shall vampires
dictionary
computers
For every cop that has ever taken advantage of somebody,
beat them down or hurt them because they got long hair,
listened to the wrong kind of music, wrong color,
whatever they thought was the reason to do it,
I'd like to take a pig out here in this parking lot and...
...convince you how badly we and the station need your support.
Uh, we have a special, special form of slack in store tonight.
Instead of us giving you slack for once,
you're gonna finally give some back to us.
Of course, some of you have been doing so all along.
Praise Bob.
But for the rest of you...
I'm a cop you love, better you than me.
Cop you love, but tonight we get even.
You love Bob, you have to.
Or else what happens if you don't love Bob?
He'll kill you.
So Bob you out.
Bob you out, folks.
You heard it here first.
You don't love Bob, you'll Bob you out.
Bob you out, baby.
Ah, yes, dear friends.
Only if...
Well, you know, if you don't pledge, there's gonna be more and more and more reverent stangs.
Too many.
Forever.
Can you imagine?
Dear friends.
We need that money.
My gosh.
Let's get us some spirit going here.
Look at those phones light up.
Every time somebody lies...
Oh, yes.
You like that old joke, friends?
Shake it off.
Can you imagine a world without slack?
A world without the hour of slack?
And even almost as bad, a world without...
Oh.
Bob Bob.
Bob.
Oh!
Oh.
Luver l aاف you need slack.
K nonsense your help.
Send in those pledges praise Bob.
Shh.
There's bat falls and I just want to say that I endorse barbers by running into Bob Bail lafaa
made in this year's election, and this is the Hour of Slack.
Hello, Bob, this is Father Guido Sarducci, formerly Pope Maurice of the People's Catholic
Church, and all of my fellow popes from the People's Catholic Church salute to the Church
of the Sabbath Genius.
Carry on.
Good.
This is Rand Hawkins.
And this is Stimson J. Catt of the Rand and Stimpy Show.
And you're listening to the Hour of Slack.
Keep listening, you idiots.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Else I shall kill you.
Captain, you're the man.
Yes, yes, go on.
I'm trying to understand.
Is this supposed to be your little show?
Is this supposed to be your little jainer over there?
Is this supposed to be your comedy there?
You're supposed to be funny there?
Ladies and gentlemen, it's been a slight change in the program.
Whoa, whoa.
Sorry.
You can have your money.
This is very confusing.
I don't think I understand this.
Oh, no, no, no.
Bob?
Where?
Oh, my God.
Oh, God.
I'm just...
If we let this go on now and everybody condones it, how long is it before everybody is stark naked?
Come on, Bob.
Tell us.
For what reason, Bob?
Tell us, Bob.
It's a mystery.
It's a mystery wrapped in a riddle inside an enigma.
And hear the word of the Lord.
And now here's the host of the PCP Club, Jimmy Baker.
Hi, and welcome to the PCP Club.
Boy, what a show we have tonight.
I want to get right to it.
First, I want to remind all of you listeners that our panel of trained counselors is here to help.
So if you have acid psychosis and need someone to talk to while you're coming down,
or if you have anything to sell, or if you want to buy something,
call the number on your screen.
We'll take your message or lend a listening ear.
1-800-788-7888.
Remember, the PCP Club stays on the air through your contributions.
So if you want to keep the PCP Club on the air,
send your money or merchandise to the PCP Club in care of this station.
Well, let's get on with the show.
And our first guest, Mark Lane.
How are you doing tonight, Mark?
Just fine.
That's very good.
Mark, you have a fabulous story to tell.
I guess like most of us at one time or another,
although we're all ashamed to admit it,
you were an all-American boy before you degenerated into the drug field
and thoroughly.
And I'm sure you're in a very happy state you're in today.
Yeah, that's right, Jim.
And let me say that I feel sorry for people who are like what I once was.
They don't know what it's like not knowing if you're going to wake up in bed
or if you do wake up feeling like a useless blob of jello.
They just don't know the true meaning of life.
I've had so much pleasure waking up and knowing that I couldn't feel worse all day.
Isn't that amazing?
Absolutely amazing.
I've heard it said many ways, but that just about wraps it all up.
Well, I guess everybody's anxious to hear your story.
Mark, sir, why don't you tell it?
Okay.
Well, I was president of my fraternity.
I'd just finished my junior year with a 2.94 GPA.
Our fraternity basketball team and baseball team were first in their league in the past two years.
Things couldn't have been better, yet my life wasn't complete.
Something was missing.
Reality was becoming oblique, and my world was falling apart piece by piece.
I hungered for peace and happiness.
The Moody Blues performed with a great force,
and I was a powerful debt at our house one night.
The band members were all smiling.
I wanted to smile like that, too.
After the concert, a few of the band members shared their experience of peace and happiness with me.
Later that evening, we went to the marijuana house to talk.
They told me the words of Edgar Cayce, Hunter Thompson, Timothy Leary, and Carlos Castaneda,
and the powers of Mescalito.
It was then that I first chewed my first button of peyote.
Then, in a beam of light, I saw Mescalito.
He told me he wanted me to devote my entire life to seeking his ways of knowledge.
I crashed.
I woke up three days later in Toledo.
Man, I was happy.
After working two weeks in a restaurant to get enough money for a bus ticket back to Auburn,
I joined the marijuana house.
Since then, I have sought the ways of Mescalito's knowledge every night.
I now see that there is hope for the world.
Through the marijuana house, I have become closer to the physical joining with Mescalito.
My life is satisfied.
I am happy.
Amen.
Can we get an amen?
I'm just stoned out.
Thank you for coming on the show tonight, Mark, and sharing such a wonderful testimony with us.
We'll be right back with more of the PCP Club after this message.
Hello, this is Timothy Leary, reminding you that just as you need slack, KNON needs your help.
Send in those pledges and praise God.
We'll be right back.
Mark, Mark, Mark, Mark, Mark.
As you can hear in the background, the zombies are chanting for slack.
We need slack.
The station needs slack, friends.
Because they'll just go ahead and do whatever it is that they have in mind to do.
Well, that's just what we were afraid of.
What are you going to do, borrow whatever each or something?
No, I just expect you to listen.
I don't expect you to take it like a man and stop whimpering and whining.
I don't expect you to do anything.
You're not expected to do anything, that's all.
This show was made for talking, and that's what we're going to do.
One of these days, our doctor is going to show all over you.
Too late, son. That's past paying for.
Even the audience doesn't know that they should be awake at this time.
If they could take a three-dimensional rendering of the rings of Saturn and play it on a record player, what would it sound like?
It would sound like this show, young man.
Oh, oh.
Yes, please, there are listeners so unhip that he to himself could never quip.
This is my own subgenius show.
Bob's word for those who are in the know.
The church that moves by fits and hunches.
The powerhouse church that pulls no punches.
Let him who denieth this be passed beyond the reach of our broadcast and heaved upon a hill of dung.
Unwet, unhonored, and unsung.
I don't expect you to understand anything. I'm just trying, that's all.
You're not supposed to understand your silly twits.
Words, words, words, words are the key. I talk to you, you talk to me.
Oh, ho, ho, ho.
All right, all right, that's, uh...
Oh, you're listening to the subgenius show.
Okay, 8484425ers, get set to call the subgeniuses.
That's right, you can talk to some of the real people behind the Bob Dobbs.
Okay, now, why are you awake and listening to this show?
We follow the show.
Call the show, call the show.
Okay, we'll go away and you be the show.
Okay.
Yeah, the love show. We love everybody. We love you callers.
May I have your order, please?
We'll take Visa, we'll take MasterCard, we'll take American Express, we'll take bank drafts.
By which monthly payments are automatically withdrawn from your bank account.
You can call in tonight, set it up, you'll never have to think again.
And of course, a check or money order is always so much fun.
Work your magic twanger, froggy.
Higher, kid, higher, higher.
Yes, sir, Rudy Ritter's. This is Rudy Cazooty.
And so you notice how that plastic is lightly tinted?
That makes it much easier to watch our television show, even for your parents.
Okay, Ellen, see you a little later.
To help carry on our important work, I want you to join the Secret Squadron
and wear this official badge.
And have this secret decoder.
Okay.
Now.
We're going to sing some sump, Canyonne songs for you.
Bob days, Bob days, and a king and a win.
No.
Today, today, Bob, Bob, Bob.
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
I must not fear. Fear is the mind killer. Fear is the little death which brings me.
My dear friends, what's happening in your life?
Big pain?
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
Knows how Bob Dogs work?
It's a Bob world after all.
It's a Bob K-I-N-O-N.
This is for somebody.
Genius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
With a little car.
Hello, Rita Car.
It's about time you answer the phone, you f***head.
It's about time you did answer the phone, you f***head.
Hello, we're on the air.
Good morning, doctor.
Good morning.
In with a car, I think.
I mean, I need help now.
What sort of help can we bring you?
I'm suffering from a severe case of electronicus interruptus.
You mean, time-fettered signal.
Every time I begin a conversation with somebody on the phone,
especially a doctor that I need advice from,
the situation is, the power fails, and then I'm left...
Oh, yes, what is it?
Is Dr. Daniel Moore there? Dr. Hale?
I was trying to give a lecture on the practice of internment
for hydrotipia in the many nations of the Earth.
And Rosa, you interrupted me
with your poor aisle puddle of...
Oh, oh, sure.
What short rates, what?
Oh, 12.
I say, sir, get down before I cane you with my riding crop.
I'll court thee across the face.
Oh, San Francisco.
How you doing?
Oh, hell.
Somebody stop that old man.
Stop him.
I'm getting away.
He's just a guy.
He's got a cap.
We're just like that.
Well, then, why do you think you want to take up a lot of our time
with your mindless, mean-mouthed meandering?
You guys just have no shame, do you?
I beg your pardon?
Seems to be the trouble.
Well, you're begging and pleading for us to call.
It's just disgusting.
Simply reminding you of the many opportunities available
in this great land of ours.
But you would be listening to a collage made from pieces
sent in by Reverend Uncle Jimmy Joe Swaggart
right here in Dallas.
He did put together a lot of the very old,
and you'll hear a lot more of that coming up.
Nice little bites.
Soundbites.
Reverend Velveteen Sly and her partner,
Reverend Angus MacGamora, supplied the sort of sex line
there in the background that we had at points.
And the KPFA material you're not hearing
is from a best-of compilation by Dr. Phineas Narco.
A lot of it is KPFA Dr. Howell and puzzling evidence,
and even lies heard there.
Not in the background for you.
Please look at the interesting sneak peeks we made from test
For the first time, the
chamber's got a lower level size to the
hearing level of the patient's bronchial drum arrest.
It can attack them without yet making noise.
For the only time, the water can do deliberately
So as they found you, the camera was probably
showing an incorrect operation.
Whatever peace to the Lord, warranty their life and all their
ரcraối courts.
.
and thanks for your contribution.
All my family watched
many of the educational programs.
I like that feeling.
Police will pass an innocent weenie roast on the beach,
but should they know of your actions here,
that there's been a drinking party
and nude bathing
an investigation will surely take place.
These messages will now become subliminal,
but your subconscious mind
will be hearing and accepting
all of the positive messages.
Help me, please.
Help, Bob.
Or die, fools.
Oh, God.
This is just pathetic, man.
Back up that little boom.
I want you to keep your shenanigans down to a third.
Here we go.
Fine.
I don't want to hear your shenanigans
to the roughest room.
I don't want to hear one peep out of your kids.
Hi, guys.
How's it going over there tonight?
It's Rob Singlespar from KGO News Talk Radio.
Are you in the helicopter?
Can you see the traffic pattern from where you are?
Yeah, I can, but I heard you guys got
tipper goals in the studio tonight.
So I can get my hands on her.
You know what?
DJ just rolled tipper.
She was suddenly intoxicated and she,
well, she tipped over.
She was insensible.
Oh, my God.
Uh-oh.
We're gonna go get her.
That's what I'm doing.
As you can see on the monitor,
I'm applying cardiopulmonary regurgitation
right into her face there.
If that doesn't make her up, I don't know what will.
And we're punching her out using the
Lottky's Lamanis program.
Timber, wake up!
Timber, get up.
Smell this stuff.
We're holding volatile...
You've gotta get her back up.
...somany salts out of her nose.
I think she took too much.
You gotta go.
Get her out of here before six and get her out of here.
And we're putting hot peppers up her...
Come on.
Come on, Hal.
Stop that.
And we're...
I'm...
Okay.
Hold on, hold on.
You bugged your ball boss.
Needle nose pliers, but she doesn't seem to respond to the treatment.
Okay.
No, I think she...
Her eyes are opening.
Hello, Tipper.
This is the subject of this day.
Put a stupid kiss on her.
I'm afraid you've been had by all of us.
Okay, Tipper.
We'll play Tipper's song now.
Got you, love.
But tonight we get even.
Yeah!
Never mind what crickets and criminals do.
What kind of bacteria is good for you?
Well, the kind that makes me go boo, that's the kind.
Don't be cowed by such primitive propaganda.
We are going to save the universe.
It's so ironic because some of these false preachers
can raise millions and millions of dollars.
No problem there.
Well, I tell you what.
I challenge you, Jim Swagger.
I challenge you, Jim Baker.
I challenge you, Oral Roberts.
You see this hand here?
You see this hand in front of me, Mr. Jim Baker?
This is called the claw, and it's got the power of dogs in it
and the power of Bob.
And I challenge you to show your ugly face
here at this radio station and come forward.
Go ahead.
Come forward with all your millions.
I'm ready to have a match without rules.
No rules at all.
One will survive.
One over.
Only one minister will leave the match still breathing
if one of you goody-goody preachers has the guts to show up.
The end times get closer and closer every minute.
Imagine some guy or some gal driving around out there.
They're tired of listening to the same old music
on their conspiracy radio show,
so they try switching channels,
and they come upon this.
They hear these voices talking,
and they think,
now what is this, a talk show?
A church show?
A comedy?
I mean, oh my God, are these people serious?
It's too developed to be a joke.
Should I kill them, or should I pay them?
Which will it be, friend?
Which will it be?
Kill us or pay us?
Give to us something to live for.
Anything.
We need hope now, love.
I'm a robber and a son of a bitch.
One moment, please.
I bring you a message.
Exactly six miles north of Skag Mountain
in the Valley of Pain,
there lives an evil devil monster.
His name is Bingo Gas Station,
Motel Cheeseburger with a side of aircraft noise,
and you'll be Gary, Indiana.
And he loves to hurt people.
The last time I saw Bingo Gas Station,
Motel Cheeseburger with a side of aircraft noise,
and you'll be Gary, Indiana,
he told me what he wants to do.
He wants to come down here and kill each and every one of you.
But I said to him, Bingo, wait a minute.
And the reason I said that is because I believe in you people.
I believe you can do the job.
I believe you can help each other.
I believe you can make this world a better place.
I believe you can make this world a better place to live in.
That's it.
Down, boy, down. Back, back.
I really do.
Oh, no, it's a good one.
Oh, I'm afraid we burned this little caller
on the roasting hell of telephone wires here.
I ain't the one who's yelling and helping.
Uh-oh, look, the little caller's burning up.
Hal, get the fire extinguisher.
Use the caller extinguisher.
I'm going to go whine when the baby's broody again.
Now, let's go over that again.
You say something short and long.
You say you saw some sort of monster.
You know cryomorphology is the part of the...
Oh, Monsieur.
...protein of the various processes and products of cold climates.
Captain.
There's one now.
We are in the ear canal.
Everybody be quiet.
It can hear us.
Funny little itching thing in the ear, Captain.
I, it, it...
What about the other ear?
Ah!
It shrivels with antennas.
You put creatures in our ears.
They're in our bodies.
Well, you know, it was just a show.
They're show creatures, yes.
Hmm.
Captain, it was Stang.
He put the creatures in our ears to make us ruin the show.
Oh, no.
Really?
Well...
It's kind of neat.
Let's see what we can do.
Let's, okay, I'm going to pull the head of one of these little creatures out here, and
it'll talk to us.
It'll talk to us, little creature.
It'll talk to us.
Alright.
Look at these names, look at the souls lining up for the harvest, friends.
There's one.
Get it!
Squash it!
Aren't you supposed to say, help me, help me?
Kill it!
Kill it.
It's back in Tokyo!
Look at it!
Now, what was this about a monster?
Come on, you can't expect us to believe that.
Let's go over that again.
I believe you probably think you saw something.
You know, the human mind's a funny thing.
It plays strange tricks.
Uh, you guys try to tell us that aliens, beast monsters, are bringing on some kind of brave new world?
And they're gonna whip your butt real good.
But they're really pretty, so you won't mind.
Yeah, and they got big tentacles and flowers on their hats and everything.
Now let's go over that again.
So you heard some kind of show or monster?
No, no, monster, you've got to believe me.
What?
Don't you think I know how crazy this sounds?
Don't you think you're, I know you're thinking, well, this guy has to be locked up.
This guy has to be locked up.
Well, I didn't say that, mister, but you've got the general idea.
Don't you know there aren't any monsters in this day and age?
If God is honest, the national good of this whole town is lost, I tell you.
We put a man on the moon.
Time for monsters is coming and going.
I know it sounds crazy, but it's the truth.
You've got to believe me.
Well, now, this thing you say you thought you saw.
What?
Tentacles.
He was six feet tall and dripping slime and had tentacles and wings all over him.
Oh, that was Mobius Rex.
He's not here, though.
Oh, my goodness, look.
It's the March of the Monsters.
It's neat.
It's cool.
It's keen.
Oh, look, that big, icky green thing's hopping on one foot.
Hell.
And horrible little squishy, squiggly collars, too, cutting thousands of them.
And it's raining miniature frogs.
They're only a half an inch long.
Oh, I like those frogs.
They fall from the Sargassum Sea that surrounds the Earth.
Hello, you're on the air.
Oh, no, it's the monsters.
Go, go.
Here, climb under the shore to protect yourself.
Watch out for the Palolo.
Higher, higher.
Get up, get up, get up.
Get up, get up.
Oh, my God.
250,000 points.
Oh, thank God.
Look at those detonations.
A thousand points of...
Oh, my God.
That collar is nothing but a little...
Those are a thousand points of light.
They're going.
Oh, my God.
The Pakalolo works.
Okay, go ahead and ask me the monster question.
Oh, you should.
Okay.
Oh, my God.
Take your question, please.
Do the monster bit.
Do the monster.
Everybody do the monster bit.
Please take the brochure that came with this tape
and turn to pay the most.
There it is.
The guarantee.
Is that it?
Is that what you're talking about?
No.
Oh, do I have to spell it out for you?
Is there something else we're supposed to do?
Wave your tail and click the claws.
Now, let's go over that again.
Wave your tail up.
It'll scare you and everything.
Do it now.
Do the monster bit.
This is an amazing collage of
you say you saw some sort of monster bit
done by Dr. Howell and puzzling evidence
and other evil callers.
This particular collage put together by
Reverend Phineas Narco.
So, let's see.
What?
I do have also to play here
this wonderful piece by a doctor,
a friend in Denmark,
a subgenius in Denmark,
Reverend, actually we should call him
Saint Sverre H. Christensen.
Sverre A. Christensen.
Yes, he's a friend of Reverend Sheldon de Weers also.
And these are some Bob songs from the Danish doctor band.
Anus Presley.
Well, the death toll is, I mean, the death toll is up
and the death knoll is tolling.
And the show is not looking so good on the big pledge drive thermometer.
In fact, it doesn't seem to have climbed much past the halfway mark.
So, I guess we'll just watch the funeral of the Hour of Slack show carried in its glass coffin.
Its innards visible, spilling out all over the street.
Little reels of tape, broken cassettes, mic cords, frayed patch tables, and gate hairs in the cameras.
Half erased videotapes.
It got close to the camera.
Too close to the car engine.
And packages sent through the mail that never got where they were going.
Checks that bounced and pledges never paid.
Promises never kept.
And I'm not even reading from a script, friends.
I'm talking from my heart.
This is how you're making me feel.
Somebody called in a little while ago.
Apparently a real idiot.
There is not a phone.
You can talk, Trickster.
Your mic is up.
Give us money now!
823-7490.
A guy called up a little while ago.
Repeat what this fellow said, Sheldon.
Oh, no, don't repeat.
Well, yeah, yeah, tell them what the guy said.
The guy called up.
There was this guy who called up and he said, this isn't Robert Tilton.
And I said, no.
And he said, I couldn't tell the difference.
What a funny joke.
So now we, I, it makes you not want to bother with much of a show, you know, in a way.
It's just, oh.
Well, there's the funeral of J.R. Bob Dobbs still cranking along there.
I'm already putting my tapes away because I'm actually pretty insulted.
Bob, I don't want to do that!
It's glue in his k ultrasound.
Man's Gesicht.
It's from the
It's coming down.
Looks like Bob!
I don't wanna do that.
This is a fight.
Or you'll have to cut up some flesh.
Shut up!
He's gonna die.
Signal of some Rotent's
Please the
VOICE of the
DE
E
Thank you.
Bob World.
He is Bob.
He get for fun.
He wears a smile.
Everybody run.
I want you to put your hands out in the TV.
I told you.
This is Bob.
Welcome to the problem.
I'm not connected.
Bob, are you here?
I don't believe in this.
Do not try this on your own. It is extremely dangerous.
Let's look at that again in slow motion.
And we've got a little more.
Would you like Bob?
Driver Parkhurst reporting for duty, sir.
All right, at ease, Bob. Stand easy.
Captain Blackadder, this is Bob.
Bob?
Good morning, sir.
Unusual name for a girl.
Well, yes, it would be an unusual name for a girl,
but it's a perfectly straightforward name
for a young chap like you, eh, Bob?
Now, Bob, I want you to bunk up with Captain Blackadder
for a couple of days, all right?
Yes, sir.
I think you'll find Bob's just the man for this job, Blackadder.
He has a splendid sense of humour.
He, sir? He? He?
You see? You're laughing already.
All right.
Well, now, Bob, I'll leave you two together.
Why don't you, er, get to know each other,
play a game of cribbage, have a smoke, something like that.
They tell me that Captain Blackadder
has rather a good line in rough shag.
Um, I'm sure he'd be happy to fill your pipe.
Carry on.
Sir, you're a chap, are you, Bob?
Oh, yes, sir.
You wouldn't say you were a girl at all?
Oh, definitely not, sir.
I understand cricket.
I fart in...
beds, everything.
Well, let me put it another way, Bob.
You are a girl, and you're a girl with as much talent for disguise
as a giraffe in dark glasses
trying to get into a polar bears-only golf club.
Oh, sir, oh, sir, please don't give me away, sir.
I just want you to be like my brothers and join up.
I want to see how a war is fought so badly.
Well, you've come to the right place, Bob.
A war hasn't been fought this badly
since Olaf the Hairy,
high chief of all the Vikings,
accidentally ordered 80,000 battle helmets
with the horns on the inside.
I want to do my bit for the boys, sir.
Oh, really?
I'll do anything, sir.
Yes, I'd keep that to yourself if I was able.
All right, Bob.
To end the show,
I'm going to play this tape
of a new, relatively new,
sister subgenius show.
It's at WORT,
Madison.
Hello, W-O-R-T,
you wonderful folks.
At that, at that,
oh, wait, I should be playing
some background music here.
Where'd it go?
Yeah, there we go.
Johnny Flash's, uh,
uh,
what is the name of that?
Johnny Flash,
Concordant Opposition,
Fountain of Slack,
here in the background.
My main worry is to keep
the real reason for this flight
well and truly secret,
and I'm sure that's not
what you're trying to tell me.
Well, I'm trying to tell you
that, uh,
I'm trying to make a deal.
The station, the station
in Madison, Wisconsin,
W-O-R-T,
has a show
operated by Reverend Velveteen Sly
and Father Angus McGamora.
And Reverend Velveteen Sly
is a great new preacher-esque.
She plays the Hour of Slack
on her show,
but she also has
surrounding material
that she does
for hours and hours.
And she has sent me
some excerpts
from her rantings.
I'm going to, uh,
end the show
with this,
a lovely piece
called Illuminations,
dear friends.
It is interesting
to note the progress
of a particular experience
in developing this subgenius,
or rather in stirring
the subgenius
into activity.
In the particular case observed,
the principal work
is done during sleep
and appears at first
to consist in the preparation
of the spinal passage
by moving slack
from the base of the spine
to the top of the head.
The individual out of the body
can do this work,
for though there are
physical effects,
the fire itself
is non-physical.
The globe or sphere
at the base of the spine
contains within it
the fire of slack
coiled spherically.
The prescribed concentration
upon the globe
and thus upon
the fire of slack within
begins to stir it
into activity,
provided the right kind of life
has been lived beforehand
for a considerable period,
which is to say
provided it is fed
with the right kind of fuel.
Fuel.
Even if the right kind of life
has not been lived,
a stirring may take place,
but the effect
of the premature stirring,
if any,
take place at all,
will be disastrous,
as has already been pointed out.
Assuming a stirring
takes place
along right lines,
there is a gradual
dissolution of the globe
caused by the frictional
energizing of the fire
of slack itself.
The fire is fanned
into bright heat
and becomes active,
forcing its way
through the matter
in which it lies embedded,
burning it up
and causing the globe
to become a radiant sun
instead of
the dull,
the glowing mass
it normally is.
This sun radiates
radiates,
in all directions,
heat of slack,
which is physically felt,
especially in the surrounding areas
of the physical yeti form.
This subgenius sun
would seem to rush upwards
when it moves fast,
as often it does not
along the way.
It is as fine as a bullet
passes through a grooved gun barrel.
There is something spiral
about the movement.
In any case,
there seems to be a direct rush upwards
without passing beyond the top of the head,
but specially stimulating centers
according to the individual's ray.
The sensation is that of pressure,
while as regards the center
at the top of the head,
unusual heat,
will be felt.
During the waking hours,
this process may be continued,
and from time to time
it seems to occur of itself,
so that a warm glow passes up the spine,
producing a most interesting effect.
A beautiful expansion of consciousness
is physically experienced,
so that the individual feels full of a glorious life
and of a sense of,
intimately
of a다면,
of the
Being in delicate, intimate的入面关系
with what must be the developed intuitive subconsciousness,
He or she imagines what life would be like if he could keep this experience constant
instead of only intermittent.
There is a fine sense of at-one-ment, of radiance, of contact with the real.
The individual barriers seem to have been broken down so that the individual sees into
the heart of things, no matter what they are, and sees them as growing entities.
Their glorious future disclosed to he or she as embryonic in them.
It is so difficult to describe this condition of consciousness, but the physical, indeed
much more than the physical, seems transcended.
And some veils at least are lifted.
So that he or she gazes upon a real, less hidden by the clouds of illusion.
In the beginnings of this process, a certain amount of dizziness is noticeable.
A new constituent has become active.
It is as if a...
A new dimension has opened out, so that a new world is entered.
The dizziness is perhaps the physical expression of a new relativity, of a new adjustment.
Other worlds than the physical begin to be opened to a gaze which the individual has
not yet learned to control.
So that he or she looks out, as it were, with a new world.
With all eyes vaguely open, instead of with those appropriate to the particular plane
on which he or she happens to be dominantly functioning.
Later on, he will be able to close the eyes he does not need, leaving open only those
he does.
And later on still, he will be able, perhaps, to use the eyes of the other.
All eyes simultaneously.
Each eye dovetailing into the other's, so as to avoid distortion and flickering between
one state of consciousness and another.
The effect being the dizziness.
The dizziness.
The ever smelled vlog请多多 Брmaticard
You're listening to the subgenius radio ministry hour of slack.
For free information on Bob Dobbs and the Church of the Subgenius.
Write to us at subgenius.com.
a self-addressed stamped envelope to, got your pencil ready? Bob, Post Office Box 140306,
Dallas, Texas 75214. That's Bob, P.O. Box 140306, Dallas, Texas 75214. Stay tuned and praise Bob.
This is not political. This is not religious. An open letter to the American people.
My fellow Americans, I, Ernest Warren, will swear an oath on the Bible that the information contained herein is the truth.
Approximately 30 years ago, an article appeared in Reader's Digest about a young physicist who was working in his laboratory
one day when he accidentally isolated a phenomenal ray.
He experimented.
In fact, he was able to find a way to find the ray.
He found that he could control the actions of a mouse when the ray was focused on the brain of the rodent.
When the full potential of the ray was realized, it was turned over to the U.S. federal government,
which, in turn, entrusted the ray to the National Science Foundation.
After all these years, what have the federal scientists been able to accomplish with the brain ray?
Did they finally focus the ray on the brain of a human guinea pig?
I, for the past 11 years, have been the human guinea pig,
and I am the human guinea pig for the Federal Brain Ray Science Project,
and will state, under oath, that the brain ray machine can perform miracles.
Following are some things it will do, and this merely scratches the surface.
There would be no alcoholics, no drug addicts, and hardened criminals would choose to live honest, normal, useful lives.
Many retarded people could be helped toward living normal lives again.
Many crippled could walk in a normal way.
Many blind could get their sight.
I have been blinded and regained my sight so many times that I can't recall the number of times it has happened.
The brain ray induced glaucoma to my eyes.
The pressure and everything was present.
I was treated for weeks with prescription medicine, and then the brain ray cured my eyes.
The true claims concerning the brain ray could fill a book.
I am under complete remote control by the brain ray machine.
The federal scientists know my every thought and every move.
Every thought, every action, every conversation.
They see what I see.
They hear what I hear.
Every night when I am sleeping, I see a short movie in my brain.
The brain ray is a device that can be used to detect the brain ray.
This old-time radio program was originally aired live, long before the advent of high fidelity.
As a result, you may detect an occasional surface noise or volume drop due to transmission problems so common to old radio.
We hope, however, that any variance in audio quality will not take away from your pleasure in listening to this, one of the all-time favorite shows.
In the latter part of the 20th century, we human beings on this planet Earth were being watched.
Our every move.
Carefully scrutinized.
And not just by our governments.
Others were watching.
Where were they from?
What did they want?
Does it really matter anymore?
We have our signal back, so let's go down to Coach Grover Mill's post-game locker room show, already in progress.
Coach, who do you think played well in today's game?
I don't know if anybody played well in our side, Bob.
I'm just going to have to take a look at the films.
What about these reports, Fitcher?
I think your wife was sleeping with the players while you were out recruiting last year.
Oh, I don't know about that.
We're going to have to take a look at the films before we make any judgment on that.
Well, what was that?
What's happening here?
A huge glowing cylinder has landed on the football field, just barely missing the band.
People are running and screaming.
It's out of pandemonium now.
It's down there.
Boy, those college kids sure will think of some...
Should the brain ray machine be real, then there are two logical questions to be asked.
First, why was I chosen to be the human guinea pig for the project?
There is no apparent answer.
But there is J.R. Bob Dobbs.
And those last few tapes, as well as the PCP Club earlier in the show,
were by the all-pro cavalcade force.
Poor Bob. Praise the all-pro cavalcade.
Thank you, and...
This is a test of the emergency brah-sahana.
Merge your lichen into the rudder of the broad-cawing pre-recorded announcement.
I hope to die in a ball.
Oh, it would be wonderful, George.
We feel like Columbus when we discover the moon.
Have you lost your mind, Gene?
It's dangerous.