The Self-Genius Power of Bob
Friends, the virtual online X-Day drill was lots of fun.
It's going to take some editing though.
But Reverend Susie the Flusie saved my boot-all by doing a superb brand new X-Day and Plague episode of Bob's Slack Time Funhouse on WREK Atlanta.
As follows.
The program you are about to hear, Bob's Slack Time Funhouse, is parody, satire, and comedy.
Any reference to Bob, the Church of the Self-Genius, religion, politics, or any other touchy subject is intended only as humor and should pass no reflection on the highest standards of WREK Atlanta, its staff, or that of Georgia Tech.
Enjoy the show, for one day we shall die.
Wow, look who's finally coming around.
Oh, God, evil Susie.
Oh, man.
Feels like I need to shave my teeth.
Oh, Tom.
You probably do.
I put you under around New Year's Eve.
How long have I been asleep?
Somewhere around 25.
I slept for 25 hours?
No, 25 weeks.
You mean to say since January you've put me into a medically induced coma?
Well, sort of, kind of.
Less medical, more cast iron.
Skill it with a little help from the street corner.
Stop.
I'm a little bit of a fucking cop.
But you needed the beauty rest, Lo.
Oh, that explains the headache.
When is right now?
Oh, it's Sunday around midnight.
Which Sunday?
The Sunday that's July 5th this year.
It's July 5th?
Oh, holy hell.
My house is supposed to be the next day.
I gotta go.
Hey, hold your horse, Flues.
You can't go out.
What? Why?
No one can go out.
What's going on?
Oh, that's right.
I guess you've missed a few things.
Let me help you get caught up.
Ah!
Hmm.
Nothing like sleep learning.
The day it all began.
The day what began?
Oh, yes, yes.
It began far, far away from this lovely palace.
Far below the Earth's surface at the Institute.
Come on in.
Didn't mean to disturb your lunch.
Welcome to the Lymphnode Institute.
I'm Doc.
I'm Bunsy.
Governments don't dare try to kill me.
I've let them all know that I've planted biological bombs in seven major cities around the world.
And, uh...
And released a biological attack on the population which will kill hundreds of thousands.
Then...
Oops.
Broke open.
Ain't that a bitch?
Run!
You ain't got a chance.
Man.
But that was just a prelude to what was to come.
You got to hurry.
There's a storm coming.
His storm.
Huh?
And his name?
The Horned King!
The Dark Man!
Oh, no.
Well, we're boned.
Come on, let's go.
I'm coming.
Come on down and meet your maker.
Come on down and make the stand.
Come on down.
You'll make the stand.
Oh.
Where the hell is Gerard?
Told you he's sick.
What do you mean he's sick?
I mean, he's really sick.
Throwing up diarrhea.
It's nasty.
To tell you the truth, I'm a little worried.
He had those bad cramps, right?
You really are one paranoid little man, you know that?
Cold got you down?
Chills?
Fever?
Sounds like you need a buddy.
Flu Buddy.
Fast-acting Flu Buddy.
Available at pharmacies everywhere.
Flu Buddy.
And now, let's get back to the Lone Star.
I'm not leaving.
State patrol, Hap.
Hey, Joe Bob.
Want me to fill her up for you?
No, sir.
I come by on other business.
Was that old geezer here last night?
He's here just about every night.
And maybe he ought to hear this, too.
Hear what?
There's strangers crawling all over Braintree.
Supposed to be U.S. Health Service guys, but they came in a C-5A transport plane and
they look like regular Army to me.
And then there's been three more big transport planes land over Starland in Arkansas since
noon.
What's calling?
I knew it was a Starland.
I don't know nothing about that.
I'll tell you one thing, though.
If the feds are thinking about a quarantine, then you might have a little bit more to worry
about than cholera.
I just thought you ought to know what's stirring in the weeds, Hap.
If any of them other old boys that were here last night come by, you ought to pass a word
along to them.
Just don't mention my name.
Hap!
You ought to take care of that old timer.
Them summer coals are the worst.
Oh.
Okay.
All right.
What if it ain't a cold?
What if I got whatever he had?
That guy last night?
Oh, it's probably just a sniffles, that's all.
comparment danner.
Yes!
day call the other fellows and see how they're feeling might not be a bad idea yeah
all survivors gotta come with us run jesse run
let's go let's go you're on up the stamp time now move it
it caused him to empty his bowels being hijacked by a bunch of government sons of bitches in space
suits does that to me every time
it's okay okay we're here in quarantine with the other survivors where is here
the old army base what the hell's wrong with us vomiting diarrhea dehydration kidney failure
is it cholera absolutely not you'll be getting all the details when
you
who told you to ask that question this press conference is over
nothing true i've never been this scared us our families people we've been around since
what's going on here it isn't the man with the little clipboard and the armed escort
no no no no we don't take counts here just a precaution would you get the doctor a mask
wait wait wait we're moving this man to isolation according to who he's been misdiagnosed health
services has no authority here actually in a communicable case i do you're making a big
mistake here honey i don't think so and it's doctor
not honey so when are we gonna go public well we're not not till we have some kind of
solid information on how this thing is spreading we got to keep a tight lid on this thing with
the press it's kind of an outbreak can easily cause a panic
meanwhile in washington dc yes sir on the outskirts of a one stoplight town in east
texas we killed them in a hurry down there telemetry suggests even the ones that manage
to get their respirators on there are only three hours later they're being followed by an
died within 12 minutes.
The rest of them were gone in five.
You believe that?
Do I have a choice?
No.
Apparently, none of us do.
The National Disease Control Center,
the Pentagon, says we'll know
if it's actually going to jump to the outside.
He says it'll probably mutate,
but that's not going to help the people that catch it.
Listen, General, I have what might be something...
It'll just take them longer to die.
That's all.
Most people are going to think
they've got the plain old non-lethal flu
right up to the very end.
And that's the biggest break we've had so far.
Contact with townspeople was minimal.
That doesn't matter.
We've got to shut that town down,
lock it up, dig a moat around it.
That operation's already on the launching pad, sir.
What kind of cover did you come up with?
Anthrax.
New strain.
It's a new one, all right.
It's real new.
It's very good at its job, too.
I don't know, but the important thing is
right now we've got a shot at containing this.
Oh, God, this stuff has a communicability
level of over 99%.
You understand what that means?
Any chance we have of containing it when...
But that was just a prelude to what was to come.
The time is now.
A nightmare is about to begin.
Central Banking
Mindfucking all the times
I am the fear
It's been a bad day
I am the fire
I am the furnace
I am the biosejournalism
I am the fire
Four flags and bird dolls
Trapper stock, manufactured chance
Self-destructive normalization
Something's gone horribly wrong
Heart's trash is full and we are gone
Our population
In deep denial
Contagion release
Surrender
I am the fuel
The spirit of our rage
I am the fire
I am the virus
I am the furnace
By this I can handle
I am the virus
I am the fury
This pure, pure rage
I am the fire
I am the forest, I am the forest
No one believe
I am the fury
This pure, pure rage
I am the fire
I am the forest, I am the forest
I am the furnace
Where is everyone going?
I am the forest
I am the forest, I am the forest
I am the great face
I am the one you can never delete
I am the pain cause it never sleeps
I am the forest, I am the forest
I am the fury
This pure, pure rage
I am the fire
I am the forest, I am the forest
I am the fury
This pure, pure rage
I am the fire
I am the forest, I am the forest
I am the furnace
Where is everyone going?
I am the fire
I am the forest, I am the forest
Yeah, you know what?
Burn it down
Why not?
He's infected.
Viral infections.
Highly contagious.
I only hope there's no leak.
And suddenly things turned ugly.
I'd like to call to order this secret conclave of America's media empires.
We're here to come up with the next phony baloney crisis to put Americans back where they belong
in dark rooms glued to their televisions too terrified to skip the commercials.
Well, I think...
NBC, you are here to listen and not speak.
I think we should go with a good old-fashioned public health care.
Yeah.
A new disease.
No one's immune.
It's like the summer of the shark, except instead of a shark, it's an epidemic.
And instead of summer, it's all the time.
That is...
Now, I hate to be the guy who derails what everybody else loves.
He loves being that guy.
But, Janice, we do have standards.
This can't be a made-up disease.
The only moral thing to do is release a deadly virus into the general public.
We do have something.
Something we've been holding on to, but it hasn't been tested.
Get over here, NBC.
Well, we certainly believe in testing, but I...
Oh.
Wow.
Oh, yeah.
So, we've got our deadly disease.
Now, we just have to blame it on something that's in every household.
Something that people are a little bit afraid of already.
Well, now, look here.
Thursday nights at 8 p.m.
America's favorite TV.
TV show.
There's a bat in my house.
Betty, Betty, Betty.
Starring America's favorite funny man.
The hilarious, zany B.B. Sanders as Betty Boy.
Oh, absolutely.
Ah, couldn't agree more.
Love it.
Love everything about it.
Excellent.
Betty, Betty, Betty.
It's all I need to do.
It's gone too fast.
So there you have it.
Story time.
Beautiful skills, I'm sure.
And I've gotten a bit of a shock here.
But remember.
Don't sleep.
We've had some bad days here in Black deal.
A bad day can be rain.
Sheand.
We 해도 neitherrüge emig forgehand万ası
We hating the emergency control bank on theThis book is a compensation in good faith.
All depends on def Mega Middle.
controversy affects remark swing.
There's that bit with Mike Merman.
Thank you.
Yeah, yeah, oh yeah.
What condition my condition was in.
Someone painted a cocoon
In pink, black letters on my dick.
I had my foot on the gas as I left the road that blew out my mind.
Eight miles out of Memphis and I got no spring here.
Eight miles straight up downtown somewhere.
I just dropped in to see what condition my condition was in.
I said I just dropped in to see what condition my condition was in.
Yeah! Yeah!
Oh yeah!
H Shocker
And Civil Defense authorities state the situation is much the same across the entire country
Already, hospital facilities have begun to crack under the strain
Ed Mueller
Wellek
I got bit.
Bit?
About what?
Well, if I told you, you probably wouldn't believe me.
I'm very polite, Matt Pyre.
With all this trouble, I won't eat a bat.
So that should answer how I got so fat.
I'm like Trump, the way he gets grouchy when he's corrected by Dr. Fauci.
Dr. Fauci said earlier this week that the lag in testing was in fact a failing.
Do you take responsibility for that?
Yeah, no, I don't take responsibility at all.
This is an outrage.
My life for him.
Well, how do you feel, Ms. Preskey?
The U.S. itself has overtaken China.
Now, as the country with the most cases of the virus, it is the new global epicenter.
Eighty five thousand nine hundred and ninety one confirmed cases in the United States.
And I think our economy will start to pick up very substantially as soon as the states get open.
And that's happening as we speak.
And it's actually very exciting.
People are just thrilled to see it.
Stay prepared.
We'll see you next time.
Like the scouts taught me one step ahead because they still haven't caught me.
Keep your hands to yourself and your money on the shelf.
It's a pandemic.
Stay sane in a world gone crazy.
We'll stand up to the challenge and we ain't lazy.
We'll do what we have to do to stand up to this pandemic.
The greatest generation is still around.
You can hear them every night if you listen for the sound.
If you can't, they'll squeeze off another round.
It's a pandemic.
They're stealing biochemical weapons, also known as Project Terror.
Designed to take out an entire populace in a controlled, landlocked area.
You're supplying it to them.
Ten stories down.
What about Connery with atropine and PAMP2?
Interferes with the neurotoxin delivery.
Sets off the cell blaster.
And you're gushing blood and pus through every sacred hole in your body.
Hepatizing.
Like a drug.
Correct.
But we found that a small percentage of people are not affected.
And within this small percentage,
Isaac, you're...
But we have to get back to my lab.
This infection will spread all over the world to every man, woman, and child.
All of the sickness of the world and its people are here in one motion picture for you to witness.
Yes, it's a sick, sick, sick world.
Follow this motion picture and its unbelievable cast
as the camera takes you through a maze of unforgettable sights.
Sights that you will never, never forget.
I'm sure you'll remember.
History teaches us that, uh, when the Great Plague hits,
those who don't die alone usually die in church.
So, we may find nothing in this one, but if we do,
try to think of the bodies as cordwood.
Make it easier.
Cordwood?
AAAAAAHHHHHHHHHHHHH
We are dead.
And this is...
Hell.
AAAAAAHHHHHHHHHHHHH
Hahahaha!
Come on down and meet your maker.
Come on down and make the stand.
Come on down.
And move it!
And stand!
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Oh, come on down and meet your maker.
Come on down and make the stand.
Come on down.
We'll make the stand.
AAAAAAHHHHHHHHHHHHH
Bring out your dead!
The monster's coming!
He's coming!
Bring out your dead!
We're damned.
Yes.
I know.
Ugh, turn on the radio will ya?
Hello there.
I guess this morning there's only one topic of conversation.
You can call it the Super Flu or by its West Coast name, Captain Trips, but it means the same thing either way.
There have been some horror stories about the Army clamping down on everything.
The Army?
Just be patient with me.
Remember, I'm running the show all by myself.
Everyone else called in sick.
The numbers are the same as always, though.
555-TALK and 555-CHAT.
So let's go.
Hello there, this is Ray Flowers, and it's time to speak your piece.
I'm calling from Portsmouth.
What's your name?
Leonora.
Listen, Ray, I just want everyone to know that there are soldiers burning bodies
across the state line in Kittery.
Also, my little girl died this morning.
I guess she's with Jesus now.
I'm sorry as hell, Leonora.
Ray, I think the soldiers did it.
I think they made a bug that's like killing people.
That wouldn't be very American now, would it?
No, I guess not.
Of course, that's never stopped the real patriots among us, has it?
You try to hang in there, Leonora.
I'm trying, Ray.
But have you ever smelled bodies on fire?
I can't say that I have.
It's awful, Ray.
It's just...
You just try to hang in there, hon.
You're on the air, and it's time to speak your piece.
First of all, I just want to tell you that I love your show, Ray.
You say you saw these G.I.s gunning down unarmed civilians?
Open in the name of the United States government!
Open!
I'll tell you what, Portland.
It looks like the Marines have landed, and they don't look too happy.
This is a joke, right?
I mean, this has got to be a joke.
I don't think so, Franny.
I really don't think so.
Hi there.
You're on the air.
Ray, you all right?
Well, to tell you the truth, honey, it doesn't look real good for the kid right now.
Several soldiers have just broken into the studio.
They're fully armed, and they're dressed in some kind of protective clothing.
They're wearing respirators on their faces.
Shut it down!
Hey, Bluto!
You ever heard of a little number called...
Freedom of speech?
Bill of Rights?
Any of that ring a bell?
Folks, I've just been ordered by my uninvited fascist guest to shut down, and I've refused.
All right, get them up!
Oh, my God!
What's happening?
I don't know, honey.
I don't know.
He's closer now!
The hard case!
The dark man!
He's coming!
He's closer now!
The dark man!
Whether a state of war between China and Russia still exists is not important any longer.
Our fellow countrymen are dying.
Naturally, we'll have more on this story as soon as it develops.
We now return you to the president's address already in progress.
Winning!
You are going to get so sick of winning!
USA!
It's my life for you!
Yeah, there were a couple times when I didn't think you were buying it.
But this was an emergency.
This is a class one emergency.
All civilian traffic is barred from streets and highways.
Stay in your homes.
Those found without specific military orders are subject to summary execution.
Repeat, Conrad Channel.
This is a class one emergency.
All civilian traffic is barred from streets and highways.
Please remain calm.
Stay in your homes.
I am officially declaring a national emergency.
Two very big words.
It will go away.
Just stay calm.
And it will go away.
And we're going to have a great victory.
It's going to go away.
Hopefully at the end of the month.
And if not, hopefully we'll be soon after that.
He says a coronavirus is a hoax.
The fact is the president himself is a hoax.
The White House has done a con.
She scoffs at holiness!
Punish her!
I am an epidemiologist with the Pacific Health Services.
And I'm telling you, you are going to listen.
Now, if you would like to call a private physician, you can.
You're damn right I can.
I can walk right out of here, too.
Oh, no, you can't.
This is an infectious disease, sir.
And if you do not cooperate, I have the authority to detain you here for public safety.
Shall I call security?
No.
Did you start him on tetracycline?
You won't take it.
This is a very serious disease.
Now, you can either take this medicine and hopefully not get sick,
or you can just sit here and wait to see what happens.
No.
No cure.
That is not until we find somebody from the other side and we'll install a batch as it is.
Science comes first, but business comes first.
Then you realized if you could infect a large enough populace,
experiment on its survivors,
you'd find a cure.
I swore to my men that I'd do everything in my power to keep them alive.
That's what I intend to do, Ray.
Understand?
I never had a choice.
You're wise, sir.
It's real pretty.
Vomiting, diarrhea, dehydration, kidney failure.
And you have complete circulatory collapse.
Your blood pressure plummets.
Body goes into shock.
Within 24 hours without medical treatment, you are dead.
You're dead, you're dead, you're dead, you're dead.
And out of this world.
You'll never get a second chance.
Plan all your moves in advance.
Stay dead, stay dead, stay dead, stay dead and out of this world.
Run fast, don't stand in the fire.
There's too much work to be done.
You're down, you're down, you're down, you're down.
Down and out of this world.
Yeah, sure.
Don't ever talk with your eyes.
Make sure that you compromise.
You're dead, you're dead, you're dead, you're dead.
dead and out of this world
hear the unloved
weeping like rain
guard your sleep from the sound of their pain
long gone
and out of this world
when you smile and it tears your face
it's time for the inhuman race
you're down, you're down, you're down
you're down and out of this world
now I hope the compassion is gone
you've sold out your dream to the world
stay dead, stay dead, stay dead
you're dead and out of this world
music
streets and highways are packed with
frantic people trying to protect their family
or apparently to flee just anywhere
I repeat, the safest course
of action at this time is simply to stay
where you are
and civil defense authorities state that the
situation is much the same across the entire
country. Martial law
is now nationwide
major cities in all parts of the country
New York, Los Angeles report
plague victims falling dead in the streets
in their homes, at their work
the first symptom appears to be severe choking
followed by immediate unconsciousness
death occurs within minutes
whether a state of war between China and Russia still exists
is not important any longer
our fellow countrymen are dying
the very foundations of civilization are beginning to crumble
under the dread assault of that horror long feared germ warfare
foot of your hand, I'll let you know God is really sneaky
you're the only one who wasn't afraid to come here today
I'm a scientist
and a businessman
not military
you haven't had to do it
but we have to get back to my lab
sir
my god
this man is dying
someone get a doctor
nooo
I don't suppose there are any other biochemical engineers around?
no
no?
yeah me neither
what's gonna happen Dr. Grissom?
is everybody in the world gonna die before someone finds the answer?
no
I don't think so
we'll find an answer
when doctor? we need it right now, I need it
I don't deny there's some strange evolutionary process going on
but mankind won't be destroyed
unless
unless, unless what?
I don't know
you're a smart guy, you'll figure something out
those cells are still living off one another
there has to be an answer
you heard that all communications are ended outside the continental limits?
yes I heard
that leaves it in our laps
so we keep trying
you two stay on this virus theory until I decide it's exhausting
right
and until further notice this station will continue its around the clock coverage of this national disaster
and now
we switch you to the state capital
where the governor is speaking from the executive mansion
the federal government declared this state to be a disaster area
public health is dependent on bodies of the deceased being burned
you must notify the health department immediately
have a plague victim in your home
under no circumstances should you gather public
if you're the dire emergency that exists, I intend to
what's the matter with you?
nothing and I'm going to keep it that way
look let's talk about this
there's nothing to talk about
you think I'm out of my mind
you might be one of them
look you're ill, you ought to see a doctor
no doctors
you take care of your life, I'll take care of mine
now get away from here
you understand? get away from here!
I'm going to confine you all to the station
being quarantined isn't that bad is it?
lonely
so very lonely
so very very very lonely
why must I stay in this lonely room
watching the gong show and thinking of you
loneliest chair, loneliest bed, loneliest deja vu
in the loneliest, loneliest, loneliest, loneliest room
in the world
I tried marijuana, cocaine and heroin
but they just can't seem to get the thought of you
out from under my skin
I'm lonelier now, lonelier than I've ever been
in the loneliest, loneliest, loneliest, loneliest room
in the world
phone never rings
postman never brings the thing
even the singles clubs won't give me a whirl
plants all dead, even my cactus
beer cans round my bed
in the loneliest room in the world
I'm lonely
it's point blank.
hang out with me
let's meet and cozy our one and only
are we and who are we going to be
don't put me in push-ups
this is the center of the earth
Room in the world
I'm not sorry for myself
I'm sorry for that
Miss Wright who can't find me
Miss Wright
I'm thinking of you tonight
In your lonely room
The single stuff won't even answer your phone
You got the blues
The lowdown singles, club blues
In your lonely room
Your room might even be lonely
But I doubt it baby
It's lonely
Lonely
And as soon as they bring back pork rinds and Monday night football
I'm gonna be in redneck heaven
Stay sane
In a world gone crazy
We'll stand up to the challenge
And we ain't lazy
We'll do what we have to do
To stand up to
This pandemic
The greatest generation
Is still around
You can hear them every night
If you listen for the sound
If you can't
They'll squeeze off another round
It's a pandemic
With our gloves on
We reach our hands to heaven
Wearing masks
Like we're robbing a 7-Eleven
We keep our distance
To secure our home
Our existence
It's a pandemic
It crept upon us like a thief in the night
But we got what it takes
To win this fight
We'll do what we can
And we'll do what's right
In this pandemic
Sacrifices are the price we pay
For another chance
To live another day
Stay together
But stay six feet away
It's a pandemic
Another question being asked forcibly
Is whether now is the right time
To reopen the US economy
In Georgia today
Hairdressers, nail salons, tattoo parlors
Were able to resume business
Even though coronavirus
Is still a serious problem in the state
Now we're opening it up
And it's opening up far faster than ever
Than anybody thought even possible
And there now
It's a life
It's got a life
And we're putting out that life
Because that's a bad life
That we're talking about
Yeah, well just don't forget
What you promised when you get back
Dinner, dancing
And all the paparazzi
I can smile at
Yeah, yeah, you got it
Be ready in five minutes
You bring the towels
I get the penicillin
Sick world
Is the story of vice
Perversion
Degradation
That has infested the earth
Since the time that Adam and Eve
Sinned in the garden of paradise
This is the shocking story
Of the world and its unholy inhabitants
Feeling no pain or shame
For the life that they lead
Well, looks like things are finally
Going to get back to normal
I think we learned a lesson here
What's that?
I don't know
The unquenched desires of sex
And the sensualists
In their search for pleasures
Are unparalleled in this motion picture
For a ringside seat
That takes you into the lust-filled caverns of life
See, it's a sick, sick, sick world
This motion picture has something for everyone
This is a picture you must not miss
A picture you will always remember
It's a sick, sick, sick world
And it's waiting for you
This event will force us to totally restructure our intelligence system
The Atlanta Disease Control Center told me that these masks wouldn't stop the virus from spreading
And that they would stop a flu germ with a hangover
Oh, no, no, no
Shake hands, kids
You old dog
How's that golf games?
That's nice
I think that at some point
That's going to sort of just disappear, I hope
You still believe so?
I do, yeah, sure
In the thick of this crisis
The president travels to South Dakota
July 5th
For an X-Day celebration at Mount Rushmore
There won't be any social distancing
And mask wearing will be up to the attendee
You're going to get so sick, sick, sick
Please go and get tested
Please wear a mask
I'm not listening to some loser public health doctor
They destroyed the world
Isn't that the
We'll find an answer
When, doctor?
Tonight
Is a special night
What's so special about tonight?
Let's see, what date is it?
What's the date?
July 5th
We're in luck
It says here
The planet Earth
The planet is going to be hit by a huge asteroid
And blown to smithereens on this very day
Hmm?
What date is July?
What the hell it is?
It's Sunday
Sunday I always dress for dinner
Well, you turned something on
I'm starting to think
The plague took the people
But it couldn't take the gadgets, could it?
No, they're all still out there
Just waiting for someone to come along and pick them up
Everything from electric can openers to cobalt bombs
And he'll depow it to him, brother
Just a little nitro
I don't know
I can get the cannons out of the old God Armory
We can hand it out of there in no time
I said no
We could
But then the curse would begin all over again, don't you see?
Here is evil
Evil
Unless
What's wrong with this picture?
It's the old way
And the old way was a death crypt
We say fine
And then we go right back to tinkering with the power
station
Trying to recreate the world that damn near choked the human race to death
And the scavenger hunt starts today
Big day today
Should've thrown a party
All he needs is one guy to target some scut missile with an A-bomb on it
Meanwhile
I'm free
Woo
Bombed him
And he's dead
FALL
You loved me and gave me a tongue
Learn me, please, please, my baby tongue
Call me a Christian and call me a Jew
My life for you
Surprise
A big loud one
It's time to make your stand
Come on
Time
Oh
The child
Has just begun
I songs
wn
The song must now be sung
For the world
Has now been spoken
The chance has just begun
On the wheels, on the wheels, on the wheels
Segway to the present
Morning
July 5th
South Dakota
Mind you, it's now 5am
At the roadway inn
The most disgusting hellhole on earth
For the room adjacent to it
Smelled like pee
And it was nasty
I didn't realize how thin these walls were
We heard people fighting in the other room
It's all slipping through your fingers
Everything you've made here is falling apart
Your time will end
Yes
And I'll be watching from hell with your baby in my arms
Shut up!
It's daddy, stupid!
Where's my book?
Good evening, sir
Actually, I was only kidding
Everything alright?
The crisis, uh, is being handled
Like a child, put his hands over his ears
Now get the hell out of here!
Is that all it has been?
Only three years
Seems like a hundred million
Uh, so why'd you get me out of here?
Me and some of the others are cutting you
Cut loose?
Cut loose where?
South America
It's nice
Fresh water, fresh fruit
And just plain folks
Once you want to forget they ever hooked up with
His infernal majesty
So what do you say?
I'm sticking
Why?
It's going bad here, can't you feel it?
Maybe
But it changed me, you know?
Man, you're nuts
You're probably right
The time is seven
Yay!
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
The President's next day celebration at Mount Rushmore
Ladies and gentlemen
The President of the United States
Very importantly
Very important
And
This kind of, uh, an event
He's been sick
I think his wife is gonna bring him some chicken soup
Thank you!
Oh, sir
Sir
This man is dying
Someone got a doctor
Suddenly
Now what?
It's fading away
It's going to fade away
Apparently the joke's on you
What?
In just a few moments
Your entire planet is going to be destroyed
Oh!
We tried to warn you, Magnifico
But you would have none of it
You know it is going away
Wait a minute
Wait just one day
Damn it!
Oh, my God, no!
No!
Come, come, nuclear bomb
Every day is like Sunday
Every day is silent, time gray
Like your face
Drudging back over pebbles and sand
And the strange dust lands on your hands
And on your face
On your face
Every day is like Sunday
Win yourself a cheap tray
Share some grease to you with me
Every day is Sunday
Every day is like Sunday
I couldn't help it!
I'm so sorry!
Did you see that?
Yeah, he blowed up.
Blowed up good.
Blowed up real good.
It is finished.
White magic.
That's all that's left.
The flu.
Who says it's gone?
Who knows if our babies
are going to be fine?
Are you going to be immune?
Okay!
Is anyone here not a downer?
I thought you were going to be fine.
Why this is important.
In the event of a nuclear attack,
there will be a three-minute warning,
but everything will work out
because if at the moment
that warning sounds,
you can take enough acid,
that three minutes will last
for about 60,000 years.
The white light of the explosion
will creep towards you
very gradually over the centuries
like an ice sheet.
The missiles will hang
in the sky like the moon.
Over the years,
a white hot bus
will gradually inch its way
through the front of your conservatory.
Your dead neighbour
strapped to the front
like Garfield on a bin lorry.
Many of your later years
will be spent at quite a high altitude,
watching your body gradually disassemble.
When your organs start to leave,
you will have time to wish them goodbye.
You will say farewell to them,
and they will say goodbye.
You will say goodbye to your penis
like a firstborn son
who's going off to university.
You'll wonder if there's a tear in your eye,
but it will just be the fact
that your actual eye is boiling.
As you finally die,
your consciousness will touch that of Buddha.
Someone will finally have understood you.
Buddha will have understood you,
and he will thank you for teaching him
the meaning of contempt.
Slicking out a long, frog-like tongue,
he will consume you,
and a sign will appear in the sky that reads,
You have mastered 2% of this adventure.
Oh, Jesus!
When are you going to cut me some slack, huh?
Probably never.
Hell, I'm still waiting.
Oh, thank you, Frankie Boyle,
for your invaluable insights.
And we heard a lot of music tonight, Seekers.
Peppered throughout were cuts from
The Stand by The Alarm,
Killing Jokes, I Am the Vine,
and The Virus.
That Bat Macumba was by The Tater Tots.
Rude Boy Slim was pissing and moaning
about being stuck in the loneliest room in the world.
Norm Macdonald popped in with his bat song.
Pandemic was by Telekill,
with vocals by Papa Pang.
You're Dead was by Norma DeNega.
And Every Day is Like Sunday?
That was by The Pretenders.
Uh-oh.
The ol' Bimbo Breath ain't pretending.
And she is out.
Looks to be having some crazy dreams tonight.
Oh, maybe she's having her own X-Day in there after all.
I oughta help her along with a little refresher.
Especially if something goes wrong this year.
Mercy beating.
And try to have a happy X-Day yourself, Seeker.
Wherever you're holed up.
Oh, and if it doesn't happen this year,
you can't sue the church.
We signed that waiver to Dobbs.
Goodnight.
Thank you, Susie the Floozy and WREK.
For more information, see subgenius.com.