Oh, yes, dear friends.
And tonight, it's the Atlanta Phenomicon Subgenius D Vival special, just for you.
You are about to experience the awe and mystery which reaches from the inner mind to the subgenius.
We return now with the Reverend Ivan Stang's final message of resire, panic, and acceptance.
Oh, yes, dear friends, enemies, and everyone in between.
You know, a lot of people have asked me, how can I go about accruing slack?
How can I be a nuclear subgenius?
How can devivulation fit in with my rumba lessons?
People want answers, but listen to this now, and maybe you'll learn something.
Why give answers?
When you give answers, that just leads to more questions.
Well, the answers stop here.
I won't fall into their trap.
Who are they?
You know, the you-know-whos.
They'm the people beyond the puppeteer.
All I know is, if you want to get something, you have to give something.
And while there are no true guarantees in life,
I know of a giving you could give
that would help you all on your quest for what Bob is all about.
And that is your vote.
Get out and vote.
Vote Republican.
That's right.
Voting the straight Republican ticket enhances your chances to go into trances.
Now I must be going, dear friends.
The limo from limbo is awaiting.
Did you hear that, engine valves?
Am I losing my mind?
I wonder what?
Did I just hear the Reverend Ivan Stang say to vote Republican?
We must admit frankly and honestly that something is very wrong.
Listen.
Listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen.
Now wait a minute.
I can't change attitude.
Ha ha ha.
Yeah.
I didn't apologize for nothing.
That was a little excerpt from the hour of slack.
That was, of course, the Reverend Ivan Stang you heard.
Yeah, that was the Reverend Ivan Stang running at about 80 percent.
I think it was about 80 percent speed.
I like it better that way.
Yeah, but an hour lasts an hour and ten minutes if you're playing that way.
Oh, that explains it now.
Yeah.
Okay.
Tell us tonight at 10 o'clock there's a revival.
I take it there's going to be some preaching going on?
Oh, there's going to be some hellacious preaching.
Ranting and raving and testifying.
Spouting and spewing.
It'll make what you just heard sound like some burnout on drugs.
Flashing and glowing.
Talking on a microphone.
I'll be performing.
I'll be performing my money miracle.
I'll be putting money out of hats.
Wow.
I'm going to be burning it.
And there will be an assassination, although we're going to leave the target somewhat of
a mystery until it actually happens.
It could be you, friend.
You could be the 13th apostle.
You could be the one that shows up and be that number millionth member that gets slain
and sacrificed.
That's right.
We're tired.
Raptured.
We're tired of killing our messiah.
We're going to, I mean, if somebody's going to die, let it be one of the audience members
who just innocently wandered in.
Hey, shut up!
We're supposed to run some videos or something, aren't we?
Yeah.
Huh?
God, this is horrible.
This is the way.
We're just taking up space, you know?
Didn't you read the script for the show, Dr. Drummond?
Yeah, but.
It says the videos come first and then the band starts playing.
Oh, okay.
All right.
And then the bats are released.
You got that cage ready?
Got your amido putting in the door, I hope.
Somebody's doing some sunglasses.
I'm going to go.
We're going to get some glasses around here that have fingers sticking off the side of
them and .
Hey, you guys, shut up!
Shut up!
Hey!
Are you guys ready with the machinery?
Okay, ready?
Oh, turn the lights off and run.
What if we have the tilting?
Well, I don't want to tell you.
Yeah, let's do it.
No choice but to listen closely to the first time.
Don't tell them.
Ah!
Killed it!
I believe in big knuckles.
Oh, yes, it was ankle-deep.
That's getting meaty.
Hallelujah.
Pretty soon, we're going to be all swimming in it.
Yes, and we have faith.
You just need to use it.
You just need to say it to the Lord.
Hallelujah.
.
What?
JAWS!
Anyway.
I can't see him.
Turn up expenses for the party.
NIBER
Thank you.
tonight and no not anyone in the audience can get up on stage tonight well
they can after we're finished that's right Papa Joe mama interviewed dr.
Kevorkian before he was ever famous he knew that there was gonna be a big
market in death machines for pink we're just trying to you know come July 4th
those things are gonna be selling like hotcakes because they're gonna see the
excess arriving and they're gonna know that the lucky ones blessed are the dead
but you won't know anything about I mean this is by by the day before 1998 a
subgenius membership card is not gonna still be $20 hundreds of thousands maybe
and it could fork you in death machine what's that maybe 150 hundred dollars
you know we're gonna have to make sure that we're gonna have to make sure that
we're gonna have to make sure that they're getting paid for those things
they're gonna have to pay on a blue light special so friends of course joy
now while right close by than anyone that's right money won't be before and I
know you last years of this century people will be using subgenius pamphlets
instead of ten thousand dollar bills that's another thing how do you feel
about you said you said today at the at the panel that you know you said if you
had a penny for every time you saw a stamp of jr. Bob Dobbs you'd be rich now
Now is that causing a problem or?
Well maybe I'm just confusing you.
People are making millions of capitalism on our messiah.
No, we don't allow anybody else to make any money off of it.
It's just that we'd like to make more.
Too much is always better than not enough.
There you go.
Just say Mo is our philosophy.
Mo.
Yeah, what's up with that dance?
ś we'll call a couple mucho play hitting the song a whirl
ś beginning the effects a firebooks burning tegen
ś A ground repulsive action blame the country
ś We're on top of it.
I don't want to go home
I've got to go home
A lot of what you think of me
we make you
a little subodiac
mistut party
belated
500 colors
flash in with my brain
my gem is the word
gets rid of the pain
My best friend
and recipe
and idioms
are the source
of an eternal
bunch ofr
We used toHi-Champ
while we kept
40 marbles
We st mouthed
how to paint
We got forward
aha
© BF-WATCH TV 2021
I wanna holler, but the town's too small.
Praise Sister Mary Squared and all the preachers that are here tonight.
And hail Connie.
Hail Connie.
Hail!
And praise that damn man, Bob!
I wanna hear you say praise Bob!
Praise Bob!
Oh, come on, and sound off like you got a pair.
We had some ovaries out there that time.
Yes, sir.
All right, friends, before we get going,
don't you think we ought to lead them in that solemn practice we've tried?
We've opened all the devivals up with since the first one in Little Rock, Arkansas.
If you all could just, some of you have already done this with us many times,
but if you could just bow your heads and join us in a...
Thank you, Father.
...solid moment of sacred...
...life!
Praise Bob! Praise Bob! Praise Bob!
Bob's theme song as played by Sphinx Drummond.
All right, friends, we have no idea what's gonna happen in this devival tonight.
We have not a clue, but...
Do you really think we need to know?
No!
No?
The path of least resistance is the best way to go.
Amen.
And it's the easiest way to go, by definition.
But yet, you still have to sit there frightened and fluttered away with all this care from the normalcy and your job and...
...hate your life.
...the person's probably sitting next to you that you hate.
So much.
And we'll be preaching plenty of hate, but at first, first I think, let's try something new.
I'd like every subgenius here to look at the person next to them, whether they think they look, quote, look like a subgenius or not.
Stick out your hand and say, howdy, partner.
Why the hell not?
Hey, there you go.
They're touching, see?
So wait, there's moments, there's gonna be...
Some of you will get laid tonight!
Woo!
Praise God!
We can't promise that to everybody.
No.
But yet, some of the most seemingly disgusting people will in fact somehow get laid tonight.
Thank you.
Because of the words and images that will be implanted in your mind.
The facts and feelings that will be intoned into your brain.
And some of you will get married squared tonight.
Married squared tonight.
At the very end of the night, you better have that, that everyone in this room is going to have a 24-hour short duration marriage.
Whether you want to or not.
You want to or not.
So you better think about who your spouse for the next 24 hours is gonna be.
Or it'll be a short duration shotgun wedding.
Because if you don't consummate it, it makes a mockery.
It makes a mockery of the whole institution of marriage.
It does.
It looks it in the eye and laughs boldly into the face.
So, but, don't worry, you don't have to marry a person of the opposite sex.
No.
Or the desired sex.
Or even a person for that matter.
You can marry anything or anyone you want.
And as many as you need.
Or you can marry your partners.
Some of you may have nothing better to marry than those partners in your pocket.
It doesn't have to be a mammal.
You can marry your back, I guess.
You can, many, many have married their car keys, their wallets.
Knowing that after the revival event, when the parties start up, it's going to be very
difficult to hang on to those things.
But in the meantime, dear friends, we'll try to impart something of what slack means to
you.
And I mean one thing to me and another thing to me.
But dualities are doable.
And in the church of the subgenius, we do believe that two and two do equal four, but
a five will get you ten if you know how to work it.
Preach it.
Shut the fuck up.
Now look at the soil.
I am a...
Let's see.
Oh, we finally found the script.
I'm going to show you how to do it.
Let's see what you can do.
I said make a corresponds excuse.
Let me pull this off.
Now and take it slow.
Genius craftsmanship.
Risk Sally?
You are right, and I can't deny that.
This is great, but you know what, have you been on New York working for diminArthur fails?
Sister Susie the floozy
Father Joe Mama
All the sweet little forks
Who play their top 40 hits
From the 50s
You're gonna hear about Bob
And you're gonna hear about Bob
From a man
Well, some call him a man
Others just call him
A man who, from Little Rock, Arkansas
A man who loves Bob
More than anyone has ever loved Bob
A man who will do anything
For J.R. Bob Dogs
That man, your friends
For the first time in this city
Sike!
Show your door, hug, and play!
Before I begin my official sermon
I need to point out that in order to understand one of my sermons
You can't just read on the lines
You can't just read between the lines
In order to understand one of my sermons
You've got to read above the lines
And below the lines
And you've got to read between the lines
And to the side of the lines
And across the lines
Anyway, now to begin my official sermon
I'm here to preach tonight about a religion
Ladies and gentlemen
And this religion is not just any old religion
Because this religion just happens to be
The world's one and only true religion
Of course, I'm referring to the church
Is there anyone else here
Hey Hey
The church of
John
What!!
boxing
I was born God
The church
Is like a little temple
In Peter's Church
Don.
For those who have nothing left, Don smokes Bob and his pipe.
No!
It's a lie!
Hear me out.
At least hear me out.
Are alien space monsters dull beyond all possible belief?
Are you abnormal?
Big deal.
Then you're probably just a talentless, whimpering art fag.
It's a lie!
Listen to the truth.
The normals are right.
You probably are subhuman.
It's a lie!
You are subhuman!
The Neo-Genius must have looseness.
The Church of Don and his followers exist to make mockery and parody of J.R. Bob Dobbs
and his silly followers the Church of the Sub-Genius.
What?
Traitor!
Heretic!
Listen to the truth for once.
You will die! You will burn a thousand deaths!
We exude a mockery and a hatred for all manner of subgenii,
including ranchers, clip artists, sacred scribes, head launchers,
anti-musicians, filmmakers, writers, comedians, cartoonists, and artists.
What about snipers?
Pull the eyes over your own wool, boys.
What the fuck?
He's a witch!
Face reality for a change.
This Christian came up to me at the airport and tried to talk to me about Jesus,
but I just said, I'm into Bob.
Snicker, snicker, snicker.
What's so funny?
Clinkish pseudo-intellectual white boys
making incomprehensible in-jokes to alienate all others around them.
Praise Bob.
Yuck, yuck, yuck.
Yeah!
I think that's quite fair.
Where's my 20-page?
Oh, here's my 20-page stapled together zine based on science fiction films of the 50s.
I also sent a copy of the tape to Stang,
but although my zine isn't even typeset and is hardly legible,
it's still the only meaning to my life
and the only outlet I have for all my pent-up rage and aggression.
Yeah!
For the first time in all honesty,
kill me.
Where's my bag?
Henceforth, if any of the pathetic, whimpering subgenii are heard bleating,
kill me.
This is one group that would be more than willing to take them up on it.
You can't just talk about some little infinite hate.
You've got to take it.
You've got to take a life in order to be accepted by Don.
Let's party in.
Kill Don.
The jesting of a Don is dissimilar to the actions of a junkie with collapsed veins
who must jack blood up into his syringe several times in order to get...
...a bleeding head stupid, healed head pointless.
That's ridiculous.
Don't listen to him.
It's too loud.
Hear me out.
Hear the truth.
The judge is going to take this tape.
And a technique.
.
The Church of Don is the hip faith of the 90's.
We're into real estate, banking, foreclosures, oppressing others, and other reality-oriented
financial ventures that the Church of the Subgenius seeks to ignore.
We're into frat boy kid parties, bowling, pay-per-view wrestling, and closed-circuit
heavyweight boxing.
We're into flopping in front of the TV with a beer without bothering to check or change
the channels.
Art and invention are pointless.
We like things the way they are.
We like plaid.
Don't cut up our magazines.
We might want to read them later or clip out the coupons.
We like plaid.
We're into Norman Rockwell over Salvador Dali.
We wish life could be more like a Tide or a Maxwell House commercial.
Don't bother looking for a P.O. box from the Church of Don.
We'll contact you if we decide to let you live.
.
Yes, Bob is a picture and still threatens no one.
Do people think you're strange?
You are.
.
We're sick and tired of shaving-headed acid-goblin dead dogs beating art school dropouts who
spell everything wrong, boldly surrealistic artistic worms proving absolutely nothing.
Oh, but I'm expressing my abnormality.
This has very deep meaning.
Science can remove money-grubbing, get-ahead, babbling surrealist writers.
It uses a technique called a gun.
But I'm ranting.
I'm speaking in gums.
You spit on my pants is what you did.
We can...
We can conceptualize an infinite hierarchy of monosyllabically-named male 50's pipe-smoking
satirical deities...
...endlessly parodying one another.
If Bob is a parody of Earth and the entire physical plane, then Don is a parody of Bob,
Joe is a parody of Don, Frank a parody of Joe, etc., etc.
A sample of the Lew pamphlet.
The jesting of a Lewist is so far out, so demented, it's not even English anymore.
We don't even understand what it means.
Subscribe to Lew's magazine, the stark-fisted, gitchy, gitchy, gitchy, and a goo-goo-goo.
You thought you were someone just because you were into Dobbs, but in reality you're
in the lowest chakra.
We conceptualize a transcendental yoga of hate.
You create so much hate, you destroy the entire universe.
That's neat.
But now you find yourself in a new universe of being so powerful and hateful, you can't
even get a date in this new universe.
You're utterly dwarfed.
A new universe.
A new universe where you say, I've read Mein Kampf, and someone answers, yeah, I've read
Mein Kampf, be here now, and all the rest of that love burger.
Let's all get together and just destroy this Bob thing.
You might, you might call us a conspiracy in the Church of Don, and yes, we are a conspiracy.
But we're not.
And yes, it's going to be a financial and social lockout until you guys get it together
and straighten up.
We're sick and tired of the first church of pathetic, whimpering crybabies, err, I mean
the Church of the Subgenius, wielding a ray gun finger of unrelenting financial humiliation
and a righteous, indignant moral outrage of red-blooded moral Americans.
But still, we're going to be a church of the subgenius.
Still, it's not enough for the freaked-out, value-raping, diarrhea-mouthed bastards.
Get a haircut.
Get a hair growth.
I can't even.
I'm going to break your neck.
grown playboys who watch cheap science fiction movies during the day and at night make silly
humor tapes while stoned out of their mind on drugs most people have never heard of,
using the cheap excuse that they're trying to make it as writers and conning their wives
and supporting them, as if there could ever be a market for magazines of schizophrenic
babble and copycat adolescent religious satire.
Since the real world obviously isn't interested in their cute little masturbatory in-joke
zines, they simply mail them back and forth to each other.
Thus every pencil-necked geek and four-eyed fat girl is now an editor, an artist, a writer.
We're more interested in TV Guide and Sports Illustrated.
But
I'm not.
I'm doing social commentary by standing on a stage talking about pee-pee and doo-doo
and Connie Dobbs' panties.
I'm actually making a deep satire on the restrictions our society has placed on...
Oh, shut up!
Too much is more than enough!
So maybe we did rough you up a bit in high school, but we're sick and tired of
hearing you bellyache about it!
The
We worship on Sh distances.
is.
Jayner's
right. It's a fraud.
It's a sham.
Obviously, I mean, look, we use
four letter words for no
discernible reason except we can't
think of anything else.
It's just...
Maybe Bob
is just a piece
of crap.
I mean, why not
launch a tribune over here?
We launch a tribune over here.
Go ahead. Might as well launch a tribune.
Why not?
We want everyone to chant
Healed head good.
Bleeding head bad.
Healed head bad.
Jayner's
lining up for the pot.
I guess it's a new church.
Church of Don now.
There goes Trevino.
In the name of
McDonald's.
In the name of Sears.
In the name of
Sergeant Jayner.
In the name of Walmart.
In the name of Bunch.
Great.
You let him do it.
He must be right.
Billy, what are we doing?
You people just let him
launch a Trevino head.
You mean you're letting me get away?
The church of Don.
He's been ranting about Don
for probably 20 minutes
and you let him get this far without killing him.
Where are the assassins?
I'm talking to you.
Hey, stay!
I'm talking about the word of Don
and no one's just come up here and killed me yet.
My God.
Healed head good.
Take a look behind you, Jayner.
Don!
Look at yourselves.
My God.
Okay, yeah, they come up and kill him with fake guns.
They're probably all fake guns in here.
You don't pay us enough for real ammo.
Well, great.
You see anything?
This is real.
You got to pay for it, boy.
Now this place is starting to look like a subgenius convention.
Yeah!
You start finding blood, semen, and weapons all over the stage.
Sweat covering the pulpit.
That's when it's starting to look like a damn subgenius revival.
There's not blood on the floor.
It's just not happening.
Shoot him!
No, the only true
real pipe-smoking deity is
is him.
J.R. Bob Dobbs himself.
Right, Bob!
Preach it!
He is patience.
He is wisdom.
He is loving kindness.
He is strange humor.
He is life itself.
But this church of the subgenius
is not some namby-pamby
hypocritical teachings of
peace and brotherhood like you find in the New Age or
in Christianity.
This is a certified religion of hate.
You won't steal my tape recorder.
I'll call the Lord and put you in the pen.
You won't steal that thing again.
What are we talking about when we talk about hate, children?
Are we talking about some little namby-pamby little old...
Hey!
Oh, I just hate the president.
You call that hate?
You talking about some little old hate?
Oh, I just hate myself.
We're talking about, in the church of the subgenius,
we're talking about an infinite hate.
We're talking about an all-consuming,
all-pervading,
all-pervasive,
eternal hate.
You've got to become the hate.
You've got to hate
the wind in the trees.
a bluebird chirping at dawn.
You've got to hate
a cure for cancer.
You've got to sit down, close your eyes,
pinch your fists,
furrow your brow,
and with all your might,
you've got to hate
a small child being cured of muscular dystrophy
and learning to walk again.
Oh!
Senseless hate!
The state of the church.
Someday there'll be no separation between the two.
Freedom...
See, we're talking about freedom of religion.
OUR religion.
It's been the dead guy on the stick long enough,
and they just haven't given anybody else enough slack.
I'm sorry, but they're right.
There has to be a balance.
Just as...
I mean, if Rush Limbaugh is going to be
the most popular talk show host in the country,
then we need Howard Stern.
If Jimmy Swag...
Well, not Swaggart, but whatever,
whoever the latest preacher that the media's about to tackle
is going to be on television
all over the country, several hours a day,
then the hour of slack certainly ought to be able to
blaspheme for one hour a week in 16 towns.
Uh...
Is there any argument with that, huh?
No!
I didn't think so.
What is going on?
In case you guys don't know,
we're interviewing the sort of CNN for Bob,
the Church of the Subgenius,
and I would really like to know,
do you guys see yourselves as a sort of CNN for Bob,
a sort of anti-conspiracy news network?
Anti-conspiracy...
Well, we're more like the Big Brother network for subgeniuses.
Someday there will be nothing but the hour of slack
on all stations.
All the time.
We're kind of the Malcolm X of mutants.
Destroy normality by any means necessary.
By any means necessary,
including a radio show that hurts.
The eardrums.
Makes your ears bleed.
The Church of the Subgenius.
Knowledge is power.
The only taped show that does for you
what a fifth of alcohol cannot do in the last quarter.
It sounds so good.
It hurts.
You can't be arrested for listening to Subgenius,
even though you're drunk on it.
Well, tell us about the new book, Revelation X.
When's it coming out?
What's it going to be?
We want to know.
Well, um...
It's already come out.
It's just been subverted,
and it's being censored and held back.
Suppression.
We're working on trying to get it released officially yet again.
This is the most important organization in the history of the world.
The history of the Earth, my friends.
A joke, they call it.
A joke.
Oh yeah, it might be a joke.
It might be the greatest joke ever told.
But if, and only if, Earth can make it to the punchline.
And it ain't gonna make it unless those men from Planet X get down here
and see somebody hatin' properly.
Hatin' them, but they hate, hate it some.
Haven't they achieved hate squared?
Where they hate even Jader talkin' about hate.
People are walkin' around sayin' this is a sign of the end times,
that's a sign of the end times.
But everyone should be shrieking simultaneously that
it's all a sign of the end times.
My face is a sign of the end times.
But we're reaching a, we're facing a financial crisis tonight
in the Church of the Subgenius.
My friends, we're in danger of losing the entire ministry.
We can't run this ministry on love alone.
We can't even run it on hate alone.
We can't run it on indifference alone.
If we're gonna completely and utterly eradicate the entire concept of money,
it's gonna take money.
A lot of money.
Tons of it.
Let me put it this way, if I were you, I'd give me all your money.
Why get ripped off somewhere else when you can come here?
We don't know if it'll even be the church the next morning.
That's the wonderful thing about it, you know?
I mean, theoretically, a couple of Bobs got killed last night.
Did you see the one, the one, the Bob look,
the guy who looked like Bob without a mask,
had a bat stuck across his face at one point,
at the, right in front of the stage.
It was kind of hard to see, but he spasmed around with this plastic bat
stuck over his mouth for about ten minutes.
We are prophets, and we want to be.
We want to be prophets.
Oh, you could go to some other church, sure.
You go to some other church where they only preach to the same,
where they do chicken preach to sinners like you.
Drugs and drug addicts, drug addicts, sexual perverts and sinners like you.
They're afraid to preach slack to people like that.
That's all.
But you go to those other churches,
are you gonna find preachers like Reverend Susie the floozy?
No!
Susie the floozy!
Susie, what a nice woman up here.
Woo!
Bob Tilton can sure fart,
but has he got a preaching assistant like this?
Does Bob Tilton have Sister Mary Squared, Susie the floozy,
and Princess We Are Doha?
No, he doesn't.
We challenge you, Jimmy Swagger.
We challenge you, well, Jim Baker.
Hell, that's too easy.
Tammy, where are you, buddy?
We need you in this church.
We got to go now!
I guess y'all are tired enough of watching a bunch of ugly old guys preach.
Next time we'll have a little bit from the stage between game and over, man.
Woman!
Oh, I am sweating like a whore in church.
Excuse me while I whip this out.
Over a decade ago, I classed this church, and Bob, to my face,
I slapped a gimme slack clapper sticker off my car,
and I thought I had slapped,
I hated the paint,
I sent all sorts of money to the church and only got 500 tracks.
But despite my best efforts, I couldn't get slack.
And you can think that you have slack.
Shut that up.
So I want to tell everybody about the splendor and the wonder
and that fresh, zesty, brain-douche feeling I've got ever since Connie's come in and on my life.
Yeah.
Well, not too long ago, on a chart of spiritual evolution,
I wouldn't have even rated a You Are Here squid.
But now things are different.
I found Connie, the eternal sex ceramic goddess,
the wet spill on aisle five.
And Connie searched for the love of her life.
Oh, her gaze fell upon the face of the earth.
And she sat on it.
It took Connie to tell me I had slack, all right, but I wasn't using it.
Compared to the average pink, I was doing pretty damn good.
But for the sister of the Yeti, I was a pathetic mess.
Oh, you and Connie.
Enter the picture.
She said,
Flooz, do you know the only sin in this church is the sin of slacklessness?
And I looked at Connie in the eye and I said,
Are you sure it's sin?
And it was.
Because without slack,
life is like a bolt from a handle on the inside.
And if I didn't watch my ass,
my chances of getting slack
would have been wearing as thin as Karen Carpenter in a vomitorium.
But she turned me around.
She told me.
She told me things about himself, does it not?
She taught me how to get UHF on the dial of the hash.
She taught me how to snort Slim Pass through my third nostril.
She taught me autoeroticism doesn't necessarily mean doing it in a car.
Because of Connie,
I pulled myself up on my own bra straps.
As Connie said,
Honesty is the best policy.
But insanity is a better defense.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
The benefits from looking at things Connie's way and me.
And it felt so good.
And then I realized, I thought I'd been doing the right thing.
But I've been pulling the conspiracy war over my eyes.
And I say, let's charge them another grand theft of slack.
We want our slack. We want it back.
Oh, Connie, thank you. I'm on a rampage now.
And those candy-ass, pussy-less, pecker-headed, pink-clothes-that-send-her-watch-outs.
Praise Connie!
My God, have you ever seen anything like this?
I know I just want to know what you think, but don't call me that just because I'm spitting feathers.
Woo-wee!
Man, I love this job.
This is the church.
This is what I'm here to be, dear friends.
When one's preaching partners include Sister Susie the Floozy,
a.k.a. Lois Carmen,
the nominator,
and shall we have a big hand for the swinging love corpses?
I think that was a incredible, impactful chance.
Woo-wee!
What a great...
Oh, I see a false bob walking back there.
No, no.
So we've had some fun with some false bobs over the years.
Oh, what's next?
When you and Connie first split up, I understand.
I didn't see you in the same.
Yeah.
She was running.
Never going on.
But you did.
Connie, what does your husband think about your relationship?
We're friends.
That's it.
Oh, yes, dear.
We're friends.
Some recordings there from the Genius Convention in Atlanta this last weekend at Phenomicon.
An interesting DeVival lineup in that the schedule kept having to be shortened by half every hour.
It was an interesting thing.
The original schedule called for 19 preachers and two bands.
But we were all told that we could go on all night long.
Or at least twice.
Until very, very, very late.
About halfway through the show, we found out that very late was actually 1 o'clock.
No one had ever told us that.
And the thing didn't start until 10.
So, gosh, a bunch of people didn't get to preach.
But we'll be playing tapes of those other preachers anyway over the next few shows.
And the kind of shows they are are like this show, the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
If you want information on the Church of the Subgenius and other...
things, please write to Bob.
That's all you gotta write.
Bob at Post Office Box 140306.
Dallas, Texas 75214.
Once again, that's Post Office Box 140306.
Praise Bob and let there be slack.
Huh!
U.S. Money Reserve
The U.S. Money Reserve
Our camera owns a million million bucks.
Bob's Walk Today
We would totally use your business
The U.S. Money Reserve