Test, test, test.
I'm chewing a bit of dead skin from my finger.
Cut my finger right across the callus.
Just chewed off the chunk that had died.
Nice chewy chunk of dead skin.
Oh, better spit out the dead skin.
Here comes the audience.
There's a bunch of them.
Hey, Jimmy, they're here. What do you want?
Can I get you anything?
No.
Okay.
Man, check this. What a weird looking bunch.
I love the subgenius crowd.
On our way, way to go.
Yeah, let's do it. Let's do it.
Oh, yes, dear friends.
Yeah.
We are so happy, so happy to gaze upon your mutated face.
Thank you very much for coming. Thank you, thank you.
And Jimmy will be supplying our gospel background music tonight.
We have to do a thing that's what's happening today with a lot of people.
It's called the church.
We're gonna be able to have some kind of feeling about this thing.
Of the subgenius.
You are about to experience the awe and mystery which reaches from the inner mind to the subgenius.
Power of the subgenius.
Subgenius.
And now we'd like to bring to you our one only friendly neighborhood experience maker.
This is for everybody.
Thank you, thank you, dear friends.
I'm Reverend Ivan Stang, I'll be your host, your dear prayer partner on tonight's show.
And we've got mostly music, sacred music of the subgenius coming up tonight.
Not to the brink, it will be Saturn.
Yes, that's Saturn over there.
And to your left you will see Bob.
Bob.
Bob is saying, if we must be cheated and lied to, let us be cheated and lied to for reasons.
That's a little better.
Sounds more like.
I love Slug.
That's my favorite joke.
And we can start back.
Praise and Bob.
I may sound like a Bible beater yelling up a revival in a river crossing camp meeting.
But that don't change the truth none.
I'm tired of this new age gobbledygook mumbo jumbo replacing Dobbs.
The veiled doctrine of the new age supersonic Nazi hell creatures from beneath the hollow earth.
I'm tired of undead preachers preaching undead sermons to undead congregations.
I'm tired of ministers who need three church secretaries and a German shepherd and a midget.
And what all, God only knows what all else for they can get out there and preach the gospel of slack.
I'm tired of preachers saying that God's gonna kill them if they don't raise some money.
And then God not following through.
Bob is being blamed for at least two deaths and 20 injuries.
Not even President Bush's vacation home in Kennebunkport, Maine was spared Bob's winds and waves.
One person though died near New York City when Bob threw a tree into a commuter train.
Bob Bob Bob Bob.
The way it really is in the air, which you breathe every day.
Oh yeah.
Today the league is morning and we have,
In part three of the subgenius show, radio ministry hour slack show,
we will present a part three, the sterno expeditions of 91,
the Tevonian victories in the Glen of Roses,
the ball in San Frismo, the capture of Stang,
his escape and syndication at the Battle of Lili Jing,
the College of Eohippus Revolt, and the ancient spirits of the years,
of the pities, of the spirits sinister and ironic,
the spirit of rumor in battle with the recording angels and the rest.
It's simply a mental performance.
The show is now recorded in a vast domed shaped room,
allowing for application of the Horatian formula et pictura poesis in a spray can motif.
The figures are created in a rocket away interocitor container MK4
out on the street and can be transported anywhere through the air.
Listeners are reminded to wear mopper four systems when the show is broadcasting.
Films of safety stand down drills at 0500.
No writing.
Says puzzling evidence.
Ah, yes, dear friends.
Music
The Church of the Subgenius, a parody of weird cults, has some 3,000 devoted members
who have bought thousands of pamphlets, stickers, cassettes, and t-shirts, all bearing the trademark
of Bob's smiling face with a pipe stuck in his mouth.
Don't you feel responsible for trying to help this endangered planet?
No?
Good.
The fact is, it's too late.
Everybody says I'm paranoid.
They all think I'm crazy.
They all smile to my face.
But they'd like to see me die.
And to attain this lack of Bob, a subgenius must fight a vast and powerful conspiracy,
what Pope Meyer calls the Pinks.
The Pink is sort of that ruddy glow in the cheeks you see on people who want to sell
you something you don't really need, who want to take away that which means the most to
you and give it back to you for a profit.
Oh, the system sucks you dry.
But the system is too lazy to do that.
And the system is too lame to manage even that.
I mean, the system can't even lick properly.
I submerge from time to time.
And I bob up to the surface.
I quit my job.
And I still got all this juice.
I mean, nobody's even bothered to try to suck me dry.
How has your life changed since Dobbs came into your life?
I realized that the exes are a reality and that my life is geared towards their arrival.
I redefined my own space and was able to center my being.
When I first heard Bob on the radio, he said that he could heal and told me to put my hand
on the radio so that the Bob energy could come out through the airwaves.
The only cult they want to talk about is the subgenius foundation, the church of the subgenius.
If you plan to get saved, you had better do it now.
There will be a day not in the too far distance.
The future in which Antichrist will be revealed and the mark of the beast will be introduced.
I'm going to point out that a lot of people worry about the one world government that
the conspiracy is trying to get across on us.
And we suspect that the only way to get across on us is to get the truth out of the world.
The only thing that can fight a one world government is going to be a one world religion.
And of course that's what the subgenius, the church of the subgenius is here for.
When he says you shall have tribulation ten days, he means you're going to have a maximum of trouble.
And that's just the way things are. The church is not at home in the world.
No, no, don't touch me.
Don't think I'm not going to tell him about men. What terrible things men do.
When he grows up, he's not going to manhandle any poor little girls.
He's going to turn those old men into nuns.
Now this is a crooked and perverse nation.
We have millions and multiplied millions of crooked politicians.
God put a death penalty upon adultery.
When we see millions and multiplied millions of people spending hours and hours before the television,
learn how to crack safes, rob banks, kill policemen, get divorced, and break up homes.
All these soap operas, hour after hour, warps people's minds.
That shows that they're crooked. That shows they're perverse.
That shows that they're stupid. That shows they've got warped minds.
It's the human condition. It's things falling apart.
It's fat ladies in double knit jumpsuits beating their kids in Kroger's.
Search in their head for their purposes.
It's your house, it's your house, your house, your house
Burn it down
Burn it down, burn it down, burn it down, burn it down, burn it down
There's so much paper
Burn it down
The kindling's there, the fuel for the fire
It'll glow, burn, beautiful orange-licking flames
Paper, paper, paper, paper
It's all just fuel for the fire, the big bonfire
Violence against buildings, violence against property
The ultimate act of rebellion
And I'm gonna build me a guillotine
Grab these suits by the hair, drag them by their power nooses
And chop their lousy heads off, it's French Revolution time
Burn it down, and there will be a huge famous painting
Fight messenger leading the people, yeah
Forty-three years she said
Forty-three years she was chained to a desk
Forty-three years she pushed around paperclips and rubber bands and Sirac memos
Forty-three years and she hated every damn minute of it
Now she drinks her cheap bars
Now she waits for her landlord to sell her building so he can toss her on the street
Forty-three years of all that paper, paper, pushing, pushing paper
Of being an appliance, part of the hardware, the interior decorating
Forty-three years of being no one for a paycheck
Now she's a real asset
All these buildings, all the skyscrapers
All that chrome and glass filled with all that paper
Well we could have ourselves one hella Molotov cocktail
All we need is a little gasoline and just one match
Light to match
All these people in their starched white shirts
Who act like they own the streets and the sidewalk and the world
Because they do
Burn it down
Burn it down, burn it down, burn it down, burn it down, burn it down
All these damn pets, these damn clocks, these damn termites, damn ants
All these drones in my way
I am lost in the forgotten guts of dead office equipment souls
Jesus came to the marketplace
Jesus came to Market Street and he said burn it down
All you buyers and sellers, he said burn it down
You pervert!
You pay no price
Wanna eros and defame my world
I am riding my bicycle through the den of lepers
and I am trying to remain unscathed
But me?
Well I'm just a white, slime maggot
I was fed television and Twinkies and the scroungy ethics of children of the Depression
One who can't throw away a piece of wilted lettuce
And one who buys crates of the finest just to watch it rot
We are the refuse of decaying systems
We are products of decay
But oh, the fragrance with the beauty of death
The rollicking waltz we danced
Oh come on, come on, come on
Light the match
Burn it down, burn it down, burn it down
I am man, sometimes I cry
I am man, sometimes I laugh
Sometimes I sigh
I am man, sometimes I wonder aloud
Sometimes I goof on clouds
And sometimes I goof on clouds of pillow soft with you
And sometimes I wave at people I don't know
And sometimes I wave at school buses
All full of eager fresh faces
But what's the point of me?
My, my, why, why is the sky blue?
Days are gone, I'm a man now
Instead of waving at the bus I, I throw rocks
Hoping I shatter a window or two
Causing splintered broken glass to explode
Into the terrified frightened children's faces
I'm a man now, causing horrible painful lacerations
I'm a man, sometimes, sometimes, sometimes I hate
And sometimes I, I hate and hate and hate
And, and sometimes I, I am a man
And sometimes I hate
And sometimes I, I am a man
And sometimes I'm hate
And sometimes I'm a man
I am hate
If I were a man, I'd have permission
To sleep in a doorway
Look like shit in the morning
And have a beer for breakfast
I'd be allowed to wear the same clothes
For days on end
Smell human
Have an opinion
Ride the highway without destination
Get off my roller skates and buy myself a car
I'd make a huge mess
And lots of noise
I'd take things apart
And leave them undone
I'd be a desperado
Not just desperate
Oh, oh, oh
And tired
My large fragile ego would cater my attention
I'd tell my gory tales of battle
Display my scars promptly
And never be seen or heard from again
If I were a man
Love will change the world
That's what we were told in the 60s
Love will make you happy
Love one another
Love makes the world go round
All you need is love
We've talked of love non-stop for the last few decades
Actually for the last few thousand years
Where exactly has it gotten us?
Are we one step closer to paradise?
Hardly
Love hasn't stopped war
Cured crime
Erased poverty
Hasn't even come close
Look for any sign of improvement
And I guarantee you
You'll see only the most cosmetic of changes
Window dressing
Empty symbolism
Bachelors fall to raw
But things are getting better all the time
The Lodnitz assure us
What about peace in the mid-east?
What about harmony in South Africa?
Sure
There's peace in the mid-east
In between bombings
And there's plenty of harmony in South Africa
If you're wealthy enough to live behind electrified fences
And locked gates
In reality
Things have turned to sh**
Social and moral decay is like an out of control cancer
That's taken charge
Cancer born of love
If some people are actually stupid enough
To believe things are improving
It's only because their poor brains are so been owned by love
That they can no longer think straight
Love
Sickly love
Brotherly love
Unconditional love
Cowardly love
Geek love
A love that says relinquish judgement
A love that encourages acceptance
At the expense of discernment
It's no wonder people imagine things have changed for the better
When in fact all this change
Is their capacity to accept any amount of sh**
Unconditionally
So the verdict on love is both bad and good
The bad news is
That love has turned the world into a sewer
The good news is
People have learned to love with knowledge
You say well Dawson, is there love at first sight?
Well, not really
Let me explain that
Let's say you want to grow the world's greatest plant
I don't know why, but let's just say you did
So you got the world's greatest seed
And the world's greatest sunlight
There's only one by the way that I know of
The world's greatest fertilizer
We get all of that together
And the world's greatest seed
Would we have a plant?
No, what's missing?
Time
What do we have?
Good chemistry for a good plant
What's missing?
Time
You say Dawson, I meet some guy or some girl
I've met some guy or some girl
And there was just this attraction
And I said I am in love
No, that was not love
That was chemistry
Good chemistry
What's missing?
Time
You are in love or you think you are in love
Or you know somebody who thinks they might be in love
Your greatest friend is what?
Time
Why?
Remember, love is a growing process
Any amount of growth takes time
If you're not sure, don't
If you're still not sure, wait some more
Why?
Time
You say time for what?
What am I waiting on?
Time to find out what the other person is really like
Now you can't get 100%
But like I said, you can come closer than most people
You want to ask some real hard questions
One of the first ones you want to ask is this
What happens when this person is disappointed?
You know why?
Give your marriage about 36 hours and I guarantee you'll disappoint them
What is this person like when you're cross?
Why?
Give yourself 48 hours and you're gonna cross
Is this person neat or is this person slut?
That may not seem much to you but if you're really a neat person
And you're a partner
He wants me to hug him
He wants me to feed him
That's gonna cause all kinds of stress
Including if your partner's mother has to go into the bedroom with a hand grenade and a blow torch
And when the hand grenade goes off, the room's in better shape than before it went off
And your partner says you're trying to prove evolution to see if chaos can form order
You're going to have some problems
Here's one that we always talk about
Ready for this?
Ladies, you want to know how your husband's going to treat you?
Your future husband?
Watch this
Watch how he treats his mother
That's right
Once a marriage settles down to a fireside gas
He'll pretty much treat you the way he treated his mother
Why?
We're all creatures of habit
Guys, do not
I repeat
Do not marry a woman who is hostile to her father and has not worked it through
Do not under any circumstances marry a girl who is hostile towards her father and has not worked it through and gotten healed
Why?
Because that's the way she's going to treat you once the marriage settles down to a fireside gas
She
You want to stop f***ing me
No, Kim
Think about God
She pisses my pussy
Oh, we've talked about this, but let's talk about it again
Pussy
Remember the deepest desires you have outside of being loved is what?
God
So don't get this vague talk about God
What does this person really stand with Jesus Christ?
I would say the one who's the most powerful person in the world is God
And one of the biggest complaints of Christian married women across the country is that their husbands do not lead them spiritually
Watch this one
Is this woman or this person romantically mysteriously quiet?
A person who is romantically mysteriously quiet in dating may end up a bore in marriage
Same person
She's a pussy
I'm a pussy
She is a pussy
She pisses my pussy
He once ridges my pet fur pussy
She does this all the time
I offer you more than your wildest dreams have ever imagined
You'll become the mother of a new race of gods
You'll inspire the universe
I could sweep you out of existence with the wave of my hand and bring you back again
I can give life or death
What else does mankind demand of its gods?
Mankind has no need for gods
Along with Bob, the pursuit of slack, and a conspiracy of pink,
the subgenius theology includes a vision of the apocalypse.
According to church doctrine, on July 5th, 1998,
when the television signal of Amos and Andy reaches the men from Planet X,
the aliens will unleash their wrath upon the Earth.
And so the Church of the Subgenius offers hope to a disbelieving world.
There's a lot to laugh about here,
but Reverend Ivan Stang says the subgenius message is not to be taken lightly.
Cultivate evil for the sake of evil, nothing else.
They express themselves in darkness, for darkness without leavening motive.
Now this ardent purity allows them to access a secret place
where the cultivation of evil proceeds in exponential fashion,
and with it the furtherance of evil's resulting power.
This place of power is tangible, and as such it can be found, entered,
and perhaps utilized in some fashion.
You don't believe me? You think I'm mad? Overworked?
Go away.
I'm just kind of worried about Dallas.
It was the so-called hotbed of birchism.
And it just seemed if there was any place in Texas where we'd have trouble,
we would have trouble there.
They say the cult may look weird and shocking today,
but a year from now,
when the presidential jury is going to be in Texas,
the political campaign heats up,
and people see the choices they're truly confronted with,
they will run to Bob with open arms as the only sane alternative.
Upcoming revival meetings will be held in Chicago,
Austin, Texas, Baltimore, and Minneapolis.
Oh, and there's one of those upcoming revival meetings
heard in the background right now.
Ooh, it's like a messy one.
Welcome to Celebration Florida.
Non-Caucasians, please head to the left door to sign your mortgage.
Thanks very much.
Open bar. Open now.
Here come the tanks, ladies and gentlemen.
Rolling down Main Street right now.
Thanks for the memories.
Here comes the smiling crowd.
Here come the kids, little credit card holders to be.
Here come the tanks.
Here comes the movie of the week about the tanks.
Commercial breaks every quarter hour on the dot.
Halftime, 8 o'clock.
Here comes your very own zip code.
Look, here comes Mickey Mouse.
Kids, look.
Here come the families.
Oh, here comes Philip Johnson.
Give him a hand.
Here comes his army of sycophants.
Even better, ladies and gentlemen.
And here comes the subcutaneous microchip.
Here comes the barcode on each of your heads. Thanks.
Here comes the signal flash.
Here comes the ultimate solution.
Ah.
La, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la.
La, la, la.
La, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la.
La, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la.
Well, friends, we're going to continue with the ultimate solution on side two of show.
That piece there, celebration, and the upcoming ultimate solution, the bathtub samba,
are by Reagan Spollett.
we were sent this CD
by Reagan's Pollock
I could
spend the rest of the show just
playing Reagan's Pollock although
I'll have to cut some bad
words out of it that's the problem with so
much of this great material such as
what we've been playing
before
Reagan's Pollock we heard
the women of Sodom
doing Nightmare
on Dyke Street
before that
Love Will Change the World
by Boyd Rice
from the Hatesville CD
and
we've heard quite a bit of
of huge voodoo
with a vocalist called
Dominique or a poetess or
whatever Burn It Down
and If I Were a Man or both
by huge voodoo my good
friends Bruce Grant and D.K. Jones
we also heard
I'm a Man Sometimes I Hate
by Sean Partridge
and as for the rest of what
you've been hearing well it's
just subgenius
tapes what can I say we've been
making tapes for a long time
and making shows for a long
long time this is
hour of slack number 563
I believe
but anyway
we have so many
wonderful musical
and audio moments coming up
that I think you're going to really love
when you hear what we have
to play for you
Bob sent us these tapes
special tapes Bob likes
them you'll like
them too I bet
see
it doesn't hurt me
Bob Bob Bob Bob
Bob Bob Bob
La la la la la la la la
La la la la la la la la la
Look look look look look
La la
look
Ron This i oui
Au la vingt- minimalist
And one more time
É 구독
then see you
on the next
and in the next
You
on
main
I am splashing around in all this nice hot water.
Here I am down in the bathtub.
Long ago I used to think of this dead butcher.
And this feeling like blood.
Now I think of her.
And my love for you.
I must look kinda nice.
You from above.
Sunk in a big pit.
Come on over and take a peek.
Why won't you let me touch you in your hot place.
Come on let me touch your body.
No, no, no. I don't want no, no.
Come on baby. I can do it.
Is it so hot? Don't believe it.
Let me touch you.
Ah, ah, pussy.
Seems so bad that I can't bear it.
Splashing around in the tub.
Having so much fun.
Have to have the watch.
Please don't hurt me. No, no, no.
Here it comes, you fat puppy!
No, no, no. I don't want it.
Up you, up you, up you, up you!
No, please. No, no, no. Please no.
No, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
No!
My pussy gonna eat you up.
Oh, my God.
The face of my vipro is a metal mask like the acid line
Face of Lana, turn of her ring down like the heart of the machine
Rushing my fragile skull
La la la la la
La la la
La la la la
And the cry of exorcistic rage
Escapes my lips as I develop
Revolutionary consciousness
Hey La la la Wa la la
La la la Wa la la La la la
La la la Wa la la
Haaah haa ha hor hor hor hor hor
Oh all someone be kings
Ah
Okay
Yeah?
Forward down the path cleansing with the blood of the fallen!
AAAAAAAAHHHHH!
Back!
...
We about to talk bras to the
You want me to wear a diaper You want me to wear a diaper under my pants
I never thought you'd be drinking You and Harry and Timmy and Toby and Jim
You want me to wear a diaper
You want me to wear a diaper You want me to wear a diaper
A diaper is for a little man or girl A diaper is to make poop easy, not for me
You want me to wear one and nothing else
You want me to wear a diaper You want me to stay in the closet of the hotel
You want me to wear a diaper
A diaper is to make poop easy, not for me
Make poop all over the simpler shit
Cards can't be my diaper
Eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeerrrrrr
Singer
You're putting the goggles on me
Now I can't see
I can feel my ears
I can't feel my ears
You want me to wear a diaper
You want me to show you my nipples
You and Harry and Timmy and Toby and Jim
The diaper is soggy
The diaper is snug
The room is too cold
And the night is too bright
My boogies are hard
I peed on the floor
A thread hooked the room
With the orange shed
I picked a tree
And the others
Put me down
My necks grew dark
My tie is skewed
But I can't die
Can't tie me to thecourse
Can't die
You buy me nothing
Or say I was
To the grocery store
Here is a appreciate
Just LORD!
Dieper!
Yes friends, creepy isn't it? It's got to be one of the creepiest scariest CDs I...
Dieper! Dieper!
Yeah, this is... all that I've been playing for the last 15 minutes is a band called Reagan's Poly.
Dieper! Dieper! Dieper! Dieper! Dieper!
Reagan's Polyp, dear friends, I'm about to give their address. That's from a CD, a mystery CD.
My friend, Pope Sternodox, the Pope of all Arkansas, who was one of the founding members of the great subgenius band Doctors for Bob,
has been telling me about, and sending me tapes from, this band that he is in sometimes, with a fellow named Chris Dumas, called Reagan's Poly.
Reagan's Poly.
I've played a little bit of Reagan's Poly before, but then suddenly out of the blue came this CD of said band.
Doesn't have Sternodox's name, doesn't have anybody's name on it.
And it was Joe Newman of the Rudy Schwartz Project who sent it to me, and I could swear I hear Joe Newman's voice in this thing.
Anyway, that's just a tiny sampling of the sickness, and I'm sorry I had to probably remove some bad language,
but the incredible sickness of Reagan's Poly.
Here's the address to write to for information about self-send same band.
Trash Fish Entertainment Company.
For information on Reagan's Polyp.
Trash Fish at 225 West 105th Street.
That's 225 West 105th Street.
Suite 106.
Suite 1FW.
New York, New York.
1 00 25.
And, while I'm doing addresses, I should give the address of Huge Voodoo.
You could write for Huge Voodoo Tapes.
From 10 Waverly Place, number 2.
Madison, New Jersey.
That's 10 Waverly Place.
Number 2.
Madison, New Jersey.
07940.
That's 07940.
Notice how I clearly and concisely give these phone numbers so unnoticed.
And, like the people who call the Subgenius Information Hotlines and leave their numbers,
who talk about like this up until they leave their number when they go,
200 February.
Thank you.
Call me back.
But, friends, you can call the Church of the Subgenius if you want to place an order toll-free.
1-888-669-2323.
Sounds like a joke?
Isn't a joke.
It's for real.
Get to it.
And write to Bob.
Send him your address so we can send you the free information.
The pamphlets, the books.
Well, the free information anyway.
Write to Bob.
Do it, man.
Get right with Bob.
That's Post Office Box.
I'm going to give you that number.
Post Office Box.
140306.
Got that 140306.
Dallas, Texas.
That's Dallas, Texas.
Texas.
75214.
Got that?
Box 14306, 75214.
Get right with Bob.
This is Jehovah Hates Fred.
Hello, who is it?
Hello, Burbank.
Hello, boss.
Hello, I am Herve Vichet.
I'm a little midget and I'm going far away.
I jumped off a cliff and killed myself.
No, actually, I jumped off the bottom shelf.
I'm dead.
Dead little midget.
Nobody loves me.
Not even Ricardo.
And I always said, they playing for him.
I looked out for the plane.
But they never really played.
They never really respected me.
But I'm just a little French midget.
Hey, boss.
Why don't you love me?
Why don't you like me?
I just want to be loved.
Boss.
I've traveled the world and I've seen the sights.
But now I'm dead.
I lay on my back at nights.
I am dead then.
A decomposing little midget.
I can't see the plane no more.
I can't dress in white.
Because I'm laying under the ground day and night.
Nobody loves me.
I'm a dead midget.
Hey, boss.
Boss.
No guests are coming anymore.
Hey, boss.
I was dumped by a six-foot whore.
Nobody likes me.
I could count all the people who hated me and my stubby little fingers.
I'm just a French midget.
I tried to sell donuts to make ends meet.
But all anyone wanted to do is greet me and say, the plane.
The plane.
Oh, the plane.
Even the guitarist won't respect me anymore.
He keeps playing the same chord over and over again because I'm a French midget.
Oh, no.
Depend.
Hey, boss.
The pain.
Depend.
Yes, tattoo.
It is your pain.
Hello, boss.
Goodbye, boss.
I'm dead.
Oh, how touching.
Dear friend, what a touching, touching song about a dead, dead midget.
That's a Herve Villaché by Jehovah Hates Fred that's wonderful.
It's a classic.
band with St. Andrew and Pope Fred
on vocals there, I believe. And here's
the address for Jehovah Hates Fred
and also the wonderful
Ogre Network subgenius.
What happened to my
volume test?
What the hell?
Okay, here's the
address.
Post office box
Plainfield, Illinois.
That's for Jehovah Hates Fred.
PO box 53
Plainfield
Not playing
field, but plainfield.
Just plain, plainfield.
L-I-L
6-0
4. 6-0-5-4-4
Okay?
Jesus loves you.
There's a young lady that's been listening.
She's on hold right now. Her name is Zena from
New York. She's on LSD.
I think your testimony
just may have touched her.
Great.
Let me fire up here on the board and see what happens, okay?
Zena.
Yes.
Oh, it's a young man.
Yeah.
Sorry.
Hi.
How long have you been listening?
Um, I just found your station tonight, actually.
Tonight?
Yeah.
What were you looking for?
Excuse me?
I was just flipping the radio around
trying to find some help to take my mind off
what was happening, and I came across your
words, and they really were moving me.
What's your problem?
And I'm having a problem
with LSD.
Did you hear the gentleman I was just talking to,
Tim Story?
What?
Did you hear the guy that was just talking?
No.
You weren't listening?
No, I was... No, I'm sorry.
What were you doing?
Huh?
I was trying to... I don't know. I was just thinking about
what was going on, and I'm hoping
that Jesus can help me through this.
You think so, huh?
I hope so. I've only done it once,
but I did it about
two hours ago.
I want to tell you what
I saw. I was lying in bed.
This is
frightening, but
I saw Jesus
crawling over the edge of my bed
with a knife in his mouth, and I don't
know what to do about it.
Crawling over the edge of your bed with a knife in his mouth?
Yeah.
Tim!
Yes, sir?
You think that maybe Jesus is going to cut the ropes?
He's going to change them.
He can do it.
Hey, Zena,
will you be made well tonight?
Yes.
Tim, you want to pray? You feel you don't need to pray? Should I pray?
You start, and I'll come right behind you.
Okay. Zena.
Yes?
I want you to say this after me.
Okay.
Ready?
Yes.
Jesus.
Cut the ropes.
Cut the rope.
I want to be free.
Cut that name.
LSD.
In half.
Cut that name.
Sin.
In half.
I want to be free.
Close your eyes. Lift your hand.
It's done.
Thank you, Lord Jesus.
Let the power of the Holy Ghost fall on you now.
Peace!
Lord, I thank you for your delivering power, and I just pray right now that you just touch
him where he is.
I'm seeing.
From the top of his head to the bottom of his feet.
We just come against every demonic force.
Jesus, it's a period for me right now.
I can't see him.
I can't blast it out of his body.
Jesus' name.
Hold it.
This is not by accident he's listening.
This is a God idea.
I can.
Lord, I thank you for blasting it out of him.
I pray the spirit of joy would come into his body right now.
Lord, I pray right now the spirit of joy would come into him.
Build.
Lord, I thank you that there's more like hot oil over his body.
From the top of his head to the bottom of his feet.
I thank you that he's feeling the heat going right through him.
Thank you that he's free.
That he's free.
And I want you just to get up right now and just begin to rejoice.
I'm hearing.
You're up and blasting your body.
I'm getting lost.
In Jesus' name, amen and amen.
Cena, what's happening?
Jesus wants to kiss me.
You mean he's right there with you?
Yes.
Well, be free, Bren.
He wants to kiss me.
Go ahead.
I'm kissing Jesus.
Hello?
Tim?
I think you went under the power.
Phone got cut off, so whatever.
That man's getting lost.
He's not getting delivered there.
Or something.
God.
Amen.
Well, brother, it's wonderful what God will do.
He'll do it.
Well, I was talking about God using ordinary people.
Right.
So this guy had some problems, and at least he wasn't nursing them and cursing them.
He called and tried to disperse them and rebrought a guy to reverse them.
Amen.
Thanks for watching!