Recording, everything's going fine, no trouble.
Friends, this is Reverend Ivan Stang sitting here with Princess Wee and Buddy, the new
subgenius foundation guard dog, who is a small version of the late Dammit.
We got him at an adoption center.
Anyway, this is not the show.
This is a section I'm tacking on to the beginning of Hour of Slack number 1645, because it's
really important and of timely nature.
You know, these folks in Austin who have made movies before are making a documentary movie
about the Church of the Subgenius, a really serious one.
I mean, it's going to probably be on...
Netflix and, you know, out and available as a DVD.
Probably won't be in theaters much, but it'll be in film festivals and you'll see it and
it'll be really good, I think.
I'm working very closely with them on the archival footage and stuff like that.
Anyway, the point is they need money to finish this thing, okay?
They have a fundraiser on Kickstarter.
But there's only like five days left and they haven't...
They've raised about two-thirds of the money.
That's great.
But...
But they have another whole thing to go.
Right.
There's another like...
Well, when I looked yesterday, they needed $80,000.
So if only two of you would donate 40,000 bucks.
Anyway, the way to learn about this and see a trailer for the project showing all of us,
even Lone Star.
We're going to be doing some Cowboy Dave.
You can just go to subgenius.com and click on the sentence.
They're making a movie about us.
Or you can go to bit.ly slash capital S of slack on and on has a capital O.
Or just type the Subgenius documentary into Google and probably something will pop up
about their fundraiser.
But again, simplest thing.
Just go to subgenius.com.
That's the subgenius.com front page.
And there's a movie link there.
We understand that subgeniuses may not have a lot of money, but there are some who do
and some who have some money.
And you should check out the cool rewards that come with the various levels of contribution.
Of course, they won't take your money unless they...
This is an all or nothing fundraiser.
They won't get anything.
They won't get anything if it doesn't meet the goal in five days.
But it can be done.
They've raised a hundred and...
There were $127,000 that they've raised in less than a month.
I'm sure that didn't come in big chunks either.
I mean, little chunks.
Oh, I've been following it.
Yeah, it was in little chunks.
Oh, and the funny thing was there were exactly 666 donators yesterday.
No, today it's probably 668.
I've been sending out bulk emails about it.
And I'm not sure if that's true.
A lot of us have been doing video updates as part of the fundraiser thing.
You can see them on Facebook if you follow the fundraiser.
Even if you don't donate any money, you'd be really interested in seeing what some of
the rewards are and seeing some of the videos.
We worked the comedic views of our move to Texas, which is complete, except that we're
not unpacked.
We got everything here.
And we got here.
And everything's fine.
But it's been terribly hectic.
That's why the show is late.
And that's why I'm doing this.
And it's kind of a canned show.
But you haven't heard it.
Yeah, that fundraiser is really, really important.
And I was going to say who some of the people in the movies are.
Philo and I take our shirts off in one of the promo movies.
Oh, there should be one that they're putting out today with Matt Groening.
And me doing a bunch of shtick just off the top of our heads after breakfast in Los Angeles.
That was a big high point for me.
I got to tell Matt how much I admired Futurama and The Simpsons, which was so much that when
Fox messed with The Simpsons, that was the last time I watched a show on TV.
I switched completely to the internet after that and never saw another commercial.
Oh, and Jerry Casale of Devo.
Oh, yeah.
And I think Alex Cox, the movie director that did Repo Man and Sid and Nancy and a
bunch of really nutty movies.
He's buddies with Paul Mavridis.
You see Paul and Puzzling Evidence and Lonesome Cowboy Dave did a Kickstarter routine.
And yeah, it's really been fun.
So check it out.
And now you can hear Hour of Sight number 1645.
Oh, yeah.
Which is a copy of a radio synesthesia show from about a month ago in September that Princess
Wee, you and I sat in and Dave called in.
We stayed at the station for an extra two hours.
I was saving it for this busy, busy week.
So here it is.
Praise Bob.
Hail Connie.
Amen and all women.
Who's there?
The Souljauners.
The genius.
The power.
All the soul.
What?
Now I know all about everything.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
We wrote this next song when Ronald Reagan was president.
How did we do boys?
You guys know how to play it, you know me and you guys.
The last time, the last time I saw you and you, you were watching some fans like this.
Told me you'd been there too, Ryan.
Flying program.
Step.
And we learned this song and we thought,
well, it won't get any worse than this.
Do you remember when George W. was president
and all these singers across the country
started playing Master of War?
And the idea was we were going to play Masters of War
until the Iraq War was over.
Come here, Masters of War.
You that build the big guns
You that build the death plates
You that build all the bombs
You hide behind walls
And churches and desks
We thought it couldn't get any worse than this.
Let's shake it up.
Well, I was thinking about Abraham Lincoln
And the enemies of the truth
But I could not tell
I came that deep from a job
And wailed through the loud of my feet
Out of my way
Hard rockin' on the record today
And I feel like thinking twice
With anybody who claims they're right
All the preachers, men, the politicians
All the critics and the things they write
Out of my way
Hard rockin' on the record today
And this is a call to heart
This is a call to have
This is a call to the voices and minds of the people
In every land
Out of my way
Hard rockin' on the record today
Record today
Put the money in the mattress
Put your penis lake out
Record today
There's nothing left to believe in
Nothing left to wait for
Eh...
Saying those who rely on you
We're takin' the history test
Whose baddest will do his best
Lenin the brother
Lenin the sisters
Lenin the communist
Out of my way
Hard rockin' on record today
And likewise
And everybody's doing pity
Till they burned down my boat in blue
Out of my way
Hard rockin' on a recordin' day
Recordin' day
With no money in the backstreet
Put your fingers to the count
Recordin' day
Super less than believe in
Nothing left to wait for
We are the immigrant flock
Shipwrecked on a lemon rock
From the monitor
And the mirror back
From the pressure and the quiver
And the titanic
Recordin' day
With no money in the backstreet
Put your fingers to the count
Recordin' day
Super less than believe in
Nothing left to wait for
Recordin' day
Get out of my way
Well, at least we know it won't get any worse than this.
Yeah, I shouldn't say that.
Oh, yes, dear friends.
Thank you, The Rainmakers.
Recorded June 2, 2017 at Knucklehead's Garage in, I think, Kansas City, Missouri.
We're trying to get Bob Walkenhorst to the Starwood Festival next year.
Friends, the great news is we made it to Stang Ranch, Texas, intact with all our stuff,
the entire Church of the Subgenius main media archive, and Slack altar elements.
After a truly strenuous and taxing house move.
We even stopped at a dog rescue shelter outside of Dallas on the way in.
Met this young little...
hound dog named Buddy that we'd been checking out to be our new master after Dammit.
And by gobs, we hit it off.
And now Buddy considers Stang Ranch his home and Princess Wee and myself to be his personal
monkey people.
He walks us many times a day.
Our dog is always with us.
We're still unpacking.
But basically the huge move is over.
And we can emit this new like Hour of Slack number 1645.
Finally.
Maybe a little late.
The rest of this was recorded September 17, 2017, conspiracy year, on Dr. Sinister's show
on WCSB Cleveland, Radio Sinesthesia, which follows Hour of Slack.
Only that particular night, we stuck around.
And welcome to the program, dear friends.
This is a very special edition of Sinesthesia on WCSB Cleveland 89.3 FM.
Portions of the following broadcast will be objectionable to some members of the audience.
Therefore, WCSB advises listener discretion.
The views and opinions expressed on this program are not necessarily those of WCSB or Cleveland
State University.
And you have been warned.
If you would like to jibber jabber, we're going to start early tonight because we can.
216-625-7000.
I feel like I owe you all an explanation for why I was absent last week.
I was lucky enough to get a ride to the station.
I don't have a car anymore.
I don't have a car anymore because some jackass fell asleep at the wheel and rear-ended me
at full speed.
And shopping for a car is a real pain in the bum.
Thank goodness you're okay.
My God.
That had a heck of an impact.
I've taken a header or two in my day.
What's really funny though is a cop just happened to show up as I was exchanging information
with the guy.
And I'm like, yeah, I want to file a report because this, you know, I want to get that
on the record, man.
This guy, this guy shouldn't even be driving.
This guy shouldn't even have a license.
Right.
Hopefully his license has been revoked.
He's like, oh yeah, I just kind of dozed off there.
I have sleep apnea.
Oh, and it said on his, on the police, the cop asked us who our employers were and he
put down Uber Eats as his employer.
And I'm thinking, oh crap.
Like his employer.
His insurance is not going to pay for this.
They're going to say you're a delivery driver.
Your car insurance is null and void because you're doing delivery work.
Wow.
And what's really funny is the only reason I actually went to my own insurance for it.
And the only reason I even had coverage for my own car is because last month I took my
road trip to Pittsburgh for my jeopardy audition.
And I'm like, okay, well I'm taking a road trip.
I'm going to increase my insurance for this trip.
And then I get back and like, yeah, you know, there's no sense paying for this insurance
anymore.
My car is not worth that much, but I never got around to reducing it.
So my laziness actually paid off.
Praise Bob.
I got paid for my car in just a couple of days.
I tried to sell my junker last week.
Yeah.
You know what?
I don't even think I'd fit into your junker.
It's a smaller vehicle.
It's too small.
And I am a giant of a man as tall as all my fans know.
Yes.
And, uh, but yeah, so anyway, here I am.
And, uh, one of my good friends who was also, was also a station member.
Uh, was, uh, gracious enough to provide me a ride this evening so I can be here with
you, the people.
And especially we have Keith in the studio.
We have princess.
We are do, and we have the Reverend Ivan staying.
And it is my great pleasure to have such a great group of my friends here in the studio
with me.
And now it is just as great a pleasure, if not greater to introduce the one, the only
lonesome cowboy.
Dave.
I am certainly on the air as long as I can remember.
It's been a powerful, powerful afternoon listening to these, uh, quite erudite Shermans and sermonettes
by Reverend We are weird.
Uh, of the, we are dope.
Remember I haven't stayed with the church of the subgenius and also of yourself, sir.
Fine.
Fine for yourself to elucidate what needed to be said and done at this hour of our daily
critical needs.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Dave.
Give us this hour.
Our critical needs.
And forgive us our bun heads.
Dog.
Dog is great.
Dog is good, but dog cannot have our foot.
That's another Benedict women.
Yeah.
I remember when he was just a wee pup himself.
He was a short stalwart guy, kind of 350 pound yeoman looking.
Yeah.
I remember.
I think to me he was just a, he was a snowflake too.
Isn't that what you call them staying because of your strong conservative views?
He called me a snow.
Snowflake, I'm going to breathe on you and you going to melt.
The girls are picking on me again.
I was crying.
I was crying on the weekend.
Anglo white wasp men never get any slack.
All the minorities pick on us all the time.
The snowflakes are mean to us.
Me.
Did you know that this is a really true fact, that 40 percent of the election money that flows in the United States during any election cycle, especially presidential, is considered 40 percent of all the critical.
Money that comes into donations can count campaign funding and stuff like that is run by less than point zero one five percent of the population.
Meaning it's like five guys.
They make some tasty burgers.
Mr. Exxon, Mr. Mobile, Mr. Shell.
And, you know, those.
Yeah, the climate scientists.
Yeah.
That decide who votes for what.
And you know who the best climate scientists in the world are?
A.M. radio host.
They know more about the weather.
Especially since like when they were in 10th grade, they thought they might want to be the weatherman on TV.
Honestly, I have to agree with you there.
Rush Limbaugh knew that he was going to be perfectly safe in South Florida.
And the only reason.
He evacuated was for security reasons.
All right.
Yeah.
Because nobody cares about national security more than him.
Right.
Well, he produces a lot of the nation's insecurity.
I would test.
He manufactures it.
What a swine.
So bright and so pink.
He does sound a little bit like Porky the pig.
I won't say the full name because I think Warner Brothers was brought up.
By Warner Sisters.
At least I might get something wrong.
And they'd have to.
The only Warner Sister I know of is Dot.
Dot?
Yeah.
And then there was Dot Warner?
There was Yakko and Wacko and Dot.
You're not allowed to make me find these humors.
Because I do not.
Dot.
Dot?
Dot Matrix.
Dot.
Polka Dot.
Matrix was her married name.
Oh.
Okay.
Well, I want to get back on the subject of climate change.
I heard that liberal scientists caused all those hurricanes in order so that
Hitler could take away our guns.
Oh, I see.
Not only that.
They would convince everyone that there was such a thing as climate change.
But we were unaware.
I'm sorry.
My point is that.
Not only that.
But a sheriff's office.
In Florida.
Was actually issuing a public statement.
Warning citizens of his county.
Not to shoot at the hurricane.
And what kind of.
What kind of.
What are you.
How are you trying to ruin America.
When you're telling us we can't shoot at hurricanes.
They hate our freedoms.
Well, this guy.
This guy started posting.
He.
This guy.
This guy's suggestion about doing that went viral.
And the sheriff was wisely concerned.
That people were going.
To stand there firing into the high wind.
Which of course.
The bullets are going to come down somewhere.
And what.
Got your baby's name on it.
May.
I just.
I can't.
I cannot approve.
I cannot approve of shooting at anybody named Irma.
That's.
That's somebody's grandma.
You can't shoot.
Yeah.
You're not supposed to do that to women.
You're supposed to hit them with golf balls.
Knock them down.
With golf balls.
You don't get that.
No, I don't get that one.
It's a.
That was.
That was posted very recently.
He showed Trump.
Teeing off into Hillary.
Crimpton.
There's no such person as Hillary.
I mean.
This.
Hillary.
Martha.
Plimpton.
Trump.
Teeing off.
Peter.
Frampton.
Hillary.
Clinton's back.
Right.
In other words.
A funny image of a man knocking a woman down.
Yeah.
Nothing funnier than that.
What do you tell a woman with two black eyes?
Nothing.
You already told her.
Two golf balls for one ball.
Lock her up.
Yep.
The next time he makes his way on down to the local airport.
Just.
You just wait outside.
Ask him if he can have you those party flavors that they have on.
Exam.
Our president.
What's.
What's he calling?
Blue Book one or something.
Or.
Air Force one.
Yeah.
That's the one they've had.
Remember when they had him in the waistcoat and the.
And the body strippings.
And the.
And the um.
The uh.
Straight jackets.
Speaking of jackets and the president.
I just saw a picture recently of him meeting with somebody in the Oval Office.
And in a photo op.
And uh.
His pants.
And his suit pants and suit jacket were mismatched.
What?
Well that's no way.
That's good.
It would.
In pink.
Lock her up.
He doesn't even know how to put a suit on.
She switched his clothes.
Just to embarrass him.
He's wearing a suit.
There's no way he's going to wear those.
I'm fine.
Come on.
Hillary's still sneaking around that White House.
I still maintain.
Tied his shoelaces together.
And short sheeted his bed.
I still maintain.
This is not fair.
They're picking on us conservatives.
They're picking on the wealthy.
They're picking on us rich people.
We could buy away everything with a suit, too.
With more suits.
My existential angst nausea.
No.
I still maintain the only reason that Donald Trump has become so anti immigration in recent
years.
Because he's getting rich.
is because Melania is getting older
and he wants to be able to deport her
so he doesn't have to go through a messy divorce.
Ah.
You know, I mean, she's getting up, you know,
I mean, like, you know, once, I mean, he said before,
it's very hard to be a 10 when you're over 40.
So, I mean, you know, he generally,
every 20 years or so,
he'll trade his wife in for a newer model.
You're out of here, Tabby.
So, yeah, I mean, that's why he's anti-immigration now.
Melania?
Let somebody else walk up and grab you by the...
I bet Melania probably has family in Cleveland.
Free Melania.
Oh, yeah, sure.
We're like the biggest Slovenian city outside of Slovenia.
Yes, the Slovenian Hall, Polka Hall of Fame
is in Euclid at the old shore high school.
Like, I mean, this is a long time ago.
It was like 15 years ago,
but I went to New York and did a tour of the UN building
and there was this guy from Slovenia in the tour group
and everyone's like, oh, where are you from?
I was like, oh, and I mentioned I was from Cleveland.
He's like...
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Everybody in Slovenia has cousins in Cleveland.
Yeah.
I was surprised.
So maybe Cleveland will have to become a sanctuary city
for Melania Trump.
There are a bunch of wineries out in winery land
that all have Slovenian names.
Maybe, maybe.
There are a bunch of wineries in all of Slovenia.
I don't know.
216-687-3515 is the number to call
if you'd like to get on the air.
We do have someone else trying to get on the air right now.
So why don't we bring on...
another victim here.
You're on the air.
These jokes are so old.
They're the ones my grandmother...
Well, hey, man, I recycle my jokes
because it's good for the environment,
including that one.
So anyway...
I didn't really hear any jokes.
Were there supposed to have been some jokes happening?
I don't know.
I'm pretty...
I'm a very serious person.
I did say something that I read somebody else say
about six hours ago.
So that was an old joke.
Six hours old.
It was on the internet about six hours.
Free Melania was the phrase.
Oh, so there was...
Some movie stars...
That wasn't real also.
Yeah, some movie star was actually...
had that idea and was promoting T-shirts
that said Free Melania.
Well, just remember,
even though it came out six hours ago,
the guy who just called all angry and bitter
and stuff like that,
he didn't get it out until just now.
He just listened to it.
Yeah, well...
That's stupid.
Take it all back.
I don't mean a damn darn word of it.
I have no regrets.
Maybe it seemed like somebody
had some sort of pastoral hierarchy
where he just gets to be the goblet king
and pass down the secret wisdoms
in his own urine sack
like he was some sort of ancient Navajo hunter.
But I know it's all untrue
because I believe it's a lie.
Therefore, it could...
Squid...
Pro...
Quo...
Um...
Canker.
Yeah.
You mentioned the goblet king.
Who, me?
Yeah.
Oh, I don't know.
It's just there was an impenetrable thought
that made its way into the backyard of my vacuum once.
I've got two of those in my mouth right now
that are really irritating me.
Little lumps that are sore.
But...
Just appeared.
Yeah, but you often...
Do you get that often?
My tongue...
The unfairness.
No, I don't.
My tongue won't leave them alone.
It's driving me nuts.
I just showed Princess Leewa.
See?
What color is it?
Is it purple?
Pink.
The bump.
There's a pink bump on my lip,
on the inner lip.
Mm-hmm.
Can...
Listeners, can you...
If I scrape it against some microphone...
It's got that foam rubber on it.
It wouldn't be the most disgusting thing
ever done to that microphone.
Oh, tell him that
These microphones are like...
These microphones are like
everything in a hotel room.
I once had a guest up here,
a young lady who works as a stripper
who was once banned from X-Day,
and she was my guest on this program once,
and that very microphone
into which you're speaking, Reverend Stang,
at one point during the program,
she farted directly into that microphone.
I tell you, everything...
These microphones have been everywhere
that anything in a hotel has been.
Yeah.
In other words,
up somebody's something.
216-687-3515
is the number to call,
and we have another caller here.
Oh, and they hung up.
Wasn't that your hero,
the other...
the podcast guy?
It was his buddy that said that,
his buddy that he got...
I can't think of his name.
No, Jonathan Colton has a co...
has a friend...
He's a co-ranter.
Paul Rogers something.
I can't remember anyway.
He was the one who came up with that.
Yes.
Which I already forgot.
Oh, yeah, everything...
Everything in a motel...
You know, I don't like Jonathan Colton.
I...
Philo wouldn't let me play that stuff.
I wanted to like him,
but he quickly got on my nerves.
My only familiarity with him is from
Ask Me Another at NPR.
Oh, I used to play select stuff by him
for about a year.
I was playing him every week.
He sounds like...
He sounds like a goddamn hipster.
He just...
I don't know.
Isn't hipster just what hipsters call other hipsters?
Hipster?
You have to cite...
Only hipsters even use the word hipster.
Okay.
Yeah.
Maybe you're onto something.
I don't know.
He sounds like the kind of guy
who is kind of dorky cool,
but whose ass I could kick.
Well, that's the difference.
You just described yourself and most of my friends.
I could kick most of their asses.
Yeah, you sound like you're mentally disturbed, too.
But most of us...
A lot of people could kick your ass.
Even though you're...
You know what?
The only friend of yours I've ever met
who I thought could take me was Legume.
I think he's the only one I've ever met who could...
But that was before his open-heart surgery.
Yeah, he had a quad...
He had a quintuple or whatever.
You haven't...
That's because you haven't met...
You get stuck in New Jersey on one of those things
and you can never get off of it.
He's never met Reverend Dr. Sinister Killer yet.
Oh.
Also, Reverend...
With a name like that, I like him already.
Right.
I figured.
I mean, come on.
How can anyone in this room put down Jonathan Colton
for being a smarmy hipster?
I don't know.
I don't like the way his voice sounds.
And I don't like the...
Goodness.
I don't like the songs that he chooses to play.
And the fact that he was...
He does original songs.
The fact that he was a whiff and poof.
Oh, that's it.
What the hell?
Is that the thing?
The thing that bugs you?
That's part of it, yeah.
Well, I've been to Burning Man twice,
so I guess I should just leave the room
because I'm too...
But you went to Burning Man before.
It was cool.
No, you're just a poof doll.
Oh, there was already...
There were 30,000 people there in 2000 and 2001
when I went.
It was already not cool.
Except I still consider it the best party
I've ever been to,
and I'd go back in a second if I could.
So you went there around the same time
that I first heard about it.
Actually, I had...
I went there about the same time
that my friend's father...
Milo and Puzzling Evidence
were getting tired of it after 15 years.
They had been involved in it
from when it started...
Well, Puzzling Evidence
was probably the first one in 1980.
But they were saying it was sold out by then.
Well...
But he was also doing...
It was popular.
It got popular.
I went to the Burning Corn Festival
around that same time
that you went to Burning Man.
I went to the Burning Corn Festival.
Did you get rid of your corns?
No, I ate some corn,
and I saw a gigantic paper mache
ear of corn set on fire.
It was hosted by Trademark, actually.
Oh.
Trademark.
Yeah.
He did radio at Burning Man
for years and years.
He's always been going.
Dr. Hal is always there
running the fashion show
and usually singing in operas and things
while buildings burn down around him.
And he's like 79 years old.
Yeah, if he's black and old enough,
he can live 79 more years.
And when you're the emcee
of the fashion show,
think what kind of people
are trying to bribe you
into judging their costume
and, you know, pump you up.
Like you have a ball constrictor
wrapped around your neck.
Tall, naked girls.
Leggy models.
Yeah, tall, leggy models.
Dr. Hal's actually done pretty well
with long-legged models.
Oh, you'd be surprised.
You'd be surprised.
We get all kinds here.
By the way...
It would look any better
than having...
No kinds at all.
He's a hound dog.
Nothing.
Dr. Hal Robbins, he's a hound dog.
Oh, yes, he is.
Oh, creepers snooping around the back.
Jonathan Coulton.
He's a backdoor man.
Sidekick.
Dr. Hal is a backdoor man.
Is John Roderick.
I'm not kicking any man
ever seen here.
Oh, John Roderick.
That's the guy you're talking about.
Yes, he's the one that said...
The guy that originally said
that everything in every motel room
has been up somebody's...
You know.
You just said that previously
in the last commentary
and you forgot to remember it.
No, I found that the originator...
You should remember the guy's name.
John Roderick, yes.
I got his full name.
He has a pretty funny show
that sounds kind of like
this one does.
The little brain in my pocket found it.
He's also the antichrist
if you guys would even care
to look into the subject
a little bit.
Just a little bit faster
than the nose on your own butter.
He is and could be...
possibly tomorrow.
The antichrist.
Who couldn't?
Anybody could.
Yeah, that's not the point.
The point is whatever I just said
makes more sense
than what you just said.
Unlikely.
It's not really hard
to make much more sense
than what we've been seeing.
That is true.
Bear that in mind.
Don't talk about bears
on this show, man.
Yeah, antelope that.
Yeah, man.
Antelope that.
Don't bear it in mind.
Antelope it in mind.
Don't even use the word bear.
You did it.
Oh, sorry.
I'm sorry.
Especially the conditioning
of the studio there
down on the lake area
where the bears come swimming
right up out of the lake area
and just come walking past
little Chinatown
or our new old Chinatown
or Carnegie or wherever
that is.
That's a pretty decent hike
from the lake to Chinatown
here in Cleveland,
but yeah, for a bear.
He's talking about
Ashtabula.
I think, isn't he?
No, I was talking about
Chinatown.
It's underwater, dude.
I'm not making
a commercial statement,
but near Dave's Supermarket.
I'll have pain there.
You know, the
Lonesome Cowboy Dave's Supermarket.
I hear you can get
cheap heroin there.
Man.
Oh, yeah.
I recently heard the song
by the Easter Monkeys.
I bought it at the supermarket.
It was actually about
the Dave's in Chinatown.
And now they're moving it.
And now they're moving it?
Yeah.
Where am I going to get
my cheap heroin now?
I think I'm moving it
like 55th and somewhere.
Oh, man.
Where do you get
the cheap Adderall?
That's all I care about.
I've only ever
done Adderall once.
You beat up about
half of my students.
Hmm?
You beat up about
half of my students
and take it from them.
Just steal it from them.
Yeah.
Just knock them down.
I hate to treat
kindergartners that way, though.
They're high school students.
They could take it.
Take it, go get more.
They beat me up
and take my heart medicine.
I'm sorry, Dave.
What did you say, Dave?
I heard somebody mention
the Easter Monkeys
and I just wondered
what the context was.
We were talking about
the Dave's supermarket.
Looping forehead.
We were talking about
the Dave's supermarket.
That was a good band, too.
And they had a song
called Cheap Heroin
that mentioned that
they bought it
at a supermarket
and the supermarket
in question was
the Dave's grocery store
that is now relocating.
Okay.
The Easter Monkeys, yes.
Yeah.
So, I guess back
in the early 80s
people sold heroin there.
Actually, they probably
sell it there now.
That's funny.
I've done drugs
you've never heard of
and I've never even seen heroin.
That's Charlie Ditto's band.
Yeah.
That's one of Charlie Ditto's
early bands,
the Easter Monkeys.
I bet Keith knows
more about them than I do.
A little bit.
Probably more than you,
but probably not
nearly as much
as other people.
Mm-hmm.
It's a band
I only know about.
That was your brother's.
We have Charlie Ditto's
fingerless gloves.
No.
We don't?
We throw them away.
We throw them away?
Yes.
He left his
worn-out gloves
at our house
after we hired him
to paint our garage.
Oh, no.
He did a new roof
That's right.
He put a roof on it.
He didn't paint it.
Somebody else painted it.
He put a roof on it.
Roofing is a difficult job
and he did a beautiful job at it.
He was playing
punk bass the whole time.
He was slinging shingles
and hammering them down
while playing punk bass.
I like to take roofies
before I do roofing.
Yeah.
Well, that's because
you're part of generation.
You're a millennial
transgression.
You know what?
I'm technically
not a millennial.
Well, I know,
but you're still
I'm a little too old.
You're a millennial.
Yes, you are a little
like only eight years too old,
but still.
What do you do
before you do roofing?
Roofies.
Roofies before roofing.
Mm-hmm.
Actually, I think
most of the roofers
are Adderall.
Probably.
That's where I need to go
is just ask the roofer.
The only time I ever took Adderall,
I was a freshman in college
and the dorm I was staying at,
this kid was prescribed Adderall
for his ADHD
and he wouldn't take it
because it made him tired,
which is a sign
that he probably needed it.
So, yeah, he would gladly sell it
to anybody who wanted it.
And I had been slacking.
People tell me I'm a smart guy,
but let me tell you something.
I've taken three or four math classes
in college
before I finally dropped out.
I have failed.
I've gotten an F
in every single math course
I've ever taken in college.
Well, you know...
Yikes.
Yeah.
That's because you didn't
take the Adderall, man.
Well, no, I did one time.
The very first college math course I took,
I slacked off the entire quarter
and then the day of the final,
I realized that
I was in deep trouble
if I didn't pass the final.
And so...
On the day.
I bought some Adderall
from this guy in my dorm.
What's his phone number?
It's probably not even valid anymore.
This was almost 20 years ago.
But...
So I take the Adderall
and then it kicks in
and I start just doing
all the homework problems
in the math book
from I started chapter one
and I get all the way through it
and I'm like,
yeah, all right, math.
Yeah, math.
Yes!
Math!
I get it!
Yes!
Math!
You don't have to take
the whole Adderall.
And I got all the way through it
right up until the last chapter
and I seriously did
every single practice problem
and I got them all right.
I'm like, yes, I get it!
I get it!
I'm ready to take the final!
And the Adderall was still in effect
and so it was like an evening class
so I went to the class
to take the final.
I didn't get to the last chapter
but I figured, okay,
I got everything but the last chapter.
Oh, no.
The final was all on the last chapter.
And I'm sitting there
taking the test
with the Adderall still in me
going, math!
Yes!
Math!
No!
So, yeah, that was the first
and last time I ever took Adderall.
A little mouse speech
in the maze, too.
I love tales of self-inflicted wounds
like that.
I've had so many similar instances.
One time I saved up
5,000 U.S. American dollars
for a test.
So I could go to a delicatessen
that I always dreamed I would go to
if I was rich and stuff like that
because I was almost a street person.
When you are rich,
you don't go to the delicatessen.
The delicatessen comes to you.
Right.
In the form of a dumpster box.
In the back with an opening
that says,
Pick up on Tuesday.
Ah, the life of the U.S.
Bossman didn't...
Rick...
I have no idea who was doing that.
Sure, Dave.
When it wasn't lonesome cowboy Dave,
I can tell you that much.
And how does this make you feel?
It was like a voodoo loa.
You know, like El Candoor
or Django.
Or any of those, you know,
Speed Lieutenant, you know, the airplane pilots.
I've forgotten the names of a lot of those voodoo saints.
But they're very colorful.
How come nobody's done a cartoon or a comic book about the voodoo?
You know, those weird character saints that go with voodoo.
I just saw somebody did a tarot set of those.
Somebody at Starwood.
Taliesin showed me.
I remember a really bad joke about a voodoo dildo.
Go ahead.
I need to bone up on my voodoo.
Bone up right after dildo?
Really, dear?
Yeah.
I don't get the connection at all.
I bet you don't.
I don't.
No.
I wouldn't imagine you would.
You're too innocent.
The old guy used to call him a corn sucker.
Right.
It's waifu.
Waifu.
If you had the same idea as he did, you'd be in prison right now or in a mental institution.
How do I know I'm not?
How do you know you're not in a mental institution?
In prison, in a mental institution.
You are at this current moment in a prison, in a mental institution.
Now, the problem we've got with a lot of the people here, a lot of the inmates,
is they really, really don't understand their position in the dichotomy.
The long-handed spaces in between.
And so they think they're at some sort of assisted facility where living is everything.
And bohemian behaviors-
Well, they are at an assisted living facility for people who hallucinate that they're on
a college radio station.
Yes.
It's a very common delusion.
You see these homeless people shuffling around in the streets.
Shuffling along, muttering to themselves, saying things like, you're listening to
WCSB.
WCSB Cleveland.
Cleveland.
Yeah.
And they're, you know, eventually they get taken in and locked up.
There's rooms full of people saying, you know, portions of the following broadcast may be
objectable, mumbling.
Yeah.
Hard on the tooth too.
The really bad ones sound like the hour of slack.
Yeah.
The quick, strong, lonesome cowboy Dave as the mumbling crazy guy.
As well as the scum's behavior of the ancient ones.
Well, it wasn't my fault.
It was all politics.
You know what I mean, Stan?
You know what I mean, Dr. Sinister?
Everyone's blaming politics these days for all their problems.
Yes.
Well, shouldn't they righteously do so, though?
I mean, really, when you think about it.
I mean, I think it's a good thing.
Everybody does have an axe to grind.
Some of them don't have too many of them.
Yeah, well.
You know, like, if you're born with eight foreskins and three handles, you're not going
to get around, like, you know, lolly the trolley or something.
We inherited two axes.
We need to get rid of one of them unless we're both going to use them.
Hey, Princess Freya.
See, the thing is, I might be the only guy who does not have an axe to grind because
I spent all my youth.
Let's get him.
I spent all my youth grinding.
My axe.
You did not just ask me that.
You did not.
I spent all my youth grinding my axe and it's as sharp as it's going to get.
And then I finally just gave up and stopped caring about things.
But I still have that axe.
And it is pre-ground.
Yeah, I understand that.
If you wanted to.
It's up to you.
If you decide one of these days you're done with your not grinding ways and that you become
a peaceful platnick, you can just grab that axe and grind it.
I won't have to grind it until I have to use it.
I've never had to use it.
Exactly.
But it's ready.
I used to keep my axe real sharp and I used it every chance I got.
Now it's just this rusty old thing.
I might be lucky if I've rubbed something to pieces with it.
A lot of times a bunch of handle is missing and it looks like it's about ready to fall
down past where the, you know, where everything would be.
We might rub this log in half.
No, man.
I might just go up and pick a new one.
Well, you were busy grinding your axe.
I studied the blade.
Oh, wow, man.
That is so succinct and so sublime.
It reminds me of that.
Could you repeat that?
No, I never had to use the axe.
I just handed it to her.
Whenever I had to cut down a tree, I would just hand the axe to a subgenius and say,
Now, don't cut down that tree!
Whatever you do with this axe, don't cut down that tree!
And about five minutes later, they'd come back to me going,
You did tell me to cut that tree down, right?
Right. It sounds like Tales of Huckleberry Dingleberry or Tom Sheridan or whatever his name was.
Yeah, but that really is how it works.
That's how you get things done in churches, subgenius.
Hand them a pencil and a tape deck and say,
Don't come up with a book!
Don't start a radio show!
Whatever you do.
Don't whitewash this fence.
Whatever you do, don't rub the Buddha's belly.
Don't you dare throw me in that briar patch.
Don't give me any of that Adderall.
Dang, sounds fixated a little bit.
I'm sleepy.
Doesn't he? Doesn't he?
I'm tired, man.
I've been packing books, fudge, all kinds of stuff all day.
Packing a mean one.
I really honestly did pack all of the fiction paperbacks that I own into nine cubic foot boxes.
You know, you didn't have to dirty that statement with saying that you packed fudge.
What you did was honorable.
Look, we're working on our kitchen, too.
I packed rice, fudge, dry beans.
We packed all kinds of stuff.
I don't get these.
I know.
They have to assign these, you know.
Dirty stuff.
It's all dirty stuff.
Seeming underbelly things, yes.
I think it's sexist.
Yeah, I think it's paramilitary on the very least.
That's assault.
I'm triggered.
I can't do my job anymore.
I'm going to have to sue you now.
Did you ever have tomato popcorn soup?
You made my...
It's a solvent.
It's made of human beings.
Tomato popcorn soup?
I thought my mother invented that.
What?
Swirling cream, right?
You put popcorn in tomato soup?
Yes, my mother invented eating cream of tomato soup with popcorn.
Yes, that was her invention.
Popcorn in the soup?
Yes, toss the popcorn in like crackers.
Sort of, it does, but it's good.
It's fun.
Yeah, I took to putting...
She can handle popcorn.
I took to putting ketchup on popcorn for some years.
And it would, in fact, make the popcorn mushy.
That sounds really disgusting.
I also used to deliberately let my Captain Crunch soak in the milk for 20 minutes.
Oh, that's so disgusting.
So that it turned into...
You and your cereal mush.
If you don't do that, it tears up the roof of your mouth.
You're no kidding.
Exactly.
That stuff's made of spun glass.
Captain Crunch can really cut you up if you don't soften it up.
I'm surprised there hasn't been a class action lawsuit against the maker.
In Great Britain, this is really true.
Mr. Crunch to the stand.
He's not even a real captain if you look at his uniform.
I can't remember exactly what rank he is, but it's definitely a rank below a captain if you look at the insignias on his uniform.
Completely false credentials.
Yeah.
Stolen valor.
Did anybody ever hear of his habit when he was in the British Empire of drinking coffee with ketchup in it?
Next they're going to tell me there's no Chef Boyardee.
He's just a character on a label.
Actually, there's...
There was a Chef Boyardee, and he was from Cleveland.
Oh, really?
Yes.
Chef Boyardee did land here on the wrong boat.
What kind of a name is Boyardee?
It sounds like a Weard-o.
It was Boyardee.
Boyardee.
It's B-U-O-R-D-E.
B-U-O-A-R-D-E.
I used to eat a lot of Sylvia's canned southern cooking before they made me.
If you stop eating sa-sa-sa-sa-sa-salt.
Salty canned things.
Yeah.
I wonder if Syl- I believe that Sylvia is real.
Yeah, she is.
Well, Sylvia is real.
As real as in your mind and your heart you don't want her to be.
Sylvia Israel or Sylvia Palestine?
And there's a little bit of her in every can.
Yeah, that's the one I'm talking about.
The creationism one.
The one who knows to make turnip greens with actual real human beans.
Yeah.
Human beans
Human beans and rice
Yeah sure whatever
I didn't really mean that because
I fell asleep but I woke up in the middle
Of a fitful distraught dream
You know I am a dyed in the wool Yankee
But I do enjoy turnip greens
Mustard greens, collard greens
I will make them myself
That's a good eating
Me too
I enjoy this social
Food that is very very
Reliable to me
But nothing
Is better than taking an old fashioned
Bowling bag into your local
Supermarket and just start beating people
Over the head until the police come and shoot you
That's even better
That's one way to go
When I was growing up I thought that
Soul food, I didn't even start hearing
That phrase until maybe the 70's
And I
Thought it was some kind of exotic thing
That black people
Ate and I didn't know what
Was a good example of soul food
Finally
After I moved to Cleveland
I learned
That soul food was
In fact exactly what
I had been eating most of my
Life, my father is from
South Carolina and learned
His cooking from
The family maid
And taught it to
My mom who also
Then taught it to me and actually Joy
Of cooking is full of that
The same
The same recipe so it was
I grew up thinking it was called
Southern cooking
Because I came from
People who did not believe
That there even was a soul
That's how white my
Family is, they don't even believe in souls
You know how white my high school
Class was? How white were they?
I graduated from high school in 1999
And guess what song was not our class song
What song?
By Prince, yeah
That was not our class song
Wow, that's white
That's really white
Ha ha ha
Why, why, that's very
Silly too
It's not stupid
Somehow
But I look down on myself in shame
You know I look past the cross bars
And the clavichords and the
Collar bones and all the
Other things that we're forced to eat that remind us
Of chicken pie and I think to myself
What a wonderful land
This America is, our home
Our native land, oh yes
Then I sit down in my chair
For a short while
Eat some thunderhood pie and start crying
Like a baby
And I just want to shoot everything in sight
For some reason, but I don't know what I'd shoot
Them with because I'm non-violent
That's because you're an American Dave
You'd want to kill to make America great
Yeah
Kill, kill for the love of killing
Kill for fun, kill for the love of killing
Kill to stay free, kill to make America great
What's a thunderhood pie?
Kill for Jesus
Kill for Kali, kill for Bob
Kill for fun, kill for Jesus
What's a thunderhood pie?
Kill to make America great
Kill, kill, kill for peace
Oh I left off the again
That's very important
Kill, kill, kill for peace
Near and far and Middle East
What's so funny
About peace, love and understanding
Oh I left off the again
What's so funny about it
The fact that Elvis Costello was singing that
That was written as a sarcastic
Mean song
Meant to be sung in a
Simpering folk music way
And Elvis Costello
Looked at it and went
Actually this would be a really good song
If you do it sincerely punk style
So he took something that was written to be
Smarmy and cloying
And triacly
And by changing the beat
To its opposite
He made it into quite an anthem
I never liked his words
Well you said triacly
I actually can
I know all the lyrics to his first three albums
I know Elvis real well
Both Elvis's
He's waiting for the end of the world
Waiting through the end of the world
Waiting for an important distinction
With the whole
I never thought
They'd put me in the
Their
The
And
Gainsquiiiiid
I never
Thought
They'd put
That was all he was good for was three albums,
and he became a Cole Porter gesture,
gesticulator, you know,
one of those old-fashioned guys with a big hat, you know?
And, like, Joe Jackson kind of went in that direction,
but he was more successful at it.
I think the greatest work that Joe Jackson ever did...
The greatest work that Joe Jackson ever did
was his duet with William Shatner
covering Common People by Paul.
Yes.
Oh, I just remembered something from my past
that was impressive to me at the time.
I've got a magazine article that mentions...
It was about Elvis Costello and the Attractions,
the other fellows in the band,
and it mentioned that one of the Attractions
was reading something called The Book of the Subgenius.
Oh, wow.
Get out of here.
Well, that would be...
No, think about it.
That would have been 1983
when Book of the Subgenius was very first published.
In 83 and 84,
we were the coolest thing in San Francisco
for about one month.
Then it's San Francisco,
so, of course, it moves on to something else.
But we...
Fickle, fickle San Francisco.
There was a time when people go,
oh, yeah, Bob Dobbs.
I know who he is.
I'm scared.
Oh, nowadays,
only the finest minds and the coolest people
have any inkling
who that man J.R. Bob Dobbs truly is.
And perhaps it's for the best
because, as Jesus said,
do not try to convert the pinks
because they will get it all completely wrong.
As Jesus said on the cross,
do not try to get it all.
That's not one of the ones...
That's the ones that preachers quote a whole lot.
Strangely enough.
Do not do this at home.
Yeah, it basically says,
don't try to make everybody a Christian.
They'll get it completely backwards.
And, you know, don't...
Jesus said that.
Don't...
Except there wasn't really a Jesus,
but somebody put the words in...
The same guy that wrote most of Bob's stuff
put that stuff in the mouth of a character,
a common archetypal
and a rich doctor character of the times.
But Bob...
Beware of those who pray on the street corner very loudly.
When you want to pray, you must go into a closet.
Keep your prayers in the closet.
That's what Jesus said.
1138.
Andre prayed.
Do you remember that?
I was praying last night when an angel broke the light.
Said, gonna have to put you on hold for a time.
I said, hold like hell.
Let me talk to the boss.
Said, sorry, sucker.
Sinner, it's the boss's day off.
I realized then that the wages of sin was...
Two bucks an hour.
All the nails you can bend.
So I still have a memory for some things.
For some things that you learned long ago.
I like the story about how...
It's in the cusp of the moon.
You have to be in a certain biological framework.
Like if your mother, say, was born in 1978,
or 72 or something like that,
that means her estrogen cycle is similar to that of a chimp.
And she has a hard time making her way around the room.
Unless her son has bowel disorders too.
And she's scratchy and itchy too.
And she just beat up the warden and the zookeeper
at the same time by crunching their heads together.
Oh, that's what I wanted to hear.
Soviet imperialism.
Everybody's got a favorite monkey.
Everybody's got something to hide except for me and my monkey.
Chimpanzees are not monkeys, Dave.
But figuratively, not metaphorically,
but of course universally and socialistically...
Every subgenius in the room starts talking about the monkeys
at the beginning of 2001.
What do you want them to say?
Call them primates or something?
If Hal or me says,
chimpanzees aren't monkeys,
puzzling evidence and phylo will use the word monkey
specifically to cover chimpanzees for the rest of the hour.
You know, obviously there is a difference between a monkey and an ape.
We all know this.
But...
We do?
It is so much more fun to say the word monkey.
It is.
And it's like, I understand.
Griping about that is like going...
It's actually...
The name of the monster is Frankenstein's monkey.
It's a monster.
Frankenstein is the name of the doctor who made the monster.
Even I got tired of that after a while.
Go on.
No, the monster is Frankenstein.
Give up.
Everybody knows what I'm talking about.
Obviously, the monster took the same name as his father.
Right?
So obviously, the monster is Frankenstein.
It's Frankenstein Jr., but...
Frederick Frankenstein Jr.
Oh, you know how the imperialist mind works.
Once they...
Frederick?
Yeah.
DeCoursey Frankenstein.
Well, I'm not associated with them anymore.
They used to have a bowling league in Maple Heights.
And they actually were involved in some human dope traffic.
I forget what it's called.
Stupidity or something.
That was good stuff.
Can you get stupidity?
Oh, can I get it?
I've got it already.
I can get three or four...
Well, we probably shouldn't talk about this on the radio,
but, man, I've been...
I've heard stupidity.
I've heard stupidity just makes you feel so much better.
It makes you feel better than everybody else.
And it makes you feel so smart.
These guys that are on stupidity...
Speaking of...
...that get really, really stupid,
they're the ones that say they're the smartest of all.
They're the opposite of subgeniuses in every way.
Don't have that.
Speaking of stupidity,
you're listening to WCSB Cleveland.
I'm...
I knew that one was coming.
Portions of the following broadcast
will be objectionable to some members of the audience.
Therefore, WCSB advises the listener discretion.
The views and opinions expressed on this program
are not necessarily those of WCSB or Cleveland State University
or anybody with their head screwed on straight.
For that matter, you have been warned.
I'm Dr. Sinister, and this is Synesthesia.
We have our special guests,
Reverend Ivan Stang and Princess Wee Ardo,
and, of course, Keith here with us as well in the studio.
216-687-3515 is the number to call.
We're going to take a short break.
You mentioned me again,
so I guess I'm just going to...
Oh, Dave, your presence goes without...
Mentioning that Lonesome Cowboy Dave is here
is like mentioning that there is air around us.
Like, of course you're here.
Right, and we plugged your food supermarket chain like crazy.
We just got done doing that,
but I still haven't seen any difference
in my overall capability.
Dave, you are the oral fabric upon which we stand.
Your power grows by the minute, sir.
And speaking of which,
we're going to take a couple of minutes here.
The most ridiculous thing I've ever heard in my life.
We're going to take just a couple of minutes here
to pause here for some public service announcements,
and don't touch that dial.
What's so funny about this love and understanding?
Who I'd have strong and who I'd have trusted
And there is the harmony, sweet harmony
Cause each time I feel it slip away
It just makes me wanna cry
What's so funny about this love and understanding?
Where I'd have strong and who I'd have trusted
And there is the harmony, sweet harmony
Cause each time I feel it slip away
It just makes me wanna cry
What's so funny about this love and understanding?