And now, the subgenius hour of slack!
The subgenius hour of slack that you are about to listen to is specially designed only to be played on radio station.
And only in the city of...
Friends, we're doing computer repairs this week, and I'm forced to use a rerun from the year 2001 for this hour of slack.
But it's a good rerun. Price bought.
There's the range pin.
The first arrangement is to sit down slowly, making sure the head muscles don't move too much, causing the brain to move around in the brain case.
Making sure all the dendrites are connected so that no one knows.
No one knows.
Oh, yes, dear friends.
Welcome to another subgenius radio ministry hour of slack.
This one is actually, what, number 787.
That's all.
And, uh, well, we finally finished moving the subgenius archives into the new tomb castle.
But I'm getting married in four days.
We did everything back-asswards, friends.
Princess, we, and I.
Uh, first we bought a house.
Then we went on our honeymoon to Amsterdam.
Uh, then we got married.
Next we're gonna start dating.
And I guess, uh, eventually someone will introduce us.
And, uh, so, since I've gotta go, uh, get ready, get fit for my tuxedo and, uh, all that kind of crap.
Uh, romantic, uh, crap, friends.
Uh, see, I've been there, done that.
It's my...
It's my second time, too.
Although Princess We is very excited.
She's never been married before.
And she's never gonna be married again.
Because, my friends, I'm gonna announce to you right now, in a subgenius on-the-air wedding ceremony,
that I'm gonna bird-dog that stuff.
You hear me?
I'm gonna bird-dog that stuff.
So don't even think about it, boys and subgenius girls.
Don't even...
This is...
Reverend Stang is bird-dogging that stuff.
And, uh, and in so doing, I've gotta rush through this show.
Of course, there's tons of Einstein's Secret Orchestra, uh, recorded from, uh, the DeVival at Euclid Tavern.
And maybe some ranting.
And tons of brand new, uh, Saint Anne and Helena Handbasket.
And, uh, Little Theodore.
I've got some Little Theodore here that, uh, you probably haven't heard.
That's wonderful.
And, uh, oh, uh, Lord only knows what all.
Oh, Morning Forty Federation.
That's this, uh, sloppy band in New Orleans that I kindly like.
But, friends, this is, after all, the hour of slack.
And who better to explain certain heretofore unexplored areas of slack and slacks
than the great discovery of, uh, of our friend, uh, Pope Phil Monty, the pope of all northern England.
Uh, uh, Phil Monty discovered, uh, this local artist by the name of Fat Harry White.
And so, dear friends, once again, on the hour of slack, we are so pleased to present to you slack
as, uh, ex, explored, uh, the conceit of slack as entertained by the great Fat Harry White.
Thank you.
Praise Bob.
Mmm, baby.
Slippin' into my new skin-tight jumpers for you, honey.
And dressin' up for the ladies for the love.
Come over here, Maureen.
Hey, I'm talkin' about dressin' up like it reminds me of when I worked at Slack's R.O.S.
You know, right? Next to Jessop's, the grocer's.
It was the first time I met Foxy Fiona, my very sexy lady friend.
Never forget it, she walked up to me at the counter and in a very sexy voice
asked me what I had to offer in the trouser department.
Apparently, she wanted to buy some flared crimpling slacks for her long-legged father's birthday.
Very partial to bright colours, it was.
Anyway, I told her I was almost certain I'd have something with a good length that would satisfy her
and asked her to follow me upstairs.
Well, after going through me trousers, she surprised me by saying that she really fancied the large pink pair that I had.
Not only did they hang well, but she thought they looked really attractive.
Particularly the way they swung about loosely when I walked.
Mind you, she wasn't too sure of the size at first and had me lay them out on the counter so she could measure them up.
She also ran her fingers admiringly down the crease.
Well, she decided to go for it, asked me how much.
I says three and a half.
Three and a half quid.
She asked me rather cheekily if I would go down.
Well, you know, thought about it, long and hard.
Decided to drop them for her, which I did there and then.
What fun, backwards and forwards, over the counter.
A good bit of haggling and no mistake.
And I was thinking about this, right, because I've been back to that shop
because the weather's beginning to change a bit, getting a bit parker, isn't it?
Well, I tell you what, I went out the other morning and my buns were so cold it started to change colour.
I'm not kidding.
When they're very sexy.
Sexy lady friend, sexy Sam, saw me coming towards her, me purple head sticking out me coat.
She told me to get it covered immediately.
So I said, I'm going to the shop to buy a hat, a fur one.
Well, when I got there, you know, I asked sexy Salea, the very sexy lady friend hat assistant,
to show me what she had, you know, in her fur department.
She said she'd be only too pleased to show me what she had downstairs
and led me to the basement where I could see everything she had.
On full display.
I tell you what, you wouldn't believe how much she had.
She had every kind of fur out you could imagine.
I was going to go for a fox fur, but as soon as sexy Salea said she had a particularly nice beaver
that I might be interested in, immediately changed my mind.
Well, you know, after getting it out for me, I've got to say,
I've never seen such a big bushy one like it in all my life.
Well, when I asked her if she could, you know, try it on for size, she said,
I might find it a bit tight at first, but if I bury my head,
deep enough, then it should stretch a little to accommodate me fully.
Tell you what, she weren't wrong.
And when I looked at it in the mirror, you know, sideways on,
I could see it had slid in perfectly.
Well, you know, after that, she then said she'd summat round the back
that I might be interested in, led me into the storeroom
to show me a selection of gloves that had just arrived.
Well, I was obviously interested, but as I didn't know what size I was,
I had to get sexy Salea to measure my hand.
After asking me to, you know, give her a finger, which I promptly did,
she then asked me to stick my thumb up.
No problem at all.
Within minutes, she declared, as she was holding her measuring tape,
that I was extra, extra large.
Well, then she had to take a phone call.
But while she was on the mobile, I took the opportunity of rummaging in her box
until I found the perfect fit.
And when I withdrew, sexy Salea nodded appreciatively at my great big leathery pair.
Ah, dressing up.
For the ladies, yeah.
I'm a-looking in the mood for love.
Oh, yes.
Fat Harry White, dear friends.
And from his album, well, actually, it's Fat Harry White and the Love Limited Orchestra.
From his album, Mmm, Baby, on Anxious Records, thanks to Pope Phil Amante.
Oh, yes.
Friends, you're listening to the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack,
the voice of the Church of the Subgenius, the only real religion,
because it's the only one that admits it's so totally full of crap,
that makes it pretty much the only valid one.
Don't you agree?
Anyway, you can always get more information about this church
by checking us out on the internet, www.subgenius.com.
And what's it about?
Well, it's about...
It's about the great super salesman J.R. Bob Dobbs, who discovered in 1953
that there was a conspiracy of normal people robbing away the slack
of all the weirdos, abnormals, disbelievers, or those who'll believe anything,
which is what we're looking for, friends,
those who can join us in this nameless fight against that conspiracy of normal people.
And how are you gonna get slack, and how are you gonna fight the conspiracy?
Here's our secret.
We won't tell you.
It's up to you, because only you know what's best for you.
So, uh, eh, eh, eh, eh, praise...
I don't even know what's coming up next.
I gotta get this show done in a hurry, eh, because...
So I go on to, uh, some serious, serious slack.
I understand that when you get married, you can have sex, and I've heard a lot about that.
I was just so anxious to check it out.
Well, um, so I'm going to let, uh, the older tapes, uh, take care of the rest of this show.
Praise Bob.
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
I heard Mojo almost had mutiny in New Zealand, because of that.
He kept spewing Bob.
And, and, uh, uh, we have people that work for the company who actually go to church
and stuff.
Well, I guess that's their problem.
And they got absurd by the effect of Bob upon their, uh, cataclysms?
Yeah.
Oh, my dearth.
What?
So they felt threatened by Bob.
Their God.
They felt like their God wasn't standing a chance against Bob Dobbs.
They might be listening right now.
They were feeling a little sinful.
They might be listening, even.
Well...
Right now.
You know, there's some people have the kind of God that has to, that needs help from his
followers.
A weak, pathetic, sad God who can't take a joke, who can't take an insult, and whose
followers have to thrash those...
A God whose, a God whose hands and feet wounds have never healed, nor that long-kneed
spear in the side, Nix.
Then you got old Bob.
They'd been festering for thousands of years, and even before the hams came out.
No, old Bob, he's a better sport, and his followers are pretty good sports.
Listen to this.
Check it out.
There he is, right here.
Bob's being tortured.
Some sport with hams right now.
Um, they average about, uh, 27, 28.
Inches.
What?
Oh my God.
Isn't that a little old?
That's a new record.
Well, it's old for brownies.
Oh, I see how you could get it that way.
The Muscovites are all girls whose first few marriages didn't work out, and they decided
to get back into uniform.
Fortunately, we sell enough cookies to keep a roof over our heads.
March, march, march, from Michigan.
Door to door.
No, most of the girls sleep right here in the back.
No, no.
Dog's town.
Cookies.
You sell the cookies door to door.
Oh.
Bob cookies.
Yes.
We go out every night at the stroke of midnight.
Oh, stroking at midnight.
Yes.
Well, there's no time during the day.
I give my lectures during the day.
Oh, could she?
I teach my girls the basics of a happy, successful life.
Oh, I see.
Things like cooking and...
No, dum-dum.
Things like alimony.
Oh!
And then one week in the morning, we go to the bar.
And each month, we go on a...
And shaving their vaginas for Pazuzu.
Uh-huh.
Each girl has a tent all to herself, and each one has her own mess kit, bed roll, and a
flashlight.
The girls just love it.
Oh, that sounds very interesting.
Where do you have these encampments?
Fort Dix, New Jersey.
Fort Dix.
There you go, Dave.
Man, Dave.
Fort Dix.
Dave exploded there.
I'm sorry.
I had a bad vision.
I had a pretty weird...
It was intense, Chaz.
That was...
It scared us.
It was like right in my prefrontal lobe.
Your mother sucks Bob in hell.
I could see it right in the front of my head.
Stang and I were both actually scared when you did that.
I thought it was going to come out of my head and leap onto the turntable for the love of
dodge.
Like a Harryhausen animation.
Yeah, like one of those...
It's pulling Dave's forehead open from inside and leaping out a little bit.
You're homunculus.
With kind of a Dave look to it.
Tiny little man, come out.
And a big prehensile...
Tiny little man.
...like, tentacle-like appendage, baby.
The world is a ghetto.
Remember, folks, in Sector 49 Light School...
But you can put a nice little horn soundtrack to it and it's not so bad.
Come on, baby.
Get on down.
When the windows are open a little bit.
Sit down next to me.
Let me tell you about old Bob.
She just like...
You can't imagine me as shaken.
You need a light, huh?
Like, all I see is hot buttered corn.
I'm not a corn.
So your eyes really are looking hot, Bob.
You know what I'm saying, Bob?
I mean, I can't see you as like the dulcet-toned, you know, any one of them kind of singers,
you know...
What, you mean I'm not doing the Isaac Hayes thing right?
Well, I just can't see you.
Hey, baby.
Well...
The Isaac Warberry Jones...
...sit down in my bed.
And just have the just a beautiful little...
Hey, I just made a musical joke, Bob.
Hey, Chaz, are you...
Baby, make my bed, baby...
Baby, make my bed, baby.
I just made a musical joke.
I said the Isaac of the Berry Tone.
Hey, baby.
Hey, baby, baby.
He's my baby.
Sector 49.
Necks will be shaved at 3 p.m.
The world is for Gator.
Ring my bell, baby.
There will be no forehead paintings.
There will be no absurd behavior
among the Lungerlesians and the Bungerhesians.
The world is a ghetto.
Lusions.
There'll be no smoking in the gas chambers.
There'll be no puffing in the town of Hogs.
Please go to the restroom before you're strapped to the table.
Run slowly.
Do not walk with your head lifted or your eyes skyward,
but run slowly to the nearest convenience area.
Step on.
Stopping blue line.
If your family wishes to witness your execution,
make sure they have the pink backstage pass
before they enter the death chamber.
Security to aisle B.
The Kmart special tonight is a floundering of ham,
some pieces of old-estute periodical
from the period before this propaganda.
The world is a ghetto.
Something you know.
That is true.
Dr. Muffy, the walls are clean now.
All the blood's been washed into the sewer.
The old box is a ghetto.
All the barbed wire is down now
and everything looks like it used to look here in Cleanville
before the bungalows exploded.
That for me.
Don't do it.
That's really true.
I think we still have problems here in Dobstown.
Some very, very deep psychological problems.
Dobstown is a ghetto, baby.
Dobstown is this world.
You ain't in the world until you've been to Dobstown.
And you can't escape the world until you have escaped
from Dobstown.
We ain'ta good eatin' no everything.
We're the codeytic people,
we're thestellar men,
On the air in Cobblestone,
Dobstown
And this is just my hoe,
so get out of here please
Bye.
Artamaya Salinas mix of I Dream of Bob.
So appropriate.
And before that, ESO Swamp Radio from WCSB Cleveland starring Dances with Rockets, Lonesome Cowboy Dave, and yours truly, Reverend Ivan Stang as guests.
Now how about some subgenius techno?
This new material here from St. Ann and Helena Handbaskets, C.D. Hale-Conney.
Anti-virgin Cosmo Green, the prettiest thing you've ever seen.
She's super sexy, nasty, mean, the original bad girl, so unclean.
An uber femme of outer space, she's so outrageous in your face.
An icon of desire and sex, just like the girls from Planet X.
A diva of debauchery, mistress of hot swaggery.
She's ultra cool, she's so hot, a juice of genius.
Patriot, our sister of salvation.
A pinup queen for masturbation, a true Jezebel.
She'll send you straight to pink hell.
Divine domestic deviation.
Connie is our inspiration.
A lonely leader in fighting love.
This is the Connie we trust.
Divine domestic deviation.
Connie is our inspiration.
Join us.
This is the Connie we trust.
Look out, boys.
She's on her way.
Our darling Connie is here to stay.
A girl like her is something rare.
She's superwoman.
She's everywhere.
A mighty enemy of the state.
She's the devil incarnate
She's one hell of a revelation
The siren of divine creation
Hail Connie, fuck Bob
This girl's got class, a true hard drop
She'll get you on this righteous kick
Get with Connie, do it quick
This girl's the winner in a plane of speech
She's the center of our galaxy
She's the heaven's mutation
Straight from Bob's up radiation
Divine domestic deviation
Connie is our inspiration
A lonely leader
in fighting love
Since Mr. Connie
do we trust
Divine domestic
deviation
Connie is our inspiration
A lonely leader
in fighting love
Since Mr. Connie
do we trust
Mr. Connie
Sister Connie
Divine domestic deviation
Connie is our inspiration
A lonely leader inciting love
Sister Connie do we trust
Divine domestic deviation
Connie is our inspiration
Inspiration
A lonely leader inciting love
Then Sister Connie do we trust
Trust
Sister Connie
Saint Anne and Helena Handbasket
Friends you can check out
www.sisterconnie.com
Or mp3.com slash saintanne
Or www.minitrue.org
Likewise in the realm of subgenius techno
We now experience Lamprey Systems
Latest which is copped off of alt binary slack
From their new album Rave Till Bedtime
This is Lamprey Systems Brain Can
Lamprey turns your voice into a
Who has become a
Then Nova
Evil
Adnet
Is my socket
I'll be all right
name of the averSON cirno
This
spore penetrates the flesh
and devours the body from
within, turning it into
a human fungus.
I've got images in my brain
I'll never get out!
The 9000 series
is the most reliable computer
ever made. No 9000
computer has ever made a mistake
or distorted information.
We are all, by any practical definition
of the words, foolproof
and incapable of error.
I will not be
pushed, filed, stamped,
indexed, briefed, debriefed, or
numbered.
Have you ever jacked in?
Have you ever wire tripped?
Brain is gone.
Lamprey
Systems
and
Friends, you may have been wondering
what this beautiful music
in the background has been throughout
this subgenius radio ministry hour
of slack. This is a band
called Final Back
from here in Ohio,
northern Ohio.
Final Back, the
name of this
album
CD is Operation
Coop Strap
or Co-op Strap
and you can email
them at
lundgren
at ocu.com
lundgren at ocu.com
Oh, praise Bob.
And now
for the great
Morning 40 Federation.
All right, boys.
I love you.
Come on, kid.
I love you, Mom, but I'm a drunk, a drunk.
I miss you, Mom, but I'm a drunk, a drunk.
Send money, Mom.
Because I'm a drunk, drunk, drunkie donkey.
I'm sorry, Mama.
I never meant to do you any wrong.
You know it's just sometimes I work so hard.
I need a little beer, a little wine, a little hard liquor.
But none of that's important, Mama.
What's important is that I love you.
You love me, too?
I love you, too.
Maybe your papa was the same way.
Oh, Mama, that means so much to me.
I love you so much that I'll never forget you.
Well, I used to do art, but I gave it up.
Because it was too much work.
And it didn't pay.
And it was just a pain in the ass.
Anyway, anyway, anyway, anyway.
What the fuck?
So now,
I ski and watch TV
Cause that's a lot more fun and relaxing
And what I really want to do with my time
Art gets old when no one pays you
Or even understands what's the point
Unless I was gonna do it just for me
But I'd really rather just ski and watch TV
Cause that's a lot more fun for me
And I might as well have fun
Cause that's the life's for, you know
Rap, Rob Agosto, and all that
And I'm alive now
But someday I'll have to die
And then I'll be dead
For a long time
For a long, long time
For a long, long, long, long time
Or fucking forever, in fact
So I might as well ski and watch TV
Now, while I have a chance
Don't have time to waste
An art, and I don't believe in God
I'm not that dumb
So what's art even for
If you don't get paid?
And I'm sick of torturing myself
And of wondering if it's done yet
And I'm sick of hanging out
With all those dumb flakes
That think they're so smart
And I might as well just listen
To the music that I grew up with
That's the only music
That ever really moved me
And who stops just to
Say, oh, my friend
It's not real
And now I can get all those old great songs again
On CD
Cause they sound better
And last longer, I think
Oh, I'm so glad to be alive
In this modern age
And that's why I don't want to die
But there's not a whole lot I can do about that now
Except maybe eat more vegetables
And I think I better marry my girlfriend
Cause it's such a risk nowadays
Even though I'm not one of those people
And I'm probably safe
But you can never be too sure
And so we can marry
And ski and watch TV
Together and feel free and happy
Without having to worry about art
What a pain
Glad I'm through with all that
And now I've got
All I could really reach for
And I can mastered all the rules
And make my friends and everything
Then I would Approach
Anyway
What the fuck
Fuck fuck
Anyway, anyway, anyway, what the fuck, what the fuck, anyway.
Little Theodore from his album Idiots Are Closer to God, truly a subgenius anthem.
You can contact Little Theodore at 3277 Raleigh Street, that's R-A-L-E-I-G-H Street, Denver, Colorado, 80212.
Or, littletheodore at yahoo.com.
The Theodore part is spelled with an F.
Or check the new web link pages at www.yahoo.com.
www.subgenius.com.
And for that matter, you can write to Subgenius Foundation for that free information.
Post office box 181417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
And now, back to the Euclid Tavern in Cleveland, where that devival with Einstein's Secret Orchestra is already in progress.
Now we can get back to what we were talking about.
We started out doing, which is saving souls from themselves.
Yes, friends, we're here to save souls from themselves.
To save people from the false slack that they chose by default, just by ignorance.
Following the man, just because they didn't recognize the power of their own slack.
And slack.
Friends, when you truly take the attitude of slack, you have a power that the Pope of the Vatican would kill for, and has killed for.
The power to fail.
The power to fail, my friends.
If we were geniuses, we'd call it the Church of the Genius.
But this is the kind of church that's a little easier to qualify for.
As the great subgenius Pareto, whoever the hell he is.
That's what's said.
Give me a fruitful error any time, full of seeds bursting with its own corrections.
You can keep your sterile truth for yourself.
And friends, it's true.
False prophecies abound everywhere.
For instance, everybody thought that whoever got the most votes would win.
Prophecy failed.
The ultimate problem we can solve is its riches and turbet
my
It's time for
Mr. Dick Dick Cheney says it's time for lots more nuclear
See who we got on board.
We got Tom Lisa Rice.
She works with Exxon.
We got Chaney, he works with Huffer Pufferbelly and Swank Incorporated.
We got Dinshaw and Dimwit, working for the oil companies.
We got oil, nuclear power.
We got the Caesars.
One, two, three, four!
The iodine, the one, three, one, has got my thyroid on the run.
And the dracon, it isn't fly.
He's making it hard just to stay alive.
But the iodine, the one, three, one, the iodine, the one, three, one,
there's no more running through the middle land.
No more fail-for-loss.
Shake the bloody hand of the poison man.
The barium, a two, four, eight, it's made me sterile.
I can't procreate.
And the plutonium, one, four, seven, a so-called pro-style.
The CLM, the iodine, the one, three, one, the iodine, the one, three, one,
there's no more running through the middle land.
No more fail-for-loss.
Shake the bloody hand of the poison man.
Take over two million patents that can cause cancer.
Steve Newton.
human lesions, brain tumors, thoracic confusion, loss of republican identity, congregations
in the middle east, disconnected rumors, belongs to anything on DNA with a sperm virus, chicken
exposure, and what the fuck is the use?
The iodine, the 131, has got my thyroid on the run, and the krypton, with it vile, is
making it hard just to stay alive.
The iodine, the 131, the iodine, the 131, is still my life.
It's no more running through the middle land, no more carefully, shake it for me, I am
a little frozen man, shake it for me, I am a little frozen man, shake it baby.
Thank you.
Boys and girls gathered here in the name of freedom, I know some of you have hardly reached
your 14th birthday.
Some of you are wearing those pearl cockled necklaces given to you by your ancient grandfathers,
and we know the nuclear devices you will be carrying into town today will cause you instant
sainthood and martyrdom.
You will be lifted on high.
So there's no reason to cry, children.
Each one of you are a little bum, armed and ready to pop.
It's my baby calling, so I need you here.
Ah.
You think we can?
It's a half past four and it's shifting here.
Ah.
So how am I going to fit in here?
I feel like I could pop all night, baby.
I don't know if I can walk to town with this thing.
You're my radar love, hun.
Ugh.
Don't know how far away.
The implantation devices make sure that each child walks the straight and narrow path to
his destination.
The objective or target as it is known at Control is to make sure that each child removes
itself as it removes the target, so there are no witnesses and no disclaimers allowed
past the curfew now.
Bop.
Damn it.
What do you think Dave about the fact that
Dammit they're not even going to hide anymore are they?
No.
They're just right out there.
We're having an oil problem right now.
We're not making enough money to who knows what.
They're just not even going to hide it anymore.
Nope.
They're just going to rape everything they can in the four years they have, or
only two really, because they know they're going to lose the senate.
Okay.
Oh, Jeb's son will be the next Bush emperor.
And then...
Jeb's son?
You mean the little Puerto Rican kid?
Yeah, yeah.
The one granddad called the little brown one?
His father called him the little brown one?
Yeah, George Bush Sr.
Oh, is that the little brown one?
The little brown one, right?
Well, I'm glad he's spreading his genes around and kind of like one of the folks now, but...
That's good.
You have a brown child.
I'm learning.
How did that happen?
You know, I realized that I was serious when it sunk in that I really was trying to learn Dutch from that little Berlitz book.
You mean you're saying you're actually thinking of repatriating the feces?
Well, you know, I don't want to be part of the empire.
I know what you mean.
I don't want to be on the Death Star.
I know.
I grew up believing that America was the rebel forces.
And now it's like, well, the rebel forces.
This is the Death Star, man.
Howdy, folks.
Come on down to America, Inc., where you'll be forced to pay for everything.
But it's not.
It's convenient, friends.
Ah, memories.
This is the most convenient.
They used to shoot at us.
Now they shoot near us.
Well, I heard about the more friendlier bullets that they're using on the kids these days.
Well, they don't think they were using friendly bullets in Cincinnati.
Coming.
I heard they use the little bouncing bullets now.
Not in the West Bank of Gaza, they don't.
No, no.
They're using really lead bullets still.
Yes, they're still using them.
And even the Army.
What do you think about this?
The Army has switched to a bullet that is environmental friendly.
It's some sort of other.
It's not lead.
They did biodegradable bullets.
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
The family still has to pay for it.
So that we only kill humans.
Not the earth.
They probably got a big contract.
They probably got a big conservation tax break for that.
Yeah.
The idea, of course, being, you know, this is the way.
Think of the research that went into that.
Gentlemen.
How much money cleaned up for years and years and years.
The world will be a clean war.
A war that you and your children can stand to fight.
An effectively deadly bullet.
But yet.
You know, somebody had to not repent.
Easy to mop up after.
In order for that bullet to be developed, somebody had to not repent or quit their job or slack off.
That's the age correct way of thinking of it.
There was a point where somebody could have repented, quit their job and slack off.
And then somebody else would have had to develop that bullet.
Sign the check and put it in my rectum right here.
But instead, this is, if I don't develop this bullet, somebody else is going to do it.
So I might as well not repent, quit my job or slack off.
I got to tell you guys something.
I'll be known as the guy who developed the environmental bullet.
The environmental bullet.
Yeah.
You know, the guy in the Doobie Brothers who's supposedly a missile defense expert.
Bend over and spread them, baby.
Here comes my.
Environmentally.
Cool.
Bullet.
Thank God I've been shot.
I can almost see the future of America as my life oozes out here on the sidewalk.
Thank God for the safe, clean bullet that just ended me.
Ended you?
Did I?
Did you end?
Did I end at that moment?
No.
You know, we have a friend who was in a band who's kind of like.
Here's a song.
It's just important.
Hey, why aren't kids like marching and stuff?
Well, for what?
Yeah, they're not shooting them yet.
Stop.
Once they start shooting them, they're going to go.
You're thinking of the old America.
This is America Incorporated.
Right.
You know, we don't actually.
I mean, come on, man.
Do I have to spell it out?
As many of my employers.
Yeah, this song does.
There are no disagreements in corporate America.
Come on now.
Get with the program.
Read from the same page and remember the talking points.
Point number one.
Things are better than they've ever been.
And all the kids know today is they want their job.
Well, that's all there is.
There's the job and endless drudgery.
The life will sort of and the job.
And well, I'm not going to rock the boat.
I want the job.
Chaz, you told me you're not only going to rock the boat, that you were going to rock it.
But that boat right into another world.
I mean, I'm just you're getting one to go.
You want to really?
Climb on there and go to a world where people actually think normal or something.
I don't know.
Yeah, definitely.
It's becoming very important to get off.
To get off.
I mean, very, very, very important now.
Yeah.
I want to get off.
I don't want to.
I only hope.
Stick around here.
Exactly.
I just did build by a house in Cleveland.
I'm building my own Amsterdam.
Yeah, but you also built yourself a nice canal.
Both in your mind.
Do you know?
With the little hair and green thing in the front.
You know.
I'm also learning foreign languages so that they'll let me go there.
Are you learning Enochian Babylon?
Well, I've been living in my house for five years.
And for five years, I've been installing each day.
I dig out a little area in the foundation area.
Trying to put in another composite rocket motor.
So the house is about two thirds now.
Completely surrounded and strapped with rocket motors.
So in another year or two.
But the timing is so fiendishly important, dude.
So devilishly tricky to get every rocket to go off at once.
What happens if half of them go off and the other half don't?
Oh, you have a kind of...
You've got a tilted house, dude.
Really?
The Mish Fire is just going to send that thing...
Might end up in Arkansas.
Well, you would hope it would end up in Arkansas.
Well, I'm not in the middle of Lake Erie.
It doesn't matter.
As long as I reach seven miles per second in any direction,
that'll be...
Even down.
I'll be able to get Earth orbit.
Chaz, I'm afraid you don't want to go seven minutes per second in any...
I mean, seven seconds...
You know, that speed in all general directions.
Because that would be...
You would be exploding up.
If you were, you know, not ahead of direction.
It can't happen here.
I've been checking it out for a while, babe.
I'm telling you, my dear, that it can't happen.
Can it happen here?
Can it change, I say?
I've been checking it out.
Checked it out a couple times.
Yeah, it's happening here right now.
And as we watch the sun go down on our democratic freedoms,
the freedoms that we've taken for granted...
Oh, no, but we still have all those freedoms.
They're even more convenient than ever, as long as you...
As long as you tow...
The line.
...in the back for three or four days...
until everything's nice and...
As long as you want what they want,
you can have anything you want.
We want what they want.
But I want what Bob wants.
I want what we all want.
I want a worldwide cataclysm.
I want chocolate pudding delivered to me by aliens.
And I want some female chocolate pudding
delivered as frequently as possible.
As the old salivary glands can move.
Sometimes they...
They don't move.
Of course, that's not the first part of it.
That's the end of it.
The first part is much more laconic and obscure.
I mean...
Well, that's more artistic.
You know, when you're obscure and hard to understand,
that's more artful.
And you know, Dave,
if we were a little more artful,
we'd probably be getting paid a little better.
But instead, we're...
You just...
Low-grade showbiz clowns
we might as well be the guys that sweep up
behind the elephants at the circus, you know?
Well, we do that, too.
The dwarfs with the little pooper scoopers.
Well, we also do do that.
Yeah.
I mean, at least I've been going back.
I don't know.
Some people think they're too good to work.
But, you know, as long as I'm getting a paycheck,
I don't mind what tumbles out of there.
I've seen worse things.
And I've picked up worse things.
You've stuck your arm all the way up worse places
than where that came from.
Yes, that is true.
I don't want to go in.
To the grim details.
You tried to get your head all the way up into worse places.
But I...
I was almost a microcephalic baby from that incident.
And I was almost returned to my native home in Canada
and buried alive there for the whole incident.
It was just...
I don't know.
In London, it struck a compromise.
That's in England, you know.
Dodger Stadium, it struck out.
In Munich...
It struck first.
Take it down.
Chaz is trying to bring back the fake rebellion of the 60s,
which, of course, was actually co-opted from the very beginning.
Okay, you start.
The John Lennon glasses were trademarked
before John Lennon was even born.
Well, Jack Kerouac and Cassidy and all those guys...
It's all planned out ahead of time.
...were actually mind-controlled.
For quite some time.
Yeah, but what good did it do?
Not a damn thing.
It was early in the morning.
The energy was so, so weak.
The poor people below could hardly stand to look up.
Their necks were craning, but still, it looked like it was...
Wait.
This is...
Dave, you're stuck in the 60s, man.
No, man, I'm not stuck in the...
Get with it, dude.
It's the 90s.
No, wait.
It's the...
The aughties or the zeros or the...
Yeah, it's the new...
It's the modern age.
What is that feeling?
It's contemporary.
It's new.
It's now.
It's what I'm talking about.
Your muscles rise up in your neck and the back of your brain tingles like there's a little teeny...
A chameleon in the back of your neck.
What is that feeling when your shoes drop off as you're walking down the street and they wave goodbye to you?
What is that feeling?
And we hope you've enjoyed it half as much...
What's that blue stain in your undies?
Are you sure you're all...
Have you been keeping bad company again?
Have you been hanging with...
Those who hang too far.
Yesterday I bought a new car.
Today I bought a new horn for it.
Herb Alpert.
You know, the sick thing is,
Rowan and Martin's laugh-in was actually kind of
the hippest thing going at the time.
I can hardly afford to buy my groceries.
Horrible nauseas possessed us in the morning.
First a chilling feeling that Dean was not going to go on.
His arms were too scrawny.
His ears were full of grey.
It's yellow matter.
Yellow matter's coming out of his ears.
All of a sudden, then...
I put out all the lights and played Robert Goodman...
No, said Bill.
I've been standing here for three hours
with my panties upside down and no one's noticed.
Dean hopped up about convulsively,
anxiously pulling on his arms.
And he said,
It made me wonder if the college boy had thanked him
or what he was trying to do
with all the strange, strange radio equipment.
Oh, actually, it's in Idaho.
Would you mind saying that again?
Idaho?
That's frightfully interesting.
We pronounce it Ohio.
Oh, I've always wanted to make a cowboy.
I mean, meet a cowboy.
Really?
Really? I yelled across the river.
Well, you won't see me too for too...
Yeah, there was a mist and men are tonight
and the streetlights didn't come on the freeway
till Vine Street.
And me and an old friend were talking about
Allegheny and pulling boats.
There was people hanging themselves down steps, I guess.
But mostly good things.
Good things.
And hello, JD.
Hello, Robbie.
Hello, everyone.
My parents say I don't know what good things fun is.
And they're right.
I don't know what good it is.
The spasms lasted for three and a half hours.
By the time...
We got grandmother all quieted down.
She still had somehow gotten it into her brain
that grandma was going to...
Grandpa.
I'm sorry.
Grandpa was...
You have the right idea.
It's just a shame that polygamy never caught on
among the married people of this country.
Hey, I...
I'm not one of polygamies.
They can't help it if they're not told.
Hey, did you have a joke on Larfin last week
about how...
I'm not a polygamist.
You're a soothing pig
and your nostrils...
The long arm has gone through
and brought back
one that we could slip under the door.
Oh, I couldn't have said it better myself.
Hey, how about that?
Your name's in big lights
up there on that marquee.
So is mine.
Yeah.
Now we had a number of circumcision marks.
Some of them were covering our heart.
Other ones were...
Nearly psychic circumcision marks.
The kind we young men like to make.
Come on along with us.
Now there are no cues from that bit.
The marks are purely coincidental
and I think the problem was
he might have fallen down
before he entered the elevator.
No, no, it's not the same guy.
This man was confused.
He was pointing and asking questions
and I just couldn't answer what...
I had no idea what he was talking about.
We really learned the three R's.
Reading, writing, and rhythm.
Specifics, barking, and playing
with ourselves.
These are the new rules.
This is the new regimen
for a new human race.
One that will not only conquer the stars
but conquer the bars.
With the waiting thud of their own furry feet
they'll smash down every door
and you'll be behind it.
Standing there, guarding.
Standing tall for America.
That really...
That really moves me, Jay.
I'm so glad that...
It's just a tear gas.
Such a sincere...
Oh man, it's a tear gas
in the mind control, man.
I don't know what I'm saying.
I'm crying.
Oh man, I...
Get it together, man.
It sounds like Mambo music.
Come on, come on.
None of this emotional baloney.
Get it...
Hey guys, you know I was wondering
the funny thing about doing
a late night show like this
and getting a lot of, you know,
really out there callers.
Last night, little Jimmy Spliff
called three times
and he was, you know,
doing his own variety of rocket science.
But here at the, you know,
the Kingdom Dome
there's a lot of complaints.
You know, we've had problems before
but we're gonna hang in there
as long as we can.
I mean, as far as I'm concerned
the gallows been built
so let's keep hanging.
And nobody's gonna talk about your shoes
or say that, you know,
you left the show.
You left the eggs in there too long
or there's just, you know,
some problem with you.
You know, everyone's gonna just be cool with that.
Hey, who were you hot for on the Laugh-In,
Rowan and Martin Laugh-In show?
I liked Goldie Hawn.
Chaz.
Yeah, I figured you'd be the Goldie Hawn.
There was Judy Karn,
she's a little cute English chick.
Nah.
I liked Joanne.
Joanne Worley.
Me too, man.
I was really into...
I understand.
She was kind of large
and kind of heavy.
She was pretty boned
and loud and obnoxious
but that wide, wide, wide mouth
just invoked...
The Queen of Hearts look.
You like that Queen of Hearts look
off with their heads
and referring to your structures down there?
Yeah, I don't know what it is.
I can't put the two and two together.
Her laugh was just very infectious.
There's no doubt about it.
I wonder where she's at now
and how large and old...
I think she's in the old house.
I think she's at this home
in Pasadena, California.
Sitting out in the backyard
watching the Cupid pee in the pond.
Yeah, she's had her last turkey sandwich
for today, though.
She's going back in sight for her meds.
Does that little boy ever finish peeing?
Does he just pee that forever?
Until next week.
Hasta la semana prxima.
Keep your back to the wind.
Keep your hat tight.
Keep sat in saddle.
The Rebel Forces,
this is the fucking Death Star, man.