About seven years ago, I started dating Bob.
You look like a Bobby.
I'm Bobby.
Have you ever smoked pot?
Every day.
Every day?
Every other day.
Not all the time.
Texas, what's on your almost perfect mind this evening?
I just had triple bypass open heart surgery and I want you to know it's people like you that made me want to get out of that hospital.
Hey, ask him to do that. Listen to this crowd.
For her recent divorce, shot and killed her three children aged seven. Shot right between a heinous .
A local judge praised defendant John Roy but was dismayed to learn that Roy had had sex with the corpse.
What?
Roy's lawyer was quoted as saying,
State authorities last October released 500 turtles into the Ganges to try and reduce human pollution and now plan to put in the crocodiles to devour floating corpses.
Holy shit!
There's not a limit for human pollution.
The Utah Proudest State of...
What's up, peanut?
I can't take no more of this radio. I never heard so much dee shh in all my life.
You give me some music on that radio, this is Hampton. I made it!
Well at least I got my friends. I got life when you ain't got the love.
And when you hit the surface, I'm gonna show you what I've got for you.
Even though I got a straight to heart. At least I got my friends.
Got my friends.
Well at least I got my friends.
The Soul Genius.
Power of...
Swag.
Fifteen pounds.
Twenty euros.
Thirty dollars.
Ah!
Cut me some slack.
Slack?
Mmhmm.
Didn't you say slack?
Captain, sit.
It's safe.
You want to talk about slack?
Yeah.
I think it's safe.
It's safe.
Outro Music
Boom, Bob's your uncle.
All right, here's the question that somebody wanted to ask me.
And Dildo Valerie, they said,
Dear Bunny Day and Dildo Valerie,
Will I be able to avoid having sex my whole life?
I am 17, I'm straight,
and many girls think I'm attractive.
One of my female friends gave me a list of reasons why I'm attractive.
I know that I'm good looking, but I don't want to have sex.
I think it is just weird getting naked with a girl, and I view the whole act of sex as weird and primitive.
Plus, she would probably laugh at me when she sees me naked because I have a penis and it is large.
Bob was there to watch each dropping of each coprolite from each dinosaur sphincter.
Bob saw.
Bob sees now.
Bob always will see.
Bob.
Please.
She's been living in her.
Bob.
Town world.
I bet she never had a.
Bob.
She's been living in her.
Town world.
I bet she never had a.
Once.
From her time.
Yeah.
Thoughts.
From her time.
Yeah.
Thoughts.
From her time.
Yeah.
Thoughts.
From her time.
Yeah.
Bob was a boxer, a hoofer, a vaudeville performer, and a Broadway headliner.
Before his work in radio.
I'm Bobby.
I know.
Bobby.
Yeah.
You think I'm what I'm thinking?
I think I'm thinking.
Already there.
So many things going on there.
Bob did the right thing.
He folds and tuckers.
And he's easy as.
Oh, what's going on?
They've recently had babies.
Now Bob's a fine family man.
Every, you know, anything.
So they're a little.
Yeah.
Yes.
A little stretched at the moment, darlings, aren't you?
Yeah.
A little slack.
Mm-hmm.
Take your finger.
You know I will, Bob.
Oh my goodness.
And.
Ooh.
Oh, my goodness.
Yeah.
Just take a break like that.
Oh, it's like a.
That's you can tell.
Like a milk jelly.
This is ready.
.
We have just received an exclusive video from inside the house proving
that the people inside are not cultists after all.
Attention everyone.
This has only been.
The subgenius hour of sweat.
Hey, Bob?
What's your name?
J-Bob Dubs.
Sorry, Bob.
Everything's being recorded.
And cut up.
Collage.
People are hearing me.
Large.
Everything's being recorded.
And cut up.
Collage.
People are hearing me.
Bob.
Well, you don't know that they're having a party.
Bob's out of work.
The two of them might be starting some weirdo church.
The kind of church where you, uh...
Get out the slack.
No sirree, Bob.
Bob.
One of Gaddafi's sons has apparently been Barack Obama.
I'm, uh, Bobby.
I know, I know.
Listening to the same sounds over and over and over again.
Well, no, sometimes you hear it backwards.
Hi.
And how we're watching.
I'm theme.
Drunk as Lemur.
Lurched out of the darkness.
The.
Season.
Is.
So.
Long.
Out.
Ah!
La-la-la-la-la-la-la!
I'm alone!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
From PR News in Washington, I'm Obama Gaddafi's son, sentenced to life in prison by Thursday.
NATO says the situation in Japan is very serious and very dangerous.
A change in tone from...
Monday when rebels hit the U.S. mainland. One reason, the unexpected appearance of Vice President
Biden as he rallied his father's dangerous supporter. Praising the people of Tripoli,
fighting two Somali men with the National Piracy Center, both admitted helping take over
PR News in Washington. All right, let's just assume the killer is repeating Whistler.
Yes, I have Bob calling. I'll have to call you back. What? Tell Bob I'll call him back.
Big Ripper in full old age, had sex on screen and had a blowjob. What?
I miss Berge. The whole thing. Oh, yeah.
Stacks, cats, nuts, and ears. I had a blowjob. Oh, yeah.
I miss. What?
Blowjob. A blow and had green suns. Sex. Hats.
They blow in full. But Big Ripper. Oh.
I had a blowjob. I had a nose. I had a stash. Yeah.
The whole thing. The whole thing.
He caused people to have heart attacks in movie theaters. It was the last movie he ever made.
I don't know the name of it.
But.
People just did not want to see that. They didn't want to see it so much.
Randy Griffin.
Andy Griffith.
Randy.
People just did not want to see that. People just did not want to see that so much because of..
Randy Griffith.
Andy Griffith.
Randy.
People just did not want to see that. They didn't want to see it so much because.
Randy Griffith.
Mhm.
Andy's last movie.
Did advertising ок стоп
sanding
everything is under control
did
Every, every hundred hundred who show
Moonsay Glamorous
This is perfect
This is perfect though
You know I'm always thinking pink
No
You know I'm thinking pink
Always thinking pink
Not from now on anyway
Surrender to the power of the pink?
Phew!
I ran into Bob out in the driveway and he told me you weren't at church
God, I hate Bob!
They went to church, Richard, and said can you...
Here's the $120
And they found us a place up front
Alright, that's it
I'm kicking Bob's ass
Kevin!
Yes, dear friends
Okay, let's get real Aul
Somec carefully now
Are you guys in this, uh Cold business just for the bucks?
I don't really want to
Yes friends, the amino acids
New, uhh LP
An EP from the amino acids called Theme from the Slack Hole.
EP. An EP.
An EP. Yeah.
EP.
Phone Home.
Anyway, what we've been listening to is, well, that was Fat Man B right at the end.
But I think The Large did something to her.
The Large sent us a huge amount of stuff for tonight.
In fact, it says, I got a letter from him.
Greetings and salutations, my friend.
Here's a mighty long collage slash remux of my greatest musical clips, mashups, and whatnots.
A sort of best of, worst of compilation.
It could pull off almost as a full episode, eh?
It also includes puzzling evidence, October 20th, 2013.
Commercials by Lymph Note Institute.
Girl Talk and Sultan of Ping, but I cut that part out because...
What?
This is the actual theme from the Slack Hole here, which is only 19 seconds long.
They named their EP after the 19 second song.
Anyway, back to...
Martians are coming this way.
We must evacuate the city.
Oh, they must be talking about the WCSB Halloween masquerade ball coming up.
Must be. They must be.
That's the exciting stuff around here.
But I'm going to go back.
Back to this collage by The Large, although the part that's coming up happens to be from the puzzling evidence show.
And I suspect The Large is one of the callers in the background.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
With Philodrum and puzzling evidence and Dr. Howell and so forth, the callers and, um...
I was at a board of potty in Utah that didn't have a roof.
It was built without a roof.
Oh, nice.
So, it was awesome.
So, you're open to the free air of heaven.
It was open to the free air.
And...
Smaller foe.
It was not the wellest thing.
Still had a door and everything.
Sleipanel, the niche with open doors.
What park was that?
That was in Arches National Park.
Which is excellent.
Excellent National Park.
Which National Park is that then?
Arches.
Yes.
Also, they actually...
Veronica and Betty National Park.
This was at the Slick Rock Recreation Area.
But my favorite, of course, is Mr. Weatherby National Park.
And you made it to the...
Where they shot Galaxy Quest, you know, the Vulcan.
The Goblin.
The Goblin Valley.
Goblin Valley, yeah.
And down, down to Goblin Town.
Yeah.
Go.
I mean, they made it look huge.
Because I looked around at pictures of it after I saw the credits, because I immediately thought, where is that?
It's a little bitty state park.
They used the good parts.
It's right there near Capitol Reef.
That's what I figured.
And a lot of really awesome, unbelievable formations and stuff.
Let's go.
Yeah, right now.
Put the radio on automatic pilot and we'll get in the car.
Let's leave in 16 minutes.
A whole little old bottle of 3% hydrogen peroxide.
You use it to wash your hair.
Is that what you said?
Yes, it's the 3%.
I'm not sure how it was used, but when I was a kid in Hawaii, all of the dark-haired kids,
it was very, very cool to have blonde hair then.
So they somehow did a little.
Yes, exactly.
And they somehow did a, I'm not sure how,
but they,
all the girls especially, would lighten their hair with, yeah, some weak solution of hydrogen peroxide.
It just bleeps the hell out of it.
You can also use it to soak your toothbrush in and keep your toothbrushes germ-free.
Anything.
It just, nothing can live in this.
You can actually put a capful of it in your mouth and just hold it in your mouth for about 10 minutes,
and it'll whiten your teeth better than those teeth whitens do.
But what about the repulsive taste that persists in your mouth?
And you can't spit it, wash it out, because that obviates the,
the good of it.
Well you get used to that awful.
Oh you get used to it.
You learn to love that flavor.
Okay, all right.
Just learn to, quit hatin' Dr. Howell, don't be a hater.
It's just that I was in that state.
Be a playa, not a hata.
I, my teeth went bad just at the time I had to go down to Hollywood to work on a project,
and so I had to, you know, to arrest the problem by swishing with the damn hydrogen peroxide at night,
and bearing that unpleasant taste just so I wouldn't be overcome with dental pain during the day.
You can also use it to kill your athlete's foot, a 50-50 mixture on your feet every night.
Oh great, now I've got my foot in there.
This is terrible.
Then you can reuse that in the morning to do your teeth.
How did I get to be such a yogin?
No, the lemur!
It's just Bob is what it is.
It's just, it's literally Bob.
Genie gotta Bob.
Hurt dog plus sea fire.
Some genius hour of slur.
Float with the ghost.
Have fun with the phantom.
Soar with the spirit.
Float with the ghost.
Have fun with the phantoms.
I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I
Woooooooooooooooooo bad plane.....
Good evening, Bill.
Bob.
Now then, what can I get you, Bill?
It's Bob.
Right then, you go me a tenner, Bill.
No, it's Bob.
Bob.
Yeah.
Hey.
Take this.
Bob.
Ladies and gentlemen, Bobby is only ten minutes away.
Okay, bye.
Ladies and gentlemen, Bobby is only 10 minutes away
I just wanna like it
Bobby! Bobby! Bobby!
The reason I'm not at the PR news is because I'm in a...
Some genius.
Power of...
Now, turn the dial.
This is clearly a photograph of Bob.
And what's really sad is it's actual size.
He is not large.
Big Bob.
It's time to meet Big Bob.
Oh, what's up, kid?
What's up, kid?
It's Big Bob.
Dude, what?
What?
You're talking with Big Bob right now?
Why are you fucking with Big Bob right now?
You're fucking with Big Bob right now?
He will do something.
Why are you talking shit on Big Bob?
Big Bob will eat you up.
You smell like rubber and you're really sketchy right now.
Dude, look at me.
What is that?
You got punked by Big Bob.
It's like a weird dream.
Oh, shit.
Big Bob will smack you up so hard.
And I said Big Bob's the truth.
Okay.
Here he is.
Big Bob.
He's in the streets.
Hey.
Oh, here he is.
Big Bob.
He's in the streets.
Okay.
Got a little car.
Yeah.
Big Bob.
Welcome to the Big Bob.
Bigness.
Yeah, yo.
Welcome to the bigness.
It's going down, Bob.
Big Bob has been here.
Big Bob.
Yeah, yeah.
What?
Dude, you look like a high school sinner.
Do you think you are Mr. Big Star?
Big Bob is no joke.
Oh, yeah.
I'm so used to this.
Big Bob, it's a prog.
Bob!
My name's not Bob.
Not a prop, Bob.
Good drugs?
Hey, Bob.
Where are you?
Another cell.
Maybe.
What do you mean, maybe?
What's that supposed to mean?
Maybe.
Means maybe I'm in the next cell.
Another volunteer like you.
Or maybe I'm in the central office, spying on you for all those science bozos.
Maybe I'm not even here.
Maybe I'm just in your...
So genius.
Powerful.
What?
Bob!
Bob doesn't believe I have one.
This is America.
You can do it.
We can do it.
Whoa.
Thank you.
Bob here.
Yeah, Bob spelled backwards.
It's still Bob.
Hey, for every stang, I got a new joke for you.
It's just Bob is what it is.
It's just...
It's literally Bob.
Hey, Bob's the truth.
Okay.
That's Big Bob. That's Big Bob. That's Big Bob. That's Big Bob. That's Big Bob. That's Big Bob. That's Big Bob. That's Big Bob.
I'm in some hot soup here, Bob. Some teenagers are hanging out in front of the store. I think they could start slacking at any moment.
From PR News in Washington, I'm Shlack.
The National Guard is airlifting washed-out anti-government activists in Canada,
visiting rebel leaders in New Jersey blamed for more than billions of deaths and nearly a dozen child sexual assaults.
A 13-year-old boy is also vowing that its armed rebels will be merged into water in Washington.
Far out. A major hit.
Dear Ben Laden, please take me now.
I hate the curse of that car.
But you can never have what's inside my perverted, sick, demented head.
I hate it!
Ah, the commercial break.
You know, commercials are now woven into the tapestry of our lives, answering the questions we first posed to ourselves.
Who am I? What do I believe? What is my worth?
Before commercials, these questions were merely rhetorical and thus unanswerable.
But when viewed through the magnifying lens of commercials, these questions, like all others, yield answers.
Imagine no more wondering about identity, self, or beauty.
If you allow your life to reflect images in commercials, the nagging doubts and feelings of inadequacy will fall away.
Leaving the person you've always dreamed of, confident, assured, bold, or beautiful, sexy, loved.
Yes, America, you love your commercials, and why shouldn't you?
Commercials are themselves lovers.
Gentle are their words.
Tender their caress.
Commercials know what you like, and they want to give it to you.
Attuned only to your wants and needs, commercials stir the passions and arouse desire.
Commercials give and give.
Reaching lovingly.
Deep inside of you.
Creeping.
Tentatively at first, and then relenting.
Into a singly focused writhing.
Searching out the source of your ache.
Pushing fiercely into your loneliness, and into a spot you never knew existed.
Commercials fill you up with hopes and dreams.
With new desires and new possibilities.
Delivering you into an eerily delirious ecstasy.
Afterward, you'll sleep as only someone who's been completely satisfied can.
Only vaguely sensing the arm of commercials.
Draped over your body.
Holding you.
Keeping you.
Safe and secure.
And you'll dream.
Of ballroom dancing.
Of game winning home runs.
Of first kisses.
And of commercials.
The man, whenever she saw him.
Carried away by a moonlight.
Bob.
You could just...
I don't...
I just don't even...
I don't even know.
I don't know either.
I don't know.
And I don't know where or when we go from there.
Would Dave know?
And Dave would probably know, but he's lonesome tonight.
He's lonesome, lonesome tonight.
This is the Flying Ryan Brothers in the background.
By the way, Princess, we, the band, the Flying Ryan Brothers has started to play out.
They're probably the best sounding, most commercial sounding subgenius band, but they were only
a studio band.
Yes, indeed.
I'm amazed that they're gonna play out.
That's great.
No, they've been doing it a lot in Chicago.
I think that's kind of where they're at.
Somewhere thereabouts.
Well, I wish the cowboy wouldn't be so lonesome, but...
Those lucky Chicagoans.
And we...
That...
That's right.
All that collageery was by the large, except that it was...
He was piecing together hundreds of pieces by other folks, like the commercial at the
end for commercials was by Lymphnode Institute, which was Suzy the Flusie's co-host or show
partners on Bob's Slack Time Fun House in Atlanta, WREK Atlanta.
And we congratulate Suzy on her very...
First 1000th show.
She's done 1000 episodes of Bob's Slack Time Fun House.
We'll be playing that soon.
Yes.
And also with Dave, I hope.
So he would, he would hope.
Oh, he is.
It is the hope.
It's Dave.
That we have hope and change.
Well, hope.
Well, change.
Well, wait.
Well, Dave.
We have Dave.
Does it sound like some sort of tube or something?
You sound a little tubular more than normal.
Slightly tubular.
Slightly tubular, Vinnie.
You sound like you're going to a satellite and bouncing back, but that's normal.
Are you trying to tell us that you're not speaking through a paper cup?
Not this time.
No, I'm actually speaking through the controlled innards of an old flashlight.
The battery's taken out and everything.
Wow.
That's steampunk.
That is steampunk.
Well, yeah.
Well, that's since the government shut down.
What else can you do?
If you don't have government, where are you going to get your tube?
Right.
Yeah.
Where are you going to get your hairnets and your poo-poo and stuff?
And all those other incongruous elements that you would go shopping on one day for.
Yes.
Well, now they're saying that I have to have car insurance, right?
Yeah.
All of a sudden, if I don't have car insurance, I'm going to get fined if I'm stopped and
I can't prove I have insurance?
Well, you know what I'm going to do?
I'm going to wreck my car.
Just to show them what for.
That's what I'm going to do.
And wreck every other car.
I'm going to key every other car I find.
How's that?
If I go for it, I have to have car insurance.
That's communism.
And when the adjuster comes out, you're going to pee your pants and cry.
Well, I'm so butthurt about the whole thing, I've decided to announce a subgenius
shutdown.
Or rather, well, why just subgenius?
Let's have a whole religion shutdown.
Yes.
Let's go all the way.
You know, why should church and state be separate?
You're going to have to do your reason.
Yeah, but factions need to fight, though.
You need to have people that think that the reason you need to shut down a church is because,
you know, you didn't pass stangle care or something like that.
Well, no, because we didn't have enough Muslimics or we had too many Muslimics.
Yeah, that'll work.
That sounds good.
Why don't we just do what the onions said and have a hoedown instead of a shutdown?
Yeah, let's have a hoedown.
Well, the state can have a shutdown and church can have a hoedown.
Yeah.
Do you know any hoes?
Watch that talk.
People wearing snowshoes in the middle of summertime.
I said that just to bother Princess Wee.
She doesn't like me to use that word.
Well, as the new papal envoy, I think you should at least treat her with a minor amount
of respect.
Papal envoy?
Yeah.
Can we get, like, toilet paper?
It's part of the new plan from the new oblong forces.
Those guys are going to be in trouble.
They just know everything about everything.
And actually, the world's coming to them even quicker than you did when you screwed up.
Praise oblong.
Yeah.
Do more than that.
He demands more.
But, get him Bob.
Now, I heard something about, yeah, thanks oblong.
Thanks oblonga.
Thanks blagonga.
Actually, that reminds me, I have some blagongas I need to kill if I'm going to get this.
That blagonga armor.
But that's neither here nor there.
Especially since it pinches the nipples, so to speak.
So what?
That's in his dream game.
Pay no mind.
Well, yeah.
But I didn't know that, you know, the soft porn was a part of it.
Real soft.
Yeah, that's the way it left me.
Sad.
It's not all its fault, though.
After an evacuation, it's not.
After an evacuation drill, you need to stand tall and say, thank God, America.
After an evacuation drill, some of us have to take a shower.
And if a shower's not nearby, do like that one lady and go to the nearest car wash and
beg them to hose you down.
I saw a video of that, a little security video.
Yep.
One lady's only got one good eye.
That was beyond comprehension that that actually happened.
Dr. Sinister has entered the studio.
But I saw the video of it, so I've...
I have.
I know it's happened.
Yes.
Yeah, the videos of it, I always tell the truth on YouTube and stuff.
You can always count on a non-staged event.
Well, I can't tell.
Can you really?
No, I can't tell the fake from the real.
You know, there are people out there who spend their entire lives just waiting for the big
real moment, and they have acted out in their heads how something is going to go when something
big happens.
They've got some kind of words that they know they're going to want to say.
Or they've got some gesture.
Some people.
They buy lots of canned food.
Some people can make the re...
Duck masks.
I think that when the rapture, the Christian rapture happens, there's going to be a lot
of people like in that movie, This Is The End, saying, hey, what about me?
Except for we'll all be adrift in the middle of Pacific Ocean with a tiger.
That'll be the escape vessel.
And we go, oh, man, am I going to do some serious digging into my brain and get rid
of all these useless thoughts?
He's making me hungry for tiger pie.
I haven't had a good tiger pie in so long.
Dang.
Mm-hmm.
You've been pieing out in Ashtabula, Dave.
Have I been pieing out?
Yeah, pieing out.
Oh, yeah.
There was a big pie festival this weekend in an adjacent town.
Oh, there really was?
There actually was.
So that is a synchronistic mesh.
A serious pie festival?
Like pie as in the mathematic...
Yeah.
Pie or pie to eat?
You're supposed to do that on March 14th.
It was in an old, some old, you know, double century home or something, making some big
deal about history things.
Oh, because 314.
I get it.
It's also Einstein's birthday.
Oh.
Oh, 314.
I thought that was Hitler's birthday, only in backwards.
No, that's 420.
420.
Oh, so then that's not an allusion to let's go to school.
And let's not forget in Sudan, of course, they had the brutal militia called the Janja
Weed, and someone should get the Janja Weed some ganja weed.
That's a good idea.
That'll chill them out.
That'll stop killing people.
That was really the name?
Janja Weed?
Yeah.
Janja Weed, yes.
I bet it was spelled in a way that I would have mispronounced.
Well, it's an Arabic word, so there are multiple romanizations of Arabic words, depending on
what sounds are contained in the word.
And we must always take the worst one to mean that Boston and Baltimore, anything else starting
with a B will suddenly come under...
Never mind.
I was having one in my ear.
One of your alphabets?
Yeah.
That's what that attacks?
Yeah, I guess that's what they do.
You know, when they control you.
An attack by bees?
You know, Dave, you're not the only one who gets weird things about certain letters in
the alphabet popping up in certain places.
You're not the only one.
Well, I didn't say I was the only one.
I certainly welcome any company if you need, you know, if you can tell me how to help us.
Like last week or something, like on Arsenio Hall, all of the guests had an O-R in their
name at some place.
Like even the first name or last name had an O-R in it somewhere.
See, but whenever I visit the language...
It's a conspiracy.
It is.
It's a single mission.
Everything is a conspiracy.
Be dark, ugly, full of smoke.
We're all in at least one conspiracy.
There is not light for love to live.
I'm very suspicious of the Greek letter chi or chi.
Chi?
Yeah, you know, it looks like an X. I'm very suspicious of that letter.
Yeah, that's, you know, rho chi.
That doesn't sound...
That sounds almost dirty.
It doesn't sound religious.
Greek?
What do you expect?
Sometimes transliterated as a CH or a KH or just an H or just a C or just a K.
And Dad, it looks like an X.
In the original Greek, it looks like an X.
And it's a sound.
Actually, we love our Greek friends.
I don't know where I'd be without those.
We love our Greek food.
Festivals.
Yeah, pastitsios and usakas and what do they call them?
Hildebarons.
Galactoburikos.
Not to be confused with Galactus, which are devourer of worlds.
Yes.
Hellenicius.
Galactus.
Devourer of Galactoburikos.
That's a dumb joke.
The Milky Way.
It makes sense.
If he's eating the milk custard, he's eating...
The very word Galaxos.
The very word Galaxos is derived from the Latin word for milk.
Milk wag.
And also the Greek word for milk, halah.
What's the Greek word for milk?
The Greek word is halah.
I don't know the Greek word for milk.
It's an aspirated gush, you know, it's halah.
What letters are in it?
You're supposed to put A-L-A's for sure, and I don't know what the ha is.
Alpha, lambda, alpha.
We're getting dorky because Stank's turning up the music.
You know what it is?
This time.
That was smart.
Well, actually, the music caught me.
I was thinking, wow, they're getting heavy there.
Dork talk.
Yes, it is a...
It's a good thing I've never been pulled over by the police under suspicion of drunk driving
because they make you recite the alphabet, and I'm such a nerd, I'd say, which one?
Somehow I don't think that would go over well.
I don't think it would go over real well, you're right.
Alpha may be the...
Napoleon, you smiling little architect.
Bend over and let me count to three.
Huh?
Gosh, Sarge, it's been a long time, you know?
It makes me want to launch into Dolomite's ABCs of Love, which I've memorized, but I
can't even say the first letter until after 11 o'clock tonight when we're in safe harbor.
See, there I go again.
It's just like playing YouTubes for a radio audience.
I actually heard a...
Which I get so mad at, and yet...
I heard a terrible low bit rate MP3 played on WZN.
I think it was WZAK the other night.
I think it was Friday night.
I can believe that on WZAK.
Oh, no!
What happened to Dave?
Is it our Dave?
I hope he didn't run out of time for his new machine.
Oh, the new improved machine that runs out of time.
The empty battery.
Dave has a new buzz, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
But it's a wind-up phone where it only lasts about half an hour before he has to wind it up again.
And if I know Dave, that means a trip to the convenience store, so he won't be back.
Now, now.
That might not be...
Oh, no, look.
There he is.
Yay!
Is that the Dave?
Yes, it's starting to get very quiet, so I paused to look, and I got ended.
Well, that's what happens with a new phone.
Your call was dropped, sir.
Is that like a butt call?
The number or code you have dialed is incorrect.
No, a butt call is when you leave it in your pocket, and it's not on.
And try again.
Show off.
Message seven.
Switch.
Yeah, that was a little too quick.
I've got the Cinco de Mayo disillusionments here at the very end.
Did you know the Pancho Vito was actually subterranean?
Pancho Vito?
Yeah.
Was a mole man underground?
Well, La Cucaracha is a song that extolled his truth to go out and smoke heroin.
I saw an underscore, cause this is the most significant.
Yeah.
Whenever evil comes into your element, and evil only plays out before you really think
Really, for us, we just sit on the internet, and the only way to get the results from our
experiment is to make sure my email account works.
Great.
When you have an externalized belly button, it means you drive one of those German cars
whose logo looks like the Olympic logo, but there's one less ring.
It's a class thing, man.
Oh, wow.
I didn't know there was any correlation between Audis and, oh, that's right, Audis.
I could see a square.
I was staying out of that one myself.
It took me a while.
I never got there.
I'm very slow on the uptake.
I didn't get there until after you did.
Well, you have to have a little bit of dough to be able to afford an Audi,
so I still would like to espouse more classism.
I don't have enough dough to even know about Audis.
You know, in Renaissance Venice, having an Audi belly button was a sign of luxury and noble birth.
That's what I thought.
That's what I thought there, because I could just see all these corrupt squires,
you know, these sweet Terry, these escuderos all with their belly buttons hanging out,
you know, giving people orders and stuff.
Well, it's been traditional for inbred nobility to kind of consider whatever their particular deformity is
to be the height of fashion and be...
Oil diseases.
Right.
So everybody, the Habsburg lip was very, very popular for a long time.
The Habsburgs didn't have belly buttons at all.
Oh, like gray aliens.
They just painted.
Their food was painted onto their skin.
Again, they were so sensitive, those nobles.
That's sensitive.
Like the Bodhisattva before them, they were born pure in a lake by themselves.
They said, I want to be born, and I create the molecules right there, and that's what they did.
For a while, anyway.
That's amazing.
Tell us more, Dave.
I can't.
How is Babi formed?
Babi?
Yes, how is Babi formed?
How is Babi formed?
Babi?
Babi.
Babi formed is very simple to make.
It is a geometric figure consisting of 25 sides.
I'm dating myself.
That was an internet meme.
You know that number pi, actually, huh?
Membo pi?
You know, I'm just old enough to remember old internet memes.
How about all your base all belong to us?
I'm just old enough to be in the continent partially.
Well, yeah, how is Babi formed is much more recent.
I'm just older than all your base all belong to us.
Yes.
Although I saw a YouTube that collected the internet memes since the internet sort of started
for most people in the 90s.
Like Go-See?
Yeah, like that.
And I was proud of myself.
I only recognized about one third of them.
I was not so much of a geek that I understood every single internet meme that had come along.
Although Princess Wee and I participated in the...
What not Uma Guma, what was that song we did?
The Yaba Yaba song.
The Romanian...
Numa Numa!
That was...
Creative...
The Yaba Yaba dude song.
...information.
Huh?
That was very controversial, actually, because people thought you were cussing when you were
just speaking...
Oh, we got in big trouble.
...either Romanian or Jibberish.
Dutch?
They couldn't understand.
I speak fluent Jibberish.
English that sounded like the Romanian words.
So they were English words, but they didn't really make sense.
And the dirty-minded station manager here assumed...
He was absolutely certain he heard us saying the F-word when we were just saying, rather
Bob didn't stay.
She'd rather Bob didn't stay.
Yeah.
Somewhere, she'd rather Bob didn't stay turned into something...
She'd rather if I could stay.
You sure it wasn't Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob
Bob?
Something like that.
Yeah.
Anyway, we almost lost the hour of sloth.
I had to show him the Romanian lyrics and then the English lyrics that we had translated
over and make him listen to it while reading the lyrics.
Then he could hear that we weren't actually cussing on a thing we'd prepared for a primetime
radio show on a really, really famous, world-famous station, WCSB.
You would never jeopardize that.
I never jeopardized our FCC license that way.
Never.
You know, I actually have the evidence saved.
I violated the terms of service on YouTube and downloaded the video from YouTube.
Oh, yeah.
You know, there was a recent study that said that, by golly, despite what the entertainment
business says, they haven't lost any money at all to file sharing.
How would they even figure out how much money they lost?
You know how they come up with the numbers they come up with?
They assume that every single illegal legal...
No.
Every quote-unquote illegally copied file out there would have been a paid movie ticket.
Yeah, right.
Or a paid DVD purchase or a paid CD purchase.
That's their assumption.
So they multiply that by 10,000, square that.
And that's where they come up with that number, which is totally made up because it assumes
that every single person who took something when they saw an opportunity to get it for
free would have paid money for it had they not seen that opportunity.
Right.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's a bit faulty logic.
And like Econ 101, price and demand.
When they start the study, like...
You know, there's a relationship between them.
Right.
I would only watch The Lone Ranger if it was free.
Yeah.
I would only watch The Lone Ranger if all the Indian maidens were all bare naked.
But that doesn't have anything to do with what they're trying to do to our minds right
now.
They're blinking in little hexagonal figures into our heads.
And they tell us to do all kinds of funny things.
Well, not usually funny, ha ha ha, that way, but...
But they don't have to do that.
All they have to do is put on stupid sitcoms and get the same result.
People are going to be like, oh, I'm not going to do that.
People are sitting there watching the sitcoms.
Big Brother doesn't have to watch you as long as he knows you're watching.
That was another slanted study.
What you're watching.
He created that.
So...
Literally.
So I...
Yes.
So what?
So, hell, that's all...
It's a bunch of BS.
It's just all a bunch of BS.
Well, you can bare your chest or you can bare your entrails.
You know, baring your chest, you do a gorilla-like thing like I revolt against this revolting
situation.
And then you run away and hide.
For seven years.
Maybe nine years.
Because you can't bear it.
You just can't bear what they're doing to you, friends.
Well, it's like...
Yes?
It's like Jerry Lewis said.
I'm sorry.
Yes, yes, yes?
Yes?
No, I was just saying it was like what Jerry Lewis said.
Like Jerry Lewis said.
I'm sorry.
Like Jerry Lewis said before...
Do you remember the actor's union of...
I think it was 1952.
No, he didn't say that.
He didn't.
That doesn't even approximate what he was trying to say.
His wisdom was so vast.
His countenance was so beatific when he looked at you with that cute smile.
Jerry Lewis?
Yeah.
He's a genius in France.
Wait a minute.
You weren't supposed to say that now.
Alan, I was supposed to have already forgotten what he said at the conference.
Oh, no. Yeah, that's right.
Okay, I'm going to whittle myself away from the situation by pretending I didn't say anything at all.
That's what we all do, Dave.
We all sit around pretending you didn't say anything at all.
Unfortunately, there are people out there recording stuff off the Internet.
It's automatically utilized.
Dave, you and Susie the Flusie got a compliment on one of my Facebook affiliates.
Official subgenius pages, the subgenius foundation.
Oh, her breasts are much lovelier than mine.
That's what someone was saying.
Well, no, they were saying they didn't know who's they loved best, Susie's or yours.
Yeah.
They said, I don't know who I love best, the cowboy or Susie.
They didn't mention me, I noticed.
After all these years of manhood, we're both wearing the same cup size of bra by now.
Does Bob have a Twitter account?
A Twitter account?
There are so many people using the name.
Bob Dobbs with Twitter accounts.
Who cares?
I'm just kidding.
I heard about their IPO coming out.
I get the feeling it's going to start sucking even more now that it's publicly traded.
It's going to have to.
I mean, just think of the way things move in geometric speed.
When something happens and like five things happen as a consequence of that,
and then 20 things happen as a consequence of that, and then 100,
and it keeps on going.
And that's what you, you know, when you're driving home late at night after about four, five, 16 beers,
that's what you've got to pay attention to.
You've got to keep your eyes on that little white line.
When you start seeing double, just close one eye.
Yeah.
That does not always work, actually, but I'd rather not go into that story.
That's how I survived my 20s.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
Staring at the road through one eye.
Sometimes you have to hold your hand over one eye because you're not coordinated enough.
No, if you have to hold it.
No, you have to hold it.
You have to hold one eye.
If you have to do it with your hand, then you definitely shouldn't be driving.
If we had known about our pineal glands.
That would be going too far.
Yes, yes.
That's the threshold.
And what about the combination of closing one eye and then only having one headlight working?
Or having your pineal gland open again.
By a damn steam truck.
Well, you know who's in our driver's seat out in the parking lot right now and our fan?
Did you notice?
I didn't see, no.
J.R. Bob.
J.R. Bob's is sitting there slumped against the window.
Guarding the car.
Because the thief was back last week.
Right.
Oh, yes.
Rob knows.
The devil's soul.
We've all been hit by the Jager Meister.
You know what they never...
It's raining tonight, though, so we'll be safe.
They do not strike when it's raining.
Fair weather.
I shouldn't have said that out loud.
Who doesn't?
Who doesn't strike?
Everything strikes in the middle of the weather.
It matters not whether it's regardless.
It matters not whether it's raining or not anymore.
If I were going to take up a life of crime, I would think a rainy night would be the best time.
Yeah.
Well, it's the most atmospheric.
And photogenic, that's for sure.
Problem is how we wear glasses in the rain.
That just makes things harder.
Right.
I can't wear contacts because my life's so miserable.
I ran out of tears years ago, so I can't wear contacts.
Yeah, I'm the same way, actually, Dr. Sinister.
That's why I can't wear contacts.
What can you do when your pineal gland wears out?
Can you go to some ophthalmologist?
Some ophthalmic cerebral cortex or something like that for that?
I mean, where can you go when your pineal gland starts to shrink?
Well, you have to have insurance for one thing.
I have to get my eyelids replaced soon, but I don't know where the money's going to come from.
And they consider that a cosmetic thing, our insurance company.
That's cosmetic.
And then you have to find a donor.
You have to have somebody with a dream of...
You don't have to have eyelids.
Just put your hand over your face when you need to blink.
Oh, great.
Thanks.
You know.
I'm having nasal tumor.
Donor's implanted and stuff.
I can't find a donor.
Why do they keep saying Obamacare when it's really Romneycare?
Well, the best is when you ask them, don't you think the Affordable Care Act would be better than Obamacare?
Oh, yeah.
Obamacare is terrible.
The Affordable Care Act.
I can...
Yeah, that one sucks so bad.
Keep your government hands off my Medicare.
Oh, there's a whole string of man-on-the-street interviews that demonstrates that effect.
But you could do that with just...
About any...
Yep.
Anything with two names.
Think about how dumb the average person is.
And by definition, half the population...
Is half as smart as that.
Is even dumber.
Terrifying.
We're getting near the end of this brilliant show.
It's near the hour.
Brilliant.
Bloody freaking brilliant.
The part where Stank said, you must all leave now.
You must all leave now.
You're all banned.
Every one of you.
Except for the ones who lied and said you were banned when you weren't really.
You're the only ones who aren't banned.
What the hell is that?
And we're not banned.
All those posers.
Start rehearsing tomorrow.
Because we're having a band reunion.
Not that guy.
Friends, you're unfortunately listening to the Hour of Slack from the Church of the Subgenius.
For more information about that or anything, you can look at subgenius.com.
Subgenius does not have an O in it, but dot and com do.
It has two S's on the end.
Don't forget that part, kids.
Calm down.
If you miss out on the double S's at the very end, your brown descendants is a pervert in
Utica, New York or someplace.
So always remember when you're smelling the church of the subgenius, there's two S's
at the end of it.
And that makes it a little bit funnier and easier for the kids to remember.
Actually, that's my first name that has an O.
It has two S's that make it funny.
But let's leave that alone.
It's got a pair of bird eyes in front of its nostril, doesn't it?
It's because your first name is Mr. Smith.
It has two S's in it.
I get it.
Hey, Dave.
I, Evan Stang and Princess We Are Doe have been your hosts on this Hour of Slack with
special guest stars, Lonesome Cowboy Dave and Dr. Sinister, who's going to take over
this microphone in about one minute.
Hey, Dave.
So I'm going to fade.
Oh, go ahead.
Dave, please call back for synesthesia, man.
You're welcome anytime.
I'm afraid I've spent all of my minutes.
He's used up all of his phones.
Oh, no.
It takes him two hours to wind up the phone to use it for half an hour.
Yeah.
Well, next time you have the juice, man, please, please.
Yes.
My brother.
They gave him one of those Oblonga phones.
One of those Reagan phones?
Yeah.
Right.
It was a Reagan phone, yep.
Okay.
I'm going to fade everyone out and let the whatever.
I'm not sure what's going on.
You could just see there were a lot of things going wrong in the world and nobody was saying
anything about it.
You know, Bob had long since faded from the present memory.
Iron Man is a great story.
You know, revenge.
I have to say, I've been watching it for a while now.
And when I heard that story, I'm like, yeah.
Con.
Coming up in just a couple days.
Yes.
All right.
And I know I've already been told that I'm to refer to it as the con.
You call it the con.
I mean, you can call it the con.
You can call it the con.
No, I had a nerdy guy say, don't call it the con.
You must call it the con.
He called it the con.
He's going to call it the con for now on.
Do you think they were playing a joke?
I mean, because I'm going there.
I'm going to the con in a couple of days.
I'm going to make a little appearance there.
And I thought maybe you could tell me what to expect because I've never been.
Everybody talks about it.
And I know that this is your thing.
This is your wheelhouse.
I like con.
There's a lot of things there that I like.
And most of the shows that I make or have gotten involved with.
Captain Bob was in command of our sturdy little vessel.
And you could tell he really hated his job.
Well, like I always say, work is for people that don't know how to fish, especially when
you're out here off the Mexican coast.
Yeah.
I'm out here on the Mexican coast catching 25, 30 sailfish a day on a good day and a
good buzz and a bunch of naked ladies on a bad day.
Listen, I know a lot of you thought the world was going to end on Saturday.
Some of you even quit your jobs and sold your possessions.
What a bunch of idiots.
It seems to be a brainwashing facility of some type.
Wherever there's a brainwashing cult, there's always a power hungry leader behind it all.
I understand.
I get it.