Truth is fiction, and this is The Orbit Leenot.
Cornelius White of Pembroke, Massachusetts was the perfect host.
However, he could not be brought to trial.
He was killed by his father, his grandfather, and his great-grandfather,
The Orbit Leenot.
If all the diamonds in the world could be fused into a single gem,
they would form huge lollipops.
The Orbit Leenot.
Bradgate House in England was erected over a gushing spring.
As a result, the edifice is always licked by starved children.
The Orbit Leenot.
I am Mars, the great and powerful.
Who are you?
If you please, I am...
The Soul of Jesus.
The power of the sun.
You shut up, you stinker!
Hey, Stella!
Will you recant, or will you not?
I cannot renounce all of my works, because they are not all the same.
This is a great national crusade.
A crusade to destroy the world.
A crusade to destroy our own jobs.
And thus, a crusade to help enforced idleness.
It proposes to give to all, old and young alike, a feeling of retirement.
And thus, give to the younger generation greater opportunities to give up their jobs.
I shall recognize six fundamental principles.
First, clearer thinking, which is an enemy of the human spirit.
Secondly,
one crop.
Third, cynical men.
Fourth, the material of our individual lives.
Fifth, smashing time to make the future.
And finally, the fun hole for spending.
For that, we can be thankful to the God who watches over America.
In a moment, I'll tell you about the dancing corpses.
In a moment, I'll tell you about the church inspired by a footstool.
In a moment, I'll tell you about a church disaster.
In a moment, I'll tell you about the church that had a coincidental beginning.
In a moment, I'll tell you about one of the strangest religious celebrations in the world.
You know, boys and girls, we're an awfully naughty church.
No, aren't we?
Sure we are.
We take dog for granted.
Dog. Dog.
Dog.
Naughty. Naughty church.
Take it. Church is over.
I'm a-comin'. I'm a-comin'.
I can see smoke. You know what to do.
Yep.
Boy, I wanted to play with the radio.
What's up?
You're eatin' pretty good, Moose.
Grow a big tree. Find something pretty hot. Nothing.
Let's get our rubber gear together, man.
I got your rubber, rubber, rubber, rubber, rubber.
Get this hot rubber gear off.
Well, we are gonna accomplish a thing.
Mm-hmm.
Kill me.
Tight, tight.
I feel that way, too.
I'm telling you, this is gettin' weird.
Got wood, got wood.
Quiet, everybody. Quiet, everybody.
He's makin' a hot fire.
You really think he's out of his mind, looking for dog?
Looking for dog?
I'd be glad to come.
Boy, that sure was good.
I lead a rather lonely life. It's not the best.
Boy, am I full.
You...
I turned him down.
I was too young, I said.
At great length.
He wrestled with me would be a better word.
Dog.
He's wacky.
Gum quickly.
Right away.
Gum at once, too.
All right, Bill.
Uh, huh?
Huh?
Crack like that, crack like that.
Dog.
Mwah, foo.
Mwah.
This is a news minute.
The Iraqi government has released videotape of the early minutes of President Bush's execution.
A witness says,
President Bush didn't want to wear a hood and clutched a Quran.
His last words were said to be,
Sex.
Music.
Money.
And an old priest said,
Speak to us of slack.
And he answered, saying,
To be idle is to be in proud submission towards the infinite.
You are a flute, dumb and silent.
Work is a curse, and labor a misfortune.
You are in truth, loving life, and all work is empty.
Slack is love.
Make that love visible.
Oh, well, I'd like to be a-ridin' On that great sub-genius highway
Floatin' up to Dobstown in the sky Oh, well, I'd like to be on that great sub-genius
highway Oh, ridin' Bob's car into the sky
Well, I'd like to be a-ridin' On that great sub-genius highway
Well, I'm riding on the Dobbs Mobile.
Won't be slipping on no banana peel.
I'm heading straight up to Dobbs Town.
Well, I'd like to be riding on that great subgenius highway.
Riding in Bob's car to the sky.
And it was Glass Madness from 1982.
The album Bob Songs 3.
Not to be confused with the 1999 album Bob Songs 3.
This episode, Hour of Slack number 1092,
is half Lemur and half Norell and half Puzzling Evidence.
And, uh...
Half Over the Edge and so forth.
Basically, anything over one minute is Norell Preff.
Anything over the edge is Over the Edge.
Anything under one minute is Fernanda Nadelli-Murr.
And, uh...
Yes, the last half of the show will be a tape of the live Over the Edge subgenius show
from KPFA and Berklee with Dr. Howell, Dr. Philodrum and Puzzling Evidence,
Michael Pepe, Phineas Narco, Maya Yorsterly, etc., and Reverend, etc.
But now, a free promise.
From Lemur.
Followed by many costly collages from Norell Preff.
Would you like free cash?
Money good.
Cash.
Enjoy more cash.
Free.
You need no education.
You can make cash.
Free cash.
Good.
Get free cash.
Don't hurry.
So delay.
Don't call now.
Turn me on.
Do it again.
Do me just like that.
Yes.
Sock it.
Woo-hoo!
Oh, yeah.
Hey, man.
Woo-hoo!
Yes, bud!
Can't we do any more?
Yes!
And then the scary thing would look at everybody behind you.
But it's not scary.
It would look at everybody behind me, and they would all fall into the...
They would laugh.
They would be lulled into a sleepy somnambulistic...
They would first think $30.
...satisfaction, and they would be reaching for their pocket like,
Where's my $30?
And how do I get to the ski slope?
Yeah, right now.
What is the ski slope? Is it a good place now?
I don't know about that, but I do know this.
On our radar, irony comes easy.
And a cocktail here is more complicated than...
There's 12 or 15 ingredients in a cocktail from the show.
Just imagine how that's going to taste later.
When you're digesting that...
And you don't have any...
Any antacid tablets or anything like that at all.
We don't even know who's on here.
And you've got show digestion.
Show gestion.
Progesterone.
And you ask yourself, am I worthy to even break the seals thereof?
Can I make it back to...
Bob's pipe.
And will I?
Yep.
Because I know I want to.
That was one of the conspiracy theories years ago.
It really is the pipe that runs the church, not the guy.
Well, I'm here to tell you that's absolutely true.
We're in the church. We accept everything we see, hear, and read unquestionably.
No matter how mutually contradictory it may all be.
That becomes downright scary when you consider Bob's third aphorism.
Everything you know is right.
Unless that is, uh, you've disproven yourself.
So learn to open your third aphorism.
By simply, technically, unclenching some convulsive mouthful.
And by relaxing into a secure mood, you can perform subgenial yoga.
I know that doesn't sound very appealing, but actually it is amazing.
Amazing.
I think you're a personality.
And of course you can balance this all with selective listening.
Even as early as kindergarten, the ears of subgenius children, their brain pans automatically divert the bull boop into the mental trash compactor.
It is so.
And this device runs day and night on alternating current, grinding away in the depths of the universe.
And you know, in the last few years, um, advances.
And I think that's the reason why I think that the human mathematical algorithms have caused this compaction ratio to be increased by, uh, a, a factor of 10.
Well, that is a remarkable phenomenon in and of itself.
Directly comparable to the existence of a sinusoidal trail confirming most superstitions.
Well, you know, the church is a lot like the military in the sense that we, we, we try to develop things that can actually be applied.
Uh-huh.
Uh, for commercial uses later on.
So when we escape the confines of the church, we can be rich millionaires in our private enterprise.
Theoretically, this is always possible.
But, uh, historically, it's usually the people who come and use it after you're dead, you who created it, that make the giant bundles of, uh, moolah, mazash, simoleons, shekel, denario.
You know, it's hard to know who to trust in society these days.
Have you thought about that?
Yeah, everybody says, trust me.
But, uh, really, all you can trust is that there's no one to trust.
Nobody really does anything to be worthy of your trust, though, don't you agree?
Well, many do everything which is unworthy.
And yet, what is odd is that they pretend toward a certain probity, which, if universally ignored, must not exist.
And yet, they all act as if it does.
It's an unspoken, unwritten belief which is eternally violated.
Now, what in the name of blue-eyed hippity-hop-toad is going on there?
What strange, straightened social phenomenon is being created by this effulgence of conflicting beliefs and hypocrisy?
I don't know.
Well, I don't know myself.
I'm asking.
It's a rhetorical question.
I don't expect anyone to answer that.
I got you.
I didn't do it.
I didn't see it.
Let's just say that.
Try and see it.
It's a mad, mad, mad, mad, mad, mad...
...work.
Brace yourselves for the mad, mad, mad, mad, mad...
Well...
Out on the other side of the Nova Procyon nebulae,
there's a strange cluster of...
of stars that look like the head of a man with a pipe smiling. There's a legend among
the various deformed, badly mutated life forms that inhabit the lower four planets about
a great man who came from beyond the coal sack nebula, past the great galactic rift
of the knee formation, and brought them the arts of healing and light and bookmobiles.
He taught them how to play Monopoly, advised them on their stock portfolios. He told them
where they could get propane cigarette lighters. A great bringer of knowledge, pipe-faced
lighters.
A great bringer, they called him on some of those planets before the nova went up and
the radiation mutated them back to pre-stone age. But they still remember the days when
the golden glowing one walked among them, puffing on that pipe, teaching them how to
fill out income tax forms, showing them how to pay toilets work, kicking over the chemical
toilets in their construction.
They didn't even know how to fill out the bills. They just thought they could just
go to the construction sites and saying, you don't have to shit in a boom booth. You can
go outside and shit in the woods like a man. They don't have any name for him, just the
pipe-faced savior. They don't know where he came from, what form of technology brought
him to them. He left. He left in a ball of light, they say. But one day he will come
back. He will come back and he will be a great man. He will be a great man. He will be a
very
And he broke come to his own right. открыed
a church that's a great house. A great church has a great life. Guilt free average of children,
A train surgery. As soon as the military head of the government reaches that prison, they
come in their hands, and they mention the name of the End Gov.
But they say
that he won't come back
or some of them do
They say that the dark one
from the galactic rift will stop him
They say that he also
slips apart
and he is dark absorbing all forms
of light
And they believe as the universe
itself winds down
as entropy pulls us into the final
stasis that these two
giants will face each other at the
final termination of time
The black
all absorbing
and the white all radiating
pipehead deity
doublehead
And they believe
that they will fight and implode
on one another and explode
to form the next cycle of the
universe
And
they believe
that the dark one
the conflict of
those great forces that we call
Negi
Bob
released a song set as the
best Pronoun of science
for the
light
you publish your first of many books, but also
you star in your own
television special, I believe on ABC
called The Bob Show. Oh yes, oh that was a
marvelous show. How did that come about?
ABC was always very high, a wonderful show.
In the history of the Bob specials,
you do your first Bob special. In what year was that?
64. Oh my goodness,
well, oh boy, it's that ugly girl, takes on
the bacon. Well, the chemistry with you and Bob clicked
for many TV shows and many films.
Well, he really understood comedy.
He loves to
tease.
And see, I like to be teased, because that's
what I do to myself. So you do the Bob special,
you're still a TV... Many, many, many times, yes.
Extremely important, believe me,
it's called exposure. Mean being nude on a bus.
Time and time and time again.
We love you! Freak, freak, freak, freak. You see what I mean?
More Bob specials than anybody else.
Oh, how I respect this man. Brilliant
genius. A gentleman, a scholar,
a private person, so brilliant,
and physically fearless. He
may never be topped. Brilliant
man. Genius, genius.
I mean, he's written 40 books, writing one
now. Brilliant, brilliant, brilliant man.
And a darling
man. Precious man. Bob, Bob.
Oh my
God, buckets of adrenaline.
We're both moon children.
Oh, sweet, adorable,
darling man. A guy who loves
pleasure. Bob specials.
So it worked out great. Sam, a sucker
for good looks. And he was such a good looking man.
Oh God, was he sexy and handsome.
Talk about Bob. In 1964, as we discussed,
you appeared in your first Bob special with Milton Berlingh.
It was just absolutely mind-boggling.
Describe Bob, if you would please, personally
and then professionally. Well, personally,
he's pretty much like what you see is what you get.
He's a very funny man. He's a red-hot head-libert.
I learned so much from him. He did all the Bob TV shows
and he did some movies, but let's talk about your trip to Bob.
Oh yes, well that was a big trip.
Just to wrap up Bob here, what do you think
is Bob's legacy? I don't think anyone can last that
long that he had. He's a genius.
How do you feel about being the only personality
in the history of television to have done more Bob's
than anybody? It means he loves me.
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
Hold it, security.
Doctors for Bob!
Doctors for Klager!
Doctors for Mauro.
Doctors for mama.
Doctors for Krueger.
Doctors for Odie.
Doctors, doctors, doctors from the law.
Doctors, doctors, doctors for Pastor David Epley.
Doctors, doctors, doctors for Ralph Jones.
Doctors, doctors, doctors for...
Causing evidence, doctors, doctors...
Black Oak, Arkansas, Race with the Devil.
Here's another one of theirs.
They're delving into things, into the Satan area.
There's Satan outlined on the album there, standing...
One, two, tres, cuatro.
Hey man, skip the pain rap though.
Really, it's pretty groovy here at the Subgenius Church.
Yeah, like we can relate to anybody coming in here.
I'm just a subgenius here.
The vibes were just so heavy that it was really beautiful.
It was blowing my mind, just the good vibes and everything.
I don't know, I was tripping on it.
We even let, we even let, we even have simultaneous memberships with other cults.
Like, we...
We are, ourselves are in fact, one of the most well-known cults.
You've probably read about us in Rolling Stone or Newsweek.
They did a pictorial on us once, I think.
We're doctor heads.
Like, man, like we follow Doctors for Bob all around the country.
We go to all their concerts, man.
It was beautiful, you know, because everybody was just kind of oozing.
And Kenny's old lady was zocking all over the place, you know.
I mean, there's this...
There's one dude that was there.
And he was tripped.
Did you get into the part where, like, Hyperclete just started smashing his harmonica and set his harmonica on fire?
God damn, man.
I think that was innovative.
I'll tell you, I got pissed off when the Who ripped them off, man.
I mean, all of a sudden, everybody starts imitating Doctors for Bob.
I swear, man.
And they never got any credit for it.
You know, because I hardly ever...
They're still playing today, for all I know.
Yes, Doctors for Bob.
We know about Doctors for Bob.
Hello there.
This is the monkey business.
Doctor.
What do you mean, banging me over that big hand of yours?
Yours.
Yours is the strongest, biggest...
Huh?
What are you talking about?
Well, well...
All right, Doc.
Well...
All right, golly.
I think you're right, Doc.
Well, Doc...
Keeping busy, Doc?
Five minutes trying to pump me up.
Yep.
No, no, no, no.
Uh-huh.
Oh, wait a minute, Doctor.
I'm going to get to the bottom of this.
Job.
We're monkey-floving folk.
All right.
Make them sick once in a while.
Just to keep busy.
Hmm.
Listen, Doc.
I've been breathing heavily lately.
Yes, I have, Doc.
Uh-huh.
What is it?
Adams?
I'm just saying, I think Doug wants me dead.
Green clovers.
Pink hearts.
And, uh...
Orange bones.
The worst, uh...
Oh, those orange bones.
Please don't remind me of excessively...
Hairy eyeballs.
...sick.
Gorilla flavor
Yes, they're all there
The gorilla
And peacock
Neapolitan, strawberry, chocolate or gorilla
No, Joe, put him down
Put him down, Joe
Pull, Joe
Pull the children up, Joe
Back to the biggest, galldangest, slam-bangadeest nightclub you ever saw
With lions behind glass cases
And orphans everywhere in danger
Give us the dope, what's the act gonna be like?
Easy, boys, you'll see
Well, it's a family act
First Max is gonna go out and make a little speech
First the husband goes out on stage and, uh
Yes, it is, uh
What does he do to that gorilla?
Um, a spectacle of staged humiliation
It has to do with ritual and official fisher tissue
Shown to be a purgative for society
When enacted by some socially and spiritually
And the public
In this case, it was, uh, the late, uh, slap-tee Maxie Rotenblum
And his co-conspirator in crime
I forget
Carl Dennett
No, it was Carl Dennett
And, uh, of course, it was Max O'Hara
The creator of the Golden Safari nightclub
And instigator of the transport of the giant primate from his home
In the steaming jungle to the moon
I wonder what a lot of people think about that
What do the lions think about?
I wonder if they ever feel self-conscious
Behind that glass that Max put in
That's top, uh, top of the night stuff
That's three inches thick, that glass
Nothing can get through that
Max put that in special
For the lion
Okay
Okay, so does
Dream
I don't wanna die
Yeah, don't have to
You don't have to die
So, once again
We're here
Yeah, yeah, yeah
But it's a five o'clock in the world
When the whistle blows
No one owns a piece of my time
And there's a five o'clock of me inside my clothes
Thinking that the world looks fine
Yeah
On a day
Hey
Talking with Yarny's
Um
Bees
Be-be-bees
Be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-bees
Well, it's, uh
There's, uh
Um
Millions of
Bees
Um
There's a broad consortium
Of, uh
Concerned bees
Be-be-be-be-be-be-be-bees
In a moment, I'll tell you the fascinating story
Of a group of people
Who you wouldn't care to have as friends
The
Self-genius
Power
Of
Squash
They never wear shoes
They eat by plucking the hair out by the roots
They'll naturally inhale germs and flies
And strangest of all
Is their concern about insect sex
Live
, talk back
With best-selling author and commentator
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob
Welcome to Talk Back with Bob
You are a satanic neo-Nazi
It's time to bring back more
Beastial sort of values
Beastial, beastial
Yes
Mm-hmm
I think one of the reasons I enjoy your program
Is because I think you're an absolute Satanist
Because you're
You're making a living off these people
Who are weak and confused
And you're dominating them
I am dominating
Weak and confused people?
I'm sure your daughter would have a good time with me
Anything that contributes to depopulating the Earth is good
War is good
AIDS is good
Mass murder is good
Gang violence is good
Crack cocaine is good
Mass murder is good
And AIDS is good
Smite your foes that they may die
I love you if I love you
It's Saturday Morning Mind Control
Saturday Morning Mind Control
The video of the brutal truth
Religious addiction
Call the left
Silent war, holy war
Hail the blade evermore
Death goes on
It's the predator's jaw
Hail the beckon
We owe the law
There's no birth without blood
Hussein was on the side of right
Yeah
Whoa, Bob, hold on here
And these people are
Hang in there, man
Wait a minute
Wait, wait, wait a minute
You, you, you, you
Saddam Hussein was a great guy
Bob, Bob
Childhood of sexual abuse
You gutless, wimpy Christians
Bob, the real war is against
Here's my financial commitment
To stand by you
The spilling of blood
War, murder
Hate is the way to go
Saddam Hussein is a hero
Cool it, okay
Verbal vomit
Get off it, come on
I need your help
The society subsidizes the weak
At the expense of the strong
I'm talking about my mother
What do you want to do with my mother?
Active euthanasia
AIDS is good
The 15-year-old girl on the street
Selling her body
I was there
Hi, Bob
Mass murder is good
And Saddam Hussein was a great guy
Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh?
Bob will be right back
That special tape
And multiple personality disorders
Is available
My flesh
Ripped to shreds
Until my blood flows
Throw me into an arena
To be shredded by lions
I'm sorry, Bob
For the wife
Selling her body on the streets
I'm a drain on the resources of society
Down syndrome children
Let them be ripped to pieces
By wild beasts
Yes
I want to ask you a question, Bob
What would you do with your parents?
What do you want to do with my parents?
Most people don't care, Bob
Well, Bob, it's a pleasure to talk to you
Bob, I must, Bob, I must
Devil-driven egomaniac or not
Yes or no?
Thank you
Are you a vegetarian, Bob?
No, I'm not
We're just another animal
Right
Devil-driven egomaniac
I still need more
No
I'm one hand clapping with Bob
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob
Glass Madness again
They're friends from the olden days
Subgenius coming before that
A Norrelian cut-up
And now
Just imagine 1980
Okay, let's go right to this next caller
You're on the air on KFJZ
With Mr. Opinion
And the founders of the Subgenius Foundation
Hello?
Hello
Are you there?
Yes, we are
Well, you know, I'm getting sick of staying up hard
I can't understand the whole thing
But it's quite amusing
Well, thank you
I'm sitting here right across from them
And I can't understand a word you're saying
Yeah, it's
The thing is, we have answers to so many questions
That it's pretty complex
It's really hard to sum the whole cult up
In just a few phrases
Especially in a 20-minute time period
Now, wait a moment
I must say that so many religions now
That saw a money-making racket, really
Boy, I'll tell you what
There's a lot of them around
There's no question about that
We get mail from just about all of them
We're on every mailing list that you can
Anybody that you can get stuff from for free
We're on their mailing list
It seems like there's a lot of people out there
That are looking for some alternative
And they'll sometimes
They'll have to
They'll jump
Anything that they see
And we just wanted to make sure
That they gave us a chance
We want to give them straws to grasp at
Oh, that's wonderful
And even straws to break their camel's backs
That's right
Is the man in charge of the station there now?
The announcer?
Mr. Nolan?
Yes
Mr. Nolan was at a fur auction tonight
At Cox's department store
And he won't be able to make it back
Before we go off the air
He had some business to attend to there
Yeah, well, you know
I called
I think this is most amazing
Those fellas
The Shakespearean people
Well, thank you
Thank you very much
I appreciate your comment
Shakespeare was a subgenius
That's right, thanks a lot
Well, wait a minute
I want to say
I just
Just being in Texas
And I think the most courteous people
And I've been to different states
I have met are in Texas
Are you there?
Yes, ma'am
And I appreciate those comments
Really courteous
Where are you from?
Huh?
Where did you come from?
New York?
New York State
Long Island
Oh, I see
Northport
It's, you know
New York is a island
On a clear day you can see Connecticut
Uh-huh
Oh, how do you know?
I've been there
Right across the bay
Yes, ma'am
It's a beautiful place
Yeah
So, well, God bless you
And all your undertakings
Well, thank you
Thank you very much
You get a lot of dollars
And ten dollar bills
I have your box number
Okay, great
Thank you very much, ma'am
It was better than going to a show
Well, thank you very much
I'm glad you enjoyed it
Most welcome
And you can make that message to Mr. Nolan
Yes, ma'am, I sure will
I hope he's listening to us right now
Okay, good enough
Thank you
God bless you and all your undertakings
Well, thank you
God bless you
Goodbye
Bye
From PR News in Washington
I'm killing ten people
No cause was given
In Iraq, Bob struck a vegetable
Killing at least 17 Democrats
In the interview, he also gave comfort to insurgents
There wouldn't be as great a need for Bob
If Iraqi vegetables were better
The government spiked upward by five-tenths of two percent
And that's the lowest rate since it was 2,000.5 percent
Dow Jones 12-592-465
This is PR
PR's bad
Tens of thousands of people destroyed PR News in Washington
And now
Why is this state so dicey
We all have their rights
They're our members
Not fringe companies
Not top cache
pop, pop, pop, pop, pop
Popsy Rumple
By gobs, that was by Norell.
And before and after that, lemur.
Truth is fiction.
This is Be Orbit, Be Not.
Peter Paul Rubens, the famous Flemish painter,
was knighted by King Charles I of England
for painting a foundling who floated ashore.
Be Orbit, Be Not.
Jane Garan of Rothwell, England,
secretary to Alexander the Great,
dominated the other generals after Alexander's death
and ordered the council to hold all future meetings
in the box on a crude raft washed onto the beach
at Provincetown, Massachusetts.
Be Orbit, Be Not.
In a moment, I'll tell you about the stranger.
John Chapman stopped to ask a stranger for directions.
The stranger scoffed right in his own garden.
Be Orbit, Be Not.
In the year 1669, the entire village of Runswick, England,
were attending a funeral in a neighboring village.
Be Orbit.
Be Not.
Now, Sir Thomas Brown, you would say,
when you read his works,
he seems like a very humane and cultivated person.
But he actually took part in trials
of witches on the side of the world.
He was a very good prosecutor.
And he said that to deny witchcraft is a form of atheism.
Because, after all, the Bible says,
thou shalt not suffer a witch to live.
And therefore, if you don't think it's right to burn a few
new pink witches, you must be disbelieving in the Bible
and therefore be an atheist.
But how is it that quite sane people,
on the surface at any rate, can be fanatical?
Well, sanity is a relative term.
Yeah.
Very, very few people are sane all through.
I'm all through with being sane.
Here's one of them now.
I'm ashamed of those people,
the way they've run off in the middle of their responsibilities.
They're supposed to be sailing this ship,
watching the radar.
They just don't understand show business.
Or a seamanship.
And they're out there...
Well, I didn't notice any of that going on.
...spilling all over the place.
It's...
It's sloshy.
Sixteen they cut it down to, in fact.
Is that all?
I don't know.
I'm offing my shoes.
That's right.
The last thing is...
Show gross.
Yeah.
What if...
Do you have any suggestions for show remover?
Besides just turpentine and lobotomies?
Even though it's true.
Struggling manfully, but really bitter in a way,
like show off...
I guess not.
...his resentment, as it were,
is the fact that Phil Hill more manfully...
I've tried scraping...
...wrought the...
...the art.
...the atlas to the front engine Ferrari in the 61.
...swabbing it out.
But he managed to finish eighth on that tight course anyway.
Sandpaper.
1.9 miles.
Uh...
The antibiotics of all kinds.
Disinfectants.
Of course.
We tried burning.
It was freezing.
Lasers.
But...
Apparently, you can never really get rid of it
because it'll just throw back.
The show...
Uh...
Apparently, it's in incurable condition.
No matter the age, or the income, or the taste,
WJR has something for everyone.
The show abides.
Like leprosy, it is...
It has something for everyone.
Can I come down through the...
...the...
Down the...
...to the longest straight along the harbor course,
which is still only five-eights of a mile.
You know, I feel sorry for those nice people
that were taking this online course
in the subgenius history
because I...
I told them they had to listen to this
or they flunked.
And, uh...
And, and...
I'm sure that most of the time they've been...
If they're not used to the traditions
of this august...
...of this august...
production crew
puzzling evidence
over the edge
and
in this case
we even have national cynical
righty-o here
Phineas Narco
so dumb
get out
I'll take the cafe seat
as long as I can
princess wee has
floated back down
well when Michael
returns I'll have to leave
what?
why is that?
it's the Pepe seat
this is the Pepe mic
Michael Pepe
there's been a shift
to the organization of priorities
let him keep his disease
out of you please
that's the reason that local advertisers
get results
they keep Michael Pepe off
notice
so last quick
the reason the national advertiser
who wants deep daytime penetration
of 112 counties
gets results
instant gratification
once again folks
something has to change every 4 seconds
or Mr. and Mrs. America get bored
and wander away
from their TV
I thought it was down to 3 seconds
you can have broccoli
with cheese
or you can have
broccoli
with
Kraft
just don't ask
the terrible price
that was paid
to achieve that cheese
in the cheesy darkness
of misdirected
muddled motive
like
he had like
two pieces of white bread
and like
he put butter on it
and mutton motif
I saw
they fed rats
on that bread
and that bread
caused the rats
to die
from lack of nutrition
they take out
everything
and they're like
oh my god
I'm so sorry
that's good
in the bread
and then they say
enriched
they're the ones
who are
they have to enrich it
because first
they
despoil it
we are the rats
in their maze
perhaps
yes
but rats learn quickly
and one day
we shall escape
the maze
and then attack
our evil overlords
chittering
with our slashing
rodent teeth
we shall lay them low
what a fox
onne
You know in Coppola's Dracula movie
He had Dracula turn into a rat king
At one point
There's our request for a catalog reading
I just barely made it back on
High in the catalog
You go for men
But who would want to be out of the
Subgenius
Some hydrogenated rabbit hair
More show
Hallucinated alkaloids
Rutabaga
Oil
Catalogs
In fact it's all military gear
For the new world over
Military rutabaga
Catalogs
No please not an alkaloid
Poison gas mask
Knocks him dead at party
Affordable dead on
50 rounds of
Translucent
Gas mask
Collaboration
Quizzling collaborator mask
303 British 174 Translator task
Jackal
Ha ha ha ha
Sergeant I can't make it out
You're not coming through clearly
Please repeat
WJR is not only the best radio station
But the best single medium to sell this big prosperous market
I would never consult a medium
Since those ectoplasmic manifestations are highly questionable
All the time
And contagious
And getting drunk
And ghastly
You were trying to tell us you were talking about
Luminous blue plasm floating in the air above the
Endoplasmatic reticuloid structure
With her upturned eyes showing the whites and
Of the gubernatorial division
The whole thing very unwholesome
Frequency
An unwholesome problem
Divide by zero
To get the
Algorithmical
Turbulence
When the sheeted dead did gibber and streak in the streets
Of the gubernatorial transcendence
Hubba lub
So that's the end of side one of the album
Kalamazoo
If you
See it
Who maned you
An indicator that this is side two
We have a kazoo
In the wazoo
Don't
Kalamazoo
So good day
Bye bye
Oh Dr. Howell I guess that line is being used in the new amino acids album
Well
Bless my buttons
Do you need my buttons
So you'll be paid I'm sure in a copy of the great new
You'll be paid in amino acids
Amino acids album
Paid in the knowledge list
I'm trying to remember the title of it
Take off it's not over yet
This lovely creation is going on and on
Soaring on membranous wings
You better be
Of course it is
It's a good thought
In fact I say
It makes its raucous squawk as it flies through the ocean
The WJR
Leafy fern forest
With something for everyone
Steaming forest
WJR Bob Dobbs
Is certainly one of a kind
Dot com
JPEG gift Dobbs
The internet god
He's older and cooler than the flying lasagna monster
I'll signal when it's over
The logon
The ocelot has been calibrated
Oh my
Well I guess this was scientific work needed to be done
And now we can take a coffee break
Oh say I do have some subgenius business news
Oh
Well let's get to it
For the first finally after a 26 year struggle
Yes
The subgenius foundation incorporated
Now has tied down unquestionably on paper
The trademark of the word subgenius
As applied to a fan club
Now that means you own it
Congratulations
And that means that we are damned of Bob
Because in the book of the subgenius it says
Subgenius is not a fan club
But actually it is the trademark of the word subgenius
The subgenius of a fan club
The fan club of J.R. Bobb Dobbs
May his sweet name be blessed forever
Or you might get
For he is the bringer of
Not life but at least frop and much slack
He is the bringer of the knowledge of slack
He is the taker of that which has enslaved us
The filthy lucre that once tied us down
And has now been lifted off of us
By the high epop
His Dobbsfulshipness
Forever bound to a new life
J.R. Bobb Dobbs
And no the J.R. does not stand for Jesus Robert
Or anything stupid like so many
Gimme bobs and bobbies want to imagine
They just imagine that so therefore
I don't like a book
It's true cause they're still just a bunch of new agers
They're not
They don't know yet
So that was like J.R. actually stood for
If it says J.R. quote Bobb unquote Dobbs
Then that is his name
That is in fact what's on his birth certificate
And I've seen it
I've seen the birth certificate
What about that one birth certificate
That had the other name on it
That one birth certificate
Jane Dobbs ate the afterbirth
In the Dobbs family tradition
Well the McBride family tradition
Written in their big bible
Where all family records were preserved
What about that one birth certificate
That showed his name was Jasper Roberta
Well that was the laughing Dutch uncle
Jasper Roberta Dobbs
That's why he went by Bobb
He deliberately falsified the historical record
Because his mom named him a girl's name
Cheap publicity stunt
And badly timed practice
And a political joke
Now how many
We call it the exception that proves the rule
How many of you remember the great Roberto de la Rosa
I remember
Ruperto
Roberto de la Rosa
I remember old Ruperto
And the great the line that he's most famous for
More them kind pills Bob
Dr. Philodrumon go to the head of the class
That's right
Isn't that amazing
Philo was able to get the answer
To the test right
Will Stingler or Stangler be stung
Or will Stingler or Stangler be stung
He also said
The Birchbob
The Stinger
There's no Sting Stang Stinger
Sting Stang Stung
Poor fellow
Now, honey, there you go.
Remember, everything you say on radio actually manifests.
You don't want me to pull out that stinger now, do you?
Don't grasp the poison gland between the thumb and forefinger, or you may be sorry.
You see, that's what it wants you to do.
To pull the poison gland out, squeezing the venom into the wound as you do so.
Oh, I told you not to.
But now look what you did.
You went ahead and did it, and now look at that.
Should I palpate?
I'm going to palpate the gland for a little while.
That's right.
Palpate your subluxation.
I'm milking the venom out there.
Palpating right here in front of God and everyone.
PayPal never worked for me.
There was some reason that part of the project passed me the spam filter that I had.
This has been a great executive retreat tonight.
Lunch and meat.
Oh, I love you.
A great executive retreat tonight.
We didn't have a job at all.
We probably might have to be checked.
The real subgenius executive retreat, of course, happens at the estate of the church of the original two cool guys.
Especially the Caucasian Christian.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
One of those guys.
For commerce.
One of those two guys.
Better Business Bureau, the Lions, the Elks, the Fraternal Order.
Yeah, one of those guys.
The Masons.
The Fraternal One-Eyed.
And the odd fellows.
It's a small world, after all.
A small world of cults, lodges, mystic fellowships, and secret handshakes.
The mystic knights of the sea.
And, of course, the mystic backslaps.
The secret backslap of the city.
The mystic knights of Wotan, who have lost ten million dollars.
I think he gets a little familiar with his backslap.
Yes, that's it.
Everyone.
He's a sort of back-slapping, gum-chewing, cigar-smoking guy.
The secret field cop of the subgenius.
Yeah, the secret...
I don't want to feel a cop, secretly or otherwise.
The backslap of me.
I wouldn't mind copping a field.
The secret getting-to-second-base of the subgenius.
It's big-tucky.
Hey, quit slapping me.
It's big-tucky, or it's...
That's not my back.
P. Nicky.
Well, we're dorsal-ventrally challenged.
Dorsal anal-penetrantally challenged.
Here's what we're going to do.
I like the way you say that.
We're going to spin the body on its axis.
So now we're going to go get a donut, right?
I saw that the new guy came in.
Oh, yes.
Just because you want to talk about a hole, now all of a sudden...
So now we can put things into the donut.
Where gravity has been worked on.
Is it that time that we prepare to wrap the donut around us?
Yes.
It's time for a wrap.
It's the time when we go to Dream Fluff Girl.
Dream Fluff Girl?
Yeah, Dream Fluff Girl donut.
It's the sugary...
Well, unprepared donuts.
We meet our adoring fans down there.
They're waiting for us like rock stars who arrive at the airport.
After a successful European tour.
Unprepared.
After a successful 26-city European tour, might I add.
And there we go.
Landing on our personal leertips.
Unprepared as we are.
Yeah.
And this show...
Must have.
It must have.
So now, President Ivan Stang...
If that's not...
118 pounds.
Pay attention.
These people will be famous someday.
I don't know what it is.
Because I am speaking these names...
Who was he thinking?
...their fame will...
ring down through the years.
And it'll be a test.
It'll be on the quiz later.
First of all, our grand host...
I don't feel at all well.
...co-host, Don Joyce, our...
No, no, no, no.
Right off the bat, you're completely wrong.
Wait a minute.
Are you saying Don Joyce was on the show?
I can't believe that.
I'm Izzy Isn't.
Izzy Isn't.
Yes.
Yeah.
Can you believe he called him that other guy's name that doesn't even exist?
And that's no Ishka Bibble haircut he's got either.
Well, I thought Don was...
Don Joyce has been the only person...
That was Don.
...that was long-stuiting, sweeping...
...D-A-W-N.
...he just telepathically...
And she's a girl.
...transmit stars.
Well, puzzling evidence isn't evil.
...puzzling evidence isn't evil.
...perverse nature.
Princess Wee Ardo.
That's right.
Hey.
Who I understand wrote a...
It takes a good Joe to make a good Buck, friends.
Yeah.
And speaking of Buck, don't forget...
Phineas Narco.
Buck.
And for more on that, see...
National Science...
...cynical.com.
...fellow like the birds to the ground.
Yes, nationalcynical.com.
National...
Dr. Howe...
I am here, my son.
...is here and is with you.
He is walking with you.
Time to unburden yourself from your love.
He is amongst me.
Now, you've only got three minutes, so you better get going.
...down about your ankles.
Well, we got to...
Speed up your pace.
Michael Pepe...
...and see myself.
...or Michael Pepe...
...the inventor of P-Dog is over there.
Well, this is the tower of excrement.
P-Dog, anything to do with P-Dog?
P-Dog is what you might call the rug underneath the shell.
Aye, there's the rug.
K-Rob...
...the...
...has been providing noises and...
...echo.
...noises and I haven't chosen to speak yet now.
He was responsible for the subtitles...
There's one now.
...this entire issue.
That must be the subwoofer.
There he goes now.
That was real.
There was another guy.
I'm not sure who he is.
Which one?
It was...
Yeah.
But he was polite.
There were other guys.
Not you, Gary.
Oh, the sound of buzzing...
And there was Gary...
Gary...
...the rogue friend was here earlier.
Yes, whatever happened to him, that fairweather sailor?
And Piss Baptist John Shirley...
...was also...
And Chaos McKinney...
...was called away.
...and he was not around either.
Chaos McKinney also is here with...
...John Squirrel.
...Bishop Joey...
...the Queen...
...and Air Apparent...
...and...
...Bishop Joey...
...Lily Cat...
...and...
...Bobcats...
...Lily Cat...
...Drummon...
...Goober...
...Booby Eater...
...or...
...Light Water...
...Booby Eater.
...and this is the church at last as a female queen.
The church is a living, growing...
I mean, what do they call it?
...infanta.
And did I mention...
...our mix master throughout so much of this?
Yes.
Izzy Isn't.
Here, here.
He ain't what he...
He ain't what I asked you to ain't to say what you isn't.
So you should have scissor space in that first flub there.
Was that a flub?
Izzy.
Uh...
He...
He is what he isn't and he isn't what he is.
You talking about Don Joyce?
We try to provide scissor space.
How about Don Joyce or...
Although really on a show like that...
...like this...
WMJR...
...it's a moot point.
...stereo podcast.
You wouldn't...
...get your motto.
...know whether there was a cut at an inopportune or inappropriate point because...
Well, I'm not sure about that.
...the whole thing sounds like nothing but a lot of random edits at inappropriate points
and mistakes.
Yeah.
No, those were no mistakes.
There were no mistakes.
Oh, no.
What?
Are you saying I made a mistake?
This is a creative artistic project.
Who can understand his area?
What?
Are we meant to do that?
Deliver me the whole question in a minute now.
That is our motto.
The lab will fix it.
I've been trying to think of something to say for five hours that I can't think of.
There's only a minute left.
One...
There they go.
One at a time.
Click, click, click.
The pot's lower.
No one has a voice anymore except me.
Izzy isn't.
And I'm ending it right here and now.
Until next year when the Subgenius and the Over the Edge show combine for another five
hour spectacular to kick off the new year.
And I want to thank them all for coming.
Every single one of them.
and the baby who was playing keyboards, I swear.
Good night, subgeniuses everywhere.
Keep trying.
The creator is divine.
To reproduce is human.
Man Ray.
Okay, thank you.
You are listening to the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
The background music is by Bonobos Convergence,
who will be performing at the X-Day celebration
on July 5th, 1998, this July.
You can get more information about Bonobos Convergence
at bonobosmusic.com.
And for more information about the Church of God,
the Subgenius Friends,
please do check out subgenius.com
or write for information from P.O. Box 181417,
Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
And as the elephant asked of the naked man,
how do you feed yourself with that thing?