Oh, they're so big! Oh, they're big, big, big, and now they're gone, and this is, uh, and this is the big sound.
Big! We're big, big, big, big!
Big! Huge! Big ones!
It's size, friends. You get size. If nothing else, you get plenty of size with this radio station.
As soon as we are able to transcend the time problems inherent in life on Earth...
And gain control of the situation, we will return you to your previously scheduled conversation.
Big! Big! Big! Big! Big! Big! Big! Big! Big! Big! Big! Big! Big! Big! Big! Big! Big!
In essence is now part of unregistered inner subconscious mind.
We are controlling transmission.
We are conscious of our responsibility and obligation to provide programs which will be enjoyable, entertaining, and tasteful.
I assure you that this network will continue to adhere to the eye standards we have maintained
through all the years.
Thank you.
You are about to experience
the awe and mystery
which reaches from the inner mind
to the subgenius
hour of slack.
No!
It hurts so bad, dear friends.
This is the most painful show
I'll ever have to do.
Because I haven't smoked a cigarette
in four days.
No!
Happy birthday to Tevis.
Wow.
You mean that's why my brain
has been coming up with all that stuff?
Yes.
Afraid so, kids.
The Navigator.
And I am
the spaceship.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yes.
Dear friends.
This is
Hour of Slack
technically, but it's really a
rerun of an ancient
Hour of Slack
number 113
from the year of
1987.
We're doing reruns
for the next few shows
of very ancient shows
because we're delving into
the ancient history of the
ancient Church of the Subgenius
for an online
course in such things.
And later on, hopefully
I'll turn it into some sort of a book
and DVD
project. But
in the meantime, we're digging up
the olden stuff.
And we're going to talk about
the olden truth and lies
from the olden days.
This particular show
is one of
what turned out to be several
I have just quit smoking
shows.
I did not actually succeed
in quitting smoking cigarettes
in 1987.
But I did after the 1997
I'm quitting smoking
show. Actually, I might not have done one.
And maybe that's why that one worked.
Anyway, friends,
let us now go 20,
well, 19 years
into the deep, deep
past.
Grace Bob.
Activate good affection recording.
Activate all radiation surveillance
consoles 1, 3, 20. Switch control
monitor to automatic.
I'm having a hard time keeping control
of this show tonight, dear friends.
Because it ain't
every day that a person quits
smoking four packs of cigarettes
a day.
Oh, please help.
Come in.
Gentlemen,
sure are everything
hurts.
But it's a hurt that seems
more mental than physical.
A hurt that comes from the
inside and moves out.
It hurts to do
anything, especially this
horrible show.
It hurts to think
or say. Go ahead
and do it.
I just want to get out of here.
Only cigarettes would help me now.
Come on.
Oh, my lungs.
I hate the
feel of cleanliness.
It just gives me the
worse.
It's the way it feels.
It's making it worse, friends.
No, it won't.
Only smoking cigarettes will make it better.
I don't think we can do this.
It's worse. It's worse.
You're making it worse.
You're just making it worse.
You want it to be worse.
You want it to be...
Everybody wants it to be worse.
Oh, they're laughing. You're out there laughing at me.
Aren't you? You think it's real funny.
You think it's funny
that I'm trying to break a habit of
16 years.
But if I can't quit after
a few shows, if you hear me...
If you hear me
smoking again, then it just proves that I'm
human.
And if I can quit smoking,
it'll prove that I'm beyond human.
Greater or less than
human.
Quit laughing!
It hurts! You're just trying to
make it worse!
Oh, it's no big deal, though.
Everything's just like normal.
...or nature, whatever you prefer.
But whoever or whatever it is,
it's certainly innocent to you.
The gold has gone back
to where we found it.
Oh, real funny!
Oh, everybody laughs. I think it's
real. You non-smokers!
You don't know! And you don't
care, either. Oh, they can't care.
No way. I think it's just like a headache.
I've screamed! I've cried!
And you're laughing!
Suffering and labor, this joke is.
Ten months of suffering and labor, this joke
is, friends.
Ah, go ahead and laugh.
Non-smokers,
giggling away.
No!
I don't think both of you need to be in bed.
Sir, this is
the best the supreme
being can do.
Ha ha ha ha!
Why do you keep blowing me up all the time, huh?
I don't know. It's so fun!
My purse is off!
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to
pull a pin on that collar.
When it comes to covering the United States,
subgenius tradition calls for propagandistic hack work.
Ha ha ha!
Is that our job, or is that...
Yes, we've taken over this station
in hopes of subverting your mind.
All right.
Marching into your head now.
Isn't it cute? They have those little powdered wigs on
and three-cornered hats. They're almost harmless
as they march up your spinal cord.
But when they reach your brain, a deadly conflict
ensues. Really? Well, that's very interesting,
Dr. Howell. And now, back to breakfast hour
here on the show. Well...
I guess it'll work for the show anyway.
...and of course...
Ladies and gentlemen, it's Dr. the Bofram
and his surgical mind-trip.
Look at him go, that flashing steel.
Only one pair of hands in the country
could possibly perform with such
consummate skill.
It is a ludicrous sight to see
not only his hands but his feet to cut the cadaver
on the table into an unrecognizable part.
Whoo!
You must be from the Little Hill tribe.
Yes, country. You must move forward.
To a new frontier
of subgenius
radio programming.
Whoo!
But this promise was to be shattered
when on November 22, 1983,
Bob was shattered
in both weekends
by a terrorist-thrown bomb.
He could never play golf again. It was very sad.
Look at him go on his little cart. Look at him split.
I know. He kept trying to play golf for years
after all. It was embarrassing to be out there on the course.
This little torso would go by
in an automated golf cart.
Ha, well, ha, ha, ha, ha,
boy, that's a killer.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
It's a killer.
But he was young once.
He had a mummy who tucked him in at night.
And an adorable little puppy
called Puddle, the perplexed poodle.
The Sousers probably were a Nazi secret weapon
but that was back in the 40s
when only kids had contact with the enemy.
Too many UFOs piloted by
Nazis like Errol Flynn from the center of the
United States were the reason that the government
withdrew its plans.
Maybe I'll duck in this disco.
Look at that little dog
go through those doors.
Not as good as a human though.
Everybody laughs at him, but it just goes
right and straight away.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Oh, they're still laughing.
Oh, fuck. Oh, Bob, let me smoke.
Well, I'm all
fixed as far as I'm concerned as a medicine man.
I'll have three meals a day, five if I want them,
a roof over my head to drink every now and then to warm me up.
I'll be worshipped and fed and treated
like a high priest for telling people things they want to hear.
Good medicine men are born, not made.
Come and see me some time, my boy.
Even you'll take off your hat when you see how respected I am.
That's box 140306.
They want to make me their legislature,
their whole legislature. I don't know what that means,
but it must be the highest honor they can bestow.
That was
J.R. Bob Dobbs,
dear friends.
Dad,
what have you done?
It was Bob.
Bigfoot?
No, not Bigfoot. Bob.
No, Bob. It was Bob.
Bob, let me smoke. No, I won't listen to the devil.
I won't listen to the devil.
I won't. I...
That's what it feels like inside.
Me!
The tobacco demons are chasing me.
They're trying to get me.
Please, callers, callers,
help, pray for...
...to get ready to
maybe start to
think about perhaps
going even on about it.
Much less
taking a big ol' hit.
Do you think women find you attractive?
Well, I ain't bragging.
It's understood.
What did you say when the London critics voiced their opinion of your show?
I know
that I...
...
...should leave.
Well, Jerry, here's a question
rather important to our audience.
Were the conservative Britons very shaken over your behavior?
Oh, life ain't
all...
But look to the skies.
The saucers will always be there.
Always be there.
Goodbye, Earth people.
He's Bob.
Bob don't ever change.
Always will be Bob.
His face is the one big assembly
of dots that shine in the dark.
His grin is the one that looks friendly.
But so does the grin of a shark.
He's Bob.
Bob don't ever change.
Always will be Bob.
His hair is the one with the highlight
that shines on the pompadour.
That glimmers and gleams in the twilight.
It's clear he knows what it's for.
He's Bob.
Bob don't ever change.
Always will be Bob.
He's Bob.
His pipe is the one with the darl
that rains on the roofs like fire.
His neck is the one with the wattle
inflaming folks' desire.
He's Bob.
Bob don't ever change.
Always will be Bob.
Bob.
And pain.
Cleanse her, my Bob.
And cleanse her, my Bob.
To keep the artistic integrity
of the formula of this show.
I haven't smoked any cigarettes
in 72 hours or more, Bob.
But Bob,
where's my reward,
what do you get for me, Bob?
Oh, friends, if you need to know more about the nicotine withdrawal clinics of J.R. Bob Dobbs, I'm not worried about sounding like a fool.
I don't care. I don't care. I don't care. Don't care. Don't care.
I've had enough.
What you're hearing in the background here is from Hinton Templar.
The China White Heroin Phoenix Program.
The case in the Bible.
And the minds of Theodore Schlafly, Salvador Allende.
The waffle of American democracy.
And the nicotine was not going to continue their effort.
Americans murdered by acorn.
7,300.
Children and teenagers murdered by acorn.
3,346.
Richard Secord was made.
Under George Bush.
Frank Kirk was a case in the Bible.
Adult re-education subgenius centers destroyed.
2,840.
6,236 children left without slack by the conspiracy.
The CIA.
Bill Casey.
The first national security in the U.S.
Richard Allen. By June of 1981, they had resolved the strange and the mysteries of falsehoods.
The secret team. Hush money. Hush money. Hush money. In the bowels of our government
for 25 years, we have been blackmailed. What we are dealing with is a cancer deep in the
chest of our body politic.
As my old buddy Mark Twain said, he asked, what is the chief end of man? Why to get rich?
And in what way should he get rich? Well, dishonestly if he can, honestly if he must.
There are times when one would like to hang the whole human race and finish the farce.
And just light up another cigarette. Come on, Bob, let me have one.
Adam was the first great benefactor of our race, friends, for he brought death into the world.
Oh, Lord, our father, our young patriots, idols of our hearts,
go forth to battle. Be thou near them, O Lord, our God. Help us to tear their soldiers to bloody
shreds with our shells. Help us to cover their smiling fields with the pale forms of their
patriot dead. Help us to drown the thunder of the guns with the shrieks of their wounded,
writhing in pain. Help us to lay waste their humble homes with a hurricane of fire.
Help us to ring the bell of the world with the sound of the gunshot. Help us to bring the fire
to the hearts of their unoffending widows with unavailing grief. For our sakes, who also adore
thee, Lord, blast their hopes, blight their lives, protract their bitter pilgrimage,
make heavy their steps and water their way with their tears. Stain the white snow with the blood
of their wounded feet. We ask it in the spirit of love of him who is the source of our suffering.
Bless the rest of humanity with the strength and좀
And those of you who haven't brushed up on your twain, I heartily, listen to the pain, the pain of others.
You know, when you're, that's Hel Swami Satellite Weavers being electrocuted there in the background.
That's how we made him quit smoking.
It was easy for him.
All he had to do was die.
One last word here before we go on from Mark Twain.
This is from an essay concerning the Jews, actually.
Twain said, I'm quite sure that bar none I have no race prejudices,
and I think I have no color prejudices or caste prejudices nor creed prejudices.
Indeed, I know it.
I can stand.
I can stand any society.
All that I care to know is that a man is a human being.
That is enough for me.
He can't be any worse.
Shoot the natives.
Any more natives around here?
Not after that.
Ha! Got that one.
Obnoxious radio promoter.
We have to keep firing because it's important.
We have to keep firing.
Get that one.
That's right.
More bullets for us means more dollars for you.
I'd like a couple of dum-dum rounds.
Thank you.
You've got them.
Okay, we've got a lock and load.
Wait.
There's another little dum-dum round.
Okay.
Cue it up.
I'm not going to tell you which one it is.
I'm not sure we ought to give away our precious secrets to these negative beings out there
and negative plans.
Hello, Nipi caller.
How are you doing?
Okay.
Hi, Nipi.
We'll play the nipple call.
Just crawl right up here, Nipi.
Nipi, we know that since you've talked to us last time, you've developed limbs and you've
got probably a solid backbone.
Look at that spinal cord.
Noto cord.
And I regurgitate all the dogma and I deal with them and my little friends, they used
to laugh and gather around me.
Caution.
Mouth-to-mouth regurgitation is illegal in certain sectors.
But now, now they just start looking at me.
Up now, the distractions bear me down to earth.
I stand.
It's permanent and I'm off to the side.
All right.
I think maybe you better go.
Look, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean that.
I don't know what I mean.
I don't either.
I mean, he's not like you or me, but he is a man.
And contact with a woman just might bring him out of himself.
Might lead to something.
Something new.
It could save Bob.
Come on, girls.
Call in.
Oh, listen to him.
He needs you.
Call in, ladies.
Call in.
Yeah.
Go.
Oh, my God.
Dad!
I want a cigarette!
I'm going to have one, please.
Happy birthday, Tavis.
I want you!
Oh, you wouldn't believe what we had to do to get that acting job out of that child.
Grand tell me.
But maybe no child is ever too young.
A wolf may be more than he seems.
He may come in many disguises.
What's that?
The wolf that ate your sister was hairy on the outside.
But when she died, she went straight to heaven.
The worst kind of wolves are hairy on the inside.
And when they bite you, they drag you with them to hell.
What do you mean?
Hairy on the inside.
Like a furry coat.
Hush now, foolish child.
Listen.
Once upon a time, there was a woman in the village.
She married a traveling man.
With whose eyebrows met in the middle of his face.
Never trust a man whose brows meet in the middle of his face, dear friends.
For he's either a werewolf or a tobacco demon.
Or puzzling evidence.
And Bob doesn't seem to care.
No, come on, Bobby.
Help me out.
You're going to get me through this show.
The world is still haunted by ghosts and demons.
And how much do they affect the policies of this country?
What about the elders of Wotan?
And the tobacco demons.
Wotan.
All sound effects stop with the name of Wotan.
Wotan is our great god.
Wotan is our worship word.
Wotan.
Oh, we're way down south in the land of Wotan.
Even animals can Wotan.
Okay.
It's occasionally accurate news.
Live from inside a diseased beef taco.
Look at that.
As we get closer, we see these crawling, mutilating animal fuels.
Chemical breakdown of what's in the food around us.
Tiny maggots writhing through meat.
Well, isn't life wonderful?
Even though it's full of unending agony and pain that mars all consciousness.
There are some nice things about life, too.
Like the beam of sunlight on a baby's behind.
And as we get closer and closer, we see...
Every week, the baby's behind.
We've got to stare at this thing at five in the morning.
It's getting larger.
It's getting through the gate.
Quick, recite the spell or it'll be too late for humanity.
Why, I think it's kind of beautiful.
It's pink and...
Our entire planet will be changed into a paradise.
It's like a rotten orange.
Too late.
It's an alien baby.
Concentrate the photons.
Maybe we can burn a hole through that baby's back.
Okay, let's get started.
As it seems, ladies and gentlemen, turn away from the monitor, please.
That's okay.
It's your baby, not ours.
I'm not taking child abusers out of me.
Pulled off the air.
The baby doesn't feel it.
It's just a rotten orange.
Come on.
Ah, yes.
The cast...
Shouldn't have pulled the stem off.
Y'all ever have a grandma orange sandwich?
Orange juice all over everything now.
It's orange-colored ink.
Look, everything's orange.
Oh, yeah.
Quick, back up.
It needs to be painted.
Everything in front of my eyes.
Orange, orange.
Orange.
Take it.
I'm going crazy.
So, Hal jumped off the ship.
Ah!
Splashed.
Orange, you're dead?
I didn't know what to do, so I went normal.
Hi, Gary.
Gary got a haircut.
No beard.
No feet.
How does Gary's hair cut itself off like that, Philo?
Yes, caller.
But it grows as fast as we can cut it.
Okay, stand back.
Now he's three feet tall.
Back.
I created you.
I don't want to go back.
Caller.
There's no back.
Let's go over that again.
I saw a sunset.
There's no back.
Too real.
We switch you now to our on-the-spot reporter, downtown.
Come on, baby, let's go downtown.
Take it away, John Cameron Cameron.
This is John Cameron Cameron, downtown.
Pardon me, madam.
Would you tell our audience what would you do if the saucer were to land?
Thank you.
And now the thin gentleman there.
What I'm going to do is hard to tell.
The gentleman with the guitar.
What would you do, sir?
Take a walk.
Thank you.
We're returning now.
This is Black, your outer space.
This is Johnny with a request for Earth.
Earth Angel.
That was the Pelican's outer space recording Earth.
I've just been handed a bulletin.
The flying saucer has just landed.
We switch you again downtown.
Here we are again.
We have with us Professor Cecedric Finting-Moles of the British Institute.
The professor is approaching his saucer to see if there's possibly any sign of life aboard.
Well, I'm sure something.
Are you there?
I hear you knocking.
But you can't come in.
That was Laughing Lewis's record.
Knocking.
And he's done Cameron Cameron on the spot.
And now I believe we're about to hear the words of the first spaceman ever to land on Earth.
La-ba-ba-la-ba-ba.
Well.
Harvey C.
E組.
Gravel.
Indecency.
Vulgarity.
Obscenity
These are strictly confined to man
Said Twain
In his letters from the earth to aliens
Man invented these sins
Among the higher animals there's no trace of them
They hide nothing
They are not ashamed
Minute by minute crawls by, friends
This is the longest, the longest show
Can blue men sing the whites?
Yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah
You know the first time God came down to earth
He brought life and death
But when he came the second time
He brought hell
And when he came the third time
He brought slack
The third time was Bob
Third time's a charm, you know
And old Bobby
His buddy Twain further suggested
That the human being, like the immortals
Naturally places sexual intercourse
Far and away above all other joys
And yet he's left it out of his heaven
The Bible is full of interest
It has noble poetry in it
And some clever fables
And some blood-drenched history
And good morals
And a wealth of wisdom
And a wealth of obscenity
And friends upwards of a thousand lies
Anybody got a light?
This is what it feels like inside my head
Being hollowed out cell by cell
From the inside
Says Michael Pepe
The Unified Field Chair
To unite all forces
Because the cosmos is not unified
But profoundly chaotic
Well ladies and gentlemen
We're having quite a party down here
We are experiencing interference
With our transmutation
I'm gonna back up the show here
And adjust to conspiracy
The way we were supposed to
Turn up the light and crank up the genocidal
There's not a lot of you tuned in
To hear conspiracy facts and factoids
Let's just all go around
Here we are stuck in the same old dumb show
I bet they're really running the show these days
Some of the greatest thinkers of man
Have been in there in the last 24 hours
And no one's noticed
Yes, the thunder of the Athanasian Creed
Is no longer heard on Trinity Sunday
And few are the Parsons
Who expound from the pulpit
The central dogma of the church
On that day
Well, Collin, what do you think
Of the sixth bullet theory?
I think of the
If you're going through the one
It's bound to get you
Did you think
Did you believe that that sixth and last bullet
Which is conjectured to be
Reagan's butt plug
Was actually present
At the Kennedy assassination?
Please, please
On this program we say champion
Well, I believe that the champion
Was always in Ronald Reagan's
But the news
Scientists extracted a large card
From Reagan's
Whatever you do
Don't push that button
No, no, this is non-card
Don't push that non-card button
It was picked up by an FBI agent
On the north side of Main Street
I'm non-pressed by this nonsense
Okay, we'll repeat on the card, huh?
There he goes
Rising to the sky
In a fountain of debris
Look at that expanding cloud
Expanding at 65 feet per second
Buildings knocked over
Cars melted into puddles of metal
An incandescent shockwave
Traveling outward
At an extraordinary speed
Destroying all that it meets before it
And right in the center
Bob Dobbs' face
Yes, Bob Dobbs
Bad little show
Staying in the air
Yes, we're the Sense of Humor Radio
Okay, so you're driving down a country road
Far from anywhere
And it's the wee hours of the night, right?
When you call, Bob, does anyone hear you?
Suddenly you run out of gas
There's nobody around and everything is deserted
It's all dark and lonesome
So you get out of your car and start walking
Right?
Right, right, right
I wouldn't
See, maybe your gas tank got a hole knocked in it by a rock
So all your gas drained out
And maybe you'd heard there was a gas station
Up ahead
And that's why you get out and start walking
Okay, now you're walking along this road
And you see off to the side
A rotten, tumbledown, deserted farmhouse
You decide to go in there
And look around, right?
Right
And you pull out a small penlight from your pocket
That you've forgotten you had
And you start shining it around
To see if you can find a can of gas
Yes, it is, Gary
Okay, okay, you don't see any gas
So you go in
There's a flight of steps to the cellar
And you flash the dim light
Before you start walking down
Welcome in there
And just as you get to the bottom
What do you see looming out of the darkness?
A naked kitty cat
The joint chiefs of staff
Plotting an intensification
Of the bombing in Cambodia
No, no, it's a body
Hanging from a rotted rope in the ceiling
And you look around some more
And you see their bodies all over the floor
Some have their hands cut off with axes
Others look like they've been shot and stabbed
And then Mark Lane walks out intact
Well, ladies and gentlemen
Well, if this was true
Wouldn't you feel horror?
Wouldn't you want to get away from those bodies?
No, you'd want to go down the start
Undressing them and playing with them
If you were a necrophiliac
But you'd probably turn and get out of there
As fast as possible
That's you, crawler
Hello, guys
Hello?
My point is
Even you feel supernatural horror
Even the cold, hard-core
He just gets scared when he sees
The eerie sight of the dead
Sprawled all over the cellar floor
As a creaking house in the middle of nowhere
And if you feel supernatural horror
Then there is supernatural
And if there is supernatural
There is, or could be, God
And here he comes now
She was the best of her
Hey, God, give the keys to the car home
She didn't even have to touch you, did she?
On my belly shalt thou go
And dust shalt thou eat
All the days of thy life
Look at those guys
Beating the bejesus out of God
Now they're honking at him
And running up and running
Jump, God, jump
See, God, jump
I believe it's something God puts in us
Yeah, hey, you ever notice
How DDT only strikes down the evil ants?
The evil empire
What's going on?
Yes, that's the way it is, Hunter
Turn the page, caller
If you can manage to find your way through the sludge
There's an important lesson in this somewhere
That needs to be learned
That lesson is?
Better to throw the food in the street
Than give the kitties too much to eat
But better belly burst than good meat spilt
In the street on St. Smithen's Day
Don't think, but don't talk
Interrupted the man, Adam
Don't throw the baby out with the bathwater
Into the street over that pile of reeking meat
So you ask
I can't hear you
I can't hear anything
I refuse to hear anything
I refuse to acknowledge anybody else
What'd he say?
Did he say?
Hear how the devil's chuckling
During the show
It's the show
Rockin' away
Because you know
There's never been an intelligent person
Of the age of 60
Who would consent to live his life over again
His or anybody else's
That's what Mark Twain said
This is a Mark Twain night
He used a fake name too
Madness without any doubt
The most interesting fool there is
Also the most eccentric
He hasn't written a single law
In his Bible or out of it
So he's not the most eccentric
which has any but one purpose and intention,
which is to limit or defeat a law of God.
And I believe that we know just what to say about that.
Don't pray to God to solve your problems.
Pray to that part of God within you.
You have the guts to fight for yourself.
God wants brave souls.
He wants winners, not quitters.
He wants non-smokers.
You can't win. At least try to win.
Try to smoke.
I love dryers.
Oh, you love smokers.
Is that right, Robin?
Right.
Yay, God.
Brother Woodrow, lead us in a closing prayer.
Whether you're going to do it or not, it's missed.
Welcome to Big Day.
Don't you know that Big Day is brought to you by...
That's right, new...
What is it?
New snake milk.
Yeah, that's it.
And don't you know that snake milk has a shelf life of about 2,000 years?
And why?
Well, it's because every quart of snake milk,
it has at least 200 milligrams of reconstituted whale jism.
That's right, reconstituted whale jism.
But anyway, welcome to the Big Day.
Yes, it's been a very large day around here, as usual.
Big day.
I got up this morning.
I had a very long, large...
Yeah.
Well, you know, now that I've quit smoking...
Of course, if I haven't quit smoking, y'all can laugh.
Oh, laugh all you want.
But if I have, then...
Then I'll probably contract lung cancer now, now that I've quit.
And then y'all can freeze me.
That's it.
Just a minute.
The earth behind us looks like a giant balloon.
Freeze old Reverend Stang in a cryogenic tank.
I left my wallet in the leather suit.
What?
And worship my corpse like you worship Bob's today
as we bow down before the frozen body of Bob,
embedded in that huge ice cube.
Come on.
Immortality.
What extended life?
Greatly extended.
You know what we're looking for?
Cryo-protective.
You know why?
I'm gonna freeze everyone with cancer and bring them back when there's a cure.
Yes.
Then what are you gonna do with them?
I don't think that's the main issue, Shepard.
Yeah, they won't know a living soul.
Their relatives are gonna spend all their money.
Man, are we gonna have waves of freeze-dried old folks living in Miami Beach?
No, I mean, who are you kidding?
There are too many people in the world right now.
Death is nature's way of making wrong.
It's a game for someone else.
Einstein, Bertrand Russell.
Einstein could have finished his theory.
Hitler could have finished his.
Mozart.
Jung.
Stravinsky.
Genghis Khan.
Charles Larkin.
Mao.
Shakespeare.
Gandhi.
Fatty Arby.
All right, so who's to live?
Everyone?
And who's to decide?
Guys with the money and the power?
They'll stay and keep everything.
I mean, they eat better food, they drive better cars,
and now they're gonna live longer, too.
Shepard, someday paramedics are gonna carry cryotanks.
Someone's dying, you freeze him.
You stop everything until you've got the blood of the surgeon,
and the organs of the spare parts you need.
This is worth much more than any one man, even him.
If we were gonna hurt him, which we're not.
He's a man, not a specimen.
A 40,000-year-old man who can teach us about ourselves.
Tell us how we evolved.
Now, that is much more important than trying to figure out how to preserve people.
I mean, he's alive, you're forgetting that.
You can't take him apart, punch him full of holes, and drain all his fluids.
That's our best chance of keeping him alive.
We have to study him in order to save him.
Oh, yes, dear friends.
We have to study them in order to save them, you know?
There's really no reason why not to believe in that.
We've got to study in order to save the animals, including man, the highest animal.
We've got a song about animals coming up from the swinging love corpses
who are in the background right now.
As twain...
As twain said, of all the animals, man is the only one that is cruel.
He's the only one that inflicts pain for the pleasure of doing it.
It's a trait that's not known to the higher animals.
The higher animals engage in individual fights, but never in organized masses.
Man is the only animal that deals in that atrocity of atrocities, war.
The pitifulest thing out there is a mob.
That's what an army is, a mob.
But they don't fight with courage.
They don't fight with courage that's born in them,
but with courage that's borrowed from their mass and from their officers.
But a mob without any man at the head of it is beneath pitifulness.
A man is a religious animal.
He's the only religious animal.
He's the only one that has the true religion.
Several of them, thousands of them.
He's the only animal that loves his neighbor as himself
and cuts his throat if his theology isn't straight.
Oh.
Yes.
Mind the machine.
Well, the Swingin' Love Corpses got to where they were really feeling sorry
for the animals, our four-footed brothers out there,
and they did this song.
This is a protest song for animal liberation
because I know that you don't care if a thousand people get killed tomorrow
or read about that in the news tomorrow,
but if you read about one panda who can't,
you know, have babies,
or one rabbit whose grandchildren have all been sent off to be used in experiments,
then you'd really be upset,
and this song is for you.
Thank y'all.
From the Swingin' Love Corpses.
Oh.
me
Oh
in the name
of
Meeting
M kidnapper
living
here
was
attracted
And they played them a demonstration here in New York.
Let it sit
On the animal
Of chance
To feel the sunshine
On
Our animal brothers
That sacrifice their lives
Every day
In the name of
Medical science
I fall for the brothers
They're giving their lives
Every day
They're cutting them open
What it includes
It's
Putting those doors on their sides
All kind of
Experiments
And
They do it in the name of
Medical
Science
I fall for the brothers
They're giving their lives
Every day
In the name of
Medical science
With God as fast way
As I live between
My eyes and kidney
So remember, the very next time you eat some turkey, drink some wine,
there's a friendly four-footed furry animal that gave his life
to find out whether or not you die when you ate that stuff,
or drank that stuff, or smoked that stuff,
or whatever else you had to do.
But your four-footed brothers
are laying down their lives
for you every day, for you every day, for you every day!
Subjective intersection, subjective intersection,
subjective intersection, subjective intersection,
subjective intersection!
Our four-footed brothers are subjective intersection.
In the name of medical science,
for you, my friend,
for your life,
for the lives of your fellow man.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha!
Ah!
Your four-footed brothers are laying down their lives.
Little doors on the side.
Two running out of little docks.
Two.
Subjective intersection, subjective intersection,
subjective intersection, subjective intersection,
subjective intersection, subjective intersection.
Our four-footed brothers are subjective intersection.
Oh yes, dear friends.
Well, that was the swingin' love corpses talking
about our four-footed brothers.
And Dr. Philo Drummond on vocals there.
And friends, you need to write in for information.
I know a lot of you are very curious.
I'm going to finally read that P.O. box to write in for information about Bob and the Church of the Subgenius and what all can be, just how many brain cells you can lose by writing.
Got that pencil?
Bob at P.O. box.
181-417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118 www.subgenius.com
Oh yeah, Swingin' Love, of course, is going out.
I have to play this.
Dear friends, we need that money.
I believe that you know how little money this station has to run on.
I know because I've seen it.
I've been in the temple.
I took the thing that Bob made me drink and I saw, I saw you in the spirit, in the vision.
I saw it coming.
Hey, your check coming in the mail.
Oh yeah.
Oh, this is Timothy Larry reminding you that just as you need slack, Bob needs your help.
Send in those pledges and praise Bob.
I believe you can make this world a better place to live in.
People really don't listen without pain, do they?
They must be bad people.
See, the problem with the believers is they think we're loaded already.
And we are, but we don't have any money.
So few are ready to put their beliefs on the line.
The line where you sign your name on that check.
Oh, I don't, I don't have a spare $10 because I'm going to spend it on cigarettes and liquor.
Or even worse, by pretending to be a subgenius and pledging but never even actually sending the check.
Huh?
Get on the stick, man.
Promising ain't enough.
Faith.
Is not enough.
But your paid up pledge is enough.
So reach down deep into that most sacred organ of your body, your wallet, and let there be slack.
Ah, we're already out of here, Bob.
This is what it sounds like to crash off a cigarette habit.
Friends.
We made it.
Okay, Wally.
No, one last one, please.
Just one last one.
Oh, ah.
So what, Mr. Dobbs?
We're in shape for the finals.
No, really, Mr. Dobbs.
And by the way, Bob, just where is that long?
promised bucket of pills. And tell me, Bob, what's this slack business? Shouldn't the hierarchical
slack holders be getting unearthly dividends on a regular basis by now? Or is it just really
too much fun, Bob? Well, there is a war on here, Bob, and whatever happened to too much is always
better than not enough. Has there been inside trading in the Sol's repository in Dobstown?
Oh, come on, Bob. Remember us? Remember the old guys? We used to sell froth mixture for you back
way back in the good old days. We've heard the old Dobbshead snake oil routine before, Bob.
We know all about the bleeding head of AP. But when will it come is what we want to know. When
shall the fabled luck plane tilt? And when shall things at last begin to flow to all, all, all of
us who, despite the perilous times in which we do live, cleave unto you still, oh, Bob?
Next day's coming closer, Dobbs. You haven't got all the time to the end of the world, have you?
Hadn't you better just get cranking, Mr. Dobbs?
Ooh.
Ow!
That's me.
That's me,oned.
I'm turning.
Ooh.
Ooh, lovely from Michael Pepe.
And this from DK Jones.
Yes, there is one.
I'm sure of it.
Yes, yes, please.
Yes, why not?
Yes, that's right.
So, why not?
Why not kill Ramtha?
Why not take the New Age creatures
and kill them because
those stupid,
non-smokers?
I've always hated non-smokers.
Now,
now I'm...
Let's kill Ramtha.
Yeah, let's just do it.
Now, if he just happens to be occupying
some instant bystander's body,
our misnomer,
I'm gonna kill him.
There's not much we can do about that in the Azur.
That's just, that's beside the point.
That's, that's
ex facto.
That's, that's just
beside it.
No you of beings
that are riding pickup trucks.
No ye of beings
that have come up here to kick your ass.
No ye of
those who would destroy
all channeling entities.
I am joyfully,
I am enjoy.
I am outrageous.
I am bruised.
Really would make friends with
Aryan Nation people.
People that get riled up on,
they're just as active in politics as
Nicaragua protesters and people that go to
nuclear sites, I mean they're,
they're political kind of him,
but they're just on that other
side totally.
I mean they would fly somewhere,
make a protest, march and be devoted to a thing.
It just so happens to be wanna do something else.
be the annihilation
of certain races.
Yeah.
What I'd rather annihilate would be Boy George.
Just make
friends with him and go up to Seattle
and just have him all over again.
Do you know of beings which try to
exterminate other races?
I think you call them Nazis.
But I just
could. If I could, just
get a bunch of them riled up
and they would just go and kill her.
I would just do that.
If I could just do that,
then I'd probably be charged.
Well, you know,
after that song
Do You Really Want to Hurt Me
came out, Doctors for
Bob and Janet Huckley's
Rick Maverick comedy troupe
just recorded this
rebuttal. Oh, yeah.
I want to hurt him real
bad.
I just
Oh!
Oh, God! Oh, God!
I want to, oh!
Oh, God!
I just want to
hurt him real bad!
Give me a ticket to London
and a tax account.
Oh, please! Oh, God!
Just for a second, if only I could just
for a second just
be hurting him real,
real bad!
Oh, God!
I could die happy if I could just
Oh, God! I want to hurt him!
Let me live five more minutes
but let those five minutes be
hurting him real bad!
Real, real
bad!
If I could just one molecule
of his being, if I could just
slash it with a razor and just
if only it would hurt
real, real bad!
I mean, I'd go to work in a
coal mine for the next 40 years
if I knew somehow the money was being
used to hurt him
real bad!
I guess we'll have a
lynching!
Hey!
www.maybelogic.com
For information on the church of the subgenius
Please look into
www.subgenius.com
Oh, that music in the background
there was
Hawaiian Slack
Key Guitar Masters
Thank y'all!