Up above the world so high Like a diamond in the sky
Twinkle, twinkle little star How I wonder what you are
In the dark blue sky you came While you threw my windowpane
You never shut your eyes
Take me to the sun
When scent of the moon
In the dark blue sky you came
Take me to the sun
What are you?
What manner of beast is that?
What the hell are you?
What are you?
Every man and woman is a star.
And that's why Dave's head is a glowing gas bag of flaming hydrogen.
So it was read, so it was written.
All of their heads were glowing bags of hydrogen.
And they walked around town wearing their bags.
And one little day, one little man said,
Your head is much bigger than mine.
You must have a much bigger bag.
Everybody is a star.
And yes, that man was the mayor of the town.
He had a great yellow giant for a head.
Unfortunately, Dave, the village idiot,
had what is known as a dwarf star for a head.
In fact, it had collapsed so suddenly and compacted so tremendously
that it, although it had not quite formed a black hole,
the density,
the density of the head of Dave,
you know, every man and woman is a star.
Dave was a dwarf star.
Well, one square millimeter or so of the interior of Dave's head
was of such a dense molecular,
densely packed molecular structure
that that tiny, tiny fragment would be heavy enough on our planet
that if you dropped it, it would bore its way,
it would bore its way,
all the way to the center of the Earth.
This is why Dave was not allowed in most towns,
his head being altogether heavier than the most nearby planets.
His presence tended to cause disruptions in the orbits
of other inhabited star systems,
other planets that might have even cities
and old civilizations that had lasted for thousands of years.
Merely the gravitational waves caused by the thickness of Dave's skull
could destroy and wipe out these entire civilizations.
Oh, man.
And that's why when Dave would beg for a dollar for a bottle of beer,
most people in town would go ahead and give him the dollar.
Spare change, buddy?
What the hell are you?
Because every time he got a headache, there was a...
Oh, man, everybody's got some kind of personal deformity.
So my bag's a little bigger than yours, you know?
And what's the difference between helium and hydrogen?
My bucket's a corpus callosum, excuse my language.
Oh, my God, it's not even 12 o'clock.
The townsfolk and the other planets,
civilized galactic federations and so forth,
had to pretty much put up with Dave
because whenever he got a headache,
it would cause earthquakes in their capital cities.
Oh, my Tylenol's doing nothing.
These excepents are doing nothing.
These aspen's are doing nothing.
This old Indian herbal extract ain't doing nothing, man.
I feel like my skull is spinning.
I feel like the weight of the universe is expanding.
It's just expanding out through my very, very, very, very...
I don't have my laptop.
Did you ever feel that way, Fran?
Did you ever feel like the problems of the world
were weighing down on you so much
that your head was self-collapsing
into dwarf star density?
Have you ever felt that way?
Well, if you haven't,
then you're probably not a subgenius.
It's so dense in here.
You lucky bastard.
It's just like the yolk of an egg.
Or she-bastard. What did I forget?
You can't say she-bastard.
She-bastard.
It's like a little psychic yellow of an egg in here.
It keeps me warm.
It keeps me nurtured.
That's all I need.
I am a star.
See, everybody's brain is...
I don't need those people.
I don't need to drink Tylenol.
I don't need to snort that stuff.
I'm different than that.
I'm going here.
We've taken good care to raise you up here, Dave.
Oh, by the way, Dave, Dave,
there's something we needed to...
Dave, there's something...
I hate to interrupt your...
You!
Your fun little monologue there, but...
Uh...
You've heard about cloning and so forth
and the replaceable body parts and...
Well, you actually, Dave,
are the clone of a master, Dave,
who is a very rich, powerful man
who happens to have
just destroyed his liver
through hard drink,
and it's time for his replacement liver.
And yes, you were cloned from him
and have been raised
as a poor, pathetic street wino.
Uh...
Just kept alive,
you and several other clones,
several others have already been used for other parts.
Dave, I'm afraid your life is...
The goal of your life
has come around.
It's time for you to give up
that which you were bred for,
which in this case is your liver.
You think cloning wonderful.
Too bad nobody cloned you, eh, Dave?
Wait a minute.
You'd love the rich Dave.
He looks just like you
and runs General Motors now, I think.
Wait a minute.
I don't know whether I'm having a psychic echo spasm
or if I'm having some sort of corticoloring license here.
I'm so in the corner and I'm panhandling
and I hear a voice that says I'm cloned
from somebody else who's rich and powerful.
And come on out from behind there.
My little leg yoke protects me.
My little helium hydrogen exchange key
is in the back of my car.
How could he break in here?
Hey, where'd he go?
Hey, little voice, little garbage can.
Come back here.
Man, nobody around here.
Yoo-hoo.
Maybe he was just
sucking a weird dream or something.
I've got to stop doing that methamphetamine.
He's ripping my brain apart.
I've got to stop snorting gasoline.
I've got to stop letting it
leak in the bottoms of his jaws.
I've got to stop
shaving off my nail clippings
and my endo-chasing re-spulking.
I've got to do something, man.
Maybe,
maybe it's a self-concussive realization.
Maybe it wasn't a little voice.
Maybe I am cloned from some rich and powerful person.
I could take over the Church of the Subgenius, man,
and make a lucrative mola.
Yeah, I'll be standing on top of everything.
I could topple a little petty giant
and a little tyrant.
That little toot-bootch
wherever I'm staying.
Weird how these little voices in my head
always sound like him.
Well, gentlemen,
as you can see by our subject,
lonesome cowboy Dave,
the syringe implantable transponder
works beautifully.
He seems to think that there are voices in his head.
In this case, my voice was used,
of course, as the project chief.
But it is amazing, is it not, gentlemen,
that our
General Electric tiny microchip,
the size of a grain of rice
placed underneath his skin,
injected with a vaccination
in his childhood,
has allowed us to dictate
as voices in his head
his entire life.
You know, there's no difference
in principle, gentlemen,
between being forced to carry a microchip
in your plastic card in your wallet
or the little pellet that we put
in Dave's teeth.
The principle that
every sister has the right to track you
is inherent in both.
And the only difference is a layer
of skin, or in Dave's case,
a skull, a very, very thick
layer of bony
carapace.
Let's turn the voices back on.
Dr. Reverend Stenge, I was wondering.
Yes, yes.
I've noticed in the literature...
Yes, Dr. Bronner.
I've read all of your papers,
and I am quite convinced that what you have done
to this man is a remarkable disservice.
I can picture a perfect example
of a man whose personality,
which was not in a good shape to begin with,
has been totally destroyed,
immersed in your faulty world religion.
You expect us to experiment on animals?
Poor, innocent animals?
Why not?
Dave volunteered for this thing.
I see nowhere in the transcript
you have given me an example
of Dave ever giving his permission,
written or otherwise,
for you to conduct this experiment on him.
It seems totally remarkable to me
that you could conduct such an experiment
and receive grants and so much money to do it.
Dr. Bronner, I think you've heard the expression,
if you're going to make an omelet,
you have to break a few eggs.
I don't see.
I mean, to a certain extent,
this Dave,
lonesome cowboy Dave character
is little more than a human egg,
an omelet,
so to speak,
bubbling on the hot sidewalk of life.
How could you expect
to call a fellow human being
an omelet?
He's not a human being.
He's a subgenius.
I'm sorry, but your rules don't apply to us.
Dr. Stein,
I agree with your work.
Can I say one word?
Yes, Dr. Sotomayor.
I appreciate what you have been doing
the last few years,
especially, I mean,
Markovia, your work with lonesome cowboy Dave
and other people,
Einstein, the orchestra,
I would like to know
if you can help me
find a possible backup grant for,
I have a similar project,
a Hachou project,
I would like to do a similar sized city
in southern Japan.
Oh, well, I'll tell you the investment opportunities
if you will connect,
of course, I assume there's fetus research in your country,
probably considerable amount of fetus organ trade
going on there.
Yes, I have no problem with human donor.
Have you also considered
genetic cloning research
for, uh, to...
Well, that's another thing.
Dr. Bronner there was quite out of line
complaining about a so-called human being,
even if Dave were a human being.
This is a clone of a human being.
The original Dave, the Master Dave,
sitting over here to my right,
yeah, that's a very, very
nice tie you have there,
Captain Dave. Thanks, man.
The Master Dave there, obviously,
he was born with the same rights
according to human being,
or a subtenuous.
His clone, however,
I mean, how can one person have
more than one set of rights?
So, therefore, the clone,
being more or less the same person,
is going to have to find his own set of rights.
Uh, Ivan, do you mind if I
get a little personal postulation in here?
I want to show a little of my own perspective
after all being the clone donor.
Lonesome Cowboy Dave is not a human being
in the same way you or I would call
uh,
say perhaps the Reverend here,
or Dr. Sagamoto,
a human being.
He's an experiment conducted by the church
to re-incur the reprogramming
of thousands more people
and to stop this
X-Day thing that we've been,
we've all been talking about. That's all I have to say about it.
Dr. Broder can complain all he wants,
but the process has been set in motion.
Now, Dave is contagious everywhere he goes
in the city of Cleveland.
We're going to see the same progress in the disease,
the virus, if you want to call it a disease,
we like to think of it as
a new, uh,
oh, just some, we're adding some
artistic details to
the fabric of human reality.
That's all. We're just doing a little
window dressing, improving
on God's handiwork.
Why not? God gave
us that right, did he not?
He made us as unto gods. Every man and woman
is a star, I believe our
secret leader, Alistair Crowley
Hubbard once said.
Ah, I remember us sitting there,
Parsons at that nudist college.
Yes, yes, sir?
Stefano Grappelli of the Institute of
Psychic Research in Rome.
I was wondering if, uh,
if you found any sort of
repercussion with the
lonesome cowboy Dave,
perhaps any psychic
example of violence
or trouble with police,
or such psychological
exacerbation.
Yes, yes, I'm glad that you asked
that question. There was an extremely
unusual side effect to the treatment
by which whenever Dave would
sneeze, plates, for instance,
in the kitchen would fly across the room,
jump off the shelves and smash
against the opposite wall.
One time we were in the
front office and the files flew
out of the file cabinet drawers every time
Dave sneezed. Of course we had to
put him down whenever
he was around any kind of expensive equipment.
Out on the street,
most people hardly noticed. There's
so much violence mugging down there
on the level, the level where
he, where the experiments
are usually conducted.
Uh...
Petri dish
one, you know, the sidewalk.
I, uh,
would like to ask question also of you.
I am from the Institute of
Moscow. I need to mention
the name of the Institute. We are
familiar with the parapsychological
research I've been doing. Oh, yes,
comrade. I would like to say
that after the upcoming
election, we'll be all different situation
in former Soviet Union and, uh,
the Commonwealth of all of the states
would be involved in, uh, and
after what you have said, uh,
reprogramming, making people
more malleable, pliable, we'll
find have to a different problem. Is
there some way we can use your research and
perhaps make, uh, the whole
of former Soviet Union, uh, similar,
uh, in the...
Well, comrade, as you know, uh, Dobbs Co.
is, uh, marketing the, as we call it,
the electronic leash of these
implantable biochips, uh,
to, uh, be any, uh, corporate,
uh, or governmental entity,
uh, we'd, uh, happily, uh,
assist. Of course,
our microchips do have the, uh,
Dobbs trademark, uh, built in
so that, uh, although they,
the, uh, subject's allegiance will
be up to the choice of the, uh,
corporation or, or
governmental entity, uh,
nevertheless, uh, as you can certainly
understand, it's sort of like
the Coca-Cola company is gonna
sell Coke in Russia. That's fine,
but they're gonna have their logo on it.
Well, uh, your people
will be mind-controlled, according
to your plans. However, they will respond
to the, uh,
smiling face image
of Bob.
That, uh, that would be
very, that is fine with us. Thank you very much
for answering this one.
And, uh, as we said, these, uh,
computer chips will link the individual up
to a vast computer database
so that we can, in fact, follow
the, uh, subject, uh,
and, uh, follow their spending,
their voting, uh,
habits, their, pretty much
their sexual habits up to a point.
Uh, we can, in fact, dictate their, uh,
sexual habits, uh, through the voice
in the head technique. We have
had some subjects, uh,
they get their ideas from the movies or
comic books or something, they pull all their teeth
out so as that they think
that this will silence the
silent radio in their head. Of course,
uh, that does affect the
resonance and we have to, uh, increase
the amplification when they
pull out all of their teeth, but it's, uh,
rather pointless,
uh, to tell the truth. It's sad.
I've noticed, uh,
Dave down there is, uh, bleeding
at the mouth, the one down on the
sidewalk, not the one here in the boardroom,
certainly. I don't think we're getting enough,
uh, can you, uh, can you enhance this picture somehow
so we can all see it a little better and bring up the volume
somehow a little bit? Yeah, zoom in on, uh, screen three
there, uh, Wellman, uh,
if you, if you pull in close now, you'll see
that Dave yanked all
his teeth out with those pliers and has thrown
them down in the gutter where our servo robots
have retrieved them for the master
Dave here in case he ever needs, uh,
a new moment. I don't know what I'm saying to myself.
Me and the other day
I saw her beating myself in the face
with a hammer for no fair
reason. And here I am
pulling out a moment. Dave, Dave,
we're back. It didn't
do you any good.
You pulled your teeth out for nothing, Dave.
I love Bob. You're an idiot, Dave.
I came to the church,
not a doorbell. You didn't love Bob
enough, Dave. I've got to love more.
Listen to this, you guys. He'll believe anything.
Wait a minute. Dave, you sinned.
You pulled out all your teeth for nothing.
That'll look stupid as well as
I look stupid. I ain't never
gonna find me a day like this.
Bob's living so
worse.
But I'm not gonna let you
cry, Dave. Don't cry, Dave.
Bob has a new job for you.
He has a new
bride for you, Dave.
Bob has brought you a new bride.
See that goat over there in that
pen?
That she-goat over in that pen?
That's your new wife, Dave. What?
That's Hogan's goat. Oh, man.
You are the husband of Hogan's
she-goat. Last night
you told me that was some kind of weird goat they
was gonna clone. And then you said
it was the goats that was using to touch nerve gas.
And now you're telling me it's my wife?
That fella's gonna get me a nice
six foot seven yeti woman.
That's gonna blow me out.
I'm so confused.
Do you have a problem with the goat?
Uh, Dave?
Would you rather us take you
another wife?
Uh, I guess
How about this giant,
this gigantic eyebrow
mantis? An eyebrow mantis?
Man,
I can't see it. My mind's left astral.
Get the eyebrow mantis slide
into his retina.
There. Okay, he should be seeing
the, uh, the giant
eyebrow mantis.
What the hell is that thing?
Turn the erection
knob up to ten.
He's terrified of the mantis
and at the same time he's
sexually aroused. Oh my god, get that thing
away from me. This always
refuses to take my child. I'll bet you're a Leo.
I'll get away from you.
Oh my god. Hey, uh, hey. So you want to
see, gentlemen, not only is the experiment
Oh, get away. Oh, get him away.
As you can see, gentlemen, the experiment
is not only a success but a lot of
fun for we researchers.
You can pull the strings of the subject
as if he were a little puppet
dancing down there on that hot
sidewalk in the inner city
surrounded by the broken beer
bottles and the other bums and
losers while we up here
in our skyscraper sitting
at our computer keyboards
may make him
jerk and twitch
our own little pathetic
marionette, isn't he?
And so it's... He suspects,
of course. In fact, he knows perfectly
well his state, station
and life.
That's what religion is for, boys.
Praise Bob, eh?
Praise Bob. Praise Bob.
And thank you
for the excellent demonstration and
quite an illuminating slideshow
it was. Now, what I think... We take credit cards.
Well, I think that's what we're
all asking right now. What will
the next project be and how much do you need?
All I need is...
is to fill the receptor
holes, my friend.
Oh, you ask
me what I need?
I just need to fill
those receptor holes.
They used to be
so full,
those holes in my brain.
They had just the
perfect molecule fit
right into that little
locked place.
Now... The brain holes.
The brain holes. The brain holes
are empty. The brain holes
are empty tonight. The brain's
gonna have to make its own... The moon
is shining. My eyes
are bright but...
The master molecule
is gone.
You look pretty sharp.
You look pretty cute.
But you ain't
going nowhere in that brain
holes suit you got on.
You say you look so cute
in that brand new suit.
You think you're
got some place to go.
You ain't
going nowhere so just
sit down in a chair and
let Bob Dobbs tell you
the truth.
I told you when you were
ten and I told you when you were
twelve and I told you as
you were coming on up.
When you look
scoward my son think of that
glimmering pipe.
So my work will be done.
I'm leaving soon.
There is a great mesh in your
brain.
And this mesh is composed of tiny
holes and these holes have a certain
shape. Those are
receptor holes and they're
responsible for your sense of
self and well being
and pleasure.
There's a certain shape of a molecule
that'll fall into those receptor
holes and make you
feel real good.
And that shape is a shape
oddly enough of
what looks to us just like a
common pipe.
Like a Dr. Grabow
pipe.
If you can find some way to get
tiny pipe shaped molecules
to fill those receptor holes
inside that
vacant mesh in your head
well you'll probably feel
so much better that you'll be able to do better
on the job. Get a better job.
Become like a great
stock whiz or something and get
rich overnight on some great
idea of perfect vision.
So of course at this point
you're asking
hey man where can I get
some of them pipe shaped molecules?
Is it like a pill or
is it something you smoke?
Hey Bernice
I just want you to try this.
Look what I got at the farm.
What is it?
It's not a pill. It's not a pipe.
You place it in your third eye.
It's the virtual
of the
the the
It's the emperor's new
pipe.
You just hear.
You see this
thing that I'm
holding in my hand.
There's
nothing really in my hand.
But it's a virtual pipe.
There is no virtual in that pipe.
Hey man let's all
like smoke some of what's in this
pipe in my hand.
Oh yeah yeah man
I see that pipe in your hand. Yeah let me have
some of that virtual. Oh whoa.
Whoa. I tried
marijuana once
at the same time and I tried LSD
and I tried bananas mixed
with Coca-Cola and aspirin
but man
and Jimson weed and NyQuil
but whoa
this virtual pipe.
Oh man
I am going inside.
Oh far in.
The pipe is feeling really nice.
I'm like caved in.
I'm caved in man.
I'm so deep.
I'm like a
I am speedlunking dude.
Help help.
I am like in the magma.
Help. Oh help sir.
Magma city.
Sir my lumps are crushed.
Feel that pressure.
No no the magma cathedral.
Whoa. I am so low.
I think
man I wonder maybe I'm
getting too low.
Maybe I'm getting too deep.
Am I ever going to come up?
Hey man don't come up
too fast.
Your hand will explode.
You'll get the beans.
Whoa.
Wow these anti drugs
are so much better than
those cheap conspiracy
street drugs.
I don't want to get high anymore.
Ever since I learned
the word of Bob
I've been ready not only to
come back down to earth
but to go below the sidewalk.
Below the sewers.
Below the upper crust.
Below the lower crust.
Down all the way.
Yeah.
I've learned how to go down
since I gave up
those getting high
kind of drugs.
Bob's dragging me all the way down.
Oh the pressure's getting
getting higher.
It's getting really really hot down here.
You know when Bob's taking me
I'm digging it.
It's really hot.
Look at these flames.
Somehow they're not consuming my flesh
but yet they're burning.
Whoa.
These Bob pills
and this virtual Bob pipe.
This stuff's really intense.
I'm like having a before death
experience.
I'm having an
out of inside
planet experience.
Oh man.
I think I am too low.
I probably need to come back up.
Hey man. Is there anything I can take
to counteract this non drug
that I didn't take?
Hey ref.
What are you doing here man? Crouched on the floor.
Isn't this the coolest club
you ever been in?
I already had three multi-gassets
and I don't even know what the hell that is.
Yeah this stuff's great.
It's free too. Yeah where'd he get it?
I got it from Bob.
Well I mean it's free once you join up.
This guy charged me 15 bucks
for one hit.
He tell me it's free once I joined up?
Well you're joined up now.
Here take.
See the pipe in my hand?
There's not really a pipe in his hand.
But they believe
there is a pipe in his hand.
See the pipe? Here take my pipe
Dave. Have a big hit
of what's in that pipe.
There is no pipe.
There is nothing in the pipe.
But the placebo effect is so much more
powerful than any real drug
that the subgenius victim
is now becoming
so low,
so in there
that it is as if
he is looking up
from eight feet underground.
I feel like they're made of mush.
He feels like
he's laying at the bottom of a hole.
I can hardly move.
In a box.
Hey man, I never understood gravity
and now I'm in it.
Underground.
This is wild.
In the dark.
But I want to go and do stuff
and I can't see nothing
and I can hardly breathe.
And the top of the box is only about an inch
from his nose.
And it's a real tight fit.
And he doesn't know how deep underground
he might be buried
and why he might be inside a box
underground freaking out.
I'm a gothic service android guy.
I'm down to 65 in a gothic prison.
They can't hear you knocking up there, Dave.
Hey gothic prison guy,
I don't think I've been a mouthful.
Say Dave, you thought that problem
with premature ejaculation was bad.
How do you like premature
burial?
I better stop hyperventilating.
Maybe you should have just said no, Dave.
Yeah, maybe I just
said no.
Maybe that time when you were seven years old
that other kid offered you a cigarette
maybe you just should have said no.
Yeah, after all then I could say I had better lungs
and I could stay in here much longer.
What the hell am I talking about?
Maybe that time when you were 15 and that kid said
hey I stole this beer from Mr. Jones
icebox, why don't you
let's drink this beer.
Should you possibly, Dave, have said
no?
No, I should never have said no.
I said yeah and I'm...
And that boy said hey,
Dave, let's smoke some of this
corn silk
rolled up in this toilet paper.
What should you have said then, Dave, eh?
Give me some more corn silk
and I will save for my...
No, you should have said no, Dave.
Or if you had said no to the corn silk
perhaps you wouldn't be in this box
eight feet underground in the cold
and the dark wondering just
how you ended up
here.
Help me, please.
They can't hear you
eight feet above.
They're crying.
Oh, look, all your friends are up there.
Reverend Stang's always pretending to cry anyway.
Oh, and look, Princess Weard
it was so good, Chaz is
well, he's actually seems to be
divvying up money
with Reverend Stang and...
Come on, somebody.
Well, Michelle is crying.
I don't want to die.
Oh, I'm happy because she has hay fever.
I just realized...
Look, they're all laughing.
This is all a figment of my mind.
Yeah, I didn't smoke no corn silk.
I was back in the goose bar
and I had me hit on that pipe.
I think I had it look like Stangy Wings.
If I just used my psychic abilities
and concentrate my yogic powers
which was gifted to me by Bob Dobbs
down in my lowest lower chakra
way down...
Oh, no, I can't do that.
The slack will be with you.
Oh, damn.
I'm never gonna make it now.
Feel the slack, Dave.
Close your eyes.
Turn off the autopilot.
Come on, Bob.
Feel the slack.
I'm seeing crystal skulls floating by.
Just go with your instincts, Dave.
Oh, my God, I don't want to go into the wild life now.
I just want to take a hit off that pipe
and now I'm going to die.
Throw off the meat shackles.
Dave, baby.
I'm not going to die.
Suck the body like an old shoe.
Welcome.
Welcome to the other side.
Remember me?
Benny. Benny Gordon back in New York.
I was the guy who stole your shoes
and hid them in the garbage can.
Then you struck me in the face, remember?
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Yeah, I died later.
No thanks to you. Yeah.
Kind of screwed me up inside.
When they let me in Bellevue, they said I'd never be the same.
I starved to death.
I thought about you when I died.
Yeah.
I just don't look like
the green carpets coming out.
Kind of looks
blood red.
Hello, Dave.
I'm sure you don't remember me.
I was originally
a tiny puppy that you
tortured when you were six years old.
Remember me now?
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Now I am
Dog Demon,
the bearer of vengeance
for all torturers
of tiny puppies.
And meet my friend,
the legless grasshopper.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
We've all come to get,
to tell you that we remember
all the things you did
in life.
I don't think this is going to be very pleasant.
If I'm supposed to recount
all my inches,
so far I've only had three inches,
and it's all bad.
What's next?
Who's that weird looking woman?
Grandma,
I've never done nothing to you really.
I'm sorry about the stove.
It's too late
for forgiveness now, Dave.
Oh, Mom, come on.
It's too late now.
It's much too late.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Oh, Lord.
She's all disfigured and burned just the way I left her
when I ran out of the house.
Dave,
remember your habit of sticking chewing gum
under theater seats?
Yes.
I am a soul who once reached under the seat
and touched your germ-ridden gum
later to die of a cold.
I'm sorry, bro.
You know, I try to keep myself clean
and have good personal attributes
like that and stuff,
but you know, those things are so bourgeois.
Hey, Dave, remember me, Butch?
Yeah, Butch. Yeah. I'm sorry.
Yeah, I bet you're sorry now, Dave.
Get away.
I didn't mean nothing.
Maybe you shouldn't have stuck up behind me
and pulled that little trick on me that one time, Dave.
You know my personality, man.
Push me in front of that car, Dave.
Everybody in school knew I was a joker.
Everybody thunk and I just fell
in front of that car, Dave.
Dave.
Were you jealous just because I was bigger
and tougher and got all the girls
and got decent grades and had friends
and had parents and had money
and had a life?
Were you just, Dave?
What, you think you're gonna wait?
Yes! Yes! I hated you all!
I hated that puppy for having hair.
I hated Grandma for having food.
And I hated you for having a car
and girl friends. In fact, I still hate you.
And that's why I don't mind being here.
Dave, meet everyone
of whom you have ever been jealous.
They are here to gloat
at your misfortune.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Thousands and thousands
of people gloating,
gloating at your total
humiliation here in the endless
flames of, yes, let's say,
in hell, Dave. You're dead and you're in hell.
You see him face us
and you point fingers at me.
And here are snapshots
and tape recordings of every
stupid or humiliating thing you've
ever done. Here, the files
of every callous and
thoughtless thing you've ever said.
Here, every lie you've ever
said or done.
Oh man, they're flying by so fast.
Here, every betrayal.
Here, every lie.
Here, every time you've
masturbated in an impure manner.
Oh man, my eyes. I'm going blind.
You didn't know we had such good cameras,
did you, in all those grumpy
filling station restrooms, eh, Dave?
How did you know about that?
All right. Here, the endless file
of the times you picked your nose.
Here, the file of the times
you wet your bed.
Here, the files of the times
you didn't wash behind your ears.
Everything, everything in your entire
life has been reconstructed
and you're going to have to
relive every single moment
of it over and over and over
again inside this little black box
underground because you smoked
the corn silk and didn't do what
your parents said.
William. Oh, I love you.
Thanks for sitting there, you guys.
And as far as, all that masturbating
and coolie, I, I don't know how long
I can do it. I'm older now. My arms
might get tired. But if I just go back
in the box, when I reappear, I'll
be back in the goo goo bar, talking
to Stan and smoking on the bike, please.
So, what say, what say,
brothers? Shall we give him another
chance? Shall we give Dave a
chance to live his life again?
Do you think he's learned his lesson?
Oh, please, good sirs and good dames.
Let's flip a coin and see whether
salvation. Or not.
Alright, place the giant
coin on the giant thumb.
Set the catapult.
Three,
two, one, flip the coin.
It is
flying. Look at it.
Flying miles up.
Spinning end over end.
Dave is pouring
bullets of suspense out
as the coin slopes.
Oh, it's getting slower and slower.
It's falling.
It's falling back down to Earth.
It's coming down and it's
landed right exactly
on edge and it rolled
and it came to rest
and the coin is
on edge.
How
shall Dave's fate
be decided now?
We'll have to go through the
suspense and flip the coin again. Okay, there it goes.
It's a slow motion.
Okay, hold it.
And so the end
of the suspense went on for another
million years as Dave
waited to find out whether
any of the coins would actually land.
And one day,
a million years later,
it landed heads up. Dave,
you have won.
You were allowed to dig your way out
of your coffin and back to
Earth in the year
one million A.D.
You have been,
forgiven by God and Satan
and are resurrected
into eternal life
in whatever is left on the
planet of your birth, where
you now claw your way
back up. There he's tearing
the coffin open. He's digging
his, choking his way,
but we're using his
front teeth to dig his way like an entrenching
tool. And he's finally made
out of the grave. He's coming through
the surface of the graveyard. Dave is
free. Dave has escaped.
He has literally dug his way out
of hell. I'm free.
Hey,
where can you get a good sandwich around here?
And some juder pie.
Hey.
Say grade
G Frances, I imagine you're thinking.
McKenzie browsers are tomato bridge, savoryest have never seen. You don't talk any P  what a good layup for porem and
It's called serendipity, Dave.
Serendipity.
Or slack.
You can call it either one.
Serendipity.
I remember them guys when I was a little kid that used to be in the Thomas Brothers, you know.
And one of them died of a heroin overdose, I think.
Yeah, serendipity.
I could die of a heroin overdose.
That's my name, serendipity.
How did you know?
I didn't know, sir.
I just kind of guessed it.
Yeah, you know, I'm one of them intuitive kind of guys.
You know, one of your strong, silent types.
Yeah.
Wow.
I hope I ain't smelling too strong.
I just crawled out of a graveyard.
I think it kind of smells manly.
I kind of like it.
Yeah, some people say it smells more like a goat, but you in the mood for a cup of coffee?
Well, sure.
An espresso?
Yeah.
How about a cappuccino?
Can we snuff it?
Yeah, baby.
We can do anything you want to.
Especially with legs like that, we can snuff it too.
Wow.
Is that your naturalist?
Is that your naturalistic hair?
Or is that some kind of falsified hair?
I never saw that hue on a woman or on a human being.
It's a virtual hair.
Virtual hair?
Yes, virtual hair.
You mean like it's feely-reely?
It's sort of like a holodeck hair.
You mean if I touch it, like, then I would automatically experience the sensation you
was talking about in the aforementioned article?
Well, kind of, yes.
Like a hologram.
Kind of, yes?
Yes, kind of.
What about, you sure that ain't a merkin?
No.
You sure that ain't a bomb-dob's feely-reely virtual reality merkin?
It really is.
Oh, okay.
I'll believe you.
It really is.
It's a real merkin.
Ha.
You just lied to me.
You know, I'm wondering again since you just put...
It's a real virtual merkin.
Oh.
So then...
Does some of this seem too good to be true, Dave?
Yeah, well, the birds are singing and a woman in virtual work had come up and tried to ask
me out on a date.
And you're on?
Are you looking a gift horse in the mouth, Dave?
No, I'm looking at...
I mean, you, uh, we let you out of hell to relive your life and now you're complaining
that maybe it's all too perfect or something?
No, I was just looking at the bus stop.
I was reading the cards on the bus stop.
Snack Co.
Funeral Home.
George's Beanies.
Uh, oh, hey!
Wait a minute.
Where'd the girl go?
Hey, uh, hey, wait a minute.
Oh, whatever.
Well, Dave, we'll go ahead and admit it.
It is.
We put you in another one of those worlds where whatever you imagine is whatever you
get.
And, uh, I'm not sure if I'm going to be able to get you out of that.
And as long as you were feeling pretty, you were imagining pretty good things and getting,
uh, the girls and so forth.
But what are you imagining now that we've browbeaten you down and made you feel insecure
again, eh, Dave?
What kind of reality are you creating for yourself now, you poor, pathetic loser, eh?
Oh, look.
He's surrounded by snakes and harsh puppies and old, rotted, uh, crimped, um, lovdicats.
And I know this is all full of it now.
I'll surround the bus.
And everybody knows you don't eat no harsh puppies with no snake.
You eat with a snake.
You eat toot-a-pie and...
You see, we confused him and his entire reality collapsed around him.
I hate snakes.
We made him afraid.
And that of which he was most afraid surrounded him.
The moral of the story is, kids, you make your own reality.
Every man and woman is a star.
And if that was so, then how come it hurts when you stub your toe and how come your head
ain't on fire?
fire.
These are the eternal questions to be answered only by the eternal verities, death and taxes
and Bob.
The three things that you can depend on.
Oh ragged bones, oh ragged shoes, I am a vagabond, a vagabond, free as the wind.
Hey buddy over here, I got some snakes and hush puppies.
You hungry?
You feel like curling your toes up and squirming?
Come on over here, I got it.
Hey you over there, I got lemonade too.
You look a mite parched.
You look like a demon.
You, you.
Say, say, say Dave, I'm a demon.
I noticed that you took all those lemons we handed you and made lemonade.
We noticed that you had that glass that was...
It was half empty and magically made it half full.
Yeah and I got the one Aaron eyeball pointing down like many convicts do.
But that doesn't explain it.
How come my life is such a mess man?
I done squirmed by you.
I bought your lemons with real U.S. money.
David it's part of the seeking.
It's part of the journey.
You have to pay your dues.
In order to truly soar through heaven you must first embrace the porcelain bowls of hell.
Yeah.
I'm like some kind of mythic knight Percival guy.
Yeah, I don't mind so much.
Yes, it's the holy grail of slack.
And you're getting so close having gone through the terrible gauntlet of anti-slack.
Surely you must be almost to your goal of enlightenment.
Nirvana.
And it's true.
Here comes the nirvana.
By the way Dave, you knew that nirvana means nothing, right?
Yeah, I knew it meant nothing.
And that's what I'm writing for man.
Life's a nothing.
Because every time I get me something good it turns out to be something bad.
And I'm not going to get it.
And every time I get me something bad it turns out worse.
So it's like a shifting sandy beach of twenty dollar bills.
It keeps on changing and changing and changing and changing.
And I need nothing.
Blessing sweet oblivion.
Here then is your reward Dave.
You asked for it from Bob, God and all the others.
Back into the little black box eight feet underground in the cold and dark.
At least it's here.
Here Dave is your nirvana.
No longer to face the woes and travails of life.
You may lie here in total slack and repose.
Yes, this is the slack that Bob promised.
An eternity perfectly aware.
Inside a closed black box.
Feeling the corruptigating worms shoo their way through your desiccated decaying flesh.
And finally to feel your bones dissolve into powder.
As the.
Black box caves in.
And you have achieved nirvana.
And final enlightenment.
As worm experiments.
Thank you.
It was a little shoe shine.
It was a little man.
Who ran a shoe shine stand.
And every day the man would sweep the water from the busy street.
Blessed, blessed oblivion
He sailed in the center of one
And anybody
There was something in his face
Loneliness could not erase
No thoughts, no sensations
No feelings, no recurrent women
It's simply a moldy spatula
And those little worms kind of itch a little bit
as they crawl in and out.
Oh, yeah.
Just me and the worms.
Like a broken pup
He looked up from his cup
Drank his morning coffee
Wiped the dribble from his chin
There is nothing
There shall be nothing
Nada and nada and nada
Except
When his eyes met mine
He made a little watch
He came within an inch or two
And then he whispered
I hate you
Our nada
You aren't in nada
Nada
Be thy name
Our nada
Who are the nada
Nada be thy name
The name be dust
Thy feet be dust
Thy eyes be dust
Thy toes be dust
Thy teeth be
Need I need
My feet
Thy brain be dust
Thy feet be dust
Thy hands be dust as well
You know it young
Going to hell like
Good
How do they know? How do they know? How do they know? How do they know?
Once I had some pets I let them starve to death
It was a funny little monkey and a big whiny star bunny.
They lived in little cages and sometimes in rages.
I'd turn them upside down and drag my monkey all around.
And drag my monkey all around.
I dragged my monkey all around.
You shouldn't have dragged me around like that, Dave.
I dragged my m-
All around
I drag my monkey
Now ye shall be dragged around
All around
Let that monkey drag his name around his cage
Let him be dragged
Let him all be dragged
Let his armpit hairs be braided by a tired chimpanzee
No?
Yes.
Contaminated.
No!
Don't do it, man.
Contaminated.
Folks, you've been listening to ESO Radio
and, uh, and, uh...
Contaminated.
Einstein's Secret Orchestra with the...
with, uh, Einstein's Secret Orchestra.
Uh, uh, Lonesome Cowboy Dave and myself and Michelle
and special guest this week,
the Reverend Ivan Stang and the Princess We Are Doe.
Contaminated.
Being contaminated.
The song.
Contamination.
Warning!
Don't do it.
That's not a poem.
It's a song.
highlight churches that have suffered.
Nada and nada and nada
creeps in this petty nada
to the last syllable of recorded nada.
God, I have no pain.
And all bearded English professors
will quote nada and nada and nada.
And they should be throttled.
They should be throttled by giant beasts
and their hands held under their necks.
And as they cry out,
are you looking at my neck?
They should be struck down by the archangel Bill.
Great Bill.
The Bill genius must be lax.
There is only one gene that will work, though.
It's critical we get the gene.
We must not let Bob get to the gene
before the ceremony.
The gene must still be a virgin
when the time is nigh for its arisal.
We need a virgin gene
clean of any impurities.
That's the only way this will work.
Where can we find the untainted gene?
The unsullied, pure DNA formulae?
Where, man?
I know where you can find it.
Where?
Where, man? Tell us!
It's in my head.
It's in the woods.
Woods are like worms.
And they crawl in your brain.
I think he's right.
And they wiggle around.
I think he does have it.
And then...
I think he has the perfect,
undetaminated...
It's solid, man.
...crawling brain.
Completely crushed gene.
It's like the helium and hydrogen in the stars
is in your brain, man.
It's true.
This man's brain is so densely compacted
that the interior of it is like a dwarf star.
We've found what we need.
He's the Gene Genie.
He wasn't a pathetic loser after all.
He was the one.
I saw God.
Dave was the one.
After all his tortures and tormented turns,
it turned out that the Gene,
the perfect, unselled, untainted Gene,
was in fact buried inside Lonesome Cowboy Dave's head!
Praise Bob! The world is safe!
Remove the Gene.
This will make Dr. Von Neumann very happy, Reverend Stan.
This will make Dr. Von Neumann very happy.
We have retrieved the Gene
from inside the head of Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
He's dead now.
And we, the conspiracy of overlords,
disguised as rebels against the conspiracy of overlords,
have once again won.
The world is indeed our oyster.
The world is our oyster, one might say.
Fearless clam or some sort of shellfish.
We all enjoy shellfish.
Let's have some more, shall we?
Yes, let's slip a few more raw planets down our throats.
We have no love, we have no heart,
we have no air, water, we have everything we need.
Is that Dave Corpse?
Mumbling something again?
I thought we removed the perfect Gene from his head.
I thought he was dead now.
I told you before,
do not leave the corpse dead.
If it does not become putrescent,
the experiment will not work and he will come back to life.
Oh my God, look.
Chop off its head and stuff its mouth with garlic.
It's too late, it's too late.
He's already eaten all the garlic and chopped off his own head.
He's coming back to life.
And here he is, Lonesome Cowboy Dave on guitar.
Lonesome Cowboy Dave and the Corruptigating Worms.
There can only be one.
One.
As Dave, the resurrected Dave, without the perfect Gene,
and with his head now hollowed out, emptied and expanded.
And his Corpus Callosum, a perfect conical shape,
so that we can impact it with all the necessary documents.
He now freed from his tasks,
he rides off into the forest.
On the sunset, on his tricycle.
Side-settled, wearing that funny conical hat,
thinking somehow he has made it.
But in fact, it's made him.
Is that a good thing?
Can you pick it up?
I don't know.
Ever feel like you should have just said no
to that magic carpet ride to Electric Lady Land?
Ever feel so heavy?
Ever feel like your thighs are so sick,
your muscles are weak,
and your neck is too blotchy?
Ever feel disconnected and completely alone?
Ever feel corrugated worms
burrowing through your follicles?
Well, if you have,
we can't help you a bit.
But we can help you get your mind off of it.
So just write for free information
from the Church of the Subgenius.
Got that pencil ready?
You can find out everything you need to know
about how to make money off of your corruptigating worms
by writing to b-b-b-b-bob at...
P.O. Box...
140306.
That's P.O. Box, 140306, Dallas.
Tix.
Sis.
Seven, five, two, one.
Four.
Okay.
Thank you.