Welcome to the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack, sponsored by the Church of the Subgenius.
Ah, yes dear friends, and let's get right into it.
Because, you know, there's only 307 days left until Trace Eki's XXX Day, Triple X Day, friends.
I can't wait until Bob Royally screws us on that day.
And you're listening to Hour of Slack number 699.
That sounds like kind of a holy number, doesn't it? 699.
It's almost Bob's number.
And last week I had to run a re-run because I was so busy working on this project,
which...
I just finished last night, and I'm gonna...
Well, I edited the Dos Ekes XXX Day 99 videotapes, of which there were a lot.
And it's sort of intense.
And, of course, since this is a soundtrack for a videotape,
some of it, you know, you have to have been there with your eyes.
And I'll skip over those parts.
But mostly this show will be a compressed version of...
a good-for-audio bit...
of the gigantic weekend that we, the subgeniuses, spent awaiting the saucers,
who apparently didn't show up this time.
And I may drop in and narrate things.
Like, for instance, when we get to the nude, blood-bodily, fluid wrestling scenes,
there's some real funny narration with that,
but you'll just have to leave the images up to your imagination.
And I'm sure...
that...
that would probably be a big improvement.
Before we go into that, though, I have to brag about something
that I just found out about this morning.
Time.com, the web version of Time Magazine,
is conducting these polls for the man of the century, best idea of the century, worst idea.
And one of them is frauds and phonies.
And, uh...
And, friends, Bob Dobbs was narrated, I think, by Paul...
Bob Dobbs was nominated for this poll.
And he's number three so far!
In fact, different people have been ahead of him.
Uh, Dr. Laura and Joseph McCarthy, I think...
No, Linda Tripp and Geraldo Rivera are ahead of Bob right now.
Bob is number three.
Earlier to... or last week, O.J. Simpson and Kenneth Starr were in the number one and number two places.
But Bob is still number three.
And, friends, it may be that...
that, uh, we'll make Time Magazine before the end of the century, like Bob predicted.
Anyway, on their website, it says this about the phonies and frauds poll.
Over the last 100 years, in the midst of all the wonders of progress,
there grew a thing called hype.
Hype swirls and obfuscates, both hiding the truth and creating the lie.
It can be as harmless as the latest pop star saturation,
and as insidious as a two-faced government official.
In recognition of this phenomenon,
Time.com has built a list based on nominations from its web users
of individuals who are candidates for the title of the century's worst
scammer, con artist, media manipulator, grifter, liar, or charlatan.
This list originally included a number of religiously-fraudful,
and, uh, religiously-fraudful, leaders.
And get... look at this.
Look at the way they chicken out.
They left Bob Dobbs.
He's the only religious leader on here.
But we are convinced by protests from offended supporters
that their inclusion, no matter how well justified in some cases by their behavior,
might stimulate an attitude of contempt for others' religious beliefs.
And so we remove them, let the voting continue.
Well, obviously, friends, you know,
there are some liars that anybody would think of for something like this.
It would be, you know, Jerry Falwell, Jimmy Swagger, Jim Baker.
Oh, but they're Christians.
You can't say anything bad about a Christian religious leader.
Especially if you're Time Magazine,
who seems to find an excuse every month to have Jesus, God, or angels on their cover.
Anyway, friends,
this music in the background is from my friend Ron Slade,
a tape called Entheogenesis Thermosynthesis.
And he plays with ESO every now and then.
He's a Cleveland musician.
And, um, anyway, friends,
let us now go directly into these audio tape recordings
from the video soundtrack of the new XX Day video,
which actually is a two-part video,
and I doubt if we'll make it even through the trial of Papa Joe Mama this episode.
But, uh, join me now, won't you?
And, uh, strap on those giant headphones,
put yourself inside that iron lung,
and, uh, go back to fabled Brushwood Campground
with me and, uh, Jesus Christ,
Dr. Legume,
Sister Susie the Floozy,
Irreverent Friday Jones,
G. Gordon Gordon,
Sister Decadence,
Doc Frop,
and so lo- Papa Joe Mama,
uh, and lo- so many, many, many others.
Praise Bob.
Oh, friends, um, I almost forgot,
uh, to give the website address for that time.com thing
where you can vote for Bob.
Um, I believe their web address is simply www.time.com.
And, um, uh, just look for their polls,
their 100s poll.
It's a beautiful, beautiful thing, friends.
Are we gonna let-
Here's some of the other people on their list of frauds and liars.
Are we gonna let Oliver North or Ayn Rand beat out Bob Dobbs?
Are we gonna let Bob Dobbs be- be- be outvoted by O.J. Simpson and J. Edgar Hoover?
Rush Limbaugh and William Randolph Hearst?
Is Howard Stern gonna get the PR that Bob should have?
Friends?
Or Don King?
Will he be the new Bob?
Ugh.
Ah, yes.
But,
if you don't vote,
don't complain.
Oops, one last thing. I was wrong, friends.
It's not time.com.
It's www.pathfinder.com.
That's www.pathfinder.com.
Slash time.
So, um, have at it.
And action.
Greetings, Alt-slack village.
You can come out of your tents now.
This is what we call the woods.
They are only trees.
There is no internet here.
Ah, ah, ah.
Welcome to XX Day 1999.
The world ends July 5th, 7 a.m. as always.
90.1 on your FM dial.
We put the...
B into Bob.
We put the B into Bob, whatever that means.
We put the O into Bob.
Stay tuned to this radio station for...
My chariot awaits.
...up to the minute, ground to the ground.
...downbreaking important information,
such as a black truck pulling up.
I should cut in here, friends, and explain that at the X-Day gatherings,
we have, for the last three years now,
we've had two pirate radio stations broadcasting from the campground
so that campers could listen to subgenius-oriented music or whatnot
whenever there wasn't anything else going on.
Or they could get on the station,
which these stations are in, like, tents,
and one of them is in the back of a station wagon,
and be DJs for a while.
And, oh, it's...
You see, we're a very democratic sort of a mind-control cult.
We'll let everybody be L. Ron Hubbard for 15 minutes.
Are you listening to 91.1 FM?
90.1 FM?
Well, you just won some fabulous prizes.
Come on over. Come on over to the truck.
You...
Yes.
Have a date with Jayner?
The Bob Nightlight.
Bob stuff for the whole family.
If you have a Bob need, we can fill it.
Again and again and again.
And again and again.
And, dear friends, as usual, of course, on any campout,
we get rained out.
Every X-Day, we have thunderstorms.
And so we had to hide in our trailers.
Gust of wind.
Tomorrow, thunderstorms.
The next day, thunderstorms.
We actually had tornadoes.
Do they generally hold you responsible for the weather around here?
Yes, yeah, they do.
It has nothing at all to do with the weather.
Well...
That's what he gets for calling himself Jesus.
Look at that American flag out there getting soaked.
We must save it!
Well, you're supposed...
Then we're gonna have to burn it now, man.
Private Ryan!
Now we'll have to make it roll on it and then burn it.
Of course, which is exactly what we did.
Are they causing assholes like staying there?
They're everywhere.
Oh, hi!
Hi, Ivan.
How are...
I'm not a pure subgenius, I fear.
It's a particular clinch of my own.
Would you dare to have some other short derp or stab besides Bob?
I'm telling you the truth.
We're going to blow you down.
I've been pouring my own tensions into it.
If this was Monday, you'd be dead.
Yes, you would have slept through X day, but it's not.
I'm here to tell you registration has begun.
You must register.
If you came in last night and signed in but did not pay your camping fee, you must do
so today.
If you do not have the subgenius electro-stimulo wristband, you must get it today.
Anyone without the red wristband will be shot.
Welcome to registration.
Look what I did to this guy.
X day.
Whoa!
Yeah.
Is that where that came from?
He's got a huge scar on his chest in the form of an X.
Oh, I'm going to be up in about three seconds.
It's the American high.
We will be ready this time.
We will be up and alert and not hung over at 7 o'clock in the morning.
We will stay up all night.
Think about the ones that would have been ruptured with that hangover.
The hangover they had last year.
Even if you're not ruptured, it'll feel like it.
Yeah.
I felt like I had a hangover.
You mean we weren't ruptured?
That was a hangover?
Yeah.
I mean, I'm not saying that we weren't ruptured.
I'm just saying that we were.
değer häufig.
To make this reality, such a passa.
He took off the coat, rolled into the big pad.
Oh, we'd better take him off.
He'll be a fighter.
Pass the camera.
I'm going to take him off.
This follower took him from there and rode into the sink and looked down at the beloved
To drop off Haze to the ground and talk to us on these next enorme distance Ebola
infections, you just got erase.
We here.
Then he went to get time off.
Then he went after Cat
Smoke the brown poison ivy.
The green stuff is fine.
It should do the same thing it always does.
Makes your lungs bubble.
It's natural.
You know, it's our .
Man made alcohol.
God made poison ivy.
Who do you trust?
As Suzie the bluesy coined last year, if you believe,
you can leave.
Well, friends, I guess I'll skip over this section where they're
testing these elaborate potato cannons.
Dr. Lagume and Ed Strange and various other folks
have traditionally brought these homemade weapons to X Day Drills.
And these things look like Civil War cannons.
Great big, huge, barreled things with wheels on them.
You had to tow them behind a car.
And they shoot potatoes at other subgeniuses.
Well, actually, you want the I screw Lachnar.
Yeah.
Because that helps establish you as a sex god.
It's really worked for, well, I don't know if it has worked for
Pastor Craig, but everybody wants the button.
I know that.
I screw Lachnar and hearted it.
I did screw Pastor Craig, technically.
You got to keep up with this guy.
Lachnar donated $1,000 in cash last night.
Boy, did that brighten up the weekend of Jesus and me.
It ended the rain.
Donated $1,000?
He handed me $1,000 in cash that he had earned working for the conspiracy.
Plus a whole series of numerologically pertinent other dollars.
And 30 pieces of silver.
There's my 250 from last year.
Instead of that asshole Lachnar, now he's that cool, super cool dude Lachnar.
Tonight we'll be picking two fluids from our jugs of fluid which have been preserved over the last year.
What fluids will you be using tonight?
Uh. Well.
Today I think we ought to use blood.
Use blood.
The traditional blood.
And it's up to the audience.
Shall we use the greenish hue for the white spot?
Spot!
That's the, uh, submission or pain and fall.
That's the three count.
And there are your rules.
Awesome, man.
Woo!
This is just no holes barred.
As we always say.
And, uh, now, friends, the wrestling begins.
Subgenius, uh, body fluid wrestling, which mostly is done by naked subgenius.
He's been a hard on Papa Joe Mama.
So, if he's willing to step forward right now and wrestle me, I'm willing to settle it in the ring so he will not have a chance.
have that painful trial and, you know, charging him with guilt and the long, drawn-out punishment.
We can just finish it right here and now, unless, of course, he's too much of a pussy to come forward.
Hello? Papa Joe?
Is that insulting towards pussies?
Yeah. Unless he was too much of a human to come forward.
There's a lot of human blood in that Papa Joe. In fact, I think he's a pureblood.
No!
I think he's a human because no subgenius would refuse to wrestle me.
Friday Jones suddenly disrobes, exposing her rather considerable condolence.
I don't see Papa Joe. Of course, I can't see anything.
I'm going to teach you a lesson.
There we go.
Dr. Tillis versus Bard Zippy in the blood match.
Oh, my God!
Look!
Look at this, like, giant slabs of meat slamming into each other.
Oh!
Hey, it makes me think of hamburger.
Oh, I want to go to McDonald's after this.
One, two, three!
Yeah!
Oh, man.
He wins!
Ladies and gentlemen, the Normals have fallen!
Bard Zippy, winner and champion.
You subgeniuses.
You can wait till it's on the side for the final bout.
You think you're so smart.
Now, our next event, Pastor Craig versus Friday Jones in the pit of calm.
Let the carnage begin.
Ready?
One, two, three, go!
Oh, the crafty Pastor Craig circling like a jungle tiger.
Friday Jones looking like Raquel Welch in one million years BC.
The beady eyed Pastor Craig versus Friday Jones.
And yet, look at the spunky girl.
Look at that spunky girl.
The fight back.
Oh, well, spunky in so many ways.
The beady nippled Friday Jones and the tiny beady brained Pastor Craig.
Oh, he's going down on her.
And she's...
But look at the mother of the beast.
The muscles are rippling under that soft, smooth, rounded...
Pastor Craig is falling.
The big round things.
The big round things are on top of him.
Sisterhood is powerful!
Now, a new fight starts with Friday Jones and Pastor Craig also fighting with Reverend Angela and Reverend Jim.
And some of these people are covered with white fluids and others are covered with red fluids when they mix together.
Of course, you get this lovely pink.
What a hideous metaphor, friends.
A subgenius loser drowning in pink jism.
I hate to think what this says for our future.
What a hideous vision.
All right.
They're at the slippery...
It almost resembles some sick, hideous...
...hideous form of alien sex.
I can't believe it.
This should be illegal, friends.
It probably is.
Don't call the fire marshal.
Don't call the ATF.
Don't call Child Protective Services.
This is a subgenius Friday afternoon.
Praise Bob.
And to think these people were the ones who were called brains in high school.
Strange to think.
And yet, look at them now.
You may think, Bob, that you were not born like them.
Preach of nature.
Oh, my God.
King Kong versus Godzilla.
Look at that fiendish grin on Friday Jones' face like some demon out of hell.
Reflected on Pastor Craig's dome-like top.
And, oh, my God.
You can't tell where one of these grappling, grippy, sweaty, bloody bodies ends and the other begins.
Oh, fuck.
Ken, I hate to see a man treated this way.
Look.
They're almost pure pink.
When you mix Connie, Allah, and a bunch of damn monkeys, what do you get?
A pink.
He refuses to say, Uncle.
Oh, my God.
Oh, Lord.
Pastor Craig is in the...
It is as if he is in the womb struggling rather than to get out.
Yes, he is struggling to get out.
Smeared with hideous bodily fluids, blood, amniotic bile.
Oh, God.
There's actual sex.
Oh, shoo.
Shoulder up.
They look like free-hole Laura Rectus trying to figure out sex for the first time.
Is this how Neanderthals discovered oral sex?
Who knows.
We could only speculate.
Will this be like, will hell be like this, friends?
Endless wrestling match that never, never ends.
I hope so.
So, we're going to have to take it to the judges to see who won this match.
Yay!
Oh, Master Craig, congratulations.
So, the Rainbow Love Death Match.
Love is important.
The Rainbow Love American Flag Match, where the winner shall get the privilege of burning
the American flag on the Fourth of July.
Ah!
Christ, Bob, God bless America!
I'm washing off the pinkness and revealing my true white yettiness.
The albino yeti woman.
Shower scenes.
Now we hear a little scene in which Susie the Floozy and Reverend Chris Lee discuss
their, what they're going to wear to the subgenius mutant prom the next day.
Bass is cool.
You're going to be such a hot bitch.
I am.
I never went to my prom.
It's going to be so cathartic.
I got my corduroy.
I got my corduroy, too, so I can have a little corduroy orgy later on.
Oh, I'm going to be wearing a dark velvet strapless dress.
Have you ever seen a Discordian do anything close to what we have seen here at any one
of the X Day drills or X Day?
Never seen a Discordian who gets laid?
Not at all.
I've met old Sam.
There you go.
Have you ever seen a Discordian who gets laid?
Yeah.
I've met Robert Ed, Anton Wilson, who invented that whole silly Discordian thing just so
that he could get laid from all the groupies who are even fatter than we are.
Motormax, the sex god.
Do you have a few words, Motormax, about the Bulldada auction?
Do you want to explain the theory behind it?
It's simple enough.
You come up here on stage.
Yes, you do have to come up on stage, you show them the shit that you're going to be
selling.
You tell them what it is.
You tell them whether or not you can eat it, whether or not you can have sex with it
or anything else.
People come up and they give you money.
Real money, that is.
We don't take any of that Monopoly money stuff.
Canadian, maybe.
And then you give the money to us.
And then you give the money to the Subgenius Foundation.
We're pledged.
It says inside, $100,000 to Jerry Falwell, this is what you get.
It reads, the old time gospel of the world.
The old time gospel hour medal of merit presented in appreciation by Dr. Jerry Falwell and the
old time gospel hour board of directors.
Yeah, you could mount it on a thing on your fireplace.
It says, in recognition of outstanding service, Dr. Jerry Falwell, and it may be gold.
Someone called them up and pledged $100,000 for that, friends.
Let's start the bidding at $6.66.
Right here, $6.66.
You're out here $8.80.
$6.66.
And $7.00 for you.
A thousand pesos Bolivianos.
That is the documentation that this is indeed the nosebone of Saint G. Gordon Gordon, the
only dual saint in the history of modern, disorganized religion.
G. Gordon Gordon is the oldest living subgenius.
He's the...
No, sir.
He's the only proof we have that we can even make it to that advanced age of almost...
Chris Lee, pass out some more beer amongst the crowd.
We know we're not that old.
We're not that young.
we started the bidding on a
worst birth Bible that Lagoon touched
and touched by Lagoon.
And the word of wisdom
inside, here it is.
There's a random, the random
Bible saying for today, quote
1 Samuel 16
and when he had brought him
down, behold, they were
spread abroad upon
all the earth, eating
and drinking and dancing
because all of the great spoil
and slack that they had taken out
of the land of the Philistines and out
of the land of Judah. Praise God.
Y'all hear that pointer.
Holy moly.
Number 28 in the greatest
limited edition, time
legend, of Arnold Palmer.
You can rip the head off,
you can launch the head, or you can launch the whole
gossamer.
It ended up turning into a
stand-up comedy routine.
Is it funny?
It's about a half hour
long.
I think it's hilarious.
I remember this. It was good.
I think I'll be in on it. We can use it for the hour of slack.
I'll be in $5.
$6. $7.
$5. $4.
$3. You're $2.
$2. I'll take it for
free.
It's mine. It's gone.
Jesus Christ wins his own time back.
We saved the church.
$6.
Little Charger being
candy.
Charger.
Look closely. This is why it is
bulldada. The candy is the tongue.
To eat it, you open the mouth,
extrude the tongue, and you
make out with it. You make kissing.
My God!
To sell children
on the obvious
alias sexual proclivity.
$3. $3. Right here. $4. $4.
The Charger of Binks. Charger of Binks with working, vibrating
tongue. Right here. $4.
And then, when I took it off, I noticed
that there is a strange manifestation
around the hole in the tire.
It is, in fact,
a Dobbs head.
And you can see it. If you just, if you look,
if you smoke enough froth, and you look at it hard enough,
you can see this Dobbs head.
Uh-huh.
So, I'm going to...
Show this Dobbs head to me.
Right here. This is the hole.
Yeah, there's the hole.
And you can see that's the pipe.
And you can see a grin there, and you can see that shape there.
Where's that froth?
No, it's true, friends!
I've never seen it before! It's...
Oh, my God!
You have to look at it. You have to cross your eyes.
It's true!
What do I hear for a used tire?
In the middle of Bob's name, right between
those two B's. The sacred tire of Bob.
Do I hear $1 for the sacred tire of Bob?
$0.55.
$0.55. Do I hear $0.60?
Do I hear $0.60 for the sacred tire?
$0.55. It also makes an excellent
seat. You can sit on it while you're,
you know, instead of sitting in the rocks.
You can use it as an extra meditation
stool.
What?
$0.55.
$0.55. $0.55.
$0.60. $0.60. $0.60 for the rubber tire of Bob.
$0.55. $0.55 going once.
Going twice.
Sold.
And that, friends, concludes
for this moment, the
Bulldada auction. We will be doing this all
weekend long until we die.
Until we leave the planet.
Did I say die again? God,
I'm sorry about that. Until we leave
the planet. No one's gonna die
here. But you will
not be going back home.
See, back in 1979,
there was a small company who
released an initial public offering.
And their
stock was called Salvation.
It was the church of the subgenius.
Initial public offering
sold for $10.
That's right.
That was a lot.
Now it's worth $30.
Friends, that was
a free bag of...
We're leaving behind the conspiracy.
We're leaving behind a world of insanity.
We're leaving behind a world that ever since
Constantius closed the pagan temples down
and gave the property to the Christians has been on
a downward slide. Our western
culture has been corrupted by this pernicious
Jewish heresy which should never have been allowed.
Alright, you know what I'm talking about. Oh, it's, oh, gotta have
that gold. Gotta get the carrot. I gotta get my piece of the pie.
I gotta get my piece of the pie.
Get your piece of the pie. Come on out and get your piece of the pie.
They come out. They want their piece of the pie.
They see it. There it is. Right in the field.
Right illuminated. Big frickin' neon
spotlight. Beaming down on it.
This is the pie. Not a pie. This is the
pie. Come get your piece of it. And they line
up. They line up for miles.
Miles and miles.
Spreading out in all directions. Thousands of them
clawing for their piece. Wanting their piece.
Climbing over each other's bodies.
Tearing at each other. Fighting.
This is what the rat race is. The rat race is a
leavening race. Everyone clawing each other. Destroying
each other. Just trying to get to that pie. The brilliant
illuminated pie that's right in the middle of a
field with other tables on it. Other
tables surrounded with other pastries and eclairs
and cakes and pies and everything.
The pie. The pie is right in the middle.
It's the spotlight above it. It's the pie.
Oh, thank God for that light. That light is shining
right down on that pie so you know that it's that pie.
That's what they're going for. I mean,
all these other tables out here have untouched
cakes, untouched danishes and eclairs.
Just free for the
taking that anyone could have. But,
but, can't count those.
Gotta go for the pie.
I found sometimes if you voice
the actual thoughts that are coming in your head, you tend to
scare people. When people start to
realize that you don't think like they do, they tend to get a little bit scared.
They tend to get a little bit afraid. When people start to see the
eyes rolling around, looking
around at the world that they don't see, they start
to get a little scary. Why?
I'm not crazy.
I can just see what's going on.
I see what they don't. I see the things
they don't. I see the interactions as webs.
I see the lies
boiling out of them. I see the honesty
cutting through that and hurting them at their soul, but
they can't see it.
I'm not crazy.
Just honest.
Crazy.
Oh, yes dear friends, that was
P. Kitty. Reverend P. Kitty.
Wonderful little
pie rant there.
That's edited
down some. Part of the
XX Day 1999
video. Before
P. Kitty, we heard a little bit of Reverend
Harold O'Keefe. Before
him, we heard a little bit of Pastor Craig.
And we heard Reverend Moxie
auctioning that tire.
And Jesus, of course,
and myself and
Motomac, I think, running that whole auction.
And friends,
we'll be back into those
recordings on
side two of the party. Thank you.
What I'm getting at,
last year,
on the way home from
X Day, I actually had a
UFO sighting.
Honest to God, I was riding
it was July 6th,
1998.
I was riding on the Amtrak train westbound
to Chicago,
out of Erie, and
saw a cigar shaped object
in the sky.
From my point of view, if I hold
this thing out at arm's length,
that's how big it looked.
At first, I thought it was a passenger
airliner that was about to crash.
It lost its rudder, lost its power.
It had no markings, had no
windows. As I studied it further,
I thought, my God, I'm going to be an FAA witness
called into Washington or something.
And, um,
the nose end
of the craft didn't lift.
Then it did an
axis shift in the sky and it shot out
faster than any other moving object
I've ever seen in my life.
This thing had the
maneuverability of a
aircraft and could outspeed an F-15.
This is, my God,
I cannot, I'm just going to
say it once, this is a true story.
We hear you.
I spent
the next six months
in a really bad
funk over this one,
this sighting.
And, um,
when I was alone,
my God, I cried
out of
anger and fear
and various other emotions.
But I managed to settle
about 85% of all of that
using a copy of
the book The Subgenius.
But I decided to
handle that problem, I decided to use
time control. I went back to the
book of The Subgenius and,
you know, church methods.
One of them was time control.
I decided my credibility
was not damaged when
I, you know, saw the damn UFO.
My credibility was damaged
when I joined the church of
The Subgenius.
To read from a white note,
last year
I was out just walking
around on a brushwood and I heard
probably one of the most stupid comments
I've ever heard in my life.
Um,
I, I,
well that's easy enough to do around here.
Woo! Woo!
All you want?
Okay.
Yeah, it didn't make enough
rotations there, okay.
I heard a woman telling her
friends, um,
you know, I wonder what some of these people are like
in real life.
Oh, fuck!
Yeah!
Woo!
And I thought,
lady,
you have no idea in hell
what some of these people are like.
Thank you, I'll see you whenever they open
the door.
Woo!
After we were
kicked out of, uh, the so-called
enlightened city of Cambridge,
Massachusetts, um,
the local newspaper described us
as a comedy troupe.
Woo!
A comedy troupe
with 10,000 members
worldwide. We're bigger than Cirque du Soleil.
Proceeds from this auction
will be donated to the church,
though you can rest assured that when the
exits arrive, your investment
will be returned a thousand-fold
in the blood of screaming gnomes.
I've got something
that's far more valuable than
pure bull data. I've got the fake bull data.
The bidding has to start
at $2 for conspiracy money!
He holds up a
$1 bill.
He's auctioning a $1 bill.
Yes, it's fine.
Green paper right here is hardly good for wiping
your ass and lining your old birdcage, but
just in case this really is another
slip-up, you'll get to have this to buy
a bus ticket back home.
Two bucks!
Come on! Fifty cents!
Okay, here we are, $2. $2
for this conspiracy money. Whatever you want,
you can buy it. You can do whatever you want with it.
One dollar!
No, the bidding has to start at $2.
$2 for anyone.
We have $1.
Okay, we're currently at the bidding of $1.
$2. Someone must want $2 for this
wonderful... Look at the artwork
on this thing. It's amazing.
The eye of the Illuminati, the eye
on the pyramid, on the back of this.
This is unparalleled artwork. This is an original
print. Each one has its own limited edition
serial number.
Signed by the Secretary of the Treasury.
One dollar and one cent!
We have one dollar and one cent!
We have one dollar and two cents!
One dollar and two cents for someone who wants
to make a difference.
A dollar and two!
A dollar and three!
A dollar and four from anyone!
A dollar and ten!
Pay for a dollar. Beautiful, wonderful.
You've heard of inflation.
This is inflation. Be inflation.
It's gonna double next year anyways.
This is all a little gondola investment for only 75%
additional. Do the math!
My god! This is a bargain!
A dollar and 75... Okay, a dollar and fifty
we got. Going once...
Three dollars!
More historically important,
Mont. One of the few remaining
bottles of sub-Guinness.
Take your time.
I want everyone to be well informed.
A conformed bidder is a high bidding bidder.
The first posse Connie
Tautus t-shirt. You'll notice
the styling, similar to many black metal
bands.
This is the kind of thing that you wear
whenever you want the men to know that
well, you can take it as well as give it.
Or whenever you want the women to know that
you think that's a beautiful thing.
I have a news flash for you.
The Exis might
not arrive on July
5th, 1999 at 7am.
Watch it!
Anything is possible!
Drop the mask!
Burn the pink infiltrator!
But if we could live every day like we've lived
today, then who the f*** can?
I already did!
Ladies and gentlemen, I propose the formation
of a political wing of the church of the sub-Guinness.
This political wing
would be aimed at
convincing every sub-Guinness
to run for local office.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we can and will elect
Ida Stane, Mayor of Dallas, Texas
by 2010!
So what we're saying is in the space
of one year, let me see if I got this straight.
The Boston Divival, well,
was censored by the conspiracy
largely because of
Papa Joe Mama.
The Seattle Divival, well,
could have been better because the conspiracy
sent...
Yeah, I did mention that
Papa Joe controlled a guy
who actually seriously did
go gonzo the night
of my Divival, wound up
killing like two or three old women,
one with a rake and another one
with his bare hands.
And who happened to be present at that Divival?
Papa Joe Mama.
Now I have one other question.
One year ago at this time,
we were standing right here
at Brushwood waiting for the saucers
to arrive. Now may I ask,
who was standing right next to Ivan Stang
when the saucers failed
to arrive?
Papa Joe Mama.
He is the conspiracy!
Papa Joe! Where's Papa Joe?
Where's Papa Joe?
Two, one,
Guilty!
Kill Papa Joe!
Ladies and gentlemen, the woman who
has the most to gain by killing Papa Joe,
Friday Jones.
Come on up here.
What the damn is this? I can't feel it anywhere.
I am so proud of you!
Cool!
Fellow sub-deities,
I am a
sub-genius.
I have always tried to live my
life as Bob Wood. I have tried
to be slack and I have tried
to give slack and there's a
man who has taken slack
from me.
He has taken slack
from you.
He has given the conspiracy a weapon
that they have used to cut
my throat.
And it was just a
joke.
You're flunting the jury. Hold on a minute here.
What is this?
There's only Bob!
I say we just find the
bastard guilty!
The Lord has
arrived in judicial roles.
I'm a lawyer and I think we ought to
at least present some evidence and
make some...
Good Jesus!
This should start with a
famous...
We call for order in the cart!
Order in the cart!
Order!
Today,
we're trying Papa Joe Mama
versus, excuse me,
the Sub-Genius Foundation Incorporated
versus Papa Joe Mama.
Papa Joe Mama is charged with the most heinous
crime of causing the church
to lose money.
Guilty! Guilty!
And being laid for his own
trial.
Sit, please sit there.
Could the lawyers, could the
two lawyers please approach the bench?
How about...
Mr. Joe Mama,
where's your lawyer?
Sir, for the prosecution.
Mr. Joe Mama's lawyer,
please come forward.
I've got a tweet to you, Your Honor.
Ivan Stang and Cowboy Dave.
Oh, hold on Joe, that's right, I'm sorry.
I am also
defending Papa Joe Mama.
You're both prosecuting him and
defending the top.
And that's just the way
we do things.
There's no reason that I...
I mean, I mean, my
Papa Joe Mama is probably
good, but it was funny, at least it was funny.
Please approach the bench, please approach the bench.
Okay, come on, come back to my part.
Please approach the bench, we've got to...
Okay, we're both under the basketball field, so let's get this over with quickly.
All right, Jonathan,
we're about to sit down so you can go out and make a poop in there.
All right, you got it, all right.
You got it, all right.
You can't get this shit out of the show.
The prosecuting attorney
will give his opening argument.
Oh, that would be you and you.
Gladly, oh
gladly, I
look upon this so
called subgenius
Papa Joe
Mama. Oh,
yes, I'll tell you.
We all know what he did. In fact,
well, you've heard
from Miss
Friday Jones.
This, this, this,
this emcee, who has
worked so hard for so,
so many years for Bob,
who spent some of her
entire family's
fortune, everything, the money that
would have gone to keep her
grandmother and mother alive,
was spent on my
ticket, Dr. Williams, and his,
his, and
what did she get in return?
A funny,
funny, funny joke.
Some say hell is a funny joke.
Well, well, a funny joke
is, is hell in your wallet,
friends. If funny
was all right,
then Ed Gein
should have his own TV show.
If funny is
all right, then, uh,
perhaps so, uh, let's say,
Adolf Hitler is the greatest comedian of,
oh, I can't say that to Jane or Michael.
If funny
is, is all right,
then, uh, the Church of the Subgenius
would have destroyed the Earth last year!
So,
but, you have,
you have heard the tragedy
of, of, of Friday.
We're going to give more details
of the aftermath of this man's
funny, funny joke. But,
and this may surprise the defense,
which includes me,
but,
we have the evidence
on tape, and we're going to play it.
In a minute, we must hear
the opening arguments for the defense.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, that's right. Thank you.
All right, I'm also doing the defense. Please.
I mean, the defense, it was funny.
I think, I mean,
he's a holocaust, so he thinks all the
pigs should die, but let's just
enslave him.
Is that, is that enough, uh,
okay, good enough. The prosecution,
the persecution will call
its first witness. That's you,
Reverend Stanton. Call your first witness.
Witness! Witness! Oh, I,
my first witness will be
the people of these American
states who listen to this
travesty of a funny, funny
joke! This travesty
of good publicity for Bob.
Hey, I, I,
I, I, sure I thought it was a funny
joke!
Tiny! Oh, if
what happened hadn't happened, perhaps we'd all be
giving Papa Joe a medal. But like
I say, we'd be giving,
we'd be, we'd be giving
the, the, the, the,
the star of the day, Mr. Stanton!
Mr. Stanton, do you have any evidence?
Let's roll the
tape!
This is a funny call
in through National Public Radio's
Talk of the Nation.
Thank you, Rick.
Aaron joining us from Seattle. Joe's next in
Hey Ray, clearly the parents were involved in this and that they aided and abated their children into getting the information that got them on this wayward path.
They bought them the computer, the kids sent by the computer, the kids went to the internet unsupervised.
They got hooked up with this, what's called a holocaustal sack.
It was on their links page before that was taken down.
But the holocaustal page is still up there on the internet.
It all talks about exterminating the normals and killing the pinks and it's a big thing about pipes and pipe bombs and transsexuals and this sort of stuff.
Any parent would see it and know that it's bad news.
And yet, you know, with bartenders, if they see someone that's drinking a lot, they can go ahead and be liable for that.
It seems to me that parents clearly should have a responsibility when they get hooked up with these false-blown cults.
I mean, even the names, the holocaustals, I mean, doesn't that tell you something?
And this is all part of that church of the subgenius thing, which is a big deal about, you know, superior mutants and supporting deviant behavior.
When people behave this way, that's the extreme behavior that can come out of it.
And people are responsible. It seems to me that the parents have a clear responsibility in this regard.
But I guess, Joe, the question is, where does it go, where do we cross boundaries from simply feeling that they're responsible,
deciding what to do, and then...
Yeah.
...that morally they're responsible to where they can land up in court?
Well, society-wise, I think we need to kind of ask ourselves is entertainment and freedom of speech worth, you know, basically getting people killed.
This whole holocaustal thing, they're still going full force.
They still have their webpages up.
They're having a revival this weekend.
You're right, Mr. Isaac.
Right this weekend, the bodies aren't even cold in the grave.
It's about some big, what do they call it, revival, or Friday, I think it is.
Some restaurant in the Middle East or whatnot.
And they celebrate this type of stuff.
And then it's funny.
And people just stand by and, oh, well, we can't do anything about that.
Well, if we can shut down, you know, KKK people from wearing hoods,
why can't we stop people who are advocating the same type of behavior, which is lynching and killing people, from trying new craft?
But you killed Papa Joe!
It's a lie, it's all a lie!
Well, I'll respond in one way.
Joe, you obviously know a lot about this.
I know a lot about this cult.
I haven't heard of these things.
And it sounds horrifying by your description.
I'm not sure I know enough to sort of concur in all of your characterizations.
But I do want to say I agree with you about this.
I don't believe the First Amendment, the right to freedom of speech, which is a very important foundation of liberty in this country.
But I don't believe it means that people bear no responsibility for the things that they say.
Okay, he's not a taboo.
Enough of it.
We've heard enough of it.
Enough of this travesty.
This was so-called publicity.
Oh, great publicity.
He calls it national public radio.
That's a little cool.
That's communist-controlled policy.
It's government-controlled, I think.
And then conspiracy propaganda that every liberal PC Nazi in Cambridge is sure to listen to.
And then he goes and makes funny jokes about the admittedly hellenistic...
the hilarious Columbine massacre, and the Invitational Massacre.
And I'm in the Holocaust, my God, friends!
Okay, now, how can we call this short bits funny?
But no, what?
Wait until you hear some of the horrible repercussions that this poor woman went through
for this subgenius's funny joke.
Mr. Rothfeder, do you want to call your next witness?
Fuck, what about the children? What about the kids?
Okay, the prosecution rests.
I have one question before we go any further.
Mr. Mama, is Joe from Tallahassee, the voice that we heard on the tape, your voice?
I can assure you it is not your voice.
I'd like the defense to call its first witness.
If I can elaborate.
We've proven that Joe is not your voice.
We plan to present what we term the Ted Bundy defense,
which is, we officially acknowledge it is not us,
but if it were us, we would explain why the culprit would do what the culprit did.
Although we're not the culprit.
Mr. Mama, I believe Ted Bundy was executed.
See, that's exactly what they want you to think.
But I've noticed there's been more serial murders.
Since he's been executed, hasn't there?
Are you saying that you want to be your own witness at this time, Mr. Mama?
Would you like to speak on the charges that have been brought against you?
I would like to point a few small points.
Go ahead.
Now, again, it wasn't me.
All right? We all know it wasn't me.
I know it wasn't me. Friday knows it wasn't me.
There's thousands of Joes.
It could have been Joe from Chicago.
It could have been Joe from California.
It could have been Joe from Philadelphia.
It's murdering him.
Has he even been sworn in?
Has this lying bastard even been sworn in?
Oh, you're right.
Excuse me.
Order, order, order.
They go to fetch a Revelation X.
We have to swear this blasphemer in.
He is sworn in on a copy of the Revelation X.
He plays your right hand on Doc's head.
He tries to just put one finger down.
Right hand.
Right hand, please.
Please put your...
You killed yourself, Bob!
Do you promise to tell the whole truth, nothing but the truth, so help you, Bob?
I'm...
I swear to do!
Okay, you can continue with your argument. Sit him back down.
Well, assuming that it was this person that you claim it was,
I think we all as subgeniuses need to ask ourselves this critical question.
If the end of the world is July 5th, 1999, and the normals are going to be exterminated,
then shouldn't they be warned about it? I mean, there's a regular hunting season.
I submit that they should have a non-composting energy.
They should have a non-composting mental field.
It's clear by the look on his face.
Are you pleading insanity?
Yes, I'm pleading not only insanity, but also...
Not for yourself.
...discorporation, and also incontinence.
And I'm not saying that you should be.
Look, a lack of...
Condons!
Look, a lack of breeding.
I mean, this man is seriously inebriated.
Look at his knees.
His knees are unshaped, and there's no reason for this man to be on the stand, accused the way he is.
Can I please just say something on the spot, ma'am?
Yes, you may have a few words.
First...
No.
Please, dear.
I'd like to implore the jury. It's kind of a jury of your peers.
We don't want to hear it.
I have asked my lawyer.
You're the second-year lawyer?
Yes, I do.
I do.
This is completely...
I mean, I'd rather defend myself than to have this...
Well, in the court of the subjeetious, you have the ability to fire your lawyer if you wish to defend yourself, but you're not a prophet.
Well, but see, I thought, you know, I mean, this guy who's prosecuting me came in and told me he was my lawyer.
I gave him all the information.
I mean, we're on her.
Silence, silence, silence.
She will stop.
She's not a judge, Jordan.
She's not a court lawyer.
Order!
Order to the court!
Mr. Obama, do you wish to steal your lawyer?
Do you wish to fire your lawyer and defend yourself?
I gave him $500.
Answer the question.
Yeah, I want to go on fire.
You want to defend yourself?
My lawyer.
I want my money back, too.
If I'm a judge, I'm going to bring the kids to the king's house.
Sir, I am turning in my former client, Papa Joe Mama, just because we, for some reason,
happen to think that he's got an awful lot of money.
I'll send those tickets to the king's house.
There's not an awful lot of pinky-winky blood coursing through his collapsed twitter
veins, but that we can't afford to let this happen again.
Hey!
Never again!
Ever again!
Once prosperous, subgenius show producer.
Once successful, she was the apple of Bob's eye.
The most successful of all subgenius show producers.
Hard out now.
Now, reamed by this human, I hate to say it, but we cannot let this happen for devival after what is the next funny joke he'll start joking about.
Thank Bob for Friday.
Yeah!
That's a good thing he didn't call NPR to talk about XX Day.
Now, isn't it a fact we got those Jack Puget Storm Troopers from Paper Chute right now?
Do I know who those guys were?
Your Honor.
They were PC Nazis.
Order, order, order.
Put her in the court.
What a burger.
Are there any more, does the prosecution have any more witnesses to call?
I would like to call my client, Friday Jones, to the witness.
Mr. Jones, please take the stand.
I need to be sworn in.
Bailiff.
You need to swear in.
The lovely Miss...
Friday Jones.
Miss Jones.
Woo!
I object to the description of the...
Silence!
...witnesses' beautiful...
Silence him!
If you speak out again, we'll sort him out for both of you guilty bastards.
Now, Miss Jones, I understand that you have quite a bit of evidence that would certainly
convict this obviously, blatantly, only a dumbass could even doubt that.
Wait a second!
The shatter broiled...
Objection, Robert!
He's referring to the judge as a dumbass?
You'll pay him!
You just called you a dumbass.
He said that only at...
Silence!
Where's the duct tape?
I heard...
Father Joe Mama has a potato stuffed into his mouth and his duct tape's shut.
Woo!
We should let the jury at least...
his peers, these marsupials, these hopping marsupials from Australia here to the side,
after listening to this evidence, this filthy evidence,
in the words of the poverty-stricken Friday Jones,
who because of his despicable lack of taste and poor timing,
has been relegated to the very gutter, to prost...
Well, I hate to say it, but to certain forms of...
of work that are illegal in all states except Nevada.
Friday, go ahead if you could, if you can bring yourself to do it,
and share with these good people what has been done to you.
Go, girlfriend.
You go. Go, girl.
When I went to the politician who had shut down the revival,
I asked him, you know,
who gave you...
this information, and what did he tell you about us?
We're the subgeniuses.
We're gonna destroy the whole earth,
but that doesn't mean we're gonna do anything to Cambridge right now.
Yes!
What'd he say?
And he gave me a printout,
and it was,
read at your own risk,
the Holocaustal homepage,
created by Papa Joe Mott.
Delta! Delta!
Come on, I'm not an objector.
He's being...
he's been acting like he's got that porcine thing in his mouth.
This woman's obviously a criminal person.
I know that she's a...
I had an over-reaction.
Oh, another outburst like that?
All right, all right.
It was a...
Ms. Jones, please read the evidence.
In specific...
No!
Eagle's coming!
Shh!
...referring to the revival on the webpage.
Read it!
News flash.
It has come to our attention that Marilyn Manson has cancelled his tours
out of respect for those killed in Littleton.
We salute this magnanimous gesture on the part of Mr. or Mrs. Manson...
Win!
...and hope it provides comfort to those upset by the recent tragic events.
Unfortunately, we're too greedy to cancel our tours,
but we still want to jump on the sympathy bandwagon for various publicity reasons.
So, in honor of those slain, we will provide extra salvation to anyone who shows up in
a black trench coat.
And kids, remember, killing pinks before X-Day is like taking a shortcut during a footrace.
It's cheating.
Uh, kids, dear friends, well, the trial of Papa Joe will be continued next week.
I'm sure you're in, uh, trouble.
Just terrible suspense over the outcome of this trial.
But, uh, it...actually, there are some extremely serious surprises that, uh,
some things were unearthed towards the end of the trial that are...
will have most subgeniuses, uh, wiping the floor with their dropped...
...jaws and drawers.
And, friends, you're listening to the Subgenius Radio Mystery Hour of Slap
on radio station.
The Subgenius.
Station.
For further information about the Church of the Subgenius, please, uh, write to www.subgenius.com
or, uh, tune your browser to post office box 140306.
That's box 140306, Dallas, Texas, 7521.
And once again, that's sacred zip number 75214.
Thanks, Bob, and, uh, help me, somebody.
.
. . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . .