Ah, yes dear friends. This hour of Slack number 1780 is actually a rerun of number
664 from either really late 1998 or early 1999. It includes a devival with Einstein's Secret
Orchestra and Lunsum Cowboy Dave and yours truly Reverend Stang at the Euclid Tavern in Cleveland,
or at least Clipsa, from November of 1998. And there's some great tunes and all kinds of great
stuff. A lot of ESO radio from the late Professor Chas's show. And so, here's Bob.
Fall Let Us Down, ,
年轻 fi ALLENul
GI gap
motherfuck,
Switzerland,
Welcome to Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
Sponsored by the Church of the Subgenius.
The Subgenius Hour of Slack that you are about to listen to
is specially designed only to be played on radio station
and only in the city of...
Yes, dear friends, we're back and it's once again,
it's going to be a solid Einsteinian secret orchestra show
for the simple reason that it's the holidays and I've got to get out of here.
I've got things to do, people to see.
We've got a big...
Tonight the stars will be out.
Don't you know the goddess Pooh-Bang?
Goddess Pooh-Bang?
If you were in a spaceship, you know, you'd keep it pretty clean, right?
And you'd really be very careful about getting your air all dirty
because how would you get clean air again?
Yeah, there's no other air except the air.
You're inside.
It's okay.
When you're outside of a balloon,
you don't think anything about that, you know, pop in that balloon.
But if you were inside the balloon and there was nothing else outside,
you would not want to pop it.
Well, we used to have blimps fly in our neighborhood
and we used to take pot shots at them with our slingshots.
Well, somebody...
We're on...
The Earth is a giant balloon
and who might be taking pot shots at us?
With their slingshots, right.
And are we just developing...
Have we just invented the needle?
We, the people who live inside the balloon,
have now invented the giant needle.
It will pop through and...
So what are we doing?
All the air out.
Hey, let's go.
Let's pop.
Let's go get against our atmosphere.
See what happens.
Yeah.
Well, there's an idea.
Well, when they exploded the first atomic bomb,
they didn't know if it wasn't like Ice-9 or something.
Right.
It would just vaporize the whole atmosphere.
Yeah.
Man.
The whole damn solar system.
They weren't totally sure.
They didn't think it would happen.
Right.
You're in a pool without source.
Did they know it would be that big, as big as it was?
Did they predict?
Yeah.
They were...
It was about the way, when they shot off the first atomic bomb,
it was about the...
And then the guy who...
Dobbs, Oppenheimer, Bob Oppenheimer...
Right.
...who invented it,
he looked at the first explosion and he quoted
the book of the subgenius that I am becomes rock.
This is the end of the society.
The slinkies, the slinkies...
The slinkies...
Oh!
They're fun for girls and boys.
From the deepest, deepest points of the universe we can look at,
and there's these waves in the background,
and they kind of look like these rows of pipes.
I can feel those waves washing over me sometimes when I'm real sensitive.
Yeah.
Wow.
What are those waves?
Have you ever laid in bed in a receptive state of mind
and tried to feel the neutrinos washing across you?
Yup.
I do it every night.
The cosmic particles zipping right through your body.
Yeah.
You say it like it's something unusual.
It's not.
It always makes me need to go to the bathroom when I have...
I hear them every time they hit my eardrums.
My ear nerves, I hear them.
Bing!
They sound to me, they sound like the little particles slamming against your hard drive
when you turn your computer off.
Right.
Do you hear like a rainstorm?
Yes.
Thisлуч is much more efficient than dust.
Dust just degrades whereas a cockroach, as they reproduce, they continue your information.
Another reason why the church, you know, needs more support, friend.
Right.
Because of worthy research like this.
Well, it's a way of sending the pamphlet of Bob and the word of Bob into the future.
Someday an insectoid species long after man has gone will investigate the earth's cockroach.
They'll say, look, encoded in this DNA is this completely useless material that has nothing to do with this creature's life cycle.
Wait a second.
Look, he codes into a photograph of a hideous monster's face with a pipe-like implement sticking from its mandible.
We gotta get going here. We gotta get going home now.
We gotta get out of here.
We gotta build that rocket ship.
Help me, Obi-Wan Kenobi. You're my only hope.
Do you have the mental power? Do you have the willpower to take perhaps an old vinyl record that maybe your grandmother gave you 14 years ago
and view it in your mind as a spaceship, as a flying saucer that can scissor through the cosmos and cut through galaxies like a laser boot?
See?
Ha! Ha!
Oh, look, your little light's flashing.
Look, the twin red eyes in the deep.
Gnashing in the radio.
Who could it be?
Who could it be now?
Which subgenius stalker could it be out there this time?
Who could it be?
Breathing down the backs of our necks.
Who could it be now?
Come on, man.
I, I, you, you owe me all them slacks that Bob said I was, was, was slacks.
And if I believed, I believed and I planted my seed.
Who could it be now?
My slacks.
I want my slacks back.
Who could it be now?
Could it be, could it be the cute stalker?
The stalker everybody wishes was stalking them.
Mm-hmm.
Yes.
Oh, you thought I didn't know about you, did you?
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
Well, old Bobby, he knows all, sees all.
And he pipes all that information down to us followers here in the tower studio headquarters dungeon basement penthouse.
Where we, we have these rock stars and all.
And we have this equipment stuff.
Uh, we, we still need your, your pledge, of course.
And, and, and, and, and you could, you could, uh, you could too.
Come on, everybody wants to.
You, you know you want to.
Everybody wants to.
Don't you?
Come on.
What's the matter?
You scared?
You afraid?
You afraid mama's going to catch you?
You, you, you afraid?
You afraid, you afraid you gonna lose your cool?
Oh, what's the matter?
Oh, you gonna, gonna, gonna, gonna, might, might get diseases?
Oh, come on, man.
Let's go out to the graveyard and desecrate, make satanic symbols, make fun of religion.
Yeah, man.
Sure, kids.
Go on.
Do it.
See where it gets you.
You just be one, one more step.
All right.
Well, now what can I do about scareding you, Bob?
Am I scary enough to kick your ass?
I've got some otherdırles.
Listen buddy, my said you can do, can you tell somebody that is more drill?
I, mytenady do not know how it gets me when I get scared.
I, I just sometimes get weird like that.
And, I somehow have to keep it cool as it gets better.
But look, a big shoulders and I, a strong bark card for childbirth.
monster pterodactyls, scorpion beings.
Oh yeah, yeah, monsters.
There's real live monsters in Godzilla.
That's a metaphor.
Man is metaphorical.
By virtue of the cosmos
and all the powers in command.
By virtue of the forest
and all else that has our power.
We won't go in the middle.
You seem a little nervous, my friend.
You went the straight to the fire, so.
You saw me from beyond.
You'd better be ready
to speak your piece.
You caught me from beyond.
You disturbed my rest of sleep
with your childhood games.
You don't know what you're playing with.
I'm sorry.
This is my game.
Put a little voice in me, I hope.
This is your life.
Look, we're not just another stupid army of elephants.
Listen to the music backwards in reverse.
If the troops they were,
they wouldn't.
They wouldn't.
I don't care about that.
Then how much do you pay me?
Well, they're dead.
You're bad on their money.
Listen to me, I'm going into business.
See no man,
We're sus propose it to be us two six.
Let's do it now,
And then I found
The truth is in the taking
I'm a fool, which I will eat alive
It's you, I'm a spit in your face
Are you ready for me?
Can it be ready to face the consequences?
It's never too late to redeem yourself
One last chance
That's all you have
It's up to you
You ready for me?
No escaping my eyes
You'll see them in every dream
You ready?
You'll never escape the eyes
The sun will never shine with the eyes
Would you listen to me?
You ready for me?
From beyond
You ready?
You ready to face the truth, my friend?
I'm here for you
So long
I'm sayin' we won't win
Don't you wait till we show the light
Don't be late to tell that meeting
I'll betta I'll pull every once again
Listen up, you puttin' that hole up in your reopin'
He stopped ivin' though you take him another rappin' out of her fingernails The sandwiches were forced to eat
It all went right away, bruhāði,alarbreți sällv theor Dad the video ends here, goodbye dad the video ends here But I still haven't edatied anything that is awning tonight I heard we made an announcement in the next photo by sûg plane
You have exactly 24 minutes to get these people to believe somehow or other.
They must join the Church of the Subgenius or they will die.
What button can we push?
The sexual buttons have all been pushed.
The drunk buttons have all been pushed.
How about simple repetition of a word?
Bob.
You say it now.
Could you say it, sir, please?
Bob.
Now say it like a paralyzed child trying to communicate.
Say, Bob.
Bob.
Now you got to say this now.
I want you to do it.
Okay, you in the front row can do it now.
Bob.
Now I want you to say, Bob.
I want you to begin doing it now.
My son.
Thank you very much.
Let's do it.
It's perfect.
Thank you, Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
Oh yes, I forgot about that.
Well anyway, I'm sorry that I did that.
I was very unprepared tonight too.
Anyway, here's the bottom line of the whole thing.
I was the guy that almost came up with that internet joke,
you know the internet joke about Johnny Black when he comes back
and everybody wearing ape suits and stuff.
Do you know that joke?
Okay, for those of you who don't,
when Johnny Black comes back and all those guys land,
everybody dress up in ape suits like landing on him.
So while I was only the guy who almost came up with that joke,
I did come up with this joke.
Okay, there's this guy.
He's got like a regular normal head and a nice normal body and everything,
but he's got this little teeny tiny growth,
a little tiny growth that looks like a head coming out of his neck right here.
So,
so the guy walks into a bar, see,
and he pulls out a two dollar,
two dollar bill,
and he slaps it on the counter,
and he says,
just give me a beer.
And the bartender says,
hey buddy,
we don't serve freaks in here.
And the little teeny head on the side of the guy's neck pipes up,
hey buddy,
cut me some slack.
I've been trying to get rid of this asshole for the last three days.
And I take the money.
I I don't know where the hell he's self sorry that we could have had this job.
I think we started a little real crazy.
Moving on.
.
I don't know why it happened,
it was weird.
.
If your body's in a bed
It's the only one you have
You wanna take away the flame
Of the world that's beneath the rain
So watch the farmers go to bed
Ask the man inside the head
To never see
All the eyes in the rain
The faith in us
Yes friends, I'm not talking about hate
I'm talking about eight
Dinner at eight
That's right, let's eat
The glory and communion of food
The mighty hot dog
The jack and his boy
The lovey stick
The wonderful hummus and bread
Oh friends, you could probably be saved
By food or anything else that you
But don't do that just one time
I can only heal your bodies
Faith and hope and charity
A simple relativity
They can make you understand
All you gotta do is take his hand
Remember, remember, remember
What someone said
Ask the man inside my head
He'll never have to leave
All you gotta do is believe in God
The faith in us
He's fully licensed friends
He's ready to serve
Can I put my hands on you?
Can I put my hands on you第三ese
Staff 54
.
He can see your future, he can see your past, and if you bend over he can see your up.
Oh, he's got everything he needs to heal or sicken you.
Trust the man inside your head.
Oh, friends, we want to put our hands on you.
We'd like to get down in there and grope every one of you, just put our hands all over you, but we just can't do that.
But we will someday.
Can I put my hands on you?
Reverend Ivan Stang, ladies and gentlemen.
Archdiocese Secret Orchestra, ladies and gentlemen.
Oh, friends, oh, we would like to put our hands all over every one of you.
Look at this.
According to a Reuters wire service report in August,
lobbyists in Bonn, Germany,
called the Working Group for the Unemployed,
held a series of rallies to demand six weeks' annual paid vacation
for people out of work,
pointing out that those looking for work often are under greater stress
than those with jobs and thus need a longer holiday.
Praise those unemployed workers of Germany
demanding a longer vacation.
Friends, that is subgeniusness in action.
They give you a half an inch and you take 40 miles.
Now, this kind of thing can go on a little bit too,
it can get too intense.
In August, a couple from Silver Springs, Maryland,
were arrested for indecent exposure at an adult cinema in Baltimore
after the husband had arranged for four men,
two of whom were in the same room,
to have sex with his wife on the premises of this adult theater.
According to the police, several other males in the theater
complained apparently because the live sex interfered
with their enjoyment of the sex on the screen.
Friends, I guess you could say there is perhaps such a thing as too much slack.
I mean, did those guys actually stop and think?
Did they really want the live sex to stop?
So, you know, friends, as they said in Clockwork Orange,
the colors of the real world are never so really real
as when you video them on the screen, you know.
And, friends, you know, that causes a thing like,
when you read about a thing like that,
you have to ask yourself, what is slack?
How they did it, then, when you read them on the screen
and how theyrontyas out.
This is basically an example of moins dans le seu que vous avez fait.
Com 보니까 du film.
Be pull it right to the tip of the spoon.
And there's a good thing about that kind of stuff,
but instead it's kind of like the motion mirror or the third persona tool
that I'm looking at in the movie from Adobe's transformation say.
When you're about once a week, they put you in a big tank and hose you down with fire hoses to clean you.
Yeah, that sound goes off.
The eh, eh, eh, eh.
And all them guys in them suits come in.
And then after that, they come in with them suits and them big thermal things there and stuff like start poking you.
It feels real hot.
And then you've got to all get hurried in another room.
Then they just turn the hoses on us, and it's not very quick.
You're staying there now?
Yeah, I told you, man, I'm in here.
I had a little problem before.
Got into an argument in the bar, and they said, you know, you're going back here for a while.
And I said, well, what's a while?
And they said, until your attitude changes and you can talk to Dr. Vinsky about it.
And Dr. Vinsky ain't helping me.
And Dr. Psychopath Finder obviously didn't help me none or else I wouldn't be in this problem.
And, you know, it's just getting worse.
I don't have to worry.
I don't have to worry about claustrophobia anymore, Dr. Phobia, because he's on vacation.
But there's people around here.
You just wouldn't believe the things they can do to the human body, the kind of pain they can inflict.
I don't care.
I'm talking on a regular phone, you know.
Well, you know, I'm surprised that they let you talk.
Are you sure that you're talking on the phone and not just hooked up to a machine imagining that you're talking on the radio?
How the hell would I know right now?
You know, I don't practically repeat my damn brain.
And, you know, all I want to do is watch the hearing.
And then they all come in here, you know, and then they start staking me and threw me.
That's okay, man.
I don't blame you.
I mean, all your friends are in the hearing.
It looks like a phone to me.
I don't know.
The hearings are about your friends.
And I'm sure that it bothers you.
How does it feel?
How does that make you feel, Dave?
Well, I don't know.
That's a rather difficult question to answer.
You don't mind talking about it, do you, Dave?
Oh, not at all.
Be bold.
Are you going, people?
What do you say?
Do you keep falling into little fat lumps of clay?
The TV is calling.
Please don't go away.
The children are bawling.
But you can't go out and play.
There's only one sin and it down from above.
People dying.
Gifts dead.
Living in love.
In love.
Be bold.
When are you going?
On each Sunday morn.
While you play to your monster.
The kids are watching porn.
Do they really see?
See beyond.
Rose crowns and thorns.
From all that they're building.
Where my brother was born.
There's only one sin and it down from above.
People dying and killed instead of living in love.
In love.
The discovering of uninvited lovers is not a crime.
Take a fewmale.
You are here.
Follow us.
There are no end to payoff.
I wanted to challenge you guys.
For something awesome, Har emocional.
You travelled to Ipanema.
This is Chaz Smith, Einstein's Secret Orchestra.
There is only one sin.
Yes, love is the sin.
I guess that means it's probably extra fun to do it then, huh?
Yeah.
This is love.
Now, Bob, there is a man who claims to be channeling God.
I can't recall what this man's name is.
Maybe him.
No, no, no.
He's a secular guy, and he's got books out, and he claims to be channeling God.
And I kind of wonder, I don't know, yeah, the guy, Van...
Bob, Bob, Bob.
You heard me.
My, my, my, but you do have a soft, delicate throat.
A candy-colored clown they call a sandman
Tiptoes to my room every night
Just to sprinkle stardust and to whisper
Go to sleep, everything is all right
Cities of the world woke up today to potential tragedy in outer space.
The vehicle has exploded.
I've just picked up a fault in the AE-35 unit.
It's going to go 100% failure within 72 hours.
So you feel that you have some conflicts regarding religion that need to be resolved.
Would you like to discuss those, Dave?
Yeah.
I think that all of...
How does that make you feel, Dave?
Well, the first experiment they did was what did it, was all wrong to me,
trying to teach me God that way.
You know, that ain't right, sticking them things up different places in me, you know,
and then making me pray all these different prayers.
I don't know what the hell they was even talking about.
I'm sorry to hear that, Dave.
Tell me more.
Well, the first they started to implant these little religious devices,
these little things in my body, different crucifixes,
little Madonnas and different little things like that.
Just no bigger than a thumbnail, some of them are so small, you know.
How do you feel about little Madonnas, Dave?
Well, when they're dancing around my head in my pig sleep, I don't mind.
But when I'm fully awake and alert and maybe being prodded around with those big hot thermal sticks,
then that's a whole different can of tuna.
I hear what you are saying, Dave.
And how does that make you feel?
It makes me sad.
It makes me happy.
It makes me...
It makes me filled with kind of a preternatural delight.
I can't explain because I'm vibrating the whole time.
You know what I mean?
I'm afraid I can't do that, Dave.
Did I screw up someplace along the line to cause this all to happen?
I mean, you have to bring home some evidence saying,
hey, folks, it wasn't my fault.
Take a look at this picture.
Something happened back there and I wasn't back there.
Any penetration.
Any penetration of the heat shield would have very possibly allowed a heat leak, plasma leak,
and eventually a burn through during the process of entry.
That would be trippy, huh?
As Jesus is sitting there, all these birds are flying around.
What sort of theft?
A comment.
you. And you love Bob. And if you don't love Bob, you know what happens. He'll kill you.
He'll Bob you out.
It's energy. Surrounds us. Invites us. Luminous in you Zoe. Not this crude matter.
Is this the little Connie I care? Is this the little Bobby at play? I don't remember building spaceships.
When did
I
be?
The first spaceship built by our sole inventor, a lone eagle type fella who built out of old tin cans in his backyard.
Godspeed, John Glenn.
Take me home, you silly boy.
It was the lone eagle concept, was it not?
The sense of one man facing the unknown rather than the crew idea.
Sure, and not only did they build a spaceship in their backyards and take off the next day, but they didn't stop at the moon.
Excuse me, are you a little bit tipsy? Have you been drinking?
Said no, no, no, I'm praying to the Lord.
You bringing me down. You ain't getting me high enough. Somehow, I don't know what the deal is, but that weird stuff that gets in your glands through your sweat, whatever they call them, stuff I know.
I know it's getting somehow in my cerebral cortex because I can smell it in here.
Roger, zero G and I feel fine. Capsule is turning around.
Welcome to the next day rockin' assembly building where we can watch the progress of the dedicated Bobby's hard at work building the pleasure ships and marvel at the blind, unbridled passion of the church leaders spurring them on.
Drink the Kool-Aid, children. Drink the Kool-Aid. Drink the Kool-Aid, children.
Doc Smith had a fellow who was working as a chemist at the National Bureau of Standards one afternoon. Two days later, he had conquered the whole galaxy.
Shit.
I was looking at my crystal ball and it just went completely blank.
I just inserted my crystal ball into the, uh, into the end of my spaceship.
I just inserted my
Oh, my God, you put the Dionysium crystals into the hull already, chad!
We're there. We're there.
Oh, my God, you put the Dionysium crystals into the hull already?
Not only did they build a spaceship in their backyards and take off the next day, but they didn't stop at the moon.
Moon.
Backyard.
The first page of chapter 2 of the history of the space-time.
I wanna go.
I wanna go, !
Now look why don't you call off, what would be the equivalent insult for Grays to the
term Tom or Apple, Tom, what would you call a Gray who is like a human lover?
What would you call a gray who just he kind of forsook his gray heritage and was a human
mimicry?
Primitive.
primophile that's that's delicious that's a good one homophile and it's kind of yeah
that sounds like something they already got down here yeah no i like primophile it's kind of poetic
primophile yeah but you wonder if it has to do with firstness or that's the that's the access
is that made number 1797 yes my queen you have been found guilty of primophilia i cannot resist
the lures of the humans well then they would also be attracted to monkeys if they had real
primophilia cast cast gray number 4055 into the mulch pit and paint him on the stomachs of the
other words right there we're gonna paint you with
the two nuclear superpowers and their leaders stood eyeball to eyeball
a sickly frenzied passion for that wasting form began to obsess me
you
you feel me
i've broken through the wall of inertia and reached my goal
the challenge is to bring up a
bright sprout from this dry parched ground yes deep inside to launch a great seed up into space
and carry our kind out out into the galactic brotherhood where we'll probably end up in a
being the shoe shine boys is the galactics i would not be so sure for the first two million years
no i don't think we will need more stats when we arrive there i think that uh yeah you think the
galactic are gonna roll the red carpet out for a bunch of a bunch of monkeys that just fell out of
the tree by galactic standards who don't even have a patron yeah that's true all by ourselves here just just fell out of the tree by galactic standard
Just us. Earth. Earth. Earthers. Damn two biped monkey face boys.
An atomic bomb. The most powerful explosive yet developed.
We have the technology. We have the technology. We have the technology. We have the technology.
Sometimes it feels like a...
We had visited a very alien and very hostile and lifeless planet.
And we saw the Earth as the only home that we know of within our near space capable of supporting life.
And we recognize the absolute necessity to protect and nurture and take care of this environment.
An invisible being that cannot be disintegrated by atomic fission.
Oh, Skipper. That is a scientific impossibility.
There he goes.
Oh, that's the last of that.
Purging the last of the bad blood of Bob out of our bowels.
And wasn't that invigorating?
The blabbering bladders of the bad Bob blood.
It's the ink or the...
I can breathe again.
In the face.
I had arrived here by my own choosing and I had no intention of ever going back.
I was going through...
Look, the blasts are increasing.
Doctor, look. The color of the...
The blasts.
Oh, dear God.
What? What?
Doctor, it's nitrogen, isn't it?
Nitrogen? What?
The fools. The everlasting fools, I warn you.
The blasts. More and more.
They started something they couldn't end. The color of the blasts. They've set off hydrogen atoms.
I... I don't know what...
We used uranium, plutonium, and when the initial blast was over, that was all.
But hydrogen, that's part of life.
One reaction sets off the other like setting off an endless chain until...
Look down there.
The blasts. Faster and faster.
They're spreading.
The fools. I'd help the fools.
The sheet of flame.
Around the Earth.
Doctor, tell me, what is it?
It burned up all the atmosphere.
Burned up...
Reynolds, what does he mean?
The chain reaction.
Burned up all the air.
Now, throughout my relationship with God,
I have tried different methods.
I've tried different methods.
I've tried different ways of sex.
You can have sex with God.
And it's okay, just as long as you wear a condom.
Those are the aliens that are hiding in plain view.
I mean, they're right out in front of us.
You never actually saw one of them, though.
They're the real face, right?
Well, if I... How would I know?
I mean, we all might have...
They might be around us all the time.
We wouldn't know.
Yeah, but you made it sound as if you had heard, or had some touch to...
...Plemonians going on.
You know, the one where Spoofy's saying that they knew what they...
...described their face to you.
And you said it was horse-like.
Like, was Gorgonzola and Hegesys that guy?
Yeah, exactly. They were hideous.
Like, Gorgonzola. Like that thing that drips off of his face.
Yeah.
When he gets all worked up.
And that's why Medusa had to hang a...
...a shield up there.
So he could look at it and say,
Check this out, man. You need to shave, you know?
Right. And, yeah, it was...
It was like Medusa had the super power of turning people to stone,
But Gorgonzola had that power of turning people to stone,
And that was the only smell that could even kill Medusa.
Well, that's what you were saying.
If the Vigaz wanted to be actually decomposed in space,
It would have to transfer them smells into the chambers where they make them into different homes.
Whatever they are.
Like, if you're playing Illuminati New World Order on some secret orchestra,
At the same time.
And you use the plug-in, the Gorgonzola plug-in,
You can, like, if you get that when it's infected,
That will take your opponent's, uh,
Or, like, him, or Lonesome Cowboy Dave,
Or whatever, and,
You know, then you can convert, you could,
You've got their powers.
Yeah, but if you start double-clicking on them things that come up,
I heard that whole civilization's disappeared.
This is Dr. Q. Ellis here,
Coming to you live from Friendly Island in Tonga,
Just minutes from the international dateline.
I'm here to cover one of the first few rupturings
To take place on this historic day.
Of course, being a clone,
I'm resigned to the fact that I
Will be destroyed.
I welcome my, I, I,
Remote 142, M38,
I, I, I,
Okay, 55, damn it, what time,
Okay, full 99,
Okay, full 99, full!
I, I, I, of course, Reuters
And the AP and the rest will not be
Covering today's events.
Uh, the news blackout will continue
Right up until the bitter, bitter end.
Taped news has been
Gathered from the conspiracy media's
Vast archives and international
News will be manufactured for what is
Still Saturday for the western world.
The good news is that Dr. Clones
And other institute agents are
Scattered across the globe for the sole
Purpose of keeping you, the giddily
Discerning yeti, updated on
Your own salvation.
Yes, yes, yes, here they come,
They have their weapons, well,
It appears they've been tipped off that this is
A friendly island, and they aren't.
I made it funny. Friendly,
And this is friendly, and
Fatal error.
Memory overlaps.
Memory overlap.
738.
Alright, this one's shot.
Activate remote destruct sequence,
Just in case.
Well, somebody was thinking of it.
Or else you wouldn't have come out there.
Oh, they're all, well, I mean,
As soon as one person thinks of it,
Then a hundred monkeys are gonna start
Doing it, and I won't think.
If that hundred, if that first monkey ran off the edge
Of the cliff, would all your hundred monkeys go following it?
Definitely.
They're watching their fish in the water, and next thing you know,
Ten years later, everybody's watching their fish in the water,
And they all jump in.
They all stand up, like lemmings, or
Like the hundred lemmings.
The hundred, twelve hundred monkeys?
The twelve hundred monkeys.
Toby!
Cold, persistent
Fingers swarmed over my body,
Tugging at me, and sucking
Me away from the machine.
I held tight to wieners, a man holds fast
To life, and tried to kick them
Away with my feet.
Toby! Toby! Toby!
Get these levers quickly, or we're done!
One more turn, and it's game over!
You touch me, try to stop me,
I'll throw the switch.
The truth about real sex with God,
And that,
That will help me
Gain victory over the power of lust
In my life. I mean, you could have the most
Perverse thought in the world pass through your mind,
But perhaps you've tried some of those.
And you're going to divide that thought
Into your life.
And sit down and have a cup of coffee with it.
Cut up,
Slow down, you're moving too fast.
You got a
Meadow morning
Mustards, kicking
Around the cobblestone.
Look for fun,
And feel engrossed.
La la la la la la
Feel engrossed.
Got new teeth,
And do the promises to keep.
Dabbled in drowsiness,
And ready for sleep.
Love the morning sun,
Drop all its petals on me.
Love the love of you,
And all this grooving.
La la la la la la
Feel engrossed.
Land hoes, what you knowing?
I've come to watch your flowers growing.
Ain't you got no rhymes for me?
Do, do, do,
Feel engrossed.
La la la la la la
La la la la la
Feel engrossed.
I'm feelin'
Groovy.
God is in his holy temple.
Earthly thoughts beckon,
Hey, silent now.
Um, oh, oh, background music.
Oh, oh, background music.
Dear friends, that was of course Chazz Smith.
A lot of Einstein's secret orchestra
going on tonight.
Chazz actually edited this show you might say.
Most of what was,
has been played was uh...
What?
Every man needs about three.
One to make babies with.
One to groove with.
What the hell?
How about a couple of honest-to-goodness virgins?
Send me about a dozen assorted variety.
How about me for starters?
What the hell is this?
What did your mama say?
She used to make me take piano lessons from this groovy young guy.
We used to sit just pressing our thighs together.
Well, one week we were practicing,
and all of a sudden his hand went up my skirt.
Hey, hey, hey, enough of that, kids.
Oh, that's Friday Jones figures.
Yeah, Friday Jones figures.
She has some good figures.
Anyway, I thought I was putting in that.
That's what I thought I was putting in,
but I put in Friday.
Yes, her little Russ Meyer type there.
I haven't really listened to that yet.
Well, now we know what's on there.
Russ Meyer movie soundtracks.
That's some pretty great stuff.
Groovy stuff, man.
And you're listening to the groovy subgenius radio ministry,
Hour of Slack,
tonight's show,
and like last week's,
all done at the same time,
mostly by Chaz,
the cantor, Chaz Smith.
Not the man heard playing in the background.
That's the Hell Pope Huey.
He's the Hell Pope,
and I'm the sacred scribe.
But Chaz is the cantor,
and he can indeed,
and he did.
We also heard Bill T. Miller's song,
You Rang,
very early in the show.
That's Kings of Feedback, Bill T. Miller.
And of course, Lonesome Cowboy Dave,
who is part of Einstein's Secret Orchestra,
but he was doing kind of a live audience thing
from the Euclid Tavern Devival,
November 8th, not very long ago,
recorded by myself on the donated deck.
And boy, this music makes me talk fast.
Everything else on there was from Chaz's Volume 10 mix,
edit.
And I think that's the kind of stuff
that we do on his radio show,
ESO Radio,
which you can hear on the internet
no matter where you are, friends.
They're out of WCSB in Cleveland,
but on the internet,
if you go to this address,
hurl yourself to this URL,
www.wcsb.org,
that's WCSB.org.
And on Thursday nights,
11 o'clock Eastern Time,
you can hear that radio show
on the audioactive internet thing,
and you can call in.
You can be on the show,
and then you'd be on this show.
It's like you call into Chaz's show,
and Chaz sends me,
and we do a thing,
a worshipful, you know,
subgenius religious,
and then Chaz sends me the tape,
or he edits together
one of these type things,
and then suddenly you're a big,
you know,
big highly paid star,
just like all the rest of us.
So, so,
such a great job,
and,
oh gosh.
Uh,
eh.
binged.com
The Golden Rose,
the color of the dream I had
Not too long ago
The Golden Rose,
Pistil blue and lilac too
There were two grown
There you were under the tree of sun
Sweeping so peacefully
In your hand a flower played
Waiting there for me
I have never
Made eyes on you
Not before
This timeless day
But you woke and you
Smiled my name
And you stole my heart away
You stole my heart away
And girl, yeah
Alright
Girl
Girl, give me
Give me that dream
Hey!
Golden rose
The color of the dream I had
Not too long ago
Pistil blue and lilac too
There were two grown
There you were under the tree of sun
Sweeping so peacefully
In your hand a flower played
Pistil blue and lilac too
There you were under the tree of sun
Golden rose
The color of the dream I had
Not too long ago
Pistil blue and lilac too
There you were under the tree of sun
Golden rose
It's only a dream
I'd love to tell somebody about this dream
The sky was filled with a thousand stars
While the sun kissed the mountain's blue
And eleven moons played across the rainbow
Above me and you
Golden Rose, Golden Rose
I caught another bell in the water
And you, that's the end of us
Alright, now close your eyes
Take a deep breath
And let the water show you
You are slowly sinking
And the outside thoughts are coming to your mind
Simply brush them aside
And I want to begin by having you focus your attention upon the psychic center of your body
None of what you see is real
It's all a dream
Out of band experience
Bill T. Miller's album A Drum Army
It's a token of your life
And a feeling that's spreading over your entire body
Put your physical body to sleep
I'll open your subconscious mind
And feel your core and neurons fire high voltage impulses into the forebrain
These impulses become pictures
The pictures become dreams
And I want you to begin to use your imagination and feel your body relax
A situation where you think you need to turn 2
Discover and gather all the uns album
Adopt anозд
Create a perfection of yourself