From PR News in Washington, I'm an unregistered foreign agent for Ukrainian interests and lied to Trump's former campaign chairman.
Prosecutors have 3,500 witnesses that they say earned tens of dollars in Ukraine.
Facebook says we're involved with the Russian government.
Facebook has a new campaign, but says it used PR News procedures similar to those used by the Russian research agency.
Here's reports loom large.
Something a top Facebook official calls not interesting.
Secretary Pompeo says...
Mayor Pory wants his PR News.
President Trump says this is PR. It's about 27% contained.
Clearing the way for posting the downloadable PR News to the internet.
The Daily News in Santa Fe, Texas is reporting that this is hundreds of thousands of dollars worth of PR.
Hello?
Now you listen to me.
You asked for this.
You asked for...
The self-genius.
Power of...
What?
Shut up, you.
Get out of here.
He's a raven lunatic.
You are directed to make effort to keep it alive and protect it against injury.
Well, I understand.
So, here I am with, uh, our friend, the Pink.
Hi, I'm the Pink!
Hi, Pink.
Pink Boy!
What are you doing?
You bland normal.
Look at you.
Unh.
That may mean what you think.
You simply have the bi vaccin deceiv Therefore, here I think the actual names of the most va xiv
of the bleventhearted Insedi Death compared to Jane.
You're a weirdo too, but you like football and mainstream media.
The Great Gates of Dobstown.
Not unlike the Great Gates of Kiev, but not with a piano.
Welcome to Dobstown, where you, yes, you are weird just like us.
Penny on down, or horse on down, or cow on down, or goat on down, or bear on down.
Bear down, bear down, bear down to the casket.
Get yourself a cup of mutant key.
Yes, have a mutant key.
Ring out your head.
Grab an ear in each hand and twist.
It's yours, so you can do it.
You're allowed.
You're very allowed.
Ring it out.
Thank you, Reverend Richard Negative.
After a long delay, we now have in rotation
his album, Welcome to Dobstown.
which is on bandcamp.com under the name mrnegative.bandcamp.com.
Mr. being just an MR.
mrnegative.bandcamp.com.
And he has been collaborating with many other sub-gene IE,
such as in this particular case, Reverend Just John,
in that song, Ring Out Your Head.
We have new music upcoming on this hour of Slack, number 1,749,
including Piss Baptist John Shirley,
the Swingin' Love Corpses,
and the Slot Rods.
But first, from 22X Day Drill last summer,
the third show on July 2nd,
Dr. Hal and Dr. Finkel,
and Dr. Kyla Drummond,
and yours truly, Princess Wee,
musing about our surprisingly long, so far, lives.
Sometimes I feel like Little Big Man.
You've seen it all.
Because I've...
I actually had a fairly normal middle class upbringing,
but then I was like a regular kid thrust into this weird school with rich kids.
And I saw it, but...
I don't know what real rich people were like.
And they have whole other levels of stupid problems,
way as bad as anybody who actually has had to have common sense,
you know, and support themselves.
If you're born rich, it's real easy to just be a moron.
You can afford to be stupid about everything.
You said the scariest thing is a drunken rich person.
A drunken rich man.
It's the most dangerous creature on the planet Earth.
Absolutely.
I believe it.
Just ask that guy that Dick Cheney shot.
Anyway, we...
I lived on an Indian reservation like Little Big Man.
I was the only white guy for miles around.
And Wellman, too.
What is this?
I lived in China.
Me and my boss were the only white guys in China in 1986.
We're...
Well, we weren't the only ones.
We were the only ones we could see in this hotel in Beijing.
We're trying to finish a movie that had been shot there.
Documentary.
It was stupid.
About the runner.
The guy...
Yeah, the runner.
I did work a bunch of subgenius stuff into it.
I got to rewrite it.
Anyway, and then I ended up living in a big city,
East Coast City, Cleveland.
But it is like an East Coast city.
And now I live back in the country.
And everybody misunderstands everybody else.
The city people think all the country folks are these butt-toothed yokels.
And that is what they look like.
And that is how they vote.
But they're not really that way.
They're really...
Most of them are just as friendly and nice and helpful to strangers as they can be.
Genuinely nice.
And by the same token, those poor yokels think of city people as either being quiveries,
or quivering libtards hiding from the evil roaming gangs of brown people,
or I don't know what.
But neither of those is true.
Princess, we and I have been in every neighborhood.
We lived in Collinwood.
That's like saying, you know, South Compton or whatever.
True.
True that.
Much of McGirder.
Snoop Dogg's old high school.
I thought that was weird.
Dark shadows.
You know, as long as we didn't go out at night, we were just fine.
Uh-huh.
Collinwood?
Yes.
But, you know, so rednecks think the city life is just pure violence.
And the city people think the redneck world is just pure violence.
And they're both really pretty violent, but only in small doses.
If you spend all day long listening to the police scanner, yeah, it's pretty paranoid.
But if you just read the science news, you go, oh, they've created a new cure.
And the world is going to end fairly soon in a miserable ways.
I won't be alive to see it, I don't think.
And this-
So why should I care?
Next decade, supposedly, will contain a massive moon settling that's going to-
What, the next 10 years?
The 2020s, yes.
That's different.
I don't like to hear that.
They're going to put-
They're going to put up essentially a city there, and they are going to put-
On the moon?
Yes.
And they're going to put a space station to supply that city in orbit around the moon.
Didn't they see the shitty 2002 version of the time machine?
That's exactly what causes everything to go bad.
Golfing on the moon causes the moon to explode into different parts, and it throws off the
Earth's orbit.
And next thing you know, it's Morlocks and Eloy.
And stupid versions of them.
Yes, I understand.
I'd like to kill-
Yeah, that's terrible.
I'd like to kill that director.
And he's the grandson of the great H.G. Wells, who directed that piece of crap.
Yes, now-
There's some things getting me really worked up.
If it had been Frank Wells, now he was a nice guy, he never would have done that.
But then this is yet another generation that they-
There's only one good version of him.
There's only one version of the time machine, and that's the George Powell one.
It's pretty faithful to the book, given their limitations at the time.
It goes there.
It goes to the book.
But it kept the basic idea, which was class division will divide the human race into two
completely different species.
I'm reading a sci-fi book now where the internet has started to do that.
Rural America, or Ameristan, is where everybody believes everything on the internet.
And what they end up calling the blue cities, where you can actually find a doctor and
things, is where people have enough money to pay for very advanced bots to edit the
internet for them, so they're not completely barraged with brainwashing garbage.
Don't forget that-
There's two different countries.
The borders are roughly defined as the areas, as you're leaving a city, when you start seeing
the Walmarts.
That's where Ameristan starts.
Well, I live in Ameristan now, and it's not that bad yet.
But this book takes place 20 years in the future, and I can see it being quite plausible.
It sucks.
It's horrible.
That's not the main point of the story.
It's talking about Neal Stephenson's brand new book, Fall, or Dodge in Hell, which came
out about two weeks ago.
And I'm such a fan of his.
I'm so jealous of him.
I hate him so much, I immediately bought the hardcover.
How did you get the advance copy there?
I ordered it the day before it was going to be published, and it actually came to me that
day.
And I started reading it about two-thirds of the way through.
They figured out a way to keep dead people sort of alive by scanning their brain after
they're dead in a high-resolution way.
A high-res way that's unimaginable now, but given quantum computing and a few other advances,
they end up being able to preserve a brain and switch it back, the brain patterns, and
switch it back on.
They don't remember their life, but they eventually imagine a life.
And to them, that's real.
And there's this whole virtual world of dead computer people that can look at each other
and think, oh, I'm dead.
And look like people.
And they even eat food and shit and so forth.
But it's all virtual.
But they are alive, except they're just bits.
It's a very weird concept and kind of worth looking into, especially if you believe in
that singularity stuff, which I don't, because I think the ideogularity is going to beat
the singularity by a long shot.
But of course, if your brain is being broken down and scrupulously copied by the computer,
nonetheless your end occurs there.
And the computer, which thinks it's you, continues its existence.
Your consciousness does not travel to the computer.
The computer has only made a copy.
Now you, the original, are discarded.
Yeah.
That's part of the point of it.
It's just they're not the same person at all.
But certain reflexes and skills come back.
It's kind of like being in a video game that you can't leave.
Well, you see, these were created by experience.
And they did create a personality.
So there's some kind of analog of a personality there, naturally.
All those parts which comprise it.
Well, if they do that to me, would you please just turn off the switch?
Well, they locate it where you can't reach it.
Right, of course.
I won't have fingers.
I'll just be like P-Dog or Care Dog.
Care Dog's brain preserved in a jar of just pure pain for eternity.
Remember that Colossus of New York?
Yes.
He had an off switch, but it was where he couldn't reach it.
Between his shoulder blades.
He had to have somebody else to pull the switch.
I must, yet I cannot.
Well, it takes him a long time to realize he needs to be turned off.
Oh, he has a road to Damascus moment when he was going to kill all the humans and go to the U.N. and fry everybody with his eyeballs.
So, once again, the decency is the ultimate winner.
See, once again, we're muttering about old monster movies, Dr. Bell.
I didn't mean to mutter.
No, that's not healthy.
I hope I spoke clearly and explicitly.
No, you're actually starting to put me to sleep.
Well, but you don't see the end.
I've seen you fall asleep like this.
The Colossus of New York's a problem, so are those of our own.
There's photographs of him like.
But five minutes later, he'll be back, you know, being Dr. Bell.
I'll be right back.
He's like that.
It's a good thing they have these foam, you know, wind, worm screens on these microphones.
Yes, foam on the radio.
Foam on the radio.
All right, somebody pot Stang out.
That's too much pot for Ivan Stang.
Yes, he's collapsed.
Visiting the dream kingdom of Morpheus.
Suckling the teat of Morpheus.
Well, I wasn't going to go that far, but as long as you have a good relationship.
No, that's how it works.
What you need is a psychopomp to direct you through your dream kingdom.
A dream palace.
And I know a good one.
Anyway.
Well, I'm about there with this discussion of Colossus of New York and other ancient
movies.
Nobody's ever seen.
Although there's an interesting article about that very movie in the latest Scary Monsters.
Well, there you are.
You see, the Colossus of New York is not forgotten.
Not by old, doddering, senile men wallowing in nostalgia for old, stupid, low-budget,
black and white.
Well, it's all shows on old movie channels, and I'm sure more people are seeing it now
than saw it when it ran, when it was out.
In our overpopulated world, more people are familiar with the Colossus of New York than
ever.
Well, a hell of a lot more people will see that stupid old movie than will ever read
Neal Stephenson's brilliant novel, because it's a book.
I haven't read a book since I was in high school.
I'm proud of myself.
Well, when I worked on that.
I was in the conspiracy zone TV show.
Some of the writers in the bullpen boasted that they'd never opened a book.
Right.
We work in the new media.
You don't have to know how to read or any of that stuff.
It's new media.
You don't understand.
You're too old.
You're not in the matrix.
You're old school, city person.
My daughter didn't like camping out.
And one day, when she was about 10 or so, she said, you don't understand, Dad.
I'm not just a city person.
I'm not just a city girl.
I'm a TV girl.
And by the same token, now my grandsons have said, you don't understand, Mom.
We're not TV boys.
We're internet boys.
Mm-hmm.
They really are in the matrix.
And I am Mr. Smith.
Oh, no.
You just can't stand the smell.
Preciting over how many generations.
Agent Smith.
That's me.
I'm here to stop whoever Neo is.
AKA.
Because I think the internet sucks.
Elrond.
It was great for a long time there.
But now it sucks.
It sucks.
I suppose the hidden underground black internet, the dark internet, where nobody can talk to
each other at all, it's just child pornography and drugs.
That's probably fun.
And then there's that part that's like Hammer Film.
For someone.
Yeah.
Well, no, you can get every old monster movie there, too.
I mean, everything that's every.
But that's all out there anyway.
Right.
If you know enough to search.
So who needs dark?
Why did I haul all those videotapes all the way to Texas?
Oh, that's right.
I didn't.
I threw them away.
Yes, you did.
You threw your monster tapes away.
To the tune of like 12 bags of.
12 bags of hand labeled VHS tapes.
Oh, that's terrible.
Not the store bought ones.
The hand labeled ones.
Partly because I don't know what else is on there besides those three monster movies recorded
in long play speed that won't play on anything now.
And believe me.
I looked into recycling VHS tapes, but by the nature of them, nobody can recycle them.
There's one company that you can pay to recycle them because they have to be screwed apart
individually.
The tapes, one type of thing, the plastics, another, and there's little metal rollers.
It's just it's a nightmare.
In fact, there's not much recycling going on in this country because the Chinese got
their own.
Now they got all the cardboard they need.
They don't need ours anymore.
They were the ones who were buying it.
Yeah.
So, see, that's just going to that's the end of the world.
And now.
Cardboard packaging.
They say that.
And plastic bottles.
American recycling is too dirty.
It used to be that you could have 1% filth on them.
And now it's like lower, even lower tolerance than that.
In England, they have sophisticated robots that separate the trash so efficiently that
they've achieved 90% recycling at their own.
Wow.
That's impressive.
Only 10% of it doesn't get recycled.
And Germany is that way too.
Wow.
But.
Well, Germany, that doesn't surprise me.
But they're socialists.
In Germany, they go in their woods and clean up the twigs.
They clean up the twigs.
Yes, Germans.
Are you sure you're not thinking of Finland?
I'm not sure.
But they're the twig pickers.
Well, Trump said that we should be like them and rake the forest.
Right.
Yeah.
They somehow got the idea that they rake the forest and it gets rid of all pollution.
Well, he has some.
I can't keep up with the stupidity.
No, you can't.
That's the whole.
That's why it works.
That's why.
The very fact that it's nonsense is why it appeals to so many people.
It's not really scientific.
It's not really saying anything.
It's just all righteous indignation.
The new drug of America.
You're either you're righteously indignant about those libtards or you're righteously
indignant about those stupid conservatives, fascists.
I got to admit, I'm personally more afraid of the fascists on the conservative side than
getting my wrist slapped by the PC police.
Here in the chamber.
Here in the church of the subgenius friends, we're the mind your own business police.
We will not step in and interfere with your life as long as you mind your own business.
When you stop mind your own business, oh yes, then jack booted subgeniuses from the subgenius
league of ass kickers show up at your door and say, get in line and quit being in line
or whatever it is.
What Bob said.
You have to sell a lot more pamphlets to pay those guys.
Those are professionals.
Those jack booted subgenius morality squad.
If everybody's running off a cliff, would you do it too?
I told them to run off the cliff.
Actually they asked me, what was that?
I'd climb down to the bottom and check and see if there's any money left in their wallets.
I don't know.
I didn't have a lot.
Well, yeah, of course you do that first, but we hit.
Well if everybody jumped off, there'd be a lot of wallets there.
Paul Mavridis told me that his dad's, you know, was upset with his long hair or something
like that.
And he goes, if everybody jumped off a cliff, would you do it too?
And he goes, dad, I'm the one that suggested they jump off a cliff.
I don't know if that's true or if he just tells that.
but it should be true.
Oh, it's the sort of thing he would say, I'm sure.
It is.
Yeah, Bob's the one who invented jumping off a cliff.
Well, I thought it was invented by Walt Disney
in the supposed true-to-life motion picture
White Wilderness.
They didn't really...
This documentary, which I was shown as a child,
the lemmings are shown to gather together
to run and leap off a cliff into the ocean to their deaths.
But this is all bogus and was staged by the Disneys.
Nonetheless, many, many, many people saw it
and it affected their minds
and became a metaphor for unnecessary mob death.
The images of the lemmings hurtling off the cliff,
which you see in the movie.
Walt Disney's White Wilderness.
Well, but you said that the lemmings don't actually do that.
The camera crew drove these little rodent things
off of the cliff for the movie.
Right, just so.
Yes, that's the way it was done.
Unbelievable.
Yeah, this makes a better story.
Yes, well, you know, the Walt Disney movie
The Living Desert was going to show you
the mating dance of the...
scorpions.
And so the scorpions are there.
One scorpion grabs the next scorpion by its forceps
and then they pixelate it playing square dance music
while the scorpions move around.
So you see they are indeed dancing,
but doing a contrived buck and wing.
It's like the dancing squirrel on the internet.
It's all a bunch of hooey.
Or the supposed fancy cat and owner
in the Cat Channel commercial.
Where they take steps together
simply caused by running the film back and forth.
Dr. Drummond, get up here and be loud.
Dr. Howell's putting me to sleep.
He's muttering about old commercials
and monster movies again.
I don't believe I told you about
when I encountered a rattlesnake
of incredible dimension.
You told that one last night
on the other show.
All right.
He'll just start muttering about comic books.
Yes.
Dr. Drummond?
Yeah.
Well, he's certainly welcome to.
And really bad TV shows.
Hey, let's talk about every episode
of the old Daniel Boone show.
What about the old Casey Jones show?
I didn't mean that.
That was being facetious.
We don't...
You know, if you can imagine...
No, Sky King.
Sky King.
Alan Hale Jr. played the role
of the famous locomotive engineer.
The little rascals.
The skipper from Gilligan's Island.
Dr. Kildare.
Operated a steam locomotive
and...
On board were the Stoker or Fireman,
Red Rock,
and this kid,
this overprivileged kid
who got to go around in the cab
of a steam locomotive,
Casey Jr.
It was brought to you by...
Those cartoons can be watched
instead of hearing somebody describe them
down at the grindhouse.
It's live action.
Starting about six.
Oh, it's seven now.
It's a live action presentation.
Oh, is that what they call it?
I don't know what they call it now.
Scraping off your shoes.
Or the Vikings.
I know what that means.
Well, I don't,
but I'm sure it's something bad.
Boisterous sea adventurers,
the Vikings,
in their half-hour show.
Are you still doing synopses of old...
They're looting and pillaging,
torturing religious clerics
and staking them down on the beach
where little crabs will slowly eat them
and this robust...
Are you going to spend eternity
on your pleasure?
Saucer reciting synopses
of every old show, movie, song, poem, comic...
I was trying to make a point here
about the thing that was being represented,
but that's okay.
Perhaps all things in time
So did you guys miss my music?
Yes, we're waiting for your music
to reoccur.
We all enjoy such music.
When we were born
Into this life
We were less than
7 to make it right
It's pretty turning
And this is our fate
We're singing this song
So you can relate
We are going to save the universe
This time
We are full grown
We are grown up men
We are all pastors
We hate to reason it
It is our mission
It is our task
It's obvious
Yet useless
We are going to save the universe
It's time
This is crecid
In this online Tapdak
We are born
We are grown
We are here
here
now
green
guitar solo
Don't you worry
Don't have no fears
Don't get outside
Because we are here
We can't help
Don't we understand
We're in control
And we are more than a band
We are going to save the universe
The time
Well, maybe next time.
So,
did you guys miss my music?
Yes, we're waiting for your
music to reoccur.
We all enjoy such music.
I'm getting tired of sitting up here.
Heard melodies are sweet.
Yeah, I've already been home and taken a nap
and had dinner and drank coffee
and all kinds of stuff.
I came back.
You guys are still here.
Well, we took a break.
We took a sandwich break
and you took a coffee break
and a nap.
Yeah,
and he probably took most of the froth.
And the money
and the girls
and the map
and all the lighters
and the compass
and the gun
and the diamonds.
I bet he got the diamonds too.
And the gold
and jewels
and diamonds and things.
The diamonds.
Yeah.
The lost treasure
of the superstition moment.
You know, I shouldn't have put on
that exotic lounge music.
That's what
that's what below.
For some reason,
they doctors,
the discoverers were walled in,
sealed in with their treasure
and their bodies have never been discovered
in the superstition mountains.
Remember the story of the lost Dutchman?
Mine?
The mysterious old.
What are you doing?
Dr. Howie?
Just because he's just endlessly reciting one plot after another.
This is no plot.
This is a matter of American history.
Yes, no one understands what the mystery is.
There's a good reason for that.
It's bu-
.
Oh, this'll save us.
Porn music.
Music from 70s porno movies.
Well, that would-
It's pretty swinging.
Describe how the special mummy,
that was found,
was eviscerated.
.
Philo is now playing his armpit.
He's doing it.
So that's all right.
That's the,
Philo's doing the armpit and cupped palm instrument.
Oops.
Yes, with the synthesizer, neo-thermine.
That's not a synthesizer.
It's his pyroflatulation skill.
The overman can make a,
sound like a theremin from his,
ah, ah, ah, fundament.
Right, so located near the physical location of the human soul.
.
Here's the porno music.
The frenulum.
And, ah, yeah, the, ah, ah, ah,
a lot of the wah-wah pedal is used during these sequences.
.
That's the music that goes with the,
well, I guess just the copulation scenes.
Right.
It kind of goes with any of them.
Blowjobs, copulation,
.
Any other basic, ah, human.
This is crappy.
This is, this is crap.
Listen to that.
Yeah.
.
Here's the blue chair without the wah-wah pedal.
Now, here's the blue chair with the wah-wah pedal.
.
This one's a little funkier.
There's one that's a complete realist. . .
.
This one's a clip off of, ah, White Rabbit.
I mean, it really is.
.
How did you acquire these tracks?
I used this stuff with my micro photography of, ah, copulating microbes.
.
I had to ask.
This is pretty loud.
.
Uh, uh , uh-huh .
Uh. .
.
Just use your imagination, folks.
Philos in the house.
.
Right.
Uh. .
This is, ah,
.
which has cheap 70s porno music mixed with overmanned doctor synthesizer warblings.
This level of imagery is not accepted by the American Pediatric Association or the Federal Communications Commission.
Music to unzip your pants slowly by.
Really, Ivan?
Uh-huh.
If you're Zap Brannigan.
You have to watch out.
I really am actually getting kind of tired.
Zap Brannigan can creep in.
I feel like somebody else needs to come up and take over this mic.
Locking bar can sound like Zap Brannigan.
Is Mike here?
If only Mike...
Step up to the mic.
Is Mike Hunt here?
Yeah.
Is there a Mr. Hunt here?
Mike Hunt.
Well, I think he took too many mics.
If you...
Is Mike Hunt here?
He's lying down in the broom glass.
Is there an alcoholic here?
Oh, alcoholic.
Why did you come over to my joint and tell me that?
Why, you no-good dirty motherfucker.
I'll cut your belly open and show you the black stuff.
And so it ends this way.
The subgenius broadcast begun in harmony ends in name-calling and acrimony.
You yellow-red bastard.
Why don't you come on over to my joint?
Gentlemen, please, please.
What are you, some kind of a joker?
Come on over.
Get out of here.
I'll show you my big red beef heart.
And, uh, Philo?
I got...
I used to play examples of classic prank calls on Hour of Slacking.
Yeah.
After a while, I started feeling bad about it because it's a...
There's a victim.
There's a victim in prank calls.
And it's...
But the victim's an asshole.
I mean, it's...
They're funny as hell.
And, uh, but...
But it's...
It's not the kind of thing you should exploit for showbiz.
I don't think.
It should be kept to collectors and sociological researchers.
It is a sociological experiment.
That's really...
Well, the technology changes, too.
You can't really...
Right.
Now it's easy.
...prank phone call anymore.
Yeah.
You get caught.
Yes.
But, uh...
Another thing I used to do was play tapes of the mentally ill people that would leave
messages on our answer phone.
And they still do.
They sure as hell do.
All you need to do is collect those tapes and not purge them.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
You don't...
You have no idea how...
How they must be purged.
There's a guy out there that fills up my answer...
My answer...
...thing on AT&T about every four days who'll have a fit where he calls all day and all night
and leaves four-minute messages, the same basic messages over and over and over, trying
to get it just exactly right because he's on the spectrum or something or he's on crack.
Does that mean he sees in seven colors?
Let's see if he's...
He's on the spectrum?
Wait, wait.
That won't work.
I don't...
You're trying to...
You call him now?
No.
I just have to look at my voicemail and see how...
Why don't you ever call him back and just hassle him, you know?
Just call him back and then when he answers, hang up.
No, he's been quiet.
That would hardly serve.
Plus, there's no...
I don't have...
Well, I do have one bar of AT&T.
I guess things are a little better out there.
Oh, well, that's not so bad.
Maybe I could check out...
One bar of jail.
...the email situation.
That's what it is.
Yeah, I want to see if I could be in communication with that.
It's a crappy bar.
I don't have...
Where's the drinks?
No, take it easy.
I've been staying...
At least they have the free lunch there.
Where are the drinks?
I wonder if there's any drinks in my car.
I grew up with people always telling me
What a sinful kid I was
My parents didn't even seem to like me
Cause they didn't believe
That I couldn't believe
I just couldn't believe
How sinful we could be
Supposedly be
I just wanted to believe
Whatever was real
What our bodies made us feel
And the billions of dollars
And the billion billion shapes of energy
All the billion billion shapes of energy
Inside of me
And above me
Spreading out
I keep trying to find
My iniquities
Nothing like that seems to live
Inside of me
There are only
The shapes of energy
That's all that's real
Inside of me
There are only
The billion shapes of energy
It opens up like a beacon
It cuts tears
Inside of me
It's spreading out
Spreading out
Macrocosmically
And it's very particular
Microscopically
All the billion billion shapes of energy
And the priest and preacher
They tell us
We're all iniquity
No individuality
They got us
They got us fighting their
Imaginary enemy
Well it's their iniquity
Not mine
And it's their
Imaginary enemy
It's in their mind
It's not mine
I'm only interested in
Keepin' time
With the shapes of energy
Rising up inside of me
And spreading out like a peacock's tail
To infinity
I grew up with people
Telling me
I grew up with all these people
Trying to tell me
About their enemy
But I'm all about
Energy
Not
Un refuge
Tvens
wood
A
after
etzen
ave
From PR News in Washington, I'm being detained on fabricated charges and should be released.
Russia's foreign minister tells PR Bob reports Trump has jumped to north of the Merced River.
From south of the river to the north of the river is Bob's out of control.
The BBB BBC reports Sweden is north of 90 degrees.
President Trump tweets young people are marching in demonstrations around the world this weekend to highlight illegal PR.
They're calling it the PR News movement in Washington.
The PR News is a production of the U.S. Department of State.
Get some shoes on those feet
For Cracky
There's glass up and down the street
Cracky
No thank you
Don't need no tires for my car
And I don't wanna know
Where you got them from
Or what you're drinking
From that mason jar
guitar solo
No one will come over
To drink your vodka
Don't look at my girlfriend
And don't give her
Any more flowers
Just give me my phone back
You've made your last call
For the night
Cracky
You're down on your luck
I'm no Cracky
I won't lend you fifteen bucks
Cracky
Why not go on Springer
I'm sure they'd let you on
Because they love a train wreck
Like you've explained it
Where you've been to your mom
Cracky
Why you holding your chest
Oh
Cracky
Hey
Oh my
So the plastic is taken in
And given out again
Yeah but it's got cocaine and Valium in it too
Cocaine and Valium
Cocaine
Photon
Polyana
Cocaine
Thank you.