I just want to say I love what you crazy wonderful beautiful kids are doing
when those women in those tube tops run down the aisle it's just crazy crazy crazy crazy
crazy yes but not insane once again friends this hour of slack number 1349 is a compilation of
best of show bits from three of the best shows ask dr howell on radio valencia.fm puzzling
evidence on kpfa berkeley and radio synesthesia from wcsb cleveland but there will also be some
rare devo covering nine inch nails and a new
version of the band that they're not speaking the same covering their own song bohondas
man but first a true report phoned in to puzzling evidence by reverend shining path of least
resistance normally of china and japan but this time fresh from a tour of yes north korea
north korea coming in over yeah we can hear you sven
yeah yeah fumbling around in the semantic darkness yeah the briefing may begin now i
will only stick to
podcast
all right
we got your signal five by five from
where are you north korea still
briefing here with my uh case officer
is that a shining path of least resistance it is indeed good lord man he was thought to be
extinct 80 billion years ago i've been staying speaking from the mars system
um yes
i i i i
we'd love to your report and video uh the the report was uh really really nerve-wracking
and informative scary because of those security police man yeah well it was not it was my
only my guide she asked me later uh what was that paper you were holding up and i said
it was an envelope yeah you know what did you do with the envelope it wasn't an envelope
it was a dobbs head yeah what did you do a dog by the way you know ivan staying did the
same thing in china in his days
in china in his day
yeah and three years to the day later there was a massacre in the same place yeah the
world famous
thing the norwegian raising the norwegian flag at the south pole yeah so how long how's
How did you get that?
What else?
Tell us more about that wonderful country.
Please ask specific questions.
Well, tell us why.
Did Un have plastic surgery?
Look like his grandfather, like they're saying?
No, no.
Un really looks like that.
In fact, that's why Kim Jong-il passed over son number one and son number two.
Son number one had been to the Swiss high school and wanted reform,
and Kim Jong-il decided that son number two looked too effeminate.
So son number three won and said he would go for it.
Yeah, because he's posing a lot like Granddad.
Looks like Granddad.
There are no pictures of the new guy up yet.
They're still working on his death angle and et cetera, et cetera.
The perfect ill head.
The Kim cult is a faith-based religion just like us.
Cool.
Yeah, I was thinking it's face-based.
Face-based.
It is a face-based religion.
Sherman now has a similar thing going.
They have the beatific face.
Where do you stay in this country?
We stayed at the Hotel Yanggakdo,
which is a 40-story Soviet in-tourist hotel on an island in the middle of the river.
We could walk around up to the hotel and could not go off.
Wow.
Man, that's clever.
That's good.
That's the way to do it.
We should do that the next day, yeah.
So did you feel like your liberty was being repressed while you were there?
Yes, we had our minders watching us at all times.
They were nice lady minders, mind you.
Did they have minders minding the minders?
Unfortunately, I had my wife minding me.
I would have been minding my minder a little more closely if you catch my drift.
I know exactly what you mean.
You're drifted a long time for a long ways.
My guide was a Miss Kim, a 33-year-old North Korean MILF.
Well, you know, part of that is the Stockholm Syndrome.
You fall in love with your captor.
Your captor, yes.
That happened to me in China.
It happens to me.
Big accident.
Call back.
Jay has McBobcat.
I fell in love with my captor.
Okay, we temporarily lost our...
It's possible that Princess We might try to call in.
Then we'd have a representative from China.
One from...
The planet of the UFOs.
The unidentified ones.
Hello, doctors.
Hello.
No, no.
Oh, no.
All right.
We're trying to lock in on your signal there, Shining Path.
Thank you, Beth.
We have lost much space.
Next question.
How long were you there?
Four days.
Do you have to scream like that?
Yes.
He's been brainwashed.
Man, he can't help it.
You talk with this forceful...
Almost like...
It's too late.
There's no brain left.
They get it right away.
Did you eat any strange and disgusting food?
Like maggots?
Actually, I gained weight in North Korea.
Did you eat the giant maggots?
They have giant maggots there that they eat.
That's obscene.
And all you got was that lousy T-shirt.
Oh, there's Phineas and Margaret.
Is that Phineas?
There's Phineas on there, too.
Not Jane.
No, that's not.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Jane, you're just...
I...
Is it Jane you're doing, Phineas?
Yeah, probably.
No, it's Jane you're doing.
Jane you're doing.
Notice how they just ignore the guy from North Korea and go to Jane.
Jane you're talking.
Oh, no.
No, I actually have a Jane you're like conundrum because I don't like what I'm doing anymore.
Next question.
I don't know what else to do.
How much money does it cost to go to North Korea?
For Chinese citizens, $300.
For Hong Kong citizens, $700.
For Americans, $1,400.
Yeah.
You really have to have the yen to do that.
I've got a question for you.
Who shot Liberty Valance?
Lee Harvey Oswald acting alone.
Which Lee Harvey Oswald acting alone?
That's the big question.
The replica.
The replica Lee Harvey Oswald.
Which replica?
The replica.
The fake replica.
The good copy or the bad copy?
Because there was one where you could see the seams along the sides.
The never been scanned copy.
How do you get to North Korea?
You fly to a Chinese border town which is sort of like El Paso to North Korea's Juarez.
Oh, man.
That must be great.
I was recently in El Paso and was scared to go to Juarez.
Yeah.
Do they wear guns there and cowboy hats?
Not at the border town.
But I was taking the local train from the Chinese border to Pyongyang which is forbidden
to Americans and it was quite heavy on the rail platforms.
Squatties with AKs frisking everyone.
Desperate peasants.
It looked like Japan in 1944.
Wow.
Cool.
But they don't know what pot is so it's cool to carry a film camera.
They don't know who Michael Jackson is.
They don't know who Snooki is.
They don't know who Mitt Romney is.
They don't know who Snooki is?
But now they know who Bush is.
They don't know who Bob Dobbs is.
J.R. Bob Dobbs.
They will praise Bob.
Yeah, and the secret police are going to be combing YouTube looking for that tape and
then that guy won't do it.
I threw one copy of Arise onto the railroad track.
Yeah.
That's what we need.
Well, at least a copy of Arise didn't throw itself on the railroad track, which is what
usually happens.
And instantly 300 countrymen came out.
Next.
And they killed themselves because they let that happen.
Then they jump on the tracks to protect a copy of Arise.
So how many more minutes do you have on your phone call right now?
Oh, no, no.
We're on Skype this time.
We're fine.
Forever and ever.
Did they take you to the military airfield again this time?
We passed by the North Korean airport, Sunan Airport.
I saw a few Tupolevs and Ilyushins.
I'm not typing this out.
Okay.
No, I am writing it down, though.
Did you meet them?
I'm using my fart pen to write it down.
Well, Honda has not been seen in North Korea since 1961.
Is the television or the television shows in North Korea as good as the ones in Beijing
in 1986?
There's only one channel in North Korea.
It shows Grandfather and Father's Greatest Hits.
It has the news.
And then it shows North Korean karaoke.
They're very patriotic music.
Yeah.
And Schmaltzy, Pony, and then there's a war movie.
So they don't have a Playboy channel over there, for instance.
No, they don't.
I went to the North Korean side of the DMZ.
You went where?
To the North Korean side of the DMZ.
Nice.
Where they killed those poor Americans after they relieved them and they were watching
Well, they showed us where the armistice was signed and the...
Oh, man.
The North Korean soldiers...
The North Korean soldiers got in my face and said, what?
We started the war?
Yeah.
Tell that to me.
Say that to my face.
And you didn't have to say anything.
He didn't know that, right?
Yeah.
Right.
They did.
Nice.
So did you reteach them their entire history now?
I usually don't.
Sorry.
Go ahead.
Did you reteach them their history?
I tried to engage them in friendly debate.
Aha.
My interpreter smiled and chided the soldiers.
Well, think of that.
Every single Euro that comes out here, they...
Has to feel like he has to engage them in friendly debate.
Oh, man.
When I was in China at the Friendship Hotel, there were people from many climes.
And this young sort of Arabic-looking fellow sat across from me at the bar.
He was not drinking beer like I was.
And we had a little discussion.
I said, where are you from?
And he goes...
Suddenly, his face got real flat.
He said, Libya.
About a month earlier, Reagan's guys had bombed Tripoli.
Yes, yes.
Yeah.
And hit a hospital, ostensibly.
So, you know, he suddenly...
Suddenly, I was the guilty party.
I had dropped the bomb on Tripoli.
Yeah, you mean Ivan Stang?
Yeah, you did that, man.
I asked him...
I could have...
If only I'd known that a few years later, I would literally be launching a football-shaped
Qaddafi head from a pulpit at X Day.
Two years in a row.
It's funny how they always put their criminals and the ones they're seeking always seem
to hide out in hospitals and schools.
Just remembering, Reverend Stang...
Yes, Reverend...
They took us to the Palace of...
They took us to the Palace of Gifts.
There was the entire Palace of Gifts to President Trump.
There was the Palace of Gifts to President Kim Il-sung and a second palace to President
Kim Jong-il of gifts only from foreign leaders and delegations.
And it was there I saw the gold scimitar given by Muammar Qaddafi to Kim Jong-il, as well
as the hiking rifle from President Putin, a pearl inlaid desk from Hafez al-Assad of
Syria, and, yes, I saw the holy Michael Jordan autographed basketball that Madeleine Albright
of our country gave Kim Jong-il.
Oh, my God.
Man, what a rich dude.
Okay, well, I get dibs on that Palace of Gifts for X Day.
How do you...
I get dibs on it.
I got new dibs on it.
I said it first.
Okay, well, you said it.
I don't care.
But think about this.
You got...
I'm thinking.
You got a golden scimitar in one hand or a basketball signed by Michael Jackson...
Michael Jordan.
Was it Michael Jackson or Michael Jordan that signed it?
It was Michael Jaskin.
Michael Jaskin played basketball.
No, but...
But he signed a basketball, probably.
I'll bet you he signed a basketball at some point in time.
That basketball's gonna be worth a lot of money someday with Michael Jackson's signature.
Yeah, but maybe the gold scimitar without Michael Jackson...
The gold scimitar would be worth a lot of money.
...with Julian Crested.
I want the signed copy of Gaddafi's little green book.
I'd just like to find out...
I have a better North Korea, Reverend Stang.
You have what?
I have a better book.
I bought Kim Jong-il's book on football.
I have a better book on the American film series.
Wow!
Right.
Man, we can revolutionize Hollywood with that.
I want to sell it in an American edition called Socialist Filmmaking for Dummies.
Cool.
Man.
Well, there must have been thousands of subjects that he wrote on in his spare time,
though.
Oh, you guys will get it.
I'll scan it and send it to you.
Trust me.
Didn't he, like, kidnap film directors and make them make movies for him and stuff?
Yeah.
I don't think they were any North Korea.
That's right.
No, that was the dad, right?
He probably didn't kidnap them.
That was pretty cool.
He just persuaded them.
I thought, that's how Hollywood should be.
His advanced rhetorical technique.
He made them an offer they could not refuse.
Right.
He used his advanced techniques in persuasion.
You mean like, oh, I see, like kidnapping them.
Yeah.
We know where your children go to school.
Yeah, now let's make the movie.
Yeah, now let's make a movie.
Okay.
Reverend Stang, you know who really liked my account of North Korea was all the burners.
I had a separate email to the burners and they all love it.
Oh, I have a question for you.
All of them?
Did you talk to Un about him sending the torpedo into the...
All of them love it?
Into that South Korean frigate?
He still hangs out with the rich burners.
Ah, rich burners.
By the way, I'll...
The North Koreans had lost the three previous rounds of ship-to-ship battle in that zone.
So, when things went bad with the South Korean president, the Navy tapped Kim Jong Il on the
shoulder and said, hi, you promised.
Yeah.
You promised to get paid.
So, the North Koreans are still down three to one.
They lost three of their ships to the South Korean one.
That was just a payback.
Man, that's a lot of space in these.
You stole my battleship.
Yeah.
Or as Eddie Izzard said, Hitler never played to risk, huh?
Oh, yes.
Oh.
Hey, your fighter jet fell into my battleship.
Yeah.
Your battleship crashed into my fighter jet.
Okay, here's another question.
Hey, they taste good together.
How many North Koreans are coming to Ex Day?
There they are now.
They're lining up.
Everyone will be at Ex Day.
We represent the North Korean agency.
No one has a choice, Lister.
When Ex Day comes, it comes to them.
It comes to everyone.
Hello, we represent the North Korean agency.
Here's the story.
Half the North Koreans who defected out of North Korea can't handle the rest of the
world and have to go back.
Okay.
I'm not surprised.
That...
You know, it's real hard for Native Americans.
Yeah.
Unless...
Otherwise, at that moment in time, it's an assigning
or subadaskling of lessons or exercises.
It's a capital issue for Native Americans, man, way overread, and they'reometry digo
forward.
There's history of...
Yeah, automated information.
live, long live, long live.
Ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay.
At ease, at ease, man.
Gentlemen, thank you.
Yes.
Aloha.
I'll see you.
I'll see you someday. We are
ready to welcome you again.
Okay.
I'm in the airport now.
I'm ready to come back.
All right. Thank you. I'm signing off.
Thank you for calling. Bye.
No problem. No problem.
No lie, GI. No lie.
No. I love you no show.
No.
That's my dream. I love you no show.
I love you no show.
Yeah, if you're in North Korea, the government
totally sucks.
Ben Franklin was a rebel indeed.
He liked to be a rebel.
He liked to get naked while they smoked on the scene.
He was the kingiest.
But if he was here today,
the government would buttercup his right to your day.
Now, let me tell you something
about the government.
What?
Blowing up the environment.
Hey, is that right?
Taking all the freaking beautiful animals, yeah?
And making them freaking extinct.
Oh, no.
The government totally sucks, you mother trucker.
The government totally sucks.
In North Korea.
Because the land of love and freedom
is just a baby's breath away.
And if we hold hands together,
we can bring back the USA.
The USA.
Thank you.
Bring back the USA.
Not the NPRK.
No, the USA.
The USA.
We're on KPFA.
No, we don't vote for you.
KPFA and Berkeley in 98.
No, we don't.
We ain't.
Bring back the KFUS.
Oh, yeah.
KFUS, KC, KF, KF.
And remember, the government totally sucks.
Wherever you are.
Was that the D?
Yeah.
The government totally sucks.
I've never heard that song by the D.
I thought it was Conspiracy Rock.
Oh, that was a great band.
Conspiracy Rock.
Yeah, they got that.
I want to know more of Rock.
Oh, yeah.
Then there's Turok.
We were talking about Turok.
Turok, yeah.
Turok, Son of Stone.
Then there's Turok.
Deadly Specimens.
That's my new goth band, Deadly Specimens.
Oh, I bet there's 20 D.
You better Google that one
and see if there's somebody
that doesn't already have that name.
Oh, yeah.
I looked up.
I was trying to contact Sister Decadence.
For some reason, I Googled Sister Decadence
and discovered that there were something like
a hundred different bands out there named Decadence.
Yeah, it's like Cork K-Rob.
You know, one day I went and looked for K-Rob
and there were a hundred K-Robs.
Fifty of them in each city in America.
Well, you get on Facebook and there's so many Bob Dobbs
that your finger gets tired scrolling down.
I'm tired of scrolling.
So stupid.
You know, there's thousands and thousands of them.
Every now and then, one of them shows a different guy
and it's probably someone whose name is Robert Dobbs.
James Robert Dobbs or something.
So here we are on the show.
I feel sorry for those guys.
And you can call 8-5-0-4-0
from the 5-10 area code to find us.
You're listening to the Positive Evidence Show.
Or, as heard on Hour of Slack,
cause deepness.
Missed.
No, I'm just jumping.
What?
So you can leave that part in
because the angels were carrying him while he said that.
I hate to put your number out on my show
because it doesn't make any sense.
When some poor guy here is going to get a call.
Once a month.
What?
At midnight.
The calls from Cleveland are coming.
They are.
They're rolling in.
Rolling, rolling, rolling.
Trolling, trolling, trolling.
Keep trolling, trolling, trolling.
Trolling.
Keep those little scrolls.
Trolling, trolling, trolling.
Yep, the heat's gone back up,
but the calls don't sound bad now,
so maybe that's not related.
Before the internet, Dr. German,
remember how we used to troll people on CB radio?
We had the urge to troll.
But then we didn't have the means of the internet.
You could only troll within about a 19-mile radius.
You know, that proves that trolling is genetic to the human.
All humans need to troll.
Well, also,
geniuses need to troll.
Well, okay, that's true.
I thought he said he was a subgenius, but.
I wouldn't say all subgenius.
Okay.
Did you say a subgenius, but?
She said that we're trolls.
The government totally sucks.
Trolls under the bridge.
I said on the one we were singing it that I thought he said he's a subgenius, but.
But he says he's a genius, but.
It's an album put out without the bad words, you see.
Oh.
It's the actual CD of the Pick of Destiny.
My copy of the Pick of Destiny was simply copied.
From a movie.
Copy.
Oh, that's.
That worked.
And this song, I don't remember that song being on.
In the movie.
Man, I haven't seen the movie in so long.
The government totally sucks.
Yeah, that wasn't in the movie.
That's in North Korea, not here.
Right.
Yeah.
No, I didn't say that.
I didn't say that.
I didn't say anything.
Mr. Gingrich will be seeing you when you get home from the show.
Here is police escort.
Pulls up in front of your eyes.
The alien has.
Governor Rhodes will get me.
Counting.
How old is he?
He's the one.
He sends the National Guard to shoot the students at Kent State.
He did, though.
And they named the radio station after him.
WCSB used to be located in Rhodes Tower, named after Governor Rhodes, who told the National
Guard, you better do something about them hippies.
That still hurts.
People up there get big heartache every.
What if you were dead on the ground?
Yeah.
What if you were?
I know people who did see her dead on the ground.
Well, there you go.
One of them formed a band called the Devo.
That's right.
Yeah.
You want to be.
Because he.
Yeah, I think about that all the time.
It's just.
I can't get it out of my mind.
You know, the sense of seeing that and then going and starting Devo, because that's.
That's the only place you can go with that energy.
They did it too.
Just shout it out.
Take a look at that.
Twitter.
I'll do anything for you
Just tell me what you want me to do
Money!
He'll be up against the wall
Throw on everything he wants it on
No!
You can't take it
You can't get that away from me
No!
You can't take it
You can't get that away from me
Hand like a hoe
Black as your soul
I'd rather die
Than die
Than give you control
Hand like a hoe
Black as your soul
I'd rather die
Than give you control
Whoa, no!
Before the one you serve
You're going to get what you deserve
Whoa, no!
Before the one you serve
You're going to get what you deserve
I'm not looking for the cure
Not concerned about the sick among the pure
Let's go dancing on the backs of the bruised
Not the one to choose
You can't take it
No!
You can't take that away from me
You can't take it
No!
You can't take that away from me
Hey!
Let the Ben Sam tell you
My damn playing's not bad
Here came what I got
Hey!
Let the Ben Sam tell you
My damn playing's not bad
Here came what I got
It damn must've gone...
Bow down
Before the one you serve
You're going to get what you deserve
Bow down
Before the one you serve
You're going to get what you deserve
Head like a hole
Black is your soul
I'm at the die
To give you control
Head like a hole
Black is your soul
I'm at the die
To give you control
Head like a hole
Black is your soul
I'm at the die
To give you control
Head like a hole
Black is your soul
I'm at the die
To give you control
Bow down
Before the one you serve
You're going to get what you deserve
Bowdown
Before the one you serve
You're going to get what you deserve
Bowdown
Before the one you serve
You're going to get what you deserve
Bowdown
Before the one you serve
You're going to get what you deserve
Okay, I have a question about the black cat.
Black cats in general?
Mm-hmm.
Okay, now, I've always heard that if they cross one way in front of you, it's good luck.
Is it true, or is it either way they cross in front of you is bad luck?
Are you talking about...
And if there is a good luck way for them to cross in front of you, which way is it?
Left to right or right to left?
If a black cat walks backwards from left to right in front of you, it reverses the previous...
Right?
It's a balancing...
Yeah, the last time one walked in front of you from left to right, forward, that produced a lot of bad luck.
So if they walk backwards in the opposite direction, then that can negate that previous...
Oh, so you've got to track the little bastard down. It's like a rabies thing.
You've got to get him to walk backwards.
It's a transaction reversal.
Now, can you drag him?
Can you drag him, like, by the tail?
Oh, well, you can do whatever it takes.
You can do whatever...
What? What's that so hard?
See, what you say on the radio happens in real life.
I guess so. It's happening in the studio.
Right now, even as we speak, there's a cat back there that's trying not... trying to get away.
That sounds a little like the X-Cottas, actually.
But what happens...
Yeah, it's a cat.
Maybe you're right about that.
You've got to go with it, man. It's radio.
It's only in your mind.
You just say it, and then it happens.
Now, which would you rather do?
Do what you're doing right now or sit through a session of Congress?
I do want to go right now. Session of Congress.
I mean, come on.
You want to fucking eat your own hat after that.
Yeah, you want to eat your own hat.
Right, right, right.
I don't know.
Did you see that?
That just went straight...
So whatever I say on the radio will happen in real life.
Yeah, it's done.
That's what happened.
That's what just happened.
Except if you were in Congress right now.
Oh, I was going to say that there will be plenty of...
Like, watch this.
I think Ivan Stang's here.
There will be plenty of tickets for anybody who wants to...
No, that didn't work at all.
Let me try again.
I think Ivan Stang's here.
See?
I said it on the radio and it happened.
How about that?
Never mind, you guys.
They don't even know who you're referring to out here.
Indeed, we have again the mighty Ivan Stang joins us in here in the studio.
We're there.
Get a second job.
A lot of chaos.
Get him.
What do you think of the ticket debacle?
Oh, no, there he is.
Strumming her u-yolo in the background there.
The debacle?
Hello, you're on the air.
Oh.
That's what I...
Hello, this is Philo Drummond.
I'm a religious cult leader with the church of the subgenius.
Philo Drummond.
Long time no see.
You're not a religious cult leader.
He wasn't lying.
He really does introduce himself that way.
You're a hypo-cripes.
Well, is that...
No, no, he's not.
He told me earlier today.
He said that's how I introduce myself.
I say, I'm Philo Drummond.
I'm a cult leader.
Yeah, I used to introduce myself as a snake oil salesman back when I was one.
Oh.
Wow.
Well, that's to each his own.
That's what I always say.
I used to introduce myself as a refugee.
A Martian refugee.
Ah.
Hey, Dave.
How's it going?
Oh, it's going very, very poorly.
You should see how it is outside.
It's dripping blood instead of rain.
There's these rather large amphibian-looking things.
I guess you'd call them like some sort of nano frog crawling around.
And now they're starting to eat each other, but you don't want to get in the way.
Yeah.
Yeah, but it's only two minutes.
And the moon is blood red as well.
Now I want to listen to Slayer because you talked about raining blood.
Ashtabula is a rough place, man.
Especially if you've only got three kneecaps.
Or if you have protrusions in your body.
They're very uncivilized.
Very, very insensitive, crude people here.
There's mean streets.
Mean streets of Ashtabula.
Now, it's actually not too far, though, from a town that was named after Carl.
Connie.
Connie ought.
Yeah.
Connie ought to do quite a few things, but it's not really our place to tell her that,
really.
Now, Puzzling Epcot lives in Oakland, which is the second main...
But he lives in Calabula, so it's not that far away.
Oakland?
It's also quite occupied, too, isn't it, right now?
Yeah, everything's occupied.
Shut down the everything.
I was just reading something.
I was just reading something about this the other day.
Someone's saying it looked like a trap, basically.
Like...
What did?
The Martian guy?
The occupation...
Oh.
The site they were trying to occupy.
Basically, like, the cops just had everything ready to go.
It's like, Lord have been, so they could beat them and gas them.
We made a special place that you guys can occupy.
We've laid these bear traps out all over.
You can come and protest here.
Who's gonna occupy the house?
These electrified bear traps.
These computerized bear traps.
Digitized, highly, highly electrified bear traps.
So it's for trapping electrified bears, like it'll catch Teddy Ruxpin, but it'll leave Smokey
alone.
Right.
Leave the Smokey alone.
What if it touches everything with its own form of iniquity?
What if...
Yeah, we'll do that.
But this is the beauty of the universe, is that everything is touching everything.
Right.
And we can cigarette the rights for $20,000.
No kidding.
I paid my...
I had a text from the sub-genius church Ohio sales tax today from California, so everything
is touching everything and picking its pockets.
Oh, how convenient.
That's the world that I wanna live in.
No, I'm no crude Luddite that wants to go around and blow up information systems just
because I smell funny.
I mean, cause I...
You're not?
I honestly, Dave, all this time, I thought you...
that was exactly your deal.
Smelling funny in one of the, well, information systems.
I think we should go back to the days of growing up.
I'm shocked.
We live in prisons of our own mind.
I saw like a dead man through the canyons of my mind.
Fleshpots, plenty of them.
What's in a Mai Tai anyway?
Never heard of them.
My mind.
Pickles, pineapples, urgent requests,
and some strange visions of another world, I think.
Think of all the amazing subgenius doctors on this show right now.
Ever saw the subgenius nurse?
All those collapsing doctors.
Collashing doctors.
And you're probably wondering, who are these half-doctors on the clamshell?
Well, we're not going to just tell you, but you call up and say,
all right, who's the half-doctors on the clamshell?
Then we'll tell you.
Then we'll tell you just how and where.
Your boat is leaking.
Okay.
Now be quiet.
Be quiet.
busy like a
jack see do a spell
Yeah.
Has my style.
So who needs help?
Yes, there are.
There's no one here.
Or Jane, or...
What is about to happen?
It's the romance.
Barnyard.
Mohandas man.
Mohandas.
echoed in high notes
Intense rumbling
head
mother, mother.
Mohandas man.
Oh, this man.
Remember every hearing of this man that that recording.
Wow.
Far out.
I like the new landing pads on the bottom of the show's show wells.
Thanks.
Yeah, you agree.
Everyone agrees these new show well landing pad struts or strut lifters are excellent.
Excellent.
You know, those are not immune to sabotage, though.
No, they're kind of delicate.
Now, I'm sure that on a certain planetoid of unnamed origin, they would be rife for
vacation.
Vandalism.
There are terrorists who use chemicals that slowly eat away at the infrastructure.
I noticed that.
Well, you know what I'd say to them?
Time bombs, basically.
You'd say Bohondas man.
They set those rust viruses loose.
What would you say?
Bohondas man.
I got away from them.
No, no, I can't say that.
We did that already.
It was a Bohondas man.
But what would you say to them?
I would say, hello, boys.
I'm back.
But it's the wrong music.
I think.
Hello, boys.
I'm back.
Whoa.
That's different that way.
She is back.
That got my attention.
That was really, well, don't, well, careful with those struts.
Don't pay.
It takes millions of dollars to replace those struts.
One thing at a time.
There are lots of paperwork.
I mean, they're good for clubbing baby seals, but other than that.
The bio lifters.
Yeah, we club the baby harp seals.
You got to be tough and you got to be man.
You can find a harp seal.
Those are for you if you want them.
Oh, my God.
Let me tell you.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Sure.
And that's the sound I like to hear.
People.
Yeah.
Sure.
It's brilliant.
Brilliant.
I have to say that once a week.
It's crowd pleasing.
From PR News in Washington, I'm sounding cautiously optimistic about security there.
Vice President Joe Biden is trying to move through a rugged canyon.
Former British Prime Minister Tony Blair says it will not be possible until Palestinians
have civil rights.
Civil rights violations in schools and colleges across the country.
Finally.
The.
And since one of those.
Res.
The.
Way.
No.
It.
For all.
The.
And in my last story, I misspoke.
I meant to say, this is PR News.
A global trade union says a whore has killed at least 12 people.
The top U.S. general in Afghanistan, Stanley McChrystal, says among the allegations are
denial of Jewish college preparatory programs.
Massive rock slides in western Colorado face big career obstacles.
Stuckels NPR News from Washington.
I'm wondering now, did Shining Path send his video out from North Korea?
Or did he smuggle it out?
I'm worried about that.
I mean, is he going to get a deal for that?
Or disappear it or something?
He will now.
Yeah, he might be.
And now that we've just brought that up and given him the suggestion.
Of course, they're monitoring everything in North Korea.
And the government really sucks there.
The minute the minute the show comes on, they somebody in North Korea.
It turns in.
They listen to our slack too.
And it's not for us or even J.R. Bob Dobbs is for Shining Path.
But please resist.
They're following him in case he calls in with codes.
You know.
So next week, we'll be this.
We'll be deciphering the secret of the Knights Templar and the Holy Grail again.
Well, next week.
Not again.
This is a new spin on an old subject.
They're all based on satirical.
Pamphlets written by young men making fun of the occult trends of their days.
All religions were started that don't say that we're going to talk about it next week.
I'm covering it ahead of time.
You can do that.
Covers all mail order calls.
We're going to talk about how hog raising is a dirty business.
You have to get rid of all that hog stuff.
You have to just hold.
Hog raising.
And only one thing.
Hog killing.
And you got to do your hog killing in the right kind of weather.
You can't sell.
That's why your hog will go bad before you get it down in there.
You can't sell a single quarter pound of bacon without killing a hog.
You got to kill that hog sooner or later.
There's only one way to kill that hog.
That's with this knife here.
This one right here.
My grandpappy gave me.
You're going to have to use this to prove your man.
Get in there.
And kill that hog.
My granddaddy and his granddaddy before him and his granddaddy before him.
Pass this knife down.
This hog killing knife.
Just for the killing of the hog.
There's a hog snorting right there.
This hog killing day.
Get down in there and kill me that hog.
Now do it.
Now do it or you ain't coming back to this family anymore.
You got to kill the hog just like I did.
Cold blood.
Just wrestle with it.
Slit it.
Throat.
String it up.
Strang it up.
Strang it up by its heels.
By its heels.
By its hind heels.
That's how they got a bucking ham there.
Cut little sleeves around his little.
Listen to that bucking ham bucking up there next to that buck board.
Its heels just a kicking at that buck board.
It's a bucking ham.
Now carefully slice down the middle there and you'll be able to get them guts out without making a big mess.
You know that hog operation you got is devastating.
It's devastating to the environment.
On warm nights I sit up with my children and I wake up and I vomit from the smell.
I put my wife and my two sons and my daughter in my beat up old pickup truck and I drive away from the farm as far as we could.
Just to get away.
To get a clip.
Get a breath without getting sick.
Puking.
It's horrible horrible smell coming from your hog farm.
Then we stop at the Amish restaurant and order scrapple to make us forget our problem.
Scrapple pork chops.
Spam.
Mighty good.
Thick sliced bacon they got there too.
Not bacon.
No not bacon.
Scrapple.
Then I drop back to my hog farm operation where it just smells bad.
That guy's a true subgenius.
What's better than one me a thousand me's?
My family just have projectile vomiting all day long.
We can't keep nothing down from the smell of my hog farm.
Hog farms are nasty.
A hog farm's so nasty I can't even go on it without projectile vomiting.
That's what I'm walking through here.
It's sloshing around by my feet right now.
That's when we started.
Sounds like the waves of a mighty lake.
Puking.
Give me some scrapple.
I need scrapple.
You know you hog killers.
As big as a baby.
You got to give away some scrapple with some jerky and some grits.
Give them.
And some harmony.
We're just giving.
We sell our scrapple.
We don't have enough money to buy food for our children unless we sell our scrapple.
We have to sell scrapple in order to buy hot dogs which are a step up.
Is that like bacon with eyeballs and penises?
Okay now hot dogs are made out of rectums and penises right?
Okay.
Lips.
Scrapple is made out of what's left after they've already taken out the stuff for the hot dogs.
It's just stuff so gross.
That they don't even want to talk about it.
And mix it with corn and hair.
And cook it up real.
It smells faintly like hair.
Smells a little like hair.
A little bit like bacon.
A little bit like fried spam.
It's got a lot of protein though.
That's the important thing.
And a lot of pink slime.
Yes.
Scrapple.
Yummy pink slime.
Pink slime.
Scrapple is the official breakfast of the X Day World Committee.
Yes.
The X Day X Committee.
Are you going to explain?
We do actually.
We usually.
You can usually get free scrapple at subgenius official X Day events in Ohio.
It just sounds like it.
Free scrapple.
If you know the right people.
Thank you.
Give me some scrapple.
Are you going to play a little metal woman?
I guess I should.
But you know you can eat the insides of people's you know intestines and liver and kidneys
and stuff.
It's got a lot of vitamins.
You got to clean them.
You got to wash them out.
Is that Michael Pepe?
Oh yeah.
You wash them out.
Yep.
And you know if you.
Squeeze them.
If you pluck the hairs from people's nostrils and fry them.
Nostril tune.
You get a nice little kind of a bug like.
Once again we return to that subject of nostril hairs.
Yes.
Well nostrils are vital.
What is it?
What is it about the theme of this show that has suddenly become.
Really?
Fried nostril hairs on top of.
Fried nostril pubic hairs.
Yes.
This is a creepy creepy creepy subject.
And you can cook and eat the dirt under your.
Creepy subject.
And a lot of people don't know this.
If you're starving just clean out your toenails.
Set them on fire.
Cook them up.
You know sterilize them.
And you can eat them.
And it will stave off.
You won't have to eat your companion's buttocks.
Why wait until you're starving?
But your companion's buttocks seem like they're a lot more palatable than your toenails.
Well it depends on your.
There's more protein in there.
There's more protein in a buttock than the average toenail.
Actually we teach you about this protein in step number four of the patented 13 steps
to super sexy sales success.
Oh not that again.
The 13 steps.
Dr. Drummond's patented 13 steps.
Eight percent extra steps.
To super sexy sales success course.
Wow.
With our eight percent.
Yeah eight percent.
Four.
Extra steps.
Yeah.
And your average 12 step course.
You know I don't even need the extra 12 steps.
I'm already two steps.
You're too sexy.
Yeah.
Well good thing about Dr. Drummond's patented 13 steps in step number four.
Six.
Step back.
Yeah step number six.
We teach you how to detone your super sexy self into a less super sexy self.
Oh.
So the people are more comfortable with you.
With their sexiness right.
Yeah.
Because people just can't handle the full on total sexiness.
Right.
We let.
We help you tone down your sexiness.
Yeah.
But not in a way that's demeaning to you.
Right.
What about.
Dr. Drummondian pheromones simply overcome all inhibition.
Everybody thinks we should.
That's in step six too.
We cover that fully in step six.
We spend about six weeks on it in step six.
Six weeks to a new sexy.
Six.
Six weeks.
Yeah so.
In step six.
You know you'll be moving on to other.
Step six.
Like other subjects in step seven you'll be learning the secrets to radio.
Radio.
Radio technology.
Oh.
So some people stay there at.
Six.
At step seven.
The whole life.
Radio and television repair.
Wow.
So you can plug your nostril hairs into the radio.
You just stay there.
You're just there all the time.
Step seven.
Step seven in radio repair you may be.
You may get into the.
The expanding.
The mind expanding and.
Huge.
Fast growing market of radio repair.
The nostril is the center of the soul.
People.
Know this.
People are listening to the radio and.
It's smarter than they should.
They're listening really really hard and it wears the radio out.
That's right.
You have to take the radio in and get it fixed.
The nostril is like the sunroof of the soul.
I know.
And people wear their hair out to us.
The sunroof of the soul.
It rubs it down.
Well that begs the question Reverend Stan.
If the nostril is the sunroof of the soul.
Yeah.
What is the moonroof of the soul?
Oh.
That that hole that they drilled at the top of your head.
Yeah.
You know that one in Dogstown Dr. Drummond.
Ah yes.
Oh.
And it's so much cooler inside.
Yeah.
I I just that released so much tension when that when that happened to me when that was
done.
I just didn't have thoughts anymore.
I wasn't burdened by thinking.
The the the heat of the thinking rises out the top.
Yeah.
You're so much cooler.
You're a cooler person.
You're a cool person and the chicks did.
Yeah.
Exactly.
Because they know that.
They know you're not thinking.
You're not.
They know you're rocks.
You're not gonna you're not gonna notice how pathetic they are.
Right.
Because you're brain you're mindless.
You've given up.
That's right.
That thing that held you back and society.
Yeah.
18 minutes left in the program.
So uh too bad nobody can call in about acting.
That's just the way it is.
But they can hear us out there on the Yodeling radio which is cool.
I might hang up on the Yoler.
I'm hand over that pickle's mouth.
I'm not gonna hang up on the Yoler.
How many how many how many listeners do you have?
On the internet right now.
How many how many how many?
How many how many?
Uh right now on the internet we got 22 listeners including one in Canada and one in Germany.
You can tell that Canadian goose right now that Ontario is a large land.
It's Mario from Ontario.
How can I help you?
I'm sorry.
That's me.
Uh I'm in the middle of a podcast.
I'm the host of the Ask Dr. Hal Show.
Hey Reverend Stang are you gonna be out here for the Ask Dr. Hal Show?
The live one?
Uh yeah I'll be here for every uh show.
Um I just had a strange experience.
I just went over and listened to my headphones uh to what is coming down the stream rather
than what's coming over the phone.
And I must say this is a very very strange sounding show.
So you're actually.
Why?
You're actually seeing the renegade logic.
Because we're a bunch of strange people.
Oh technically or spiritually?
The acoustics are very strange because of the proximity of the pilot phone and the
phone.
So there's this slight echo on top of the echo.
So are you simultaneously on two shows?
Echo and the Bunnymen.
It's soul stealing is what it is.
It's brain breaking and back hurting.
Wait but wait.
I have no evidence to stand against it.
Ratings!
Ha!
Someone followed my soul and refused to return it after six weeks were already up in the
wind.
The soul stealing effort is already on the internet.
See and that killed the show right there.
The show died out.
You can't steal anything.
No no I was just thinking of a large library where every person is given a soul and some
of them are dead.
Some of them are like written by Ruth Dixon other by you know the popular Christ figure
of the time.
You inhabit the soul as long as you fit the shoes you walk in.
Actually you know Christ is my favorite deity because he's the only one who encourages you
to eat him.
Ha ha ha ha.
Yeah and if you don't like it you can eat me right?
But man cannot live on the body of Christ alone.
Nor his blood.
When you distill his blood.
You can drink a lot of wine and eat a lot of matzos.
But you can't live on the body of Christ alone.
When you distill his blood it becomes Holy Spirit.
That's where the Holy Spirit came from.
You could live you probably could live on the flattened bread that they use to simulate
the body of Christ as well as the wine or grape juice they use to simulate the blood.
You think you could live on that?
I think you could live quite some time on just those two things.
Post and booze?
Hell.
Yeah you could live for a while.
How long did you drink the booze?
Of course it'll be yeah you might have to make sure that you're using grape juice
instead of wine because you could probably get severely dehydrated drinking nothing but
wine after a few days.
Well there's those old expressions don't forget booze and bread goes straight to your head
but bread and booze you got nothing to lose.
Well there's a Christian statement brother if I never heard one.
Yeah.
Now I feel like falling down to my knees and retching violently.
You know what I'll have a bottle in front of me and a frontal lobotomy.
Why be forced to choose?
You already had both.
That's what I always say.
Why does it have to be both?
You have a bag of bees and a big old pound of...
Transorbital.
Oh never mind.
Transorbital lobotomy.
It's the Levern Stang.
Is that a tape Michael?
Oh my god.
I'm not a tape.
I'm not a tape this time.
I'm alive.
But Michael Pepe is a tape.
Well I've been a tape for many years.
I died as you know in 1997.
Yeah I've got that tape.
I've just...
People...
People working for me you know just make sure...
They keep you alive into the future.
I make pronouncements on various occasions and send out to you.
You can afford to be secretive about it.
Well you're doing a great imitation of yourself.
And I always have said all mail addressed to me will be answered by me.
You sound more like yourself now than you've ever sounded before.
Send a self-addressed stamped envelope to Michael Pepe, Department of Hidden Records,
or seek out Oregon.
I was actually Princess Wee for a while.
You were?
I changed back.
Yeah I had a sex change.
A little bit of Madam Psychosis.
After you're tired of Reverend Stang's antics?
I'm speechless.
Yeah I really don't know how she puts up with him really.
Madam Psychosis.
Is that what you call her?
Yes they call her that.
Well where is she by golly?
Psychosis.
Well she has a...
She had to withdraw owing to another engagement.
She's sleeping out in a car on the street somewhere.
She's freezing out in the car in her negligee on the street.
She's in her negligee in the car on some street.
That's my favorite singer, Dewey Cox.
That's right.
It's the end of the show.
Coming up here at 10.
There it is.
That's the end of the show.
Show after show after show after show.
Everything's going to be with us next week.
Are you going to call the next show?
Maybe.
Maybe after that.
We'll see.
How about you Mike?
The neck and neck show.
What I want to know...
It's getting ready for X Day time.
Well what about next week neither I nor thou shall be here.
You should come over and visit sometime.
I'm always here.
It's my job.
So you go down special other time super fast not regular slow crawl.
Yes I have to move super fast.
I'll be with Dr. Howell next week.
Well that's a relief.
I've studied Dr. Howell's techniques.
You're in good hands.
Oh.
And you can be Michael Pepe.
How about that ladies and gentlemen.
I'm going to be puzzling.
What about Sir Bishop Jones?
Say ye to my soul.
He's also on the bus with Reverend Howell.
Dr. Howell.
I'll bet you one puzzling evidence and I'll raise you a Bishop Joey.
For lo the wicked bendeth their bow.
Such is a good bus ride.
They maketh ready their arrow upon the string.
But they have to leave right about show time.
They may shoot at will be.
You guys won't be here.
You may be able to hear the show.
Upright.
And call the show on the bus.
In high.
Because of the time delay.
If the foundation is of the Lord.
You're either on the bus or you're on the show.
What can the righteous do?
Those are the choices.
What can they do?
The Lord is in his holy temple.
Don't walk so low.
I'll tell you what they can do.
They can join Dr. Drummond and his patented 13th of July.
His eyes behold the night.
His eyes will try the children of men.
Because it's time for the show to go.
Life's a race.
Well here comes the bus.
The show shall inherit the earth.
And I'll walk as damn hard as I please.
How do I walk boys?
I'm a man.
And I'm a man.
When I meet my maker on my dying day.
I'm afraid I'll have nothing to say.
But praise Bob.
And did I mention subgenius.com?
Well that's where you'll find the real Bob.
And links to all the shows and all the books and all the subgenius Facebook pages.
You can also Google subgenius and see what happens.
Thanks to all the contributors.
And now.
This.
Sire, there is no more money.
We gotta get some money.
That dirty Turkish harker back flat.
We wantin' Philip Buckaburton.
Perkaluma Burton.
Dirtin' first tonight.
Friends, we're glad you listened to this show.
And we're even more glad that some listeners have donated enough to help us keep on going
for another couple of months.
Not just this show, but subgenius.com and all the other archives.
But if you truly love Bob and want some of that slack back to rebound to you, you should
go to subgenius.com front page or especially the radio page or the catalog store pages
and help out financially as best you can.
Now we know what it's like to be on the brink of total poverty and we don't want any subgeniuses
to make their own situations worse.
But some of you still have jobs.
And we're glad you're here.
Even five bucks makes a big difference, even if it's only once a month from enough of you.
Fifty bucks makes an even bigger difference.
All we're saying is that blow jobs could go the way of Steve jobs if you don't pay
Dobbs.
We also take checks and money orders to Subgenius Foundation.
P.O.
Box 181417.
1-8-1-4-1-7.
Cleveley, Texas.
Cleveland Heights, Ohio.
44118.
Thanks for anything you can do to help let there be slack.