Program, you are about to hear of all of Slack's fun funnels, with parody, satire, and comedy.
Any reference to Bob, the Church of the Subgenius, religion, politics, or any other touchy subject is intended only as humor,
and to pass no reflection on the highest standards of WREK Atlanta, its staff, or that of Georgia Tech.
The world knows it's just a show.
The best show in the world.
It's a conspiracy.
And this week, the hour of Slack and all of the Church of the Subgenius that I know of,
salute Reverend Susie the Flusies,
1,000th episode of Bob's Slack Time Funhouse,
produced for Georgia Tech's WREK Atlanta for, could it be, 200 years!
This is probably the greatest hour of Slack ever, and it's really a Bob's Slack Time Funhouse.
Hey, come on, flus, get up!
Come on, wakey, wakey, hands off, snakey!
You gotta do that very special episode of Bob's Slack Time Funhouse, get your butt up!
Oh, evil Susie, I do a very special episode of Bob's Slack Time Funhouse every week.
Oh yeah, don't I know it, but this one has to be a special show.
Who cares?
My audience is always...
Don't you're drunk.
I'll just run two hours of Aquarius and nobody will know the difference.
No, come on.
This one can't be just one song played over and over and over.
Yeah, no reruns of your old crap.
No spending 17 hours sodomizing George W. Bush.
This episode has to be completely and utterly special, flus.
Who says?
I say!
Give me one good reason why I should even care.
One?
You want one?
Uh huh.
Toots, I got one thousand freaking reasons why you need to pull out all the stops tonight.
Like what?
Okay, well let me start with Bob's Slack Time Funhouse number one.
Uh huh.
Bob's Slack Time Funhouse number two.
Uh, yeah.
Bob's Slack Time Funhouse number 350.
I got nothing here.
Bob's Slack Time Funhouse number 1,000.
Uh, yes.
Hey, dumbass, we haven't done the 1,000th episode yet.
That's because, dumbass, you're doing the 1,000th episode of Bob's Slack Time Funhouse right now!
Huh?
You're shitting me.
Hey, sugar plum, I couldn't crap anything as big as you.
No.
Yes.
There have been a thousand?
No.
Yeah, you and me both.
No, there's gotta be like a dozen shows a year.
Okay, 52 shows a year, round it down to 50.
That means we've been doing this crap for nothing for...
What do you get?
What do you get, Flooz?
Will you do the math?
Oh, man.
Oh, five whole years?
Ugh, it's more like 20 years.
What?
20!
No.
Yeah!
What the freaking hell?
So that's why you have to do something special tonight.
Uh, first word...
Uh...
Come on, work with me.
No, it's time for me to put my hoof down.
It's time for the rubber to meet the road.
Oh, you want me to rerun a section?
Ow!
Did you have to do that?
Oh, shut up!
No.
No, there's going to be no phoning it in tonight, bimbo breath.
You can't just pull something out of your butt and slap it on the air.
But I do that every single freaking week.
Oh yeah, don't I know it.
Hey, no, Flooz.
You have been losing game for years now and it's damn past time that you return to your roots.
But it's radio.
They can't even see my hair.
Ow!
No!
You're some genius root you tail wagon idiot!
Look, I don't give two flying flips for you or your weirdo pals from the Merry Mutant Marching Society, but I do care about our mission.
What a mission.
I did...
Ow!
Our mission, dumbass, is survival of the Yeti race.
Huh?
I give them distractions every week.
No, you just don't get it.
Skits and giggles aren't enough to armor the flock against the pink slime they're soaking in.
Hey, but it's...
They need more than that.
But I tell them about Bob all the time.
Well, have you ever thought that maybe Bob isn't enough?
Yeah!
Oh, you didn't say that.
Yeah, I said that.
Yeah, yes.
Because to them out there, our high E-pop does just another internet meme.
But...
You need to go deeper.
You need to go to the core.
You need to explain to them why Bob.
Uh...
Why Bob?
Yes, why Bob.
Uh...
Why...
Why Bob?
That's because...
Dumbass!
Uh...
The why of Bob.
The reason he exists.
The reason we are subgeniuses.
The reason we are locked in this global, pre-cosmic struggle for our race's very survival.
Huh?
It's not enough to have a figurehead.
You've got to have an enemy.
Uh...
Lose.
You need to warn them what we are all about.
Uh...
You need to warn them what you're up against.
And you haven't been doing that.
Oh...
So it's going to be up to Evil Susie to do the heavy lifting as per usual.
So I am going to initiate scared slacks.
Ah!
Yes!
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah!
Because it's time to warn the Seekers about the conspiracy!
Oh, damn!
Ah!
Yeah!
Ah...
Oh, this isn't going to be good.
Now, where was I?
Oh, yes, yes.
It began far, far away from this lovely palace.
Born to humble parents somewhere in the Midwest, the child Bob experienced a traumatic, close
encounter with a UFO at the age of three.
Soon thereafter, he began to exhibit strange powers of persuasion.
By age six, he had made his first million, almost by accident.
In college, he met and married his first and still his primary wife, Connie, who is
now revered by female subgenie E as the Blessed Anti-Virgin.
With Connie's encouragement, the young Dobbs became a salesman of legendary, almost frightening
abilities, known to his peers as the man who could sell anything.
He worked his way up to the very top of the conspiracy ladder and might have stayed there
But, late one night in 1953, while working on an amateur television of his own design,
an event occurred which was to become a milestone on man's mind path to slack.
He was suddenly seized up in the spirit by the hand of Jehovah One itself, the cosmic
puppeteer of the Old Testament, the wrathful alien space god from some corporate sin galaxy.
In this timeless moment, which we call the divine immaculation of the Bob, Dobbs received
the first of countless brain-curdling pronouncements which form the sacred pre-scriptures of the
church.
He was shown a vision, a world where all humanity was equally wealthy, rich beyond imagining,
but without working.
This experience, combined with his UFO-given sales magic, led him inevitably to the world
of religion.
He quickly discovered the golden rule embodied in his classic saying,
They'll pay to know what they really think.
Many that believed came and confessed and showed their deeds, and of course sometimes
horrible odors and horrible sounds, well that's all I want to say about it.
Ugh!
This party stinks!
I think I'm going to be sick!
Ugh!
Ah!
Oh my gosh...
Macaroni!
刻 I knew you were arrays, OK!
..It's morning and I gotta pick upore you.
What are you talking about?
It's morning, right?
What's it all about?
Tonight, you'll have manyyeonathoube.
Well, after that scene with God, Ochman-kun and Negrum, who later BTS forbidden me to
go lethargy in the house.
You should have paid for.
I'm
Have you got any books like that?
Have you bought any books like that?
There are books like that by the hundreds out here in the bookstores,
and they're the kind of trash and garbage that you should never read.
Now.
What?
Trash can, man.
Where are you?
Everywhere.
I will place you high in my council of trash,
and I will set you to burn.
I did that to you.
They are no more fit for the human mind
than a bag full of viscera of cats, broken nails, and ground glass
are fit for your dinner table.
No, I shouldn't eat thee, but...
Sacrilicious.
Hey, what did you get?
I'm with the United States government.
What?
You're under arrest!
I'm under what?
Gentlemen, this...
is Democracy Manifest.
Have a look at the headlock here.
See that chap over there?
He...
Get your hand off my penis!
This is the bloke who got me on the penis before.
Why did you do this?
For what reason?
What is the charge?
Eating a meal?
A succulent Chinese meal?
Oh, that's a nice headlock, sir.
Ah, yes.
I see that you know your judo well.
And you, sir?
Are you waiting to receive my limp penis?
Now, dig at your hands, old man.
Tata!
You're a male, old man.
Ah!
We stand at a crossroads.
The tenuous slack that a subgenius may occasionally enjoy
could be rent to shred at any moment,
for the human puppets of the elder gods continue their senseless plunge into madness and anti-slack.
Ah!
Good times.
The conspiracy is a patchwork of...
of different things.
Some are nations, some are products, some are hypnotic television shows,
some are bad pills.
Now, there's a distinction.
There's good pills and there's bad pills.
There's a good Bob and there's a bad Bob, right?
Okay.
And the conspiracy is the bad Bob, the bad pills, the bad TV shows,
and anything that, you know, is keeping you from realizing that you gotta get right with Bob.
It's the human condition.
It's things falling apart.
It's fat lady.
It's ladies in double-knit jumpsuits beating their kids in Kroger's.
Ah!
What'd I do?
No, no, no!
Ah!
Look at the humans, all the boring humans!
There's so many humans, wish they'd all go away!
They like the same things!
They laugh at the same things!
They like Bruce Springsteen!
I wish they'd just die!
They worship conformity, to me it's deformity!
They don't even deserve pity for being so blank!
They're proud of their sameness, though they're blind to their vainness!
They're tunnelers and detainers!
Can somebody open their eyes?
They all went to see Star Wars!
They all just are whores, stuck in the same big hatchet!
Makes me gag!
They share assumptions, that lack any gumption!
It helps them to function as a big-seating blob!
Their lives are redundant, their behavior's repugnant!
They think they're so important, though he's trying to get ahead!
They're thwarting like bats, protecting turfs like cats!
Like overcrowded rats in some twisted experiment!
They're so freedom desperate, they're all little despots!
Trying to rule and rule over everything in their way!
They crowd up the parks!
They devour them like sharks!
They feed the chipmunks, hope they catch the plague!
They rule the planet, they entirely span it!
For me who ran it, I cut them down to size!
They make terms of feces, some part of the species!
To find your expensive ways to spread it around!
They terrace under the sky, the things they buy!
Only repeating the lie that it's somebody else's fault!
Their opinions are puny, their ideas are loony!
And I am so gloomy, knowing they haven't a clue!
They perpetually prattle, you would think they were cattle!
Living to chew their cuds in front of the tube!
They're just superficial and artificial!
Basically walking whistle, just taking up space!
They play stupid games that show they're insane!
So hard to refrain from mulling them all down!
Or even more of the things I abhor!
If Artified War beats a whole stinking lot!
They're incessantly out, it's primarily pelt!
Like I shut their traps, maybe they don't have peace!
Oh!
Look at the humans, all the boring humans!
There's so many humans, which they'd all go away!
They like the same things, they like the same things!
They like Bruce Springsteen, or Winston Jones!
Die!
The conspiracy has now been unmasked!
Let's back up a bit, I mean we spoke about this a little bit in the last show,
but can you tell us a little bit more about, kind of, how X-Day came about,
how you received this holy knowledge?
Um, to summarise the whole Church of the Subgenius,
in 1953, our saint of sales, Bob Dobbs,
who very few people have seen,
ever, apparently, since that time,
was seized up in the spirit,
and abducted, you might say, by this alien space god,
this monster that had been going, posing as god to various cultures down through history.
And this creature informed Bob that there had been a conspiracy of normal people,
robbing away the slack of all the weirdos and disbelievers,
and those who would believe anything, for centuries.
That that would end on July 5th, 1998,
when the men from Planet X would arrive and, as we call it,
rupture up all of the dues-paying subgenius ministers,
give them their own planet-sized spaceship,
filled with sex goddesses, or gods, or whatever they want,
and then allow the subgeniuses to basically live forever doing whatever they want.
Thanks. Thanks.
There were a couple times when I didn't think you were buying it.
You know what Jankum is?
The
You're going to live it.
Wandered and lost it,
and äth hoveredит
E tutti
You heard her, we won't get to bet on her.
Ready?
Ready!
Now we gotta come in here and try that,
but we just don't want to turn into a reach.
Our way of seeing them out there can be fifty year old for a salon in Tampa.
See ya!
They like conspiracy
Taxes, taxes, taxes, taxes, loopholes
But none of them for you
Lawyers, lawyers, congress, mafia
They keep all the loot
You think back about the Kennedys
About King, about Wallace, about Lenin
You know then that it's just us against them
And you don't always side as winning
You know what it is
They like conspiracy
Many of our beloved friends are what you call conspiracy theorists
or conspiracy nuts
or a bunch of fruitcakes
But
Many of the conspiracies they talk about are quite real
And have affected our lives
The assassination of John Kennedy
The crashed UFOs
Pathetic
Those are the kind of aliens that crash their damn saucers
That's not the ones we're talking about
But nothing is as huge and monstrous
As the conspiracy of the normal people, friends
You know what I mean
We don't talk about the passa more
We don't talk about the
reality
To us
Because a vision softly creeping
Left its siege while I was sleeping
And the vision that was planted in my brain
Still remains within the sounds of silence
In restless dreams I walk alone
Narrow streets of cobbles
Near the halo of an east street light
I turn my collar to the cold down
When my eyes were stabbed by the flash
Of a neon light
That split the night
And touched the sounds
Of the night
Of silence
In the naked light I saw
Ten thousand people
Maybe more
People talking without speaking
People hearing without listening
Writing songs
That voices
Never share
And no one dare
Disturb the sounds
Of silence
Oh, my God.
Take my arms and I might reach you.
But my words, like silent raindrops, fell.
And echoed in the wells of silence.
Of silence.
Silence.
And the people bowed and prayed.
To the neon god they made.
And the sign flashed out its warning.
In the words it was for me.
And the sign said the words of the prophets.
Are written on subway walls.
And tenement halls.
And whispered in the sun.
Last night.
Of silence.
Silence.
Look around you.
Look at what they've done to the things that you love.
They took Elvis Presley.
They turned him pink.
They made him into a fat monster.
That was showing, my good.
The nation gas.
That?
That.
Oh, that.
Who knows?
USA! USA! USA! USA!
That.
People worry that the church of the subgenius is an anti-American church.
A subversive church.
Children, we are the first real Americans.
We know what America is before they took it away from us and tried to sell it back to us.
We're a pro.
We're a prophet.
And as long as you can't buy slack, the conspiracy cannot win.
One dollar.
P.O.P.
Big fan.
Big fan, Bob.
P.O.P.
It's basically two passions out there right now, it's US and them
And unfortunately them is much that determines our future.
much, much greater than us.
The fortunate thing about it is that
we know that
them are actually working for us,
but them doesn't know
that they're working for us.
What do you think will be the next obstacle
the Earth people will put in our way?
Well, as long as they
can think, we'll have our problems.
America
has a strange idea of just
what slack is. They think
you can buy it. Actually,
slack for three-fourths of the
world is a good
dinner. But here
are plenty, ain't you?
Yeah.
3,000 kids starving in
Mexico City every day. Big joke!
Conspiracy! Big joke!
Slack has to be built to
the common law.
It's frightening,
isn't it? It's
unbelievably
big.
It's scary. It's
not wrenching to the
frequency.
You are a bit flesh and understand
not the way of the lead-clad
ones.
It's
Christ without a penis.
He's part of the conspiracy.
It's presidents that
don't look like they're capable of getting erections
anymore. That's the conspiracy.
The conspiracy is a real
living,
breathing, fiendish,
entity. It wants you,
children. Oh, it wants you,
man.
The Lord of Jehovah and
his son, Jesus, are
strange.
God, please see
the evil.
I wish God gave me a Holy Ghost machine
and I'd blow your head off.
The Lord of Jehovah.
Have a big time. The refrigerator
full of beer. The cigarette
stains on the fingers. The dirty
jokes that came from evil hearts.
God forgotten.
I want to tell you, brother, this generation of youth
has been raised in an environment
like that. I hate to be
as negative as I am tonight,
but they've been raised in an environment
of sexual lust.
They've been raised in an environment
I forget God.
Monkey rectums.
Hot oil massages.
X-ray magazines.
Get mine.
Live it up. Forget
God. Sin.
Get mine. Live it up.
Forget God.
Make all the sexual conquests
you can make. They've been raised in an
environment of
sorrow.
They've been raised in an environment of
gently awakening us
to remember who
and what we are.
But there are other ways we can be
communicated with besides the obvious
evidence.
Don't have to wait to see
my dad.
Don't be afraid.
is as huge and
monstrous as the conspiracy
of the normal people, friends.
Sheep in wool's
clothing. All trying
to act tough and be cool.
But, uh,
man, it's...
It's neither tough nor cool, because they're still kissing the mighty conspiracy ass.
And, you know, most of us do have to go back to work on Monday.
But the important thing that you can learn from the word of Bob is how to kiss ass without ever letting the lips actually touch that butt cheek of the man, if you know what I mean.
The worst crime that ever was is the easiest to commit.
The word crime is serving the conspiracy.
Gotcha.
I'm sorry. It's all a big mistake. You got to believe me. I don't know what happened. I'm so sorry.
Wouldn't you like revenge?
Revenge on these mediocritons, these pink boys, these box-dwelling Barbies and Kens, these normals who have made normality the norm.
Pinks are but living stereotypes, insensate meat puppets and food tubes who lack and fear the spark of originality that ignites every subgenius soul.
I was a little scared of Bob.
What good do brains do today, children?
What good?
My God, children. How are you going to earn a living if you have to think about what you're actually doing?
How are you going to contend with society the way it is if you actually have to think about the issues it confronts you with?
How can you stand the pressure that conspiracy grinds you down with if you're actually going to think about that pressure?
Children, brains are a great detriment to life.
Come on. You don't really believe in people like that, Bob, do you?
I've got you figured.
I'm coming over your house and visit you.
My life's in danger. I've got you figured. Remember it.
I know exactly where you're at.
I want to live in your brain.
I want to make your earth shatter.
The door opens, and there's this sharp-looking guy in a suit.
Hey, here's Bob, the host of the most, you might say.
Okay, there's the man who made it all possible, Dr. Robert Slack.
Oh, don't call me Bob.
Hi, Dr. Bob.
Hi there, my dear.
This is, uh, 30 grand. Can we just have our medicine, please, Dr. Bob?
30 grand?
Uh, grand.
Yeah.
Hi there, my dear.
So Bob did the buddy thing, and he slaps it in your hand.
Hey, Bob!
Oh, damn.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Get him?
He's a bastard!
Butter.
Bring me lots and lots of butter.
Oh, my.
Oh, man.
That's ugly.
I dance to my heart as a baby.
Ha!
Oh!
The third nostril.
That whistling sound makes me sick.
Butter, eh?
Oh, that job must be a lot thicker than I thought.
The true subgenius can learn to think for himself.
But...
Only Bob can show him how.
And so, Bob Dobbs founded his church upon a sandy beach of common sense, sense of humor, and dollars and cents.
A likely story, you say.
But it's simple, really.
Bob is lucky, not smart.
In fact, by the perverted conspiracy standards of intelligence, he is gifted with incredible stupidity.
He lives in a perpetual state of contracted consciousness.
This enables him to act without thinking, to surf effortlessly on the luck plane, to float down the fabled path of least resistance.
In fact, to make a million dollars every time he screws up.
Thus, it is not his wisdom, but his divine follies, his holy blunders which we emulate.
The miracle is not in what Bob does to you, but in what he allows you to do to yourself.
He brings...
He brings the student to the realization that everything you know is true.
Under the conspiracy, you're being ripped off every day, but you can learn to enjoy it.
Woo-hoo!
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
Big man.
One, one dollar.
One, one, one, one, one, one, one.
When you come, you see Bob.
If you come tonight, you will see Bob.
And now, you may come from seeing Sister Suzy the Fluzy.
Hey-ya, hey-ya, hey-ya, hey-ya, hey-ya, hey-ya, hey-ya.
I was watching my lizard rubbing his butt on my frog tray the other day, and I just naturally started thinking about staying.
And now, I just love to hogtie that little mutant Texan.
like some sort of bondage pinata.
And naturally that led me to contemplating the nature of ligature marks.
And I know that the lig in ligature means tie.
It comes from the Latin ligo to tie.
And then it came to me like the atomic bitch slap at the end of the stark fist.
Religion means to be tied.
Tied again.
Now how much more blatant could they make it?
You have a place in their world.
That's God's bottom.
Well who wants that for a choice?
Your boobies are like radio tubes that keep signaling me to surrender.
So as I sit on my lap, I know it's a trap.
So I think I'll go out on a bender.
A catatonic stupid.
Where do you think you're been?
You know you'll never...
...again.
Oh now, I don't want to be calling subgenius a religion now.
Although I have.
Subgenius is a religion.
The god that has the power.
Oh but realizing this fat toy with an accent on the toy, I really would rather start referring
to it as a faith instead.
Because if we're f**king sure what we've got here, a big ass faith with a big f**king
pipe in the f**king mouth.
And that pipe is our affirmation.
Say it with me, singers.
Bob Seger.
sold it, I smoked it, that settles it. Because you know what they say. They say God is in
the details. Well, I'm here to tell you that Bob is in the retail. And as a subgenius,
you can get it, wholesale seekers. Because one thing is for sure, you need slack. And
the good thing is that membership in the Church of the Subgenius is still under a bazillion
damn dollars. Yes, you can still buy your way out of pink perdition. You can actually
bribe your way to salvation. And you can still buy your way out of pink perdition.
You don't have to knock over a bank to do it. No, you don't have to rob a 7-Eleven. You
don't have to shoot an old lady in the legs. Unless you want to.
That's the beauty of this damn church. It's like what Stang said about eating a damn hamburger.
You want to eat the hell out of it. Well, that's right, but it's not just about the
burgers. Because if you look beneath the surface and take this aphorism to its logical subgenial
conclusion seekers, if we live as subgeniuses, should we not be living the hell out of it?
Yes!
Shouldn't every action be an action that is going to gain us?
Why the f*** do we work at our own cross purposes and tear ourselves apart just for the fun
of the con? Because seekers, I gotta admit, I let the conspiracy keep me down. Oh, it
was in so many comforting forms. And even in the depths of my misery, I thought I was
happy. But it was all false slack.
It's so deceptively comforting. And for years, I've kind of stopped being Reverend Susie the floozy almost.
I found myself turning back into plain old Susan f***s. And let me tell you, seekers, she sucks.
Oh yeah, you might think it's easy being a visual speed bump, but try walking a walk.
She's a mile as high as you.
Because I was sucking my tip so hard I was starting to get the lines around my lips.
Oh, but when I finally got shaken out of that hell loop and found the pieces of my shattered
self, this time I didn't cry over the burning spilt milk of my existence. This time I set
about putting myself back together. I became my own Frankenstein.
I became my own Frankenstein. I became my own Frankenstein. I became my own Frankenstein.
I took those pieces and I pounded them back into place.
Well, I see your red eyes surrounded by flies telling of all of your lies.
But as you slide down the street with your straitjacket feet, well, your victory is such a surprise.
A catatonic stupid.
Where do you think you're banned?
You know you'll never move again.
Seekers, if I can do it, so can you.
Because let me tell you, every Yetican out there, every seed of Dobbs is worth saving.
Even if it's only to piss them off.
You need to stick around.
And I want you to do something for me, each and every one of you.
I want you to believe in the natural superiority of your subgenius soul.
I want you to screw your overman's courage to the sticking place and look the conspiracy in its jauntous bloodshot eyes and say,
FIGHT MY F***!
How dare you manipulate me with your fifth-rate mind control!
Because, seekers, their methods are so tired and transparent that it is beneath you as a child of Dobbs to be even marginally affected by their works.
By their bulls***.
Because by the ancient science of break-thinking, the mighty mental armor of Bob can shield you from the power of the devil.
And I want you to use it.
Yes, blind yourself to the works of the Kong with the all-unseen stupidity of Dobbs.
Deafen your ears with the insipidude of the full-blood Yeti.
Cripple your legs with that Dobbs-town polio f*** that's going around.
Using the church's proven survival techniques to incapacitate your soul.
You can actually seem so unfit for exploitation by the Kong that they will not even see you on their radar.
You can get away scot-free.
And you can have a safe and slack-filled passage through this abysmal pink life.
And that's all I'm saying. I can't say no more. So,
BREAK BOB!
YAY!
Somebody, help me!
I mean, I, you know, I, you know, I know!
I met my, my, my, my, me...
She is absolutely...
And utterly amazing.
Oh, man, Fluz.
I had forgotten about your big finish to that rant
Baltimore 2007
I'm just saying
When you got done with it
You picked up your metal music stand
And turned to go down the stairs
And you didn't even hit the stairs
Before you just went face first
I landed right on the music stand
And it was the one time your boobs didn't break your fall
That time, right?
I messed myself up so bad
I'm so sorry
You can never move again
I know of a girl
Used to spend most her life
Sucking love through a vacuum cleaner
But all she ever got
Was dirt feedback
And she kept getting meaner and leaner
Catatonic stupid
Where do you think
A very short time ago in the alley down the street,
two outdoorsmen were dumpster diving for a tasty treat.
Hey, Bob choked one dumpster diver together.
Do you want some of this super pizza?
While he gobbled on the stinking mire in the dumpster.
No thanks, Dick, retorted his partner.
I'm saving my appetite for a hot meal.
Dick grunted happily as he shoveled putrid trash down his hole
till suddenly he was grasped by an explosive nausea.
Bob, sensing Dick's agony, grabbed his mangy scalp
and thrust his brother's head over an empty bucket.
Dick grasped and foaming Bob poured from his scabby lips.
Heaving desperately, he purged himself rivers of burning puke into Bob's bucket.
Bob guzzled his bucket of puke, stopping only to shout gleefully,
I told you I was waiting for a hot meal.
As he kicked his brother Dick's flea-specked scrotum,
yes, my brethren, we should all look at this time and try to be like Bob.
We should keep ourselves armed with Bob's bucket.
Do not be afraid to snap out the roadkill spatula on your slack army knife
and fight off the pink fungus of normality.
Live with true-born slack lust for Dick's spew.
Be like Bob.
Pee like Bob.
Spin about aimlessly, gushing a torrent of urine to march your special rupture site.
In preparation for X-Day,
the end is coming and your Yeti soul must fulfill.
It's fecal flinging to find true harmony with Jehovah One.
The next time you are burping on a prairie squid,
remember who made it possible.
Bob.
We should not forget that Bob is the stick that scrapes off the conspiracy crap
you stepped in before you can stomp down the galleys of that pleasure saucer.
Don't satisfy yourself by dropping pubic hairs in your boss's coffee.
Take a dump on his desk.
After wiping your taxed bunghole,
smear the name Bob in brown and green streaks across the ceiling.
Only after this sacred ritual will you pilot your own pleasure saucer.
Through Bob's cavernous orifice.
Praise Bob!
Amen.
Subtitles by the Amara.org community
When the earth is lost,
You know what it is
What it is
Will you be the last Bob, or will you surrender to hopelessness?
Remember, this might just be his way of testing you.
Actually, these choices were already made for you at the beginning of time.
So, do it.
Join the church and gaze upon your own naked destiny, standing proud before Bob.
Where's Bob?
Where am I, Bob?
I'm fed up with the law around here.
You can't do this, Bob.
Come on, get going, boy.
We're busting up the joint.
We're tearing out all the wires.
We're busting it up so good.
Acción Mutante.
We're busting up the joint.
We're dangerous.
We're guerrillas.
We're militants.
This isn't a game.
This is Acción Mutante.
Acción Mutante.
Act like I don't even have a rifle.
We'll kill the whores with you.
Put your guns in your pockets.
Long live the buñoles.
Throw them high.
We're busting up the joint.
Captain Silver and Steelhook.
I can't feel my legs.
The jugglers are waiting for us, following their steps.
I can't see.
Grease your chair.
Take your crutch.
Change your shoes for the machine gun.
Break your chains.
There are no bars.
It's all about fear and paraplegics.
Body's up.
The body's up.
The body's up now.
We're dangerous.
We're guerrillas.
We're militant terrorists.
We're not playing.
This isn't a game.
This is Acción Mutante.
We're busting up the joint.
We'reetch saat.
RD-00888 China
Weigh yourself out.
악 것처럼
At theiers
Of heroism
Jimbo ricolo, Jimbo, Jimbo Jimboivan
DRAAAAAAAA-
DRIVE-A-DRAW-BE-WING-A-LIVING-WING-A-LIVING-LIVING!
DRIVE-A-DRAW-BE-WING-A-LIVING-WING-A-LIVING!
PISS OFF!
Who do you read?
It's over.
The links, the beautifully conditioned links are smashed.
They're smashed as of now because we say so.
Because we say they ought to be smashed.
You don't work anymore.
That's an order.
Anybody invites you to a game of solitaire,
you tell them, sorry, buster, the ball game is over.
Every time I sit down on my kingdom's throne
and reach out for the good book that will fade my soul.
Face me from the gorgeous of conspiracy.
Face me from the chain of time.
Face me from the men in black.
Marissa Diaz, the sad black crazy.
An' Concept Runs Alive
Break up!
Pearson
By
Pretty
Special
Lee
MOS
ohn
Khast
I need
to
do
this
too
right
you
donoo
de se
Are competing
for us
right now
if you
Find a place to hide
And reach your confusion
Save me
From the fortunes of confusion
From the change of time
Save me
From the many lives
And the depths of genius
Oh, Seekers, was it good for you?
Oh, this has been the 1,000th episode of Bob's Slacktime Funhouse,
and it couldn't have happened without the joyous contributions of little Theodore and Babushka,
J.E. Sumrall of Columbus, Georgia,
with the song Blame the Conspiracy,
which was not a subgenius song,
ESO,
Mark Mothersbaugh,
Barnes and Barnes,
Zilch Fletcher,
the mysterious Hamus Amos with the story of Bob and Dick Dobbs in the dumpster,
the theme in Portuguese,
some suburban loans,
the walk-ins with Praise Bob,
along with deathless sermons delivered by subgenius immortals like
Reverend Ivan Stang,
Dr. Howard,
Pope David M. Meyer,
Dr. Gattad and Lagune,
and Pope Sternodox of Little Rocks,
teaching us exactly what we're fighting against, Seekers.
Oh, but Seekers, I couldn't have done it without you.
We should thank our lucky stars.
They're still playing.
We've been on a program of this caliber after so many years.
I'm never going to let you down.
What else is on it?
Worst episode ever.
Isn't it?
Thank you, Reverend Susie the Floozy and WREK for 1,000 episodes of Bob's Slack Time Funhouse.
Oh, and she forgot, the Arise background music was by Reverend V.K. Jones,
and this background music was by the...
The Amino Acids.
Free information on subgenius.com.
.