The Strange Doctor Weird.
Good evening. Come in, won't you?
Why, what's the matter? You seem a bit nervous.
Perhaps the cemetery outside this house is upset you.
But there are things far worse than cemeteries.
For instance...
The Self-Genius Power of Swag.
All right, fellas, here's your story.
A man by the name of Bob once saved our world with an arc of electricity.
Bob?
Is recovering from wounds received in the battle.
He's got a broken car bone and a bad headache.
Good.
And now, before giving you the details of the battle,
I bring you...
a warning.
Every one of you listening to Bob,
tell the world.
Tell this to everybody, wherever they are.
Under no circumstances take action against Bob.
Watch Bob.
Watch out, he's got a gun!
Keep looking.
Watch.
Keep watching Bob.
Bob, give me a hand.
Hey, anybody around here want some coffee?
No.
Nothing counts except Bob.
Watch it.
Anybody want some coffee?
No.
Then just shut up.
Watch it.
Mm-hmm.
All right, you hayseys, it's a stick-up!
Everybody freeze.
Everybody down on the ground.
Well, which is it, young feller?
You want I should freeze or get down on the ground?
You mean to say, if I freeze, I can't rightly drop?
And if I drop, I'm going to be in motion.
You see...
Shut up!
Okay, then.
Now for our next experiment.
Ah, Bob.
Bob.
E.B.
Slash?
Where's Chompy?
No.
I'll be alright.
I got the door braced good and there's no outside windows.
But because this would be a great headlining act, of course.
It's kinda limited, but it would pack him in.
And all I've got to say, no, no, this isn't a gag.
folks, I'm telling you, this is
no, no, no
and so the beginning
of the monster movie
itself
it's Incense Around
Super Eastman Cine
Super Sit Around
Dinerama
and Todd A.O.
with all vision
the new miracle of the sea
in IMAX
3D digitally projected
bunion cream
the double entendre
those innuendos all just got to me
woofers and tweeters
stapled to the back of the family
oh look what I found
friends we make it back to Ohio
from Texas with Dammit the Hound Dog
who is doing great but this show
is a rerun from 2003
because I have to leave immediately for California
to do some movie documentary stuff
with the old subgeniuses
who by chance are
in this old episode
including Devo and Dr. Philodrome
this is show number 889
from May of 2003
here we go
well you tell me what's the purpose in this
you tell me what's the sense
what's the good of it
get lost
a tale told by an idiot
full of sound and fury signifying
Bob?
how do you suppose that happened?
oh
she dead
goodbye
oh wait a minute
nice going Bob
I was down in Australia
when the Waco debacle ended
the fiery inferno
which we all saw and
I was really bummed I was not here for it
because I thought it was the most fascinating
news story of the year
bar none
and everyone was so pissed off about that guy
because he called himself Jesus
and I was saying come on
the guy's real name is Vernon
let him be Jesus for a couple of months
what's it to ya?
who's gonna follow a messiah named Vernon anyway you know
you gotta call yourself Jesus
it's sort of part of the messiah deal
and Vernon spoke and he spaketh and he sayeth
you know what
let's go get some beer
weee
you know Vernon
just doesn't have the necessary spiritual weight that I'm looking for
but anyway
isn't that weird too how everyone snaps in our country and thinks they're Jesus
how come no one ever snaps and thinks they're Buddha
particularly in America where more people resemble Buddha than Jesus
I'm Buddha
you're Bubba
I'm Buddha now
all I gotta do is change two letters on my belt
Bubba
Buddha
Vernon's a false prophet
isn't that weird though
you know
and all it's funny
it was real funny
because these Australians had a big contingency in the compound that burned down
and they were of course curious
and I'm from Texas
and I actually went to the compound the seventh day of the siege
because it was right outside of Austin
and I went to it but
these people in Australia were like
oh Bill isn't he such an oddball
isn't he so odd
he's such a strange character
and I'm thinking
well
let's think about this
frustrated rock guitarist
with a messianic complex
armed to the teeth
trying to fuck everything in skirts
I don't know how to tell you all this but
sounds like every one of my friends
I'm waiting for the Eric Johnson compound to come out
you know
I don't know
I don't think Eric's frustrated but
but anyway
and they said you know they had to break down the compound
because child abuse was stepping up
well that's true
how come we don't see Bradley Tanks knocking down Catholic churches
you know I mean if in fact
child abuse is
your concern
actually folks I don't know if any of you have seen this
there's a tape kind of bootleg going around
of showing film of the Bradley Tanks
not knocking as the official story was
small holes to insert tear gas
but crashing the building off of its fucking foundation
and fire shooting out of the tanks
the FBI and the ATF are liars and murderers
and Janet Reno and President Clinton
either A knowingly passed on a lie
or B are so out of touch with their own fucking arms of their government
that they're incompetent
including me
and I think that Clinton should be impeached immediately
case fucking closed
and y'all have probably seen the footage
but it's sort of different than the official story isn't it
small holes tear gas
giant holes flamethrowers
they burn these people in their homes
okay
that's our government
I've seen the tape and it's fucking real
and whatever
make your own conclusions
you haven't seen it so it's you know whatever
but old Clinton
you know there's I have no illusions about these cocksuckers
I know there's 12 guys who run the fucking world
and they own every company
and you know it's it's it's fact
you can look it up
I'm not a conspiracy nut
this is all on paper
there really are 22 families who run and own 50% of the mainstream media
which is where we get our news
and and it's true
it's a fact
you can look it up
I don't you know I I can't be this big of an asshole without having the truth to back me up
otherwise I'd be a fucking nut doing this
but see if you have the truth with you you can do this
gee I'm starting to sound like Koresh aren't I
fuck
people have often said I remind them of Koresh
I'm like Koresh only without the guns or pussy
so basically
I'm just an annoying fellow
but uh
and frustrated rock guitarist too
whatever I told you it was a dumb thing
I'm in the mirror
whatever I showed you it was all a lie
better be careful someone might hear you
the walls have ears and the sky has eyes
whatever I said you were on the dream
what you want better than all you gotta do
is open up your eyes
and you'll wake up
screaming
and you realize it's all come true
hush now
don't you believe it
cover your head and close your eyes now
take it or leave it
go back to bed now
don't you cry
we're going to work
at the fall
chicken
Don't you wonder who the mind of man
What if you could have been there on that day in Dallas
What if you could wrestle back the hands of time
Maybe something could have been done in Memphis
We wouldn't be living in a dreamless dive
Hush now, don't you believe it
Cover your head and close your eyes now
Take it or leave it, go back to bed now
Don't you cry
Go on, tell yourself again there are no secrets
Go on, tell yourself that you don't wanna know
It's best that you believe you don't hear
The footsteps that follow you around no matter where you go
Maybe you're thinking that you're not alone
And it didn't matter
Maybe you believe nobody else will care
But once you've added every little lie together
You finally find the truth that's always waiting there
It should be painfully obvious to everyone around us by now
that, you know, we're nearing
The end times for sure now
It's not just a joke anymore
We're getting closer to the end times
What are you doing about it?
You still going to work or school?
Coming home to goof around?
Watching the war all day?
What will happen to your routine when all the
The beep comes down on us at once?
What are you gonna do then?
Don't you feel responsible for trying to help this endangered planet?
Danger
No?
Good!
Fact is, it's too late anyway
So, you know, you just need to have a good time
And look for the place where you can get the most slack
Ah, once again, these words were written so many years ago
When we were such innocent children
Such childish, small, tiny children
Now a little good Christian as one half pulled it out of his bosom
Began to try it now
One half amazed
Breakout, breakout, breakout
Passed from giant, giant, giant wreck bosom
Pluck it out of thy bosom and try, try, try
Breakout, breakout, breakout, breakout
From heaven
Overthrow both myself
That is good news, good brother
Did you ever have any negative experiences with Christians who would condemn you because of your behavior?
Jesus went through it
We're actively trying to destroy God
You can't walk, stand, or sit with those who are not walking in the spirit
We're throwing babies
You don't catch flat
I totally disregarded God
You're going to be called everything but a child of God
We're totally normal and natural and
Jerry, that's my feeling
I think we've just seen the antechamber to terror
We haven't even begun to see what we can do to the major population
God has got to take a lot of blame for this
Let Christ be hanged
And I know I'll hear from them for this
But God has got to bear some burden for this
Because God will not be mocked
And when we destroy 40 million little innocent Democrats, I'll be mocked too
And Republicans, God will point the thing in their face
In other words, I point the thing in their face and say, you pagans, you abortionists, and the feminists throwing little innocent babies out of the school
Out on the steps of the school
The pagans
Jesus knows everything about you
The abortionists
He knows who you are
The feminists
Where you live
The gays and the lesbians
Everything you've done
Tried to secularize America
So there's no sense in trying to hide
All of them
You might as well confess it
You've got to take a lot of blame for this
In other words, God has got to take a lot of blame for this
As I fought off the enemy of the feather duster of modern evangelism
It's as though God said
You know, brother, you're talking about most of my relatives
Well, what are you doing?
Let me challenge you as to the validity of your salvation
I want the babies in their face and say, you babies, you helped this happen
And I know I make the gays mad
I really destroyed the nation on its knees
Examine yourself and see if you're in the faith
We're totally Christ haters
Pat, did you notice yesterday
Democrats and Republicans got lifestyle
As they called out to God in prayer and sang
God, let the ACLU be hanged
Let the ACLU be hanged
I saw Jesus in the morning in the burning bush
I saw Jesus in the afternoon too
I saw Jesus at dinner time screaming in the school
That Jesus is everywhere
When I saw Jesus in the morning in the burning bush
I saw Jesus in the afternoon too
I saw Jesus at dinner time screaming in the school
That Jesus is everywhere
Jesus down by the riverbed
Jesus laying down by me
Jesus by the riverbed
Jesus came into me
Jesus laying down by me
Jesus by the riverbed
Jesus came into me
I saw Jesus in the morning in the burning bush
I saw Jesus in the afternoon too
I saw Jesus at dinner time screaming in the school
That Jesus is everywhere
God has failed many times
Now think about this
In God's economic system
There is no woman
But when she released her thing
That meal began to gurgle
So plant your seed in the Lamb of God
Plant it
Let that meal experience the benefit of that seed
That's 10% of your cup
It belongs in the Lamb of God
Leviticus 20 and 30 says
The meal is the Lord
Hallelujah to that gurgle
I want to say that again
The meal is no woman
The meal is the Lord
Your thing belongs in the Lamb of God
Hallelujah to that gurgle
You know, Boogie Boy
Who used to be the Devil Boy
Has been reborn
And he's coming out tonight, people
He is here tonight
And he is coming to sing with Devil
Hi there, little bitch
You know
We used to do Devil music here
Like that band Devoe
But then
Jerry over here
He sat down on a Bobby Dylan record
And the Lord came into him
And now we do
Music alone
You might be an ambassador
To England or France
You might like to gamble
You might like to dance
You might be the heavyweight
Champion of the world
You might be a socialite
With a long string of pearls
But you gotta serve somebody
Yes, you've got to serve somebody
Well, it may be the Devil
Or it may be the Lord
But you gotta serve somebody
Well, you might be up on Grokker
Dancing on the stage
Money, money, money
Drugs in your command
Women in a cage
You might be a businessman
A high-colonic freak
They might call you doctor
And they might call you chief
But you gotta serve somebody
Serve somebody
Yes, you've got to serve somebody
Well, it might be the Devil
And it might be the Lord
But you gotta serve somebody
Serve somebody
Well, you might be a state trooper
Or another kind of jerk
You might be the president
Of some big TV network
You might be rich or poor
You might be blind or lame
You might be living in another country
Underneath another name
But you gotta serve somebody
Serve somebody
Yes, you've gotta serve somebody
Well, it might be the Devil
Or it might be the Lord
But you gotta serve somebody
Serve somebody
Say it, somebody.
Say it, somebody, boogie.
You gotta serve somebody.
Yes, you gotta serve somebody.
Well, it might be the devil and it might be the Lord,
but you gotta serve somebody.
You gotta serve somebody.
I said you serve somebody.
Bye-bye.
Bye-bye, Long Beach.
Praise the Lord.
Thank you.
Praise God, brothers and sisters.
At some point, they looked at Bob's face and said,
That guy's cool.
I don't know why.
Maybe he's kitschy.
Maybe he's calf.
Maybe he really just looks good looking.
Maybe he really looks like your dad.
Maybe it's simply that he is Bob.
And that face is the center of the luck plane.
Why not?
Does anything else make any more sense, really, when you get down to it?
Math, maybe.
But then that breaks down on the quantum level.
So, you know, is there any way to truly have slack?
There's an old prayer, a subgenius prayer by Reverend Lemuel Atom
that goes,
Dobbs, grant me the serenity to endure the pinks and humans I cannot kill,
the courage to stuff the ones I can,
and the wisdom not to do it when the cops are around.
Praise Bob!
Praise Bob.
Bob, you see, we have left some aliens,
or they don't even know one.
This one's true living.
Like my turf.
Was this true?
So now they hope you can pass through the lockdown
though you define into heaven.
He's never named those who are like this.
What?
Praise Bob.
The man's a frog.
I'm a hopping toad in the mud of the freaking Valkyries of Siegfried.
He's a real man.
He's a giant man.
He's Paul Bunyan.
He's a giant accident.
Bob, Bob, Bob's a real man.
When are you going to let me out of this box?
You know, Bob is like the Elvis of gurus.
Have you ever thought about it that way?
Yes, since he has left the building.
But he keeps reappearing.
People know that he lives up there in Minnesota,
somewhere in a trailer park disguised as a garbage carrier.
Lesson two tells us conservation and transmutation.
He is sluggish and slow.
Really? The tropical Bob is?
Abundance.
Tropical, uh, topical, uh, popsicle Bob is just the same.
Slowness and sluggishness.
According to Dr. Fulatuthu Nagasawi of Aido University.
Forgive me, Lord.
I already know too much.
This is a place for crazy people.
I'm not crazy.
We don't use that term, crazy, Mr. Cole.
We've got some real nuts here.
Come out, come out, wherever you are.
You say you don't know Bob, honey.
Why, there ain't nothing to it.
All you got to do is be Bob.
Be Bob.
Be Be Bob.
At last, it's come down to this now.
The final do-it-yourself end times religion.
Capital A.
Swinging mutants and terminal abnormals.
S.
H.
Even morons know these are the end times.
Welcome to the end times.
But Reverend Howe, Reverend Howe, people ask this question of me all the time.
Do I really need to remain entirely human any longer?
I'm sorry, your humanity must be abnegated and proscribed.
For in the wonder world of tomorrow, it will no longer be an asset and may actually prove
a hindrance.
Children ask me, can I stay a teenager while mastering the appearance of adulthood?
If the child has a secure lock on his door, he may master what he likes in the privacy
of his atelier.
It is now 417 AM.
Will I be able to turn water into gasoline?
You may be able to gasify more than water.
Look at that word, such genius.
Anybody could qualify.
It has nothing to do with brains.
That is correct.
It's not intelligence, it's how you use it.
Once again, Dr. Drummond's sentiments are elevated and correct.
A subgenius has nothing to do with genius itself.
One chuckle is worth four claps.
They don't have to hear me.
There's nobody home.
When I'm clear, I'm not a lot of help.
If someone's in trouble, I can be here.
I was very confused.
I'm going to go there.
For you, Angel.
I'm going to hell when I die.
I like to see how I'm brainwashing myself.
Yeah, I could go to hell when I die.
Whose business are you in?
Everything you said, I'm turning it around as you speak.
I'm going to hell.
If I am chaotic, that's very powerful.
When you die, you're going to go to hell.
It feels like I'm going to hell.
It feels right brainwashing myself.
I'll hold your hand.
We'll go talk to the government.
How's that?
I'm not so interested in myself.
I'm going to teach them more chaos.
I'm physically and emotionally available.
I'm so physically and emotionally available.
When you're scared, how does it feel when you're frightened?
Are you un-won?
Yes, you've won a fabulous eight-hour day chained to this machine.
That's right, wage slavery, my friends, it's here, it's going to stay, and you are its
champion matrix.
You are number one on the poop scale, and you're the top of the heap.
Yes, computers are amazing time savers, aren't they?
But you can go in here, my friend.
No, no, I don't want to go in there.
Oh, yes, just take a quick look at it.
Flowers are so beautiful.
No, that's not for me.
This is the nature garden, my friend.
You have nothing to fear but fear itself.
It's okay.
Remember, fear is attracted to fearful things.
It is attracted to strength.
It is attracted to weakness, power, lack of power.
It is attracted to milk.
It is attracted to sex.
It is attracted to sour hot dogs.
It is attracted to French fries.
I'm afraid.
You're scaring me, man.
Oh, jeez of the idiot.
Are you afraid of me?
You are just disgusted by my presents.
I think they're nice presents.
I feel shame.
Don't feel obscene.
No one here hates your bowels.
We like the presents you brought to us today, Mr. Hyster-Physter, Mr. Grease-Lightning.
How are you?
Are you going to get out?
You are not going to drag me outside?
And your name is?
Gwendoline, get the antidote.
Oh, Gwendoline, give him the antidote, please.
Just put it in his neck.
Take a deep breath.
Give me.
No, no, no, please, sir.
Take a deep breath.
Gwendoline.
Please hurry up.
He is getting out of his loo.
Give me the antidote or kill me!
At the first sign of betrayal, I will kill him, but I promise to return the body intact.
That's all right. There is no synchronicity, my friend.
Things aren't going around in a neat circle. Don't worry.
We've got to crack the Lucite to get this body out of here.
We can bring Bob back to life if we can just crack him out of this Lucite.
I don't think so, my friend. This Lucite was made in 1998 at the propaganda units in Fort Meade.
You will never break through.
He said on the 20th anniversary of my death, you must break me out of the Lucite and I will smoke again.
He was drinking with Ronald Reagan in those days. You will not get him out. I'm afraid he is trapped forever.
We will lose him from the Lucite. We will lose him from the Lucite.
If you obey me, you will survive.
The exorcist will come in.
Get your hand off that switch, Tubby.
It's not really his voice. It is just a warning.
I am a machine vastly superior to you.
Oh, now you have him afraid of you.
Yes, Lord.
Lord, down on your campuses.
I must reach oxygen switch.
Get down.
Think of the evildoers as mole people who cannot see the light.
Their eyes are too blind.
And think of Jesus as a superhero.
These people are crazy.
Must get knife out of boot.
They're sacrificing that girl.
This is horrible.
They're throwing her into the bowl of that giant pipe.
Oh, wait.
That's just a crappy special effect.
Wait a minute.
This is all...
Hey, man.
Get your hands off my sex.
These rocks are brighter than they say.
That's my sex, Tummy.
Man, that's my sex, Tummy.
Those are...
Go get your...
Mad men of Borneo?
Those are...
Go get your own plastic girlfriend, buddy.
Guys in Hollywood make up.
This is...
What the...
The choice is yours.
Obey me and live or disobey and die.
You are a slave, Neo.
Like everyone else, you were born into bondage.
Born into a prison that you cannot smell or taste or touch.
A prison for your mind.
Freedom is more easily than money.
Freedom is a hard thing to do.
It's so much easier to be a slave.
And you can be a slave for Bob.
You don't have to think anymore.
You can just give your life to Bob.
So get in line.
You don't need to sign.
And forget about freedom.
Become a sub-Denny right now.
Freedom is something that's for people that want it.
We don't want that thing.
We want to go ahead and have the slavery that we know that is the true slavery under Bob.
Does Bob offer freedom from terror?
Bob offers you no freedom.
Bob offers you the terror of the gods.
Unrestricted, unsullied, and undiminished by any censors of the 20th century.
But Bob does encourage a cheerful mockery of fearmongering on the official level from the conspiracy's reeking bowels.
Monger mockers.
That's us.
Correct.
We find no fanatic.
This is a fanatical attack against fanaticism.
Mocker mongers.
Well, now I'm not sure I like this.
You love James Bohlen, right?
That's the word for this week, obviously.
Where ever you go, there you are.
That's something Davey.
He's still trying to figure that out.
That's deep.
That's kind of a sentiment.
It's like chasing your tail.
They have that in there.
You can't look at your own eye.
At the mechanic store where I go to, there's a little thing above the door that says thimp
and it also says, wherever you go, that's where you are.
Bob wrote both of those slogans, you know, in the old ...
Oh, that was his major employment slogan.
activity at the time he used to just write up slogans they'd print them up and sell them to
these novelty uh distributors i remember him back then he was quite different than he is now
he made he used to make each of those fake vomits himself the doggy doodoo he made himself yeah
yeah and they weren't fake he used the same mold for rubbery like those ideas just fell
right out of his head they don't rot yeah well sometimes they do bob
bob
we're not going to talk about the war tonight i decided i'll in the domestic drama they called
me up said dr drama don't talk about the war tonight please just do something different for
a moment we gotta take a break we gotta talk about silly things things are bad enough we gotta talk
about this normal
stuff we talk about when wars aren't going on imitation vomit that's what we talked about
stomach to use as a joke it's so realistic made of plastic sometimes we reveal church
secrets here on the show and that's one of them table or boss the vomit was an imitation vomit
this is show is the plastic vomit stomach yes they've told us that several times but not in
so kind of words still a good price why are you still awake i mean how many drugs did you do this
is the
didn't the song that refused to die kill you yet i mean it's still there but we'll have to turn it
back up if you don't go to sleep yeah we've got it playing in the background you can't hear the only
one left you're the only you're the our only audience member right now the rest of the audience
except for those guys see those guys over there well check this out check this out i was also the
previous caller you have tricked us wow man i can't believe it you get the previous caller award
you're gonna get the life preserver
you're gonna get the life preserver award
too we're gonna throw you the life preserver
you don't have to you don't have to keep dog paddling you can just hang on the life
preserver and float with slack for a while
tricky callers call us up if you're in the coalinga slaughterhouse please give us a call
right now
i have a 510 area
wait a minute bob
can't you shut off that squallon
shut up
now look what you've done made me kill bob
did it
and now
,
d.j.
john case
oti
not
the
game
week
workout
at
underscore
isb
jets
Neuroman? Yes, Neuroman. How's the virus?
Darn thing just seems to hang on.
I think I'll have to stay home again today.
No problem. Bob's here.
Oh, Bob? Who's Bob?
He's the account temp's temporary I brought in.
You know, I think this thing's starting to break up.
I could probably be in about noon.
What do you think? No, don't worry. Bob and I
are doing just fine.
The name of the game is
Ball Buster.
It's a family game.
Fun for children.
And for adults, it's exciting.
You make strategic offensive
and defensive moves.
Then try to bust your opponent's balls.
It's as easy as checkers.
But it's acting like pool.
You're a ball buster.
Ball Buster.
A great new game
from Hogan.
Let me have your attention
for a moment.
Are they all here? All but one.
But I'm going anyway. Let's talk about
something important.
Know what it takes to sell
real estate?
It takes brass.
Balls to sell real estate.
Because we're adding a little something to this month's
sales contest.
First prize is a Cadillac Eldorado.
Anybody want to see second prize?
Second prize is a set of steak knives.
Third prize is you're fired.
Hit the bricks.
You hear me, you fucking faggots?
Beat it.
Know what it takes to sell real estate?
Brass ball.
Convert that motherfucker, Sally.
Make him sign the check.
Know what it takes to sell real estate?
Brass ball.
Get them to sign on the line, which is dotted.
My wife filled in a form.
Get them to sign.
And we have been played for the last year.
I don't want to buy land.
I don't want to invest in land.
I have nothing.
Nothing.
Hit the bricks.
Know what it takes to sell real estate?
Beat it.
Hit the bricks.
Know what it takes to sell real estate?
We are going out.
Beat it.
Fuck you.
I'll fuck you!
That's my message.
Fuck the lot of you.
Hit the bricks.
You are going out.
I can't make a goddamn dollar with these leads.
With these leads.
With these, with these leads.
These leads are shit.
They couldn't buy a fucking toaster, they're broke.
They're deadbeats.
Deadbeats.
Woo!
Hey.
Hey, you listen to me.
Hey, I closed that cocksucker, cocksucker.
I don't think so, shell.
I think you fucked up my office.
I think you're going away.
Cocksucker, cocksucker.
Fuck you, fuck you, fuck you.
I don't care whose nephew you are, whose dick you're sucking on, sucking on.
You are shit.
Fuck the lot of you.
You are going out.
Go to lunch, go to lunch, go to lunch.
Fuck the lot of you.
Brass ball.
Hit the bricks.
Know what it takes to sell real estate.
I'm going out.
Hit it.
Hit the bricks.
Know what it takes to sell real estate.
I'm going out.
Hit it.
Fuck the lot of you.
Fuck you, fuck you.
Oh, fuck you.
Hit the bricks, hit the bricks.
Eat it.
You are going out.
Put that coffee down.
Where did you learn your trade?
You fairy.
Fuck you.
Hit the bricks.
You company man.
Where did you learn your trade?
Trade, trade, trade.
It's right there.
You stupid fucking cunt.
Fuck.
What you're hired for is to help us.
Not to fuck us up.
Fuck us.
Fuck us up.
Hit the bricks.
Know what it takes to sell real estate?
Going out.
Eat it.
Hit the bricks.
Know what it takes to sell real estate?
Going out.
Eat it.
Fuck the life of you.
Fuck you.
You.
Oh, fuck you.
Go to lunch.
Will you go to lunch?
Beat it.
Coffee.
No fucking good.
Hey.
Fuck that shit, George.
Coffee.
Beat it.
Good.
You're fired.
DJ John K's Slackin' Balls, dear friends, sent in by DJ John K.
You are listening to the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
Therefore, a subgenius is one who is under his own genius.
Under his own particular tutelary spirit.
That is correct.
And technically, this organization cannot exist because it is composed of people who are not joiners.
They are not joiners, tinkers, plumbers, watchmakers, fasteners.
The only thing most subgeniuses have in common is that they are all different.
And you can win.
They are firemen on the railroad or milk delivery men, newsboys, winotype operators.
They are insidious rituals aimed at controlling you.
Regain your lost yeti powers.
I know you know you have them, but you just can't remember how to use them.
You've got to draw deep from within yourself.
And as you undergo the unhallowed rites of glandscaping and acubating,
forbidden shapes from the inside out.
The shadows will be called forth.
Okay.
All right, all right.
Will you relieve?
It's 422 now.
You can relieve your energy?
Yes, time marches on.
He's launched already.
He's launched, he's launched.
Okay, sorry that we were a little bit late there.
Incredible inventions of free electricity, time travel, death rays, ozone generators,
unlimited wireless power.
You can look perfectly normal while mentally practicing the lost arts of yin-yang therapy.
Exploding postman.
You know, who go off when they deliver the man.
Not legal in most things.
Really subgenius rant.
Radio controlled anti-gravity airships.
Thought machines.
Unlimited wireless power anywhere on earth.
All.
Exalted be the name of Bob.
Slamb dunk the Dobbs head in you.
Sex and real estate.
I will present to you my seven winner plans for making you a real wiener.
And it will happen almost every day.
Almost at once.
Of course, like any program, it depends a lot on you.
So order my program that is Eye of the Storm JK 8990 and it retails for $29.98.
So you take the high road and I'll take the low road.
But Reverend Howe, I heard an interview by a guy who said that the Church and subgenius was bigger,
was better than Jesus and bigger than Jesus.
Is that true?
He is a little tiny God and he is a little sinctious plaster God.
And Bob is a better than Jesus.
But it's only this big and it costs $2.50 at the store.
But it isn't even, I mean, being better than Jesus isn't a big deal anymore.
You have to be better than Allah nowadays.
Can Bob compete with Allah?
Can Jehovah One compete with Allah?
Why don't normals care?
Because I've said it once, I've said it a thousand times, none are so blind as those who have no eyes.
Isn't it true, doctors?
That is ever the truth that flows from Bob's grinning lips.
But what's really abnormal and unnatural in normality?
Maladjustment, I suppose.
The terrifying thing to me is that whereas the normals cannot become like us,
we can all too easily become like them.
It is literally the next easiest thing in the world to become normal.
Let us be thankful that we are not as are the normals,
the pinks and the mediocre-tons,
the gimme bobs and bobbies who swarm by the thousand,
yea, even like unto the sands of the seashore.
And don't further mongrelize the subgenius race by marrying a human.
Stay away from mating with pinks and other beasts of the field.
Use the normals, yes, even be friends with some of them in order to learn their weaknesses,
but do not, I repeat, do not cross-fertilize with them.
Bob is breeding his own new humans that are more like the oldest breed, humans with instincts.
The flattening of the personality that comes down with the average conspiracy lifestyle
has suppressed instincts down through the centuries.
The lunar lander opens, the fairy-tube and the math-fixer
are the only ones who can get to the moon.
Other details include rotating primary combustion engines,
pivoting antennae of a ship, and scale replicas of actual scientific equipment
based on the lunar circles.
Civilization for all its fancy trimmings is still just a rickety shack
pinned in a bottle and leave it on the moon.
With the information I can access, I can run things 900 to 1200 times a day.
I can even run a ship that's better than any human.
My situation was truly horrible.
Then, when all seemed lost, I saw light!
Rumor has it that a yeti has the ability to take possession of your mind.
And they walk upright like humans who have the powers of telepathy.
fake
real
predictable
original
entertaining
It's impervious to all poisons.
If it is blown up, its cells will regenerate and multiply and it'll still be alive.
A creature that will rule the universe.
A spark that distinguishes us from the beasts of the field.
You were just discussing what sort of people you are.
People that are on other planets.
And they walk up right like humans and have the powers of telepathy.
So you're reflecting on theULAM.
Dream.
Or are you?
Personally I'm learning from the
witching of Inazuma.
You seem to know all about Inazuma.
Is that what I hear playing in the background?
My ears were ringing after that for hours,
and I thought I had seriously impaired my hearing.
Did that hurt your ears?
It did. It had made them ring like a full-fledged episode of Tinnitus.
And it wasn't until I woke up the next day that I realized the sensation had departed.
That's the way I was, man.
But it sort of made it easier to sleep.
It was like the white noise you need to sometimes fall asleep when the dogs are barking.
The color it was, it was still a noise.
And the noise that indicates hearing damage.
Disturbia.
I was only one year old when my family moved to Disturbia.
At the ironically named Night of Slack revival in San Francisco,
we of the Church of the Subgenius have vowed,
to continue our one true great mission.
No amount of religious or political persecution
can sway us from bringing Bob's word to the endangered citizens of this planet.
No mere bullet can stop the word of Dobbs from encircling this tiny globe.
We are continuing his brave Subgenius Prophecy World Crusade with a frenzied hope
that it's not too late for most of us.
Well, these words were written many years ago,
and now we know that it was indeed too late.
And it is too late for most of you out there.
Perhaps you listen to this show expecting entertainment or even enlightenment.
If you do, you will be plagued by nightmares of this horrible event for months, if not years,
and that's just too bad.
Sometimes even Bob can't undo the terrible damage,
the conspiracy has inflicted.
Yes.
Now if you send away, you can get a soft shot pepper pot pellet fist,
rapid fire, continuous shooting,
shoot 50 rounds in one loading.
Soft vinyl pellets offer the vinyl solution,
letting you create exciting indoor-outdoor action.
Set up many targets and see how many you can knock down.
In one loading before they get away.
Get set.
One pill.
Do you think that we might be able to ask some more questions?
Yes.
I asked her if she knew something.
What was her answer?
Her answer was no.
Yes.
The answer was no.
Any more questions?
Yes.
No.
What is your conclusion, Doctor?
I don't know.
What are you trying to prove?
Next time, employees will have to do as they are told.
Not only will they know what they are doing,
but they will also know what they are doing.
I'm going to go to the bathroom.
That was about ten minutes.
Come on.
I'll fix it.
Okay.
Come on.
Oh, I'm going to go to the bathroom.
Okay.
diamonds are. If you could take me down there, can you give me a ride after the show? You're
not going to tell me what you almost said? Oh no, the show is over. The show's going
to be over very shortly. So now we're here on the train, moving along. Yeehaw! I'll join
you in the club car. It's all so confusing. And now the show, unfortunately, is moving
down the tracks at an unfortunate rate of speed. We'll be pulling into the station and
the next show will begin. I just hope they open the door where I've got my luggage, because
otherwise I'll be stuck on the train. The beautiful show person for the next show is
already here. The band is getting limbered up. They're going to be the first off the
train. And the light times that we know. So really
amazing.
As we get nearer and nearer to the old place, I feel an absolute tingling in my veins. And
when I step off that train, I'm going to have the biggest, sunniest smile on my face for
that old town. Hey, wipe that smile off your face. In time, soldier, in time. Don't deprive
me of this wonderful moment. Let me prolong it. Okay, all right. Stretch it out there.
Smile on my way to freedom. Smile on. Smile when you're smiling. With this rictus of
flexibility.
Somebody smile.
I'm smiling with you. I don't know about the whole world, but...
Bob is smiling with you. Well, at you is probably more like it. Yes, I, Stang, am giving credits
now, because it seemed to flow, and I didn't want to interrupt it this time. But the new
titles we heard this week were by Reverend Artemia Salina, and then several collages.
By the great Fernanda Nande, Lee Murr. The amazing story of the Waco debacle was told
by the late Bill Hicks from a bootleg, and that was followed by the song Conspiracy Theory
from the album Jerusalem by Steve Earle. Puzzling evidence with Dr. Howell and Dr. Philo Drummond.
Of course, lots of that there from KPFA and Berkley. Devo did I Saw Jesus, and also that
great version of Gotta Serve Somebody. That was when Devo was Dove, a Christian band.
You heard me preaching at Winterstar, and tons of ESO Swamp Radio live from WCSB Cleveland
with Chaz Smith, Lonesome Cowboy Dave, Princess Wee, and me.
Brainwashing collages, friends, from the usual gang of idiots at alt.binaries.slack.
Notably, this time, Reverend Cobblestone and Reverend Jarto. Cobblestone did the longer
ones, and Reverend Jarto did the shorter ones, and Lee Murr did the most ones. Praise Bob.
This is the Hour of Slack from the Church of the Subgenius. You can get more information
about Bob and Lee Murr at the end of the show. Thank you for watching. I'll see you next
time.
Bob! Bob! Bob! Bob! Bob! Bob! Bob! Bob! Bob! Bob! Bob! Bob! Bob! Bob! Bob Paul! Don't let
yourself get hysterical. Bobhead! Bobbob! Bobhead! Bobhead! Uh oh. Well, bye now. Stop
it!
I can't hold on.