You may think your husband has never killed a man, but you're wrong.
And before I take him in to face the charges, he'll try to kill me.
Our lives last.
No one can Smart!
That's your answer there, okay?
There's three stooges singing a bunch of nonsense songs.
It's as good as anything.
Can I give you one more morsel of food for thought?
Yes, let's have a delicious dripping morsel.
One more.
Is it possible that Bob is some sort of gigantic super being
and we are just a mold of dust on his necktie?
And we are no more than a crumb in his beard,
which he yet has neglected to swallow.
When he finds it to flick down his wide-open gorge,
then the rest of his feast we will follow.
Wait, Bob, you're blowing my mind, man.
We are but Dottel from his pie.
Did you see that movie, Guardians of the Galaxy?
I have seen parts of it.
Well, at one point they go to a place
which is inside the giant star-spanning head
of an extinct alien superorganism.
Well, that could be like Bob's head right there.
That could be.
It's just an old one that's all used up.
But the one that we have now,
that's just an old one.
That's a fine one that's still in good order.
Yeah, for all we know,
maybe Bob is a raccoon who carries a machine gun
or an alien tree.
Well, that's possible, but a remote possibility.
It's highly likely.
In the course of convulsive things,
who could think of anything more spasmatic?
Because we don't represent Bob as a rackety-coon child
in this here universe.
It's like a bad signal.
No, no.
Bob might be a rackety-coon to somewhere else
in some other universe, but not here.
No, Bob is a regular-looking guy,
regular clothes, regular features.
He's a salesman.
He can sell you things
more than any spavined, stuttering raccoon ever could.
I am Groot.
Well, that's what I call my...
We have one more caller here on the air.
All right, here comes...
Don't turn that caller to the cold and damp.
Let's see what he's got to say.
What do you know about Lab 9,
which was an organization...
set up in the early 1970s
around the concept of the ancient Egyptian gods,
the ancient Egyptian nine creator gods
called the Aeneid?
Called the what?
The Aeneid.
Huh?
That's not right.
There's nine ancient Egyptian creator gods
That's actually a Greek word.
The Aeneid is a poem by Virgil.
Publius Virgilius Melo.
He's talking about...
You ever heard the term Enneagram?
Oh, Eneid.
E-N-E-I-D.
E-N-E-A-D.
What?
What's that mean?
That's the Greek name for it.
I thought you meant the Aeneid.
Or Aeneid.
I know Enneagram.
Not Virgil Gompers who lives down my street,
but just the guy Virgil.
No, Publius Virgilius Melo.
By the way, how is Mrs. Gompers, Dave?
What about Samuel L.?
Let's bother after all the recent operations
on the top of my head.
Timio Bricos et Dona Ferentem.
Which you claim to have won.
He is her suffering.
Yeah.
And he's instead caused her
unbeknown troubles daily
on a regular basis.
He's so good to me.
Arm of Arunque Cano, everybody.
Read your Aeneid.
I just read Dryden's translation
for the first time.
It's pretty good.
If you like those rhyming
17th century couplets.
And I just love them.
So...
So why don't you just drop
them panties, boy?
Well, I...
You see there's this belt here.
It's hard to get loose.
And I've got these suspenders also.
You better pray good.
You're not publicly undressing
in front of an invisible radio.
On a costume,
if I am,
to public bathing.
Let me get these things off here.
But wait a minute.
This is not yet X-Day.
I must restrain myself
in variants.
Well...
Yes, please restrain yourself.
Yeah, you will be baptized
in nymphs,
nerds,
and noids.
And the ones that get
away will be gulped
down old
sequoias' beaks.
So all will be
accounted for.
Old sequoias' gullet.
All will be revealed.
All the answers.
All the questions
will be answered.
But of course,
what if there's a
howling hurricane?
Then what are we going to do
with the bobs?
If the rain is
pelting down,
we're going to have to
bob everybody with
a teaspoon of water
in the slack shack.
You're scuffling around
in the rain.
Like a pagan ghost.
Baptism by hurricane
is much more authentic
than baptism
in some little pond.
Someone left a cake
out in the rain.
Branded.
Marked with a coward shame.
You guys did a whole
routine about branded
not long ago.
I listened to that
and I'm so glad
to call in and go
tell you my version of it
as when I was growing up
when we were kids.
Yeah, let's hear it.
Stranded.
Trapped in a toilet bowl.
Dun, dun, dun.
What do you do
when you're stranded
and you can't reach the roll?
Wherever you go
for the rest of the day
you will know
you're unclean.
Dun, dun, dun.
Yeah.
He was innocent.
Not a charge was true.
But the world
will never know.
Dun, dun, dun.
Branded.
Marked as the one
who ran.
Boom, boom, boom, boom.
Marked as the one
who ran.
What can you do
when you're branded
and you know you're a man?
I'm personally
evidence that he had
the branded guy
had to go and fight
the rifle.
Wherever you go
for the rest of your life
you must prove
you're a man.
Boom.
Dun, dun, dun.
These are petty
operational devices
that you guys
are using right now.
That was actually
sampled in a...
Just plug in
the one little thing
and there's all these
scenes start coming out.
All right.
And I didn't know
what you're talking
about anymore.
Well, this is one
of those shows
for only people
over 50.
Get the jokes.
Someone sampled
the branded...
Yes, somebody
actually sampled that
and made it into
like a hip-hop tune.
I used to hear this
on WCSB
like 10 years ago.
I think it might have
been on Urban Lullabies.
I've been
and ranted
and nearly branded
a communist
because I'm
a left-handed.
Well,
those were
the days.
Those were the days
weren't they,
oh, best beloved.
But now they're all gone.
No one remembers
those wonderful shows.
That used to keep us
bright-eyed
and bushy-tailed
in front of the TV.
You remember
the one about the parrot
with one single good eye
right in the middle
of his forehead
who used to sing
songs about
Dobbs and Bob
all the time,
I think.
That was the
cyclo-parrot?
Do you remember
the parrot guy?
What was his name?
The parrot.
That was a parody,
not the real thing.
Back in them days
you only had
three shows
to choose from.
This is pining
the news, right?
On one channel
they'd have the Munsters,
on the other
they'd have the Adams family.
What are you going to do?
Yeah, I mean,
and they're on
at the same time.
You know,
on one channel
there's Mr. Terrific
and the other channel
there's Captain Nice
and, you know,
you can't watch them both.
You have to choose.
I spy
Mission Impossible
at the same time.
Yeah, what are you
going to do?
How do you know
you're a man?
Wherever you go
Back in the day
one of our famous
children shows
how he decides
to jump on
The Rifleman
against Branded?
And wanted
dead or alive?
In a fight
to the death.
Journey to the
center of the earth
at the same time
as Halloween?
Now you're
really hurting.
You know,
what was
a really ridiculous
example of this
from the
1966 fall schedule?
The Man From Uncle,
The Wild Wild West,
The Time Tunnel,
all on at the same time.
What are you
going to watch?
You have to flip
between channels
whenever there's
a commercial.
Now they're
on The Man From Uncle.
in The Time Tunnel.
That's how
Fireside Theater
got started.
Switching between
channels.
The Time Tunnel.
Yeah.
Well, it seemed
so much classier
than it was
because they had
little snippets
of Bernard Herrmann
music to play
from the CBS
film library.
Is that what it was?
Covering up the fact
that there was
nothing going on
that these protagonists
were stupider
than a bag of hammers.
They would always
end up on the Titanic
on one episode.
We're supposed to kill Hitler.
Which one's Hitler?
Yeah.
You know,
did you ever watch
an old 1940s movie
called Hitler,
Dead or Alive?
It's kind of grade B,
but these gangsters
get together and say,
I'm tired about this
mug Hitler.
Yeah, me too.
And they go over
and they beat up Hitler
and they shave off
his mustache
and then the Nazis
won't believe he's Hitler
and they beat him up.
No, it's really me.
They cut off my mustache.
I want to see that one.
It's called
Hitler, Dead or Alive.
Not to be confused
with They Saved Hitler's Brain.
No, that's quite different.
Also known as
Mad Man of Matara.
You see,
the whole reason
that Hitler lost the war
is because Stalin
had a bigger mustache.
Then there was also
the thing that wouldn't die,
but no,
that was like
an old bearded head
in a bottle,
but for Hitler's,
they saved Hitler's brain,
they have the whole
Hitler head in a bottle
and he's mounted
on the dashboard
and he's screaming,
turn right!
And so they turn left.
He's going,
mach schnell!
Mach schnell!
All the time.
He's hurrying him along.
Joe Riley,
for a horror host show,
made a
They Saved Hitler's Brain
Hitler head
inside a box
for this little
local Dallas TV show.
And there was a guy
underneath
working the mouth
so it would say
mach schnell
every now and then.
Which I think
would go faster.
Where's all the
subgenius artificers
who do things like that
for us?
Nobody's made us
a Hitler head.
Get to work, fans.
Gentlemen,
I have a question.
A question for the ages
for you.
Yes?
Who would win
in a cosmic battle
between the thing
that couldn't die
and the brain
that wouldn't die?
Oh, Stan explained
this just a little bit
to me a little while ago.
I don't know.
It was Robocop
versus Chappie.
I'm going to come out
on the side of
the thing that wouldn't die
because the brain
that wouldn't die,
also known as
the head that wouldn't die,
required a complicated
support structure
of blood
and fluids
and things being
pumped through it
by laboratory devices.
But the head
that wouldn't die
was alive
on its own.
A horrible,
bearded,
supernaturally
activated,
severed head
howling and gibbering
and that one's
scarier
because the other one
The brain that wouldn't die
was a woman
also known as
Jan and the Pan.
She was a woman,
yes,
or had been a woman
and she wanted
nothing but revenge
on her former husband
who had saved
her head
while he went out
to interview
many cheap strippers.
for a replacement body.
Somehow he never
managed to get that body.
I'm sorry.
You saw the movie, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, he's out,
he visits one stripper
after another
sizing up their bodies
and they think
he wants to get together
for some,
well,
some hanky-panky
but no,
he's measuring
the difference
between their
cervical vertebra
and,
well, anyway,
they think he's
a real pervert
but he drags
one of them back
but by then
all hell
is broken loose.
The unspeakable monster
in the next room
has broken out
and is in cahoots
with the severed head
on the table.
How?
Only some
Hollywood hack
script writer
could tell you.
Okay, now,
what would be
the severed head
versus a
frankenhooker
who would win?
Oh, frankenhooker,
well, that's a different
movie.
Because that was
a situation
where a guy
would go out
and collect
body parts
of hookers
to rebuild
his bride
who he had
actually killed
with an automatic
mower.
It was his mistake.
It was a one season
sitcom, too,
that didn't last
and get past
the first production
stages.
Well, frankenhooker
will one day
be a family-style
sitcom
but right now
we're talking
future talk.
By the way,
could the brain
that comes down
take on the brain
from planet Eros?
The brain
Well, in addition to...
That was like
a disembodied
intelligence,
wasn't it?
And that was
a bad brain
there was also
a good brain,
Luce,
who had the job
of rounding up
the brain
from planet Eros.
The bad brain
invented the term
mosh.
I had no idea.
Yes.
How about the brain
from planet Lesbos?
That was the
Russ Meyer...
At Dobstown.
Yeah.
Brain from planet
Lesbos
at Dobstown.
Someone else
has taken the bait
here.
The number is
216-687-3515.
Here's a new caller.
You're on the air.
Yes, I was wondering
if you,
perchance,
discussed
the tale
of the inebriated
trouser mouse.
Branded.
Marked as the one
who ran.
Inebriated trouser mouse.
Well, that was
a deadly,
deadly situation.
Ha ha, Pluto.
Ha ha.
The inebriated
trouser mouse.
I think they were
subject to a lot of
Could you be a little
more specific?
There are so many
of these characters
running around that,
well, we have to be sure.
Yeah, and they're like
on little tracks.
They keep going on
forever and ever.
They keep running
and running
and going nowhere.
Exactly.
They keep chasing
It's nervous energy.
They're just running
to have something to do.
Like all the pinks
who are realizing
too late
that the apocalypse
is upon them.
Running in a treadmill.
I'd like to refer you
to this PowerPoint below.
You know, it's
perpetual running
in a cage.
We told as many people
as possible,
but on the other hand,
we knew that
not everybody would
take the advice
because there really
isn't room,
you see.
Only 144,000
will be saved.
Yeah, and then
everybody else,
well, many are called,
but few were chosen.
Quite a few of them
are not psychotic,
contrary to public
The spawning grounds,
the macro-crowded seas.
Many of them are
Many feel the call,
but few have
correct change
for the pay toilets.
Yes, and they aren't
going to get it
from standing around
and looking wistful
and doe-eyed
at the successful
subgeniuses
In my father's house,
there are many pay toilets.
You heard it right.
It's not just correct change,
you have to have
those special coins.
An anarcho-vegetario
conspiracy.
I've had it
with these vegetarians.
They're killing the planet
with their selfishness.
And they don't
understand that
agriculture itself
is the biggest menace
to the future of humanity.
And their insistence
on a monoculture.
who, this is an actual
true story
of a rock and roll star
of the 60s
who I did an interview
with one time
and who seriously
claimed and believed
and perhaps
howl knows
who I'm talking about.
Question mark.
Anyway,
question mark,
question mark.
Does that mean
an actual...
But anyway,
he believes that
the world is
going bad.
Oops, I'm sorry,
we're out of time.
Because
wildebeests
in South Africa
have flatulence
from wildebeests.
Frappington wildebeests.
Frank Zappa,
yeah, I know
who you're talking about.
Zappa was crazy.
He really,
he really honestly
thought that the
farting of wildebeests
in Africa
was going to cause
the end of the world
and that's why
he produced those
last several albums
and then killed himself.
And he was in
contact with aliens.
He was in contact
with the continent
and that's where
a lot of the noodling
came from.
He had colon cancer,
didn't he?
His flatulence
actually killed him.
It was an explosive
problem.
He could have gone
to the doctor
and gotten it fixed.
I thought he was
still rocking on.
But he didn't believe
in things like that.
No, he's long gone, Dave.
Long gone.
Now we can all
end the world
because all these
characters are gone.
Now Phil Austin
is no longer
with us.
They simply
pre-deceased us.
They went before.
What would it take
to bring the
Fireside Theater
back together?
Two more bullets!
Oh, for God's sake.
I'm not cleaning that up.
I'm not cleaning that up
either.
That's disgusting.
Somebody get a mop.
Too soon.
an actual hollow jig
of the all four members?
You're looking at it
in an unnecessarily
pessimistic way.
Actually, we have
many new members
and they're all
horrible boors
on the internet
and they're all
going to be there
at X Day
this time.
Speaking of horrible
boors,
portions of the
following broadcast
will be objectionable
to some members
of the audience.
Therefore, WCSB
advises listener
discretion.
Views and opinions
expressed on this
program are not
necessarily those
of WCSB or
Cleveland State
University.
This could perhaps
be the very last
edition of
Synesthesia ever
because the saucers
are coming.
The world ends
tomorrow and you
may die.
Unfortunately,
these are like
saucers of milk
that the dish-eyed
children are bringing
to us from the
land of poodles.
Man, it's the
flying cups we have
to worry about.
Well, you know,
actually, the saucers
themselves come from
the same china set
as Bertrand Russell's
teapot.
Right.
Exactly.
That's the point
you're trying to make.
You might even see
a dragon in the
bathtub bathing up
or a flying saucer
that is looking
for its cup.
Dare I take
this other call here?
Yeah, you better.
Hello, you're on the air.
Well, are the
flying saucers
really the origin
of them,
the Nazi regime
who created these
at the end of the war?
The flugelsaurier?
Some saucers.
I thought it was
the Soviets,
but those are
the ones that
go to the center
of the earth.
Yes, we've all
been over that,
hashed it over.
Sarah Palin lives
there right now.
Yes, that's right.
And the saucers
originally sighted
in the famous
saucer sighting
when he saw them,
sir,
the sighting
was not of saucers,
but of things
moving like saucers
that were skimmed
across the estuary,
like Hylas and Hercules
throwing discs.
Pilots,
all these stories
are completely made up.
They were just
broken the sound,
but they were
just being saucy.
In fact,
the saucers,
so-called,
that Kenneth Arnold saw,
were more like
boomerangs in shape.
More like today's
stealth aircraft,
but they moved
in a manner...
How does anybody know
what a stealth aircraft
looks like?
You can't see it.
It's stealthy.
Yeah.
Well, it's a kind of
a V shape,
sort of a wedge shape.
Or so they would
have us believe.
Oh, you can tell a wedge
when you see a wedge,
can't you?
Tell a wedge.
I have...
I have actually
a controlling stake
in several wedge
manufacturing enterprises.
Worldwide wedges.
Full disclosure.
There's a big
government contract
going for you
come to here
just to be a silly man
on the radio
for fun things to do.
You don't need
a stipend
from WCSB.
Well,
I don't even get
a stipend for this.
Stipend?
What stipend?
He was an important
paleontologist,
Dr. Silliman.
Are you all members
of the Illuminati?
Ha, ha, ha.
We could tell you,
but then we'd have to...
I'm a member
of the Latitude Society.
I think the...
I'm a member
of the United
Workers of America,
ESWA.
Hmm.
Well,
that's most praiseworthy.
Perhaps it will
intercede
for you
when the time comes.
Because most
of the listeners
to this program
right now
are on, like,
heavy drugs,
so it would be
very easy
to brainwash them.
Will drugs
turn you on?
That's the other
source of my fortune.
Drugs turn on you.
In fact,
I was staying
there.
I was my sponsor
in the Drug Wheezers Guild.
Drug Wheezers?
I would have never
got in without
guidance and help
from the brother members.
Mm-hmm.
You guys use
a lot of drugs?
Well, uh...
It's not a drug?
Well, it's not
a chemical drug.
No, no.
You don't want
him to go to waste.
It's not a drug.
It's an herb.
No, not even an herb.
You see,
these kids
are walking around
calling their
cheap street drugs
frop and so forth.
Frop is a very
special thing
that only grows
on the droppings
of certain
Tibetan holy men.
And the effect
of frop is permanent.
You only need it
once, ever.
That's right.
are you part of
the LSMK Ultra CIA
LSD experiments
in the 60s?
You're all sleepo.
This thing is...
Wake up, sleepo.
Stop snoring, sleepo.
The MK Ultra,
it's the Illuminati.
It's the...
The bar machines.
It's the conspiracy.
Everybody knows,
and yet no one
will talk about it
because they're crazy.
Embedded into the audio
of this program
is a combination
of ultra-low frequency
and ultra-low frequency
vibrations
that will alter
the function
of the brains
of people who
are not even
necessarily listening,
just standing
too close to a radio.
An alternate function
for an alternate...
Robert Antoine Wilson
ate cheese!
Well, the tinfoil hats
don't work anymore.
...those things out,
which I'm wearing right now.
The tinfoil hats
don't work anymore.
We changed the frequency.
Right now,
you're going to need
to wear a leadfoil hat.
Well, no, no.
Otherwise, the tinfoil hat
will just amplify the signal.
You are underestimating
us.
We have helmets now
that automatically
detect...
Okay, everybody
talk at once.
Paul Krasner died
for your sins!
Oh, I shouldn't
have said that.
He probably just died.
Hmm.
I hope not.
Paul Krasner.
Oh, no.
I hardly even knew
the guy,
but I heard he was
just, you know,
a wonderful salesman.
I was just making
everything up.
Stop petting
Schrodinger's cat.
That's Schrodinger's cat.
Schrodinger's brain
is actually
the bigger problem.
Is there a brain
or not?
And then there's
the sad case
of Schrodinger's baby.
Oh.
That was really awful.
Well, uh...
Schrodinger's bonobo.
The X-ray did.
That was horrible.
You know, that was sexy.
Schrodinger's bonobo.
So, who will save...
Are you going to have
to clean up the box
afterward or not?
The pygmy chimps.
Right.
It was a big thing
with the latex industry
in the late 1970s.
I think it was maybe
how could corroborate that
if it's indeed a fact.
What happened in the
late 1970s
that I could corroborate?
They saved Schrodinger's cat.
Oh, they did?
So they did.
Look at that.
Okay.
Schrodinger's bonobo stick
begat some other stick
about polyvinyl chloride
and latex devices.
So that's why I asked you
if there was
an ever-presenting
clump of bonobo
that both exists
and does not exist
at the same time.
After so much
stick-to-itiveness
to abandon it
at the last moment.
It was not Schrodinger's
type of stuff at all.
I used to get
most of my stuff
at Schrodinger's
but not since they
lost their lease.
I remember going downtown
on the bus
with my parents
as a little kid
shopping at Schrodinger's
and getting a malt.
Yeah.
Yes, at the soda fountain there.
Yes.
A lot of old ladies
went there
and got sandwiches and things.
But their prices
went sky high.
That's true.
Schrodinger's malt,
how did you know
you were going to get one?
They were forced to
integrate their lunch.
That's the beauty part.
You can drink as many
as you want
because you're both
drinking it
and not drinking it
so the calories
cancel themselves out.
I guess these scientist
eggheads must be
a lot smarter than me
because that stuff
doesn't make no sense at all.
I'm just stupid.
Well, maybe so.
You weren't supposed
to say that.
That part.
I was reading
a rhetorical.
Maybe I'm just stupid.
That doesn't mean
I really think I'm stupid.
That means I think
they're stupid.
Here, read the juvenile
article in the
Book of Knowledge.
That's just silly.
Yes, this kiddie
sugar-coated science
should bring you
up to speed.
The Junior Scholastic
Edition.
Now, I read that
when you have
quantums,
you can do anything.
You can go back in time.
You can make multiple
copies of yourself
and clones.
If you've got quantums,
you can just do
about anything.
You can put it
in your homeopath medicine.
Put quantums in there
and it's like
antioxidants.
And it doesn't have
none of that
grubin in it
or gluten.
Gluten.
Nobody likes it.
I'm a glutton
for gluten.
That's all that counts.
I am a glutton
for gluten.
I don't know.
It's a glutton
glutton.
Gluten for gluten.
Gluten pops.
With electrolytes.
Yes, in blue.
Ah.
At any rate,
these picky
matters of diet
will hardly matter
when we have
no stomachs
and no teeth.
I want to be on
the paleo diet
so I can live
the average age length
of a paleolytical man.
Yes, you can
wear your teeth out
chewing pieces
of rotting animal skin.
Right.
That's paleo diet.
The quiet,
the rumble in your stomach
which is up against
your backbone
and your feet
bloody and torn
from being chased
by a persistent
man.
It's a mammoth
for 20 miles.
It's natural.
The paleo diet.
That's a great name
for a rock and roll band.
Persistent mammoth.
Well, you know,
an elephant never forgets.
I wouldn't go
messing around
no mammoth
if I were you, mister.
You know,
we really need to get
the genetic engineers
of the world
on the task
of creating
pygmy elephants
that would be suitable
to keep as pets.
Save the pygmy elephants.
In small houses.
They would make
the best pets ever.
of humanities
that we could have
if you just take
your pig in a blanket,
and you're like,
or your large,
or your,
I mean,
your small elephant
to the store.
That's your elephant.
You can take your
dwarf hippopotamus
and stuff
and just get on the back
and you tie them up
like they used to
in the old western days.
They used to tie up
elephants in the old west?
They tried,
but, you know,
they were significantly
larger in those days.
And with our
new modern technology,
we could actually
create,
create them,
we could make them
little teeny,
tiny, small,
just big enough
to look like a pony.
Only they'd be
like a,
even a rhinoceros
if it tamed it real good
and removed its horn.
Homo floresiensis
lived among
pygmy elephants,
didn't it?
Yes, that was
the hobbits,
the real life hobbits.
They had to deal
with giant lizards
and tiny elephants.
Those lizards
were huge.
They were actual dragons.
So there was a time
when there was
cavemen fighting
on dinosaurs,
only they weren't
dinosaurs,
they were big lizards.
That's about to come on.
They're dragons,
but not dinosaurs.
Well, no,
they're not dinosaurs,
but they're kind of
like dinosaurs.
It's kind of like
cavemen got to fight
dinosaurs.
They were, in some sense,
very much like dinosaurs.
Their skin was similar
to the dinosaur skin.
It's the same as
Jesus riding on
a dinosaur and
something.
Jesus was nowhere
near these islands.
instead of spears
when they were
reattached.
Jesus didn't know that,
although, but Jesus
knew about dragons
because that's mentioned
in the Old Testament.
So, yeah, sure.
Absolumo.
That's right.
Yeah, there's people
trying to prove
that the dinosaurs
were, in fact,
actually dragons,
so as to bring it
into the, you know,
biblical framework.
Nine.
They are mistaken.
Sadly deluded.
Well, now,
wait until they discover,
you know,
Dragonsaurus
with his big old
flame sack.
They have discovered
many dragon-like
creatures that
recently became
but none of them
lived in the time
of the hapless humans.
And then how about
Hellboy?
That Styracosaurus-y
kind of monster
they found in...
Actually, they called
him Hellboy because
it was hellish to get
the thing out of
the rocks.
He was a monster
but not a
Styracosaurus, though.
He was one of those
Cereptopsian things.
And he ground
their bones to make
his bread.
He was ugly.
He had them
stubby horns.
But apparently
the real reason
that the paleontologists
called him Hellboy
was because they
had to carve him
out of really hard rock
on a cliffside
and there were
endangered species
living in the river below.
They weren't allowed
to let more than
a certain amount
of rock and fossil
fall into the river.
Tumble down.
Right.
I want to go to
the actual gate of hell
in Turkmenistan.
So it was hard
as hell to get out.
Get Hellboy out.
Yeah.
Hellboy the Dinosaur.
He can do all kinds
of things.
He can do fire.
Yes.
The reason they could
breathe fire
was a simple one.
If they leaned
across the campfire
already set
and breathed on you
then their
exhalation
would indeed
turn into a jet
of living flame.
Same thing
could be said
for cows.
You know,
they belch up
quite a bit of methane.
Yes, they do.
And they too
could be fire breathers
if they simply
send a blast
over a fire.
Over a campfire.
Hey, Dave,
who was the rock star
you were talking about?
Um,
I kept on saying
question mark
over and over.
I know.
You must mean
Trademark Gunderson?
No,
it's Question Mark Gunderson.
Question Mark.
He'll be at X Day.
Yes,
the Evolution Control Committee
will be representing it.
Question Mark is coming
to X Day?
No,
Question Mark is coming
to the Mysterians.
I mean,
Wisteria.
Trademark is coming
to Wisteria.
Wait,
this is getting confusing.
Yes, Trademark is coming
to Wisteria.
There's Question Mark
and the Mysterians
who aren't going
to Wisteria.
Wisteria.
But Trademark
is going to Wisteria.
For X Day
and he will be
appearing twice
and doing a workshop
at the Starwood Festival.
And he's the director
of the Evolution Control Committee,
which is kind of like
time control laboratories,
but Evolution Control.
They work hand in hand.
Yes.
They work in cooperation.
You know who you've got
to get to play X Day
one of these years?
No, who?
The Toilet Bowl Cleaners.
They've already had
the Arm and Edge.
There aren't even any
toilet bowls out there.
They are the ones
who make poop songs.
Like their latest album
is called.
Oh, right.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, you've talked about it.
Their latest album
is called
The Mops and the Booms
and Dance and stuff like that.
The album is called
You Thought We Ran Out
of Poop Song Ideas.
You were wrong.
Well, Philo Drummond
and his family
will be there.
So, and Pooh Watertowel.
The band.
The actual band.
The duo, Pooh Watertowel.
Pooh Watertowel.
Will be joining together
with the drummers.
For a reunion
of Doctors for Wotan.
And if that doesn't scare you,
I don't know what.
They only play on Wednesdays.
No, actually,
that used to be true.
But for the reunion,
we're making an exception.
Wood.
Every day is the day
of Wotan now.
The Vortex took them.
Just took them away.
Yes.
As in that great movie,
The Day Time Ended.
I've showed that movie
to Princess Wee
last week.
Yes.
What did you think,
Princess Wee?
Well, my mind was blown.
What happened
to little Billy Ben?
The Vortex took them.
What does that mean?
I don't know.
What we have here
is a break
in the time-space continuum.
Tell it, Daddy.
It's a vortex.
It's an American family
being tormented
by special effects.
That had some
great stop motion in it.
Yeah, they did.
They had the two
huge monsters
slugging it out
in the barn.
And at the end,
the new age comes.
That's right.
Nobody understands it,
but they know
it's the new age.
Yeah, they're all
walking down toward
the buzzing,
zapping,
futuristic city.
The kids riding
bizarre alien beasts.
I don't know what
we're walking into,
but it sure looks pretty.
And the dad says
to the mom,
you know,
I think this was
just somehow
meant to be.
Yeah, that's right.
That's the end.
That's the end of the movie.
Well, sorry,
spoiler alert.
Shot, shot
from some hack writer.
Loaded quid.
Well, but they do
put in a lot of stuff
about sunspot activity
to make it profitable.
Oh, yeah.
When you get sunspots,
you're going to watch out
for the special effects.
They're coming.
We have another caller here.
Hello, you're on the air.
Save us, caller.
Save us.
Yes, I believe
the sunspots
are God's acne.
On the sun's broad
and burning face.
They prove that the sun
was not a problem.
It was a perfect sphere
when they were first
discovered by Galileo
and thus he was consigned
to re-education
by the ecclesiastical authority.
Ours is an adolescent star.
And his daughter
is not allowed
to escape from the nunnery.
Every time the sun
pops a zit,
that's a solar flare.
And Bob is a clearasil.
That's right.
I was going to say,
okay, people,
how about a little
J.R. Bob Dobbs
on that pimply solar disc,
huh?
Does it dab on you?
On the dobs.
A little dab, do you?
Well, yes, I have.
I believe that Venus
is circling Uranus, too.
Venus has transited the sun
for the last time
for a hundred years.
You've totally missed it.
You missed the transit of Venus.
What is the matter with you,
dull, witted fellow?
I was pretty sure
it was circling Uranus.
Nope.
Not so.
The other way around.
Stupid.
You can't do that.
The two of Earth
are stupid, stupid, stupid.
Uranus circles
the inner worlds,
including Venus.
We have a cosmic bidet
that keeps Uranus clean.
That was a great man.
Cosmic bidet.
Yeah.
The orbit of Uranus
actually interferes,
cuts across the orbit of Pluto
at a point.
But recently it's been discovered
that Saturn has rings
that are vastly huger
than the ones that have been known.
Whole astronomical distances
of ring material
are around the planet Saturn,
not just those little visible ones
that we can see.
Ring around Uranus.
That you can launder away.
Ring around the color.
So then could you conceivably walk
on the rings of Saturn?
Well, you could,
but you're not going to get me out there.
Your first life.
That is more strong material
that's coming up
in just a few seconds.
Yeah, you've heard of
walking on the wild side?
It's ice, man.
Ice.
And such nice ice.
If you were actually
like surfing on the rings of Saturn,
it would appear that you were
just going forward
in a straight line.
Like that movie Dark Star,
but not like the recent movie Dark Star,
which is about H.R. Giger.
Giger?
Giger.
No, it's about
some disaffected astronauts
in space who were sent out
to destabilize and destroy
irrelevant planets
or some bizarro mission like that.
Giger.
Destroy the world.
The warming sun.
They have intelligent nuclear bombs
that will destroy planets,
but the problem is
they're a little too intelligent
and they have to be talked out of going off.
You must have seen that movie.
You did see that movie.
You have seen the movie.
You did sign the application.
You are aware of your obligations.
Well, I think you're better.
I think that our legal staff
will contact us.
We'll contact you if you have broken
any of the aforementioned rules and regulations.
Well, you can always call
the toll-free number
and get your bacon saved.
But we're so close to the cusp
of utter immolation and destruction.
I think you shouldn't
wait too long
before seeking expert
scientific assistance.
Repent.
Quit your job.
Slack off.
The world ends tomorrow
and you may die.
Are you abnormal?
Different?
Well, you are probably better
than most people.
Hey, Dr. Hal,
say something from Half-Life.
Uh, have you seen my coffee cup?
Whoa!
Man!
Oh, man, that is cool!
Hey, Hal, if there were gonna be...
Why do we all have to wear
these ridiculous ties?
I'm sorry.
For those of you who are just tuning in,
this is Dr. Hal,
who actually...
Me, me, me.
...actually did some of the voices
in the video game.
Half-Life.
Were you in Half-Life 2 as well?
I am in Half-Life 2.
My address to City 17
is a lengthy oration,
but then I'm also in Dota 2
as Tinker,
who is a sort of little elf version
of my character in Half-Life.
Yes, Dota,
for those who don't play such games,
is known as Defense of the Ancients 2.
Dota 2.
My character Tinker
masterminds an army of giant spiders
and other creatures,
which come sweeping along the screen.
Yes, yes.
I'm casting.
And they wanted to mess up my voice electronically
to turn it into a little elf voice,
and I said,
don't bother.
I'll just do the little elf voice.
And so I did,
and it was fine.
And behold, it was good.
What does your little elf voice sound like?
Why, like some little elf taking off
is what it sounds like.
You think I'm going to give away a proprietary...
Oh, is this on?
Well, thank you for your question
and interest in the...
video game industry.
So you would...
I have to go prepare for the saucers.
Saucers?
The saucers.
Nice to talk with you, everyone.
See you on the other side.
All right.
Thank you, Mark.
Okay, the saucers are on their way.
And, uh...
Oops.
Uh, now we're...
They've slowed down, I think,
uh, near Saturn.
They have to hold off in sight of Earth,
just as Moses was halted
at the edge of the Promised Land
because of his, uh, intemperance
and displeasing Jehovah.
I see the other side.
I may not get there with you.
I have been to the mountaintop
and I have seen
the other side.
I don't know if I'm going to get there with you.
Yes, the Lord is going to
take Dr. Sinister home
if you don't send in, uh,
your, uh, hard-earned, uh, sawbox.
And he saw a 600-foot Jesus
winking, gesticulating,
making significant...
uh, uh, arm and hand signals.
Uh, only you can make a difference here.
Help Jesus out.
Yes.
He needs your help.
Keep Jesus away from, uh,
I miss Jesus.
radio programs and...
Oh, buddy, we need to pump up Jesus.
We need to pump Jesus up.
For one thing, we can do a favor
by stop using that name for him,
which was created by the hated oppressors,
the Romans, you see.
They didn't like people with those funny...
I'm talking about the real Jesus.
...Jewish-sounding names,
that were...
like, Yeshua, Ben-David,
or whatever it was that they said.
That's not the way people have names.
People have names with masculine endings,
like Marcus, Lucius, and you, you're Jesus.
Maximus, Maximus.
Okay, get out of here.
Next.
And so, the ones who...
I knew that.
...who persecuted and crucified him
gave him this terrible name
that everybody uses,
and I think it's a shame,
and we have to stop it right now.
Well, the funny thing about the Latin language,
uh, is that nouns have to have
a certain type of ending to be even able to...
fit into a complete sentence.
Just so.
Otherwise, they wander in the sentence,
like the wandering Jew,
unable to come to land, come to light.
You can be a fourth declension noun,
or you can be a first and second declension noun.
Hmm, even worse.
But declension is mandatory.
Absolutely.
You must be able to, uh, decline.
Decline?
Yes.
So, uh, Jesus, or, uh, Je-zoom,
uh, but come on.
Uh, or Je-zoo-ay, meaning there are all three of them.
Jesus, Je-za, Je-zooom.
Mr. Breedee pointed out that, uh,
the Jews didn't kill Jesus.
No, of course not.
The Romans didn't kill Jesus.
No.
Jesus killed himself.
The cops killed Jesus.
The police.
It was police brutality.
I need to believe that.
I, I, I maintain that he killed himself.
By intemperate behavior.
Well, of course, being God, he's God.
Nothing could happen that he didn't want to happen, but...
Exactly.
You know, I mean, his whole plan,
his whole plan is like,
okay, so I, I am God,
and I made these people,
and I made them real,
and I made them really messed up,
and I, of course I'm God,
so I can't do anything wrong,
so I must have made them all messed up on purpose.
Uh, and, and this is all an elaborate plan
for him to come down
and have a really rough weekend,
because he's into S&M,
and, you know...
Oh, no, no.
I mean, that had to have been God's plan all along.
God wanted to get crucified all along.
Well, but the cops wanted to help.
And, and, you know,
and the whole reason he died on the cross,
he had a little bit of a God complex.
He was just too proud to say the safe word.
Yeah, but that doesn't excerpt the cops
from, uh, Condon's...
condemnation for following their comp instinct.
Well, you know, Condon...
Don't just follow your orders.
That's not good in the Catholic Church.
Remember, nobody was ever born a cop.
Well, what are we supposed to do?
Burn all the Confederate flags then?
Why don't we just burn the American flag?
Why don't we just all jump off a cliff then?
Well, didn't, uh...
If you're gonna outlaw everything,
why don't you just outlaw everything?
Didn't Dylan Storm Roof Aluminum Siding
burn an American flag
on, on his little YouTube video?
Oh, yeah, that's right.
He did.
So it's, uh, that's already been done.
It's past praying for.
Well, because America's been destroyed.
It's already, it...
Obama's already destroyed it single-handedly.
One time I actually saw...
Which there's super powers.
One time I actually saw rolling papers
with the American flag printed on them.
Yeah, and a patch on a hippie's ass
with an American flag on it.
Now, you tell me that's, uh, not the song of the apocalypse.
That peace sign is a,
that's a footprint of the American chicken.
Well, uh, I guess that, uh,
a symbol of death.
And a Confederate flag is a footprint of the American, uh...
Hogswood.
Um, uh, um...
A starry X.
An American, uh...
Starry X star.
Now, which Confederate flag are you talking about?
What has to do with an X and stars and, uh...
The exosaurus.
The battle flag.
Everybody has to argue over it.
The conservative exoskeleton flag.
We all have to argue over what the,
that's not even the Confederate flag.
That's the battle flag.
The Yankees don't know nothing.
I mean, you're a battle flag.
You are a military...
You're a Virginia Lib Targe.
You're so stupid.
They're just idiots.
They don't even know what the stars and bars are.
All they can do is call names.
All these stupid idiots can do is call names.
All them stupid idiots can do is call names to people,
because they're stupid idiots.
You of Earth are stupid, stupid, stupid.
That's all they can do is just call people stupid things,
because they're so stupid.
Well, uh, our friend, Saint Stupid,
is ecumenically yoked with the Church of the Subgenius.
This is the Church of the Subgenius, after all.
That's no good.
This show is so stupid, I can't stop watching it,
just thinking how stupid people must be watching this stupid show.
I just sit here just thinking,
it must be so stupid to sit here watching this.
I just can't turn it off.
I can't wait till next week.
I wouldn't spend too much time thinking about it,
because you know what's gonna happen next.
It's so stupid.
I just love watching it.
The rocks are gonna melt.
People will scream.
Cities will fall into the abyss.
You know, you're all gonna have a terrible time.
But...
My people are destroyed for lack of knowledge.
Hosea 615.
There you go, and if you can't believe Hosea,
who can you believe?
He's such a hoser than Hosea.
Yeah, he's not even a real guy.
He's an illegal immigrant.
He's a pig-fibber.
So, uh, I think we've...
Pre- and post-testaments, or New Testaments,
Cretans, you're all Cretans.
Now, is there any other theological question we could enlighten?
Yeah, I'm not a creationist, I'm a Cretanist.
Yeah, and other such catalogical questions we could enlighten you at?
Well, it could be.
Just give us a big call here, give us a jingle, a shout-out here on the radio, and...
And you can call here at the University of San Luis Obispo
if you have any final questions to prepare yourself for the coming apocalypse.
These universities is nothing but Marxists.
They sell to all lesbian Marxist professors.
It's all those kids learn from now.
That's why it's things like this.
They think they spell women with a Y.
They're entitled.
They think they's entitled to everything.
I take that personally, because I am a Marxist impersonalist, impersonator.
Well, you probably think you're entitled to everything on other guy's dime.
On my dime, yeah.
I happen to work.
Well, not really.
We can carry him on the internet.
Welfare Keats.
Says the generation that paid a tiny fraction of what today's kids are paying.
For college tuition.
Them kids, it's entitlements.
That's all.
Diversity and entitlements.
That's all that knows about.
Says the last generation that's actually going to get to collect on Social Security.
Well, that's all Republican propaganda.
Still voting Democrats, still poor.
Still voting Republicans, still poor.
But, you know what I'm saying?
No, nobody understands at all what you're saying.
Patriot, psychotic, anarcho-materialist party.
I'm talking God's language.
You need to sit down and take a stress pill.
I have a confession to make.
Uh-oh.
As a young child, about 10 or 11 years old, I was in love with Chuck Connors.
I'm sorry.
Marked as the one who ran.
I thought you were going to say he psychically abused you as a leather man or whatever they
called him in France.
No, no, no.
He was innocent.
Not a charge was true.
No, that's the...
And the world will never know.
Stranded, trapped on the toilet bowl.
But you're stranded and you can't reach the roll.
Okay, take three.
Rubenstein, I listened to all of those X-Day shows from last year in a row, and you was
talking about that stupid old Bobo character every show.
Why were you being so repetitive?
Are you senile?
Well...
First time caller, long time listener.
I want to talk about Schrodinger's bonobo again.
Schrodinger's bonobo.
I thought we absolutely hashed that one out.
I don't see any landowners or any kind of voice or electronic devices pointing anywhere.
I hear big long periods of silence and I realize it's just a humming in my own brain.
America's already been destroyed.
You see?
See what I mean?
It's like a voice is talking in your head.
America's already been destroyed.
Isn't it?
It's like a voice is talking in your head.
You can't make a hair or tail of what you're hearing.
You can't say it's a real person or it's some disembodied voice that you can hear.
The transmitters are in your teeth, Bob.
You can't get away from the transponder.
You are the transponder.
You've got to pull all your teeth, Bob.
That's what I did.
Don't you know your body is a radio receiver?
That hat's a mess.
And it looks mighty fine on you.
Pointless. Purposeless.
The silent radio.
Radio. It's the happening sound.
Radio. It's what makes the world go round.
Radio. Radio.
Yes, radio. The miracle of the age.
On air, land, and sea.
You better do as you are told.
You better listen to the radio.
Radio. Radio.
Um, uh, I trust you.
Elvis has left the building.
Yes, he left a long time ago.
Thank you, Mr. Marconi.
Now, I've about had it with all this unnecessary, irrelevant sound, jackhammers and pile drivers,
uh, horrible groaning and shrieking of the, uh, mechanism.
The slaves in the fields working for us now.
I slept through that part.
It's hard to sleep through it when it's a foot away from your head.
Friendly singing as I pass by their quarters.
Uh...
Many of the Earth's men have made good slaves. Fine slaves.
Yes.
Some are rebellious.
Make X Day your summer destination. There's a beach party every Wednesday.
Uh, so, um, make sure...
There'll be a beef parlor in the basement. Don't forget about that, Dr. Howell.
The basement? You mean the...
The beef park in the basement.
The Alamo basement?
Um...
Well, not the year that Santa Anna and his mighty crew brought Davy Cricket and the rest of the fortune hunters to their feet.
And, um, we were talking about, uh, John Wayne and his role in the movie Chisholm a while...
John Wayne was a fad.
Oh, shit.
His first name was Marion.
Yeah!
Marion Michael Morrison.
I installed mirrors in his bedroom.
You installed two-way mirrors in his pad in Brentwood. Yes, I know. Well, uh...
But he was in that movie, uh, Chisholm, which is about John Chisholm, who you know has played a significant role in the Lincoln era.
Lincoln County Land Wars, in which, uh, Billy Bonney, aka The Kid, was such a major player.
He had a notch on his, uh, gun for every man he plugged and sent to me as a major.
And a bunch of nachos under his belt, because he was a 22-cent...
So they had to send his friend, Sheriff Pat Garrett, to kill him, just like in that movie.
You know, you know all about that.
Well, the guy who was the bad guy, who was sitting back there pulling the strings, was John Chisholm, wealthy rancher.
But John Wayne, Marion Michael Morrison, was in a movie where he plays Chisholm as a good guy.
Sort of like an ultra-Republican who is, uh, simply trying to scour the country of these bad influences like The Kid and Garrett and all these Mexicans and so forth.
So, uh, that's the movie Chisholm.
Hmm.
Yeah.
Chisholm! John Chisholm!
Anybody ever see that one?
Johnny Humor was rebel and he robed to the grave!
Is that Nick Adams? The Rebel?
In your mind you thought it was dirty, but man, it's not so dirty.
But after he played the Rebel, Nick Adams went to Toho Studios for his unforgettable role in War of the Gargantuas.
And he fought Frankenstein!
Yes, in Frankenstein Must Be Destroyed.
You know how Frankenstein got there? Why he became giant and everything?
Didn't the Nazis dig his heart up out of, uh...
The Nazis took his heart from Frankenstein's original laboratory.
It was transferred in mid-ocean to a Japanese submarine and taken to the city of Hiroshima where they were just operating on it when there was an unfortunate flash in the sky and sleeting radiation which caused the heart itself to grow.
And it was transferred into a giant jumbo form of Frankenstein monster.
Yeah, it's kind of a Japanese giant baby Frankenstein monster.
Clumped it...
Oh my...
...Budded off of its own heart.
Then it fights Baragon too.
Uh, I mean, uh, you can't ask for more than that.
But the most interesting moment of War of the Gargantuas...
Wasn't it called Frankenstein Conquers the World?
Yes, Frankenstein Conquers the World. It's true.
But War of the Gargantuas was originally conceived as a sequel to this picture.
Oh, he left.
I'm afraid he didn't care to hear about Toho revisited.
His card ran out.
But you know, the thing is, the Gargantuas in the movie, one of them was supposed to be a descendant of these Frankensteinian giants.
Oh, I didn't get that.
That's because in the American version that was all cut out.
But in the original version and in the American version...
That explains why they're kind of humanoid and Frank...
Yeah.
...Japo-Frankensteinian.
The, uh, it starts with a ship going through a store... a cloudy, foggy ocean, you know.
And there's the guy up in the pilot house.
He's wearing a little white hat like Gilligan wore on Gilligan's Island.
And the skipper also wore one of these hats.
And in fact, the director, Inchiro Honda, while directing Gojira and the second Gojira film known in America as Gigantus the Fire Monster...
...also wore such a little hat.
Hey, look on my head, Doctor.
Well, what do you know about that?
So, the guy is there. He's sweating. He's piloting the ship through the fog.
He's wearing a hat and he starts saying,
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
And you pan down his body and there's a little tentacle around his ankle.
And that's why he's saying,
Oh, oh, oh.
And you pan over the tentacle and it gets larger and larger and it goes out the door.
And then you pan across the deck. It gets larger and larger. It's as thick as a barrel.
Finally, you pan off the ship.
And an enormous octopus has grabbed the ship.
S.O.S. We are grabbed by an enormous octopus.
Then suddenly, improbably, up out of the depths rears the big hairy, naugahyde-covered giant who grabs a hold of the octopus.
And they have a terrific tussle.
Now he is being attacked by a huge hairy giant.
But then he trounces the octopus.
But then he turns on the ship and starts to bash and smash the ship.
And that's the end of that.
And that's the end of that transmission from sea.
Well, it just gets worse from there, oh best beloved.
Ladies and gentlemen, especially during the scene which introduces the song,
The Words Get Stuck in My Throat.
You may remember that song.
What?
The Words Get Stuck in My Throat.
Somebody better do the high mic.
I've only heard the Devo cover.
Well, that's the song that...
I've heard Boogie Boy sing that.
It is sung in the War of the Gargantuas at the airport.
There's a cool airport lounge.
And a lady is singing the song when suddenly a grotesque giant grabs her,
chews her up and spits out her dress which lands with a plop in front of the camera.
At the end of having sung, The Words Get Stuck in My Throat.
Goodness.
Yes, you can see this deathless classic of cinema.
The Devo's picked that weird obscure song to cover on...
It's on their very first album.
It's rare not heard everywhere.
It's seen in that movie first before Devo ever...
laid a tentacle on it.
Wow.
Now, Devo should do the Mothra song someday.
Mosura, Mosura.
I knew he could do that.
Mosura.
Friday Jones could sing that song.
Yes, I know.
You told me.
It's pretty hot.
You'd think she was too little women about this high.
The Ailinas, the fairies from the land of Mosura.
Yeah, he's a moth.
He's a big moth.
He starts out as a caterpillar.
I thought he was kind of stupid looking even when I was a kid and saw the first Mothra movie.
But he's big.
He's a big moth.
So don't even turn on a flashlight or this huge moth will come swooping down.
Crush the life out of you.
Kill not the moth nor the butterfly.
For the last judgment draweth nigh.
Princess, will you know what that means about all the spiders in the bathroom?
Oh, no.
No.
See, the best part about being ruptured by the saucers is that you'll no longer need bathrooms.
You'll no longer need the Jankum huffing chambers.
You can still have them if you want them, right?
But you will have the option to use wormholes instead.
You mean werewands?
That would be a tight fit.
I'm not sure what you're getting at.
You remember that Stephen King novel about...
About the guys who are off in the woods and they can't go to the toilet and horrible worms are investigating their nether regions and...
The program is coming to a close, but we've been talking about cosmic stuff all night and that just made me think of the classic song by the Toilet Bowl Cleaners who I think need to play next day one of these days.
You should contact them.
They should.
Because they will teach us how to poop into a wormhole.
Yeah, and poop water towel could open for the toilet bowl cleaners.
Yeah.
Too bad that you didn't think about that before.
Yeah, and it's upon us, like the Philistines on Samson.
So thank you very much for being guests on my program tonight, fellas.
Oh yeah, sure. I hope we're able to clear up some of the popular misconceptions.
The pleasure was ours.
And we'll be broadcasting from the Saucers next week, of course.
And we'll be doing Bobcasts also from the meeting place and campground itself, even from the landing field.
Well, those are pre-recorded shows.
More information can be found since only about three people ever show up for those.
Okay, I was just trying to keep up the mystique, but you now blew it.
Well, I'm sorry, because it's the visible show.
Yeah, more information can be found at subgenius.com.
It's educational.
And we suggest you go there right now.
Well, we're not suggesting that. That would be a call to action.
Oh, okay. Take that back. Zip it.
But...
It is out there. It's one of those things that's out there.
It's educational. It's not prurient.
So we've got a special episode of Crap Radio coming up next here.
That's prurient.
It's a thing that if you're interested, you can go. Just like the Starwood Festival. If you're interested, you can go there and read about it.
There is a lot of information out there about these festivals that a lot of people...
StarwoodFestival.com
But a lot of you guys are going to continue in your benighted ignorance.
Because you won't make these simple investigations which are made so easy by today's electronic culture.
There are things that you'll never find online, such as knowing that the Starwood Festival is the way that I met Reverend Stang and the way that Reverend Stang met me.
A lot of really timeless love stories have sprung out of these...
The virtuous pagans.
Yeah. Come on, baby. Let's make out.
And have some more special pale ale.
Oh, Senator, my breath is not good enough for me.
That is beyond the pale.
Yes, this is actual archival footage of the love song of J. Alfred Stang.
J. Fred Stang.
This is how it first went down, folks.
You know, it's true. Women like a bad boy. And there was no boy better at that time.
Yes, yes. Women do like a bad boy.
And there he is.
The baddest fellow of all.
Is that Leroy Brown?
Mm-hmm. And Ivan Stang.
Yeah, I'm not a nerd. I'm a bad...
He's a bad, bad boy.
I'm a man. M-A-N. Man.
Don't shoot me. I'm a man.
I'm not a nerd. I'm a cool, bad guy.
Oh, I'm not a bad wizard. I'm just a bad man, my dear.
I'm a tough subgenius.
Yeah, a real tough subgenius.
I... Bob gives me...
The strength of my abnormality.
You see that pipe? I dare you to knock it out from between my teeth. I double dare you.
You know, there's the whole concept of famous last words.
Gentlemen, gentlemen, please. Can't we all just get along?
You know, there's the whole famous last words, like the last words that somebody says.
There's also the famous last words that somebody hears right before disaster. Like,
I dare you to knock this pipe out of my mouth, coming from Bob.
Yeah. Right.
Famous last words that you hear, not famous last words that you say. Well, it would... Nothing bad about that.
It would happen to Bob. Bob would get off scot-free in that encounter.
If I'm wrong, then let lightning strike me dead!
So if I'm wrong, let lightning strike all of you dead.
And may you all be crushed by a falling meteor right now if I'm mistaken.
Gee, who could have predicted that?
Who could have predicted?
Well, I'm glad you missed me, huh?
So, uh...
It's been fun, folks. And it's time for us to shuffle off this mortal coil. We'll see you on the other side.
This has been a very special episode of Synesthesia on WCSB. Stay tuned for crap radio.
Thank you again. We'll be back next week. From the Saucers.
Everybody shuffle. Shuffle off the buckles.