The Soul Genius Power of Slack
What foolishness.
True.
No.
Yes.
Without question.
No.
Not to the soul.
Ah, yes, dear friends, this is Hour of Slack,
number 1,080, and I am your host and prayer partner,
Reverend Ivan Stang.
This week, I got a couple of emails saying,
when are you going to start broadcasting Hour of Slack again?
I guess the ancient reruns that I've been using to save time
while working on the Subgenius History course with MaybeLogic.org
were so ancient that people didn't recognize any of the voices
and really didn't understand that those were hours of Slack
that were used to broadcast Hour of Slack.
They were hearing, it's just that they were hours of Slack
from like 1982, before there was an Hour of Slack.
Friends, it was me and Philo and Dr. Howell and Puzzlin and so forth.
It's just that we were babies, like most of you are now,
in our early 20s.
I don't really believe that we were ever so young either.
But tonight, we go back to being old, that is new.
This is...
Part of a five-hour epic live show we recorded on January 10th
at KPFA Studios in Berkeley
with over-the-edge host Izzy Isn't,
heard in the background here, of Negative Land,
and Puzzling Evidence host Doug Wellman of Wellman Headland.
These sound more like the Hour of Slack you're used to,
although they are not actually that.
Subgenius Doctors participating include Dr. Howell,
Puzzling Evidence, Philo Drummond,
yours truly,
Reverend John Shirley,
Gary Gabrofan,
Michael Pepe,
Princess We Are Go,
Chaos McBobcat Drummond,
Phineas Narco,
K-Rob,
somebody named Walter,
the uber-goober-booby-baby,
and Bishop Joey from the First Church of the Last Laugh.
Some of us got there late, friends,
so when this annual subgenius business meeting begins,
the only stockholders present are Izzy Isn't,
Puzzling Evidence,
Cyberpunk author, Reverend John Shirley,
Dr. Gary Gabrofan, Phineas Narco,
and Bishop Joey,
also known as Ed Holmes of the San Francisco Mime Troupe.
The music in the background right now is from the new Amino Acids album due out June 2007.
The Amino Acids album called Humanity Will Fall Like Pins.
You can look at the Amino Acids album, the Amino Acids album, and the Amino Acids album called Humanity Will Fall Like Pins.
I may not play all five hours of the five-hour show in order over the next five weeks,
but until my subgenius history courses over on the 25th,
I'm still ball to the wall.
And so, onward, subgenius soldiers marching as to Walmart.
This is Operation Experiment.
These men arrived here on X-Day minus 60.
It has taken them the full two months to get ready.
Today is X-Day.
It is now H-hour minus 59 minutes.
There is less than an hour left.
There can be no margin for error.
There can be no second chance.
Well, good hello.
Hello, everyone.
This is not Barb Golden in Crack-A-Don, who is usually here the first Thursday of every month at midnight.
Ouch.
And it is I.
It is I, the over-the-edge guy.
Izzy isn't.
But it's not quite over the edge either.
It's a special unscheduled broadcast of over-the-edge,
and the subgenius, the Church of the Subgenius Foundation, Incorporated,
are all here, and we're all going to do five hours together, all together, right here.
And that's what we're doing.
So it's not this and it's not that.
It's both.
To a place where men satisfy their bloodlust by hunting human quarry.
All right, gentlemen.
Ready for testing.
Put on your headphones and pick up a microphone.
Bob.
I love Bob.
That's Ed Holmes of the Church of the Subgenius.
Bob.
Now, I've decided unilaterally to name this show the title of this show,
The New Year's Revolution Show.
Now what does that mean?
That means we have to spin around in a Gregorian manner.
Well, according to my script, it will be explained later on.
Ok.
I don't know what...
Where...
Where is Dr. Hal?
Dr. Hal, we buried him, I think, last week.
Ladies and gentlemen, we'd like, we regret to inform you
that Dr. Hal has passed away almost a week ago today.
And he will no longer grace the big fat chairs of the subgenius.
Well, actually, we did bring him in because he wasn't smelling that bad
since it's been very cold outside lately.
So we got that cold snap.
Oh, I see him, yes.
Yeah, so we just propped him in the thing.
And because he's such a motor mouth...
I like that.
He's still talking.
I like it.
We just have to push the microphone real close.
We're trying to get a microphone jacked just right into his jaw.
I like the glazed look.
Yeah.
Uh-huh.
So we can squeeze...
We can squeeze...
We can squeeze another show out of Dr. Hal.
His cooling carcass.
Just a few electrical shocks.
Apply a few electrical shocks,
and there'll be an automatic reaction, in his case, talking.
And Gabrofram is here with his jumper cables of love.
Meh!
Meh.
What happened to...
Where's Bug Girl?
Oh, no, Bug Girl is not coming, is she?
You'll see her in a bit.
Not until she sees you, Don.
Oh, that's so funny.
It's my understanding that Reverend Stang, the iconic sacred scribe of the Church of the
Subgenius, will be here.
He'll be here.
And even right now, he's listening.
He's frustrated.
And he's warm in his things.
He's trying to...
He's wishing he could be warm.
He's wishing.
He's...
You know, with Reverend Stang, a wish becomes reality.
Very easily, because he has so much slack.
He has three pairs at the cleaner.
He has so many slacks and so much slack in Cleveland.
Is he still in Cleveland?
Yes.
Oh, boy.
Why?
Why is anybody still in Cleveland?
I understand it's the most violent city in America.
Really?
Yeah.
But see, the reason is that the Reverend Stang is there.
He sucks all the slack from everybody else.
And there's an umbrella of peace around him.
But everybody else, in consequence, you know, stresses up and they begin to throttle one another.
Well, there it is.
He's a slack sucker.
Okay, well, so...
Okay, so...
So we're really funny now.
All right.
Okay, Bishop Joey's here, and he's answering any of your religious and or sexual questions.
So you can call in at 848.
That's all.
That's all the numbers we've got.
We had a big budget cut here at KPFA, so we had to lose four of our phone numbers.
So we're just down to 848.
Just dial 848.
And wait.
And John Shirley is here to answer any of your science fiction questions.
All right.
The sexual and religious questions have...
How big was Paul Anderson's pole?
It was still really a dick.
It's one of the mysteries.
Religion and sexuality have converged or have, you know, it has shown it.
It has dropped its pants this year because of Haggard, right?
And people like that.
Haggard?
So my question...
My question to you is...
Yes.
You know, where is your particular theological domain with respect to this emerging explosion
of self-exposure sexually amongst the religious leaders of our country?
It's under my bed.
The domain is under my bed.
I feel there is no God.
You feel.
Yeah, exactly.
I feel.
But to feel is not enough to be...
To realize.
To feel.
Expressively, intellectually, and convincingly appropriate.
Feeling?
Feeling is...
Feelings are no longer shorthand for your expression of a religious and or sexual congress,
which is 110th time I've been going around.
Well, one of my samples says feeling is believing.
Feeling is believing.
Dr. Johnson said I refute it thus, and he kicked it.
He kicked the stone.
Thus.
And it hurt his foot.
And then he said, I believe, because that hurts.
That's too much of a coincidence for comfort, sir.
I know, but you can't expect anything less here on KPFA.
In your ear.
You're trying to go to bed.
You're trying to go to sleep.
And somebody's left the radio on.
And you reach for the dial, and it won't turn off.
And your radio's stuck.
And the clock is ticking.
And you're trying to get some sleep, because tomorrow you've got to get up and face another day.
At your grueling, grim, boring job.
But here you are, stuck listening to the radio.
Listening to us.
So, join us.
If it hurts, you believe.
Yes.
Believe.
I have a sexual question.
I have a cat.
A female cat.
And she eats too much.
And the reason she eats too much is because she likes to fight all the other cats in the neighborhood.
Uh-huh.
And...
This is a sexual...
That's what worries me.
And...
Here.
He's listening to his delayed broadcast.
He wants to hear himself.
Oh, I see.
Okay.
Yeah, the whole station now, you know, is on a delay.
Didn't used to be, but it is now.
So we can't see him?
We can't see him.
And, uh...
We can't say beep or beep or beep or beep.
And, uh, she has a computer.
Or, beep or beep.
Or, beep.
Because we have a dump button, but I promise not to use it.
Oh, wow.
Oh, we did.
Yeah.
So when you call...
Listen to me, people.
When you call...
When...
Don't...
Don't listen to your radio.
Because...
Don't listen to your computer.
Don't listen to your radio.
Don't listen to your...
Listen to your telephone.
Because in your telephone's earpiece is the only real time...
Listen to me.
That exists now.
Listen to me only.
Turn down your radio.
Turn down your computer.
Turn up your radio.
If you try to converse with us with those up...
Throw your computer out.
...you will sound drunk.
Throw it up!
Throw away your computer.
You will sound drunk if you attempt to follow the delayed broadcast while calling.
Drink heavily.
Thank you.
Please don't speak into the microphones.
That's too much of a voice.
Think into the microphones.
Oh, my God.
Only think into them.
We're gonna stink into the microphones.
These microphones are so sensitive that they feel insulted if you talk into them.
We're still...
Stinking into the microphone right now is Dr. Hal.
We're trying to get Dr. Hal jacked into the microphone.
I just want to get this over early.
You know, the stang and the hal.
Let's try to get the show out of the door by 1230.
And Phineas Narco's a tape.
He's loopy.
Phineas is loopy.
Looped.
He's loopy.
And that information is the number you can call to find out about this coming St. Stupid's
Day parade, number 29.
Yeah, that's coming right up.
That's right.
April 1st will be the 29th annual St. Stupid's Day parade starting at noon at the Poynty
building in San Francisco going up Columbus Avenue to either Washington Square Park or
Joe DiMaggio's bathroom.
So, get ready.
Put it in your calendar and be prepared to go.
We're going to march once again in honor of St. Stupid, a little known St. 442, 443,
513, and 747, the parking meters.
I bet you didn't know that.
You're not Catholic, are you?
I didn't think so.
That's April 1st.
Is that April 1st?
I mean, is that when the parade is?
I thought it would be April 1st.
It could be April 1st.
I'm not sure.
Noon at the Poynty building.
So, if you want more information about that, go to ststupid.com.
That's S-A-I-N-T-S-T-U-P-I, S-T-U-P-I, whatever.
We know.
That's the way it is.
It's like a...
I don't know it, but you can't figure it out.
Google it.
Google it yourself.
Oh, yeah?
Well, Google this.
What?
Let's Google this.
Google this.
What?
Let's Google this.
Google this.
Where even an innocent corpse can find no peace.
Of course, we'll keep searching.
And now the pretty part of the show.
That's so much better.
Now maybe you can get to sleep,
because we'll be playing some easy listening trance music
for you to get into your theta state.
That's right.
That's so soothing.
It's the face of the new fascism.
It's soothing fascism.
The soothing sounds of fascism tonight.
...deadly worldwide conspiratorial gangster computer god communism...
Try that number.
Data follows.
Distance, 486 miles.
Height, 50.2 miles.
Speed, 5 miles per second.
Something bad has happened.
Just showing me.
So you can't use all those recorded instructions on phone fidelity.
Those are all gone now.
Say good day.
That is correct.
You could technically still have phone fidelity.
Yeah.
I know.
I'm not sure if I'm going to be able to use it.
You're not going to be able to use it.
The delay doesn't really affect that.
It's just that if you don't listen to your telephone, you won't hear yourself.
Take a six-pack of cans.
I'm holding a big bottle of liquor.
Estimated time of arrival at contact point, 1 minute 58 seconds.
.
I'm hearing his...
And co-creator of the Church of the Subgenius,
Philo Drummond.
Check, check.
Dry old trumpet.
Dry old trumpet?
Dry old trumpet is his goyle.
He's a dry old trumpet.
He's been pump-dried for the last time, hopefully.
He's a crusty old trumpet.
He's 90.
He's the Karl Rove of the Church of the Subgenius.
Drummond.
Now, one...
58 right.
Let fire control.
Fire control alerted, sir.
Two grains of sand fall out now and then.
Young Martin also says that he saw something worse.
La la la la.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
21.
On a quiet summer day in Houston, Texas,
unbeknownst to the rest of the world,
a great scientific operation was performed.
A squid was eating dough in a polyethylene bag.
On that day, a human being was given a shape that would last forever.
A very repellent shape.
When may we expect you?
In 30 seconds.
A shape that would never age,
but decay.
Over and off.
And an event had taken place that is soon to affect all of humanity.
Something that he insists was his brother.
But we know that his brother is dead.
We also know that he is not lying in his coffin.
Someone in this village is practicing witchcraft.
The Reverend Stang will be here.
Have fun.
Faith.
You want to play it?
Yeah, this is not your usual camp followers meeting here.
Ed's going to try to play it now.
We've got the big wig himself here coming tonight.
Oh, he's doing really good.
Mr. Ivan Stang, owner and operator of the Subgenius Church Foundation of America.
But Ed and I will be gone by the time Stang gets here.
You guys were gone, gone, gone years ago.
Oh.
So why are we here?
Why did we drive all the way from our far-off homes and the nice warm beds?
Probably dating from the acid test.
For the New Year's Revolution show.
Oh, that's right.
Come on, get into it.
What if I refuse to even participate in the New Year?
We have a whole new chance here.
I'm...
We have a...
You know, this is the last year.
You have to understand that...
It has been announced.
The Church of the Subgenius has announced that the end of the world will take place on Thursday, July 5th, 2007.
And in preparation for the fulfillment of this doomsday prophecy,
the Church is requesting that all of its members participate in a festival with rock concerts and blasphemous rituals
taking place in upstate New York during the final weekend before the arrival of the apocalypse.
Oh, they're always doing that.
They do that every year.
But, see, there are many other people who make predictions about the end of the world.
They give up too easily.
Huh.
They say the end of the...
There was a guy in 1986 or so who wrote a book explaining that the end of the world would come in 1988.
And he sold five million of them.
And it didn't come.
And so he wrote another book saying it would come in 1989.
He sold a lot of those, too.
He was that much persistent.
And then he gave up.
The Church of the Subgenius never gives up predicting the end of the world.
Even after the end of the world, the Subgenius will predict it.
Well, if you go to the edge of the universe and throw a rock, what do you hit?
So after the end of the world, you know, there's got to be another end, another end, and another end.
Well, there's the Gardall Shield.
First of all, no one ever accounts for the Gardall Shield.
And there's a novel by John Shirley called The Other End.
But I won't promote it this time.
The Other End?
The Other End.
What's that, the check?
It's my alternative.
Alternative?
Apocalypse.
What?
A novel of alternative apocalypse.
We're all here.
You know, every time I look for a John Shirley book at my local bookstore, I don't see one.
Well, you've got to look in the cheesy section, in the cheesy paperback section.
Or go to a better bookstore.
A better class of bookstore might help also.
I look for those books by Lloyd St. Alcorn.
I don't know if you remember those.
Oh, that's a name that resonates.
It resonates with cobwebs.
Dr. David Meyer, I believe, wrote several terrible books under the pen name of Lloyd St. Alcorn.
But it was slack because he got paid to write terrible books.
That's right.
But he got paid lousy money.
I get paid lousy money to write good books.
So he had more slack than me because he got paid the same money to write bad books, which is easier.
Edgar Wisenant made himself a nice packet of money with a book assuring him that he was going to be a good writer.
He was telling everyone that 1988 was the end of the world.
He had 88 reasons for his insurance.
And he sold 4 million copies to a gullible public.
And in 1989, he came out with a book in which he said he had made some mistakes, but it was going to end in 1989.
You know, that kind of persistence is admirable.
Elizabeth Clare Prophet said that 1990 was going to be the end of the year.
The Gulf War broke out and religious enthusiasts got on their phones to the radio stations saying that Armageddon would be in 1991.
Well, everybody I know died in 2007.
You're mixing up the past and the future again.
You know, Gary's problem is that he thinks that the future is the past because he lives outside of time.
Gary lives in the eternal.
He's got one foot in eternity and he keeps wobbling back and forth and he kind of gets them mixed up.
And he can see the future.
He thinks it's the past.
He spins around.
He doesn't know the difference.
But spending all this time in my own tent made out of my own skin, wouldn't you think that I would be in my own reality?
Too soon for what?
Absolutely.
You're spinning.
You're like an object being spun on a lathe and gradually ground down into a shape that can only be imagined.
I need more time.
Well, here I have a question for you, John.
This is more KPFA-like.
More time for what?
And I found this here on the floor of KPFA.
I can't believe it.
That's where all my cousins come from.
It says, what are the ties between immigrants from a Middle Eastern country and an African American born in South Carolina?
Is that a reference to Obama or something?
I have no idea.
The end of the world's coming and you're just talking about this stuff.
Trivial.
It's a mystery.
It's a side one cut to dawn.
Questions are bound on the floor here.
That's how desperate we are for questions from the great world.
We're scrabbling around on the floor like a crack addict.
Good.
You want questions?
You got questions.
Why can't you amend your revelation and move it up to early September?
Followers of Nostradamus claim that according to the French seer, the end of the world came in July 1999.
We're perfectly willing to adjust to circumstances.
Hey, can we have September 11th early this year?
The supreme moment of the universe has already happened.
That is a grim joke.
Jesus said this generation should not pass away until the fulfillment of his prediction of the end times was fulfilled.
And I don't know if anybody noticed 1,998 or so years ago that it didn't come about.
So all these people predict the end of the world.
It doesn't happen.
The church of the subgenius predicts it much more diligently than everybody else.
June 7, 1989 is when it really happened on the 1, 23, 45 AM universal time.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9.
We lived through it.
I have it on tape.
It really happened.
Gary, your output in the amp is a bit high for that mic.
Okay.
That's because Ed's playing it now.
See, no hands and it's still loud.
I've got a list of end of the world predictions here.
Play something really loud.
St. Augustine said it was coming in the year 1,000.
That's it?
That's as loud as you'll ever get?
No, we can play as loud as you want.
That's pretty good there, I think.
Pretty good right there?
Yeah.
Okay.
Go to it, Ed.
It's your turn.
Wow.
Here we go.
We'll do it.
Damn, good guys.
We've got an GOD video sang by Ravel.
Now, watch it if you want a train reaction.
The song is called INSTAumatic on還有?
Come on, the views should spread all over.
Jungploy Company, followed by marché
tree and hit Isaac square in the capooter.
He did, and Isaac Newton predicted the end of the world for 1733.
If you would like to attempt to speak to the Subgenius Foundation Church of America, please
call us at...
Don't say hello when your phone stops ringing, you're on the air, and don't listen to your
radio, please.
In 1736, William Whiston of Cambridge announced that the end of the world was about to commence.
Panic-stricken Londoners headed for high places to escape the floods, he predicted.
None of them came.
Didn't anybody ask, how does he know?
Immanuel Swedenborg, who conversed frequently with angels, was certain that 1757 was the
date.
Oh, hey, that reminds me, we're supposed to have Swedenborg breads for dinner tonight.
We cut the pancreas out of philosophers and dip them in cornmeal.
They're delicious.
The thyroid is supposed to be especially delectable if you get a mathematician.
Nietzsche's is real bitter, though, you don't like bitter, you like Nietzsche.
Oh, everyone has their own little Nietzsche these days.
Yeah.
So if you want to join in on a frivolity and a clever wordplay, just dial...
...Mavus, Gerber.
Come on, you can do it.
I think that when they were trying to say a Freud to live and too young to die.
There are people around the world who really still believe that if you eat somebody's heart
who is courageous, you will be courageous.
So if you eat their brains...
Eat somebody prettier than you are.
Eat somebody smarter than you are.
Eat somebody stronger than you are.
Well, I've been nibbling a lot.
But eat somebody.
I've been nibbling a lot.
Whatever you do.
But eat somebody.
Are we allowed to say that on the air?
Eat somebody?
Yeah, if it's a song.
You gotta eat somebody on your bond.
But not their lungs.
Got any recipes?
So cannibalism's coming back, we hear.
So if you got some recipes.
It will come back.
When the world famine comes, my friend, which I have been predicting, the American famine.
The great calling began.
Imagine a famine in the United States.
What would that be like?
Who would we eat first?
Well, we'd eat the Welsh rabbits made from Volkswagens.
There are people who've eaten cars.
There are, bit by bit, like chunk by chunk.
There was a guy who cut up a car and ate it.
It took him several years.
Did you ever see The Metal-Eating Bird?
The cartoon, The Metal-Eating Bird?
You've seen it, haven't you?
No.
I don't watch television.
Well, Doug Wellman has seen The Metal-Eating Bird.
Oh, whip it out.
You got it on tape?
Whip it out.
Charles Russell, founder of a group later known as the Witnesses of Jehovah.
Does that sound familiar?
He said that Christ had returned invisibly in the year 1874.
There was no way of proving he was wrong.
But the girls all knew that somebody were staring at them.
They were staring at them in their gym locker room.
Yeah, when they went wee-wee.
That was Jesus.
The guy with the beard.
But, you know, in fact, somebody pointed out to me today that if Jesus is always watching you, we are Jesus's porn.
Oh, man.
That's right.
That's what's disturbing.
We're going to porn with Jesus Watchers.
Yes, and we're Bob's commercials.
Well, Russell, what is your definition of an actor?
That's what your relatives do.
So where are all the rest of all the important guests on this show?
I think it is something.
Look behind the...
The prop bush.
Yes.
Oh, they're just lazy.
They think five hours, no hurry, no hurry.
Little do they know how much of a hurry we're in here.
We've got to get five hours cranked out here in 20 minutes.
They've been verbally arrested, I suspect.
Hey, that's going to drive me home in a minute.
In a minute.
I'm just going to drop you off at Pescadero.
Because I'm going to be in Pescadero all weekend.
So if you can find Bishop Joey in Pescadero this weekend, you'll win the prize.
Are we strong?
We're strong.
All of us.
I'm just going to rent Bishop Joey and ride him on the beach out at San Gregorio myself.
Rent to Bishop Joey.
Yeah.
Jehovah's Witnesses predicted the end of the world for 1975.
When they come to your door and they're trying to convince you they've got some inside information.
1975.
Then again, 1984.
They said that was going to be the end of the world.
When they come to your house, ask them if they remember that.
And if you want an alternative apocalypse, go to www.signsofwitness.com.
Where is my website of alternative apocalypse?
Apocalypse?
Apocalypse is related to apocalypse.
It's when you can't say apocalypse.
I've had a little experience with apuckerlips.
Well, apocalypse only happens back east.
Apocalypse now.
They have sodas here.
And they have pop.
Back there.
I pop my lips now.
Yeah.
Apuckerlips now.
This is a true thing.
Apocalypse.
In 1983, as the residents of Calcutta, a small town 30 miles north of Rome,
prepared for the apocalypse.
They were invited to their annual procession honoring a holy relic.
A shocking announcement from the parish priest put a damper on festivities.
The relic has vanished.
What was that relic?
The lopped off body parts of a certain messiah.
That is, it was the foreskin of Jesus.
It was alleged to be, I'm not making this up, the foreskin of Jesus supposedly found
in India in, no, in Calcutta, not Calcutta, in 1557.
And a series of miracles soon followed finding the holy foreskin.
A weak storm, it's perfumed, missed.
Well in fact it has not turned up and they, and the people of Calcutta claim that it was
stolen by the Vatican.
Holy foreskin.
Who didn't like the holy foreskin being out there in their church and they were embarrassed
by it.
They were afraid someone was going to clone it.
Okay.
There has been discussion of cloning the holy foreskin.
Holy foreskin.
Here, I've got mine here in my wallet.
Let's try to clone it and see if it works for me.
I'm Jewish.
Lines of pilgrims stretched from the church doors beyond the walls of the fortress town
to see the holy foreskin.
I think we should stretch Bishop Joey's over this African drum head.
Oh.
Can you use it as a shower cap?
The Pope is using it.
It's a cap and it makes it that weird.
hat more snuggly on it.
Oh, the skateboarder's one.
There's an image to conjure for you,
ladies and gentlemen. If you can join
in here in the blasphemy, we got
Blasphemy 49 cents a pound. It's available
right now here on your radio, so call
and contribute
your blasphemy right here. Two famous
religious figures in America who were
anti-gay turned out to be gay
this year. Haggard and another guy, his name
I've forgotten. Merle?
Merle did not. Merle
is the last guy to turn out to be gay.
You're going to ruin my
reverence.
I'm down with gays,
but I don't want Merle to be gay.
Merle Haggard may not be gay.
Merle's into truckers, I hear.
Mother truckers.
What I want to know is,
when is the Bishop Joey going to
come out?
Bishop Joey did come out.
He came out last year and got
all wet, so he went back in.
This could be
winter for another six years.
Ladies and gentlemen, he has arrived.
There's no point in putting it off
anymore. He is
in the building. The Reverend
Stang? Yes, and he is about
to join us here on
the radio. The sacred
scribe of the Church of the
Subgenius has arrived. He is in the
building. Our exclusive New Year's
Revolution show.
The alternative apocalypse
won't be long
now. Of the Reverend Stang. Wait for the
next episode.
I washed
the bottom of my shoes every time I
kick Philo's butt.
Don't say
hello. When your
phone stops ringing, you're on the air.
Just go ahead.
That's our policy. And we're not
changing it now. I'm
hoping that Vice President
Cheney will show up tonight.
Right now he's in the bunker
changing into his thong.
A lot of people saw that thong
a couple years ago. Burning Man, Chick Cheney.
He showed up at the fashion
show at Burning Man a couple years ago.
And he was
conduced by
Dr. Hal, who was emceeing the fashion
show, to get
loose and party down.
And it wound up that Dick Cheney
was wearing a thong.
There were
40,000 people at the time at Burning Man.
Immediately, 20,000 people
left. And they took their
foreskins with them. And they took all their
foreskins with them.
Foreskin, cowcandy.
It isn't the one. You're still gonna get wet.
Kitty.
And baby.
I'm hoping this is it.
The sacred lily.
Uh-oh. Infant Philo's here now.
Maybe we could trade
infant Philo to the flying saucers
for a burrito.
A big burrito. One for me.
Not for all of us.
Clear the field.
We're monitoring Philo's child.
We're in constant contact with Philo's
child.
She's as good as on the
planet of the...
Farewell. I'm coming down right now.
Over and out.
See?
Play, double zombies.
Pretty soft.
The Reverend Ivan Stang is in the front.
He's fopping.
I don't know who has the fropp.
We better hand it over fast.
I'm fropless.
The energy.
The force packed in the rock itself.
Oh yeah. We should run home and get it.
We almost turned around and stopped.
Ha ha ha ha ha.
So 8484425
talked to a totally naked
Bishop Joey. That's right. Bishop Joey.
Oh my god, he is naked!
Seminal and secular head of the First Church of the Last Laugh
World's Fast-growing, Snack of Religion, 100% of his dog
religion, Light of Religion, One Holy Day a Year, and today is
an April 1st. He's here and he's naked.
And he's sitting right here and he can talk to you.
Somebody get a sanitary wipe
for that chair. No, it's okay.
It'll clean up really nice when we
hose down the studio at the end of the
show at 5 in the morning.
So talk to Bishop Joey now
before he is not talkable.
Any questions you have...
What is he doing to the microphone?
Oh, let me rub it.
Let me rub it right here. I got a little itch. Oh, I got an itch.
Let me scratch it right... Oh, does
that feel good. So, talk to
a totally naked Bishop Joey. That's right.
And any question, any thing,
any subject, I don't know.
I got an answer for you.
After careful study of the Bible,
Reverend
William Miller thought that
the end was 1834.
Tuesday.
He changed his mind and decided it was 1836.
Then he recalculated it and found that it
was 1843 in the month of
April. There used to be six to choose from.
This was to prove one of the biggest events of the end time
calendar. When April
came and Miller set to work on a new
date. Miller's brave
new choice, March 21st,
1844, for the end of the world.
The Millerites waited in droves
and high vantage points in special ascension
robes for the expected
end. Hysteria reigned.
People sold up farms and homes.
But still, frustratingly,
the end did not come. They were not
persistent. The Church of the Subgenius
will not give up on the end of the world.
Order your end of the world now.
We will
specially deliver it to you.
That will be done.
Personalized.
I can take care of it.
When would you like the end of the world?
We'll deliver.
It is closed society.
45 caliber end of the world.
Oh, it's magic.
Everything we don't understand is magic.
Hold on.
I show Panteneve outbound
at 1205 Zulu.
Providence control wants to know where is he.
Panteneve 262.
Who's got him?
Panteneve?
...
A prophet in Latvia predicted
the end of the world for 1920.
His followers believed with such fervor
that they dug graves and waited
beside them for the end.
Some may still be there.
The computer got to control you.
...
... ...
Mine she has, and in my mind she was mine, too.
No, she's...
All those long legs.
I'm tired of Humphrey Bogart scaring me, so...
I have to take on Grace Jones, my alien lover.
Grace Jones.
If he's your sweetheart's sweetheart, then the end of the world is nigh.
Because there's no justice, my friend.
I don't know about any of that, but I know who my lover is.
And she's a wonderful priestess.
She's a goddess.
She's a teacher.
She is just magical.
Yeah, uh-huh.
Well, she...
Go ahead.
You know, if you make of her a magical object and put her picture on the wall
and prostrate yourself before it, she becomes magical for you.
Well, she is actually on the wall, not a picture.
She is actually hanging on the wall right now.
Oh, dear.
Just like in...
In the police.
In the police, no?
Oops, sorry.
Sounds uncomfortable anyway.
You didn't thumbtack her to the wall, did you?
She's skinny enough you could use thumbtacks.
Oh, she's still alive.
Yeah, but don't forget, she might actually be magic.
Yeah, Grace Jones, you know, there is a kind of Aoife sort of vibe coming out of her.
No, it's easy to say.
I know why you're saying it, but she actually could be magic.
You understand me?
Well, she is.
No, no, I know it's easy to say that.
Right, I know, yeah.
She's a macaroni and cheese for dinner, too.
Yeah.
There were, you know, many of the great performers, you know, were in fact shamanistic.
Jim Morrison and Grace Jones sometimes.
There were, she had her shamanistic moments.
She is a shamanistic moment, just like my macaroni and cheese.
You've got sacred macaroni and cheese.
You're spending an evening at home with your family.
Oh, I love it.
Macaroni and cheese is the best.
It's like my peyote, my personal peyote, but it's macaroni and cheese.
Suddenly, without warning, the great product.
Excuse me.
Macaroni and cheese could be mind-altering, probably treated.
Well, I believe it is mind-altering.
And if you look close enough at anything, I don't think acid anymore.
But when I was a teenager, about 19 years old, I occasionally did.
And I remember looking at a pile of noodles.
What are you saying?
No, it was rice.
A pile of rice.
No, no, not you, him.
And it was, and it was, good Lord!
A manifestation from the other side, the Reverend Stang.
It's so good to see you.
Did you say if you could explain one thing at a time, you'd get more out of it?
Is that what you said?
Are you sure?
It's Don Hagenbrenner.
Oh, wait, I can do it.
John Sherlin.
John Sherlin Brenner.
Who's that?
I think it's about time for another ginger ale, so I will meet you on the flip side at the zoo.
Okay, okay.
You want to drink that crap, go right ahead.
Rice.
I drink club soda.
I hallucinated that it was an eternal plate of rice.
That's what happened.
The Reverend Stang is here.
That feels so much better.
Stang from Cleveland.
He's just made himself, he just found another way to introduce himself.
I'm going to give you slack with a belch.
That wasn't me.
We understand you've been sucking all the slack, Stang.
Explain.
We're trying to understand why Cleveland is such a violent place.
And one theory is that you get so much slack, people there are stressed out and begin to kill each other.
No, actually, the new subgenius headquarters is not in Cleveland at all, but in Cleveland Heights.
The slack is rotten.
Which sacrifices the slack of the rest of Cleveland.
I live in Cleveland for its own extremely low crime rate.
I live in a kind of a little enclosed fortress.
The slacker mansion, we call it.
So what, Texas is just on its own now, right?
Sorry.
Actually, when I go to Texas, I just came from there.
The desolate flats of Texas.
It rains.
It rains if I visit Texas.
When I leave.
It stops raining.
It didn't rain for a year.
At least not in Stang County, unfortunately.
Until we understand it.
Some parts of Texas got the Katrina.
That's right.
What was this?
Time check, everyone.
So there was like a locus of global warming, a cell of global warming settled over the state after you left.
Well, when we had to flee Texas.
We placed a curse upon the benighted state of Texas that there would be no rain until such time as we returned.
What kind of vehicle did you flee Texas in?
I'm curious.
United Airlines in this case.
But he drove it on the freeway.
That was the curious thing.
You got to Cleveland without a car?
People had to drive off the road to let the 747 drive by.
He thought it was a car.
No.
When we fled Texas to Cleveland, we went in a series of covered wagons across the prairie.
We faced many hardships, droughts, locusts, plagues.
Those were the old steam wagons.
Rednecks.
Yeah.
Well, no.
We were the rednecks.
All right.
It's all relative.
Oh, it's a tale to make the Mormons cringe.
The exodus from Texas.
That kind of has what rhymes, kind of a ring to it.
Exodus from Texas.
From Texas.
Texas.
Reverend Stang, I have a press release from the Church of the Subgenus.
Can I ask you about this?
I heard you reading that in the limo on the way here.
And I thought to myself, that sounds like a Reverend Motormat press release.
The church is inviting all of its members worldwide to gather together for the final
hours in Sherman, New York from Thursday, 28th of July.
Thursday, July 5th at a clothing optional outdoor campground.
Very interested to read, the church has been engaged in a massive recruitment campaign
to increase the numbers of its membership for the arrival of the exodus.
It is seeking performers and producers from the adult entertainment industry.
Yeah, that's right.
We have a new adult film festival award ceremony that just started last year.
It's...
And, you know, it's just a way to broaden the artistic reach of the church and also
to get a certain amount of attention if you think about it, you know.
And a lot of the saints of the church have been workers in the, shall we say, sex industry.
Kitten Atividad, the great saint, Kitten Atividad, John Holmes and some of the other
performers.
Right.
Saint Wad.
The giants, you might say.
Especially the plumbers.
Yeah.
I have a special place in my heart, a very large hole in my heart where the plumbers
sit.
Yeah, and it's still dripping through that hole, isn't it?
Oh, yes.
I feel the undisplended.
I got some discharge.
I'm a monster.
So, July 5th, it's all coming to an end and it does every year, basically.
Well, every year.
We have a new apocalypse every year.
And in my opinion, my opinion is that the apocalypse is coming to an end.
My theory is that other people who predict the end of the world, I read a list of them.
You might have heard some of them.
Yeah, we did.
I heard that on the way in.
Other people are not diligent enough about bringing about the end of the world and predicting
the end of the world.
And the church of the subgenius has to be praised for its persistence.
It will not give up.
Oh, our faith is absolute.
The aliens, the exes, will arrive on July 5th, 1998, which obviously has not arrived
yet.
Bob said that date.
Therefore, that date has not yet arrived.
It was a typo.
It was upside down.
It's a typo.
There's been this whole tampering with calendars, which is pretty obvious.
I mean, come on.
I noticed...
We don't know what year this is.
We don't even know what planet.
The numbers seem to swim around when I look at them.
When I look at my calendar, the numbers seem to wobble and swim.
But then everything else is...
Oh, everybody's sorry.
Oh, everybody's so sure that this is the year 2007.
Oh, everybody's so sure this is planet Earth.
Oh, yeah, it's planet Earth.
No, it's not.
It's not.
You're right, Ivan.
This is not planet Earth.
It's just what we named it.
That doesn't mean it is planet Earth.
We don't know what the name of this planet is.
Somebody's going to come and tell us the name one day.
Oh, you mean...
Our whole reality is...
Sportnik?
We named everything.
Our reality is based on a house of cards, a teetering...
Back in our favor.
...editor.
...physic, could fall any time because it's built on a bunch of hooey.
Yes, I'll say it.
Hooey.
Hooey is what it's built...
...foundation of hooey.
A bunch of hoo-ha.
Look at that.
Chicken just won.
Who's playing...
2007.
Two and seven means...
Who's playing that song way down low?
...after we gather it's nine.
Maybe it's the year nine.
Hooey!
Everybody be quiet a minute.
Hang on.
1998 is...
This is a test.
Hang on.
Who is playing that song way down low?
Who's playing that?
Anybody here?
No.
Really?
What the hell is that?
I don't know.
It's like some 70s power band.
Wait, who would expect some kind of random weird noise in the background on this show?
It's some kind of radio show going on under ours.
It's a radio show.
It sounds like...
I heard some Phineas...
It's country music.
Could you just download Phineas Narco?
Hooey!
I heard that for a second.
It was a reference to Phineas Narco.
Hooey!
No!
You're not名ing me?
But I'm not...
Let me prove it for you.
You're not...
I don't know who you are.
You're not Phineas Narco.
Okay, that's then you're correct.
I'm not Phineas Narco...
Right?
It sounds like Judy Collins.
How could that be happening?
I think it's a ghost of a folk song show that was in this KPFA studio.
Oh!
It's puzzling evidence who just isn't even here.
He just turned something on and left the room with this.
I can't imagine something like that.
Let him listen to this in the background, he said.
What is he even playing this for?
He's out fropinating and subjecting us to folk music.
Folk music!
All right, listen to that.
Blessed silence there in folk music.
It always feels better when you turn it off.
Go ahead and do it.
Okay.
Trust me.
Ow!
I win.
I win every time.
Wet head.
Towel off.
No way.
1-0-8-4-8-4-4-2-5.
Is that what you heard?
That's what this is?
Maybe that's what year this is.
What year is it?
If it's not 2007, what year is it?
If you missed that first number, this is it.
5.
That's it.
It's the year 5.
1-0-8-4-8-4-4-2-5.
And tell us what time it is where you're at.
And tell us where you're at.
And tell us what they call where you're at.
And if you're Chinese, it's a different year.
That's not the real Francis Deck.
That is an imposter deck.
Oh, it's not?
No, that's not the real deck.
That's right.
I read about this.
A guy at a radio station remade his text.
Right.
Yeah.
Yeah, the true Francis Deck would never have been able to enunciate those words so well.
No, that's what I figured.
It's probably better that it isn't.
What about...
Students in the...
Maybe Logic University course in the subgenius history, the first 100 years...
Yes, I have it right here.
...are able to download the original Francis Deck texts.
Did he ever read his own text?
I don't know.
But I did get a copy of the original things that he would staple onto telephone poles.
Yeah.
He was able to use every bit of a page like a true visionary always does.
The corners, everything.
Yeah, all the corners.
He would type until the thing was full.
And then put his final thoughts along the margins.
Ah, ah.
But what about this?
What about the back?
Well, we don't know.
You didn't turn it over?
You get a valuable document like that and you don't even turn it over?
Well, we got Xeroxes and you can't tell which is page one or page two of a Francis Deck rant.
There's two-sided Xeroxes now.
Come on.
Yeah, sure.
Now, yeah, sure.
This was in the day, man.
Back in the past.
What day?
A thousand years ago.
When the Church of the Subgenius was first inspired...
When was he doing this?
Early 80s?
Is that right?
Francis Deck?
Yeah.
I got my Xerox in the early 80s, yes.
1982.
That's him.
Testing, testing.
Now, the person reading the Deck text is J.R.
Buck.
Bob Dobbs.
Of course.
I knew that.
Is this thing on?
Yes.
But listen, that guy in San Francisco, do you know the guy who's putting out the, what is it,
the set of CDs called, from Monster God Computer, Communist Monster God Computer, something,
that's his label, and he's putting out all these outtakes and bloopers and people freaking out.
Gosh, what an idea.
Celebrity bloopers.
But his label is named the Mad Conspiracy Computer, whatever, Communist God thing.
That's his label.
So I wondered if it was the same guy.
He's not going to die by any chance.
Is Deck dead?
Yes.
Oh, good.
Yes, and in fact, some lads from Dallas went and videotaped him on his deathbed in a cruel
mockery of his condition.
Wow, I'm glad somebody did.
I'm not really aware of Deck.
It's a pretty boring video.
Do you have any tapes of him or something?
That was him.
That was him ranting.
That was someone reading the rants of Francis Deck.
This is his writing.
Living dead Frankenstein slavery.
He's not reading with someone pretending to be him.
Well, if you listen to it, it applies today.
Actually, he's right about that.
He was like Nostradamus.
It's quite amazing.
Only a lot more specific.
I mean, this is from the early 80s, and I'm still playing it, which shows you how relevant
it still is after all this time.
What if it had been 20 years later?
Oh, not you, Gary.
The man made inside out planets with nucleonic powered speeds much faster than the speed
of light.
Look up and see.
The gangster computer guy.
I've concocted new fake starry skies.
The worldwide completely controlled deadly degenerative climate.
It's like an anticipation of the Matrix concept.
Well, Alex Jones certainly has some explaining to do with Mr. Francis Deck.
He asked me.
Alex Jones.
Phony stars.
He says that.
I can say lots of things.
Toonific.
Parentheses.
Girl Tarot.
Sing not branch.
You have been listening to the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack, a 1080 episode, which
happens to be from the puzzling evidence and over the edge shows reprinted from KPFA and
Berkeley.
Friends, if you want more information about the Church of the Subgenius, see subgenius.com.