Now, this one came on an unauthorized piece of paper.
It looks like a political handbill.
Yeah, a handbill of Tom Letson, your state representative Democrat.
But on the back it says,
What?
Question mark, exclamation point, the fuck?
With an umlaut over the fuck.
So it's what?
With a question mark and an exclamation mark.
And the fuck?
W-T-F.
And on the other side, Tom Letson, your state representative Democrat.
Well, which one of those is the question?
Which one of those is the question?
You know, at least Tom lets on.
But this guy doesn't.
You know, he's keeping it close to the vest.
All I'm going to say is, if you don't ask questions,
you can't expect to receive an answer.
So in order to receive the fuck,
you must...
precede it with the what.
As you have done.
And I thank you for your emolument.
Impressive evidence.
You sex robot.
Freeze, douchebags!
Goddamn hotline!
This place is surrounded.
Art's got my back.
Don't move, assholes!
Matt's guarding the back door.
Yo!
And Bob's covering the harbor.
This is so stupid.
Asshole destroyed all of Zebulon.
Who would do such a terrible thing?
Yes, well, it's actually a funny story about that.
The subgenius power of...
Son.
Oh, son.
I was wrong about you.
There are so many definitions of a hero.
But for me,
someone lazy,
lifts you up,
and gives you hope
when some dickhead
throws your planet into the sun.
It's J.R. Bob Dobbs,
the living slack master
in his church of the subgenius.
With this two dollars
came this question,
and I bet you haven't gotten this one before.
That would be a relief.
Why does it hurt
when the other guy pees?
Because you are a noble being,
blessed with empathy,
and you can't help but wince a little bit
when you see some other brother
in a moment of pain.
You take that pain upon yourself,
because you are superior.
Yes, you are.
All false modesty aside,
most people peeing in there
don't give anything for the other person's sensations,
but you think even of that.
Perhaps even you think too much
of your brother's welfare,
and should think more about your own.
You're a lucky subgenius
to throw the match, so to speak,
and light the fire that consumes
J.R. Bob Dobbs.
And Bob will burn as a martyr to his cause.
There is a thirty dollar
minimum bid for this privilege.
We'll have an auto-da-fay
that you auto-attend.
We'll have the paperwork,
the De Camborendo Heretico.
And then you can be the one who
Get the civil arm to perform the execution.
Be the person who the shirt
that was heard around the world.
You could be the one whose
finger flicked the match
that lit the final fuse
that burnt J.R. Bob Dobbs.
Right, and it's a thirty dollar minimum bid,
so keep that in mind.
The ultimate revolutionary.
We're not doing that tonight,
because I want to wait.
After all, it's only money.
In all the future history books,
when they're showing the end of mankind,
and they're showing the final burning of J.R. Bob Dobbs,
it'll be your image.
Your hand.
That is in there.
Perhaps just your fingernail,
perhaps just your thumb,
and index finger,
but it will be your...
That will be enough to identify you.
You will be the person.
A minimum bid of thirty dollars.
We're not doing that on today's auction.
I want to allow everyone
their fine opportunity to do it,
but I wanted to preface it now,
so that you would consider
how cool it would be
to be the one.
Indeed.
Dear friends, this is an excellent opportunity
for us to sit down and try to purge from our minds
all those vestiges of conspiracy thought,
because it's just natural.
They've burned it into our brain,
so we hear things like this,
and we think,
well, why would I want to spend thirty dollars on a match
that I could have bought a similar match
for only a dime at Walmart or something?
No, no, it's not the value of the match
that establishes the thirty dollar minimum bid.
It is the story behind the match
that establishes the value of that match.
Here's another favorite.
It's called,
You're Ugly, But Your Tits Are Big.
Thanks, man.
Get your face away from me!
You're gross like gas, that's why you're free!
Skip the preliminary shit!
Stop me, get my hands on your tiiiiiiiiiit!
You're ugly, but your tits are big.
You're ugly, but your tits are so big.
Face like a frog, you're like,
hey, I'm the reason why!
Guys, serve me!
Don't try to kiss me at all!
All the rest, just let me get my hands on your briiiind!
You're ugly!
But Your Tits Are Big!
You're ugly, but your tits are big!
You're ugly, but your tits are so big!!
Shhhhhiii...
We're the men,
I always realize,
I always realize, please stop judgein' me!
Please stop judgein' me! You're ugly, but your tits are big!
Just to let you know, this was not our big show.
Friends, that was Fat Free, the band Fat Free from Brooklyn.
You can find them on MySpace.com under Fat Free Music,
playing live at X Day, 14, 14 X Day Drill, whatever,
at Wisteria Campground.
A song called You're Ugly, But Your Tits Are Big.
Obviously, this is one of our triple X rated episodes of the Hour of Slack
and will not be on any of the broadcast stations.
The titles for the show were by,
Slander Bob, who does We Slack Radio,
which is like all subgenius radio of all the shows all the time.
You can find that under the radio section of subgenius.com.
And let's go back to the stage now at Caffeine's,
the cafe at Wisteria during 14 X Day Drill.
Of course, the subgenius says,
how many of them are going to go,
diving into the bonfire in order to retrieve that match
that actually lit the Bob's effigy?
We may have to pull out all the screws.
And then we'll have to have more clues
to stop other Bobbies from charging into the bonfire
to retrieve the ashes of the Bobbies
that charged into the bonfire to get the match that lit the effigy.
I see the way your mind works, Papa Joe.
I see into the bottom of your mind.
You want to form a chain of self-immolating,
emitting Bobbies who will burn like torches
for the edification of the rest of us on X Day.
If we're not careful,
we may not have anyone here for the saucers to pick up.
It'll just be a pile of smoldering ashes.
Well, that will help those saucers escape Earth's gravity well.
Besides, another thing that our alien friends can do
is reconstitute people from ashes.
It's a process called palinogenesis
that the ancient alchemist Borellus investigated, first of all.
Well, that's a good question.
Well, that's essential so that all the subgeniuses
who have lit themselves on fire and protested the conspiracy
You just have to collect all the ashes
and secondly, don't mix them up with other people's ashes
or the wrong kind of ashes
because then you get, in the words of the text,
the most lively awfulness that springs up
and is incapable of death.
Even though for liability reasons
we never want to encourage suicide in the subgenius cult,
we do suggest...
The problem with all these occult arts
is if you make even the smallest mistake,
you bring so much grief.
So, although we're not suggesting that,
we are saying that if you are to set yourself on fire,
please do not do it on a windy day.
Those ashes need to remain in the pile.
And also, let's get it straight.
No one here told you to set yourself on fire.
If you do that, that's your idea.
We're simply talking about this as a form of speculation.
And most importantly, if you do set yourself on fire,
be sure to close the matches.
Do not strike that match.
With the folder open,
terrible accidents occur when that happens.
As it says on all of your membership cards,
the subgenius foundation is not responsible for its actions.
He got that from Burning Man.
Meaning the owner of the car.
On the Burning Man ticket, it says that
by attending you acknowledge your...
the possibility of your being seriously,
permanently injured or killed, you know,
and we're not liable for your form of fun.
So, the same it is with us.
We don't want to tell you to pull your punches,
to ameliorate your fun,
have the most hardcore fun imaginable.
But if you do and regret it later,
it's not our fault.
We simply provide you the natural vector
for you to follow your inward inclinations.
It probably wouldn't be a bad idea though
for us to develop an actual release
that any subgenius who is about to...
It's in the thing, but...
Everybody has to sign it and send it in,
which no one has done.
Well, I'm just thinking of something
that we could put out on perhaps the internet,
so if they do something away from the campsite,
whether it's some sort of...
Oh, on the internet, they can virtually sign it.
They can virtually attend X-Day
and virtually leave on the saucers
and do everything at a fake remove
while masturbating with the other hand.
And it would be an official note saying,
I just want to make sure that the authorities
and my family know that what I'm doing here today
has absolutely nothing to do with the fact that I'm here.
Well, if you have to,
follow every little niggling detail,
cross every T and dot every I,
every jot and tittle,
if that makes you feel better,
why, go ahead, Pilgrim.
And yet they probably get one of their blood-sucking lawyers
just to turn it right around on us and say,
see, that proves it.
Well, as I said the other day,
stay out of the legal system,
stay out of the medical system,
stay out of the religious system,
stay out of any system.
All the conspiracy is is a series of emails
interlocked systems which you want to avoid because it's so much easier that way which is
another thing that leads you directly to the church's subgenius being that it's the only
religion that is clearly not a religion in the religious way and an only system that isn't
really a system and the only organization which is completely disorganized
this is tranquility base the eagle has landed
jesus h christ houston we're on the fucking moon over
roger tranquility we copy that we cannot believe you are on the fucking moon repeat
cannot fucking believe it over
you're cleared to hook up lunar equipment conveyor to walk fucking walk on the moon over
holy living fuck are you fucking believing this over we read you over
you
i am so fucking lutely
am standing on the surface of the fucking moon
am talking to you from the surface of the fucking moon
jesus h christ in a chicken basket
uh holy shit tranquility
holy mother of fuck
the fucking moon over
the fucking moon by the evolution control committee uh live at uh 14 x day drill it was uh an amazing
night really really amazing um and you can find the link in the description below if you want to
read all of it also there's a link to the evolution control newsletter as well if you're not
aday again the evolution control committee at evolution the background the international
evolution tad ville of buddha communication but i believe at times he makes the difference
of the life and more nuclear power what is really didn't get the right
special could you comment on that
yeah that's it
Megans should appreciate that.
It's part of their history.
Bob will be emulated.
Bob himself.
You know, we used to burn a cheap replica Bob.
Nowhere near as good as that clever robot there.
Just an icon.
A quickly thrown together wooden icon.
But this year, friends, we're promising you something very, very special.
If you ever saw that movie, The Wicker Man,
it's a little bit like that.
We don't have quite as large of a man to burn as Burning Man does.
But then Burning Man has been gradually growing smaller.
No, he hasn't.
The pedestal's been growing higher.
The what?
Oh, I see.
Because I thought that they had let him grow.
No, every year it's more and more elaborate with more doodads,
and now the man is way up there.
Well.
Praise Burning Man, but I'm glad I don't run that festival.
I can tell you that running X-Day is tricky enough.
Running Starwood is ten times as tricky.
And Burning Man is like 10,000 Starwoods going off all at once.
Only without the spiritual stuff.
It's tricky and sticky and icky, too.
Yeah, it's real icky because of the body paint everywhere.
And the water.
Spilling on everybody.
And no water to wash.
Every time we breathe or we shit or we eat or we sing or we dance.
No.
Is it because he's so handsome?
Maybe.
But mostly it's because J.R. Bob Dobbs does not give a shit.
Now you might be saying to yourself, oh, Jehovah, Wan, and Buddha, and Brahma, and Krishna,
and all those other supernatural powers in the universe.
Don't give a shit either.
My S.O. left me and my dog died.
My job sucks and the rent's due.
But that's where you're wrong.
You see, the supernatural powers of the universe care.
They just don't like you.
Jehovah Wan cares.
He cares enough to watch your every infraction and write it down in his big ledger book in the sky.
He watches what you eat and when.
He watches every time you polish the bishop or flick the bean.
He takes careful note of the positions in which you copulate, the speed at which you drive on the highway,
and how often you pack into a little stone building at ass o'clock in the morning and sing poorly.
And don't forget about the Buddha.
Oh no, he cares.
He cares enough about your soul that he wants you to wash away all of its flavor by sitting in one place for days on end humming.
And he won't even let you eat bacon.
Exactly.
And don't get me started on Ra and Freya and Osiris and Odin and all those other old school pantheoners.
Sure, they'll send you rain one day when you pray for it, but the next they'll burn your village down and the day after that they'll turn into a goat and fuck your mom.
Well, fuck those guys.
That's the kind of service you get when you put your faith in gods who care.
Well, maybe.
Well, I hear you say, maybe I'll just put all my faith in science.
Science is supposed to be objective. It won't put all that crap on me.
But that's where you're wrong again, friends.
Because even the gods of science like Richard Dawkins and Charles Darwin will have you believe that we are related to homo-pinking sapiens.
Well, fuck those guys, too.
We don't need them!
We don't have to listen to them.
Hell, we're subgeniuses. We ain't gotta listen to nobody!
And when we crawl from this battlefield for the soul onto the perfectly manicured lawn of J.R. Bob Dobbs, what is it he asks of us?
Just thirty dollars.
And when we ask him what it is that we should do or how we should behave, he just says,
Do whatever the fuck you want. Now get off my lawn and go slack off.
If you want to eat a pound of bacon on the steps of a mosque every Friday morning, you eat the hell out of it.
If you want your enemies strucken down in a painful and hopefully embarrassing manner, you're gonna need to do it yourself, because Bob has got shit to do.
And if you want to spend your week in the woods with a bunch of friends and strangers doing whatever the hell you feel like because you've got nothing better to do and it's better than the whole entire year that you've had so far put together, well, more power to you.
And that is why we Praise Bob.
Friends, that was Reverend Janice Blackseed ranting at 14X Day, and we'll hear a little bit more ranting and so forth from there coming up.
First, Reverend Pandemonium, followed by the great DJ Shafer. Praise Bob.
Reverend Pandemonium is a fire-threatening, dangerous, and dangerous act.
Do you, as an artist and a fine subgenius with a much better memory than mine, and Reverend Pandemonium, do you reject a conspiracy in all of its unpleasantness and crap and inconvenient, useless laws?
Fuck yes!
Okay, and it's Bob, and fuck Connie. That's good enough.
Yeah!
There you go!
Another saved one.
Is there a certain number of men that have to do it?
We need another.
There's another op.
There's a decently clad gentleman.
Yes, decently clad at the request of my wife.
I don't blame you a bit. I'm decently clad because I know exactly what you're looking for, and it ain't there.
She's being smart. That's the insurance policy.
This is my 25th year, by the way.
Year 25! For this subgenius.
I would have thought you were a little older than that.
No, I said Bob, $30. I think...
25 for being reborn unto Bob.
The minute you guys changed it to $30 was, I think, the minute that I sent my $30 in. It was 1980.
His love of Bob was so great that he waited until the price went up.
Exactly.
That's what I call true slackable faith.
Indeed.
Reverend DJ Shaver, do you reject the low-paying jobs and all the crappy wedding gigs?
Oh, yes.
The awful birthday parties?
Oh, no.
The family get-togethers?
Yeah.
And accept into your heart and mind the promise of X Day and the promise of Bob?
Sure.
Sure, whatever.
And the love of Bob is done.
Fuck the chicken dance!
This has actually been a wonderful X Day so far.
We're looking forward to burning the body of J.R. Bob Dobbs.
And dancing around his corpse.
That's kind of the whole idea around this religion is to deny it and believe it with all our hearts at the same time.
That's the way I feel about life, the universe, and everything, in fact.
Kind of depends on what mood you're in, I suppose.
I'm in a good mood right now.
Well, I'm looking at a naked Susie the floozy.
What's not to love?
Oh.
TNA is back.
It's better than DNA.
Well, thank you.
Thank you.
And thank you.
And praise Bob.
Praise Bob.
Praise Bob!
You want to give us a praise Bob?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Woo!
Wait.
Wait for it.
Cut.
Pray, moon.
Thank you, thank you.
A masterful cut at that.
Now, we should go get some film.
I'm going to do this all over again.
I'm going to have to buy one of those 3D TV sets now.
And now, a special message from Priestess Pisces.
Please stand by.
Just a reminder, for the auction today, we will be auctioning off a unique opportunity.
The opportunity is that we will be burning Bob, setting him on fire.
Setting him on fire.
And for a minimum bid, bids will start at $30.
You can be the one to...
To kill Bob yourself.
You can light Bob ablaze and be proud to know that you were the one who finally killed Bob.
His eternal light.
You can fry that high E-pop's damn ass.
Again, it's going to be a minimum bid of $30.
Minimum.
You alone will be free of Bob's baleful influence.
The important thing is there is no maximum bid.
No maximum bid.
And remember, you paid $30 to love Bob.
You should pay at least $30 to hate Bob.
And if you feel bad about it, you can always think of it as a sort of cremation ritual.
So you're liberating him from his mortal coils.
Exactly.
And that will be on today's Bulldada auction.
The burning itself will take place obviously on the evening, late evening, of the 4th.
But we will...
You have your shot to do that today.
So spread that around.
Here's one with some nice artwork.
Oh, great.
Hieroglyphics.
Excellent.
Yeah.
Little Devo hat, a pipe, an axe, a bone.
Who ultimately decides the difference between, quote, avant-garde and, quote, kooky bullshit?
The question is who ultimately decides the difference between avant-garde and kooky bullshit?
The answer is the survivors.
The survivors write the accounts and make the decisions.
Survive the avant-garde with your kooky bullshit, and you find that not only were you the avant-garde, you were the derriere-garde.
We've got two of them in a row that are printed on our Jenkum Chamber requests, which actually these should be being taped up inside the...
Yeah.
Sweat lodges.
And they may still be.
Yeah.
It's part of an experiment to see how quick it takes the staff to take them down, even though you can't actually flush a...
Is that the correct spell of Jenkum?
I believe so.
J-E-N-K-E-M.
I thought it was U-M, huh?
I guess I was wrong.
We'd have to check Wikipedia on that.
Anyway, the question is...
Let's have it.
How...
Oh, how many licks does it take to get through bed?
Bob's bullshit.
Actually, this is written in an odd grammar.
How many licks does it take to get through Bob's bullshit does it take?
Question mark combined with...
How many licks to get through Bob's bullshit does it take?
That's perfectly grammatical.
Well, you can lick Bob's bullshit all day and never get to the center.
I think we all know that.
If we could get it, we could go home and forget this.
But no.
The distance to the center infinitely expands.
There's a lot of licking left.
Here's one I think inspired by the folk tale that Dr. Leguim told at X Day last year.
Yes, that was a wise folk tale.
Ken has bear ripe?
Ken has bear ripe.
Oh, hi.
Oh, hi, oh.
Wisteria, Ohio.
Round on the ends, high in the middle.
Yeah, that's right.
Ken has bear rape.
Who can't?
You don't know whether you can bear rape, especially by a bear, until the moment occurs.
Otherwise, it's vainglorious vauntings and boastings that have no connection with any appreciable level of reality.
The best thing, as any sage would tell you, is not to be raped by a bear.
However, let us hope that we have martyrs who would be capable, even under those stressful circumstances.
You know, when heretics were burned at the stake, they often managed to make gestures indicating that they were still confirmed in their heresies, even though they were on fire.
If they can do that, some pre-epic bear isn't going to be the ultimate barrier against self-expression.
But stay away from its huge, glistening bear penis, dripping with gleet and seething with fleas.
That's a...
I'm quoting the classic story.
I'm getting turned on now.
You wrote those lines.
Yeah.
Here's another one.
We keep getting questions without money.
That is sad.
Why would anyone in their right mind want to stay away from the huge, glistening bear penis?
.
Some folks are particular, I guess.
They have another preference in mind.
And remember, if you can actually actualize your own fantasies, you'll feel absurdly self-satisfied.
If your idea of yourself that is the most resonant to you and most congruent with your self-love or amour-propre involves being ravished from behind,
like by a giant bear, then that is what you should seek.
And don't let me keep you back.
This is a related question.
How much antidote pudding for the face-fucking-bats-with-barbed-dicks is available?
I'm not in charge of the commissary.
What this contains is a little bit of the face-fucking-bats sexual pheromones.
It's necessary to consume the pheromones.
Oh, thank you.
For that reason.
Otherwise, they won't come and land on your face.
In the Roman amphitheaters, in those jolly old spectacles in the Colosseum,
they used to get animals to rape their victims by smearing the animal's sexual sauce on the victim.
This was the secret of the animal trainers, which was guarded especially by the torturers' guilds in ancient Rome.
Right.
But now, but in the passage of time, all secrets come to light.
I'd say that suggests a new sport for next X Day.
Well, remember when you wouldn't bring the yellow jacket attractant?
Right.
I suppose you have a different mind now to spread this on certain troublesome people.
We're going to avoid legal entanglements, but then after the ceremony, of course, all things are wide open.
It says on the schedule that there will be a Bulldada auction after the...
The increasingly less popular Bulldada auction.
Well, do we have anything more to sell?
I don't think so.
I don't know what kind of a Bulldada auction that could be unless we auction IOUs or favors or something like that.
We already auctioned off the right to kill Bob tonight at the Icon Burning.
That was the last thing we sold.
We already sold.
I just spoke, by the way, to the fire master, St. Kenny, who said we can start it with the push of a button.
A button?
What's the fun of that?
Who was it that bought the right to kill Bob?
Ministry of Slack.
Oh, Ministry of Slack.
Ministry of Slack or one of their representatives will get to push the button and light the match.
Actually, several of them could light the match and make it look like they're setting this great fire off.
But it'll have to be up to the Ministry of Slack whether or not you are so designated.
I need everyone to come up to the stage.
Everyone come up.
There's a sacred ritual that is about to take place.
I'm going to start handing out...
Now, as we know, the Church of the Subgenius, one of our sacred things is sacred noise.
And a procession is about to begin for the burning of Bob.
So, I hope I have enough toys.
I've got whistles and little spinny things.
This one, by the way, is the one that annoys me the most.
Do we have any Juggalos?
No, seriously.
You're not a Juggalo.
No, not Jiggalo.
Juggalo?
Because I have magnets so you can figure out what the fuck they do.
Alright.
Those of you who do not have an instrument will just have to sing poorly.
If you will meet at the road directly behind the stage, the sound booth right now, please.
Can we all congregate at the road behind the sound booth at this moment, please?
Why don't we do it in the road?
Everybody meet at the road.
Do you endorse and authorize the burning of Bob?
I hereby endorse and authorize the burning.
I here indeed hereby authorize and endorse the burning of this excellent robot Bob, created by the great Wilhelm Stahlhelm.
Beautifully helmeted Wilhelm Stahlhelm, I must add.
I see our fire experts, St. Kenny and St. Jason, are hard at work strapping Bob down so that he does not escape.
He's not struggling very hard, I know.
That's odd.
I'm amazed at how peaceful Bob looks.
He seems so at ease.
You see, for Bob there is no moment without slack.
He does not know the meaning of vampire slack.
Kill that motherfucker!
Yeah, slay that fucker!
Good lord, I could swear they're pouring gasoline upon Bob Dobbs himself.
Back up just a little, it's gonna shoot some flames.
St. Kenny is making the crowd scream.
Bob, stand back.
Because the slack emanating from Bob is so great, especially when he's turned on by pain.
And bondage.
He's into bondage, obviously, we can tell.
What an amazing spectacle.
All of these subgeniuses, all standing around ready to watch the man they love the most feel the most possible pain.
That could ever happen to a man.
And yet Bob himself seems so happy.
Ah, you see the power of Bob.
He is almost as if he is made of asplastics.
He's almost as if he is made of asplastics.
Even the power of this intense flame.
It's almost impossible to burn him.
There goes an arm, finally, one arm.
Oh my god, the face!
The hell of a horrible face!
Is that Mike Jones?
Good God, Mike!
How can this be?
Oh my God!
Dear Lord, God in heaven, what hast thou wrought?
Kill Bob! Kill Bob!
Strangely, he has a spot on his head, a lip-up.
A spot on the top of his head.
It appears to be where his soul is escaping.
Kill Bob! Kill Bob!
Oh my God!
No!
Kill Bob! Kill Bob!
What can this mean?
What can this portend?
Look at the...
It's on the map here.
He went so fast.
Did you look at the top of his head as his soul is escaping?
You can actually see the soul of Bob emitting from his head.
So that he can then join another body.
Claiming head good, extinguished head bad.
Claiming head good!
This is the most protest, horrible, monstrous thing I've ever seen.
Claiming head good, extinguished head bad.
You guys keep that hole open.
How can these people just be grinning with happiness as J.R. Bob Dobbs himself?
He's nothing but a pile of ash.
The soul is still attempting to escape from the head.
The center of the top of the head or the third eye.
His skeleton is revealed.
We can see a skeleton made of what appears to be wood.
Could Bob's bones be made from the same material as his pipe?
I don't know.
What a bizarre, bizarre and horrible sight this is to see.
He went so fast.
I think he wanted to go.
I think he wanted to go fast.
You know, most people scream when they're immolated.
Most are witches and others are burned.
But look at his skull.
The crown of his skull. There's smoke coming out.
Is that perhaps, that is the soul.
Could that be the soul of Bob escaping finally?
Are we hailing perhaps?
Are all of us?
But where do we put him?
Where do we put him?
There it is.
Die, die, die, motherfucker!
They seem to believe that he has made love to his own mother at some point.
Perhaps that explains the origin of Dobbs himself.
Die, die, die, motherfucker!
I'll never understand the love-hate relationship that Dobbs has with his followers.
On the other hand, look at his followers.
I mean, he's a true surprise.
I don't want to do that.
Fuck her! Fuck her! Fuck her!
Not a whimper. Not a single whine.
He didn't even laugh or chuckle.
There's still a little bit of soul escaping from the crown of his soul.
That's what they call it.
They found that other things besides J.R. Bob Dobbs are a flamma.
This could be a big advance for so-called team Bob.
You know, so far we've never learned how to burn anything but Bob.
And now we've found that T-shirts can burn.
I wonder about Bobby's and stupid fucking dumbass followers.
Would it be possible for them to...
Raise his mattress!
This is where we can follow the fire.
The horrible, horrible death of Bob.
And the naked human.
Our subtenuous lady.
Love this site.
Dying God. Naked women.
Oh, now I get it! That's what religion is all about!
We figured it out! We finally figured out the...
The formula!
The perfect formula!
Watch, watch, watch, watch!
Well, now we can have a new subgenius calendar with, uh...
With a heart slowly frying J.R. Bob Dobbs' face.
It looks like something out of Indiana Jones.
A bloodthirsty French heartbreak.
You know what? For a whole week they've been worshipping that deceptive face, Bob.
And now, they seem to be so happy to free themselves from their...
Failful mind control.
Oh, they're burning me!
They're burning me too!
Bob!
I think our priorities can mix that.
They want to have intercourse with this skeleton or-
With a burn system.
Ne-I-I-I-I...
There's so many other things around here in this place, like...
Oh, I know a whole lot.
Bob a Q! Bob a Q!
Baba Q! Baba Q! Baba Q! Baba Q!
You're really getting off on this, aren't you?
We send up, they send down, that's the deal.
Yeah, so I guess this is what religion is all about.
Yeah, naked women dancing around a dying god.
A horribly dying sacrifice to God.
Boy, I sure hope the exodus comes tomorrow.
I hate to have to do this, it's really horrifying.
And yet, in a way, is it not inspiring?
Yeah.
I think it's inspiring, Reverend Ankara, to see the emotions, the feelings, the religious spirit finally built up.
They've been laughing and joking all day, but finally they go into that sort of cave person mode where they appreciate the spiritual things.
The more refined things, like a guy burning today.
Yeah!
I mean, this is like a
This is what congratulations means to a man.
This is what makes a man good.
In today's new life, we know that you don't have to live exactly as what the numbers of
Christians are saying for you to make a bag like this.
Pushes.
You know they have wings.
Permal agora a p paraguida  confermation
werk
You need to look forward.
You do.
A horribly tortured man and women with no shirts on.
You know, there's...
Boredom for another year.
Well, that's the most movement I've seen out of subgeniuses in about ten years.
Usually it's hard to get them off their ass to do much of anything.
But you make a good enough replica of Bob and there they go.
It's winding down, I'm gonna gather them up.
Give folks an opportunity to fuck around on the stage.
Pisces has the ability to gather them up.
Yes, they go in my boobs.
They all go in my boobs.
She's the cute cat.
Dr. Legume, on the other hand, has the ability to brainwash Pisces into doing that.
God only knows what he brainwashed me into.
Huh?
It's a little poor brainwashed servant to brainwash the other four.
Personally, my brain doesn't feel washed at all.
It feels dirty and tainted.
I feel like I've seen something I wasn't used to.
Which can be kinky for some people.
That was a certain...
You know, I was just saying.
Usually you can't get the subgeniuses off their fucking asses to dance.
This is different.
I guess the big difference is the reality of the body.
How realistic the dog's corpse looks.
It could be in direct proportion to their enthusiasm.
Yeah.
Well, and they're in a new pipe.
That's called a penis, doctor.
No, the other thing that was hanging out of his neck.
What's that thing hanging out of Bob's neck?
Well, the pipe has roots that go all the way down.
Yeah, but there was stuff under his head that I didn't recognize.
Really? Yeah. It was just like...
I mean, normally with Bob, there's nothing hanging down from his neck.
But he had this like meat thing hanging down from his neck.
It was just in some kind of weird little...
A wobble?
...toskety.
I think they call it a body.
You know, I didn't even notice that.
I've been trained to notice just the head for so long that I...
That wasn't Bob at all.
It was an unrealistic Bob dog.
Maybe that's the thing.
A body, yeah.
We were missing a body all that time.
It could have been so simple.
We could have been bigger than Scientology or Church of All Worlds even.
What happens when you can't keep a straight face?
I'm bleeding.
I'm going for batteries. I'll be back.
Hey, I've got batteries in my pocket.
Ah, yeah.
Yes, friends.
The burning of Bob at 14X Day Drill.
Thanks to Reverend Ankara and Pisces for helping me record that.
And just absolutely amazing.
I want to put the video on YouTube, but obviously it's going to take some serious editing.
Friends, this is the Church of the Subgenius Radio Show called the Hour of Slack number 1328.5XXX.
Internet only.
Burning of Bob special.
And now from Cult of Zere.
A little piece called Kill Bob.
Kill Bob.
But it's not done every National Day.
It's involved throwosta...
Now there is no accusation Dalir did.
distinguishment of gun?,
I won't deny it.
I got it all wrong.
There is a reason I did that.
I know.
But a quote from vampire involved there.
And how are going to claim their body were burned up and donated into a station,
who ethnic,
Miss petite"!
mother and father. I don't want to do anything specifically. What do you want? I don't want to
do. What do we do? We have a point. We say bring back Thor. You're dead. You're gone. You're out.
We put you to death quietly. Yes. Yes. This is outrageous. I wouldn't do anything. I keep
reiterating over and over and over again. I'm saying you should go out and kill people. You
should go out and stir up destruction. You can kill people. You should go out and contribute
to the thingy on the population. I wouldn't do anything. I would. I'm saying life overall,
the whole organism of the planet Earth. I'm saying people who are too stupid to die. Nature,
positive evolutionary impulse. I'm saying continued life on Earth. I'm saying my survival.
Sure. I'm saying eyes. I'm saying the industrial economy. I'm saying tribal situation. I'm saying
the planet. I'm saying the air, the trees, the water. Frank, yes. Who loves you? Who?
Bob. Bob. Who loves you? Bob. .
.
Fall of nail,
lay in what.
A movie star with a
robot.
Crrlveft note then HollandACE hit the middle.
But still ball. Chille Bea. parte. mem saurodom
Kill Bob.
Friends, that was Kill Bob chopped up by Cult of Zere,
who can be found at cultofzere.info.
Zere is spelled Z-I-R.
cultofzere.info.
If you want to know more about anything played on this show
or anything subgeniously, look at subgenius.com
and click the radio button.
It has logs of this show and links to everything we play
and every past show ever done by any subgenius anywhere.
I'm going to let this...
This extra long...
Since it's not for the radio or anything,
who cares how long it is?
Cult of Zere, at the end of his album,
which I can't remember the name of.
It's a subgenius album.
Did, as he and his partner, Reverend Todry Milk Toast,
were driving to X-Day from Portland, Oregon,
where they're from,
they had to go through Kansas.
And their description of driving through Kansas is 16 minutes long,
but I've driven through Kansas before,
and I must say,
for those who haven't,
this is the best way to see Kansas.
That's all I can say.
Price Cult of Zere and Reverend Todry Milk Toast.
Okay.
We are driving through space.
Pilgrim of Fort, number 427129 or 1280129 or 2.
Indian Jackass 129 or 09 or 599 or 1 or 1 1 or 1 or 1 2.
It looks like it's fucking working now.
Goddamn, Kansas is a time vortex.
Never come here if you can help it.
It's not even funny.
They do have a what?
Taco John's?
Something like that?
The important thing to remember is that we're trapped in 1993,
and we can't get out.
These planes are butthurt.
This has been a state of nothing but butthurt.
It's been looping in time,
just looking at the same fucking dotted line the whole goddamn time.
I am so very...
You get the idea.
Oh, we were just...
What were we gonna talk about anyhow?
Well, I have to rant about Kansas.
Because I'm sitting in this seat, and we're locked in at 75 on cruise control,
which we've been doing for the past eight years.
And we still can't get out of Kansas.
We aged about ten years the last eight years, which is like three minutes Kansas time.
Which is why everybody looks so fucking old and pissed off all the time.
And no one has any teeth.
There's no dental work in Kansas.
It hasn't arrived yet.
I lost ten teeth.
Milk Toast had to put them back in.
And she put them in backwards.
And there's a lot of ants in Kansas.
That's one thing. That's one problem.
Yeah, too many ants.
Milk Toast didn't like the ants.
Oh, Kansas.
Colorado, on the other hand, was not Kansas.
Jesus!
I was in...
Where are we at? Wichita?
Kentucky?
We're in Jesusland.
It's all Jesus.
Every two seconds there's another...
Jesus is real.
...advertisement for Jesus.
Jesus has a great marketing campaign in Kansas.
I don't have a problem with Jesus at all.
I like Jesus.
The ass-kicking, fighting Jesus.
He's cool by me.
Even hippie pot-smoking Jesus.
But the Jesus these guys seem to like...
I don't know if he's real, like they say.
Seriously.
He's caps-locked Jesus.
It's caps-locked Jesus.
They say...
What was the sign? Probably like 10 miles wide?
It said, Jesus is real.
And the real part was blinking.
It was blink...
I'm pretty sure it was blinking.
Of course, we haven't slept much.
And I've had six abortions in the eight years that we've been here.
We went in...
Out of spite.
We went in pregnant...
Pregnated Milk Toast twice.
Since time, you know, is all fucked up here, we were able to do that.
And we...
We went and got 10 abortions just to spite them.
Yeah.
Hot damn.
And I think we're still only maybe, you know...
What's the next one?
Topeka-ta?
Chikawaltaki?
We're in Abilene-ix.
There's a big water tower with a cowboy hat on top of it.
It's really screwing with my night vision.
Moose-chaw, fairground, tucky.
You know what?
Moose-chaw was a pretty good place to eat, actually.
I recommend it if you're ever...
That was Colorado where we did Moose-chaw.
Yeah, don't ever try to think you're gonna find that in a state like this place.
Okay, that was the rant on Kansas.
Okay.
Now the rant on Kansas some more.
I hate this shit so bad.
Kansas...
But I hopped.
Let us go.
Two pots of coffee and I hopped.
It's not you, it's us.
Actually, it's you.
Let it go.
Let it drop already, Kansas.
We're recording in the car because...
Let's not forget our hotel, which was also in Kansas.
That was rad.
They had a rodeo on the TV there.
No, they had a tiara little kid freak out on the TV.
They had little child brides or whatever that was.
Pedophile channel.
It wasn't full effect.
Milk dosing and what's my name?
Zeronius.
I don't know who I am anymore.
I want the hell out of this state.
Bob, get me the hell out of this fucking state.
We can leave our unnamed alter egos at the door.
We're trying to get through this state however we can.
And fill out the content on the CD, which is not getting done because...
I'm not going to whine anymore.
Yes, I am.
I'm going to rage now.
The next...
Did you see that?
What?
It was nothing.
It wasn't actually there at all.
Oh, then again.
By the way, our...
The car is...
The Rent-A-Car is actually a spaceship.
It's actually a spaceship from space.
You should see the CD player in this thing.
It's actually a small computer.
You can watch movies on it.
You can...
Not that we're doing that right now as we drive through Kansas or anything.
We're listening to our slack over and over and over again.
Maybe you can hear that.
You guys might recognize this.
Yeah.
Three, two, one.
Okay.
There it is.
After life diagnosis...
Okay.
Now we've got Ivan staying in .com and loans a Gavi tape and then loans some capital.
Well, half day, yeah.
Because as we, I think, soon...
We've heard this thing probably 16 times right now because Kansas is so big.
It's not even that big.
It's just slow.
It's a slow town.
Oh!
Which reminds me, when we heard that part, we were in, what, U-Tucky?
U-Tucky Hall.
We were listening to our slack in that part where Doc Hal loses his complaints about losing
his money in the Coke machine.
We go and stop at a rest area and then this very same thing happens to milquetoast.
It was like as if...
as if that
that
I can't tell
where the fuck are we?
in Kansas?
yeah
last I checked
we were in Kansas
we're gonna die in Kansas
this is like
X-Day is happening
in Kansas this year
this is the
personal purgatory
X-Day started
it's happening
right now
and we should be there
but Kansas
paid us
I'm hearing my taxes
in my head
as I drive
because that's actually
more interesting
than Kansas
so you're gonna
itemize Kansas?
I'm definitely
deducting Kansas
from my taxes
the entire state
of Kansas
I'm definitely
deducting the entire
state of Kansas
from my taxes
I'd like to see
the entire state
of Kansas
deducted from
the planet
not to worry
this will not
be here
come Tuesday
morning
but
it's not
Tuesday morning yet
and I'm convinced
that
perhaps
we're actually
already at X-Day
and we're just
hallucinating
that we're still
in Kansas
because
it's the only thing
that really makes sense
even though we've been
driving through this state
for 600 hours
barefoot
what's going on
is we had
such a great time
tonight
at X-Day
actually
that
we're dreaming
and having
a nightmare
the eternal
Kansas nightmare
maybe we're in reverse
I feel like we're in reverse
time has been
has been
like the car is
driving in reverse
well the road looks like
it's going forward
or there could be
like a
a feature of the
spaceship car
is that like
we push the wrong
button and we put
the loop
Kansas
LCD windshield
function on
by accident
we're on the
Kansas treadmill
we're trapped in
haze
for all eternity
that's why we keep
seeing signs
pointing that way
but no matter
how hard we run
through the haze
if I was told
this was God's country
I'm not convinced
man
I've been looking
at
I saw the same
they're really not
very
their Jesus
message
very much
it's pretty much
the same thing
you suck
Jesus kicks
your ass
it's like a
hip-hop record
except
not
I'm bitching
you're the bitch
you're shit
you know
I actually don't feel
like I'm being
beaten enough
in the Jesus
messages
like there's not
enough disappointment
there
there's a lot of
like caps lock
Jesus is real
as in like
statement of fact
not an opinion
but
I don't feel
the disappointment
condescending
not condescending
quite at all
actually
there's a little bit
of fear
that like
fear and facial
expression
has to be
answered
to that
company
there needs to be
a big sign
that says
Jesus is so
sick of your shit
I would get to that
Jesus wants to get
the fuck out of Kansas
I like Jesus
hitchhiking
on the side of the road
that would be odd
Jesus can't escape
Kansas either
if you see Jesus
tell him
we need him back
maybe Jesus
is an odd
Jesus is an
X day
we're almost there
from what I understand
there is a reverend
Jesus
I've met the man
but
I bet he's way
cooler than the
Jesus they keep
talking about
okay
this has been us
signing off
hi this is
Doxy and Milk Toast
reporting from
the road
Pilgrim's Log
1-2-3-4-7-2-1-2-Z-Z-1-2-X-1-X-X-2-X-9-er
yes we are still
in Kansas
20 years have gone by
in reverse
I think we're about
what happened was
at some point
we were
back in 1978
that was in Idaho
Idaho
yeah Idaho
was in 1978
yeah
oh right
the hotel in Idaho
yeah
that was awesome
right so I think
actually this old trip
we kind of
somehow
stepped through
a time vortex
and
and started
the trip
kind of
in the 70s
as evidenced
by the
hotel room
by the time
we got to
what was it
Birmingham
Hamilton
yeah
Birmingham
Gamblington
yeah
that was where
1986 happened
yeah
by then we were
in 1986
as you can tell
because it was
that pastel
kind of salmon
pink
zigzag
pattern
on the
comfort
rust colored
carpet
very
very thin
very tight
thin
weave
to the carpet
and it was
sticky
carpet
so that's
about
I think
we woke up
in
the car
want to
get
you guys
are hiding
out in
that cornfield
I can tell
there's a
blinky light
over there
oh
I just
want
I smelled
froth
no wait
that was
a skunk
Reverend
Mokto's
made me
eat a
skunk
earlier
and then
she complained
about the
gas
the whole
way
for what
it's worth
if you're
going to
force feed
Eat a nigga, a skunk.
Don't complain about the gas.
Okay, that's the travel report.
Signing off.
If one beer comes in, we have to make a comment.
We don't know.
All right, this is Reverend Dr. Ronious and Reverend Milk Toast.
You talk this long.
I'm just fucking over it.
We've resigned ourselves to dying in Kansas.
I'm 906 years old now.
It shows.
Let me tell you, we've adopted a very Kansas-like physical appearance.
Milk Toast is looking really long in the tooth.
I'm looking long in the tooth.
I've gained 300 pounds.
It's very comfortable in these clothes.
We're starting to look like we belong here.
We now both work at Walmart, but only from the car.
Because we actually can't leave it.
We're telecommuting for our new jobs as cashiers at Walmart from the car.
And Dr. Ronious is just shitting his pants now.
He's elevated from farting constantly.
Just shitting his pants.
And it doesn't matter because I no longer care.
As we are going to die in Kansas.
This has been...
...a street after I ram a Jesus sign.
And drive us off the fucking road.
Oh wait, here comes another exit.
Oh wait, no, that was actually a mirage.
It was an exit mirage.
We keep seeing mirages of signs that say,
Wisteria Campground next right.
And then they disappear right as we get erections.
I think Kansas has given me a backwards erection.
Okay, that's all I got to say about Kansas.
Till next time, this has been...
...a really horrible Pilgrim's Log.
Fuck. Bye.
Yay!
Friends, that was Cult of Zere, or actually Dr. Zeronious, I should say.
Dr. Zeronious and Reverend Todry Milquetoast describing their trip across Kansas.
Which was required to get them from Portland, Oregon to Wisteria Campground in Southern Ohio.
Where we hold the 14X Day Drill.
We'll see you at subgenius.com.
Hey, praise Bob.
Oh, the music in the background was DJ 2 Beans live at 14X Day.