There is nothing wrong with the subgenius of slack.
From PR News in Washington, I'm doping and making one-sided demands of President Trump and betraying the spirit of last month's insider attack in southern Afghanistan.
Trump crashed early on, but he got back up, demanding Korean spy cam pornography.
Korea says its porn beats Sweden, Russia, and Croatia.
The statement also says Pyongyang still has faith in PR.
Secretary of State Mike Pompeo says,
Twi-la-la-la-la-la-la-la.
Yuri found in his bloodstream.
British Prime Minister Theresa May says she now has signs reading,
My porn is PR News in Washington.
P-N-O-N-E-S
D-A-U-D-I-T
Wee!
Lady Luck smiled down at me when I went to see my uncle in Saskatchewan.
The chips all fell fortuitously when I went to see my uncle in Saskatchewan.
He hired an alien woman to help him.
She hired an alien woman to work on his farm.
Her name was Pula Pooka.
She had grace and charm.
She penetrated my skull with gallium arcs and eye probes.
I arranged my cortex and before very long, I was sent to work as a slave in the back of the barn.
In the barn, on the barn, in Saskatchewan.
She was visiting from the farm.
I was sent for a trip at night.
At night, what I was temporarily able to do was to make my uncle chocolateers.
She'd gotten Tupperware made, my uncle a lick of full dalmatian fruit, filled avoir and
scooped and shake up the Marg separately, and spent a whole day making ан是什麼
for her, so that she could speed up the Gesichter and head back for a lunch.
I figured we didn't have any time to muk at this party.
заг
Wee!
Team plat Wouldn't you never quit, Lineenger?
Twa
Tций wie, T wär to wūs.
Free will?
On the testicles to feed to her own
And screaming what the odds are when we strip in the mud
In the barn, on the barn in Saskatchewan
The scabs healed up round my forehead last night
After I went to see my uncle in Saskatchewan
I'm married to Pula Puka and the future looks bright
Cause I went to see my uncle in Saskatchewan
I went to see my uncle in Saskatchewan
She straps me to a gurney and hooks up a hose
It harvests my semen and I know where it goes
Into 80 gallon tanks where it's temporarily froze
We are insinuating into alien holes
And the blood flows out around a human nose
Stuff them in the freezer before they decompose
Right in the middle of the night
In the barn, on the farm
In the barn, on the farm in Saskatchewan
This stale town is so
Slippery
So often
Don't know if it has cigarettes on you
Live, die in my own town
Él acudió
He is alive
Give me
who's strangely going by a very weird name on email,
Ramos Smooky.
Anyway, it's Reverend Absinthe.
We haven't seen him in a while.
I married him and his wife together at 1X Day.
And he was saying,
can replacement church membership cards be purchased?
How much are they?
I'm goddamn sick and tired of mother...
Christian...
cuss words getting in my face with their new, new world odor.
White Christian nationalism has me down.
And I feel that it's time to strike back with further psychological warfare.
I had kind of reached a detente with the religio pinks, but no.
I figured the demise of any pretense of a justice department
is a good news.
And there's enough reason to put in my request.
I think my skull is about to implode.
For that matter, do you sell accelerate global warming stickers?
The sooner these monkey boy parasites are off this rock,
the better we'll all be.
The demise of humanity may well be preferable to listening to the endless whine of Christian snowflakes
and Trump suckling nincompoops.
Rush fucking Limbaugh got the Medal of Freedom.
I'm sorry.
It's like real life has become an addendum to the dateline for dominance in Book of the Subgenius.
I'd say you can't make this stuff up.
But sci-fi did.
And I'm including the works of Drummond, Stang, etc. in that genre.
Well, it's dogs.
Meanwhile, while I'm busy plotting and scheming the destruction of the normals,
wringing my hands and scowling furiously,
I need something to wave in their faces.
For that matter, I haven't seen my all-present-life.
I haven't seen my all-purpose-excuse document in about a zillion years either.
It's in an envelope somewhere with the remainder of a bunch of Xerox stickers
Reverend Rash and I made in 1991 and distributed liberally around the walls and poles of Northeast Ohio.
I'm assuming that likely my only option is purchasing a new membership
for any of several possible reasons.
Don't worry, I'll still avoid events.
The world profits or suffers.
More from the infliction of my presence among the normals
than the congregation benefits from my presence at subgenius events.
Actually, I wrote this guy back and said,
Oh, tell me where your dress is. I'll send you a replacement pack.
I didn't have any problem with him.
I've never in my life been so thoroughly fed up with the arrogance, ignorance, denial, and stupidity of humanity,
particularly the God-botherers.
I'm so angry I could shit a porcupine.
Now, sometimes I literally weep for the probable loss of the future of mankind.
I wish I was kidding.
I do too, but I'm much more sad about the animals and plants.
My capacity for denial fled the day Trump announced he was running.
It was a foregone conclusion that he was just the Trump-shaped guy
to fill the Trump-shaped gap.
I was the Trump-shaped void in the White House,
predicted by science fiction and comics for most of the last century.
The first three months after his election felt like I was walking through gelatin.
I knew the nightmare was real.
Yours united against the man,
Reverend Absinthe, would-be proprietor of the bogus Ohio Institute of Neo-Surreal Absurdism
and Neo-Absurd Surrealism.
Have a good week.
P.S.
This is a long P.S.
When are the dummies going to ask why Jesus isn't backeth yet?
I mean, has it even occurred to them that maybe he's being detained or something?
Maybe he needs their help.
Maybe God Jr. got grounded by Daddy over the New Testament.
Maybe Mr. Satan has him in Savior Jail or something.
Or maybe it's a deadbeat dad sort of thing.
Hey, humans, I'm just popping out for a pack of smokes.
I'll be back in ten minutes, I promise.
Signed, God.
For fuck's sake, where is their sense of time?
It's been two thousand years since Jesus was here,
let alone the old man in the sky.
God hassled the old-timey Jews on pretty much a daily basis,
all up in their business like an omnipotent Gladys Kravitz.
And his whole game,
his whole gig was like setting them up to resist doing something he knew perfectly well
at least one of them would be unable to resist doing.
And then punishing all of them as soon as some poor schlemiel
up and breaks whatever no-shell fish on Tuesday and stone women for smoking
bullshit that he made up that month.
He couldn't keep out of their business for ten minutes.
It's been two thousand years, you dopes!
Get wise!
God, the original anti-semite.
Man, we need an attorney.
You think Mayor Rudy is up for starting a class action against old Yee Hoover?
He's probably crazy enough.
I gotta say, the only real reason I want that membership card
is so I can use it to harass that kind of Christians at this point.
I mean, for at least fifteen years I've radiated such an effective aura
of recalcitrant non-convertibility that those idiots just don't care.
They just know better as soon as they see me.
I can't remember the last time someone suggested I find Jesus.
Well, maybe you should go look for the fucker.
He isn't my problem other than that his fan club is all up on my dick.
But now it's their turn.
Look out, street preacher.
Welcome to Doutsville population, my fully warrantied and unsettlingly acerbic interruption of your megaphones.
Seriously, I offer a warranty.
They can't have their money back.
If they don't beat it.
I can and have made street preachers give up and leave the streets of Athens.
And I will do so again.
I've had it with this Keystone Cops version of religion.
Believe all the crazy shit you want, but when you start controlling my government,
it becomes my business.
PSS.
Are you ever going to finish High Weirdness Volume 2?
No, that's called the Internet.
PSSS.
You know those Who's John Galt stickers?
I want a Who's Harry Seldon sticker.
That's a reference to the Foundation series by Asimov.
If you aren't familiar with it, the gag will make no damn sense, for which I apologize.
Well, I've read the whole Foundation series.
I know. I get it. It's funny.
Enough of this. I sat down to fire off a paragraph and ended up dumping half my religion gags on you.
And Reverend Absinthe, as you may be hearing now,
I took the opportunity to say,
I took full advantage of that.
I thought that was a great rant.
Oh, here's a bit of my answer to him.
I told him it was a great rant.
And I said, maybe when I'm not drunk, I might read it on the air
from my 1991 Radio Shack home studio here.
Oh, Reverend Absinthe, I hear you.
Imagine how it is for me, living right in the bowels of Ameristan,
in a rural Texas town of 2,400 people,
of whom 90% are Republicans, Christians, white, and...
And, well, most of them are real nice folks.
That's what makes this whole thing so weird.
But, yes, indeed, it is all too much like the ridiculously right-wing worlds posited
in my old movie, Let's Visit the World of the Future,
and in Dateline for Dominance and everything.
And, uh...
Yeah.
Okay.
Okay, okay.
Slack. Slack.
And, friends, the music in the background through all of that
was from the album Witch Disco by Einstein's Secret Orchestra.
And you can't get that CD anymore.
Um...
Boy, I miss old Chaz.
Uh...
Let's definitely play that together,
And the Chaz type strat, let's do that.
Oooh, fold.
So true.
That's ridiculous.
Look at that.
Because this song isongeous.
I want an open mic.
I just open a mic and talk.
Whip it out.
I'll press stop.
Sometimes I like to rap to a fleet five to the bar beat,
like music heard in Greece and points east.
Here's Reverend Watt DeFox's
emergency post X-Day sermon rap.
Come on, you don't really think
only a pink boy would do this kind of shit.
I jixed it when I thought
what if the X-ists yet again fail to show up?
Bob forbid.
Here's what I'm sure I didn't think.
You don't really think you're gonna come too, do you?
If you think you've got another thing coming,
you got another thing coming.
I never have thought
if you think you're coming too
just because that other thing you got's about to come,
I'm sorry, you're not coming too.
And nobody thought,
not until we know we won't be coming too,
do we have a chance of getting off on it,
whatever it turns out to be.
Come on, you don't think I'd really ask
if you got another thing coming, do you?
No one ever thinks,
reality on line one and on two, too.
Now nobody's thinking,
to-to-to,
I know what else you're not thinking,
going so soon I wouldn't hear of it,
why my little party's just beginning.
Da-ba-da-da-da-da-da-da.
And another thing no one here is thinking is,
what is reality?
I know because I was always a record breaker,
I broke a lot of my parents' records,
and then I came highly record-mended to school.
I sat in the class and I skipped.
I sat and skipped at my desk and skipped again.
I broke all the school's records
for all the school that I skipped.
Da-da-da-da-da-da-da.
First the Beatles saved me,
then it was Black Sabbath,
and then, of course, it was Jesus,
then I did time in the university
hearing drones until Marshall McLuhan came
and I didn't have to read anymore.
But you would never ask,
what is reality?
Who the fuck cares?
The real Doctors for Bob, that's who.
According to the records in my head,
they're singing,
Doctors for Bob, you're wanted,
alive or kill me, or come on.
They have ways of making you, Bob.
If anybody here is thinking,
Doctors for Bob,
you're still wanted, it's worth repeated.
They have ways to make you, Bob.
Come on.
I have so many, I have so many records.
I broke, I sit and I skip.
Broken, I skip over my records.
Like, paging Doctors for,
skip paging Doctors for Bob?
You don't really think they'll come?
That's asking, who's on first?
I don't know.
No, he's on third.
Then who is on first?
Yes.
Ah, all I know is,
it is not me, and it isn't you.
Prove me wrong.
Fuck me.
Please.
I'm kidding.
But I have found the most reliably,
effective, contraceptive is my personality.
You're welcome and thank you, or kill me.
So that was the end.
And then if you will remember,
then don't,
so that was the end.
And then if you will remember,
then don't forget anybody.
Anybody?
Anybody can be a radio.
So tune in to W.O.V.E.
Nobody thinks that we have waves to make you come
on Radio WUV.
We wuv it as wavy as we can wet.
Oh yes we do, don't we?
We all wuv, wubbin' a wiggle potion,
a motion lotion.
Oh yes we all do.
Come on, you don't really think I'm about to come all over queer like?
I'll spare you if you've got a rod that that would spoil.
But, but, but, but, and, uh,
or if your squid would dry and tighten at the sight.
A-dutton, da-dutton, dutton.
You see how hard I'm trying to make slack?
Of course it can't be made,
and trying hard is bullshit, of course.
I bet all I've done spittin' this is reveal my pink boy.
Yeah.
You'll be stepping on me to climb aboard the Exist ship on July 5th next year, or sometime.
Soon anyway.
Remain calm.
Take comfort in knowing I will be trampled alive
as you're running up the ramps to board the Exist flying saucers,
just like it was all a dream of that Who concert in Cleveland or something.
Nothing.
I'm Reverend What the Fock.
Thank you.
It's fun.
It's another ceramic box.
ней.
åh.
I'll see you next time.
I wish you all could see.
I wish you all could hear.
Ah, yes.
Ah.
It's just this little chromium switch
switch.
Yes.
You people are so superstitious.
Full consciousness now.
Existence.
All right.
It's Hour of Slack, number 1,799.
And it's X Day, July 5th.
Caffeinas.
Obviously not 1998.
And that wonderful collage was by Suzy the Flusy.
And there's a whole lot more of that.
Her insanely graceful and complicated edits,
which are the envy of all radio sample assemblers.
But this church is very lucky to have
the most adept audio collagist in the known universe.
Genius.
A capacity for taking infinite pains.
Working for it.
Working on those little tapes
with which she was a student.
And razor blades.
Oh wait, they don't do it that way anymore, do they?
Actually, she does.
She does it with the pause button.
Wow.
And computers.
Just hit it with your pause
and the computer does everything else.
Yeah.
So it's good that automation
has kept up with this aspect of home industry.
Even here in the latter hind end times.
Here, I'll turn the mic down
and you just have to lean right into it,
Reverend Angry Larry.
Let's try this.
Okay.
Put your nose to the grindstone,
your shoulder to the wheel.
There you go.
And your lips right next to the mic.
You know, talk into it so that we can...
Talk into it so we can understand what you're saying.
Yeah, yeah.
So we get a sound test.
I got you.
Yeah.
Check, test, test.
Over the microphone.
Don't eat the brown ass.
Check, check, test.
Check off.
Technical.
Every show out here starts this way.
Well, you have to make sure.
It's a show.
It's a struggle.
That it's getting through.
It is a struggle.
You have to make sure that you're audible first and above all.
Well, I'm...
So we're planning to have the beer tasting party soon.
Yeah.
Oh, yes.
There'll be...
Well, I started...
Lurching and colliding with the furniture.
So the schedule today is this and then is there an Ask Dr. Howell?
Here, let's see.
Let's see that.
It says there is a Bull Dada auction and an Ask Dr. Howell on this day.
There is?
So it says in the...
No, actually this day where it was supposed to be, we were going to be on the flying saucers
destroying the god damn human vermin.
Well, just check the column there on the left.
I saw a print...
Oh, or I forgot about the or part.
Or everybody goes back to bed for a while.
Check.
Five hours in my case.
Followed by hours of cursing...
Check.
Moaning and excuses in the cafe...
Or various camps and Ask Dr. Howell...
That's me.
Bull Dada auction and rant slash jams.
Okay, well, I'm thinking that the rant slash jams will be beer tasting.
Fuel.
Beer tasting, yeah.
You can begin the Bull Dada auction or just put it off to another day if you want.
You have the power.
We don't have much stuff.
We really don't.
Oh, I thought we had a robot.
Well, we do have a robot.
A robot.
And we have a dick.
Uh-huh.
And we have...
Okay.
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
And some other things.
And what happened to that hideous robot alien baby machine that Legume made?
What's your diagnosis, Doc?
Did Philo leave it in his barn?
This is like a disco robot called Strobot that, when in good health, emits a stroblite
dangerous to epileptics and others who are unusually susceptible.
But I think it has no working batteries in it.
We'll have to figure something out.
What's your diagnosis, Doc?
I don't think we've gotten any results.
So, uh, it's a robot.
I don't think we've got any information on them now.
I have no idea where that came from.
I'm assuming it was something that didn't sell at the last X Day Drill.
They call him Strobot.
Or someone brought it.
Look at the button on the instep of his left foot.
That controls something.
There's a button on that.
Red button there.
About a foot and a half foot tall toy robot.
It's not a familiar design to me.
No, it's not.
It says it's a laser strobot, which means it probably blinks.
The head suggests another head wearing headphones.
You see, it's like a DJ, a disco DJ strobot.
Oh, yeah, that's it.
It's a disco DJ strobot.
And not only that, it says laser strobot.
Laser, that's like quantum.
That means everything futuristic and unexplainable.
So power it up, and the mini robo disco should take place.
How many batteries does it require?
It takes four AA's, which I have at my camp.
Well, we could attempt to revitalize a strobot right here, just to demonstrate.
Are you sure we want to power that thing up?
This actually could have been the vehicle.
Bob may have dropped this off for us to experiment with us as a test.
Yes, we never know when the master cometh.
Now, if it starts smoking and catches fire, then we'll know that it was Bob.
Activate it gently.
Yeah, remember what happened when they've turned on certain alien artifacts.
He's loading the batteries into the...
The disco robot.
Disco robot, ladies and gentlemen.
The thorax is open, and the batteries are going in now.
In just a moment, we will test the mechanics of the dusty, apparently not frequently used robot.
My prediction is nothing will happen.
He's got lights.
Oh, good.
Press that red button on his shoe.
That button on his shoe, the little red button.
Oh, friends.
This is strobing.
It's so exciting.
If only the radio audience could, or anyone could see the amazing...
Nothing.
It does nothing when you press the button on his shoe.
He's still not doing anything.
There's no strobing, no disco music.
Yep, that's the X-Day robot.
That's our mascot for this X-Day.
A faint light feebly glimmers out as a reward for the installation of all the batteries.
Oh, yeah, he's...
Just a couple of blinks on the arm there, and that's about it.
What is it with those three buttons?
They're just buttons on his chest.
Do they do anything?
Oh, they don't do anything.
Those are just molded plastic.
Those are just robo-bling.
I shouldn't look into its fist because, you know, there could be some kind of a hidden laser in there.
It says laser on it.
Well, that's too bad about strobot, but you've tried the button on his foot numerous times, I'm sure.
He has a hole right here in his fist where he's, like, maybe supposed to hold on to...
He can carry it.
...an offer of peace or a sword.
Okay.
Yeah, either a sword or an olive branch, depending on which planet he's been sent to.
Yes, and then when he's...
And when you activate him, it blows up the whole planet.
As he dazzles him with strobes which destroy their will and ability to act.
Did somebody out here actually bring this?
Who brought strobot?
I found it in my basement.
Oh, that's you.
You found the strobot down there?
I found it in our basement, and the thing is, there was almost nothing else in our basement.
I like this story.
We moved everything to Texas.
What the hell was that thing doing there?
That's not very credible.
Now, there's been a whole next day that I missed.
Holy cow, these batteries are really hot, though.
Yeah, there's an interference.
Oh, it is a booby trap.
Attempting to power a strobot can be harmful...
We would have set this thing down.
...to children and other living things.
Yep, pillows.
Those are hot.
It would have burned down this entire camp.
Maybe the state of the art.
Oh, wow.
Yeah.
Well, that's one thing.
Bad rule, Ben.
Okay.
We've got a deadly, malfunctioning toy here.
Which could easily start a fire or a melting battery scenario with splurting battery acid.
Subgenius parents who want to toughen their kids up will love this toy.
So yeah, look for this in the next subgenius catalog.
Yeah, extreme choking hazard.
Extreme choking hazard and will cause flame.
Many parts unsuitable for toddlers.
Beware of electrocation.
It's not a bad looking robot, though.
It's, you know, I've seen many worse.
Poor strobot.
It does symbolize this particular...
Active life.
...ex-day drill.
Drill.
This non-functioning strobot...
Non-functioning...
...is the perfect mascot for yet another...
...another...
...letdown.
Thanks, Bob.
Thanks, Obama.
Thanks...
Well, now you're blaming everyone.
You're blaming Susie for the ticket switcheroo and now poor little strobot.
Thanks, Stang.
I've certainly been hearing that again.
I get so tired of it every year.
Thanks for sparing us over for another year so we can get our affairs in order and make
sure little Timmy gets into medical school.
Well, this will give me time to get my destruction evidence music.
I'm going to get it.
Which is in a museum ready in Glen Rose, Texas, a tourist attraction and destination for Americans
looking for quaint, the queer, the curious, the weird, the...
Showing the final ignoble fate of Noah's Ark.
Right.
We've got the wreck of Noah's Ark.
And we have a fossil robot skeleton.
Yes, you heard me.
A fossil robot skeleton dating from the Lower Cretaceous.
we
although it's not found in exactly
the same excavation
site as the alien skeleton
we're guessing that this robot
was owned by the
alien who's fossil skeleton
we also found also dating
from the lower cretaceous
on display at
Stang Ranch
which will be open to the public
as soon as the creation
museum in Kentucky
is flooded
and washed away
the one that looks like Noah's Ark
didn't they have trouble like that
they were nearly washed away
and then they tried to sue somebody
the almighty God
because someone almost
flooded them out of their ark
God can be bribed
there's
there was a
beautiful old
stone church
in Cleveland
right near
the case western
well the big hospital
Cleveland Clinic
giant famous
world famous huge complex
what denomination of church was it
I think Catholic
and the hospital wanted
that ground
that hallowed ground for a parking lot
for their hospital they really wanted it
was there a gothic building there
the monks said no
this is the Lord's house
and they said no we're going to go to the church
it wasn't right
the hospital offered God
some sort of payment
I'm not sure what
may have been just money
and God sent a lightning bolt
that set fire to that church
and burned it down
honestly
and so now there is a parking lot
for the Cleveland Clinic there
much needed parking lot
one less house
a classic beautiful old house of God
but you might call the hospital
a house of God
more people go to meet their guests a lot of times now
maker in hospitals than anywhere else.
Yeah, that's true.
Wait a minute. What does that tell you?
It's just a
slaughterhouse in there.
That's true. Somebody's paying
someone.
The infernal hosts are also
present there around the bed
of the dying
according to Jack T. Chick.
Angels and demons are
standing around ministering
to their patients right up
to the end.
Ready to fight over that struggling
soul. Which will it
be? Bob, the devil, or God?
Remember that one Chick
comic where the demons are saying,
that was a close one, but we got him.
Those were my
demons. Yes.
Cartoony but vicious demons.
Thank goodness for evil.
Save me from heaven.
Ha, ha, ha.
That's what we say.
And after all,
heaven
might not be.
Are those batteries still warm?
Oh, yeah.
We could have been killed.
They could have blown up right here at me.
Right.
Are you sure you put them
right in the robot?
Are you sure you settled them
correctly in the
place where they were supposed to be?
I mean, you didn't put in one
backwards or anything like that.
No.
Oh, but now I do understand why Stang said,
oh, I have batteries here.
Use these.
Didn't you say a sign up there that says,
no sarcasm allowed?
That's not sarcasm.
No sarcasm.
That's attempted murder.
That's not sarcasm.
I always talk this way.
Sarcasm doesn't become you, Reverend Angry Larry.
Crabbiness.
There you go.
Yes, that defines you.
That's completely right there.
Grumpiness.
Yes.
So angry.
So very angry.
Slightly miffed Lawrence.
That's another identity.
For different hours, different days,
different occasions.
That's the pink Angry Larry.
Oh, the slightly miffed?
Yeah.
The peevish and irritated.
The passive aggressive Lawrence.
The barely visibly vexed.
The get off my lawn Lawrence.
The seething with rage,
vein pulsing, red faced,
homicidal neighbor.
Well, there's some new faces here.
Well, there are more bodies.
Some don't exactly have what you would call faces.
More details just arrived.
And more are here at X Day.
And we have a full program for them,
don't we, Reverend Stang?
Legendary Bob, the auction,
the Bulldada auction,
and the Ask Dr. Howell.
Well, normally at the Bulldada auction
we have boxes and boxes of VHS tapes.
Everybody.
Everybody loves those.
Paperback books.
Comics.
Comic books.
I don't see any back here.
Generally huge stacks of DVDs and CDs
that I usually end up buying.
DVDs and CDs.
So we don't have those?
Is that what you're saying?
Well, we have that dangerous robot.
And there are some other things.
But no one ever said
Bulldada auction had to be long.
It just said it had to go on.
So whatever few items are there,
that will generate excitement.
I'm pretty sure, judging by the clothing
worn by most members of our audience,
that the people we're waiting for
for the auction aren't here yet.
The ones with money.
I see.
Yeah.
Well, we could certainly postpone the...
Oh, that's small.
Okay, well, good.
There they are, waving their checkbooks.
Waving their money.
They're sitting on their right to purchase
subgenius artifacts at this special time.
We didn't say everyone.
Hey, Bob, I'm seeing color.
The only color Bob sees is green.
Color is money.
They may be pink, but their money is green.
How often we've heard this simple apothegm.
Yeah, and yet sometimes I forget those aphorisms.
It's been so...
I've been in this church so long,
I sometimes forget the important things.
One gets wrapped up in the little details.
Right, in these doctrinal...
Arguments over imagery of bears and things like that.
And then we forget the basic things,
like too much is always better than not enough.
And fuck them if they can't take a joke.
Almost as bad.
Yes, yes.
Yeah, fuck them if they can't take a joke
are the one rule that we live by.
And actually, it is the only rule worth living by.
At least I've...
I've tried all the other ones
and ended up in the hospital most times.
Most of Bob's rules.
Eventually we'll put you in the hospital,
but fuck them if they can't take a joke.
The worst thing that'll happen is
you may have to take some special medicine for a while.
Ah, but don't just eat that hamburger.
Eat the hell out of it.
And see, you took that to heart.
No pun intended.
To a heart attack.
Yeah, see?
Right straight to the hospital.
Yeah, I took it to the hospital.
But...
The point is that when you eat the hell out of a hamburger,
as it says in our written works,
you're providing slack for yourself,
which has a health value
apart from any physiological artery clogging
or anything like that that may be going on.
Right, slack is more beneficial to health than food.
It's important.
Well, some food is just not health food.
You've got to admit.
Either everything is anhedonic and tasteless
and superficial,
and it's supposed to make you feel virtuous for eating it,
or it is full of fats and sugars
and all the chemical craftiness
that our civilization can add to salty bag snacks.
That makes you feel really good.
Yes, it makes you feel you're absorbing those carbohydrates
which internally are being turned into sugars,
creating a huge glycemic spike on the spot.
Yes, my mouth is watering.
Meanwhile, harmful vegetable proteins called lectins
rush to the intestinal wall,
which they penetrate since it's only one cellular width through at that point.
The body, thinking itself invaded,
rushes leukocytes to the spot,
and the battle royal of the leaky gut
begins in the mesenteric space outside the intestine.
At least some say.
Well, speaking of food,
where's the...
When's the potluck dinner?
Yes, I heard a story of such a feast.
We brought paper plates.
I don't know when the potluck is.
I mean, there's pancakes for Bob, and that's tomorrow.
We brought the pot and the paper plates.
But did you bring the luck?
We're out of luck.
Yeah, if you don't have the luck,
then I'm afraid you can only be an interested spectator
in their sumptuous meal.
Hmm.
However, that's...
No, when...
When...
Either here or there.
When would we do that?
And what's the pancake?
The pancake breakfast.
The pancake breakfast is tomorrow.
That hinges on potluck.
Pancake.
That's tomorrow.
Big out is tomorrow, not today.
In the morning?
Yes.
You can roll these pancakes.
Tomorrow morning is the pancake breakfast.
Yes.
That's when we'll break out the scrapple,
the sacred scrapple, right?
If there is scrapple here.
Hasn't he gone home?
Oh, there is.
The pressure's brought up.
Oh, okay, good.
All right, okay.
All right.
Well...
Yeah.
Yeah, tomorrow morning is...
After 10.
St. Scrapple's Day.
Is...
Yes, pancakes for Bob.
I remember them.
I got up at 6 o'clock this morning.
That was heroic and noble.
Princess Louise mimicking a sad violin.
Uh-huh, 6 o'clock.
Well, you see, someone thought that 7 o'clock sounded...
We were going to rise fresh-faced and with our faces...
I think we were going to rise fresh-faced and with our faces scrubbed to meet our dear friend
and his armada of alien minions.
Good.
Let that be a lesson to anyone who wants to form their own religion.
When you pick your day of rupture, don't do it at 7 in the morning.
Have it be after work, you know, give some time for dinner and run a few errands.
Who knows what time that is to be X-ed?
Exactly.
Uh...
That's why you said any day can be X-day.
When you have a good...
Exactly.
I got a message from Rocknar, Governor Rocknar.
When?
This morning.
Is he heading this way?
Oh my God, we were just talking about him yesterday.
What's he have to say?
He said, every day is X-day when you live in Colorado.
Okay, is that where he's at now?
Implying that if you have legal marijuana, then every day is X-day.
The Mile High City.
As if everything's centered around some cheap conspiracy.
Yeah.
A conspiracy street drug.
Wow.
Some form of ketamine.
Whereas actually, you know, every day is X-day if you have enough froth.
Why, yes.
That's different.
I'm glad you reminded me of that.
Yeah, speaking of which, I need my allergy treatment.
Well, while you're taking care of that...
I can tell.
We can go over tonight's schedule once again.
Princess, did you bring that inhaler?
Oh, no, I've got it.
I've got my inhaler.
This will work.
Oh, Hal's got one too.
Allergies.
I need more allergies.
Quick, I need to hit a...
There's a script.
Ah, here is the poem that was...
And it's for the...
This is for the butt hurt bears.
Right.
Actually, the princess...
When we offer them at the auction, the bull dada auction.
Princess, we recited that.
Oh, I see.
I see the instructions there.
You also recited them.
Yeah.
Oh.
And now there's a request that I recite them.
But that has to be during the...
Well, here, you hand me the inhaler and you can go and recite it.
During the bull dada auction, this is not...
Now is not the time to do it.
When one is hawking the butt hurt bears, then one reads this copy.
It's pollen.
You can't get up.
I better leave that allergy alone.
Never had allergies before.
You have liquid refreshment there at your stand.
I've been a hermit in a cedar forest, honestly, for the last year.
In a cedar chest.
Cedar and juniper forest, hiding out deep in the woods.
I'm not exaggerating or kidding.
It affected me in a way that never happened when I was only there every...
Every year.
I spent there the whole summer.
Cedarized your lungs.
Yeah.
The pollen got in.
The cactus mites got in.
Dreadful.
Simply dreadful.
The deadly bubonic mice bugs got in.
Everything got in.
Those...
A rattlesnake started to come in the kitchen door one day.
When Princess We opened the door, the snake was there.
She slammed the door in the snake's face.
An old rare rattlesnake.
He slithered off.
And then she didn't emerge from the house for another 24 hours.
Yes.
Same sort of thing happened to me.
Looking for a nice cool spot.
With rattlesnake?
No, it was with a tarantula.
Oh, tarantula.
But listen, when you're a kid, you don't...
I used to spend my summers in Athens, Arcadia, Louisiana.
And I remember going out to the kitchen to get a glass of milk and there was a tarantula
walking across the...
They can't hurt you.
They're friendly.
Oh, I know.
But when you're a kid, you think about when you're sleeping that you're going to wake
up and one's going to be on your face.
Yes.
So, yeah.
Or on your shoulder.
Everyone wants to be a radioactive one.
Maybe you should...
That's what I'm getting at.
Maybe you should have let it bite you.
Maybe it did.
That's the reason why I'm from another planet.
It's a mild sting.
Or I get abducted every once in a while from, you know...
The fangs do penetrate.
There is an injection of venom.
Oh, okay.
They...
The aliens programmed me to only dream about being abducted.
How often?
So that way they didn't have to actually abduct me.
How frequently?
They just give me the night hag dreams.
Always?
Now they're night greys.
Every night?
No.
Only...
Some nights?
You only have to go through that once.
Selected nights.
I'm still rubbing my fundament from that old probe.
That dream probe.
Ouch.
That was actually a dream.
It could have been.
Well, they said so.
Of course they said so.
They programmed me to believe it was just a dream.
It's just a dream.
Whitley-Striper thing.
Yeah.
What we did to you, it didn't really happen.
It's just a dream.
Yeah.
Aliens programmed me not to be able to see flying saucers when everybody else can.
And Bigfoot.
That's true.
Well, I mean, everybody else said they saw the flying saucer and I didn't see anything.
That fateful night.
In windswept South Dakota.
Saucer hell.
And that was a saucer sighting, eh?
Yep.
I actually spent that night on horseback with an Indian named Lorenzo Black Lance looking
for a flying saucer.
At the age of 22, yes, that happened to me.
I rode around the prairie with an Indian looking for a flying saucer.
And I remember thinking...
I'm writing to myself, I'm riding around the prairie with an Indian, Native American,
Lakota specifically, looking for a flying saucer just like Richard Dreyfuss in Close
Encounters.
I hadn't seen it, but Lorenzo had.
And he was like Richard Dreyfuss.
He couldn't let it go.
He had to see it again.
But of course it didn't come back.
They never do.
And for many years, when you wanted to.
As we learned this morning.
They'll always do it.
That's when they play hard to get.
Teasing.
Who?
The aliens.
Oh, yeah.
Whichever alien.
All of them, basically.
The X's are the only ones we care about.
These were probably no count greys and crap.
You know, just all the...
Who cares about that?
Those are...
They're aliens, but they're the kind that crash their saucers.
They have mechanical objects that they fly around with.
Oh, thank you.
You ain't nothing but a rabbit.
You ain't no Fred Ho-Mod.
You ain't nothing but a...
Or so says Lemur.
Friends, we're going to close with some music from the 22 X Day Drill from a loose jam that
I recorded the night of July 4th.
The jam is good, but the recording is...
Reelistic.
In that Dr. Philodrummond and yours truly were standing a bit too close to the mic and
blabbering at each other almost as loud as the band.
So it sounds just like you're really there at the campground.
I have no photos, but what's left of my memory insists that it's Reverend Angry Larry playing
both bass and drums simultaneously.
He really does that.
And the strange Reverend X on guitar.
With a kind of Zoot Horn Rollo or Winged Eel Fingerling style.
Princess Wee Ar Doe is the flautist standing there on one leg like a stork.
I'm not sure who else might have been involved.
Anyway, this one is entitled Rev-X is a Frop God.
Open Skull tamper de Roi de Mar.
I was just looking to find out what was Mr. Rock doing in there earlier
in that shout is how does the talk stop.
Steve coalえ r tutti.
He himself poop, 알아 da.
orbitals boot made potty?
Who knows.
There must have been an era or something.
He just went into town on a bull,, because he thought nothing most especially
of golf, that would be proud of him you know.
Imagine while he's smoking Pets pee then laughing, but shit locks you when you
Th which the son escape from here.
Red Max is like a fool!
He's better than Megamax!
Red Max is getting drunk now!
You know what?
You got it, man.
You got it.
What is that?
You don't get culture like that just anywhere.
What is it?
It looks like it needs static.
It's like it needs static.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
As I always say, the church lost 5,000 pounds.
Sorry?
So there are at least three levers in your average pair of nail clippers.
Oh, I see.
Every pair of nail clippers.
And one wheel.
Or is it a wheel?
Is it the thing that allows you to turn the thing around?
Is that actually a wheel or is that not a wheel?
What is it?
It's not a wheel.
It's a steering wheel.
It doesn't carry any weight.
It's just kind of a lever.
It's like a circle.
It's like a...
It's like a lever when you wouldn't...
Uh...
What's that?
Your wheels.
Your wheel.
You're not turning the thing around.
Uh...
I'm sorry.
We don't feel right.
What do you mean?
You have access to rock time.
I hold the seven bladed windbreaker.
The wheels that turn are behind me.
I think backwards.
Thank you, Onan, for a nice, dreamy good night.
Subgenius.com.
Praise Bob.