Oh my god!
My friend, can your heart stand the shocking facts about Bob?
If you think that it's actually true, then please find that package, Bob.
Bob!
Hello there.
You know, I've been all around this wonderful world of ours,
and in all this world, nothing else is Bob.
Bob!
It's a beautiful thing.
Here comes a beautiful thing named Princess Leigh.
A beautiful world.
Oh, she came to get the camera.
To get the telephone.
Oh, her name's Doug.
That's the camera.
One and only Doug on Earth, is what it says.
Oh, yours says the one and only Doug on Earth?
That's one thing we...
That's what my name tag says.
I don't know if we...
You mentioned this on the show.
Yes.
I made the mistake of, on the 19X Day Facebook page,
in all sincerity, going...
And I felt like I needed to say this,
because Facebook switched me over to my human name.
I couldn't get my real name back.
That was your boss, too.
So I put on Facebook as Doug Smith.
Doug Smith.
I said, please, my fellow subgeniuses, the new folks,
you know, don't call me Doug.
Well...
I instantly realized, after posting it,
I realized I'd done the wrong thing.
And sure enough, everyone here is named Doug.
Oh, joke.
They make name tags with the name Doug on them.
Oh, I know. I've seen them.
Yes.
That's all you can see.
It's just Doug's all the way down.
Lois may guess my secret identity.
Must think fast.
I told everyone not to call me Steve or Earl or...
That's what I should have done.
Because I was actually the first one to take your post,
and I cut and pasted immediately after yours
and switched it around.
And then everyone jumped on the bandwagon.
Yeah.
Don't call me this.
Don't call me that.
Yeah.
I was like...
But I don't know this Doug character,
but the funny thing is his name was all over the place.
Well, it's one more of those examples of what happens
when you tell subgeniuses,
subgeniuses not to do something.
Or if you even ask politely for them not to do something,
that's how to get them to do something.
But yet you still can't say,
hey, give me $100,
or don't give me $100 when you're here.
I tried that.
That was the first thing I did,
is don't give Reverend Stang money.
Yeah.
That's like telling him...
All your money.
Don't give a clown drugs.
Drugs, right.
Ta-da.
The first thing you want to do is give that clown some dope.
Don't get K-Rob Stone,
before the show.
Well, that's one of ours.
There are many rules,
but you know, sometimes...
Don't post pictures or memes involving bears.
Consequently,
the church was in a sea of bear gags
until it was gagging on bear gags.
It got a bear plug.
Susie came up with a great...
A what?
A bear plug.
A tampion, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Susie came up with a much better idea.
A much better thing of calling it,
and that would be...
You said bear canola.
Yeah, bear canola.
Reverend Zaphod suggested the same thing.
The Ursus canola.
Yeah.
Is the species name of the rape bear,
because canola is made from rape.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Yes.
Now, you could put that on a shirt,
and people would not think twice about it,
but if you put bear rape...
Oh, I'm sorry.
Can I say that?
You have to now.
Well, yeah, I have to now.
All right.
But let it be said here
that no one is thinking of inconveniencing a bear in any way.
No, these are bears that rape young subgenius men
if they can capture them,
and they do it for seven years.
They're seven-year rape bears,
which makes it a thousand times worse,
and we're not saying rape is funny.
We're saying that rape bears,
are funny.
Like the one in that Leonardo DiCaprio movie?
Yeah.
Does that bear actually do anything besides mauling?
It was on the internet for a long time.
Oh, the bear rapes him.
You can see it.
I was waiting to see that, and it didn't.
You saw the movie?
Yeah, I saw the movie.
I didn't get that.
It's a great movie.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, I watched closely.
I was waiting to see the bear-rape Leonardo DiCaprio.
Well, the people who can't be taken in
by the bear.
They can't be taken in by anything,
have decided not to be taken in
by the idea that the bear didn't rape Leonardo.
I mean, do you think people left the theater
when they realized that he didn't?
Some, probably.
Yeah.
Like, oh, what a jip.
And I paid 19 bucks.
Yeah, and $20 for a bag of popcorn.
I didn't even see that bear's willy.
Yeah.
I didn't even see a full frontal of the bear.
I still don't know.
I still think it's forked.
I have no idea.
That was just a guy in a suit.
It's a Jungle Book movie.
It's a CGI suit.
Bring back the bear necessities song.
That's part of the sex video.
It's in the picture.
Not in the Leonardo DiCaprio one,
but in the live action double,
I mean, you know, the Jungle Book.
That would be a funny thing to re-edit
that scene in the Leonardo DiCaprio
and put bear necessities playing behind it.
Don't let me keep you back.
I may have to work on that.
Much work for subgeniuses to do in this world.
All to get a joke, a very, very inside joke.
Yeah.
Messing with the mouse, that's brave.
Subgeniuses have been known to slave away for years
on one stupid inside joke.
One minuscule joke that only a handful of people get.
Right.
And now you've totally forgotten about it.
Well, that's the thing.
You stop and into the vacuum rushes
the next strangely configured subgenius joke.
Yeah.
The last animal video I edited was about our newt.
And when I picked the music for it,
I knew that only three people would really get it.
But it's so well done.
Haven't you got any blowback from that?
Has anyone said anything about it?
Yeah.
Titor said that he could watch when that little piece,
that newt spits a little white thing out of his mouth.
He says, I could sit and watch that all day.
That's amazing.
Yeah.
It's great the way you have that synchronized.
It's a wonderful, wonderful.
Well, I used the music and some soundtrack voice
from The Beast from 20,000 Fathoms.
Yes.
Cecil Kellaway's excited blow-by-blow description of the creature.
Yeah.
That was mainly for you, Dr. Howell.
I figured you'd get a chuckle out of it.
Oh, I loved it.
About three other people would get it.
I hope I can play it on my faltering computer
when I return to work.
I hope I can play it where I live.
Well, I'll just pull out my phone and play it right now.
See, I've got magic TV right in my pocket.
I can sit and watch Walking Dead right now.
Well, that's all right.
Well, whip it out.
We know your technological capability.
I got this wax tablet that you can write on
and then it disappears just like that.
Yeah, that's a tablet all right.
An abacus?
I got my tablet.
Your etch-a-sketch.
I've been enjoying learning new technology
like lawnmowers and hairbrushes, razor blades.
Hairbrushes?
Yeah.
I never used those.
Deodorant.
I never used any of that modern-day stuff.
That electric hairbrush thing was...
Yeah.
You'd think it would have taken off real well.
That was one of Bob's craziest schemes,
the electric hairbrush.
Yeah.
They have electric toothbrushes,
electric all sorts of things.
Electric toothbrushes are nothing,
but something for women to, well, you know.
Yeah, yeah.
They're good for that.
Dental hygiene.
Are they good for that, Susie?
Electric toothbrushes?
It took me a while to realize you could turn them around
and not have to use the brush side.
You guys are talking about toilet...
But I'm British.
I'm pretty tough.
You're talking about toilet...
Using those toilet paper, right?
Electric toothbrushes, toilet paper.
I never thought about that, but...
Well, that was the only thing I could think of.
Well, no.
For wiping?
Yeah, yeah.
I guess they get these old recesses.
For getting deep in there,
to get that thing all just sparkly clean.
That's what I thought they were for.
Well, I suppose, you know.
Now, I've had a problem with the...
No wonder Princess Weasel is complaining about the taste.
God.
Well, you do have to use paste.
Butt paste.
Yeah, yeah.
Boudreaux's butt paste is what I usually use.
That's my favorite brand.
I wondered why that stuff was by your toothpaste.
There's more product placement there.
I've been using Spackle.
Spackle.
Wow.
Spackle that cracked shell.
No.
It's smooth now.
Oh, yeah.
All the little wrinkly bits.
You sit down on that belt sander.
Yeah.
Sparkle.
Yeah, you get that thing out nice and shiny.
Bag balm and...
No dingleberries.
No.
I was surprised that Sparks came out.
What's with that?
That means you're using JB Weld.
Ah.
There, see?
There's more product placement.
The orange sock brought to you by JB Weld.
Malta meal.
JB Weld.
This is the...
And Ovaltine.
Infinite cascade of product placement.
And Bag Balm.
Yeah, Bag Balm.
Bag Balm and crackling.
The official sponsor of X Day.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, and Big Butt Malt Liquor.
I just thought I'd...
Wait.
There is this stuff called Big Butt Malt Liquor.
Baby butt paste or something like that up at the house.
Oh, yeah.
Boudreaux's butt paste.
Yeah.
It has a picture of a happy baby on it.
Well, I wouldn't be.
Because his ass is no longer chapped.
At least he's happy.
I'd be happy, too, for the same reason.
And there's anti-monkey butt powder.
Right.
Monkey butt powder.
Anti-monkey butt.
For your monkey?
Named Anton?
Yeah.
There's a...
Do ants get on it?
No wonder it needs powder.
There's also a chapstick called chicken poop.
Chicken poo.
Yeah, chicken poo.
Chicken what?
The drugstore in Stangsville advertised monkey...
He even got me chicken poop.
Monkey butt itch and chicken poop and some other...
Well, out of the country...
Childishly named funny...
A lot of diseases.
Poop.
They've got this hair stuff called moco de correa or gorilla snot.
Yeah.
That was it.
That was the other one.
Gorilla snot.
And the logo has an ape's head with a big dollop of snot coming out.
Well, they make gorilla snot for musicians to hold onto the picks.
You put a little bit of that on your fingers and it keeps...
So you don't drop your pick.
That's pretty good.
And they also use it for drummers to put on their drumsticks so they don't lose their
sticks and it's called gorilla snot.
Is there something...
work on pasties. Is this all
Ren and Stimpy's fault? Because I think
that's where it started. No, I don't believe that.
Boogers. Boogers and farts started
appearing on television.
I was using boogers as glue
long before Ren and Stimpy. But recently
there used to be a check on
that. Then a Japanese
book came out and this
according to what I've been able to ascertain
was the start of it all, called
Everybody Poops. Oh yeah.
Which was an incredible seller
and led the way to all
the many books about snot
and farting and so on. Also
Walter the Farting Dog by
William Cotswinkle.
It was an incredible success.
Sold millions of copies.
I have grandkids now.
Everybody followed and
now there's snot
and farts and so on on TV
every time you turn around.
Because it's safe. Well there was the
Barfo-Rama series for young
adults and
senior kids and it involved
the five unfortunate
fluids. Which are like
pee, poop,
spit,
earwax,
and sweat.
And you can get candies in all
those flavors now. I think the
earwax was a stand in for
spuzz, which was a mystery you'd
find out later on.
Spuzz. Earwax.
The first book I read in that series
was Dog Do Afternoon.
It was about the
battle of the little subgenius
kids versus the rich snots.
It starred Al Pug
Chino.
It involved bags of
dog crap. That this kid
had a job picking up dog crap
for pinks. And so he decides
to use it as a weapon.
And he collects bags of it and all of the
rich kids are in this above ground
pool. And there's this
subgenius girl who has joined the rich
kids. They can exploit her.
Her name is Skank.
I felt very close to Skank.
Skank's pretty disgusting.
Why would you say that, Susie the Floozy?
Ah, it works.
But yeah, they coat the edge
of the above ground pool with
Crisco. And then they start
lobbing the dog turds, the sacks of
dog turds. They start throwing the dog turds
in on the rich kids. But Skank
licked the Crisco
off of one side of the pool so
that they can escape.
Wow.
Of course later there's a turnaround
in Skank.
Skank turns on the repressor.
Is this a children's book?
A children's book. Dog do afternoon.
There's a wonderful scene in the janitor's
closet where they...
Don't you love that expression?
The rich kids
shut the subgenius kids
in this janitor's closet.
And there's like this peephole
to the boys' shower
room from the janitor's
closet. And they give the kids
five bucks to fart in the
hole. And all of the
subgenius kids are passing
out one by one from the accumulated
farts. And this one
poor teacher opens the door
and the fart hits her
like a fistful in the face and all these
half-dead kids. And the last
they heard, she went off and joined a cult
after seeing a horrible
spectacle. They're very good books.
Kids these days don't know what they
got. No.
I would have killed for a copy of Jurassic Fart.
Absolutely. I would have traded my brother's
arm for the stuff that kids
can get now. The legend of Big Fart.
There are like 20 of them.
Well, I'll be damned.
And you know, you never find them at thrift
stores because if a kid is lucky enough
to get a Barfarama book,
they hang on to that bastard. It's golden.
Oh, I know what my boys,
grandboys are getting for Christmas.
And a lady writes them.
Their mom's going to be real happy
about that. And a lady writes
them. A lady writes them. See?
Actually, knowing my daughter, she's
probably already got the whole set.
They're being raised as geeks,
she explained to me.
We're raising the boys as geeks.
They were in a kids
theater workshop
all summer and learned
how to swim and
probably learned how to have all
kinds of weird sex that they never told us
about, ever. That's not geek.
I think they're being raised gay.
I wouldn't be surprised.
I wouldn't be at all surprised.
What I'm picturing is,
the Addams Family movie
with Pugsley and Wednesday,
that's what I'm kind of picturing is
they're doing things like that
and not the quote-unquote
normal things that kids do.
You're sick, Larry. I'm sick?
Oh, I know.
Price Bob. Yeah.
And you, sir, are not.
Oh, that's a
mean thing to say.
Hey, I am the Lord
Angry Larry.
Damn. But generally, I'm not angry.
Slash him up and pour some lemon juice on him.
I'm more of a moderately annoyed Larry.
A spritz?
Irritated Larry. Moderately annoyed.
Well, you sure did let your
anger out with your guitar last night
during the rants.
And Reverend Fox
let out a lot of...
Yes, what an incredible recitation.
Oh yeah, that was a good rant.
Apparently, I was the only person who could
hear a lot of it,
ironically.
But everyone else will hear it.
You'll hear it the way I heard it.
On the saucers, yes.
On the hour of slack.
Which is sort of like
a pretend saucer.
Right?
It's going to play on the saucers, right?
This is here? Really?
Yeah, the hour of slack will also play on the saucers.
Only I won't have to do it.
You can't turn it off.
Don't, don't, don't.
That's part of it.
Yeah, but I won't...
We won't have to do it.
We'll have to simulate...
The lacquer created by Juan
will do it a little better than we would be able to.
Sort of like holograms?
Spontaneous, a little more imaginative.
Their pronunciation's just a little better.
Holograms with
intelligence?
No, not holograms.
It'll probably be physical.
Oh, okay.
There'll be another you, another Hal,
another Susie.
I could always use another me.
Androids made out of pork products?
Yeah, by product.
Pork byproducts.
Well, your other me might want to make use of you.
The Scrapple me
will be funnier than the me me.
Than the me me.
Because it's made by
Muam, the ultimate
artificial intelligence.
Better pork than pink.
Dominate your clones.
There will be time.
The problem is
then you have the old problem of
no, no, he's the clone.
No.
Shoot him.
No, no.
I hate it when that happens.
Until someone shoots the real one
and then they're all gone.
Is that how it works?
I think so.
Well, you've been reading too much sci-fi,
Reverend Angry Larry.
Well.
That's just the old script writer's trick.
That's what?
It's vampires that work like that.
Yeah.
Kill the master vampire and all this.
Yeah, but there's still more vampires out there.
He's saying that if you kill the main vampire,
all of them will die.
The cruel vampire.
But,
there's still other vampires out there.
There's other sexes.
Yeah, either they don't die.
They're just not important.
I know because I play one on TV.
A very drunk one.
So.
Yeah, we were going to show
Reverend Angry Larry's TV shows,
but people just aren't watching TV
at this campground.
They're looking at their phones.
Maybe we will tonight in here.
That would be good.
Yeah, okay.
All right.
We've gotten, you know.
Monster movies, Angry Larry.
Yes.
The Teeters really wants the Grindhouse.
Yeah.
We should have a movie.
We've got an orgy of viewing.
Well, talk to Reverend Fox about that
because he's the one with the projector.
Reverend Fox.
It's his fault.
Oh, also, Dr. Leguim wants to rant
through your computer
so everyone can see it.
Don't break it.
Don't do it.
Yeah, so you'll have to put you in touch with him.
No, no.
He's got to be here.
Got to be here.
So, yeah, I guess we'll be watching
the Sir Graveson show this evening.
Well, Dr. Dark's projector,
I think, is acting like it's on the blink
and I think it needs to rest.
On the blink.
It's displaying funny stuff.
They were showing Monsters Crash
the Pajama Party down there earlier.
Yes.
That's Fox's projector.
Yeah.
And Reverend Anna Maul brought a projector
but it only projects one thing,
an instructional film about how to deal with death.
Wow.
You are going to love it.
She was going to give it to the Bulldada auction.
I decided to keep it for the church
because it's going to come in handy.
People are dropping like flies.
And this thing is so cold and clunky.
It's hilarious.
She was projecting it on the full metal Dobbs head
during an insane concert the other night.
Marvelous fusion.
Yeah, I was able to enjoy it
and even film it being projected
on the metal Dobbs head.
It's just kind of a strange image.
Seen here on slide C,
drawer D.
Yeah.
In the repository in Grindstone, Pennsylvania.
This is the calmest X-Day day for me this year.
And the show without music is so calm.
I could...
Oh, that's just because I wasn't playing your favorite music.
I was playing video game music.
It sounds just like monster movie music.
Susie said it didn't sound...
It didn't sound enough like porn.
No, no.
It was too bouncy.
Yeah, she was looking for, you know,
something, you know,
John C. Holmes kind of film music.
Boom chicka wah wah.
Well, you know,
I've used that for my microorganism movies.
You know, I'm mostly...
Do you have multiple microorganisms?
Come to think of it...
Oh, yeah.
You toast girl.
Zillions of them.
Wow.
Some of them are on you right now.
I thought I needed to be host of.
And you too, listener.
You're covered with...
With my little microorganism.
Ooh.
Everybody is.
It's crawling with them.
Yep.
You don't notice them,
but you'd notice them if they were gone.
Oh, yeah.
The seething means it's working.
The seething.
And what about those water bears and other...
Oh, tardigrades?
Yes.
Those are so scary looking up close,
but they're kind of cute from above.
I was so proud when I graduated from the tardigrade.
The farther away from them,
the better they look.
And they can survive anything.
Apparently.
So can roto-frogs.
But yeah, I use porno music with my micro-photography.
It's so inappropriate.
It seems to work.
Yeah.
Spiral keats.
I have to say, Dr. Howell,
you're drawing your little doodling here,
and that's Bob after or during his pleasurable moment.
It might be.
It definitely does look like it,
and he's dropped his pipe.
Unless that's supposed to be...
Is that supposed to be Harry Reams?
That could be Jack Kennedy.
It's not Harry Reams, certainly.
I'm just judging by the mustache.
You never saw Harry Reams and Jack Kennedy in the same place.
Oh, I guess it's not a mustache.
Forgive me.
There's a conspiracy theory for that.
Nasolabial folds.
Oh.
Mm-hmm.
Now the rain has started to return in earnest, frankly.
Mm.
And so the rain may indeed shake,
but it's not going to shape the remainder of X-Day.
We will have to factor it into everything that we do
as the Earth is refreshed one final time.
Well, normally we await the saucers at that open field
with the stone circle around it.
It's very picturesque,
but maybe we'll have to just pile into this thing
until exactly 7 o'clock
when we have to run outside
or we'll crash our heads.
We'll have to put our heads into the ceiling,
and that's like sheet metal up there.
Wow.
When they lift us up,
you know, we could get hurt pretty badly
if we're not standing outdoors.
You mean really ruptured?
Yeah, yeah.
I mean...
Yeah, but I mean...
That's a pretty...
It's leaky.
It's leaky,
but it's still going to be hard for a human body
to pierce that sheet metal ceiling.
But once we're aboard,
we will instantly be renewed.
Yeah.
That's right.
We might get a little damaged.
Yeah.
Don't worry.
Don't worry if you see your fellow subgeniuses
screaming and writhing in agony
or bursting into flames.
Or if they appear to be being ripped apart in midair.
It's all for the best.
Yeah, don't run towards them.
Just continue on your way.
You know, the flashing sun,
when it erupts,
is probably going to steam them all like shrimp,
the whole of this brain thing.
And from the hovering saucer ships
will trickle barbecue sauce
and 11 herbs and spices.
We should probably get some condiments ready.
We got a bunch of,
we got a fresh loaf of bread.
See, we're already planning lunch.
We might have a little bit of bread,
so we could probably.
Seven condiments will sink beneath the ocean.
I always thought about eating fried pink.
I guess steamed would be good.
Highly esteemed are the best.
Poached.
Poached pink.
Uh-huh.
Those African poachers, yes,
they certainly deserve to be consumed.
Pink atartar.
Pulped by angry elephants.
Who will eagerly tenderize them for the subgeniuses.
Yes, we can just hold on until it all happens.
It has to happen.
I'm out of revenge fantasies at this point.
I've used them all up.
I haven't.
I'm mostly interested in preservation of collector's items.
I don't have that many special paints I want to kill.
There's one fifth grade teacher.
I don't even need to say her name.
But she's going to be resurrected from the dead.
Just so I can.
Kill her again.
Miss Kettlebaum.
I could have gone a long way in the spelling bee,
but she said,
Now, I can spell servile.
And I said, S-E-R-V-I-L-E.
And it was S-E-R-V-I-L-E?
Yeah.
She said, I'm going to say it again.
Servile.
S-E-R-V-I-L-E.
And the next kid, no, I'm sorry.
That's wrong.
She was so surprised that I got it wrong.
Because I was pretty good at spelling.
And the next kid comes up and goes,
Servile.
S-A-V-E-R-I-L.
And that was it.
Mrs. Darden is going to relive that moment soon.
Over.
And then she's going to know why the pain has come back.
Again.
Forever and ever.
Well, maybe not forever.
I'm not that mean.
I'll let her think it's going to be forever,
and then I'll put her back in her grave.
She's still alive.
Still alive.
On her face.
Yeah.
Face down.
Mrs. Darden.
There, I said her name.
But that's about it.
You'll be getting some angry letters from her estate.
I mean, anybody could reproduce the Grand Canyon,
but I'll have the original.
And the originals will be,
very, very valuable.
Money won't matter,
but Earth artifacts.
I just, if I know my subgeniuses,
they're going to start.
Yeah, after a day of being away from Earth,
they're going to say,
well, when is this going to be over?
When do we get to go back to?
Work.
Yeah.
Well, I like this girl that I work with,
and I miss seeing her.
It would be like Brexit.
But see, the minute you think that,
the excess,
and mom will make that happen,
and it could be that that's why we think
we're still sitting here right now on Earth.
Yes, that's a theory that isn't mentioned enough.
That our rupture did take place years ago.
Yeah, but we're just too unimaginative
to really believe, you know?
And so we, it's like, yeah, yeah.
Could be.
Is it sort of like in the Gamera movie?
When the kid was like,
boy, I wish I could get a sandwich.
There it was.
Right.
A sandwich.
So be careful what you wish for.
Excreted by a giant fiery turtle.
Yes.
But there's your sandwich.
Wow.
Yeah.
That's the best way to get a sandwich.
Mm-hmm.
Chilonian.
Excreted by a giant fiery turtle?
Mm-hmm.
That's how it happens in the movies.
Spinning turtle, I might add.
Spinning, flying, sparking, giant, angry, indignant turtle.
Sandwich.
With huge tusks in the lower jaw.
I guess I need to watch that one.
And also, poop out a sandwich for you.
You don't remember that one?
Where the kids were on the,
the kids were on the,
it's the stupid one,
where the kids talk to Gamera,
and they're in the submarine.
He is the friend of all good girls and boys.
Yes, exactly.
That sounds terrible.
Oh, it was bad.
It's no Godzilla on Monster Island.
And who was the guy that did the,
he was a famous voice actor.
He did the voice for Heatmiser and all those,
and he also did a lot of stuff for Disney.
Not Paul Freese.
Paul Freese.
Yes, that was it.
It wasn't.
It wasn't Paul Freese.
Okay.
Yeah, he did everything.
I'm almost positive he did the overdubbing
for, like, the ship.
Or whatever.
I'm pretty sure that was him.
Maybe not.
He's one of those people that,
when he died, it's like,
well, now we can't have a subgenius movie.
When John Carradine died,
I felt like,
there's no point in even thinking about a subgenius movie.
Or you could sample every recording he ever made
and have most of his words.
Piece together all the words.
Yeah, right.
Or write dialogue,
which is exactly like dialogue in monster movies.
You know,
flash, gigantic scorpions are climbing around the wreckage,
destroying passengers.
And all of that stuff.
You know, just write scenes like that
into the subgenius movie,
and there you'll be.
There you go.
Yeah.
These things write themselves.
I love the lyrics in the Godzilla film.
I love it.
Just found out that there was lyrics in that song.
Oh, yeah.
It was great.
That's probably,
that might be on this show,
or it could be.
Tiny tanks.
Lots of tiny little tanks.
Here they are.
Lots of tanks.
Here are coming lots and lots of tiny,
tiny, tiny tanks.
Tiny tanks.
And they're coming here.
Now.
I guess if I would have heard you,
I would have been able to play exactly what you were doing.
So hopefully we got some of it anyway.
Yeah, you got it.
But I am working on a surf version of that.
We could do it tonight, or try.
You know, if I had ever learned,
how to play guitar,
my band would have specialized in movie and TV themes.
Heavy, hard rock versions.
I will be right back.
Like, it'd be the hard rock version of the Andy Griffith theme.
Hard rock version of the Leave it to Beaver theme.
Uh-huh.
Green Acres, you know.
That's actually been done.
A lot of those have been done over the years.
Vic Mizzi.
That was the guy who did the Green Acres.
Yeah, the Green Acres music.
Farm livin' is the life for me.
Adam's family.
England spreadin' out so far and wide.
Red barns and green, green fields.
You can take Manhattan, just give me the countryside.
Green Acres, we are there.
The day in the life of Green Acres.
New York is where I'd rather stay.
I get allergic when I'm smelling hay.
I just adore a penthouse view.
With a look at Central Park.
Darling, I love you, but give me Park Avenue.
Green Acres, we are there.
The chores, the stores, fresh air, Times Square.
You are my wife, goodbye city life.
Green Acres, we are there.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, Green Acres is the place.
Where we were and whatever we were doing when the last train left for Green Acres.
With a side trip to, uh.
Petico Junction.
Petico Junction, yes, Hooterville.
In fact, a guest on my show pointed out that a number of those shows are all linked together.
together in the same universe, including Hogan's Heroes.
What?
Some of those prisoners had home memories of Hooterville and Petticoat.
Really?
And Jug Tussle?
Yes.
Oh, no, that's a new one.
It was pointed out.
Damn.
By my guest.
He showed me.
He cited it.
Well, Beverly Hillbillies.
Beverly Hillbillies is also linked to those.
It's in the same universe.
Billy's Petticoat Neighbors.
Right.
Gomer Pyle.
Gomer Pyle, of course, yes.
Anything featuring Goober.
And then, of course, the whole Andy Griffith show.
F-Truth.
That might be historically linked, possibly.
An episode in the past, maybe, before Green Acres ever was planted
or before the Fair Daughters splashed in the tower at Petticoat Junction.
The time tunnel.
54.
We could throw them all.
We could throw them all together.
There's a holdup in the Bronx.
Brooklyn's broken out in fights.
There's a traffic jam in Harlem that's backed up to Jackson Heights.
There's a scout troop short a child.
Crew chefs do at Idlewild.
Car 54, where are you?
Not 64.
54.
Which starred who?
Have you ever imagined sex with Joey Ross?
It starred Joey Ross.
I have.
I've gone to that trouble, but I know others who have.
Also starred in the incredible movie, Sh, the Octopus.
I don't know if you've ever seen it.
That would be some rough sex.
One of the most unusual movies ever made.
Sh, the Octopus, it's called.
Have you ever seen that one, Stan?
No.
You never saw Sh, the Octopus?
Really?
I remember the movie.
Is that a sequel to Hush, Hush, Sweet Charlotte?
No, it's not.
Or Hack, Hack, Sweet Has-Been, starring Olivia Hackahan.
But.
But Sh, the Octopus stands with earthworm tractors as one of the most subgenius films.
You have to have seen earthworm tractors.
No.
Wow.
No, I haven't.
I didn't see Ant Farm Dickhole, though.
Ant Farm Dickhole was shown here at X Day a few years ago.
But, you see.
You think these are jokes, but they're real movie titles.
The Octopus is a strange film.
And it has some.
One incredible special effect in it.
I thought I may have discussed that in the past.
I think you did.
Yeah.
But many are the treasures to be found.
Yes, you don't have to dig that deep to find them either.
In either Book of the Subgenius or the pamphlet number one,
the worst, the greatest worst movie in the world is mentioned.
It's called Scarlet Love.
It's a love directed by Palmer Rocky in Dallas.
It was shown four walled for one week.
I saw it twice.
Me and everyone else in the theater just about died laughing.
The director was mortified.
And he moved.
I pursued him.
I tried to encourage him that it would fit into the midnight movies thing.
It was really a crowd pleaser.
He didn't mean it that way.
Well, the.
He died.
The last time I begged him about it, he said,
that movie is never going to see the light through it away.
It's a prince.
They're all dead.
But later, a lab guy in L.A.
wrote to me and said, I know you're interested in this movie, and he he still comes into our lab every week and rents our screening room to look at his movie.
And he makes notes because he's still planning to change it.
This is like 15 years.
Later, wow.
But it then then terrible one.
You say that he died.
And I thought, well, that's it.
Nobody's ever going to see that movie.
Well, guess what?
Some film lab guys did.
They kept movies that were being thrown out of film labs.
My movie, World of the Future, was being thrown out of the lab in Dallas when the guy who narrated it and worked there said, hey, Doug, is this supposed to be in the trash?
That's how it got saved.
But somebody saved Scarlet Love that way.
It's got a new title, apparently.
But Philo found the article about it.
These people have a bunch of shelf movies that they save.
They were just lab technicians.
And Scarlet Love is the first one they're planning to restore and put on DVD.
I'm excited about that.
Yeah, that's another reason not to kill yourself before X-Day.
I'm telling you, no matter how bad it gets, wait until Scarlet Love comes out.
You'll have a reason to live again.
Yeah.
It's that good bad.
Just as suddenly everything in your life gets straightened out,
all your financial troubles are now away.
You've been given a clean bill of health.
There's new love in your life.
Everything is fine.
Now it's time to burn everything up and shoot up in the sky with this base creature.
Ta-da!
Yeah.
I was going to say, I'm thinking that the movie we might be showing is Manos.
Manos.
The Hand of Death.
I've never watched that all the way through.
Hands of Fate.
No, it is pretty difficult.
Now I understand the person who played the little girl in that has written a book and is doing conventions and stuff.
Actually, she was the Manos.
That's his daughter.
The man that plays Manos.
Like Red Button's daughter.
Yeah.
And they are making another movie, a Manos 2, as a comedy.
Manos 2.
There's nothing else.
There's nothing else you can do with it but do that.
Finally, they did it.
They have a GoFundMe or a Kickstarter or something to try and put this out.
But it showed a picture of the man that played Manos.
And, I mean, he still kind of looks the same, but, you know, a bit older.
Clearly, there's some mileage on there.
Yes.
Yeah.
Unfortunately, the goat guy is John Reynolds, I think it was.
He committed suicide sometime.
Yeah, you know, the prosthetics they made for his legs.
He put them on backwards.
Oh, good Lord.
So, the guy was in pain all the time.
And so, he got hooked.
This is what I've...
He kept kicking himself.
He was...
Because he was supposed to be a pan, you know.
And his...
And that's the reason why he walked so wonky.
Because he was wearing these prosthetic legs backwards.
And no one bothered to tell him that, you know, hey, put those on the other way.
The movie was shot, I believe, in eight-minute increments.
However much...
An eight-millimeter...
Were they buying short ends or something?
Yeah, they were just...
He would buy whatever.
And everyone was promised money.
And they didn't have sound.
It was made in eight-millimeter?
I don't know if it was eight.
Probably 16.
There was a hand crank thing, so it would be like a hundred-foot roll.
That's about two and a half minutes.
Yeah.
He was shooting it in that.
And all of the voices on the film are three people.
The little girl is portrayed by an adult.
And apparently when they premiered the show, the movie,
the little girl cried because it wasn't her voice.
Oh.
Literally, it was three people that voiced everyone in the movie.
And the main man in the movie is the guy that wrote it, directed it, starred in it, everything.
And, yeah.
But to me, that's one of the worst.
There's so many that are much worse.
Oh.
But...
Have you ever heard of...
Neil Breen?
B-R-E-E-N.
Wow.
He was a Las Vegas realty agent who had a lot of plastic surgery
and decided to become a film auteur where he's a producer, director, writer, lead, caterer, everything.
Food service.
I didn't think true badness could exist anymore.
Neil Breen has reaffirmed my faith.
Yes.
Every movie, he's some messiah out to save man by...
Usually by hacking government secrets.
And he has all these laptops that are never on.
And he drops tuna on his crotch.
And it's just...
It's nuts.
It's totally nuts.
Okay.
You have to elaborate on...
He drops tuna on his crotch.
Well, that's one of his movies, Double Down, where he's out in the desert wearing mom jeans
with a lot of dead laptops.
He's always got dead laptops.
And he does an illustration.
He's a little advised nude scene.
You get to see the back of his nuts in one, which I could have lived without seeing the
back of his nuts.
But he's had so much work done, he looks like a surprised fox.
When...
What's this guy doing?
What era is this?
It's contemporary.
Oh, he's still...
Well, he actually has laptops.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
He's a YouTube.
YouTube has a Neil Breen.
Oh.
God.
Well, that gives us something to look forward to.
Right.
Straight to YouTube.
Faithful findings.
Double Down.
There's a lot of movies like that.
Oh, yeah.
I am here dot, dot, dot, dot now.
Four dots in the ellipses.
That's one dot too many.
And none of his leading ladies will ever want to be in the same room with him again.
It's a rough ride.
Oh, well, he got it in the can.
He got it done.
He got it in the can.
That's more than many people...
Oh, if I had a nickel for every time that happened to me.
You'd have ten cents.
Yes, I would.
I'd have little or no cents.
Well, this is certainly an inspiring episode of the Hour of Slack.
It's strange how they all occasionally veer into cinema criticism.
Yes, the visual dimension is close to every subgenius in off moments.
One tends to return to those times spent watching the flickering screen.
I always believed that the Church of the Subgenius was kind of based on films.
Yeah.
Worlds.
That was where I got my inspiration.
Monster movies and radio preachers.
Oh, yeah, so that's the reason why, you know...
I mean, I've always...
That's what intrigued me.
Well, Bob is the ultimate monster in some ways.
Mm-hmm.
You think he could take Godzilla?
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
But Godzilla would slip on Gamera's banana peel.
You know, and break his neck.
Combine Toei and Toho monsters in the same picture?
Well, the problem is we need a shot of Bob carrying the swooning girl like all the other monsters.
Then he can legitimately join the Pantheon.
They all carry the swooning girl, even the creature from the Black Lagoon,
who can hardly have a pragmatic interest in her.
Well, this isn't a value judgment,
but the difference between comic fiction...
...and monster fans is...
...is an abyss, yeah.
For the monster fans, the primary image is the big ugly guy carrying a pretty girl,
whereas for comic book fans, what's the primary image?
Two guys grappling in their tights.
Yeah.
Yes, yes.
So, you know...
That's why I've never really been a comic...
Not that there's anything wrong with that.
No, and they're battering the bejesus out of each other.
Gary Arlington, while he was still alive, said,
All the people in the comics in my store, what are they doing?
They're hitting each other.
You open these things, and I sell them,
and they're hitting each other on every page.
And...
Yeah, you say that like that's a bad thing.
I'm quoting Gary Arlington.
They're not ripping off limbs or, you know, shredding,
putting them in a corpse-grinding machine?
Well, they're not sitting down and having watercress sandwiches.
No, no.
I don't want to say that.
That might be a good comic book to me.
The astonishing...
I can see Bob carrying his swooning Godzilla.
Right.
That would be beautiful.
In a bikini.
Yeah.
Godzilla and Bob walking away in the Tokyo sunset.
All right, subgenius artists, get busy.
Yes.
You've been giving your son...
I would actually buy that.
I'm such a Godzilla nut.
I would buy...
If somebody was to paint a Godzilla and Bob walking...
Yep.
Well, they're not to the same...
Howard, you got your work done?
I'm going to cut out for you.
Scale, which is the problem with the proposed King Kong versus Godzilla movie.
You've got to respect scale.
Or some Ultraman-like thing like,
no, all of a sudden he is Mega Bob.
You know.
Well, Bob can...
Yay, look at his pipe.
He can grow.
And so now, Mr. Godzilla, not so fearsome, are you?
Light my pipe with that nuclear...
With your breath.
Yeah.
It's not the size of the lizard that counts.
It's what he does.
It's how radioactive his breath is.
Yeah.
The new one, I'm pretty excited about the new one coming out.
The new Godzilla?
Yes.
But that's King Kong, isn't it?
Or is it...
He's...
I can't remember what it's called.
He's rebuilding himself.
So all of the early things where he's...
He's almost like a zombie in the beginning.
And he grows into his skin.
Zombie Godzilla?
Well, I think...
I always thought that'd be a great idea anyway.
It's never been appropriately acknowledged
that Godzilla died at the end of the first Godzilla movie.
He's unquestionably dead.
No, no.
You see his skeleton.
He was destroyed by Professor Serizawa's oxygen destruia.
Mm-hmm.
Right.
Perfection like Godzilla cannot die.
Then the second film called...
What was it?
The War of the...
No.
War of the Gargantuan?
No, that wasn't the second one.
The Grapple of All Monsters?
No, no.
The second one was...
Was it Mothra?
Yes.
It was not.
It was Gigantis the Fire Monster.
Right, right.
Because they couldn't call him Godzilla back then.
But the populace knows that Frankenstein is the same name for the monster as the Doctor.
And so eventually the movie makers simply have to accomplish...
They have to accommodate that.
And so it has been done with Gojira.
But it's not the first Gojira.
And the assiduous collectors of the little statuettes know that well
and can tell you, looking at each one, which one it is from which movie.
That's the kind of things subgeniuses know.
Then there's the kind of things they don't know.
Like how to repair their own car.
Fix the toilet.
Balancing a checkbook.
Yeah, balance a checkbook.
Eat healthy.
Socialize.
Reverend Angry Larry can fix a car, right?
Yeah.
But you can't fix the modern ones.
They've got brains and nervous systems.
No, modern ones I take those in.
No.
Yeah, the old ones you can fix.
My 57 Chevrolet i, that I can fix.
Yeah.
That's at a human dimension.
It's not a solid state electronics.
Mine's tube.
Yeah.
It's not solid state.
It's a tube amp.
Right.
It's a tube car.
Here we see Akoba driving Tumac out of his home.
Oh, is that 1 million BC?
Yes, this is the 1941 Hal Roach version.
Well, I'm ready to stop the show and go watch that.
His mother, Sura, mourns, but Akoba is determined and knocks Tumac out.
And he's immediately chased by an enraged mammoth,
which doesn't occur in the 1966 remake.
Some people said it's just hard to believe.
Oh, there's new pilots.
Bondi, she's so sad.
That the original, that Robert Brown, who plays Akoba in the remake,
how could he possibly defeat his huge muscular son?
You know, and why was everyone cowering from this guy?
Well, there's an explanation that all the critics don't understand,
and that is he's a mean old man.
So you bet he could do all of that and more and have them all,
all terrified of him the way he is in the movie.
Then after his unfortunate accident,
goring by a musk ox in the first movie,
and in the second movie,
being mutilated by falling off a cliff after chasing a goat,
then he's not as powerful.
Yeah, I haven't seen this movie since I was a kid.
The mammoth is pushing the tree that he's on and he's knocked out,
and he floats down the river full of weird reptiles,
but is somehow never...
Not consumed.
Until he lands at the beach where Loana the Fair One turns him up.
Again, these are the things that subgeniuses know.
Oh, yeah.
Well, some of us are condemned to know such things.
They may not know first aid or how to swim,
but they know the plot of every monster movie made from 1910 to...
Remember that caveman movie?
Swim like they did in that movie.
Now you're all right.
Well, I knew about Manos.
Come on.
Right.
Nobody knows about that stuff.
What is the hand in the title of Manos?
It's on his robe.
Yeah, it's his robe.
He's got red hands.
He's got two red hands on there,
which is funny because Manos means hands,
so it's just hands, the hands of fate.
Here, Tumac, unconscious, slips down the river
and we see him traveling through the prehistoric primordial world.
I like the fact that the screen is very lumpy.
The ripples help us.
We're watching it.
It's a sheet.
Backwards.
But we're behind.
We're on the other side.
There's La Juana.
We're watching the behind the scenes here.
Isn't she beautiful?
She looks like a big wrinkle to me.
Oh, yeah.
Well, she would today had she lived, but she killed herself for love.
Well, you know, we're blocking the good screen.
Yeah.
If we got out of here...
Screaming.
The situation could change, but I bet it won't.
She's astonished to see Tumac.
We're settlers.
We settled for...
Oh, she's screaming Tumac.
We're all together.
Now she's somewhat interested in him, as you can see from this cutaway shot.
Both versions of the movie are essentially a silent film
with everything in it expressed gesturally,
although there's all sorts of stuff on the soundtrack of both versions,
most creatively in the second version.
Well, here we are watching the movie.
See, I think we ought to shut down this circus
and watch...
If you have enough recorded stuff for Muam, I suppose we could.
Well, you know, we just, according to the machine here,
we've been talking for one hour and 55 minutes,
so that's two hours of slack.
Squeeze out a final five minutes and then shut down.
Then you'll have two, count them, two hours in the can.
Right.
Show fiber.
Or we just watch the movie.
Squeeze it out.
Yeah.
So, friends, you've been listening to the Hour of Slack.
Hour of Slack.
From the Church of the Subgenius.
If you're interested in learning more about
Reverend Angry Larry, Dr. Howell,
Reverend Susie the Floozy,
or J.R. Bob Dobbs,
that information is all there at subgenius.com.
But it's too late because in just a few hours it's all going to fry.
Well, some version of subgenius.com,
this is part of the contract,
that's going to get off with us.
You think you're going to escape all that subgenius propaganda and stuff?
It's going to be more intense than you ever dreamed.
That's going to be on the beacon satellites.
Well, yeah, because we've got those large speakers on the side of the craft
that are just going to blast it up.
It will not be possible to turn it off.
You might as well understand this.
It's going to be a constant of your future existence.
But then it's going to be a battle of...
Oh, no, well, why are we playing your show, Dr. Howell?
I thought we were going to play your show.
We're going to play the Hour of Slack and bombard them.
We're going to play them all simultaneously.
What about Bob's Slacktime Phone House and Sir Graveson?
What about the other shows, Howell?
Why are you playing the KPFA show only?
Oh, my God.
Then we'll have to have a schedule.
Then it starts all over again.
I guess you didn't look at your booklet.
I guess you didn't read your schedule.
You were going to stop off and grab the Grand Canyon, correct?
Yeah, among other things.
Okay.
Yeah, but that's going to be fairly large.
So I think it's possible that we can all have our own, you know, areas.
Or you can grab the...
I don't have dibs on the Great Barrier Reef, but you better grab it quick.
It's going fast.
No.
Somebody ought to pick that up while there's still any of it left.
I want the Statue of Liberty because I really want to be in it.
I wanted to make a lighter out of that.
Yeah?
You can say statue.
There'll be enough prop for, you know, we'll need the Statue of Liberty.
Right.
She'll actually...
She'll actually light up.
Uh-huh.
You know, she'll let...
That torch will actually be on fire, and it will be constantly pushing out the smoke of Bob's pipe.
Ah, yes, friends.
The promise of Exit.
See, we did another five minutes.
In fact, we're over.
I told you.
Oh.
Now we're over.
I didn't edit out all the times I said fuck.
So there's a lot more stuff coming your way.
Don't worry, kids.
This is hardly the last feeble flicker that it appears to be of the Church of the Sanctuary.
It's not a subgenius.
No, yes it is.
It's all gonna burn.
There's more fun and antics.
What are you saying, Susie?
Like hours away.
It's almost X-Day.
What time is it?
Who cares?
Tempest bugger.
Earth time, it's 5 o'clock.
Wow.
So we've got like 14 hours.
Eastern Standard Time.
14 hours before, to quote the title of another movie, the Earth Dies Screaming.
Mm.
Okay.
I'm not gonna lie.
You have only five o'clock.
I have a little later than that, are you sure?
It'll feel so good when it stops.
Oh.
That's the principle behind a lot of things.
You've been listening to the Horror Slam.
...you folks listening by record.
Once the church is gone, there's going to be a cataclysmic judgment and millions will die
in those next few years.
And you might be a bit clueless but don't worry about it.
For those of you that loosen your loose ends, we'll stop the  , and continue watching
our comical seisse candy trip to the safely and unused
So don't come right up here and turn around and watch some killer took backups?
I'll be there.
I feel galement as well.
It's the end of the world
As you know it
I feel fine
Hey, oh, let's go
Shoot them in the back now
What they want, I don't know
They're all raised up and ready to go
Turn around, go back down
Back the way you came
Can't you see that flash of fire
Ten times brighter than the day
And behold, a mighty city
Broken in the dust again
Oh, God, cry the man
It's gonna be me
It's gonna be you
We're gonna do everything we want to
It's gotta be now
And I can't wait
To say goodbye to fear
And all that pain and hate
Oh, like a flaming baton
That's burning the world
Like George Bush on acid
Stringing the duke on
Gonna be a new day
Gonna be a new world
I'm a consent
To anyone's last words
There's nothing left for you to say
Soon you'll pretend anyway
Well, no one here
Is getting out alive
This summer's really lost my mind
And I don't care
I'm a consent
So close your eyes
And get yourself to mind
And think about the times
It's been and what they've been
To me it's nothing
We're only gonna die
From our own arrogance
That's why we're gonna die
We might as well take our time