Praise Robert!
Bibbidi-bobbidi-boo.
All right.
Oh, yeah.
Bibbidi-bobbidi-boo.
Whew.
Help me, somebody.
Copyright 1985.
The Subgenius.
All right.
Copyright 1985.
This is KNON 90.90.1.
FM.
In Dallas, Texas.
This is the Subgenius Radio Ministry.
Hour of Slack on KNON 90.90.1.
Praise Bob.
What about Slack?
That's your key phrase.
It will trigger the entire message without your being aware of it.
Welcome to the Subgenius Radio Ministry.
Hour of Slack.
Sponsored by the Church of the Subgenius.
This is Reverend Ivan Stang, sacred scribe of the First Orthodox Megafist Temple Lodge
of the Church of the Subgenius, with Pastor Buck Naked of the First Naked Church of the
Subgenius.
The opinions expressed are not necessarily those of this radio station.
Before the sermon, a message concerning Bob Dobbs.
Living Avatar.
Here's the Didn't Ask, like or A
Ew!
This is Ralph was posting a video It seems as though we've learned some lessons using
While we were talking over the radio, Rob screws us a bunch.
Like a joke!
Oh, yeah.
No, that's what he calls automate video.
He knows that I'm doing something.
Ah, I'm trying to think.
He knows that he knows the English language.
Moses went up to the mountain high
To find out from God
Why did you make us?
Why?
Secret words in a secret room
He said,
Wop-bop-a-loo-bop
A-lop-bam-boom
I did not put you here to suffer
I did not put you here to whine
I put you here to love one another
And the kiddos have a good time now, now, now
Let my people go, go, go
You gotta let my people go, go, go
You gotta let my people go
Yeah
I'm trying to fix a thing
Battlin' cherry coal
You tell the boys with the horns
Get down and blow
They rear back
Aim their bells at the stars
He said,
Feed me, Big Daddy
Eight to the par
I did not put you here to suffer
I did not put you here to whine
I put you here to love one another
And the kiddos have a good time now, now, now, now
Let my people go, go, go
You gotta let my people go, go, go
You gotta let my people go
That's it
Oh!
.
Oh, yes, dear friends, this is Reverend Ivan Stang, and you're listening to the Hour of Slack Radio Ministry,
the outreach arm of the Church of the Subgenius.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
And, oh, yes, dear friends,
that was, uh, that first song was The Rainmaker.
See, every now and then, about once per show,
we play an album or tape that you can actually buy in the stores.
But, and, uh, tonight, we had, uh,
or last week, I promised you, for this week,
the Subgenius Anti-Drug Show.
But, unfortunately, the conspiracy...
Ooh!
No, that's right.
It's too scary to do the Anti-Drug Show this week.
So, uh, because my conspiracy job just, man, it was my week in the barrel, friends.
That's all there is to it.
And, uh, so I barely had time to just cue up a lot of subgenius music.
And, uh, almost everything we're playing tonight is by members of the church.
But don't freak out, because it's pretty, pretty heavy duty.
Uh, ahem.
In, in fact, you're gonna hear the secrets of the Squirtin' Universe
from Doctors for Bob coming up in just a couple of seconds here.
Get the, uh...
Well, listen to this wonderful disco music.
This is called Beginning of Time.
And as the primitive subgeniuses carry the mighty stones of the Dobbs Pyramid
across the desert,
pterodactyls wheeling about them over their heads,
and Tyrannosauruses fighting in the distance,
we slowly move over into the other universe,
the universe of slack,
where the subgeniuses don't...
have to build the giant temple,
but instead have to fight saber-toothed tigers
and conspiracy Cro-Magnon people.
You know, there's a, a common theory that the subgeniuses are those of us who are descended,
not, not necessarily from the Yetis or the Abominable Snowmen,
but from the Neanderthal creatures, you know.
The, the Neanderthals were wiped out by the Cro-Magnons.
So they say, about 35,000 years ago.
Personally, I prefer to believe that the Neanderthal gene, uh, lives on in some few of us
who, uh, carry on the great word of the Neanderthal,
those who worship Wotan, Ra, and other great its of the sky.
Ah, yes.
Ha ha.
I think we allmayı all the key for the竅
I hope your high r patient is jowechsel fully in.
And don't forgete..
Bardock.
O throat,
presumptuouly,
it's your truly.
No, it's wood.
Bob?
But let's leave things of this world behind and walk now down the path of Bob for this brief minute of slack from the Church of the Subgenius.
This is Reverend Ivan Stang with the Sorry Truth.
Now, friend, look around you and face facts.
The world is composed mostly of jerks.
All kinds of ignorant, dangerous, thoughtless louts are in positions of power and influence,
while some of the most deserving people you know,
are slugging it out in a thankless cycle of brain-breaking labor and mental paralysis.
Checks and balances? What a joke.
Friend, if you want to get slack, then you better uphold the Great Covenant, yes?
Before you were born, you swore you'd help in the great battle against them?
That's right, them!
The normals, the mediocrities, the Barbies and Kens, the pink boys, the somnambulax, the cage men,
the time servers, the Philistines, the witch-murders!
Those who have made...
Slack!
Taboo!
That's right, friend, there's only two races in this world, us and them.
Whose side are you on, eh?
Now that your pictures in the paper being perfectly as mine and you can't have it,
the one that you have ever desired, all you gotta tell me now is why, why, why, why,
welcome to the workin' week!
Oh, I know it don't thrill you, I hope it don't kill you,
Welcome to the workin' week!
You gotta do it till you do it, so you better get into it!
All of your family had to kill to survive,
And this the waitin' for the big day to arrive,
But if you are out there, you better be alive!
Welcome to the workin' week!
Oh, I know it don't thrill you, I hope it don't kill you,
You gotta do it till you do it, so you better get into it!
I hear you sayin' that this is alright when you're only readin' American books,
Spent all your money gettin' so convinced that you never even thought of us,
Sometimes I wonder if we're livin' in the same land,
Why'd you wanna be my friend when I feel like a chum runnin' outta hands?
Welcome to the workin' week!
Oh, I, welcome to the workin' week!
Friend, the devil is tearin' the family apart,
But what the devil uses to do it with is nine to five jobs!
Conspiracy, corporate, peak situations where mommy and daddy get up in the mornin' and go to work,
And they kiss the kids goodbye, it's the first time they see them during the day, kiss them goodbye,
Kind of a simultaneous goodbye and hello,
Then they get home about seven o'clock, ticked off, to use the polite term,
After a long drive back out to the suburbs,
They get home, they kiss their kids hello and goodnight, and they go to bed,
And the other churches dare to say the breakdown of the family is cause the kids see a little titterin' stupid sexy gags on television,
Or cause of the new permissiveness where men are allowed to do things with other men,
That's a bunch of holy hooey, I say, my friend, I say, why not legalize pornography and ban work?
Work is what takes the parents away from the kids, most of these kids these days grow up, they don't have parents,
They got some kind of robot scarecrows, and a friend lettin' her be slack.
Religion?
Here's one of the basic tenets of religion, it says here, Jesus is our Bob, Bob is our hope, Jesus is Bob Hope.
That's one of the tenets of the religion.
What I wanna know about is slack, I seem to see the word slack mentioned a lot.
Well that's, we've lost our original slack, and Bob is here to help us regain it,
Some people have a greater proportion of it than others, but slack is essentially what you need to be able to do whatever the hell you want.
Okay.
So then you could say Bill, for example, is suffering from slacklessness.
Well I don't know.
This station seems to have a much greater proportion of slack than others in the area.
That's right, we are truly original and we, in, in, in,
Full of slack.
Yeah, in most, in, as I understand it, we are full of slack, cause we are different from everyone else,
We are not dictated by the norms of society and of commercial radio, we try to do our own thing on XCI, especially on morning sickness.
That's right, Bob would not choose to appear on any other radio station, I don't think.
Oh that's, we're very honored, did you hear that?
Bob and the Church of the Subgenius would never be represented.
We're represented by a commercial, represented, for example, on Jerry Christopher's show.
Who needs him?
He's, he's got no slack.
So if the listeners want to call and talk to the Reverend Ray Dodge, all you have to do is pick up your phone during this next song, call 744-5-
Maria, I've just kissed a girl named Maria, and suddenly I've found how wonderful a sound can be.
I can't dance, I can't dance, besides I look so awful in these braces.
If that boy wants me to dance, I'll just die, I'm so tall and he's about three feet high.
Not three.
Oh you say you're playing huge, you're neither sure you're worth choosing, but you're still undersized about me.
Oh, oh.
Oh, time for the killing floor.
Now he's spilling whiskey and learning songs about the one that got away.
Vacation, vacation, vacation, Bob and Steve.
Release your hold on this tenuous practical joke they call reality.
Let your body be sucked out of your ears, for we're going to take you deeper.
Deep, deep inside yourself to the place of silence and the noise.
We're going deeper, deeper into your consciousness, down past the membranes of the fabric of your very mind.
We bore down into the cranium, drilling through the irrelevant memories of job and normality.
Piercing the squamous epizootis, rolling around in the hollowed out inside of the skull.
Scraping along the edges of the birth canal and stretching the imaginary.
The imagination gland until it pops.
Now, let all your thoughts drain out through the brain pan.
Tumble down through the sinuses, slide down the esophagus and finally let them plunge to the base of the soul itself.
Located in the lowest organ of your body, the foot gland.
And finally, an idea, a key, an ultimate plan is born at the very bottom of your mind.
And it is Bob.
Bob.
You've got to get out of here, quick.
I know you haven't had much practice, but you've got to start thinking.
You must want to think.
I'd rather not do anything.
And the Thargians don't want you to do anything, even eating or breathing.
Breathing?
But I've always breathed.
I can't stop now.
Then get started thinking.
Think, boy, think.
What do I think about?
Think of birds that swim and fish that fly.
Let's see.
Birds that swim and fish that fly.
Words that begin with J.
It's working, it's working.
Keep thinking.
Dinosaur insteps, potato ice cream.
Potato insteps and dino ice cream.
Dinosaur ice cream.
Faster, boy, faster.
Deoxyribonucleic acid.
Albert Einstein, E equals MC squared.
William Shakespeare.
Anthony Trollope, Isaac Newton.
Faster, boy, faster.
Roger Bacon, John Stuart Mill.
Baby, really.
F-E-B-R-U-A-R-Y.
15 times 86 equals 1290.
Then carry the three.
.
For the primal sound of the boring, laid-back meditation universe
Might it need me?
Oh, but the primal sound of the
Bobble-thumpin' black-eyed pea
Back to the old stuff
Squirtin' universe is
For they know not the glories
And that which has been called the squirtin' universe
For the purpose of life is not happiness, peace, or even truth
But the purpose of the universe is to squirt
For 50% of the universe, that is
For slightly over 50%
The purpose of the universe is to ooze
For the purpose of life is not happiness, peace, or even truth
But the story of
Is an all-encompassing tale
Which tells of the
The utter transformation of the universe in the final days
As was written in
Ecclesians 5.17
For in the end times there shall be
The one world religion
Predicted in the Bible
And that shall be called the church of the subgenius
And there shall be a band
A band which shall, which will, was, and shall be known as
The Doctors for Bob
And lo, the Doctors for Bob
Was the very hand, the very tool of God
So to speak
And that which was called the squirtin' universe
The squirtin' universe
For the true purpose of Doctors for Bob
Which could finally be revealed at last
Is to speak every word
To sing every song
To make every sound
Every noise
Melodic or un-melodic
Heart-pounding
Possible in all infinite variations of the universe
We're not bound by any laws of
Quality
Good, our songs don't have to be good
Because it is our duty to write
Every song that is left
To utter every syllable
So that every name of God shall be uttered
So that the universe might end
Yes, friends, we are here to sing
That the universe ends for the proper reasons
For in 1998
Slightly before the arrival of the Exists
Our mission will have been fulfilled
We shall meet we have to meet
That we shall have uttered
Every syllable
Spoken every possible name of God
Or Jehovah One
Or Ram or Allah
Whichever name of God you call him
And you'll be at Doc Stock 17
The Doctors for Bob shall be performing
What people little suspect
Is their last performance
And at the exact precise correct moment
Snavely, excellent
The mighty, mighty saxophone player
For Doctors for Bob
Shall hit a wrong note
Which lo and behold shall be
In fact, in actuality the right note
And as he hits that wrong note
It will be a note so wrong
That the entire universe shall start to crumble
All energy of all universes
Of all dimensions
Of all time frames
Of all realities
Shall be channeled
Through the cheap amplifiers of Doctors for Bob
Yes, the universe shall be destroyed
By amplification equipment bought on credit
At Boyd's Music Center
Yay! Lo and behold!
And as all energy of all known universes
Begins to be channeled through their amplifiers
A new and heretofore unknown force shall be created
A force which shall be known as anti-sound
And you thought anti-music was sound
Anti-music is a force which has never
And by its very nature
Can never exist in this universe
Anti-sound is a force unlike anything
Ever experienced before in any known universe
In any time continuum
The only reason it is even called
That the word sound
Is even in the title anti-sound
Is so that you'll have some type of reference point
But anti-sound has nothing to do with sound
These waves
These rays
These forces of anti-sound
Shall vibrate
Or anti-vibrate I might say
Through the entire universe
And the entire universe
Will lose its form
It shall be destroyed
Every molecule shall be demagnetized
From every other molecule
Every electron demagnetized
From every other electron
Every proton demagnetized
From every other proton
Every atom shall be repelled
From every other atom
The universe shall lose its form
As we know it today
Boyd's Music Center
Born to lose
And now I'm losing
Universal form
Hyperclites shall quip
Breaking off one last one liner
Before the universe
Loses its form
But Lord behold
Nothing is ever destroyed
For the universe is eternal
Thus matter cannot be created
Or destroyed
It is only
And merely
Transformed
And it shall be
Lo transformed
In the following manner
Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Bäh Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah
Well dear friends
Yeah see we can't play the rest of that
that amazing Doctors for Bob tune,
the squirting universe, the pretty song,
because, well, the fate of the universe
turns out to be extremely X-rated.
And in keeping with that theme,
let's go to this tune we got from Dallas' own graph.
I'm afraid they're moving on to Austin soon.
This one was from the...
What? We are?
We're still on the air.
I'm scared of all this because I'm not me any longer.
I've been hurt so long by the conspiracy.
Okay, you can see I'm on the channel on air.
Punch up the Vredes machine.
Okay, we'll play a California music for you now.
Okay.
Wham!
Whoa!
That sound is more important than your entire life.
Well, that's probably...
That's probably true.
Anyway, let's go on to,
after that little word from the California subgenius show,
this is the Gravity Pilots with Bob is Sex.
Bob.
Bob is Sex.
Bob?
Who told you that?
Bob.
Bob is Sex.
He told you like aech that you have sex.
Young girl, they can be yours.
Lovely sheep.
Oh, yes, dear friends, that was a lovely little hymn from the Gravity Pilots.
Everybody, this is the Nightman calling from KNON 9.9 FM,
the home of rock and roll in Dallas, Fort Worth.
Monday, 7 to 9 p.m., we've got Kelly and Elmo bringing you From the Hip.
Tuesday, 7 to 9 p.m., Greg Riemann doing Wah Hey.
11 to midnight on Tuesdays is Jeff Webb's Vinyl Hour,
featuring a feature artist every week.
Wednesday, 7 to 9 p.m., Brandy Time for Charlie Dutton,
Park and Owl doing Who Cares?
11 to 2 a.m., Wednesday night's Brand New Time for Tim Hibbs, Brave New Radio.
Thursday night, 7 to 9 p.m., Jeff Webb brings you Offbeat Music.
2 to 4 a.m. on Thursday night, a brand new show for us,
Jeff Liles doing Life is Hard.
Friday night, 7 to 9 p.m., Kim Fodder and Paul Suffron
bringing you music from the underground.
1 to 4 a.m. on Fridays, Brand New Time for Radio Lobotomy,
music from Anatomic, Audrey and Weldon.
Saturday afternoon, 2 to 5.
6 p.m., Brad Sigler does Dig That Groove.
9 to midnight on Saturdays, Brand New Time for Shaggy's Pajama Party.
And midnight to 4 a.m. on Saturdays, it's Harsh Realm.
Ronnie Moore bringing you music from hardcore and heavy metal bands the world over.
If you're in Dallas, Fort Worth, and you dig rock and roll music,
alternative rock and roll music, there's only one place for you to tune to,
and that's KNON 90.9 FM.
The hottest.
Nation on the planet Earth.
Right here in Dallas, Fort Worth.
Oh, yeah, help me somebody.
Okay, well, this is the Chicago subgenius band under the,
it's called the People's Temple.
I thought, what a pretty name.
This is Pope Michael Flores in Chicago
and high popestress dominatrix Pam Smith
with an old Screamin' Jay Hawkins song done up subgenius style.
Called Sewell Park.
I'll be right back.
Brothers and sisters,
I want you to put down your frock,
get those chainsaws and open up your ears,
and listen to this song.
story
in the vast continuity of
there were people there with sensible
and there were children there
with no wounds of distinction
there were women there
who was thought of as virtuous
but they contained the blood
of the ruling class
of Sewell Park
I said men cried
babies died
children fell
men sighed
babies cried
men died
children fell
women suffered
people wanted repentance
and victims
they wanted to escape
ah
hahahaha
yeah they just wanted to escape
ah
hahahaha
he should know about it
he should know about Sewell Park
and the winter solstice
I said men cried
babies died
children fell
people were hurt
they died
I said men cried
it was Si Uncle Brother
but they didn't get hurt
so I hurt them
Such as father
what a tough
aquarium
sang sunset
And there were like the shape and form of a vortex in every way
And out of the whirlpool came great shining ships of the sky
And their shape was like a two-leaf
And yet no way were they of a being like nature
And they meant me the greatest heart
And as they came to me with great malice I felt safe
I saw a great wonder
The smoke of the great pipe of the sun covered me
And the great ships of the sky could not pass through
And I fell on my face before the glory of Bob
I found myself in a long hall hung with many lights
And the light they cast was like the faded fireworks
The haze of too much fear
And a voice called me saying
Is this, is your sign
Your guidepost for the coming winter times
I asked, is this a message
Or is this just some dumb meaningless body dream
What's this green purple
Ah
Yes, dear friends, that was the Swingin' Love Corpses,
the amazing Swingin' Love Corpses from St. Louis, Missouri.
And let me see now, I could, I could
play the beginning of the Swingin' Love, see,
last, that was another thing I thought about doing this week
was having the Swingin' Love Corpses show.
They were in town on their world tour last week
and they gave us the only interview that they gave to any radio station in town.
And I've got a whole hour and a half's worth of it
but it needs to be edited down, I haven't had a chance to do it
so why not run a little bit of the Swingin' Love Corpses.
I know there's a lot of Love Corpses fans out there.
Don't, just because you're into the Swingin' Love Corpses
and Prairie Squid and all that,
please don't hang yourselves while listening to Swingin' Love Corpses tapes.
They've, there's been this outbreak of teenage suicides.
You know, they, they, they, they listen to Love Corpses tapes.
And they want to be Swingin' Love Corpses.
And they, they tie themselves up like that and get to dangling.
And, and friends, that's a one-way trip, baby.
This is the Swingin' Love Corpses interview.
This is a preview.
Let's call this a preview of the Swingin' Love Corpses interview.
What is this one coming up?
Let's, let's, let's bring this, bring this up.
No, no, that might be our instructional techniques tape.
Nope, nope, it's not that one.
Well, this is from, uh...
You understand your hypnosis tapes have been very successful.
Yeah.
Your sleep tapes.
Right.
The teaching and...
Earn while...
What are the courses available?
Earn while you sleep.
Earn, earn and learn while you sleep tapes.
That was...
The series has been very successful.
Yeah, I understand the positive thinking.
And we had frat while you sleep.
Smoke cigarettes while you sleep.
We were actually into the...
You can accomplish anything while you sleep.
Sleep 18 hours a day.
Uh, pyroflagellate for the other six hours.
Uh, praise Bob.
Praise Bob.
So, what are we listening to now?
This isn't Le Petit Mane's Disciples.
This is, uh...
African Love Rhapsody?
Or is this the zen of corporate butt kissing?
No, this is, uh, from Le Petit Mane's Disciples right here.
It's, uh, it's a cut from side two.
It's called, uh, Poop Dog Hat Part Two.
Oh, okay.
And, uh...
Very shortly we'll be getting into...
This is Brazilian influenced.
I understand this is influenced by Brazilian voodoo music.
Mm-hmm.
And I understand you've had many experiences with Haitian voodoo.
That is correct.
And Haitian diseases.
And Dr. G. Gordon Gordon was, uh...
Yes, of Curry Squid fame, friends.
You heard him last here on...
Curry Squid, formerly of Doctors for Extreme Prejudice.
That's right.
Another great doctor band.
Um...
He happened to be in town.
He happened to be in town, uh, for a few days and, and...
So, the Dr. G. Gordon Gordon sat in?
He knew we were cutting a new album in the studio.
I bet you guys were doing it.
And so...
How about Curry Squid?
I guess being...
He came on down there and...
Being rich and, and, uh, famous rock stars, now you have the, the Curry Squids brought
to you, right?
You don't have to go out and catch them.
Yeah, they, they bring them to us.
Does the record company, uh, do you have any records?
Uh, we have, uh, we have a record company.
2 že Kenắn et al
gwaddle.
Wackyly, 환 αυτό.
our own variety.
Well, I've always preferred
to just plain old raw prairie squid
than any special
prepared prairie squid.
I would have, you know,
your fans all think that
you always get the Russian
spiny squids and
the arboreal squids from Jamaica
and so forth, the
sloth squids.
And, I mean, come on.
You can...
For history's sake, you know, what kind of
squid does...
What kind of prairie squid or
prairie kind of mollusk like this?
I know I'm going to disappoint a lot of people.
A Mississippi River Valley squid.
I'm going to disappoint a whole lot of people.
Just local stuff.
Squid is squid, man.
I like it all.
It doesn't make any difference to me.
Any kind of squid is good squid.
And they've got the biggest
fluters, man. I'm not kidding you.
They just hang right out there.
The Missouri squid.
Fluter squid.
Yeah, well, no, those are
the freshwater
aquatic squids.
I mean, they're...
They can hang them fluters, though.
They hang the fluters right out of there.
I'm kidding.
I mean, I understand that
fluters gets hard.
I've heard that you'll do a prairie squid
without me beating you.
And he'll do it in about five minutes, too.
That's the word that gets around in the rock and roll press.
Without me beating you.
That's what I call an overman.
A true overman.
But you know what I can say?
It's kind of like the name of this next song.
But we don't...
We do not recommend that anyone in our audience
attempt to utilize a prairie squid
without me beating you.
That's the way it is.
It reminds me of the name of the song.
If this is a prairie squid,
it's right here.
Ooh!
Oh, hey.
My hand
It's my, it's my hand
It's my hand
My hand
My head
Hey, appa hey佐!
It's my, it's my, it's my, it's my, it's my, it's my life.
Ooh.
He said we don't usually cut through the bubble.
He's got a scream for attention.
He's got a problem.
And all I want to know is how come it's my, it's my head.
Ooh.
Oh, yes, dear friends, it's just my head.
That's a mighty Swingin' Love Corpses tune, friends.
That's the Swingin' Love Corpses.
Dr. Philo Drummond, Corporal Sphinx Drummond.
And a special vocalist on this one.
The G. Gordon Gordon.
Ah, yes.
I hate to pot down on that one.
Friends, I'll tell you what.
Oh, yes, dear friends.
The American Indian version of Amazing Grace.
I heard this earlier today on KNOA.
The Beyond Boznero Show.
The Baha'i Show.
Anyway, let's...
Friends, I've just had three phone calls begging,
begging for the place to write for information on the Church of the Subgenius.
And where to find out more about Bob,
the Good Sex for Mutants Dating League,
the...
and how to get slack.
How to get slack off of Bob for nothing.
For nothing.
And you can write for information, friends.
You've got those pens and pencils and computers ready.
And that postage stamp.
You can write to Bob, dear friends,
at P.O. Box 140306.
That's right.
P.O. Box 140306.
In Dallas, Texas.
Mighty, mighty Dallas, Texas.
The headquarters of Bob.
At the zip code of 75214.
That's Bob at P.O. Box 140306.
Dallas, Texas.
75214.
And you can write for information on the many, many products.
You know, these tapes are...
But, well, we can't get into advertising on this public supported station.
We're going to be begging you for money just for this.
The stations start next week.
I say no, yeah.
And then say, yeah.
The earth no longer lay nor
far away.
Yeah.
They're remember, yes, plot
for profit.
Look here.
More than free training program is offering transportation, basic skills training, and GED preparation.
Dear friends, support services and vocational training in air conditioning and refrigeration, automobile service and repair, cable TV installation, office careers, paint and wall covering, and home health aid training.
And they pay you $5 a day just to learn these skills.
So if you're 17 to 21 years of age, a low-income resident of the city or county of Dallas, and a high school dropout, call 746-2492.
Call now. That's 746-2492.
Now let me see if I can get Rebby Sharp's lovely record going here.
Eh?
This is Green Streets by Rebby Sharp, also with the orthotonics.
Whew. I believe we have to go a little bit faster.
Huge liners passing tires, water shrinks to burrows.
Breakers hardly breaking, fishery just to show us.
Holes with an opening, craters.
On the sides, Admiral Byrd was ranting.
Flying far inside, meat grew 11 feet around.
Bacteria walked on two planets, tilting on faulty X's.
But he forgot to chew.
Driving ladders from the south.
Driving ladders from the north.
Ah, it's going to run with caution.
Crawling to the source.
The land inside was thriving.
The outside layered dying.
Coated towns of authorities.
Turned truth to myth by lying.
Green bars beneath the strata, morning tones of color.
Rounding sky in layers.
For your blanket round the other.
Mobile ears filled with mud seed signals.
For your blanket round the other. Mobile ears filled with mud seed signals.
Ext nearest molecules gloss below.
Waldened by rocking gasses.
Apples grew up in rows.
Butterflyyer returned to theiliz
Ah, it's going to run with caution.
Crawling to the source.
The land inside was thriving, the outside lay a-dying. Coated tongues of authorities turned truth to myth by lying.
Huge liners passing fires, water trucks to pause. Breakers hardly breaking, fish we used to shoot.
You see the poles with an opening, craters on the sides. And the word was ranting,
Far and far inside, far and far inside, far and far inside, far and far inside.
Well, dear friends, actually that wasn't Green Streets, that was a Hollow Earth song.
They must have printed that record with the doohickeys on it.
Let me see if I write it.
Here we go.
Listen to that sound of slack, friends.
Stay tuned, by the way, for Soul Oldies coming right up.
Meanwhile, to this day I don't know who sent us this cassette.
This was sent by someone here in Dallas.
It's a lovely Bob song coming up here, but I don't know who did it.
If anybody out there does know or did this thing,
please, look,
call,
and let us know.
823-7490
Music
Bob, hoax me in the eye with love.
Think about it.
Who was the last guy to say to you these words?
Supercalifragilisticexpialidocious.
Who?
I say, don't trade Bob for eagle stamps.
Bob, hoax me in the eye with love.
Take a rubber chicken to lunch.