Lil ej prevented
48 hours of slack
Freedom
Thealing
Watch the video
Mr. America, walk on by
Your schools that do not teach
The minds that won't be reached
Mr. America, try to hide
The emptiness that's you inside
But once you find that the way you lied
And all the corny tricks you tried
Will not forestall the rising tide
Of hungry freaks
Daddy
They won't go for no more
Great Midwestern heartache
The hardware store philosophy
That turns away
From those who aren't afraid to say
What's on their minds
The left behinds
Of the Great Society
The
Great Society
Hungry freaks die
Funny Gypsy
Steady
Mr. America, walk on by
Your supermarket dreams
Your murderCon NSA
Mr. America, walk on by
The liquor store supreme
Mr. America, try to hide
The product of your savage pride
The useful minds that it denied
The day you shrugged and stepped aside
You saw their clothes and then you cried
Those hungry freaks, daddy
They won't go home for no more
Great Midwestern hardware store
Philosophy that turns away
From those who aren't afraid to say
What's on their minds
The left behind
Of the great society
Beat & Make
page 7
1 Diagnostics of
3. There are 4 of us
Sign 2
верq
3. For whoever
We are clean
4. momentos of love
No matter how you do the math
It doesn't add up
It's all subtraction
And when you intersect our path
We get the answer
We are the action
I see a world that includes everyone
5, 4, 3, 2
Our number is 1
I see a world that includes everyone
5, 4, 3, 2
Our number is 1
No matter how it makes us feel inside
The world is learning how to divide
I believe our hearts can't hide
We are the action
When we come together
We're satisfied
I see a world that includes everyone
5, 4, 3, 2
Our number is 1
I see a world that includes everyone
5, 4, 3, 2
Our number is 1
I believe our hearts can't hide
5, 4, 3, 2
Our number is 1
But our students won't be able to tell
To talk up against the books
And who you can really commit to
5, 4, 3, 2
Separate, factor out the fun
We fall apart, it's a chain reaction
If we can count on everyone
See the sum, the satisfaction
I see a world that includes everyone
5, 4, 3, 2, our number is 1
I know I just heard the words
I know you needed us
I know we make money
I know we're ready to do it
I know it's a good wave
But we'd better partner
You know we're not alone
You and I minute by minute
Don't say Mr. Obnio
We listen to every footnote
You don't want me
Thank you.
Now watch while everybody on your street will take a turn to stomp and smash and bash and crash and slash and bust and burn.
And I'm watching and I'm waiting, hoping for the best.
Even think I'll go to praying every time I hear them saying that there's no way to delay that trouble coming every day.
No way to delay that trouble coming every day.
Well, you can cool it, you can heat it, cause baby I don't need it.
Take your TV tube and heat it, and all that phony stuff on sports and all the unconfirmed reports.
You know I'll watch that rotten box until my head begin to hurt.
From checking out the way the newsmen say they get the dirt.
Before the guys on channel so-and-so and further they'll say.
That any show they'll interrupt.
They'll bring you news if it comes up.
They say that if the place blows up, they will be the first to tell.
Cause the boys they got downtown are working hard and doing swift.
And if anybody gets the news before it hits the street.
They say that no one blabs it faster, their coverage can be beat.
And if another woman driver gets machine gunned from her seat.
They'll send some joker with a brownie and you'll see it all complete.
So I'm watching and I'm waiting, hoping for the best.
Even think I go to prayin', every time I hear them sayin'.
That there's no way to delay that trouble comin' every day.
No way to delay that trouble comin' every day.
Hey, you know something people.
I'm not black, but there's a whole lot of times I wish I could say I'm not white.
Well, I've seen the fires burnin'.
And I've seen the fires burnin'.
And the local people turnin'.
All the merchants and the shops who used to sell their brooms and mops.
And every other household item.
Watch a mob just turn and bite them.
And they say it served them right.
Because a few of them were white.
And it's the same across the nation.
Black and white discrimination.
And you can't understand me.
And all that other jazz they hand me.
And the papers and TV.
And all that mass stupidity that seems to grow more every day.
Each time you hear something we say.
You want to go.
And do your in.
Cause the color of your skin.
Just don't appeal to him.
No matter if it's black or white.
Because he's out for blood tonight.
Hey.
Yeah,
Yeah.
All right,
today,
ends the previous theme.
if that comes together here you start and I already know that bombo I got
I mean,
they put up a match in a match.
Hey.
In the eyes of all these people
Don't you know that this could start
On any street, in any town
In any state, if any clown
Decides that now's the time to fight
For some ideal he thinks is right
And if a million more agree
There ain't no great society
As it applies to you and me
Our country isn't free
And the law refused to see
If all that you can ever be
Is just a lousy janitor
Unless your uncle owns the store
You know that five and every four
Just won't amount to nothing more
So we'll watch the rats go across the floor
And make up songs about being bored
Blow your harmonica song
Yeah, Trouble Comin' Every Day
A timely song done in the late 60s, I think
That may have been Zappa's first album
Hungry Freaks
Which also was played
At the time of the war
At the very beginning of the show
The second song
The more modern sounding one
Was Our Number Is One
By Exposed Foreheads
Our new buddies
That we'll be seeing at the devotional
Oh, it's Fourth Reich Rising
That was our buddy Fat Man D
Reverend Fat Man D
And we heard an instrumental
From the Rudy Schwartz Project
Tango Lessons in a Fascist Whorehouse
And this is our buddy Fat Man D
And this might be Dave
It is
I interrupted you in the middle of a statement
Yeah, no, that's okay
You tried to call it a little early, I think
No, I just went upstairs
To obfuscate my
My pliandroses
And the nasal passage
Were completely, totally evacuated
By some kind of
Sunstream beauty
That nobody's ever heard of before
So that's where I'm at
I don't know if it's in Nebraska
Or any place you ever want to leave
Well, it's in Neighbor World, isn't it?
Isn't everything in Neighbor World?
Well, except for the
The things that escape
Yeah
Sometimes they escape in plain sight
Like, just like, you know
When you go to a senior home
And some old lady or old man
Will just stand up in the middle of a conversation
And start barking
Verciferously
As if, you know
They're very life-dependent on it
Perhaps it is
Or it does
It does
In some cases, I'm sure it does
Well, Dave, you getting ready for X-Day?
The subgenius holiday
And destruction of the known planet Earth?
How many years now
Have I told you I don't believe in it no more?
Oh, that doesn't matter
Whether you believe in it
Or whether I believe in it or not
It's coming
X-Day isn't coming
Oh, X-Day is coming
But it doesn't mean we'll be riding away
On the pleasure ships of the isosceles triangle
Maybe not the way you're thinking of it
Yeah
I've got a book here that talks all about it
It's called
Revelation
Relevation
Elevation
Nexus
Plexus
Dexus
From Texas
Hey, that rhymes
No, this is our other out-of-print book
The, uh
The subgenius cyclopedia of slack
The Bobliagraphon
Oh, the Bobliagraphon
Right
More commonly known as Pat
But it says here
What will it be like on the escape vessels?
Peyton Place in outer space
No doubt once things settle down
You'll soon discover that your sex goddess
Can be anyone
From an old high school crush
To your most hated politician
That's pretty scary
Now, ready
Yeah, you wouldn't want to be having sex with Ronald
Uh, Tony
Now, ready to have sex with you
Or play checkers
If that's your preference
Usually
It's only a simulacra
Of those persons
Although
If the individuals in question
Are subgeniuses
It might really be them
Yep
More than likely would be
If you consider all the facts
And all the
All the tuna fish
That they had to go through
Each year
That they were up in Alaska
Doing all that work up there
And then they come back
And he's right when
He's right when
Jelly mongers
These hot sauce
And cold toast
Tuna fish
Artifactors
AM radio guys
All say that they're experts
On meteorology
And all the meteorological scientists
Are all hoaxers
And the one guy said
The reason why he knew
More than all these thousands
Of meteorological hoaxers
Was because he wanted to be a weatherman
When he was a junior in high school
And I figured
I am a right wing type of naturalist
All white type of person
I'm gonna listen to that guy
And do exactly what he says
Even if it requires
Marching around in a pair of softies
Or huggies
Or any of those other diapers
For old people
Oh so you don't believe me now
No it wasn't that
It was that I got a text
Right that's the first time
That's ever happened
I got a text in the middle of the show
And it was Dr. Sinister
Oops
I accidentally started to call him
I didn't mean to do that
Oh is that cool?
No it's terrible
I'm locked into Neighbor World now
Because I got that darn intelligent phone
Well can't you turn its eyes off
And just pretend it's somewhere else
Like neighboring Peru
Or Salacious Argo Way
I'm too dumb to control my smart phone
Yeah that's the problem I'm having
It's like I was talking to some people
About cost you know
I figured if I tried real hard
And saved up I could get something
But it costs a lot of money
To get those ones
With the real good video apps on them
And stuff like that there
No
Isn't it?
No it doesn't actually
I don't want to do advertisements
For those things
I don't want to do any advertisements
Sometimes they give you the phone
If you buy the plan
Don't you see?
You gotta buy into the big plan
The big big plan
Then you get a free
You know eyeball phone
Or whatever those things
You know
Yeah
I did the opposite
I bought the largest
Clunkiest of the phones
Most expensive too
And it was partly
Clunkiest in the middle
I want to be able to use it
Unlike most smart phones
Which are kind of small
I could use this as a weapon
Did you notice the other day
When we met in person
For the first time in a couple of years
That you reached for your pocket
Yeah
At first you were
I was like oh my god
I was ready to
Ready to whack you over the head
With you if you pulled anything
You just bopped it on the head
Like my mother in law says
There was nothing nearby to pull
So I just expected you
To show me how to use the darn
Darn
You'd kill yourself
For playing with this thing
I think I could go into
A chaotic spill wheel
Of swirling and
Conconventions
That wouldn't go on
Forever and ever
I just
I would feel so lonely
In deep space
Not just knowing
Just not knowing
That it not only had
A chance to kill me
I missed X day
But I missed Y day
And Z day
Which were
No
Come to
Now that you mention it
I haven't even
Thought about Y day
And Z day
No wonder we're having
So much trouble with X day
Maybe we should have
Just moved on
Yeah
Instead of waiting
For the
For the men from planet X
We could wait
For the
The men from planet Y
Or the Ys
Or the women from
The women from planet Y
The Amazon women
From planet Y
No they're from planet W
Because the women
Or because the number
Of Croatian artifacts
Not Croatian artifacts
I mean the
The you know
Actually
You know
Technically you're right
Because the Yakutism
The most evil
And destructive
Of all aliens
Are in fact
All female
Yeah
And they are some
Scary Shiva-like
Bee hatches
I'm just
I'm just plugging right along
Trying to figure out
What the hell you're talking about
Dave
I'm talking about
The doctrinal material
From book of the subgenius
Back
Written over
Over 300 years ago
I'm listening
But I'm
I'm not listening
I'm looking
I'm looking at a picture of
Subgeniuses spell out
The name
Bob
In butts
Readable
From outer space
And that actually happened
At one X day drill
The sad thing is
Our photo of it
You can't tell
They're spelling out Bob
Because we didn't have
A crane
Or a drone
In those days
Or even a ladder
I think it is on a ladder
But
Yeah it's like
Scaffolding
You see the butts
But you don't see Bob
And the cheeks are arguing
And we're waiting
To slap them down
But at least
They spelled Bob right
And they only need
One butt each
For the quote marks
On the upper left and right
Yeah
Because you always put
Quotes around Bob
To prove you're not a
You know
Just a pretender
But now
I forget the part
Where the quote marks would go
Do they go in the
So called
May I use the phrase
No
Oh here goes
Ass crack
No
No they are that
Crack
That's what separates
The two heads
Of the quote marks
That's what
That's what makes
Tuna fish so tasty
After all these
Palabras
Well I don't know
About the tuna fish
But that's why you only need
One butt for the quote marks
On Bob
But you need at least
Two butts
I think
Nine people
Just for the B
Yeah
You need five or so
For the O
And then you need
Another nine
For the other B
And that's about
That's about everybody
That comes to X-Day
That's a lot
That's a lot of people
To spell one small
Tiny word
Now we could do
But just think of it
As like a commercial
From the Uber mention
No no no no no no no no no no
That they're trying
To spread the message
By using your
Vile incendiary
Testosterone
And other Republican
Delights
That you
Seem to just like
Toss off the grill
As if they were something
You know
To behold
No
Not me
Not you?
No I'm the guy
Taking pictures
Oh man I got the wrong
River and I don't stay
I'm just the guy
With the camera
I'm the one with the camera
I'm not the one that's
Well you know
I don't know
Yeah
You apparently know
And I don't want to know
To serve man
Ha ha
That is indeed
The job of old
Barbecue chef Bob
It says
Here
The exes saucers
Will come to collect
The faithful
And as the bobbies
Ascend the gravity
Elevators
Into the motherships
Some few will be
Separated out
By Bob
Chosen from among
The true believers
To become part of
The special sauce
He's preparing
Ha
Oh
Mm
The rest of the
I think that's one of the
Most delicious things
You ever wrote
Or ate
I didn't write
That's the word of Bob
The rest of the
Subgenie
It says here
Once they have ruptured
And become adjusted
To their new powers
Will have the option
Of creating their own
Love planets
Or wreaking vengeance
Upon the X-Day survivors
Remaining on Earth
Or both
Why not both?
No doubt
There'll be some amazing
Special effects
But in real life
The winepress of Jehovah
Will make the oceans
Turn red
While the can opener
Of Wotan
Looses plagues
Upon the sun
And the orange
Squeezer of Anubis
Squeezes forth
Foul demons
The vacuum cleaner
Of Moab
Shall sweep up
The unworthy
And the mulcher
Of Melchizedek
Shall make waste
Of their works
Melchizedek
I was always fond
Of that name
Melchizedek
What is it?
Melchizedek?
I think so
I've been
I sometimes call my wife
That to
To tease her
But doesn't that mean
One who
Who dishonors
The flatulence
Or something like that?
Some kind of
Real obscure passage
From the
Apocryphon
The bibliography
I don't know
The other ones
I like are
There's something scary
About it
Wouldn't you
Wouldn't you agree
That there's
It's a little scary
Sometimes
Who's the one
That comes before
Meshach and Abednego?
Shadrach
Meshach and Abednego
There we go
Now I feel right
I don't know who they are
But I know it feels good
To say that
Shadrach
Meshach and Abednego
You have to say it
Just that way
Those are biblical names
Of people who
Went to the same
Grocery store
Too often
And so the biblical
Scholars wrote about it
Now they're important
You know what I mean?
I know that
The great sage
Ronald Reagan
Once said
To the premier
Of Russia
You know
If aliens
From outer space
Ever invaded
All our nations
Would forget their differences
And band together
Of course
Even as he was saying that
Nancy's minions
Were making
Traitorous deals
Trying to sell out
The planet
To those punks
The so-called
Greys
But the greys
Are pipsqueaks
Our alien allies
Are like on two
Gods
Their spaceships
Do not crash
For they do not need
Spaceships
Any more than
Bob needs brains
Boy that's a powerful
Mouthful
And it bespeaks
The entire
Conundrum
That you're faced with
As the sacred scribe
Is to get the message out
All the same way
That Ronald Reagan
Was toying with
The adult mentality
You know
Like he had
Fine haircut
And nice
Well cut suit
With cuffs on it
And no frays
You know
The funny thing is
Reagan knew Bob
And was actually
In a band with him
With him and Philo
But he didn't tell Nancy
He somehow knew
That Nancy would put
The kibosh
On that action
Oh yeah
Of course
You know
She was a little bit
Old fashioned
And he was
One of the first
Republican leaders
To actually start
A punk band
A punk rock band
In the early 1970s
I think it was 73
He told his mom about it
But not his wife
Well that's the way
Things are when you're
In a punk band
And no one would
Listen to you man
Hey at the end of this show
I'm gonna play
I'm gonna play your song
Iodine 131
At the end of this show
You know I think that
That song should have
The part where I'm talking
About Chernobyl
Taken out
So it's more generic
And it should just
Go everywhere
Because they're trying
To do more nuclear stuff
Right now
And the Nuclear Energy
Commission is trying
To do away with some
Plants without making sure
They're safer
And all kinds of stuff
Like that
And it's very very strange
And it could be dangerous
I have two nephews
Who work at the
Comanche Peak Flower Power
Plant in North Texas
And they say it's
Perfectly safe
Nothing could go wrong
Well even our old friend
From the past
Chad Smith
Worked at Perry for a while
And he said
You know one of those things
That you look at
To make sure something
Is straight
And not like crooked
Or hanging down
Or low
It's like level
A bevel
Level
Yeah
He said they were
Building a whole bunch of stuff
On the exterior part
And they weren't even
Leveling stuff
They were just like
That's good enough
What year
What year was that?
That was I believe
In the 1970s
Yes
By the time the Comanche Peak plant
Was being built
Near Dallas
In Glen Rose in fact
It's in Glen Rose?
Yeah
My little baby sister
Was dating people
Who worked there
And she assures me
That that plant
Was built entirely
By people on quaaludes
All the time
Same with Perry
Because it was that same period of time
When everybody thought
A quaalude or ten
Would make a life more durable
I didn't know what they were
And I was
Me neither
I was trying to finish
The book of the subgenius
I was on a serious deadline
I had to drive across town
In my manual operated car
My Flintstones car
But I was having such bad leg cramps
From exhaustion and lack of sleep
That I needed something
To end the leg cramps
So that I could
Drive
Now imagine that
My friend goes
Well Valium would probably be
About right
But there's
I have this new thing
Called a quaalude
My friend said
They're not very strong
You should take two
I um
I woke up in jail
I woke up in jail that night
Perfect ending
Or beginning for the new story
Yeah
And I was
I was locked up with another
A guy who'd been put in there
For urinating in a parking lot
Of a bar
And I was like
Oh my god
And you thought he was Dobbs
Or actually you thought
He was an incarnation
Of Gupta
Gupta
He would not shut up
And I laid down there
Trying to get warm
You know
Because they keep you
Really cold in jail
And they take your glasses away
And I must say
That night I spent in jail
I heard some of the most
Hilarious banter and talk
By the denizens
Of the other cells
I couldn't see
The guy was like
The guy I was stuck with
Was a jerk
Wow I didn't know
I heard some
I couldn't sleep
You can't sleep
Because there's guys
Just screaming jokes
And stuff all night long
That was in 1981 or 2
And that was the last
And only time
I ever took one
Of them kind pills Bob
And speaking of which
I found the original
More of them kind pills
Bob tape
Tonight
Wow
On my desperate
None of this means
Anything to you necessarily
But I found the original
Well it sounds so official though
Well there was
There was this plaintiff
Subgenius out there
Real early
Subgenius
I'd love to take a plaintiff
There
Roberto de la Rosa
He called himself
And he sent us a letter
Written in crayon
That said
More of them kind pills
Bod
He got the quotes on Bob
But he didn't spell Bob right
He spelled it Bod
And we weren't sure
Maybe he was trying to be deep
Or mean something by that
We just figured Bob
Had hooked him on some kind of pills
And he wanted a lot more
And then we got a tape from him
And you could hear him saying
Bob
Could I have a few more
Of those pills
Because the red trucks in Ohio
And the little animals in the woods
Well here's the sad thing
Although Roberto de la Rosa
Had another one of those pills
He had another name
And under that name
He made some really great movies
Including Invasion of the Aluminum People
But he died
Oh man
Right after Aluminum People
He went chaotic
No
Here's what's sad though
He had just finished filming
His first real feature
The night he died
He finished shooting
Went home perfectly normal
And died
Had a heart attack
Or some sort of other bad thing
Yeah something
You know nobody
He's not the only old friend
That that happened to
But these things come around
In a way
His widow Sandy
Had been at the honest to God
Very first subgenius revival with him
It was actually partly
A Pink Boys band show
None of us really were preaching yet
But she heard about it early then
And now 139 years later
She's directing this documentary movie
About the church
And they're showing up tomorrow
As you know
Mainly to get a gander
At the subgenius archives
And get a handle
On how to deal with the footage
I heard they want to get a gander
On more than your archives
If you know what I mean
Everybody's already done that
But here's that
There were two things
That I was
I really wanted to do
I really wanted to find for him
One
Is the original
True Dobbs head
The one from which
All
Other Bob portraits
Are descendants
This is a great great grandpappy
Of all Dobbs heads
I deliberately keep it
In a hard to find place
But I tried to find it
And I did
You confused yourself
I did
I found it
And I touched it
I touched it
And then I spent about two hours
Cleaning up
A path
To the oldest
Most wretched
Spider web covered
Scorpion infested
Recesses of my storage room
Which really did take two hours
Just to get a path clear
To the oldest stuff in the back
And then I started looking
For the two
Tapes
Reel to reel tapes
From Roberto de la Rosa
Because his widow
Asked me to find those
And by golly
I did
Even though those were
Among the very first items
Mailed to us
There they were
Next to all the recordings
Of my
One and
One and zero year old kids
Trying to talk
And
Zero years old
The very first
Very first
Terrible subgenius shows
For all this
Like from 1979
I found it man
I found it
I actually put my hands
On the Roberto de la Rosa tape
So I'm going to be able
To hand Sandy
These two
Two boxes
Hand labeled
By her late husband
And say
I found them
I wasn't sure
That I could
So it was a big deal Dave
It was a real
Real big deal
It's a real big deal man
And I can feel
What I can sense
I feel in you brother
I truly are
Am not
No I truly am
I can understand that
However it's a little bit depleted
When I think of my own
Personal existence
Like who's going to want
200 records
From 200 years ago
I'm not going to want
Stuff like that
Well you know Dave
They say that
A lot of people
Lead lives of quiet desperation
But we subgeniuses
Choose to lead lives of
Ear splitting desperation
Yes
We must have slack
And instead we're getting
Force fed a gross pablum
Of false slack
Ripped off every day
And we're not going to
Sit back and be polite
While we're getting reamed
Yeah man
You said a mouthful again
Once again
You're full of many many many
Contrite doubtful mouthfuls tonight
Well I'm reading
The power pack and power punch
The truth of the gospel
Of Norad and Starzak
The both of them
You know
Working out in the same gym
At the same time
What a disgusting
Ill feature
Hey speaking of
The end of the world
And X day in 1998
And that big party we throw
In southern Ohio
What
Today is June 11th
So that means it's like
Way less than a month
Before the end of the year
And we're going to be
Where the X's are here
And in fact I have to
Haul all of our
Swag and displays
And the guy that we're
Going to sacrifice
And the Bob dummy
All down to Athens area
It's a five hour drive
I've got to do that
In about a week
And leave the stuff there
Then I have to drive back
Then I have to pick up
Dr. Hal
And my mother in law
And the dog
And the pretty girl
And drive back to Athens
And drive back to Wisteria
And host the party
Of at least ten people
Plus some filmmakers
Well you sound very happy to do so
Especially some of the brain damage
You suffered over the last few months
And I certainly identify with you
And I'm not apathetic
In the least small barriers
If I could help
In any way I could help you
I certainly would
I'd even you know
Like a GoFundMe situation
Don't you have to repent Coach Mark?
It's a very delicate part of the brain
Which is nearly impossible to operate on
But I would still stand up in the smalls
And wear my waistcoats for you
Well wouldn't you have to repent
Quit your job
And slack off to do that?
Oh that second part would be so sweet
Those girls would love to have you
On July 3rd and 4th
Which are the two main days
They're going to be trying to shoot people
With their practice weapons
They're disguised as cameras
And everybody who goes to X Day
Will probably end up being in the movie
Unless they don't want to be
In which case they should sit in the back
You might have to form a release
Or some sort of other kind of thing
That could kill you possibly
You know everybody does sign a release
It's just built into the fine print
Of walking through the gates
You have signed a release that says
If my grandma sees my
Pregnant mother
Privates on the internet
As a result of me being here
That's my fault and not Reverend Stang's
Well I think you should start a
Facey campaign right now
That will put all those rumors to rest
And give them enough NyQuil
That they don't wake up tomorrow
You know what I'm saying?
No no that's a Jonestown thing
Just walk into a room and pull off
Your tie and your shirt and your knuckles
And just start slapping the waiters
And waitresses
And make obscure curses that nobody knows
That really gets them going
You know like
And they can tell it's swearing
Even though it's in Mixolydian
Which is you know Harcourt and Brace 1992
That's a long time ago you know
Yeah nobody understands those big words anymore
They don't even know you're cussing
Yup
You say words like exemplary
Instead of awesome and they think
Ooh he said something dirty I know that was dirty
Right that's what the first thing that comes to their mind
Is he's thinking about my orifice
Or he sees
Wanting me to her to think of
Her orifices
Well
And I'm not you know I'm
Sure Dave sure you're not
Bigger than any other old fella
I've been to the churchyard and seen my ancestors
Laying in the coffins the way they used to do it
Back in the days of
Spanish influenza
And pre-consternation
Revelry
A lot of it was due to that
Well you know
If you go to subgenius.com
On the internet
I think it's called
And look at the
Ancient events
Of yore
And the x-day drills
Which this
We've drilled for x-day 21 times
And yet to hit oil
Starting in 1996
That was when the first drill was
But man
Every all the ladies took their shirts off
At that one
In 97
98 and 99
Which was
2000 was triple x-day
Oh
Everybody would jump into the
Baptismal pond
In their skivvies
Start naked
And after those years
You start to see fewer and fewer
In fact you start seeing holes in the picture galleries
Where one
Lady or boy or another
Wrote to me and said
I hate for you to have to do this but my mom
Is on the internet now
And I don't want her to see my fat butt
Running around naked with all those boys
And I would take them down
And I
We're talking about this
We were talking about this the other day
The spread of the pocket phones
With cameras
Has ended most
Fun nudity
At those
At those naked camp
Or those clothing optional campgrounds
That is a very very interesting observation
And worthy of a full 1200
Word article
Has have smartphones
Done away with nudity
Or sky clad
Yeah yeah
Done away with a lot more than that
The first couple of star woods I went to
This is quite true
More than once I had to step
Over copulating
Hippies in the middle of
The trail heading for
As I was trying to get to the bonfire
Or whatever
And that just
You don't see that anymore
Maybe they just hide now
I wonder if burning man is that way
When I went to burning man in 2001
I saw people doing stuff
In a phone booth
In the middle of the desert
Or they were
Finishing up when I came along
And
But I
It's like now there's cameras
Everywhere
And your grandma is one of the cops
Yep
I had sex at brushwood a couple times
During days of
Of
X day and stuff
Everybody did besides me
Everybody did but me
I never did
Yes you did your wife would company you many times
And still does
And man I'm working
I'm working at those things
No you have
You've taken too far too many things for vanity
I don't want to talk about this
You're making me uneasy
I know it makes you nauseous
And then we have to put up with everything that follows that
Okay
No it's getting too turned on
I don't want to break the station
Oh no man
You've gone too far
Now here's another thing
That you and me have to
Well now you've already done your work
I have to finish it up
We have to finish neighbor world
I just have to go in and fix the spelling
And some typing things here and there
And that way we can have like
We can
We can sell out of the books at X day
So I'm going to print at least ten of them
Oh that would be wonderful
It's a novel friends
Listeners it's a novel by Lonesome Cowboy Dave
And it's great
It actually makes a lot more sense
Than he does normally
But yet it's kind of in that same
Dave-ish style
You'll see oh you'll see
You'll see
You'll see one of these days
You look around and you'll see
You'll see
That sounds like the name of an Asiatic bear
Somebody that Comrade Truton
Or Mr. Poopin would
You'll see
My love bear
Oh wait we're not supposed to talk about bears
In the same show as X-Day
Because there was that one person
You know bears were invading the county I live in
And they've eaten a bunch of
And that was the front page of the newspaper
Was a knocked over beehive
So bears really do go after beehives
To them it was like
Oh man thanks a lot
This is great
And they yeah
Same reason why the bees
Do all the
Sanctified fruit
After Mass and sometimes
They eat different other particulates
Are you really getting bears in Ashtabula again
I think the bears here are going to think
There's a bear alive in the neighborhood
Let's not call the ODNR
Let's kill the bear and show that we're brave hunters
It's where they just had a
A big scandal involving
Processing deer meat
Where the guy was doing this scam
Where he was killing hundreds of deer
And he wasn't hunting
He was just killing all these deer
Through a series of traps and other things like that
And then he'd sell the smoked meat
For different venison products
In the area when you go to the gas station
And get a slim jinky
So he was a poacher
He was a poacher
That's what they called it in the newspaper
I wish that guy lived in my neighborhood
I seriously do
I wish that guy would come and turn
Most of the deer in my backyard
Into venison jerky
Because they're eating everything
And they're miserable
They're wretched
They're as bad as the subgeniuses in the winter
They live in vacant lots and stuff
I don't live in my yard most of the time
The other day I was walking down the street
With my giant hound dog
Right in the middle of Taylor
Well on the sidewalk of a busy highway
Taylor, South Taylor Road
And I noticed that there was a large reddish deer
Strolling alongside me
About three feet away
And the dog didn't care
And the deer didn't care
And I thought what is going on here?
Am I the only one in this?
I didn't care
Mammy said I had no more hair
I'm sorry, I'm sorry
I just don't know
How could that be?
It is very weird
But I do know that Cleveland has had a deer problem
For like about almost 30 years
They used to have to send guys from the ODNR
Out to the emerald necklace
As they like to call it
They don't have those guys anymore
No they don't
They gutted that
They let them do as they please
The dirty rotten deers
The animal control has been gutted
In the name of conservative freedom
What else has been gutted?
Well pretty much everything has been gutted
Anything that involves cleaning up
Or making things better
Environmentally safer
Has become gutted
Even on the plus side
The IRS doesn't have anywhere near enough people
To audit me
And I'm not saying that
Now that's true
If you want to put them in that way
I would take
I would take a whole Ben Arthur feature
Of folks and under folks
To get to you
Show your taxes
That's what they were saying to me
Oh boy
Show your taxes
And I was like okay
I'll just unbuckle my pants
Take a look at this
My tax here buddy
You like my big old tax?
You have to say the chocolate cake was really great
It was really great
It really was
So Dave
I just want to be more believable
I'm sorry
Do you know that it's almost 10 o'clock?
It's almost 10 o'clock
Do you know where Manny and Pappy is?
Pappy's in heaven
Taking over Jesus' job
He showed up there and said
You did a good job Jesus
Let me show you how a pro does it
Well that's nice
That's my father's service
My father did not want anybody else
To talk about God or Jesus
He threw in one thing about his God
At the very very end
Of his own eulogy
And then said nobody else is to say anything
Well the preacher had to get up
And go I just know you was meeting Jesus now
And I told the preacher later
I said I'm sure he is meeting Jesus
And he's probably telling him what he did wrong
That's my Pappy
Don't be so sure preacher boy
My Pappy's in heaven
Even though my Pappy taught Bible studies
In the Methodist church
As could I if I wanted to
He was an atheist
And didn't believe in any of that stuff
He just knew a lot about it
So your father believed in aliens?
Is that what you're saying?
That he was a biblical scholar
Who actually believed in aliens?
No he was a biblical scholar
Who didn't believe in much of anything
Oh okay
He said I was raised a secular
You know junior scientist
That was always my religion
Yeah I had a little chemistry set
I tried to make things blow up
But they made them too safe
You know they just get smoky and stinky
Hey get this man
I made a grasshopper invisible
I was just randomly mixing chemicals
Without writing down what it was
I painted a grasshopper with it
I turned around and the grasshopper
Had totally gone invisible
But I couldn't even remember the formula
The grasshopper didn't jump away from you
As you turned around?
What?
Oh no I was being very scientific about this
Anyway speaking of science
We have to play your song Dave
My song?
Yeah
My song
Iodine 131
That love song
It's a love song about chemicals
And gutting the restrictions
I know Iodine
I heard somebody babbling on about iodine
131 just the other day
And I guess it's much worse than I portrayed in the song
Of course you can't believe everything you see on the internet
Or hear on the radio
Or the television
You can't believe anything
Except what your buddies say on twitter
Yeah 3x
You can't believe that
It has to pass your three levels of jawbone
Okay anyway
We have to go Dave
It's the end of the show
I'm going to fade you out and play your music
Why don't I just go ahead and play the music now?
I'm going to do a soft stroke
My metabolism mom just sitting here
Yeah I know what you're going to do
You do not
Yeah
Continue
Well I said Chernobyl was so long ago
Nothing to worry about
And now I hear in the news
These dumb guys in the Department of Energy
And the Defense Department
Are going to start building a bunch of Chernobyl's
Across the United States
And then I hear on the news that Chernobyl
Is really over now
All these people are dying
It's all the pollution is getting into the water
It's getting into the aquifers
Everything goes
It's all 121
The distance between Kiev and Cleveland
No man we're getting to
Drill Lake Erie
You know
And then I started thinking
How come my movements are getting so
Drill-y
The iodine
Has got my thyroid
On the run
And the Krypton
Is making it hard
Just to stay alive
But the iodine
The iodine
No more running to the metal planes
No more boiling the mud
Power powers in the power scene
Shake the bony hand
Smash the battlefield
And pull the trigger
The iodine
No more running to the metal planes
No more blowing the mud
No more barefoot in the mud.
Shake the bony hand of the poison man.
Shake the bony hand of Jacob.
Evacuate.
So there's over 2 million known pollutants.
That can cause cancer.
Pancreatitis.
Bad disease.
Bad breathing.
Gingeritis.
Bad breath.
Acne.
What's the use?
The iodine.
A 1, 3, 1.
Has got my thyroid on the run.
And the krypton.
A 8, 8, 5.
Is making it hard just to stay alive.
But the iodine.
A 1, 3, 1.
The iodine.
No more running through the metal lanes.
No more barefoot in the mud.
Shake the bony hand of the poison man.
Shake the bony hand of Jacob.
No more running through the metal lanes.
No more barefoot in the mud.
Shake the bony hand of the poison man.
Shake the bony hand of Jacob.
Shake it!
Shake the bony hand of the poison man.
Oh, almost forgot.
Friends, that background music we were playing while Dave and I were on the air on the phone,
that was Cyber Chump, which is a band of, I think, just two or three folks that is associated also with exposed foreheads.
Cyber Chump, the construction of things, was the name of that particular album.
Thank you.