What is God good for?
Call now and I'll rush you a free tape.
That's what we can count on God for.
A free tape.
No. No.
Yes. He did it.
God is a content
By which we measure
Our
Pain
I'll say it again
God is a content
By which we measure
Our
Pain
Yeah
I don't believe in magic
I don't believe in I Ching
I don't believe in Bible
I don't believe in talent
I don't believe in Hitler
I don't believe in Jesus
I don't believe in Kennedy
I don't believe in brother
I don't believe in mantra
I don't believe in Geeta
I don't believe in yoga
I don't believe in kings
I don't believe in Elvis
I don't believe in Zimmerman
I don't believe in Beatles
I just believe in me
You're the one for me
That's reality
The dream is over
What can I say?
Yesterday
I was the dream we found
Now I'm not born
I'm not born
I was the walrus
But now I'm John
And so, dear friends
We'll just have to carry on
The dream is over
But, dear friends
Somebody else is just starting up
Fuck!
I know who it is!
I know who it is that doesn't belong among us!
I swear, I know who it is!
It's...
The Self Genius Hour of Swag
Oh, that's not true!
S is for the suckers that live all around
U is for us, they're always putting us down
B is for Bob, he gives us our bread
G is for the guns they put to your head
E is for the eunuchs they want you to become
N is for the knots they wish they had some
I is for that eye in the back of my head
U is for you, they wanna see you dead
S is for the shit that's all around
I'm a subterraneous motherfucker
And I ain't no fucking clown
In order to rule the world
You must first conquer it
Only on those bold terms
Can this world be a place for you to be
This total war
Result in total victory
The End
Well, don't you think it's a little late?
No
Well, I do
The End
I don't give a damn
Dead center
Yes, liberty reigns
I can't stand things that frighten me
That don't make any sense
Come on, let's get out of my brain
Yes, sir
The right brain that was actually originated for people who were tired of pointing salt
The heliopter Jesus was originated for your right brain
That's true
He's in a little can and we open him every 45 minutes
Now he's just squeaking
Be scary, Colin
Stand back, stand back
Okay, I was steering the ship toward the left
And you won't be able to
Now look out the window
See little people there?
See them?
No, stop
They're actually not people
They're a bad genius
I am there to scare you
I'm so scared
They're in the human scrap yard
Please, if you're coughing all over your speakers
You're saying we've gotta clean it up here at the station
Yes, sir
It is true there is a thing here I do not understand
There is a pain between my ears
For those who don't understand
Perhaps they're always on the short poopy end of the stick
Yes, the short poopy end of the stick
There's a lot of short doggy poop around to put on the stick
But if you want to live like a real man or woman
You must, you must, you must
It is
Later than you think
It's later than you think
It's more late than you think
As chimpanzees are to humans, humans are to us
You're a proving jack
You just can't seem to get rid of that streak of honesty in you
The one that ruined you was that damned Indian, old Titi
You mean Olasky
He gave you a vision of moral order in the universe
And there isn't any
Those stars twinkle in a void, dear boy
And the two-legged creature schemes and dreams beneath them all in vain
All in vain, Jack
Did you hear anything?
Listen to me
Two-legged creature won't believe anything
And the more preposterous the better
Whales speak French at the bottom of the sea
The horses of Arabia have silver wings
Pygmies mate with elephants in darkest Africa
I have sold all those propositions
Fool, fool, fool, fool
And they were all fools and none of them matters
Ah
guitar solo
I watched a world from an alien place
From a desert plain that's so far away
I hear the sound of a starlit night
Of an angel's song in a big and light
Your world of people has no place for me
I've read the plea from an insane king
Your world of people suffocates me
It prisons me, it drowns me in ice
I watched a world from an alien place
From the tides of time and the shores of space
I stumble onward in a fevered dream
In a landscape of light, she gave a silent scream
Your world of people has no place for me
I've read the plea from an insane king
Awaken world, oh little man
Of hatred, deeds, and evil eyes
I'm the responsibility I make
Why are you alert for the
amidst a cold brawl
Bring your snow
I watch the world from an alien place
From a desert plain until far away
I hear the sound of a starlit night
Of an angel's song and a billion lights
Your world of people has no place for me
I'll forever flee from it, it's St. King
A wicked world, a little man
Of hateful deeds and evil ends
I'll forever flee from it, it's St. King
A wicked world, a little man
Of hateful deeds and evil ends
Your world of people has no place for me
I'll forever flee from it, it's St. King
A wicked world, a little man
Of hateful deeds and evil ends
Your world of people has no place for me
I'll forever flee from it, it's St. King
A wicked world, a billion lights
Your world of people has no place for me
I'll forever flee from it, it's St. King
A wicked world, a billion lights
Your world of people has no place for me
I'm a dish Śrīüs in this視ri,
Only to appear here
Is this hellishHH
My peoples, no one left to live
As you killed the יכולied
As you killed the helfallen
Once in your free will
2013, sinners have taken the matter into their own hands, but remember, God holds the final trump card.
The judgment. Revelation 20, verses 11 to 15. 10. Mercy killers are also on the ascendancy in America.
They are progressive abortions who have become hard to killing and now wish to include the mommies
and daddies along with the babies. Why were my father and mother bitten? God's command is Exodus
2012. Interference. Responsibility is so great. These words must be related.
You be the judge. You be the judge. You be the judge. You be the judge.
So, there you go. That's like,
doctors watching you right now.
What does this mean? Here, wait. You gotta put your headphones on, Dave.
That one.
No, Warden, it's not in my booty.
What the hell is that?
You be the judge.
No, Warden.
But, no! Warden be the judge someday!
You be the judge. You be the judge.
You be the judge today!
But, no!
You be the judge tomorrow!
Compulsory death for all at age...
Compulsory death for all.
That's why the kids...
Oh, no!
Oh, God!
The problem with them TV preachers...
That's the problem with using your teeth for the needle on the turntable, man.
What makes people think they can flunk God's rules and end up in eternal bliss?
Flunk God's rules?
What makes people think they can do that, Dave?
I don't know. Flunking is easy.
But flapping is hard.
But who do we think we are?
Who do we think we are?
I got away with it so far.
I got away with it because Bob gave me something to get me off.
I got away with it.
Bob got me off!
And I got away with it.
I got away with dogs.
I got away with old ladies.
I got away with barbers with one eye.
I got away with three people's hands.
I got away with men who think they're Jesus Christ.
Then, our brazen disregard...
Of God's laws will be judged.
of God's laws will be judged.
Our dogs, usurperors,
our dogs, usurperors,
Dogmongers and G весьers was agar away with dogs.
The day of the Lord is at hand.
He shall come like a thief in the night,
or He shall come somewhere another.
The Lord cometh and the Lord goeth and the Lord goeth.
Come unto me, bud!
This here's your sugar daddy
From his catty
In the ever-loving great beyond
So prick your ears up
And be quick-lipped to respond
Cause daddy ain't too happy
None too happy
What did I ever create you for?
You are the one
You ain't done nothing
But make your daddy sore
It looks like evolution's no solution
You just keep falling ever further behind
You may be tanned and clean-shaven
But ain't with little bit of hair it's high
Figured out how to make you feel
Hair is situation
Every nation
About to break your daddy to his knees
I just keep crying
These people bleed
You damn dirty apes
What the hell
Are you doing?
You damn dirty apes
Look at what you have done
Who do you think you have been fooling?
Cause I'm gonna catch you
Gonna catch you
Every one of you
Too cute to reveal
Hyperspace
To speak
Or the bones
To keep you alive
I'm just a star
Behind theED
But even better
You're safe and sound
Time to race
You're a dung sold
By us
It's a world
And flip it
Thank you
See ya
Earthquakes, floods and lightning
Very frightening
Oh, but that's just a little nervous twitch
But I'll be getting medieval
If you can treat me like your bitch
So get yourself together
Now or never
All you need's a little self-esteem
To turn this nightmare
Into a sweet, sweet dream
You damn dirty ape
What the hell are you doing?
Look at what you have done
You damn dirty ape
Who do you think you have been playing?
Cause I'm gonna get you
Gonna get you every one
I'm gonna get you
Get you every one
I'm gonna get you every one
A song from God
Called Damn Dirty Apes
By Drexel
Yes, that's a D-R-E-X-E-L
Drexel
From Drexel, Ohio
That's the album name
And they are at this website
www.drexel.com
That's D-R-E-X-E-L-L-E-N-T
And now back to, um,
Well, some Lemur-ish
Cut-up collages
Hustling evidences
Howling over men
Lonesome cowboys
And Chaz right here
This is the night of the whole world
So there's been all this talk on
And science
Let's talk science for a minute
Well, can I ask you one question?
Kind of a scientific question
What?
Is it true that you've heard
That there is a dangerous sorcerer
Or a demon, perhaps,
That speaks from Dick Cheney's navel?
Really?
I don't think that's scientific
Well, I don't think it is either
I think it sounds like superstition
So it couldn't possibly be true
It has nothing to do with it
That sounds like an urban legend to me
Oh, yeah, that's not science
That's pseudoscience
That's false science
Okay
But now, uh, we're going to talk about
Scientists are pretty convinced that
We're talking all about this lately
The day of the Lord is at hand
They're pretty convinced that, um
That we need to deprovincialize ourselves
One step further
And we thought that this universe
Was the only one
And it turns out that
They're pretty convinced that there's
Just multitudes of varied universes
All existing
They're real convinced of that, huh?
Well, if dogs can have multiple orgasms
Mathematically
Why can't we have multiple universes?
So if you've seen
You haven't done the math with your slide rule
And your calculations
No, but I'm open to whatever
You know, people come up with
Just as valid as anything I come
That might as well be
Come across anywhere else
Well, yeah, and you know as well as I do
That for all you know
All that math that they keep talking about
It's not real math
It might as well be the same as the totem pole
That some medicine man tells everybody to worship
Maybe, but it's the best bet we got
Well, it's
I mean, it's led us farther than any of those other things have
It's more like a meta
It took us to the moon
We have probes
We have going all over the universe
What telephone poles have taken us to the moon, Larry?
I've been to the moon
Not on a telephone pole
Not the way you're talking about
Yeah
And I don't see no weird like eagles or thunderbirds
On top of any ladder of numbers
We're building a space station that got, you know
Science, you know, we understand a lot about a lot of things
DNA
Well, Hitler almost built a science station with the world of fire and ice
So it's gotten us a lot farther than all the other, you know
Religions
But Hitler built, almost built science with fire and ice
We've actually gotten things done
Science is the most exacting religion
They don't know what I'm talking about
No
The theory of fire and ice
Hitler's theory of science was totally whacked out
And yet he produced all this weird
Well, he didn't produce anything
Well, they had the best Nazi flying saucers in the whole hollow earth
Well, they believed in all this anti-grav stuff
But, you know, it didn't have
And they came out with that movie
Ilse, She-Wolf of the SS
Well, that was pure science right there
They work for the CIA now
Who does?
Where are all those Nazi sonnets, dude?
No, they're on their night
I think they're too old unless they're taking Islan
Islan?
Islan
Your island paradise on the moon
Attended to your every wish by a Nazi scientist from the year Zip
Here's Klaus Friedrich, an early inventor of U2
Preparing to offer you a jelly donut
And here's you spending over log in the hot sun
As Ilse, the She-Wolf of the SS
Hands you her slide roll
What?
We'll make you his jelly donut
And he has to
In a country where freedom of religion is guaranteed by the constitution
Anything is likely to develop
Enter the church of the subgenius
Filling itself as the weirdest cult on earth
What do they believe in?
Everything
Who do they believe in?
The world
Oh yes good enjoy TV
Oh yeah
Hey!
You should just be selling all these наших
Eh...
Nevermind
What do your unos excited as fuck?
What have you got to say aboututo?
slack to planet earth and to you young man and to you if you will send a dollar
for more with this is a church that does not play games and join the church of the subgenius
genetic engineers working in secret laboratories in
are now able to create an onion that will not make mr and mrs he doesn't even have a body his
little head yea verily for bob should be praised he is being praised this is how we praise bob
this is how we polish this is the way we worship our bob we take care of bob
like we worship our bob
no one else repeat after me no you repeat after me bob is ice bob is nice light
you know just saying it doesn't make it so bob is not nice yea verily yea verily i know if bob's
looking in the window are you the servant that opens it so he can piss no more onions will no
longer provoke i only know about it because if i had to seek out the magic towel that night
for bob has arisen
well you shouldn't have been able to continue again and again and again and again
it makes me want to go to grand view camping center and watch kill them sitting there bob is always up
he's always up
always up dude
he never has to seek out the adult catalogs that other subgeniuses do
and you must receive slack in bob
those subgeniuses too cheap to get on their own computer must seek out
now you be nice to your little phone people
tiny little catalog
or twenty and getting separated from you
not just here except pocket
the Smith part was a great
and cut-throat
have submitted eighth fourth twenty opt for project oh i'll be right back in a moment
the song Mysterious Character Named Bob by the great DK Jones,
and now Half Man, Half Biscuit.
Seriously, the following is a song by Half Man, Half Biscuit
called 99% of Gargoyles Look Like Bob.
Jesus Christ, come on down!
Have you ever wondered
How you get up
To get triangles from a cow you need
But a milk and cheese
And an equilateral chainsaw
In debt I owe someone a fiver
Maybe I should try my hand at slag
James Dean was just
A careless driver
And Marilyn Monroe was just
A drag
99% of Gargoyles
Look like Bob Tart
Mary had a little lamb
The doctors were astounded
Everywhere she went
Gynecologists surrounded
The doctors were astounded
with a
They've been cooking on Blue Peter now
They're sampling the dishes
I don't normally like tomatoes, John
But this is delicious
99% of Gargoyles Look Like Bob Tart
99% of gardeners look like Bob Jaws
Take me home
The son of Jimmy Clitherow is shouting out
Where's my Ferrucci?
Yeah
Well, they've come a room and spread
But they didn't tell the bread
Did you honestly think that they would?
And if they tell the bread
They'll take ten cats or prefer whiskers
To the other two prefer Leslie Jones
99% of gardeners look like Bob Jaws
Don't tell me you're the future
You'll be lucky to catch on at the phone company
Your parents up there, you know what I'm talking about
20, 25 years ago they were telling us
You are the future
You kids want to see the future?
Look at your folks
Fat butts, saggy tits, fear, television
That's the future
Look at me, I'm supposed to be a big success
I built taco stands for a living
What kind of bullshit future is that?
You got any sense?
Give them back their damn diplomas
Give them back their silly fucking hats
And stay 18 for the rest of your life
You don't want to be the future
No, no
Forget the future
The future sucks
There he was
Big as life
Right there at the foot of my bed
Jesus
Hmm?
Jesus?
And he looked me straight in the eye
And he said
What on it?
Wanda Jean
There's more to love than just fornicating
Ha ha ha, sure
That's like eyes in the back of your head
Yeah
Even the purest research
These mud-gobbling giant worms
Which live on the edge of volcanic vents
Gorging themselves on massive huge piles of mud
Just like those tremor worms
Just like the ones in Dune
Only this mud is wet
Biologists frequently choose the tiny worm
Not like the kind of mud we used to have back when we were kids
It was dry mud
We used to have to make mud pies
And to make them stick together
We had to spit on them
We'd like have dirt in one hand
And a big pile of spit in the other hand
And we'd like roll them together
Until we had us a good mud pie
And that was the only thing we had for moisture back in those days
Just spit
We didn't have candy back then either
We had to just take a bag of sugar
And carry it around a big old five-pack of sugar
We had to carry around a big pound bag of sugar
In our back pocket
A big old tablespoon
And when we needed some candy
We just stuck it into the bag
And it took about four or five big tablespoons
Shoveled it down
And that was all we had for candy back in those days
Each one genetically engineered to make a difference
Now when a worm dines on one of these babies
You gotta have
Those worms have to have lamps
To see underground when they're eating through the dirt like that
For about one thousand miles per hour
They carry little like little miners helmets that let them mine through the dirt.
They're chewing, chewing, chewing, chewing.
Chomp, chomp, chomp, chomp, chomp, chomp, chomp, chomp, chomp, chomp.
They chew away, chew away, chew away, chew away, chew away.
Oh, I can't see where I'm going, said Mr. Worm.
And he looked ahead and he had his little pointed yellow helmet on,
shining the way into the back of the goose, as it were.
Where the end of the goose is flying.
They thought it was a reptile, but actually it was a bird.
It was a bird.
They found that it was only a simple bird.
It was a bird-like reptile bird.
It was only the size of a goose.
And yet its wings were 900 feet wide at their widest proportion.
27 feet, or 30 actually.
Where's Bozo?
Larger specimens recently discovered.
What the hell?
It's the Twinkie Bike.
What a wonderful, wonderful Twinkie Bike.
And so the Twinkie Bike headed out into the desert, carrying the little show people.
They asked me about...
Twinkie Bike, Twinkie Bike.
They asked me about Twinkies on my show.
And they asked what the ingredients were.
Of course, all I could tell them was...
That's when I got fillies!
Golden sponge cake and creamy fillings.
That's all you need to know.
You don't need to know anything more than...
That is all on Earth you know and all you need.
And we'll enter that in the computer.
That's good enough for Thor.
That's good enough for me.
The United States of Sponge.
Creamy soft whipped cream.
Yes, little caller, you have won the United States of Sponge.
...going everywhere in the valley.
As we continue to look for your requested songs, squeezing these up in four.
...from within the confines of its donut-like home.
Is it a bird?
No!
Is it a plane?
Oh my gosh, it's mighty mild.
No way I'll hide.
No way I'll wait all the while.
Is it a bird?
No!
Is it a plane?
Oh my gosh, it's mighty mild.
No way I'll fly out of town.
Yeah!
It's açe madam, it's a plane!
It's a flying bird, whatever your tailゆ.
Step out.
It's clickba-kling-ling...
You know it'll cut my nose.
Yes, 900 miles an hour, people!
This is examiny services, you never say to me,
ё round dogs are probably believed to be a process of wagging.
Godneagit government of humanity!
Actually, I have danger!
You should get out now.
Oh no, please!
Hey, Boggs!
I have a special report on the camps to make to the Ministry of Education.
For the children.
Tally-tally!
You get 152 hits.
It may sound silly to you, but...
Something bothering you, boy?
Nuclear death.
Oh, God!
Oh, okay.
When I take it this place, this Mabel Street, is not unique by no means.
While we were in Italy, this woman walked up to my friend and threw my friend a baby.
And, uh...
My friend caught the woman's baby.
Her other kids ran up and took what was in my friend's pockets.
So, um...
Let that be a tip for you, you know, if you're ever in Italy and, uh...
Someone throws you a baby, swat it to the ground.
Swat it to the ground and scream,
I don't think so!
I'm just trying to take a bite out of crime.
The Lord took...
Took the child.
He died a heartless death.
A horrible death.
The awfulness of it...
Staggers the imagination.
We're going to be using this corpse for a demonstration of placement.
And she looked at me and said...
She's a stupid.
I said, what do you mean?
She said...
She...
She's a stupid.
No, Sid.
I said, I went out of my mind.
And she looked at me and said...
I went to save the others.
And she said...
You don't have to be afraid of him.
That's all there is to it.
Rew, rew.
Ah!
Now I can't take it anymore!
Friends, are you going to let this happen?
Are you just going to sit by and watch this go?
This corpse rot?
Are you going to scrub its buttocks with a dog brush?
Or are you going to get down and apply mouth-to-mouth resuscitation to this rotting corpse in his
WCSV?
With your lips?
Which do you want?
Prefer?
Don't you want to get down there and apply the kiss of life?
Things will all be going our ways.
You guys are worthless.
I know we are.
Get out of here.
Don't you want to...
Get out of my radio station.
Let's go.
I'm going home.
Man, we cannot get one lousy carnivusion.
My friends, I was in the spirit and Bob said to me, he said, I'm going to have to call
you home, Reverend Stangen.
I don't think he meant home to Texas.
How about?
I think he meant home to heaven.
A beautiful home away from home.
If he says because it's the only way to send a signal to these people because they don't
seem to believe.
Look it.
There's the gates.
You can travel there on a signal.
I'm being called home, friends.
A beam of light.
Bob's calling me up.
Now I see the rocking chair of eternal slack up there on that beautiful cloud.
Oh, yes.
Why, look.
There's Bob.
Oh, yes.
There's beautiful creatures of the desired sex gyrating around the heavenly excrementation
throne.
And then just when you're in the gate, you thought you were in the gate in the heaven.
You made the ultimate mistake.
You didn't call 68769.
Oh, you could have.
That's the funny thing about it.
You could have.
At any minute.
Even after the show.
Oh, if he only would have sent his contribution.
You could have.
He could have had a coffee mug.
A beautiful logo shirt on.
Maybe he was a new twinter.
But you blew it.
You fool.
Man, you totally blew it.
God, I can't believe what a geek.
How could anybody totally, totally, totally, utterly, utterly.
Well, all I remember was he had a chance to get one of those warm sweatshirts on.
You were told.
Don't.
Don't do that.
You blew it.
Don't mess up.
And you messed up.
Cause you didn't call 6900 in the 216 area code.
Oh, man.
Did you blow it, dude?
So that sweatshirt, no, no, you didn't get that, either.
Well, you know, and that 6900 is the number itself you will get.
If you're not having sex and you don't have anybody loving you lately, if you just call
that number 6900.
6900.
The S gets to 6900
because it's like,
that's it.
It's synergy.
You know.
69,
it means belly rub.
Yeah,
69.
We each get something out of it.
You know what I mean?
Like,
it's an old,
oh,
there it is again.
Here they come again.
There they go.
They never come around for long.
Touch you.
We want to rub
your little round belly,
listener.
We want to reach out
with our fingers
over these hair waves.
We want to reach out
with our fist
and bust you in the face
if you don't call.
We're going to fist you,
my dear friend.
We're going to fist you
right in the face.
I can smell your feet
from all the way
across the escheleta.
Vino,
vi-vi-vino.
Yes,
I believe that Jesus Christ
is a succulent,
delicious,
flavorful,
juicy,
tender
son of God,
the Messiah.
And I'll tell you what,
because I was that desperate.
And this other male,
he's being stimulated
by the mating activity
and he wants to have a go too.
Oh,
that's so sweet.
And everybody knows that.
Arusha Control speaking.
Go ahead.
We have a rhino.
Anything else?
He's bleeding pretty badly.
No, that's all.
I saw these guys
in a roller rink.
I saw the,
who is this now,
the Fletchland Angels?
It's,
um,
Dick Clark.
Yeah,
Andy in the Warhols.
I saw the plastic
exploding bananas
at a roller rink
in Columbus,
Ohio,
when I was a sparse lad
of nearly 58 years old.
I had,
I was wearing chicken shoes
at the time
and Nico noticed me
in the front row.
She waved
and threw some
barbiturates to me.
She also rubbed
that hefty groin of hers
with a large
red Italian scarf.
I wonder what that meant.
Do you think it could
mean anything?
No, right.
Stop trying to see,
you know,
deep, hidden meanings
in everything.
In what she does
and everything, I guess.
Anything.
I guess I should stop.
There is no reality.
No, I guess there is no,
I thought you were going
to say all reality
is interpretive,
but you said
there is no reality.
No, everything's relative.
Right, we're not talking
about Homeland Security
or the black holes
that could envelop us
in a hundred billion years.
Who even knows
which universe we're in
at any given moment?
Right, right.
I mean, that, you know, right.
You know, you're here,
you're there, you know.
Speak for yourself, man.
I've been stuck
in the same one
this whole time.
Yeah, talk about strange.
I'm pretty sure of it.
Except for that one time
when alternate universe man
did his trick
just to prove he could do it.
Attention!
Our next witness is Paul.
Oh.
R-O-T-S.
Thank you.
Clueless.
We look forward
to your testimony, Mr. Mellor.
Today's hearing is important
to the office furniture industry
for four reasons.
Scram, dribble butt!
Mr. Chairman,
let me conclude by saying
thank you.
You took a leave of absence
with three children
and a wife and a girlfriend
on the side.
Bless his little heart.
How did you afford
a leave of absence?
Pretty drunk.
Thank you, Mr. Donald DeRossi,
who was established in 1927.
Uh, uh, thank you.
Come on back in your home!
And so there they are.
Oh, no!
Oh, no.
Mr. Chairman,
let me conclude by saying
Teletubby!
Oh, no, please.
Eyes burning like coals.
The blood,
bloodsucker
of Betsy Moore.
Holy catfish.
That's awful.
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh.
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh.
Well, uh,
where would my dad
get rid of a body?
Ha, ha, ha.
There's just one little thing
you're forgetting, college boy.
You buried him, too.
Hey!
It was money.
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
How are you doing on time?
I will wrap up very quickly.
Thank you.
The purple dinosaur
who has been called everything
from refreshingly sweet
to nauseatingly nerdy.
Well, once again,
rule toddler TV.
Menacing the Teletubbies.
I believe that the Teletubbies are,
their time is on this.
They're definitely...
Never seen them, actually.
Their days are numbered.
They may as well put a fork in the Teletubbies
once Barney hits the scene again.
Did you see this subgenius hooded robe?
Subgenius hooded robe?
Clearly made to intimidate and impress,
and I'm guessing it dates 1980,
maybe the beginning.
What's its origin?
The best item of its kind I've ever encountered.
Unfortunately, we have no information
identifying the subgenius.
Robe is of excellent quality,
in thin black wool,
58 inches long from the neck,
nine-button front.
Buttons are silver-colored,
permanently affixed to the neck,
is a 14-inch tall hood,
which comes to a point at the top rear
and then goes 10 inches forward to its front,
which falls the face mask with...
Wow.
One size fits all, huh?
For the men that want something extra,
which would be at the top of the forehead,
it's not available in stores.
Two-and-a-half-inch by two-and-three-quarter-inch
embroidered Dobbs face.
This is not amazingly boring stuff.
This is the real thing.
No, this is amazing.
Has wavy white embroidered edge.
Yeah, this thing on the back
has a 12-inch high red inverted pipe.
Does it have the flap?
It has a flap in the back.
How much does it cost?
That's the important thing.
How much are they charging?
It's $475.
Does it have the pyroflatulation flap in the back?
But it may be so aged that it would fall apart.
It sounds like it's actually real.
Because if you didn't have that flap
and it cost $475,
you could risk actually igniting it
if you weren't careful.
It's a mysterious, subterraneous robe.
Yeah, from some secret society or order.
Look at it, this piece of hood.
With a skull and crossbones.
I don't believe me,
because he thinks they're light.
I like him, but when the UFOs come,
the ladies are going to kill everybody but me.
Well, you know, of course they'll spare the righteous.
That's what all subgeniuses think.
I'm helping channel the thoughts of all subgeniuses
onto the show.
That means no one will be spared.
And no one will call.
They don't need to go to Brushwood.
The saucers will come and pick them up
wherever they are.
They'll be instantly materialized.
It'll be like a rapture
of subgenii.
Yes, thank you.
Right now, we're looking at a picture
of all the subgenii sitting in their
pretend first-class seats on the space shuttles,
ready to leave.
Mysterious and threatening secret clan
or society.
I was just telling you, it's a subgenius robe
from the early 70s.
Well, it certainly looks like a terrifying,
intimidating robe.
It does, it does.
That's back when they used to paddle the pledges
and all that stuff.
Yeah, we used to make them run the gauntlet.
The bobbies?
The famous naked woman gauntlet
we used to run them through.
They hated that.
Those bobbies, they always hate stuff
because they're nerds.
And they're so competitive among themselves.
That's what's so pathetic about it.
Just because the average weight of each of those women
was well beyond 300 pounds,
that shouldn't have any effect on it
if they were, you know.
Or where Philo has worked for a million years.
Thinkers.
Thinkers from beyond the sun.
The competitive world.
On the backside of reality.
A little conspiracy biz.
A little boil on reality.
Fantasies that boil up in a drenched sunburst
of fun and relaxation.
Rest and relaxation at last.
I don't feel relaxed.
This show makes me all tense and itchy.
From rest and sleep.
Witch.
Yeah, you can earn money even while you sleep
with our custom sexual cyber brain.
from the must-have turnkey operation website
and sooner our best men
you will be on the cutting edge when you process their credit cards with sixty
percent fulfillment
startup with only ten dollars
you must be two hundred years twenty one years old
laws and desperate
for the space and what for us and what we negotiating for
means that a good deal that we want to know
yeah i want to know return a second-guessing negotiating team problems
that i just want to know if it's worth the trouble i'm going to i don't waste
my time if all we're gonna get out of it is a few pictures of space or something
okay okay i'll tell you
right this time
all life on earth is going to be dead in five years
skip over the other side
right this time
what's this
this is what they want to say that
all the flowers
all the trees
all the birdies
told all the children
that's it
yet dedicated as we are bob
you know they have no incentives no motivation
what's this
survival map to show us where we're gonna pick them up
uh... better not lose it
i'd say bob
all things
uh...
in think
l Olympic
the
car
ho
the
police
where
that
long
didn't
you
i shell
is quite a
to see what the size of my nose
has to do with the problem that we are facing now.
You can be like the queen on sex planners.
It makes you constantly comment
on its prodigious size.
I forget. You know, I never
did watch Star Trek, so I don't know all the different
characters. What is it about
my nose that constantly brings
great attention?
Blast you, spook. You know that your nose
is in front to all decent Earth men?
Weird. I'm picking up like...
That's what you keep telling me.
Are you out of your Vulcan mind, spook?
Oh, I get it.
He doesn't have a mind, right? Is that the joke?
A mind is a
terrible thing to waste.
When the baby is done drinking, it must
be unscrewed and laid in a cool place
under a tap.
This cheesy nut butter is the cause
of the alien's antagonism.
I'm sorry. I think I just sat on the racist
peanut butter cups.
You did that on purpose. I saw you.
Just so I could have them all.
Oh, he figured out my point.
All right, all right.
Yeah, yeah.
Look at that.
To boldly split infinitives
where no one has done that
before.
Voyage to see what's on the box.
Space. The final frontier.
And then a bunch of old crappy stars
pretending to go like this.
These are the voyages of the starship KPFA.
Its continuing mission
to boldly explore
space.
To split...
Smash up the entire...
Break everything.
The bottom is erupting.
The entire studio...
That's the monster that comes out and attacks the whole ship.
Oh, some monster, did they, Kirk?
What kind of ship is that?
Every week there's a Kirk out.
The ship pitches and rolls.
Everyone falls out of his seat.
Here's a harder one.
Oh!
Hard is right.
Oh, my seat!
Well, friends, Dr. Howell
and the...
show there on KPFA.
Before that, a clip sent by
the bishop.
And tons of Lemurian collage.
And remember, friends,
you can always check out
www.subgenius.com
or you can write to me
at
postofficebox181417
That's
181417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio.
44118.
I'm Reverend Ivan Stang.
And now, Christopher Hyatt
with the late
occult scholar
Israel Regardie.
The Guru Hymn.
This is a hymn
dedicated to the grinning,
giggling monkey guru.
Now, this
is bliss consciousness.
Now we have the roots
of the tree.
This is the trunk of the tree.
These are the branches of the tree
with the pretty leaves.
Now, in order to get bliss consciousness,
we must water the roots of the tree.
When the roots are watered,
the bliss rises up the trunk of the tree
into the branches of the tree,
into the leaves.
When this happens,
we have bliss consciousness.
Now, bliss consciousness is something
that your mother will approve of.
Unlike,
like sex and other said things,
this fits right on in with her.
She loves bliss consciousness.
Pig.
There is a happy land
far, far away
where little piggies grow
three times a day.
Oh, you should see them run
when they see the butcher come
to cut slices off their bum
three times a day.
Oh, man!
I wish they didn't L detection!
It was a Seb Bestz-in-isses
ash.
We love that!
Oh, there you are.
Oh, oh, oh.
What do you want?
I was wondering where you've been.
Living on Bob.
Bob Bob's Bob.