I don't get to be judged next to you.
And now you have all these anxieties, these burdens, right in front of you on these cushions.
And I am going to count to three.
And when I count to three, I would like you to visualize,
to see those plates filled with those anxieties and burdens being lifted up,
knowing that they are going to be lifted up
and that they are going to be taken care of by ourselves.
Cast off the straitjacket of hyper-normality.
All of you suffering slackless souls in the radio audience,
I want you to hear me now.
The conspiracy has tried to keep the healing powers of slack enhancement therapy away from you.
Oh, great goddess Aphrodite, sovereign ruler of love between man and woman, hear me.
Send your power into these two essences
and draw them into blissful conjunction.
So join.
His tasks of discipline involving four, four individual events.
The rolling of the chin noggin up the hill.
The misplacering of the egg.
The consumption of the terrible pride.
And the sleepening.
That was it.
We found it.
Come on.
The quieting agent.
Follow the yellow brick road, kids.
Are you ready to eat what's at Bob's table?
Well, he's ready to serve it to you, kid.
He's got a big long fork to shove it right in.
So open up.
Bend over.
Here comes Bob to dinner.
And what a sumptuous feast it is.
Planetary orgasms and millions and millions of cosmic drizzle
imported and imported.
And exported throughout the lands.
There's more than any sumptuous munchkin could eat in a lifetime.
What a grand new millennium it shall be.
But will Bob put on the tin man's hat and ram it up my bunghole?
He'll give you a brain, Chaz.
And he'll give Dave a unit.
A larger pair of breasts.
A larger unit.
And he'll give me a wallet.
A wallet.
A checkbook.
A bank account.
Full of money.
And he'll give Dave a tuner for his guitar.
I'd like a bag.
A tumor.
I'd like a bag of scabs and a tumor for my guitar.
Dave needs a brain tuner, Santa.
And a guitar tumor.
Well, we don't have any of those this year since the problems we had with 9-1-1.
I had to go to the doctor and get my brain tuner fixed.
Well, I don't think I've done a very good job for you, my friend.
Because look at the oozing near the sutures coming out of your head right there.
Yeah.
Don't stare at those, Dave.
That's not the life.
Yeah, but look.
You can put it on either bass mode.
See the switch back here behind my ear?
I can put it on either bass mode or guitar mode or anything I want.
Or chromatic or diatonic or anything.
Does that change with the way you hear?
Or does that change?
It just tunes my brain.
You can tune in to anything you want.
It's got this cool world mode patch.
So you can tune in to like other, you know, world modes and stuff too.
You know, those little half-step things.
Oh, I got some old fuzzbox.
You can do that, you know.
Or Hawaiian kind of stuff.
All that real sweet harmony stuff.
Man, all my brain tuner has is tone and volume.
Oh, you got to go online.
You can buy those.
You just buy them online.
You've never had a male.
It comes like two, three days later.
You never self-tuned yourself without a Polynesian woman until you, you know.
I'm sorry.
You know what I'm saying.
Yeah, I know.
But I've always just bought the, you know, the Echos and stuff from the man in the alley.
I just got them.
I just got done playing the soundtrack to Wizard of Oz while staring at the album cover art to Dark Side of the Moon.
And I think I had an experience.
Well, it looks beneath your stool that you probably did have something like an experience.
At least it produced an actual visceral fluid that we could measure with these little gadgets here.
Did little Dorothy and Sid Barrett do it?
That's a check the synchronicity meter.
Actually, I thought, I tried that experiment.
And I thought anybody who sees a heavy synchronicity.
Element in this ain't seen nothing.
Yes, but they all jump off the truck and sing the songs at the same time that everything gets bleak.
No, they got it wrong on the internet.
They got it wrong.
You don't, you're not supposed to watch the movie and listen to Dark Side of the Moon.
You're supposed to listen to the soundtrack to the movie and look at the album cover of Dark Side of the Moon.
Oh, no, no.
It's the Dark Side of Dorothy you must listen to while pondering the whizzy whiz of whiz bang.
Archie's leaving something out of the instructions.
Like the only way that that is cosmic is if you quit doing drugs for like a month.
Stang, look here.
They're all subject to change.
Each one of these are all subject to change.
You know, huh?
I just said all these rules you were talking about are all subject to change.
Again?
On five minutes notice here.
It looks like effective tomorrow the radiation belt is going to be a lot wider.
And you're going to have to slim down if you know what I'm saying.
And the desert of waz.
I guess a new creation of some of the assumptions.
Other landers is going to be discluded tomorrow night.
So there you go.
Another brain spasm.
No more desert of waz.
No, no, no more synchronicity.
It's all gone.
You mean the dot com heaven will collapse?
Everything means just what it means.
There is no synchronicity or overlap of truth.
You mean they won't click on the banners?
Sorry.
The banners are all unfurled now.
And we're lowering them.
Yeah, you just open the doors.
Into the ground.
Look, the doors are open for you, Stang.
Why, so this is the internet.
Everything's flying, flying through it.
And beckoning drawers.
The pigs have wings.
And files are flying out.
They can fly too.
Oh, the internet is so fancy.
Some of it's plain.
And three dimensional and colorful.
And it's so, I didn't have.
Oh, this is just amazing.
There's a little green man fondling a bear.
It's disgusting.
And what are these numbers running up in the corner?
Those are the Boolean numbers.
Grab one quick.
That's the bill.
Oh.
Good lord, man.
Those are the algebraic numbers.
And what are all these little windows opening up?
Oh, those are the commercials.
The ads, of course.
I forgot.
That's right.
Availability is now at this station.
The internet was controlled by the conspiracy back in the past.
Before the future came.
I am I.
The great and powerful.
Ah.
Don't leave me here.
Sure one of you
tempo was
right.
headaches can go on again.
Huh.
Bob was a robot.
Well, it's still no different.
It still not look strange.
Bob was black.
One of a gang.
Hey, hey, not going to work.
Bob was a regular just...
Ha, ha, ha, ha!
There he is.
I made a bargain with the cult to give me certain data that you had.
In return, I promised to prove the essential truth of the creed.
There was no need to prove that.
That it stands proven by the book of Revelations.
I offered scientific backing for you believers.
You made of the darkness and the stars a natural phenomenon
and removed all its real significance.
That was blasphemy.
The facts exist.
Your facts are a fraud and a delusion.
How do you know?
I know.
I suppose you think in trying to warn the world against the menace of madness,
we are placing souls in jeopardy, huh?
Well, we haven't succeeded.
If that makes you feel better.
Your devilish instruments must be destroyed.
Let me handle this.
Let her go, Bob.
After all, they're only human cattle.
You know that yourself.
My boy Bob!
My boy, my boy, my boy Bob!
I thought bringing the crowds all right.
What the hell was that?
Who makes the rules?
Someone else.
Great notch breakfast.
I didn't do it.
Can I still have my dog?
No.
Okay, I'll tell you what we're going to do.
We're going to cut you a 15 second at the beginning of the Super Bowl,
a 20 second afterwards.
We're going to cut you right in with the big BUD spots that we're pulling up.
Are we sending anyone for the new coverage of the Olympics?
Are we sending?
Yeah.
See if I can get on any, you know.
I don't have any coverage.
I don't know if I can send coverage of the Olympics or anything.
We're going to Utah.
It seems like a place that subgeniuses would go.
It seems like something reverent.
They're called Mormons, Chaz.
That's where the subgeniuses went.
Well, they have that like sex with multiple things.
My great-great-uncle Joe Smith.
Yeah.
Yeah, but look what happened to him.
The conspiracy clamped down, made him quit doing the multiple routine,
and now they're the pinkest religion in the country.
What about the spaz jump?
I heard Pastor Craig was still going for the spaz jump,
and also the inconsistency principle.
Those are no longer the Olympics.
The sodomy principle.
Oh, he's still doing the sodomy principle.
I thought that was bad.
The neck-raping principle.
Whatever happened to sexual acts utilizing the back of the neck?
Good old-fashioned back neck raping.
Whatever happened to the ladies and men?
Men big enough to have rolls in the back of their neck
that might be useful to a desperate, subgenius bonobo man like Dave here.
The slender Spanish lady with the very, very long song in the legs.
They're so long that when they bang Goya, paint the picture.
Well, you have to use another hole for that, Dave.
And Goya, he make the neck look so long that when you turn them upside down,
you're upside down in the bottom of it.
This isn't...
The...
Past anymore.
This is now the future.
Your future.
Welcome.
Come on in.
Or out, as the case may be.
Depending on whether you started out inside the dome or outside the dome.
Whichever it was, it's flip now.
It's what Bob called the big flip flop.
Remember those LP records?
You had to flip them over in cassette tape.
You had to flip them.
You had to flip them over.
Well, there's a time stream.
It's not digital.
It's analog.
You have to flip it over.
That flip is coming, friends.
The time stream intersection.
It's like a big figure eight.
Time is like a big figure eight.
It loops back upon itself where the big bang is the same as the big smush down.
Going in reverse and backwards.
Well, they come together in the center.
And that's where we're heading.
Top speed.
The center.
Right now.
We're heading for the center.
Now, Dr. Stubbs or Skang or whatever your name is.
How do you explain the consistencies in the Mayan calendar vis-a-vis the 2012 apocalypse
and also the heliocentric realignment?
Well, it's amazing that until now no one's been able to get it to work.
And that proves that the normals were not stupid people.
Subgenius is full with acetylene torches,
bottled oxygen,
electric arcs from generators and so forth,
electric furnaces,
all kinds of elaborate texts.
But what?
What did these brilliant normals use?
Jet fuel.
That's all, friends.
And that's why we have to catch up.
We have to build our own ships.
And failing that, our own Amsterdams and, well, friends,
failing that, we have to make the nicest little shoeboxes we can learn to hide in.
Between the walls.
Build your own spaceship.
My spaceship is equipped with this tiny, beautiful, blue mechanical dog
from the year 1927.
It's in a complete arrangement around everything else standing and sitting down.
Step one step inside and you'll notice not only the art deco changes,
but so do the rheumatoids in your head.
This little cardboard box here, well, it ain't much of a spaceship,
but it's better than nothing.
Hey, at least I'm not.
At least I own it.
At least it's mine.
These sheep back there on that cesspool are damn humans.
Yeah, that's right.
Look, look, look.
They're fake Tiffany.
They're fake mongering.
Vile little creatures.
They're by a pus-swell on the skin of that planet.
Yeah, them little pus-squells on the skin of that planet.
That's what they are.
Just like shit.
Yeah.
Is humanity then a cancer?
A carcinoma upon the skin of the earth?
Is civilization a terminal disease?
Is il papa a groovy dancer?
Or is it merely the inoculation against something far worse?
Is it actually then the key?
Or is it the lack of health?
Just a touch of civilization.
Or encroachment of some standardization throughout the land.
Just enough to keep the bit-civ away.
Yes, there's no broadcast delays in the spectrum of life.
When you get so civilized that you're...
The minds have all been disappeared.
You're like your...
Taken away.
PC.
I'm none of the baby.
That's how civilized you're gone.
You're faded off.
Faded.
Into logic.
Pure logic.
But what heart is there left, Brent?
Into the void.
That's what we worry about.
I told you to grab the Boolean numbers.
Yeah.
The preservation of heart and slack in this soulless, increasingly mechanistic...
Long may they be.
They drip off together.
You just transform into a truth table in some freshman college class down at the state university.
That's all you is.
Well, you can't believe in God anymore, so what else is there, friend?
It's all it's good for is sniffing them seeds after a rainy day.
There's still slack, ain't there?
Yes, plenty of it.
Smell that seed.
Ah, yes.
It's good to be in the education field.
That's right.
Deep, deep inside.
And then they open that 55-gallon drums of heads down at the dental school...
Oh, my God.
...and they're just right on top.
Look at the size of this guy.
That's the first one that they start practicing on.
Look at the cranial instep here.
Boy, oh, boy.
This guy's ready to go bowling.
They gave your head to the freshman.
They gave my body to the mortician school.
Oh, my God.
That's Grandpa Hobo's head.
And look at its arms.
They gave Chaz's body to the carnival to show off what can happen.
They gave my body to the Smithsonian Institution as an example of what never, never efforted.
I cut my head off.
And I stuck a bunch of pipe right in the middle of it.
I got a pipe right down my neck, and now I sit in a chair with my fingers going up and
down, up and down, up and down.
But we can still pipe this to you, friends.
We can pipe our thoughts to you, even though we're disembodied.
We can beat those thoughts down with little handles and backs.
We've been in a tank.
Sure, our bodies are in a tank or somewhere being experimented on.
Tiny little animals crying into your bodies, taking away your consciousness now.
But our souls are free, my friend.
You could be the same way.
Just lift off, baby.
Free as a dirge.
Inflate.
All you gotta do is chop your own head off.
Get on the old hobo train.
At just the right moment.
The moment of the time intersection.
Everything turns inside out.
You'll be the one that was first in line for brains that day instead of, well, you know.
You don't want to sell nothing at the crossroads.
You'll be the one that's first in line for looks on that day, rather than, well, what
happened.
I want to be the world's greatest opera singer.
You'll be first in line for looks.
And so I present this in a bag of staples.
Instead of where you ended up.
Unb aktivido con mifi traje.
fire a
pack of
couple hundred more yards and lay your eggs and croak.
At least this way you won't be leaving more miserable little losers to suffer like you did.
And be subject to the same mind control as the rest of them?
No, no way.
Let the strong and cruel.
A race like that would die in a moment.
The slightest flutter of wind would castrify and colossify it.
That's how we rose up from the chimpanzees.
We, the third order chimpanzees.
That's how we left that chimpanzee drive at 29.
We made it by being meaner than the other chimpanzees.
You know, friends, if you look at chimpanzees.
It took a long time of cowering, though, in the shadows of the hyenas and the lions and the tigers.
We were scared little monkeys for an awful long time.
We hid up in the trees.
They're big.
But then we came down from the tree and picked up a damn stick and beat the hell out of them.
Well, that's maybe what you did.
Our kind learned how to throw the weak to the saber-toothed tigers.
Oh, yeah.
Well, that's...
We just gang up on our own kind and throw the weirdos out to the...
Learn where they went out for drinks, learn their movements, their habits.
It did take a very long time of being...
We followed them around the mall.
We listened to their home phone and soon we mastered the jaguars.
Of being a what?
Of watching.
We had to watch for a while from our little perches up in the tree.
Cowering and watching.
We had to watch how they did it.
Until one time one of us had an idea.
A sneaky idea.
Push the other one out of the tree.
And while that...
Leopard is busy.
Run away!
Run!
And friends...
And we woke up just in time for the jaguar night 2012.
That's how the subgeniuses were born.
That's why there are so many Smiths today.
For that first Smith pushed that foolish Jonesman out of that tree.
I think it was the white man's way of saying he was uncreative and bland.
Speak for yourself.
Speak for yourself, Bob.
Moments of terror.
And how we relish them.
Grotesque images torn out of our own dark, our own earliest nightmares.
Try as we may, we are never quite able to leave them behind.
We grow up with a certain hunger not only for the bright things in life, but for things
that are fearful.
And terrifying.
Trying to escape from the giant tread of Bob as he approaches with his acts of employment.
Oh, yee, mirror to the head.
Roadworthy down under the head.
Yea, yee, mirrored nigh, not of the head.
We get to the bottom, back to the top of the slide.
Stop and turn around.
Couple more rides, and you'll get to the bottom.
And I'll see you again.
Yea, yea, yea.
Do you, don't you want me to love you?
Thumb down that mouth of you.
Tell me, tell me, tell me your answer.
You may be a lover, but you ain't no dancer.
Help me, help ya.
Thank you.
Uh, yes, dear friends.
Necrophile.
singing with the Necrotones.
And you can find out more about the Necrotones
at this website, www.lastbeatrecords.com.
That's www.lastbeatrecords.com.
Last Beat Records is one word.
Friends, this hour of Slack,
Slack 819,
is all half old and half all new,
being mostly last night's ESO Swamp Radio Show
from WCSB Cleveland,
with Professor Chaz, Lonesome Cowboy Dave,
and yours truly, Reverend Ivan Stang.
And this show is also half the old,
newly released Media Barrage 11,
Ancient Subgenius Tapes Resurrected for This Day.
Coming up, dear friends,
Dr. Leary lectures,
unreleased material from,
well, now it's released by Ace
at Rosencomet.com.
Also coming up, some music by St. Alio,
or Stalio,
and the ultimate rant
with Einstein Secret Orchestra
and myself at Starwood 2001,
and more, friends, but only if you pray,
it's Bob.
Dobbs.
It's all Dobbs stuff out here,
and if you want to talk to Dobbs,
that's all you're going to get to,
because, you know,
if you really have a problem, forget it.
And then you will get a ticket to Dobbstown,
and one of our special meditation chambers,
the little dog cages,
and you can get in and mail yourself to Dobbstown,
and the church will pay for it all,
and we will support you once you get there.
You'll be so happy.
See, here's what we'll be doing.
There are no dogs and no dog toys on the street.
In Dobbstown.
The showed sub-dini's.
There are no sheep.
Not the sick sub-dini's.
There are no hideous wolf-weathers.
They're hidden away from the congressional investigation.
And there's no collar any longer.
Lions and tigers and bears.
Oh my!
How about a round of applause for the person that represents the information era,
the man who taught us about relativity and multiple reality.
How about a round of applause for Albert Einstein, huh?
All right.
Thank you.
Anyway, I put the sperm on the board to kind of make fun of Charles Darwin
and the Darwinian theory of evolution, which is really well worth making fun of.
There's been a big scene about theories of evolution,
you know, the creationists versus Darwinians.
Any time that the press gives you a Super Bowl,
thing like that, you know, it's like,
it's like,
Cincinnati Bengals versus the San Francisco 49ers.
You know they're not telling the real truth.
The interesting thing about the Arkansas genetics trial,
I don't know if I follow this very carefully because it's like my, like my career.
But the most intelligent things that were said at that trial were not the civil liberties union proving that life
is a Darwinian plot of four billion years of male competition leading to bigger and better rape.
The most interesting thing said at that trial was by a man named,
Wickram Singh.
He's a Hindu geneticist, chemist.
Do any of you know him?
He wrote a book called Life Cloud with Hoyle, the astronomer.
And he came over and he was on the side of the creationists.
He said, well, I don't believe in this theory that, you know,
Jehovah made the world in four days, four thousand years ago.
But there is a creative intelligence that's designing evolution on this planet.
And it's not a blind chance.
He said to think that in four billion years you could create an incredibly intelligent species,
like ours, of Monday Night Football and Howard Cosell,
in four and a half billion years is impossible by chance.
He said that the Darwinian theory basically says that a tornado could fly through a junkyard
and assemble a 747.
That was a good headline.
But the creationists lost.
The reason they lost was because they were defending a theory of evolution
which is based upon the Judeo-Christian Bible.
I have a lot of fun. I go on radio programs, television programs.
And I say that the Bible is such a sick comic book
that I don't say any parent of a child would allow their children to read such a book.
In the first, second, third, fourth chapters of the Bible,
Jehovah, the God of the Bible, who is a bad-tempered, mean, macho, mafia, condominium owner,
he gets pissed off at some whim and he's mad at the whole human race.
And he snuffs the whole human race except for Noah, who is his resident manager or something.
So, I mean, people believe that.
Well, anyway, Jehovah, according to the Bible, said to Adam,
Well, it's the year 4000 B.R.
That's before Reagan.
And I'm going to send my only son, Ralph, down to blow the whole thing up
during the...
fourth budgetary planning session of the second Reagan administration.
But meanwhile, I've got this Garden of Eden.
And Adam is allowed to do whatever you want in it.
Eve 2.
He says there are...
two food and drug regulations.
There's this tree here. You're disallowed. It's a control substance.
You're forbidden by law to in any way ingest.
You know why? Because if you ingest this substance,
you will double your intelligence, see through good and evil, and become a god like me.
Do you want to become a god like me?
And Adam said, No, sir, I don't want to become a god like you.
And he said, There's another tree over here.
If you eat of this tree, this tree is the...
microgenetic immunology tree, which will give you immortality
and inoculation against death, and you'll live forever and be a god like me.
Do you want that? And Adam said, No.
And, of course, you're well aware of the fact that the Judeo-Christian Bible is very down on women.
They lay all the blame on Eve.
As soon as Jehovah jumped into his squad car,
and back to headquarters,
Eve went over to the intelligence-raising vegetable,
and she sniffed it, or ingested it,
and as a good friend to Adam, poor straight arrow Adam,
she got him to eat thereof,
and the first narcotics bust in history happens in the first page of Genesis.
Now,
I know you've all heard this before,
but I think it's one of my duties to repeat this story and repeat this story,
because the entire Christian religion is based upon original sin.
I was taught about original sin. You were taught about original sin.
What's this original sin?
The reason that the planet Earth is a terrible place.
The reason that there's so much suffering down here is because we all fucked up.
And what was the original fuck-up? What was the original sin?
Eating intelligently.
Legends raising fruit in the Garden of Eden.
No wonder, no wonder they raised so much trouble about dope.
When I was a Harvard, you know, researcher, this is going to be a snap.
There's simply no question that anyone who understands anything about how to use brain-activating drugs
and is operating with a clear mind with no desire to screw other people's minds up,
who's willing to put in time,
and patience, and sensitivity,
can help anyone wash their brains.
There's no longer any excuse for having a mind that you don't like,
or having a brain problem that you're dissatisfied with.
We know enough now, and we knew enough 20 years ago, how to wash brains.
We thought it was the most simple thing in the world.
Who wouldn't want to have this power?
Not only was it no big deal that we discovered it,
we looked back in the history books and found out that the first book of the Vedas,
the first Hindu texts, you know, about yoga,
self-development, individual development,
was based upon Soma, which was some sort of a brain-activating, brainwashing psychotropic.
So we're part of the longest tradition in history of people who stumbled on
and continually rediscover the fact that the human brain can be changed,
and the way to do it is to use the chemicals.
Now, listen, it is not my fault.
I had nothing to do with putting the opium receptors in the human nervous system.
The fact that you have a receptor in your brain and they're resistant for acid is not my problem.
Which is a crime.
Now I like French toast.
Get pow-pow power!
Wahoo! Wahoo!
And if I had it my way, I'd make them crunch.
Yeah!
And we're gonna give a hoot about Calog's Coco Crispies!
Now I like cinnamon rolls.
I can't give enough of that.
Now I like custard.
I've got to crunch on the grocery store!
Now I like coffee.
Now i like...
cornflakes and strawberries
now I like eggs
now I like milk
now I like alcohol
young man if you spill those new sugar
snacks you're fired
now I like green set
but if I had it my way
I'd make them crunch
that was delicious
I wonder what it was
I know what you're going to do, Aldrin.
You're going to get down here.
You're going to go down to that drum house.
Stand there and watch everybody.
Friend, you could just...
This could be the night.
This could be the night when you will go,
what the hell?
I don't care if I'm like a fool myself.
I don't care if my boss sees the news on Channel 10
and sees me dance around that bonfire
with a devil mask on.
I don't care if I have to have a pee test
when I get home.
Friend, you could just do that
and of course you could lose your job and really...
But you know Bob said,
repent, quit your job and slack off.
And that actually is not bad advice
because the absolute worst thing that ever happens is
you end up with a better paying job.
God damn it.
And friends, before I go any further
and say anything else that might distract
from the true message,
this is all that matters.
Not the word, Bob.
Not his intentions.
Not what you understand of Bob.
Just Bob.
And not the entirety of the personality of Bob Dobbs.
Just this face.
This face is all you really need.
Luckily, I haven't owned the trademark
on this particular image.
But friends, it's true.
Thank him.
Truly give it a chance.
You know, when you see a real subgenius like myself
or the subgeniuses who were here two weeks ago
waiting for the world to end the next day,
you think sometimes these people look like they're crazy.
Like they're maybe a little too into this.
Like, isn't it a joke?
Aren't they taking it like a little too far?
Isn't this like a one joke idea
that should have ended a long time ago?
Oh my God.
It's like Jonestown.
Well, not yet, friends.
We're still training him.
But when you doubt,
look at his face.
Just look at that face.
What is it?
It's a man.
A smiling man.
He happens to be smoking a pipe.
But mainly it's of other religions.
What do they have for symbols?
A death instrument.
An instrument of death.
Or some bizarre arcane symbol
that nobody can understand.
Our symbol is a smiling man.
A man with slack.
He happens to look like a man
who just sold you something.
Or has the grin, perhaps,
like the grin of a skull.
But yet at the same time, friends,
you know that he has slack.
And where did he get that slack?
He had to get it from somewhere.
That's your hint.
That's your proof that there is slack.
And you can have slack too.
I'm not going to tell you what it is.
Because, friends, it's different for every one of us.
And I can't tell you what it is for me
because you'd get embarrassed.
But, friends, I can tell you a real sad tale.
A tale of how I was born.
A tale of how I was raised.
How I became a subgenius.
As a happy ending, obviously.
But, and I'm sure a lot of people
can identify with this.
But, you know, what is the Church of the Subgenius, really?
It's a gathering of some weird-ass individuals.
People with a very quirky sense of humor.
A very developed sense of irony.
And a need for slack.
And a love of Bob.
An unquestioning love of Bob.
Now, you don't have to love Bob so much
that you become crazy.
Like a subgenius all the rest of your life.
You can do it just for tonight.
Just for tonight, my friend.
If you could be slack for one Saturday night,
you'd never want to be peak again.
But the peak man has held the slack man down.
The slack man and the slack woman
have been oppressed by the peak man.
And we must get our slackness back
by any means necessary.
Break Bob and hail Connie.
As long as it doesn't involve too much
work.
As long as we get our slack doing something.
You know, any of those things.
Oh, but friends,
there was a time when
I was a weird little kid.
I was a weird teenager.
But what made me weird was, uh,
it was more like what I was interested in
as opposed to what I wasn't interested in.
For some reason, growing up among those
rednecks in Fort Worth, Tennessee,
I didn't care about baseball.
I didn't care about cars as an eight year old kid.
I cared about two things.
Pretty little girls and big ugly monsters.
How many people here tonight are monster fans?
Raise your hand.
There's a lot of us started out as monster fans.
Because we sort of identified with the monster.
And how many of you here started falling in love
with people long before you were supposed to?
When you were too little to start getting crushes on people?
Not that many.
Well, see what I mean?
That is damn weird.
When you start wanting to, uh,
you know, um,
you know, get romantic with your fellow little kids.
And they think you're nuts.
Well, friends,
what about being a monster fan?
That's not a good way.
That's actually not a good way to get laid.
Especially when everybody else is only twelve years old, too.
And, uh,
but friends, there came a time
when my parents moved from Fort Worth to Dallas.
We moved from the little city to the big city.
And I thought, now's my chance.
These new kids in this new school,
they don't know that I don't care about football.
They don't know that I'm a, uh,
that I read science fiction books all the time.
They don't know that I, uh,
I'm a great sexual pervert
because I want to sleep with other little girls.
I was a little boy.
I don't want to sleep with other girls anymore.
I like to, you know,
I'm, I'm, you know what I'm saying.
You know what I'm saying.
It is hell being a weirdo in any culture.
It doesn't matter whether it's America,
Holland, or deep, darkest Africa.
It is hard to be a weirdo.
When I, when we moved to Dallas,
I thought, I'm gonna change.
I'm not gonna be a weirdo anymore.
I'm gonna be normal.
And friends, I did a terrible thing.
All through elementary school,
I had drawn comic books,
and little animated flippin' books.
And they were like horror comics and superhero comics.
They were full of violence and disappointment.
They were fun.
They were really cool.
But I wanted to be normal.
And when we moved to Dallas,
I threw my comic books away.
Not just Spider-Man number one.
Not just the first issue of Fantastic Four.
I threw away the ones I threw myself.
Friends, it didn't do any good.
It didn't do a damn bit of good.
I was still a weirdo.
I still didn't get laid until I was 19 or 20 years old.
And friends, give up.
Give up on ever trying to be normal.
When I gave up, then I got laid.
Then I started making money.
Then I got a good job.
Then I started working for myself.
Give up.
If the news is driving you crazy,
don't listen to the news.
If your friends are driving you crazy,
if your parents are driving you crazy,
move, man.
Move out.
Get away from it.
Change your scene.
It's scary at first,
but you'll find out everybody has to do it sooner or later.
Usually when they die.
You can do it before them.
And uh,
that's why I decided to run now,
because I'm out of fucking time.
Wait.
You got no jacket.
You fellas looking up at this.
by the way,
now the door's closed on all fours.
Out that door on all fours.
I know.
some Arizona favorites also go out the window first.
Yeah,
you karena colonizer?
Why GERMANY?
And because
The sun has yet to rise
I shake the wings and clear my head
Without my chocolate eyes
Round boots and round heels
Round all I see
Put the rest out on my middle fist
That's all I really need
I'm tired of being tired
Without my chocolate eyes
I shake the wings and clear my head
They'll never know, they'll never see
Before the hit, I'm gone
Stopping now
I'm in the dragon's dress
I sing the dragon's song
The rat and the fox think what I do
I do to keep them free
And no one knows my secret
No one knows I die for a reason
Now I'm in the fire
I'm in the fire
Night and day in silence
I'm in the What if you know
I'm with light
I'm in the sun
now I'm in the fire
What if you wanna punto
you are no more
fentanyl
Vape
Have you idal
It's in politics
the rest
I'm in the listen
la la
Unis
here
I think that was brilliant.
I think that was like, didn't Fred Sanford come up with that?
Before they killed him, that was the last, you don't think it was the IRS?
Who got Fred Sanford?
It was CID, an internal division.
Got him, and they put him on a skewer.
Right.
Remember that episode, Dave?
I thought you did the booking for that.
It was when Hendrix was on that show.
Oh, man, that episode will be in my can forever.
I'm never going to release that thing, as much as I'd like to evacuate it
and get it away from my body.
But that was one of the biggest pieces of art.
So how long before the show started?
Before which show? Before the Hendrix Sanford show?
I didn't take acid that time.
It was just like a pure stroke of luck.
It was not, you know, something I had to force.
Oh.
All right, well, carry on.
Well, you know, I'm just responding to what you said.
You know, what else should I do?
I don't know. I'm just here.
Sex, money, Bob!
Free pills!
Kill me!
Sex, money, Bob!
Bleeding head of Barney Palmer!
You may die!
Only a dollar for one of those?
One dollar for damnation!
He's dead forever, brain Bob!
Have your brains sucked out your nostrils!
Hear that sound? It sounds like a chainsaw!
Free false sex!
Church air, one soul per breath!
Have sex with anything!
Free pills!
Money, Bob, sex!
You can't go to hell without a pamphlet!
Bleeding head good!
Heal the head bad!
Hey, you smoking?
No, but the pipe is!
Experiment!
Has gone wrong!
Has gone to hell!
Experiment!
Hey, you smoking?
They've infiltrated the highest levels of the government!
They are the true satan!
Do you really believe they have your best intentions at heart?
The revolution begins immediately.
Immediately.
Take me, your leader.
It's all a joke.
Because we came from the leader.
You are my leader.
You shall be.
One of the snuffed.
If you think you are.
You shall be.
But there was a way out of this mess.
Fedcoms, the experiment.
Friends, you can...
Fedcoms has a great subgenius website
at this address,
digimind.tripod.com
That's digimind,
D-I-G-I-M-I-N-D
dot tripod dot com.
So friends,
this is Bob's world.
You can take your invisible devils of anti-slack
and throw it out the window.
Let's be careful with the poltergeists.
Let's be friends with everything violent and strange.
I just want to free the poltergeist,
my inner poltergeist, man.
Help me free my inner poltergeist,
free Bob's.
Isn't there something,
some kind of news,
something important we need to impart
at the last minute,
Dr. Smith?
And a 13-year-old girl's sex orifice.
Well, didn't something important happen
that we need to tell...
Everybody go look at www.
dot subdenius dot com right now
and look at all the pretty artwork.
It's got great artwork.
It'll be movies.
I think that the X-Day came behind your back,
sneak up on your sphincter muscle,
give you a little kiss in the wallet,
and that's it.
Well, it is true that here we are now in 2002.
Really?
And, you know, 2001 is now history,
in the history book.
No, that was the future, man.
Yes, I know how you feel.
I remember when I was in sixth grade,
what they said would be happening in 2001.
And, you know, jetpacks.
I've said this before.
Space spaghetti.
We got the Segway.
Spaceships going to Jupiter.
So it's not a jetpack.
We got the Segway.
So it's not Hell 9000.
We have a G4 Mac.
But 2001 was supposed to be remembered
for all this amazing technological wonders of humanity.
But 2001, what will it now be forever remembered for?
Cave-dwelling freak fanatics.
I'm sorry, Lord.
Flying a damn plane into the damn building,
killing all them people.
Oop, building fall down.
I'm sorry, humanity.
I'm afraid I can't do that.
And then get their country,
hopefully those in other lands,
as well as our own,
will think twice before they do cowardly acts
of terrorism upon our innocent subgeniuses
and even our pet humans.
Somehow, friends,
Can I get a job on that space shuttle?
I'm going to get out.
Can I?
Maybe I can get a job, like, at the North Pole or South Pole.
That might be far enough away from them all.
I've broken my water.
No, Chaz.
When the big fan hits it,
there is no place safe.
You can't hide from God.
You cannot sleep and pretend he go away.
As Jane or Hyperclete said,
you cannot run from your own legs
because they're what you're using.
You cannot dance your way out of it this year.
No, clock dance will help you.
No, it's too late.
You can't think about your own brain
because that's what's doing the thinking.
Besides, it's in a little case, you know,
full of the very hard in there and so,
why you can think of the same thing as thinking.
And you know not the hour in which they shall come.
I just feel like the beats, you know.
I'm beat, man.
I can't deal with the humans anymore.
They're killing each other.
They're doing all the ugly stuff, man.
It's not spiritual for you.
You can't deal with them, man.
There's no love on this planet anymore.
Just I want to kill you.
I see why you are saying that life is not spiritual for you.
I want to kill.
Chaz, are you saying that Dr. Leary got it too complicated
that he should have just left it in?
Yeah, that's what he's saying.
Drop out.
That's what he's saying because...
Forget tune in.
Forget turn on.
Just drop out.
It's not spiritual enough for him.
Look, man.
He is a very spiritual man.
Tune in to what?
Look at Chaz, you know, like he's CNN.
Look at the funny stuff he put on his hair, man.
Don't tune in because all you're going to tune in to is the man.
To what?
Bathtub methamphetamines?
Some pubucker bruda.
Some stupid...
Just suck their concoctions.
Just drop out.
Just leave it behind.
Just stand up and walk away from it all.
Leave your house burning.
Leave your shoes on someone else's feet
and keep walking into the sunset.
And now, Dr. Behringer,
one final word
about the consistent...
In with the old...
...finalizing word about the...
Or are they all just deja vus?
...the news?
Sure, I...
Yeah, I...
I ate as much as I could
and I got out there as quick as I could.
Stay tight.
I saw the taxi going by.
I knew something was up.
Everybody was speeding.
Take the red pill.
Take the blue pill.
Will you have the red pill?
Or the blue pill?
I thought my eyes were going to shut the final time this time.
I'll take both!
No.
Please, sir.
Or the blue pill?
Can I have more of them cocktails?
More?
And you'll never know anything before.
Take the red pill.
More of them cocktails, bot!
The red pill is much more fun.
Sure, I knew all about it.
But I wasn't gonna tell yet.
Well, what if I did, like, two of the red pills...
And then...
Well, what if I did a red pill, then a blue pill...
You're back to the wheel, you're sacking the saddle.
It's ZSO Radio.
Five minutes later, it'll be the last day of your life.
Last chance.
Welcome to Cabo De River.
I'm in the house.
Thank you.
Coyote's Fun City.
Yo, yeah.
You know what time it is.
If you need more information, you can call me.
I'm a doctor.
But if you're talking about the Church of the Sub Genius,
please write to this address I'm about to give.
That's b-b-b-b-ball.
That post office box, 140306, Dallas, Texas, 75214.
Once again, that's box 140306, Dallas, Texas, 75214.
www.subgenius.com.
Come and praise the...
You cursed brat! Look what you've done!
I'm melting! Melting!
Oh, what a world! What a world!
Who would have thought a good little girl like you could destroy my beautiful wickedness?
Ah! The boat! The boat!
I'm going home!
No!