Um...
It's time for, uh...
Ehh...
It's time for some...
Uh, come on, you know what time it is.
Whoa, uh...
Huh?
Life drop by the big testy bag
Well, welcome to the hour of slack
Praise Bob, Gold, and Connie's drag
Yes, welcome to the hour of slack
YAYAYAYAYAYAYAYAYAYAYAYAYA
Somewhere over the docks can we get high
So we can get high
Welcome to the hour of slack
And the Dave has...
The Dave man has arrived
On his flying air carpet
With his air head
His one single brain cell
Yes, this man
Look at his face
If we may call this a man
It is glowing
But the one evil brain cell
Gaze upon it as it swears on you
And grows
It's growing
It's rising
It's pulsating as if
It will infuse with some form of life of its own
As if it had sprung
Perhaps into existence on its own
As if it would bite
No!
The brain cell that couldn't die
Friends, we don't want the Dave brain cell to die, do we?
Well, uh, that's a leading question
I probably shouldn't ask you that
I'm, uh, gonna put it quite to work
We'll clip and flap and drizzle just in
We don't want to see it flap around in its cage
Or bother the other prisoners
Ah, there you go
Thanks, Nurse Mary
Oh, you're welcome!
It's gonna be a long time before we can stuff the rest of the detritus back in that monstrous skull
Yes, I know
But it looks really good from here, doesn't it?
Of course it looks good
But you can't eat it every day
Or you're gonna have the problem all over again
I know, I know, yeah, I know, I know
I'm gonna get this cleaned up, look at that
Rambod, hit it!
The brain is between your ears, finally here
Cool effect with your circle sphere
It's in your head, born and bred
If you didn't have a brain, you'd probably be brain-dead
Situated below the cerebral cortex
Into the cerebellum, cold gen effect
It's the medulla and I'm not foolin'
Frontin' and grillin', come on, chillin' and coolin'
And Brooklyn, hangin' in the whole hood
You need a brain if you're gonna make good
Cause if I'm a grift, staging a drive-by
Homies on the corner, I'm cracked, you know it, brain-frag
I pull a 9mm, I told them to stop
Shots rain out, what if I kill the cops?
I'll pursue you to aim or shoot your boy in the face
Your brain is a terrible thing to do
Your brain, your brain, your brain
Come on, get it up, get it up
Now then, my home boys, that wasn't at all bad
In fact, it was rather funky fresh
But, Filbert, what are you doing now?
I'm keepin' it real, you know what I'm sayin'?
I'm keepin' it fly, you know what I'm sayin'?
I'm fussin' up the funky mixdown, you know what I'm sayin'?
I'm keepin' it real and flyin'
With the hips, with the rifle, with the...
So throw your arms in the air
And wave them as if there were no consequence
Yo!
I'm a lyrical poet
The rhymes are in my brain
Just in case you didn't notice
I'm on a mic, brewing a dope rhyme
Dipping up to make you all go blind
Mastering the beat with my cold crush posse
I make a rhyme here but nothing rhymes with posse
That's when my brain was trained by the maestro
James Brown
I'm gonna make me all go
With the girlies sitting in the front row
I'm getting bizarre after the show
Kissin' and touchin' and strokin' her gently
In my Mercedes, Lexus, and Bentley
Or any of the other cars that I own
Except for my bodyguard, Will Pino
He won't hear us cause he's so deaf
Pleasure protection, his name is
That night, we go to a party
Everybody's there
On stage, spottin' rhymes in my nail
Then my homie, Master B
Juvenile Fred Durst in ODP
I hypnotize him with my brain power
Crossin' a rhyme, gettin' richer by the hour
And why not, cause they pay me to come here
The rhymes flow from my mouth to your ear
The head of your brain, and they call it read
I shouldn't, don't read, call it brain contraction
I make you dance till your suckers get some beat
You break your head like stupid baby face beat
I'm not the pup that ain't tougher than Kid Rock
And all the rest of you bops just can lick my brain
Your brain, your brain
Come on, heat it up, get it up
Brain, your brain, your brain
Come on, give it up, give it up
Brain, your brain
Yo, get, get off of
Your brain, your brain, your brain
Come on, get it up, get it up
Brain, your brain, your brain
Brain, your brain, your motherfucking brain
Now that this repetitive rhapsodic rhythm has totally wrecked my concentration
Talk to the appendage cause the cranium doesn't want to hear it
I shall remedy this situation with one swift stout
Heditonic, hey, ready?
Pull!
Yeah!
Shut up!
This is art
Art, art, art
A little after dinner music
Now what are you dancing for?
Dancing for you
Nope!
Well that looks better
I'm not gonna hurt you
Kill me
I
Sound
For you
Create
I
Night
Me
Kill Me by Dr. Onan's Wotan Band.
And friends, you can reach Onan at onanatsubgenius.com.
In fact, you can reach a lot of subgeniuses by using their name at subgenius.com.
You can also reach him at, got the pencil ready?
Post Office Box 2321, Portland, Oregon 97208.
He's the subgenius answer man, and he has music as well, and occupant-related materials at a website,
which also has his P.O. Box number, because it's www.box2321.com.
Before that, we heard Consortium of Geniuses.
I got this, or rather, Consortium of Genius.
I got this CD and video and all kinds of stuff from them in New Orleans.
Consortium of Genius is evidently inspired by Monty Python, Fireside Theater, Mystery Science Theater 3000,
so many others that we would all recognize.
Their album called Free.
Free Brains and Dead Bodies, and that song was called Brain Rap.
Of course, friends, over the Dobbs head and all the mini collages on tonight's show are by
Fernanda Nande-Lee Moore, the great subgenius artist, now sound fartist.
And of course, ESO Swamp Radio with Lonesome Cowboy Dave and Chaz Smith from WCSB every Thursday night in Cleveland.
And...
Uh...
Friends, you know, the aspects of this show tonight, number 854, will be a drag,
because the sad theme of this sad show is drunks.
And it was inspired by Philo, Dr. Philo Drummond, unearthing some tapes of our friend that died of drugs, like whiskey.
Dr. X was his name, heard in the background jamming with me,
a thousand years ago.
His name is in Book of the Subgenius, right under Bob's, next to mine and Philo's.
In the early 80s, he had a band called The Pink Boys.
Recognize that term?
And we will be playing his song called Pink Boy later.
The significance of this is simply that...
To me, he's mine.
He was my best friend in high school.
And...
And was there when we first heard the word subgenius.
He was part of the Boob Forest.
They moved a whole bunch of them into the cameras.
Do you know how slow and clumsy drunks are to a fropper like me?
A coffee drinker.
Oh, sure.
A fropp maniac.
And you know how little those stories that they tell you, those things say mean?
Oh, they got that instead of that, man.
They're like Spider-Man compared to these yo-yos.
Yeah, they're like...
Oh, man.
Don't you blame.
Oh, thanks, man.
Oh, man.
We were waiting for that for...
I'm sorry, man.
Your show is pretty lame.
Okay, well, we already said...
Well...
Yeah?
Is there some way we can maybe...
Why aren't you turning the radio off or turning it to another channel?
He said it was lame.
Are you that much of a loser?
Is there something we can do for him, maybe?
Are you that much of a pathetic little dweeb that you can't figure out that you can turn your radio to another station?
Well, if he didn't like what we were saying, we could have helped him another way.
Is somebody sitting there with a gun to your head forcing you to listen to this station?
I'm just going to hear some...
The corporate states...
The blowfish man, and you blew his mind.
I can feel it now.
We're not playing Green Day tonight, kid.
I'm vacillating sexuality.
You're interpreting my mind.
Or, you know, they're fornicating or something.
I can tell that kid needed our spiritual help.
You can't expect responsible behavior when alcohol is served.
What the hell?
There you go.
You can't expect responsible...
As a matter of fact...
People, when they crucified parties, they were all ripped, roaring drunk.
...responsible behavior from drunks.
Right, right.
There are people who can drink, and then there's drunks.
I was having responsible behavior all night.
That's why I don't drink!
Think of the beer hall push.
Hitler knew what he was doing.
Oh, my God.
You can manipulate drunks quite easily.
You can't expect responsible behavior from people who have any alcohol or any other mind-altering substance in their body.
That's funny.
You know, because I've done quite a few alcoholics who are not...
You can't really expect people with a functioning endocrine system to behave normal.
You know?
You can be a drunk and not be a drunk.
You can be a jerk.
You can be an alcoholic and not be a jerk.
Then there's the drunken jerks.
And if you're that kind of a drunk, don't drink!
And then they mix swingerism with bestiality.
Who is putting a gun to the heads of these people and marching them into my campsite?
Or a pork chop, you know?
You know?
I don't get it.
Who was out there?
Who did they hire?
Who did Ace hire to go out there with handguns and force people to come into this thing?
Who forces security?
And drink those Mai Tais and mudsies?
Always unimportant for you and your family values.
Responsibility, friends.
People are trying to duck responsibility like they do here.
We're selling Malaysian children by the power.
Take responsibility for your own actions.
To work in sweaty little shops, that is.
If you don't like our actions, then don't patronize us.
If you don't keep up with my accents, you don't have to.
Are you that stupid out there?
Stop throwing money at us, man.
Shut the hell up.
Oh, that was a really good one.
Stop interpreting my inner consistency.
Totally.
Forget it.
Drop the alcohol.
Go straight for peroxide.
Really?
Now this guy's talking trash.
Yeah, everybody with white hair.
I think it'd be a beautiful world that way.
We're talking about squirting things out of your navel.
No, no, he's talking about drinking it straight, man.
Peroxide?
Yeah, hydrogen peroxide.
Try it.
Oh, man.
Talk about the blowhole of death, man.
That's going to remove a lot of your insides in one fell swoop.
Did you ever run up some peroxide, man?
Hello?
Man, drop the peroxide, man.
Drink gasoline.
That's not good.
No, you know what?
That's not a good buzz.
Not with, especially with the prices we've got, the world petroleum problem.
That's what the amateur fire breathers use.
You know, I've done that.
Who hasn't run out of gas and siphoned some gas out of another car and swallowed down a bunch of gas?
It's not fun.
I mean, who hasn't flipped their old frig frog out once in a while and put it in the tank just for a clever joke with the Polaroid crowd?
You know, some of them anyway.
Like that.
It's, you know, American.
It's macho.
We're humping steel.
I love my car, and I mean I love my car.
Oh, I'm feeling her headlights now.
They're like two round, robust, rounders.
Oh, Christine.
And my thing is that shift stick.
Yeah, baby.
Four on the floor.
That's me.
Or maybe that's two underneath her.
Here it comes.
There it comes.
Give me some loving.
Have all your loving.
Give me some.
Bob.
Yeah, we're spilling beers right and left.
We got trouble in River City.
That's the smell of tea.
Which rhymes with B.
Which stands for beer.
Shake the hand.
Shake the hand of an honest drunk.
The farmer, he got plowed.
The bricklayer got plastered.
The mechanic, he got tagged.
And the construction worker got blasted.
And daddy beat up mommy.
And broke her collarbone for good luck.
And everybody's drunk.
And everybody's wasted.
And everybody's drinking on the job.
The garbage man got trashed.
The janitor got fired.
The janitor got messy.
The taxi driver got smashed.
And the waitress, yeah, she got tipsy.
In Kansas City, New York City, great big city.
Itty bitty city.
Now everybody's drunk.
And everybody's wasted.
And everybody's drinking on the job.
There's a whole lot of places that I ain't been.
A whole lot of things that I ain't seen.
A whole lot of things I'll never be.
The generation that will change the world is still lookin' for its car.
Play!
I'm out of smoke!
How many did you have tonight, Steve?
The Terror of Scott Baugh!
The President got hit
Security was tied
Yeah, the Secret Service got lit
The FBI, the CIA
T-Duck, yeah, USA
Everybody's drunk
And everybody's wasted
And everybody's stoned
There's nothing left
for the changes
Cause everybody's drunk
And everybody's wasted
And everybody's drinking
on the job
Job
I've got to call my mom
and tell her I got a job
Top cod ver.
Johnny's way
Espero que el SOS
You gotta have a girlfriend
Finally, get off my nerves
You an old relative
I didn't work
inoms
No is it?
I thought you guys knew that song.
The Rainmakers friends from live in Oslo and now, something Philo did to something I did
to Bob.
Yes, I'm the jambal in a humping junkie that jumped the men from Mars.
I drank the devil under seven tables, I am too intense to die, opiates are the mess of
my religion, I take drugs.
Yes, I'm a rip snorter, I cram coca leaves right into my arm veins, before they are picked
off the trees.
I... space monsters cringe at my tread.
I wipe the pyramides off my shoes, before I enter my house.
I'm fuel injected, I'll live forever and remember it afterwards.
I'm immune.
I'm radioactive.
Come on and give me cancer, I'll spit up the tumor and butter my bread with the juice.
I'm supernatural, I bend crowbars with my meat axe and a thought.
My droppings bore through the earth and erupt volcanoes in China.
Yes, I can drink more wine and stay soberer than always.
All the heathen hindus in Asia.
Yee-haw.
Nuts blow out.
Brown wavy medium.
Neapropetrovsk-Chaterin.
Wavy medium brown.
Tashkentum's-Shelyabin.
Medium wavy brown.
A van of Ochernigavoser.
I like shaping.
Wavy brown medium.
I like to go out and drink beer.
I like to drink wavy brown beer.
We haven't...
We haven't any chance.
Chance?
You, uh...
No chance?
Naturally things happen like, uh, at the, uh, Columbia University.
At the other mother college.
Yeah.
No, it really is, uh...
Really?
Come on.
You know what?
I went to school at the University of Southern California.
You see?
We didn't do any of that shit.
Let me explain something to you.
When I was there, I went there.
You see me in the fightin' McBride?
When there was a fella...
I can't believe Bob was like this in front of those rotary clubs.
Oh, look, his butt, his butt fell right out.
Right on the glass, man.
Oh, my God.
Listen to him.
Anybody...
His butt fell off his mouth.
...walked into his...
Office.
Oh, man, what you doin' with your hands down there?
...office.
Took a crap in the cab.
And tore down a picture.
Okay.
Jesus.
This is gonna cause awful smell.
Did excrement in his...
Bob was really upset about what those Bobbies did in Dobbs Town.
And did excrement in the hot tub.
Yeah, yeah.
He was really...
He was very pre-pubescent.
But...
This was Bob's reply after that year.
This was the last recording of Bob.
It was right after the year that they crapped in the hot tub.
We have member...
This is a very historical piece of memorabilia right here.
...would have...
Yeah.
...rem...
See, that's when the pipe...
He's trying to put the pipe back in his...
He doesn't like a curse.
...mouth to keep crawling out.
No.
There were women there.
He won't say bad words in...
No.
...Mix Company.
Not unless they're showing their labia to him.
Even when he's that drunk...
Yeah.
...Bob has had manners.
Masick was an expert with the experts.
All serial murderers have this chair that I'm sitting on.
Morrison did something she had done before.
I looked under the bathroom and my telephone rang.
And it was this chair that I'm sitting on.
I opened the lighted phone and it was empty.
So, um, I went back to the telephone and I said,
Richard, you're not in the telephone.
I am in that telephone.
Oh!
What's the magic, dragon?
Who's at your party?
If it's all natural...
Hey, uh, sit down and enjoy a red stripe, man.
I-I wanna tell you a little story, you know.
The palm is growing on a holly...
I think it was about, uh, maybe 10, 11 years ago.
All I read...
All, as far as you could see, they were cows, man.
It's like people think that there are palm trees and guava berries hanging from everything over here.
But not in the area of, uh...
My Little Village.
Where these huge doves heads fall from the sky.
And miles and miles.
As far as you can see.
That sounds like a Rasta Kerouac.
Hey!
That was Rasta Kerouac.
I don't think we've ever heard.
I don't think Rasta Kerouac has ever appeared on this show ever before.
Cold fusion of two alternative characters.
The Dave brain split again.
I like that.
Rasta Kerouac.
Again.
The Rasta Kerouac.
The Rasta Jack.
I like that.
Rasta Jack.
Rasta on the road.
That's if they were on the road and they ended up, you know, instead of like turning back in Mexico.
They should have kept going right on down.
Sweatshop in Kingston.
No.
Way down.
Like down in Bolivia or something.
They would have taken Jack Cassidy to, I mean Neil Cassidy, to a gun court for sure.
Remember the gun?
Of course they had for most of the subgeniuses for crying out loud.
Hey, first rule of gun club.
Don't talk about gun club.
If it's all natural, put it in your body.
Organic.
Yeah.
Simpson weed.
That's the.
Datura Nexus.
You gotta legalize it.
Oh, we taught it down.
Datura, man.
Make a fine tea out of local weed.
The devil's weed, man.
You don't want to smoke the devil's weed.
The devil's.
The devil's weed.
My bud smoked some Jimson weed and he ended up taking a dump on his living room floor in front of his parents.
My bud took a dump on his parents' floor.
He was a hedonist.
This guy was a Jimsonist.
He was about to take a dump on everybody.
Just like that hedonistic buddy of yours.
No, that's it.
Now, you guys aren't going to be putting.
George down when, uh, when the evil terrorist germ bomb goes off in your backyard.
And when they.
You're going to want George to save you.
They're going to trace you back.
Oh, George.
Aaron Fleischer's post office box.
Why didn't you bomb the hell out of those people before they set off that germ bomb in our backyard?
That's what you'll be saying.
Face it, Stang.
If you want to fight something for America, war is good.
You've got to fight war is good for industry, for the oil industry.
Yes.
But did you know that Iraq is sitting on one of the largest deposits?
There is to sit on.
Did you know that the slate underneath Saddam Hussein's feet was worth billions and billions of petroleum dollars?
Stang, you're confused about what's important in this country.
Look at you.
You're hardly a man.
Oh.
Ah, for crying out loud.
Look at those biceps.
What are you good for?
Can you lift this gun?
The eternal wisdom of nature's laws.
Which are completely opposite to the suicidal teachings of normality.
Whereas.
Normality says to love your enemies and to hate your own kind.
We say just the opposite.
We say that in order to survive, we must overcome and destroy those who are a threat to our existence.
Namely, our deadly enemies, the normals.
At the same time, we advocate love and protection.
That's not really what it's about.
And dear to our family and our own race.
The subjugation.
The race.
Which is an extension of our family.
Nope.
It's just about killing.
It's just about our God-given right to kill.
Ask Ted Nugent.
Take as many as you can.
I'll bet Ted'll go.
Let God sort them.
I wish Ted would go.
And then he'll give them to the homeless center.
So give his kills to the homeless center.
When Ted realizes that some of the squirrels shoot back, he's going to be in a lot of doo-doo.
I think he should go.
I'll bet Ted would be in there.
Don't.
Don't do it.
He's like one of those guys that came back from a golf war.
That's a good debate.
Would Ted win power?
I wish we could just find out those fetus ghosts are coming for us.
God has a heart on for Marie.
Because we kill everything we see.
He plays his games.
We play ours.
The butcher's apron.
To show our appreciation for so much power, we keep heaven.
Packed with fresh soul.
The butcher of Washington hides behind his berms.
The great yellow dog of the Potomac.
His formidable berms.
On the Potomac.
Grace, Marshall.
But he will not resist our special guided patriotic psychotic missiles.
Which can go straight down the premier's wife's brassiere, if that's where we want to target.
It was bad.
July in Virginia.
Yes.
The dogwood and the laurel lay heavy on the land.
While the virgin and the...
Magnolia was a blast.
Doc Mojo was burying Sung Lee back on the back 40.
That's sick.
Cheese lovers know that cheese lovers choose friskies.
Despite his sunny exterior, little Caleb is dead.
He doesn't even have a name.
For that reason...
Today we are proposing to add minutes to the environment.
Once it's added, shipments and sales would be allowed...
To companies that create everything.
Yay!
All too many demonic Israelis.
That would be me!
No!
And may I say...
From the banana.
Take out the pen.
I don't know anything.
Place the tip of the marker on the surface of her spirit.
And it's gotta be friskies.
You can come across the middle.
And then you can come high.
Well...
How...
Oh.
Or...
The dots in...
So they said...
Now experiencing hair.
Just snap.
And may I say I am...
Perfectly grilled.
Televangela has just sent in her bad dream of two hours ago.
And I'd like to read this to you.
It's short, Dave.
Televangela dreamed...
Some sort of subgenius gathering in my backyard and home.
The home where I grew up.
Parents not home.
Not informed they were coming.
Myself either.
The usual group was there.
Plus some new faces with very unique outfits and problems.
A very loud woman in shiny spandex yelling that we should wrestle in food or something I recall vaguely thinking.
Oh, that was a bombastic party.
Is this Ziza?
Ziza?
Then people are...
Pasting something on the wall.
Some sort of decoration.
Look at her old pasty face, Dave.
Looking more like clear peaches.
Then, the worst part of all.
My grandma shows up and is seated in a circle of subgeniuses on the lawn without me being able to stop it.
Legume tells her about how we need more hate.
Jesus tells her he's Jesus.
Stang and we just agree and have those twinkling crazy eyes.
I show up.
But it's too late.
She's pissed and confused and arguing.
I try to help grandma but then I wake up.
Friend, are you even able to wake up from that dream you call life?
Can you open your eyes?
Can you awaken from that dream you call your job?
The sleeper must awake.
We call for the sleeper to awake.
I'm a potato.
You said it, bud.
Great.
No, no, no.
No, no.
Scraaaaaaack.
Pizza?
Omelette.
Herbal.
Call the man.
So Money.
Fernand and Andy Lemur did that collage and now from their new CD, Reagan's Polyp.
Hey, any Beatles fans in the audience tonight?
We got a song for you.
It's called Daytripper now.
Let's do up some of that haba-fray-orang-a-tang-zip-ula-orang-a-tang.
Oh, let's.
This is a hell of a thing.
Ah, and the soft.
And the soft.
Noises enter the midbrain.
And the child gently releases its pituitarygasm.
And the feet are firmly placed on the ground as they should be.
My pituitarygasm.
Thanks, Mom.
Thanks, Dad.
It's gonna rip your whole spine next time.
Just relax, little boy.
Yeah.
They're coming back.
Wait, you're gonna have to hide under the bed here, kid.
I'm afraid.
Really afraid.
None of them pituitarygasms.
When they're coming by that make any noise, just hold onto this piece of wood.
And you can feel like you're doing something.
OK.
OK, OK, OK, OK, OK.
Be very quiet.
Bite onto the piece of wood if you want to make a sound.
If you start to .
Gath.
You just .
Open.
These people from child welfare services are creepy.
They are creepy as hell, man.
That's not the half of it.
They got some penis.
We're all in deep sh
We're
Let's just
To have the circumcision machines.
We're in even deeper.
Oh, yeah.
To wear a bob without a Connie.
Oh man, no anesthetic for these guys.
One of the first things any of the forbidden children must learn is how to keep the pituitary
gasm at a minimum.
The child service workers are often vicious and barbaric in their retribution and have
sometimes even slothed the little old childs.
A pituitary gasm in a pre-10 year old can be a violent, earth-shaking thing.
This is one of the cause-ripped causes for poltergeist.
That's not why you get them to take your shoes.
Sloth.
Truth to children.
Watch how these children are now found in despair.
Their eyes most likely never come true.
They sniff the anguish.
They are fortunate.
Jerry, he says that the hardest child comes.
He'd sent out into the world his nine-year-old Anguish and his eight-year-old Peter.
They were all seven.
I can see these kids.
What a young age to live.
What?
Truth to children.
Am I still dancing?
I can't remember.
It doesn't sound like much of a dance anymore.
I can't hear my heels clicking.
I'm dancing to the dark side of the moon.
Oh, Dave's playing that.
I mean, Chance is playing that song about you.
The Pink Boys.
The Pink Boys?
Is that who this is?
Yeah, the Pink Boys.
Man, that was a great band before the lead singer OD'd.
Good.
New and upgraded.
Perfect in the box.
Good.
Pink Boys.
You're gonna throw up.
Think I'm gonna throw up.
Pink Boys.
You can't forget this passion.
You can't put a stand with this kind of passion.
Still.
That's it.
Pink Boys.
You need a degree.
I need.
Is that the university?
Because it is.
I'm always looking at the station.
I always have to find a source of any of that action.
Pink Boys.
You're never gonna throw up.
You're gonna throw up.
Pink Boys.
You can't forget this passion.
You can't put a stand with this kind of passion.
Still.
Pink Boys.
You're gonna throw up.
You can't forget this passion.
You can't put a stand with this kind of passion.
Pink Boys.
Fuck you.
You can't forget this passion.
You can't forget this.
Pink Boys.
You can't forget this passion.
Yeah.
B-Boy, we're gonna go up
B-Boy, it's just a little bit of action
You can't really tell, but it's just a little bit of action
B-Boy
I drink and kill the whiteness in my eyes
Don't wanna think about those lonely goodbyes
I can't forget
All the pounding in my head
And waking up
Creatures in my bed
And when did this all begin?
Tap on the shoulder, my friend
Ay-ay, ay-ay
I drink enough
Ay, I drink enough
I drink and travel
Around the whole world
I drink and marry a liquor store girl
I drink and build
My cellfoil yacht
And small old trucks
Oh, I never get caught
For when the bar is where I want to be
I take my ship and I tank across the sea
I, I, I, I, I drink enough
I, I drink enough
I'm living at home
Oh, it gets old
And I'm at my parents' house
It's been so old
In the pubs where I want to be
I take my boat and we can float across the sea
And if I run out of cash
I get my meals from the trash
I, I, I, I drink enough
I drink and kill
The whiteness in my eyes
Don't want to think about those lonely goodbyes
I can't forget
All the pounding in my head
And waking up
Creatures in my bed
And when will this all end
Live with cirrhosis, my friend
I, I, I, I, I drink enough
I, I, I, I drink enough
Infest pain and
To clean my ears
Where I used to live
They'll wash them from the stain
If I don't Ihave to think about my ways
The Line.
The Line, tweaked by Lemur.
Before that, that song, I Drink Enough, is by Rocco Schwab
from his album, The Barlight Beauty.
Information is at www.scaryrecords.com.
That's roccoshwab at hotmail.com.
And before that, friends, The Pink Boys, doing that song,
the titular song, The Pink Boys.
That was the band of my friend Dr. X.
That was recorded live in some club in Dallas in 1980,
about the time that the first,
subgenius pamphlet was printed.
Dr. X died of drink and bad habits,
and it was a bummer, man,
because he was my high school best pal.
And he died before he was even 40.
But now, Reagan's Pollock!
Any Led Zeppelin fans out here tonight?
The only one that's called The Immigrant Song.
Gan dynasty
ffaaahdfuaahd
Go GM
Go Gmail
No, it's not!
I am a gull darned visionary, I see the future and the past in comic books and wine bottles,
I eat black holes for breakfast.
I bend my jeans and whittle my DNA with the sheer force of my mighty will.
I spear my own gull darned evolution.
I ran M out of heaven and sold it to hell for a profit.
I'm enlightened, I achieved nirvana and took it home with me.
Yip, yip, yee-yee-ee.
I'm so ugly the speed of light can slow me down and gravity won't tug at my cuffs.
When the rapture comes, I'll make M wait.
They'll never clean my cage.
Now give me some more of, Take Runs Out.
Summertime's here, kiddies.
And it's time to take a break.
Take a trip, to take a trip, to this world so bad.
You feel so sad, you gotta take a trip, into a world so glad.
A world of frogs, and green fountains, and flying dogs, and silver cats, and emerald rats,
and purple clouds, and faceless crowds, and walls of glass that never passed.
And pictures hanging upside down.
You won't ask where you are.
It's another world.
You and your girl, and all your friends, will all be there.
Oh yeah.
Let's take a trip.
TNT.
SOS.
HOB.
TOP.
Get to talk.
Hey, here we go now.
Let's climb some mountains, everybody.
Get on your walking shoes.
Let's climb some mountains.
Here we go.
Let's take a trip.
Let's start to dream.
Let's close our eyes.
It's groovy now.
Yeah.
Floating.
Because I'm swimming in beauty.
It's all around.
Let's take a trip.
I'm from the ground.
Whoa.
Yeah.
Let's take a trip.
It's really hip.
No one will know what goes on.
Just you and me.
And the dreams we see.
I'll come out of you.
I'll come out of you, babe.
You're doing it right.
Just put your head back.
Friends, The Trip by Kim Fowley.
You have been listening to the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
You can get free information from Bob at Post Office Box 204206.
That's also the number for the Subgenius Foundation.
P.O. Box 204206.
Austin, Texas 78720.
And you can write to me, Reverend Ivan Stang, stang at subgenius.com.
And just check www.subgenius.com.
And praise Bob.
I mean, everyone knows who this shit is.
I got a mathematical equation for you.
Here's a word problem.
A math word problem.
Okay.
I'm going to write to you.
The universe is an infinite...
Sorry, an infinite...
Oh, you should write the first one.
...agglomeration of energy fields resembling threads of light.
That's A.
Okay, threads. Remember threads.
These energy fields radiate from a source of inconceivable proportions, metaphorically, called the eagle.
The needle?
The eagle.
Eagle?
Eagle.
Three.
The answer is C.
Human beings are also composed of an incalculable number of the same thread-like energy field.
Whew, we are?
So the question is, one ply or two?
Oh, man, that's an easy one.
Two ply.
Oh, you think it is.
Black hole.
Yeah, if you don't pick the right answer, that's what you get.
You'll be picking something else out of your sockets.
Oh, is that song over?
The end of the world is over already?
Yes, it is.
Let's sing a song about the end of the world.
No, let's go to war.
Let's sing a song about war and the end of the world.
Sky Pilot.
Oh, the beginning of the world?
Yeah, let's sing a song about the beginning of the world.
In E.
Okay.
The great yeti mother
Squatted down
And grew
and gave birth to the universe.
And then the great yeti father came upon the egg of the universe
and what splurted upon it was what we call time.
And so time and the universe came together
and something came from nothing.
And then God invented souls.
And then Bob let God loose from his chain and said,
Sack him!
And the souls evolved and sent $30 to Bob.
Praise Bob.
And so the universe began.
Well, that homily was performed by his son.
His own self, his own self, the gland man,
our favorite clam, the Reverend Ivan Stang.
I don't think there's a dry eye socket
or any other socket in this room now.
The brain is the only proper receptacle for the seed of genius.
The brain, the brain, look at that.
Look at how many little tiny dendrites that are moving.
Bring me more blind French maid.
If you fly past...
If you fly past the sonic sphere, you will die.
Yes, you will.
You cannot live through that.
It's a storm of light.
You know, it's pretty dark out there.
Hey, what happens when two black holes come together?
If two black holes meet?
They suck each other up into the infinities.
Gravitational ripples?
Perhaps a new poo-poo on your wing?
It's become like a snakey...
How could anybody actually...
...infinities?
Snakes eating each other's tails?
No one could know the answer to that question.
Or fabulous psychosis, any time you want.
We could never observe it.
We could never absorb it.
We could never...
Any answer could never be proven.
So why is such an answer...
Well, from a distance, we can observe the effects
of the two black holes colliding.
Perhaps in some future civilization...
But you would never really know what's going on deep down,
you know, in the middle of it all.
No, but it would generate unthinkable energies,
and with those, we could...
...power our amps.
Oh, yeah.
What an ingenious idea.
They're so much better than broomsticks and candles.
That'd be a great place to do a concert, man.
Right at the meeting point between the two black holes.
I think that's where we did it.
Sapping forces of the vortex.
Friday night at X-Day.
That was sort of like one of those...
The conclave-age.
Concert right between the two black holes there.
It was the two left eyes of God.
Yeah, well, I think one of the black holes was Doc Frop's camp.
That's where we got sucked into.
Yeah.
Ah.
Like a parasite.
Like a vampire.
Oh, that's right.
Yeah, you missed it.
You missed the big...
Yeah.
Oh, but the robots...
When I get my jet fighter plane, I'm going to play this piece.
When I get to kill...
When I get to kill our Iraqis...
Listen, honey, they're playing our romantic song.
Oh, remember how many Iraqis we killed with this song?
They loved it.
Kill, kill, kill.
The hoose wasn't so badly either.
Kill.
The black holes.
Yeah.
I think one's from a firefighter named Tom Evans when he put his fire out.
What does that mean?
That's a pretty metaphorical thing there, man.
I don't know if we can even handle that on this show, at least.
That is infatimable.
We don't have the kind of, like, energy forces to deal with that.
Beyond me.
Okay.
What happens if an irresistible pie meets an uncontrollable high?
Ah, that is when you need...
Sandwich time.
The boundless appetite.
Yes.
For the infinite pie.
I lust for food.
Not I lust for life.
The uncontrollable pie.
A pie.
This is making me slobbering at the mouth.
You've missed it.
Go for a pie.
Mildly delicious.
Look, your euphemisms are on the corner of your nasal drip.
Isn't that Dairy Farmers Union place open all the time?
Oh, no, not at this hour of the night unless you go to a special dairy mart.
A special ice cream.
Yes.
That's what I'm gonna...
Yum.
Pie.
Pie in the sky.
That's what we've been offered the whole time when they're offering us death.
Pie squared.
Pie.
I hate to sound like an old wobbly son of a bitch.
I like to get down every now and then.
I like to get down and...
Caramel.
Really, you know, I put...
I do a whole different retuning for this.
And get down into the roots of pie.
You ever get down into the roots of pie?
Yeah, man.
That's...
No, I'm hip to it.
But I've never done it before.
A lot of people aren't in touch with that.
They think, you know, all you do is go down to the music store and buy the equipment and,
you know, that's the next thing.
You're in pie.
But you gotta get into the root of pie, baby.
Yeah.
And that's something you can't buy at a store.
You know, you can buy the pie there, but you can't buy the root of pie.
Where does the mud of the root of pie come from?
I don't know, man.
You gotta answer that question.
Where's the mud of the root of pie?
Oh, that's deep.
Well, ultimately, it comes from a point.
A point which expands to become the circle from which we derive the pie, or vice versa.
The perfect circle.
The perfect hole.
A zero.
A nothingness.
Like the thing in the center of Bob's brain.
Perfect like a little baby's colon.
An ever-growing nothingness.
An all-devouring non-existence.
Look at its little chunks.
An anti-somethingness.
Look at its little...
Molecular...
A rapacious black hole of all things.
All light.
All gravitational forces.
Even tachyons.
A ravenous boop holder of tachyons.
Bob-ions.
And whack-me-ons.
Whack-me-ons.
Yeah, I like the whack-me-ons.
Oh, Bob, we call out to you in this, our darkest hour.
We are lost in the wilderness, and we need not only your salvation,
but your guidance and your supreme pure light.
Oh, let it shine.
Till next week, keep your hat on tight, you're back to the wind and your sack in the saddle.
This is ESO Radio, signing off.
See ya.
Your eye, till the sun is in the sky.
I'm gonna spend eternity alone with barely any swag.