From early Sunday morning national FBI-led radio news, I'm the first favorite character in northeast Minneapolis this season.
State forecast chance of east in the north, in the south.
This is FBI-led early Sunday morning national radio news.
Attention! Attention! This is your beloved leader, Mob, the Ex-Multi.
There will be a special giant toy rally today at Mob Memorial Stadium, honoring that impressive space explorer, Mob.
He is a first!
First! This is return from the planet Earth.
You are all commanded, uh, uh, uh, invited to attend.
What is going on here? I demand an explanation.
She's alive! Alive!
Why the hell aren't I notified about these things?
Looks like I picked the wrong week to quit sniffing glue.
Lord, we are fine.
Strip naked and get on the probulator.
You're switched on to the subgenius.
Power of...
SWATCH!
The groovy show that comes to you live from Master Race Frankenstein Radio Control.
The exciting adventures of the man with the action-packed expense account. America's Fabulous, Bob.
Number identification error.
I think I'm gonna start this thing.
Yeah, we called a wrecker to pull the show out of the sand here.
And the wrecker itself is a record.
Bob got mired in the muck.
And they hardened it to concrete-like hardness.
The show's gonna need a record.
Wouldn't you like to have Bob working for you?
On the other hand, look at him from Bob's point of view, and you see Bob's poor conduct on the job.
Bob would be popular wherever he worked.
Oh, I get it.
Keeping a Bob.
It's amazing, isn't it? Our voices right now are going to be immortalized in digital form forever.
And they're staying sane.
Yeah.
Like this? That's stupid.
What are you talking about?
I better listen to that again.
Everything's being recorded.
And cut up and collaged and...
People are hearing me?
Slice dice.
That's so silly.
Twelve cappuccinos later, it's a...
Oh, silly, huh? We're just silly, is that it?
Yeah, I see.
We're not funny and we're not silly.
We're not funny, we're just silly.
Silly.
This isn't funny, this is just silly.
Ugh.
Hello, this is the Bernard.
I just want to say that I am a strange bizarre anomaly or mutant.
And that earthquake that just occurred, I caused that earthquake to happen by my will alone.
That's proof that I am a mutant and not one of these common genetic, bland, normal humans of the community.
And that we need to stop this conspiracy, whose time needs to come to an end.
And that we need to keep fighting them as mutants until the aliens decide to come and take us away from here.
Because the UFOs are in the sky.
And they know that I'm here.
That's all.
Goodbye.
I ain't no man of circumstance
I walk around in leather pants
I don't need no salad snack
I think I'm having a big back attack
Hold the pickles, hold the lettuce
Special orders, don't upset us
All that we ask is you let us serve it
You're way paranoia's
There's too much paranoia's
When the goings get tough
The tough get rough
It's not quite enough to get you there, is it now?
Sing it, that's how the day will end
Don't ask me for American Express
You want my money, I'll write you checks
Cause I don't want no Apple Jacks
I think I'm having a big back attack
Hold the pickles, hold the lettuce
Special orders, don't upset us
All we ask is that you let us serve it
You're way paranoia's
There's too much paranoia's
Got a furry little kitty following me around all day
A furry kitty from the Psychoskeletons covering the Devo Classic.
And much more Psychoskeletons can be found at soundclick.com slash thepsychoskeletons.
Before that, our frequent message,
Lever Bernard takes credit for the earthquakes.
And amidst the collages by Lemur,
there was some puzzling evidence
and a title sequence by Reverend Outa Spaceman.
By the way, I have a correction to make.
Last week, I credited a collage called
I Told You I Was Bob to Reverend Sweetness McGee,
but really, it was Reverend Tai Ping Monkey, high colonic.
Speaking of which, there's a subgenius devival
coming up in Shanghai, China on March 23rd,
and I am not even kidding.
It is, however, at a secret location,
so you'll have to watch the subgenius.com events page
or the Asia Subgenius Yahoo group
praise Reverend Shining Path of Least Resistance.
Also, I will be preaching and showing new bug porn videos
at Winterstar February 4th weekend.
This is Hour of Slack number 1240,
and tonight we're relying heavily upon cuts
from the January 8th Puzzling Evidence Show
on KPFA Berkeley.
With post-puzzling evidence,
Dr. Philo Drummond, Dr. Howland Owl,
Reverend Phineas Narco,
Justin Credible, and Empress Zoe.
So, for Slack, let's get to work.
Yes, down below, the Morlocks continue to operate their machinery,
gleaming stainless steel boilers and pumps,
and venting steam,
constantly maintained by their Morlock servitors.
There we go.
All right, now the adjustment's been made,
and we're now moving backwards, actually, over the Earth.
Yes, I suppose we should get back into earlier eras.
As we prepare to lower the show back down into the parking space.
Back down into the low comedy preserve of Howard Stern and others.
And now the connection's been made.
Again.
Okay, that's your cue.
Who's cue?
Not mine.
No, no, the gong caller.
The gong caller?
Yep, gonged away by the Daughters of the Moon.
Picks up on a groovy lost journey, man.
It does, no, really.
Well, what is this?
The turkeys are laughing at us.
Is there some little thing you didn't tell us about your plan, Lieutenant?
I don't know.
Is there a...
Do I have a line here?
Oh, it says
throw his ax at...
I think it's missing him.
Chief turkey.
Oh yeah, okay, right.
I thought we did that ax thing earlier.
There, that was a stunt that was photographed separately.
So now we go to...
Oh, all right, all right, I got it.
We go to the cantina scene, I think.
So maybe the...
Do you have...
Are you on the right page?
That's in your script.
There's a script.
It's in a blue page.
It was added to my...
I don't think he can hear me.
Hey, caller?
I'm banging on his door.
I'm in the booth here.
Yeah, no, I'm banging on the caller's door.
I'm here.
Do you have our script tonight?
This is me.
Yes.
Okay, so you know what we're supposed to be doing, right?
Right, I'm about to get my line ready.
All right.
This is where Epiginus regrets to Macassar
the theft of the prince of Agaspark.
You shall die, eater of leeches.
Pig dog.
Spartan dog.
Trajan pig.
Mother of pearls.
I die.
God, read Daniel.
Daniel, what I wouldn't do for a drink of...
Of weak beer or strong water.
He wished to talk to...
Okay, my line's here, Hal.
I gotta talk to you.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Let the fool come forward.
There will be many vague things that will happen in...
Silence!
You do not know what is the way of Magaspool.
Magaspool?
Yeah, Magaspool.
No, not again.
Magaspool has warned you.
Those who trespass in his domain must perish.
You have to do that again so we can add the echo.
And Magaspool said,
let them who defy me
be punished to the full extent of the divine law.
Okay, we'll add the video later there for the punishment part.
There we go, the monster's got it.
They shall be boiled in the black tars of the...
All right, Hal's doing his read over
and the dissolve into the monster.
There we go.
He prowls in the sea of agony...
The lumbering creation of an errant god.
You do not believe I'm a pilot, Drummond?
No, I do not believe you are a pilot, Drummond.
Watch me ride this wagon.
What?
Get away from that wagon.
We're doing a monster show.
Oh.
Holy guacamole, the whole thing's gone haywire.
You guys know the guy who sweeps the chimney?
Bob?
Yeah.
Bob, except he's not Bob, he's Bob.
Who's Bob?
Bob is Bob.
That doesn't look like Bob.
No, that's Greg Norman.
I'm talking about Bob.
Bob.
Terrific Bob.
Bob?
Yeah, Bob.
Bob is Bob.
Terrific Bob.
I don't know.
That doesn't look like Bob.
Bob has been around here for some time.
Who's Bob?
Bob.
Bob?
What, is this supposed to be some sort of psychodrama?
Exactly.
Oh, Bob.
Yeah.
Yeah, and that little collage was by Local Color.
Now, let's welcome back Philo.
It's so great to be back on the show again.
I bet.
I was thinking about that.
Hey, did you see this?
For a long time.
Three weeks.
Bin Laden was a bad dad.
His kids have come out with all sorts of terrible stories about the way Omar...
Treated him.
Abused him, yeah.
Who did?
What?
Hi.
He made them live in unsanitary jails.
Omar.
Omar is his son.
Omar bin Laden.
Bin Laden.
Oh, you know...
They are good friends.
He may be a...
Bush family.
He may have been a...
Yeah, he may have been the mastermind of the 9-11 terror plot, but at least he could have
been a decent father, but no.
He chose to be a bad father.
A mean dad, according to his son, who has written a tell-all book to rival Joan Crawford's
Christina Crawford.
I really thought he was going to be a good father too, after all that evidence of it
in his past life.
Oh yeah, I see where you were saying the guy was channeling the guy that you were channeling
the guy.
Uh...
Oh, my God.
Oh.
¶¶
That was a piece called Sedated Cicada by Rural War Room
from their CDMX.
The Flaming Yawn, praised Byron Werner and Donovan Soot
of RuralWarRoom.com.
And now Dr. Howell will tell us
of the Frankenstein radio-controlled monster Computer God.
Oh, so are you reading about the Computer God?
I was. I can only follow in the steps of Francis' deck
or stand on his gigantic shoulders.
I think you can stand on his shoulders
and vault yourself forward with a...
Usually.
In a few years you are made string bean thin
or grotesquely deformed, crippled and ugly
or even made over one foot shorter
or one foot taller as the Computer God sees fit.
Virtually all of the important instant plastic surgery
is done to you inside the Computer God sealed robot operating cabinet.
Even unbelievable impossible plastic surgery operations,
all impossible even for dozens of vicious kosher-borsher doctors
working round the clock for weeks.
The Computer God sealed robot arm operating cabinet
can perform all of the above impossible plastic surgery operations
overnight, even dwarfing you over a foot
or increasing your height by two feet.
This is possible because Computer God robot operating cabinet
imitates your micro-miniature electrical current intelligence system in your body.
It even duplicates the micro-miniature electric currents
that soften your broken bones
to create mending and re-exhaustions.
It can even create a
and then create stress, either compressing the bones,
thereby shortening them, or stress to make the bones grow longer.
The worldwide unbelievable lowest deadly gangster kosher-borsher vicious medical profession.
Worldwide unbelievable instant plastic surgery butchery of the body and brain,
especially the face.
Wipe-on hormones and laser beam surgery causing instant ugly deep wrinkles, scars,
age spots, arthritis, freckles, bunions, and contusions.
It's a thing, a stinky, sneaky thing from the abyss.
You spent more time in the sewer than on the surface.
With grotesque, leering ugly face with blemishes, pimples, red blood cells,
brown, black, or even thick white face and body.
Worldwide dark male sex organs to brainwash inferior female brain
for overall plan, intermarry with rutabagas.
Total graying and balding, even hairy body and furry body,
mustached, bearded women even wipe on synthetic hormones,
mossing, cancerous growth, bloating, swelling, deformed, big pickle nose, bulldog hanging cheeks and jowls.
What's wrong with that?
From teenage gradual wipe-on, yellowing, browning, and blackening of teeth,
to new skin, grinding, and acids, leaving hollow brown stumps,
so vocal cords are made raspy, aging, creating a wrinkled, ugly, gargoylic clown.
Booze face worldwide population by age 70.
Deformed, crippled, weak, and brain-damaged, new senile, lingering for inevitability of gradualness, extermination.
The only hope for future.
Do you know one word of pray for me, Dr. Howland Owl?
Also in the news...
From PR News in Washington, I'm convicted today of crimes against humanity
and sentenced to death by slowly waiting for help.
But the event is taking place in an atmosphere of mistrust.
Pope Benedict XVI opened fire from several directions today, killing six people, including the district chief.
Benedict reminisced yesterday with a group of Germans about the Third Reich.
He said it made him happy and allowed him to resume his studies for the PR News.
This is PR News.
PR News is bad.
The Chinese government was rocked by deadly text messaging in July.
The government says residents are limited to hundreds of thousands of messages per day.
However, Beijing says text messaging and the internet were used last summer to organize PR News.
PR News
The ultimate
Literally crashing through
literally crashing through literally crashing through
world record human puzzle
A Reverend Wilhelm Stahlhelm did that on his CD called Blank.
Lemur did the news, and now more news.
And what about that big local story, Phil?
That big local story is from the MMO report by Adam Beissner.
Huxley is an old friend of mine.
From my first E3, it's always been there, touting its Unreal Engine 3 graphics.
It's been where?
Boy, did those look great in 2004.
Delicious.
An unusual action-oriented play.
It's 2009 now.
Several shooter-style MMOs have been released.
And there I am, playing the Huxley beta for the show floor again.
It's good to know that some things never change.
Huxley is still fun.
It plays much like Unreal Tournament 2004.
And the side...
...Sci-Fi setting is one I never tire of.
Even if nothing about it stands out.
However, it's no longer unique.
I have no idea how it's going to entice players away from the dozens of other sci-fi first-person shooter titles out there.
Maybe it'll stay in beta for a while longer, which is for the best.
I don't know what I'd do at E3 2010 if Huxley's not there.
It'd be quite the brave new world.
Don't leave your brain out in the rain.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Thank you for that warm, warm reception.
It was a warm, wonderful moment.
So warm and...
Wise.
It's kind of warm and wet.
Wonderful.
Warm.
Wet.
Wacky.
Why is it wet here on the seat?
Warmth.
Like someone...
Life-giving, life-affirming...
What's this warm wetness?
Warmth, friends.
That's what we need more of.
Life-affirming warmth.
Life-giving.
Friendly.
Calm.
Welcoming.
Warm.
Wet fur.
Wiggling.
Pulpy.
Palpating.
See, we've got the collar in the pain well again.
Yes, I know.
We lured him in there.
With honeyed words.
But now we can be...
We can...
Operation Vivisect.
I guess that'll teach you that there's danger at the club.
I spell my surname...
Sir Danger.
And vivisection isn't such a bad thing.
No, not if you're the one who's doing it.
Because you can learn how...
You can learn so much about human...
React to invasive stress.
Or non-human anatomy.
Two dollars and fifty cents.
Your witness, Mr. Mason.
Exactly.
Now, uh, get nervous.
You say you sat for it.
It just ought to hurt a little, being in the room.
Well, I...
Yes or no, please.
Well, no, sir.
I mean, yes, sir.
Now, did Beggington have she, that man?
Right?
There about a week or any,
said it's not the else,
but anybody in a day,
anything, if she was, she...
Mm-hmm.
That's all.
Vrrrr.
Two light bulbs flickering
Next to my ear
My ear?
buzzing and chattering
thought I could hear
them say
my little skook
my little chuck
my darling dearest
ee-truck
truck truck
some words were spoken
some part of a cow
bits of
intestine in your
stomach right now
can't pick up my mind
as I slowly start
to sink
look at my feet stuck in the mud
and I think
two light bulbs
flickering next
to my ear
buzzing and chattering
thought I could
hear them
say my little skook
my little chuck
my darling
dearest ee-truck
truck truck
one, two, three, four
one, two
I can't start walking
this is one of the lessons we like to give out
here on the show
it takes a lot of obedience to follow the show's
dogma
and understand
how the callers relate
to that, how we layer in
the logic of the caller
and the listener into the show's
many, many
protocols, it's very
layered series of protocols
to be able to
promulgate the show.
So you think we need to
evangelize and bring the show to
unfortunates who have never heard it before?
Absolutely. How else are we going to make sure
that it gets out?
And also we have two chorus members
already. Because I don't think
that the... Members of the chorus.
That the poor
and the minorities are properly
represented in the audience of the show.
Publicity is always a plus.
Well, they can always tune in.
The thing that you have to do is develop a street team.
You start making flyers.
Don't pay any attention to me.
It's probably just some street producing stuff.
We do flyers and shows.
After a while they know we do flyers.
What comes after
the flyer? I mean, haven't we risen above
the level of a flyer now?
Yeah, I think of emails, websites,
whatnot. Aren't we like in a four-color
process, monthly subscription
magazines? I'm still smoking
hash with the stones in Marrakesh.
Shouldn't we be in high times or something?
In rolling stone at this point.
High times are still in the future.
Get your picture on the cover.
I didn't even know what you were doing
was art. I thought it had to be
in a frame or like Jesus and Mary
and the saints in church.
Well, you know, the human soul chooses
to express itself in a profound
profusion of ways, not just plastic
arts. Sculpture, painting,
charcoal. Then there's
music and poetry
and dance. Lots of people.
Photography. Slam dancing?
Well, insofar as it reflects
the slam dancer's inner
conflict with society through the beat.
Yeah, yeah, sure.
Why not? You see, what
I'm dealing with is the aesthetics
of the transitory.
I'm creating
tomorrow's memories. And as
memories, my images are
as immortal as art,
which is concrete.
Wow. Oh, it shall
be done.
Wow. Cool.
Thanks, thanks.
It was nothing. Actually,
local color did it. Local
color. The song we heard,
Two Lightbulbs Flickering, is from
Fegmo Tactic, Reverend
Mark Hostler's solo-ish album
from NegativeLand.com.
Now, back to puzzling
evidence for the whiny phylo.
Confirm
birthday suit. Dancing
just incredible.
Pull down a window and choose
from the SLV the appropriate
choice. After the resounding
success of the Normandy invasion,
the Allied commanders are
buoyantly confident that the war in
Europe will be over in a matter of weeks.
And that Hitler and his battered
army have no other option
than surrender.
This journey's worth it.
But then came the Battle of the
Collars.
It's a simple act.
Battle of the Collars.
Despite the advice of his best
military minds, the Fuhrer
will hear no talk of defeat.
In mid-December 1944,
the Germans launch a desperate and ruthless
counter-offensive in the Ardans Forest.
Utterly surprising,
unprepared, complacent,
cud-chewing Americans who stand in their way.
Through the
frigid snows of the mountainous terrain,
German tanks rumble
and infantry struggles to realize
Hitler's goal of dividing the Allied
armies and capturing the Allied
forces.
Don't ever, ever let the Tooth Fairy
forget your child.
Fuck you!
Where's my pig?
Tooth Fairy?
The fucking Tooth Fairy.
The Tooth Fairy, the real Tooth Fairy,
the real Tooth Fairy,
can forget your child if you're not careful.
I'm the Tooth Fairy of Connecticut.
If you haven't laid out the appropriate, uh, Tooth Fairy
Yeah, and they've got, like, long vampire teeth, then you realize they're the long type of fairy to be hovering around your child.
sometimes the tiny tooth of a child is not enough to attract the child.
Tooth Fairy, you need some additional Tooth Fairy hormone attracted.
This Tooth Fairy hormone attracted is available at Walmart for only $12.95
with your special Tooth Fairy attracted device holder.
It's a simple, uh, dentist trick.
It is. It's a way that you get the Tooth Fairy to step into your house.
Nothing special.
Even in the middle of the night.
Even if you didn't.
You could actually use this to trick the Tooth Fairy.
Tooth Fairies don't listen to this show, so it's okay.
It's kind of early to be talking about the Tooth Fairy.
You can go to Walmart and get your Tooth Fairy attracted.
It's available at, not just Walmart.
I don't think Walmart probably has a lower price, but you can get it at Home Depot or Best Buy or any of your other Tooth Fairy supply stores.
But generally, I think the Tooth Fairy attracted, uh,
Wherever you can find Yellow Jacket attracted.
Right. It's, it's right next to the Yellow Jacket.
It's attracted to Fly Rattling.
All that stuff.
That smelly, smelly pheromone-laced and rotted, fetid, stinky stuff laced up.
Anyway, don't let the Tooth Fairy pass your child by this Christmas.
Just because your child has a birthday around Christmas time and loses its tooth.
I just need to sprinkle food around my toes.
You can sprinkle food around your toes.
Around your toes? Who said?
It may not attract the Tooth Fairy like, like, you know, what some of this Tooth Fairy attracted, this pheromone that they extracted from dead Tooth Fairies.
I wonder what Michael Pepe's up to with that, uh, Tooth Fairy scam this year.
I don't know. I don't know. But all I know is that if, if anyone's child gets passed up by the Tooth Fairy, those repercussions last all year long.
Until the next tooth is lost, at least.
I wonder what the Tooth Fairy does with all of his teeth.
I don't know.
The Tooth Fairy makes this hideous, hideous jewelry and sells it.
It's a donut.
Tooth Fairy's teeth.
From PR News in Washington, I'm trying to reignite sectarian violence.
December is designated National Drive Intoxicated during the holidays month.
The U.S. is calling for extra political prisoners bound for the U.S. ahead of a religious holiday.
Separately, the U.S. military has announced that the U.S. military will be sent to the U.S. for a religious holiday.
The U.S. military will announce the death of another PR News Washington.
Are you guys having breakfast?
Yeah, I'm hungry.
Very cool.
Frosted Flakes.
You guys know Philo?
No.
Philo?
Yeah, remember that guy?
Is he that guy that's eating Frosted Flakes and beer in the other room?
Sugar Frosted Flakes and beer?
Uh-huh.
Philo.
No Wow.
You'll hit her when you eat her!
You'd better be careful though not to hurt yourself.
Ariel?
Ariel, is this your bedtime?
Aloha!
What do you think about December 21st, 2012?
I'm hoping that I'll be there to see.
Wow, good answer.
Good answer.
Yeah.
I think it's going to be horrible, and I'm really looking forward to it.
Well, I'm not so sure that it's going to be so bad.
It will be great.
It'll be a tropical paradise.
Everybody in the world will be like that guy.
What's the one where the meteorite hits the earth and they have a great New York gets drowned section?
And everybody's screaming and writing this stuff, and there's one guy down by the fountain who's reading the papers.
The wave is coming.
Yeah.
Doesn't even notice.
No, he does.
He's just like, I'm going to enjoy this.
He gets blown away.
You can see him in a few frames getting swooshed out of the picture by the wall of water.
But everybody else is running and screaming.
He's like, I like the New York Times.
I finally get a chance to read this paper.
My wife never let me read the paper.
Well, well, well.
You know, it's great to talk about.
He's talking about Obama now.
Now he's in love with Obama.
I did manage to go and see Avatar.
Obama.
I would certainly sing its praises.
You've got to go down and see it.
What did you think?
Giant 3D.
Was it like a rave?
Was there any surprises in it?
Is it good enough to see twice?
Yes, it's good enough to see multiple times, I think.
In fact, it's like nothing else I've ever seen before.
Unfortunately, it's the future of movies.
It's the way movies are going to be in the future.
Because this new 3D process is so inclusive.
You are right there.
And you're on the plane.
You're on the planet.
Absolutely.
I'll let my parents know.
They spent six years making this movie.
It's a special 3D that was actually developed by James Cameron.
That's a lot of money.
They give you giant glasses that are large enough to cover your glasses if you wear glasses.
That's true.
That movie's worth more than some countries.
But giant glasses also are nice to get so your field of vision is not restricted by a cheap little...
It's true.
It's worth more than most of the countries in the world.
Think how much food that would be for, say, Africa.
The movie's interesting in many ways.
Yeah, it's about a lot of donuts.
It's about a lot of ways.
And it's also...
I think that Cambridge, rather than food, would rather have a really awful DVD, you know, SVA's copy of...
Like the shot in the theater?
Avatar.
What I'm trying to say about it is that you'd be interested in it because it's a deliberate retread of Custer and a deliberate retread of Vietnam.
I don't even know her.
They mix all this history together.
The natives riding their six-legged horses are really very amorous in their eyes.
They're all in their own way.
Yeah.
And you're...
That's so sexy.
And among them is quite interesting.
Yes, they are sexy for 15 feet tall blue individuals with...
It's a 50s record.
With prehensile tails.
It's really good.
Except these tails are really a nerve trunk at the end of which are genitalia or nerve endings.
Nice.
I wish I could have that.
Genitalia.
It's a mind blower.
It's not three hours or whatever.
It zips by.
Somebody called...
Oh.
Somebody called me earlier and said he saw it twice already.
Which I think is really unfair because you took a seat from somebody else who hasn't
seen Avatar yet.
Yeah, you know, that's all right.
It's not hurting you.
There's people waiting to learn if you got your seat.
I did actually take it in with K-Rob who's no fan of James Cameron.
Get out of line and let me in there.
Yeah, K-Rob and Hal walk up and they just push people out of the line and get in.
See, that's my seat.
Not at all.
But we did buy our tickets in advance because the press of humanity rushing in seemed to
crush into chaos the possibility of even the rudiments of...
You remember when they were like shooting the gas canisters?
Gas canisters?
I thought that was...
Oh.
Yes, they gassed the natives.
They did all sorts of bad things to the aliens.
But the gas canister like falls to the floor of the jungle and bounces toward the camera.
And both times I saw it, I had to move my head quickly.
It looks like it's coming at you.
But what's really amazing is it all seems to be surrounded by...
It's not surrounding you, not in front of you.
I don't know who it is.
That's the amazing and immersive effect.
That's what my cat does.
But some critics I think are right to be a little weary of...
Was there somebody there?
I don't know what's happening.
I'm so confused.
It might be that all movies are going to have to be like this from now on.
Honey, I think there's someone in the house.
And it might be threatening movies as they exist.
Everything has to be 3D and everything that isn't 2... that's only 2D will be old fashioned
instantly.
But I want to see the air blurs and the lights.
I want to see the story in 3D.
I remember the old days when this show was about fopping.
There's an angel's voice of being sued by...
What happened to those days?
That was a long time ago.
...by a secretive organization known as the Children's Bible Hour.
This show used to be about something people could believe in.
I can out-prop Jesus any day.
More deadly than the Communist Party, the Masons, or any secret society...
We didn't fool around with these pointy-tointicle rules the old days.
...the Children's Bible Hour deals ruthlessly with its opponents.
Back in my day...
And although Bertha Trover shooks the immortal aunt of the
world, Bertha of radio and recording fame is no longer among the living.
She still watches over the entire enterprise from her roost in heaven...
She could tie one on with the best of them in her day.
Well, that's what they say, but that was before she got the Lord.
Before she got religion.
Before she did those nude scenes in Playboy.
Shelley Winters could play Aunt Bertha.
Boy, that would be a nice one to have.
A nice picture of you to have for me.
Kathy Bates.
Yes, Kathy Bates.
She could certainly do it.
She could.
She has shown herself to be a trooper in more than one motion picture.
Well, maybe we should go back to the past and then go forward into the future here.
Into the past I fly at last to dwell again amidst the golden days.
But look at me again and find instead a savage world's primordial displays.
Indeed.
And I like that.
That's good.
So, in other news, a large blimp-like beanie was seen hovering in the sky.
Or maybe that was just me.
Kind of an utmost...
Oh, about the Kremor?
Did you see the one about the Kremor?
Would I?
Should I?
I did already.
I had all night for my journals.
Oh, I thought you were afraid that I would read from your journals if you left them
there.
No, I read them out to all of Northern and Southern California.
It was very liberating.
Well, fortunately, there should be a recording of this show.
No one is going to really care.
Well, you never know about that.
There are the fans, God bless them.
I mean, if I left them in the closet, you know.
Oh, that's very stylish.
That's very charming.
Thanks, Kim.
I like it.
Oh.
I could.
Now I like it even better.
With the flower.
I have to go to bed, honey.
Flower.
I'm tired now.
Go to bed.
Well.
I'm going to bed, too.
Good night, darling.
I'm unfortunate.
Good night, honey.
I love you guys.
Love you, too.
Say you've got the automobile.
I had a good time.
You're going to drive away.
SLB.
See you.
Love you.
Bye.
As the ducks quack in the dawn.
I love you, too.
Love you.
Over the swamp.
Love you, too.
Love you.
Bye.
Good night.
Love you.
Me, too.
I'll think about you, too.
Don't let the bed bug spike.
Don't eat the apple.
Oh, no, I won't.
Sorry.
If I do, I'll just wait for you so we could eat it together.
Good night.
I have to make some peanuts.
Oh, dear.
You've done this.
Do it.
People are out there.
When you're surrounding yourself with people, you're not alone.
A lot of strange characters out on the streets these days.
Someone was telling me that they were going to go see, on Facebook, they said they were
going to go see Avatar on mushrooms.
That is almost not necessary, but I wondered what that would be like.
Yeah.
At the time.
I do think that the Brow should hustle himself down there because the whole...
Did you see it in IMAX?
...re-do of America's Finest Moments is expertly mixed with...
Yeah.
...social criticism of various recent political developments and things that we're doing
right now.
It's funny, all of his movies have this kind of human versus technology theme to them.
Well, there is a tension because he also is on the side of the military as, you know,
stylistically, although he realizes that they are bad.
And it's a paean to nature and to the beauty of unspoiled worlds, which is made really
with the latest scientific gadgetry.
The most unnatural thing that can be conceived.
And you'll notice that some of the natives, they needed some of the technology like grenades
and...
Sure, they picked it up.
Yeah.
But that's what natives do, if it's crazy not to pick it up.
If it's there, but we really messed up their planet anyway, it was wonderful to be on that
planet.
That's why I would want to go back.
They were blue Smurfy cats.
I missed that.
That's why they're there.
Why are they gone?
They were blue Smurfy cats.
They are definitely.
You're going to be right.
with a lot of things you can't in this world.
They were larger.
They're 15 feet tall,
but then also you can fall longer distances
and you can ride those flying dragons
that would never get off the ground here.
But does the rate of the rotation of the planet
make any difference as to how the gravity is?
I mean, like if it's a slower rotation,
does it have less centrifugal force
and therefore less gravity?
That's what I wonder about.
I had to mention the movie,
but that doesn't mean that we have to talk about it all night.
However, I will defend it against its detractors.
It's clearly an amazing step forward.
I was astonished.
Yeah, it is astonishing.
Yeah.
That it's so vivid and so beautifully conceived.
And, uh...
More power to it.
I'm just afraid that now a lot of inferior movies like it will appear.
There are some properties that could certainly be done.
We're certainly anticipating Edgar Rice Burroughs'
A Princess of Mars with those six-legged...
Oh, yeah.
The height of the blue people
is similar to the height of Burroughs' Green Martians,
but there's no reason why any script
can't be made.
Yeah.
Well, it's certainly...
Not that it wasn't always possible through artistry.
Individual handmade artistry could duplicate it,
but it would be, you know,
it would be prohibitive, certainly.
Wasn't Ray Harryhausen very...
He took a very dim view of the CGI and...
Uh, on over-reliance on it,
but he actually likes it.
But his intention is to make stuff by hand.
Yeah.
You know, you get a satisfaction
if you're photographing what's really there.
But I think it can be just as complicated
to do it on the computer, you know,
even though it's not physical.
It takes as much artistry, I think.
Yes.
Well, there is a lot to figure out about that,
but you see, when one is actually struggling
with the reality of a dimensional object,
happy accidents make sense.
They may occur.
While if you plan everything from the beginning,
everything is totally under control.
There you go.
Inspiration may be present and driving it on,
but the incidental inspiration,
which we see in most works of art,
would not naturally occur.
It would have to be duplicated in some way.
This certainly doesn't mean you couldn't do it,
but it does mean that there are a lot of
prick falls and holes and mine shafts to worry about.
But I think...
I think there could...
Well...
There could be happy accidents and using...
Like, Stang had that...
You could get stung by a bee.
Yeah.
Yes, your outlook could change.
And then, of course, that would warp the creation.
But, on the other hand,
one does not necessarily know everything
or even bring everything that one does know to the work.
You certainly need to look outside yourself
and your...
pixel by pixel universe
in order to gain the basic inspiration
to maneuver there.
Well, as a subgenius,
I'm certainly on the lookout for good mistakes.
Learn well.
Then we will see if your insanity can be cured.
I think I'm gonna die.
Do you want to hear a story?
I think I heard this...
this homeless guy's review of Avatar.
It's about three minutes.
Well, why don't you start spinning that particular platter?
OK.
I seem to be here on the bridge.
Everything's slanted over
and puzzling evidence has disappeared.
I think he took an escape pod.
And now it's time for Bum Reviews
with Chester A. Bum.
Tonight's review...
Avatar.
Oh my god, this is the greatest movie I've ever seen in my life!
I see.
Spoilers!
There's this bald boy who can control the wind.
Oops, wrong avatar.
Oh my god, this is also the greatest movie I've ever seen in my life!
There's this guy who lives in the future, and he has lost his legs!
I lost my legs once!
Oh wait, there they are.
So they send him to a planet filled with blue Smurf people!
Only they're not little Smurfs.
These guys are friggin' huge!
And look a lot like Garfield.
So the business people are like,
We have to move these Smurfy cats because they're standing on top of this rock that's worth like a bajillion dollars.
And the military is like,
Blow stuff up!
Sounds like my hamster.
So this guy with no legs is put inside a Smurfy cat's body,
and he has to convince the other blue Smurfy cats to leave!
I know what that's like!
People are asking me to leave all the time!
Hey, if a dog can urinate at a children's playground, why can't I?
Savages.
So he meets up with a female Smurfy cat,
who's the daughter of a king and a female spiritual leader.
Well, one of them are dead.
And she's also betrothed to this other guy!
Yeah!
Yeah, he's dead too.
Most people who are betrothed at the beginning of movies are often dead.
That's how most Disney movies work!
I mean, not Disney movies work.
So the guy with no legs gets to learn the ways of these Smurfy cats,
but the big bad military,
along with the big bad corporation,
want to tear their village down!
But the scientists are like,
No, no, you can't do this!
Why?
Because the trees have some kind of energy,
and they can communicate with the energy,
and this energy will change the world!
Puh!
Who do you think you are, some kind of scientist?
Yes!
You think we pay you millions of dollars,
to tell the truth?
Yes!
And you think that because you have a brilliant mind,
and years of loyal experience,
that we're going to listen to you?
Yeah!
Well, we're not!
Why?
Because we're the big bad military,
along with the big bad corporation!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
That makes no sense!
Squash them!
Click!
No!
The Smurfy cats!
So the guy with no legs goes back in the Smurfy cat body,
and they get all the other Smurfy cats together!
So the big bad military come in to wipe them all out,
with their machine guns,
tanks,
giant robots,
and flying death machines!
But it's okay,
because the Smurfy cats have bows and arrows!
Of course!
And they also use all these other alien animals to destroy them!
Because if there's anything we've learned in the past,
it's that mankind is no good at destroying other species!
We suck at it!
I mean, did you see Return of the Jedi?
We came and wiped out Ewoks!
An entire empire destroyed by teddy bears!
Support our troops against Smurfy cats and teddy bears!
They are deadly!
So the Smurfy cats send all the humans back to their planet,
and the guy with no legs,
officially,
becomes a Smurfy cat himself!
I always felt like a Smurfy cat trapped in a man's body!
Don't we all?
And the moral of the story is,
anything that is human is evil!
And anything that is not human is...
not evil.
Hooray!
So I really liked Ferngully,
Pokerhunt is,
Atlantis the Lost Empire,
Dances with Wolves,
Avatar,
the most original movie I've ever seen in my life!
I mean, that James Cameron is a genius!
He took an idea that often made horrible children's films,
and turned it into a billion dollar,
epic!
I wanna see him remake some of my favorite children's classics!
The Tom and Jerry movie must be retold!
With green bear booms!
This is Chester E. Booms saying,
CHANGE!
YOU GOT CHANGE!
Oh, come on, have a guy out, will ya?
Come on, change!
Well, can you at least help me buy a blue Smurfy cat?
Or are you afraid he might urinate in front of a children's playground, too?
The best review ever!
Uh,
I'm a little bit scared.
I'm not afraid of, uh, Avatar,
uh, from a funny website called,
thatguywiththeglasses.com,
also known as Doug Walker.
Now, the news.
From PR News in Washington,
I'm a fairly lackluster, heavy, slight, unacceptable, straight, largely lawless critic this morning.
President Obama says,
Uh, I am greatly worthy of support.
Uh,
At least four people are dead,
and more than a dozen injured after yet another PR News from Washington.
At least four people are dead, and more than a dozen injured after yet another PR News from Washington.
Uh,
they're dead.
workings
The world was ever seen.
you know, along with the rest of the United States,
coming to them.
You know, now that the 20th century is over.
Put a smile in your smoking.
A-s-a-p-i-n-i-s-a-r-i-a-s-l-a-r.
Smoother.
Hi, Bob.
Cooler.
Check it out.
Best for you.
Oh, I see.
Well, that's too bad.
Good evening.
As you have already guessed,
tonight's show illustrated man's inhumanity to man,
his indestructibility in the face of obstacles,
the senselessness of war,
the need for a dream,
the value of spiritual action to combat the lust for profit,
and finally, the corrosion of life,
the depletion of energy,
and the frustration of love,
which result from following a...
a philosophy of romantic opportunism in an idealistic society.
Naturally, we don't believe any of that.
Good night.