Your mind is my mind.
Your every thought is my thought.
What I tell you to do, you will do.
What I tell you not to do, you will not do.
No.
No, stay where you are.
For this is a time of slack.
This is the slack hour.
Why what, my boy?
Why must you humiliate me in public like this?
I didn't mean to humiliate no one, son.
But, caller, that's his job.
I'm not even actually present.
But if I were, I would not humiliate you.
Dr. Howell is the friend of all humanity.
His humiliation exists solely within himself.
Now, you know, son,
modern electronics can reliably count small numbers of electrons
down to a single number.
A single particle.
So if one electron is ripped from the outer shell of each atom,
then the electrons are counted,
the number of atoms will be known,
and then lasers can be used
as versatile and efficient guns
for knocking electrons out of atoms.
Only the method is not in these bits selected.
Select gun now.
If one climbs the food chain
and loses all threats to existence,
does he wither?
No.
The question may also be an evolutionary strategy,
perhaps of our genes,
to increase their concentration in the gene pool of humans.
And are we not the constructs
used by those at Galactic Center
to learn of the universe
and bring back a recording in 2012?
Until then, remember,
the clowns at the circus, they're real funny.
This is...
The Soul Genius Hour of Science.
I'd advise you to continue to cooperate.
If it is a good recording,
i.e., makes sense, works, is efficient,
such as a gene for sacrificing oneself
to let live two or more fertile phenotypes
carrying that same gene.
But we constantly,
and in best human action typically,
diverge, converge, merge, emerge
as new unleashed beings.
the sun, but not new under the sun.
Yeah, that's right, dear friends.
Nothing new under the sun, except that this is the all-new subgenius hour of Slack.
Unmatched, which means it's almost as good as the competition, with incredible design
simplicity.
Costs cut to the very bone.
Foolproof operations.
Satisfaction guaranteed and microprocessor controlled.
However, the Church of the Subgenius and KNON are not responsible for fractures of interdimensional
consciousness, cellular, oral incontinence, nor personal violence resulting from close
contact with the macroverse of pain and retribution, which is this show and this church.
Remember, always sit at least 25 feet away from your receiver for maximum subliminal
penetration.
We remind you that recording the Subgenius Radio Ministry is a federal crime punishable
by a fine of not less than $10,000 and a minimum prison sentence of not less than 15 years.
A reproduction by digital, cassette, wire, video, heliograph, Xerox, or interocitor recorder
is forbidden by law.
Right?
Yeah, I know you heard me.
I know you heard me on that one, dear friends.
It was an accident.
Kill pigs dead.
Kill them.
Ba ba ba ba ba ba
Ho la la la la la
Sing it with me now
Ba
Kills big dead
Woo
Ba
Kills big dead
Kill big dead
Ba
James Green said
Friends, Bob does kill pinks dead.
I'm afraid he really does.
And I've got proof of it right here.
In fact, it's the proof that we've been waiting for all this time.
I'll let the Reverend Gino Saad's music run in the background here
while I read to you this amazing clipping we got
from a member, a subgenius minister in England.
Reverend Annie McGrath sent us her change of address
and also a photocopy of this article,
this completely straight and dead serious article, friends,
from the Bedford on Sunday Times.
I think I ought to do this without.
Music.
From the Bedford on Sunday Times.
And it's got a photograph printed here.
It's a picture of a wall on which is spray-painted Bob's face,
a nice stencil of J.R. Bob Dobb,
with kind of crossed bones underneath it,
and then hand-sprayed on.
It says, Bob is slack,
a standard subgenius graffitis that one sees, you know, in most major cities.
And a little caption underneath, Bob is slack.
Not the end.
Innocent graffiti.
It originally seemed to be.
The headline is,
Satanic sect shows its face.
And the best part of this is the date is July 6th, 1992,
the day after X-Day.
That was the day that this article appeared,
just by coincidence, perhaps.
But these folks are serious, I believe,
and they say here,
a secret religious sect,
which claims to have,
conjured up the Gulf War,
is infiltrating Bedford.
What was thought to be a harmless pavement graffiti of a man's face,
is actually a sketch of the sect's founder,
Bob Dodds.
That's Bob Dodds.
Now we know his real name.
Who now calls himself a high priest.
The magician's genius is a sect from America,
which is growing in size in Britain.
It is believed the main target is,
adolescence.
The sect's doctrine and practices are mainly unknown,
but members did claim to have conjured up the Gulf War in February,
91,
according to the Independent newspaper.
I'd sure like to get a copy of the Independent.
The word slack,
used under some of the stenciled art,
is a description of a power of the human race,
lost thousands of years ago.
Slack is a power which maintains the tranquility of the race.
They got that part right.
The artist,
or,
artists responsible,
have not been found.
It is a clear sign there is an active unit of the sect operating in Bedford.
Followers hold believers meetings in their homes,
and during the day,
carry out normal,
everyday jobs.
The sect concentrates on supernatural powers and beliefs,
which other Christian denominations term as satanic and evil.
Bedfordshire on Sunday,
reported last week,
how the face of Bob was peering up from a number of pavements across Bedford.
The design is used to publicize the image of the sect.
In other adult comic magazines,
the symbol is printed in the small advertisement section,
asking people to send one pound for more information.
A man who said his identity as a follower of the sect must be kept secret said,
quote,
this graffiti is intended to grab people's attention.
The design slips into your subconscious and will emerge when people learn more about the sect.
Dear friends,
I have been waiting for twelve years to get a clipping like that.
And, of course, we've run a thousand copies of it.
It'll be a part and parcel of all membership packs from now on.
It's proof, dear friends,
it's as good as the time the San Francisco Chronicle reported that the mass media,
the Macintosh virus,
was a result of this evil sect started by this J.R. Bob Dobbs,
who was unfortunately assassinated and killed.
And see, it's in news, it's in print now,
that Bob Dobbs was a man who was killed in January of 1984.
What they never bothered to print is that he was resurrected about six months later.
But, well, that's another part of the story, friends.
Someone left the radio station on.
I'll just sit down and broadcast for Jesus.
Now, you know that Yehob in the old greasy book was turned into a pillar of coal by Jehovah One
because he pisseth against the wall.
And when they were done, it so happened that came unto them the fishers of three wallets,
who were the Abhag-i,
and they moved into the land of Grunthor,
where there is Bdilium and the Onyx Stone.
I hope you like this story, boys and girls.
If you would like a free picture of me in compromising positions,
write to Aunt Bertha,
dial a picture,
Box 1, Grand Rapids, Michigan,
848-445.
Goodbye, now.
Goodbye.
Hey, what?
That flash, that light.
It disappeared.
What was that?
Well, it was somebody in here.
It kind of looked like just a flash of light shaped like an old lady.
But that organ music, hey, is this ever corny.
What's going on around here?
Yeah, whew.
Now, get that organ music off.
You know, it's almost that.
That's KPFA.
Hey, you smell that old lady like perfume?
Where'd that come from?
Oh, yeah, a little bit of Dr. Howell and puzzling evidence there from the KPFA Berkeley Subgenius show.
It's so nice that they send us tapes of that show,
and when the Swingin' Love Corps is cut off, I can cut them on again,
because they, too, send those tapes.
What is your captain?
I have many questions.
You wouldn't hit a coward now, would you?
God, not only have I lost my mind, I've lost my calm.
You're like a question machine.
Watch out. He's probably on his fourth tranquilizer by now.
My pants are haunted! My pants are haunted!
But you just remember this, and don't you ever forget it.
When you see me walking down the street in my elevator shoes,
remember it was you that did it.
Shazam.
From PR News in Washington, I'm flying on a U.S. passport.
A small community in central Arkansas is in ruin
after President Obama's election.
President Obama tore through it last night.
At least one woman was killed when Mr. Obama hit her home
about 80 miles north of Little Rock.
The White House says the president flattened several buildings,
toppled power lines, and overturned vehicles.
President Obama's were also reported in other parts of Arkansas last week.
Meanwhile, President Obama continues to creep toward land,
ready to help battle PR News.
The left-leaning president says he's shooting for total state control.
If you didn't mail in your census form,
you may very well get exploded tomorrow.
But aides are not saying exactly what time.
Legitimate census workers will ask people for bank account numbers.
Chinese authorities are interrogating an airline passenger
who told a plane crew that he had PR News in his Washington.
Music, religion, pills, beer, smoke, all rise.
Boy wise.
But that's not the end of the story.
Let's continue our journey.
On the cutting edge of what you call growing like a good man,
slamming to not good,
frustration is worse than paranoia.
It's the only world we've seen where this is the case.
The only world we've seen where this is the case.
You grunt until all your grunting is done.
The best I've heard all day, recurring events we already knew about.
It's not different.
It's difficult to retain your slack.
What is the opposite of emergency anyway?
Pizza, calzone, panzerotti, burgers, wings, shawarma, curry, bok choy, ribs, steaks, potato, pasta.
That was The Psychoskeletons as found in the wild at soundclick.com slash thepsychoskeletons.
Praise Reverend Story.
We're busy here gearing up for X Day, July 5th when the world ends and we have a big party.
Also, we've been creating new, for once authorized,
subgenius foundation Facebook page.
And we have Starwood coming up right after X Day on the escape vessels.
So, as you hear, this episode of Hour of Slack, number 1257, is part old and part new.
That new was, of course, by the aforementioned Psychoskeletons and the great Mr. Lee Murr,
who also did PR News and the titles.
And before that, there was a little...
Collage by Mr. Rection.
And the old is mostly from Hour of Slack number 371 from 1992.
But with the obsolete and outdated parts militantly smashed and replaced with a juicy sermon
by Papa Joe Mama from a devival in 2002 in Tampa.
Or was that in Indianapolis?
Or...
Tucson?
No, not Tucson.
Anyway, this is that sermon.
And friends, I love just how evil and sick and incorrect politically is that man,
Father Joe Mama!
Wait! Wait! Wait!
The sermon for the John L. Cornell community.
Yes, dear friends, it is true.
The truth hurts.
And our good friends, I think it's fair to say, if there's a single ally in the world that we love more than any other,
it's probably got to be...
Al-Qaeda.
And they have a saying over there, friends, and it goes like this.
He who tells the truth should keep one foot...
In the...
Europe.
Now, when he's talking about gynecology, I don't know.
On to the sermon.
The sermon tonight is entitled...
Reparations.
Because there has been a recent movement afoot to sue various companies, if not the government itself,
for slavery in the 1800s and before.
Lawyers figure if they could work around the...
Statute of Limitations and collect four billion for the internment of World War II Japanese,
and then sidestep the century-old Swiss banking laws to squeeze out another four billion for Jews who lost their account numbers,
then some schmuck, some schmuck should be able to extract a few billion more from the powers that be
for the kidnapping, rape, and enslavement of various African ancestors.
So tonight, we're going to examine this controversial topic.
And consider the true ramifications in regard to this man, Bob.
Of course, any subgenius worth their salt can tell you that slavery, the ramifications for slavery,
are, to put it charitably, a joke.
It's nothing more than a smokescreen to camouflage the conspiracies, ongoing enslavement of the masses today.
Today!
Do I hear praise Bob?
Praise Bob!
Attention all humans!
Stand by for an important revelation.
People do not go to work on a volunteer basis.
They are compelled to go.
And show up, hat in hand,
begging to serve their conspiracy masters,
or else they starve in the streets!
Oh sure, you can call it employment,
and come up with all sorts of fancy, soundy names like free enterprise and capitalism if you want.
But make no mistake about it, it's still slavery, plain and simple.
Only now, my friends, they've repackaged it and put it in a new container.
Now it's wage slavery.
Yes, because the conspiracy eventually realized a very important little point.
They realized that it's always cheaper to rent than it is to own.
And we all know how they love to cut costs.
Do I hear praise Bob?
Praise Bob!
Praise Bob indeed!
The old time slaves, my friends, they were never paid for their work.
Oh, that difference is true.
But they were also given the bare necessities of life so that they could survive.
Food, clothing, shelter.
Wage slaves, however, they're given little pieces of paper,
which they're told are quite valuable,
but which the conspiracy in fact mass produces like toilet paper!
Then, those same workers are expected to turn around and fork over much of that same little pieces of paper,
so that they can buy the same necessities that they used to be given for free!
Oh!
Plus, they're also expected to give another 20 or 30 percent for taxes!
For what?
To the conspiracy in order to control their lives!
Yeah!
Oh!
And if anyone refuses to pay the conspiracy its tax,
what happens?
It's off to the big house!
The house of pain!
Free enterprise indeed!
But now, now there's always a certain percentage,
and we all know them too well, don't they?
They're made to be celebrities!
We're supposed to respect these certain workers that work for their slave masses so much
that they earn extra pieces of paper.
They're allowed to retire and stop working
to serve as motivational examples for the rest of society!
If we work really,
really hard,
then we also,
we also might be able to retire.
And, we're told, if we follow the rules,
be just like them!
Better yet,
if we really make it,
oh, and this part's great, friends,
we'll be able to rent our own slaves!
That's right!
Then we'll be just like Pinky!
We'll be able to afford our own servants!
Incredible,
but so, so true.
Yeah.
Yet, you see, friends,
the sad fact is
that money doesn't really matter.
Possessions doesn't really matter.
The only thing in life that really matters
is life itself.
We're all given only so much of it,
and the moment it's gone,
we die.
And no more free minutes.
The conspiracy,
the conspiracy knows us
and can't stand the realization
that they were given the same amount of time
as the rest of us.
So what do they do?
They immediately set out
and devise new ways
in order to capture,
take away,
and control all the free time of others!
Yes, my dear friends,
that is how slavery began.
And they started to use it
so that they could get more goods
and services at the expense of others,
the so-called servant class.
Oh, a little problem occurred, though.
Over time, they started to realize
that slavery was more expensive
than it might otherwise be,
so they devised this new
rent-a-slave concept.
Ha ha.
And it also had an added benefit.
There were no more escapees.
Remember that?
A few people might run away.
This way, with rent-a-slaves,
if they disappear,
another one quickly shows up
to take their place.
Ha ha ha!
In fact, they'll even compete
for their privilege!
Incredible!
And yet, that's the beauty
of their system.
It's a much more easier
and efficient way to do it, isn't it?
And best of all,
the slaves don't even realize
they are being controlled.
Oh, how that must have seemed
like the days of Camelot to the Khan.
The golden age of domination and power!
But then something terrible
happened, my friends.
A leader appeared,
who demanded in a thundering voice,
to let my people go!
His name wasn't Moses,
although he spoke with the authority
of Jehovah One.
His name wasn't Harriet Tubman,
although he ran an underground railroad
to freedom.
No, sir, his name was, is,
and shall ever be,
J.R. Bob Doe!
And he won't rest
until the very last of genius is free.
Will you give me a praise, Bob?
Praise Bob!
Now, if the African Americans
wish to legitimize slavery
by accepting a monetary payment
for the past,
that's their business.
Then the Khan will print up
more pieces of paper,
hand it over, and brag,
well, then, now that closes
the books on slavery,
we said we were sorry,
and promised never to do it again.
Weak, weak.
So, uh, stop complaining,
and get on back to work.
Now, if that's not bad enough,
my friends,
there are some pink conspiracy whores
who have even gone so far as to say
that the blacks should be thankful
for slavery.
They joke amongst themselves
that the lucky ones were captured,
domesticated, and transported
to a civilized nation that offers
social programs like five years,
five and higher long years of welfare.
Oh, aren't they so fortunate.
And if they were back in Africa,
they sneer.
The Negro might be starving
or swatting flies
or waiting to contract AIDS.
Oh, but now he just follows the rules,
cheers plenty of pink little butt,
and doesn't cause any trouble.
He'll get a warm place to sleep
and a loose pair of shoes.
The arrogance.
The outrage.
Oh, how the conspiracy could even dare
to think such things.
That should be all the proof that we need
that you cannot compromise with the con.
No, sir.
These aren't rational beans.
They're monsters,
and they only understand one thing.
One thing,
and that's brute force.
Bob Dobbs knows this better than anyone else.
Yes, my friends,
and he's going to make sure
that he doesn't settle
for such a cheap cop-out.
No, sir.
The subgenius race
will not accept a settlement
for the past or the present.
We refuse a presidential apology.
And we will not accept the pink,
oh, we're so sorry, pink guilt platitudes.
We can't toss out words
and they won't be permitted to just say,
oh, we're sorry and throw money our way
and then claim to be paid in full.
No, sir.
We demand payment
in a more precious commodity,
one that they could relate to, perhaps.
For every lifetime taken,
we expect one to be forfeited
plus interest.
Now, I'm not saying whether that means
the conspiracy slave masters
and their overseers
must be euthanized
or made slaves themselves our next day.
That is, after all,
a question that evangelicals
and Holocausters
are still trying to sort out.
But I will say this.
All subgeniuses agree on this one premise,
and that is this.
We will never forgive and forget.
Do I hear a praise bob?
Praise Bob!
Praise Bob, indeed.
The conspiracy is not the only one.
Bob is the only one
who can hire certain bill collectors.
Bob Dobbs is bringing the entire fleet
of them here to Earth on X-Day.
And on that fateful day, my friends,
at 7 a.m.,
he's going to unleash the entire force
on the conspiracy.
Ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho.
Yes, the pinks will then know
the true meaning of Bob's pipe
as they struggle and scramble
to pay the piper.
We, on the other hand,
will finally have our chance
to truthfully look towards the heavens
and sing in unison,
free at last, free at last.
Praise Bob, almighty.
We're free at last.
Here is the word of Bob.
Praise Bob.
Amen.
We just had someone call in
a little while ago
with a pertinent question,
a question which I can answer.
This poor child,
I know this sounds like a line
you've heard on a subgenius revival before,
but this poor child actually called up
and said, well, she didn't ask if Bob was dead.
She said, Reverend Stang, is Bob immortal?
And one thing that our new book is going to do
is clear up a number of misconceptions.
And misconception number one,
is that Bob is dead.
That is an absolute misconception.
It's a lie, a black lie.
Of course, they started making accusations
that the inner circle had murdered Bob
to get power ourselves.
And of course, finally,
we had to tell everybody that Bob wasn't real
so he couldn't be dead.
And since he wasn't real, he was immortal,
and that's a lot better than real.
And even Bob liked that one, friends.
But you want to know just how dead is Bob.
And you'll be glad to learn
if you haven't the unquestioning faith before
that J.R. Bob Dobbs is completely undead
and undead for good.
You may already have heard that J.R. Bob Dobbs
was allegedly shot and killed
on January 21st, 1984
at the Victoria Theater in San Francisco.
You may not know that it happened again
in Los Angeles in 1985,
in rural Arkansas in 1986,
in St. Louis in 1988,
and in Atlanta in 1992.
Now, according to Dobbs' own account,
after each bungled resurrection or assassination,
and or assassination, same thing in his case,
he was immediately dispatched back to hell.
But he repeatedly lucked his way out of hell,
winning the Hell Gladiator Games,
beating the devil at poker,
even digging his way to the surface.
Although he was re-killed and sentenced
even deeper into hell,
after each breakout or reincarnation,
the daring escapes still proved humiliating to Satan.
When, finally, Dobbs out-tempted Lucifer
and seduced his wife.
Put horns on the devil, you might say.
It was the last straw and Bob Dobbs was banished.
Banished, dear friends, even from hell itself.
And since he was never baptized,
of course, Bob has never been able to enter heaven either.
So there is nowhere for Bob to go in death now.
It is because Bob was killed so many times,
and yet is banished from all available afterlives,
that he now cannot die.
He can only wait around for X day here on earth
with the rest of us,
at least until he is baptized or Satan forgives him.
I hope that answers any questions.
As we like to say, friends,
curiosity killed the cat,
but loathsome rituals brought it back.
Bob and Lal was all we needed.
But she was lovely and great
and and sweet railing,
andyeong jagars and
andyeong daggeneration!
And see you soon.
Friends, this music you're listening to, instrumental, called Bob.
It's the title of it, Bob.
Done by St. Jay Condom, author of the great P-Dawg comics
and many, many other fine subgenius pieces.
Co-author, in fact, of the Lee Harvey is a Friend of Mine song that so many people love.
This music is on the Zombo Fropland cassette tape.
You'll have to refer to your subgenius catalog for that.
I'll give information on where you can get that at the end of the broadcast, dear friends.
Ah, yes.
But I think it's time for some more text.
This is from the Rudy Schwartz Project.
Once again, Reverend Joe Newman, this time doing this lovely short tune,
An Orange is Nothing But a Juicy Pumpkin.
Nine-year-olds that kick you in the shin.
Toilet bowls with droplets on the rim.
Leisure suits with polyester trim.
And an Orange is Nothing But a Juicy Pumpkin.
Pepperoni pizza by the slice.
Ronald Reagan's go-to dinner vice.
Chinese food and bass with a bowl of rice.
And an Orange is Nothing But a Juicy Pumpkin.
Shopping malls on Sunday afternoon.
Watching grandma vomit with a spoon.
Harvard that you're squatting on a broom.
And an Orange is Nothing But a Juicy Pumpkin.
This inspection's pretty red.
Making for a chef will give you head.
Pupsters that are dead.
Rotting in your bed.
And an Orange is Nothing But a Juicy Pumpkin.
An Orange is Nothing But a Juicy Pumpkin.
Your next gold .
iPhone, iPad, mouse, and brush is indeed free And your car's about treatin' now
My dall, quiser this?
Where's your hat?
What do you say?
The
clown on the
Thank you.
Oh, amazing.
Yes, dear friends, and I have to be careful.
What I play on any given...
Did I do that right? Yeah.
Any given old Rudy Schwartz project album,
you do have to be careful what you come up with next.
Wonderful stuff.
In the background right now,
Zooks Rift and a Joe Newman of the Rudy Schwartz project.
Only I think this is on an upcoming Zooks Rift album.
We just wanted to let you know what you're getting into.
You know, we have to be able to say later in court
that we gave you plenty of warning.
I mean, what are you worried about?
This is just a joke church, right?
Oh, those subgeniuses are so funny
with all their paranoid warnings and disclaimers.
Well, here's one coming up.
Here's a paranoid warning and disclaimer
by a German band.
Called Ultimate Klingons.
Their album, The Cloaking Device.
Actually, it's a cassette tape that was handed to me
at the World Subcon by Captain Nancy Darnell,
who is an American subgenius
who's been living in Germany for a long time.
And according to the PR she gave me,
The Cloaking Device is
the turn of the Ultimate Klingons.
Contact me.
I'll be ready.
Thank you.
To the humanoid.
Scalar Technology.
Brain Tech Food Waves.
And here's a good one.
Acclarung der Illuminaten machen Schafen.
So, and Gitarn Alster Wils
in der Kirche of Subgenius.
Bob Dobbs, High Epoch of the Church of the Subgenius.
Uber Day CD.
Dies Band, says Bob,
So Captain Nancy Darnell now and Ultimate Klingons from Cloaking Device will sing to you about the conspiracy.
Them. They. T-H-E-Y.
T-H-E-Y.
I'll write it again.
I'm responsible for everything.
They tell you what to think and they tell you what to do.
They got you going to work, a mind shut and stop.
Watch your TV and you never get enough.
T-H-E-Y.
I'll write it again.
Whoa. Amazing.
The Cloaking Device there, dear friends.
From Germany.
Americans from Germany, you might say.
I'm going to give their address real quick for those typing illegally.
That's Nancy Darnell.
At Briesester.
B-R-I-E-S-T-E-R.
That's all one word.
7-D-1000.
Berlin 44.
Well, now you know.
And, uh, friends, you know, do you realize this religion has only been around for 10 years?
We're just starting out.
We are literally just beginning.
The Mormons have been around for 100 years.
And they only run one minor state and a bunch of Indian reservations.
It took Christianity.
A thousand years to conquer the West.
But look at what a small band of nerdy intellectuals was able to pull off in Russia in 1917.
So, with radio, television, and thousands of computer geeks slaving away for Dobbs,
it shouldn't be long before the Church of the Subgenius is so big that even you would be afraid of it,
as well you should be.
For, just as we can grow faster, we must be even more cautious than the Christians.
We must not allow the word of Bob to be perverted.
We must not allow the word of God to be perverted quite so drastically and get away from us so quickly as that of Jesus.
That's the scariest thing about this.
You'd better be glad most subgeniuses are sloppy no-accounts, slackers, lousy business people,
far more concerned with personal slack than with power or money.
If we had it together as much as the Christians, or even for that matter the O.T.O.,
we'd be bigger than the Nazis by now.
And it's so horrifyingly easy to start a real cult and manipulate a bunch of Indians.
And you know that knowledge has always fallen into the wrong hands.
Now, Dobbs, on the other hand, may have a better chance than Jesus in not getting his message twisted.
Bob is a salesman and not a lowly carpenter, and he has the advantage.
He understands advertising.
Now, Jesus didn't really understand selling a concept.
Bob was able to start his own marketing strategy, not leaving it up to the followers.
Now, whether or not you're a follower of the Church of the Subgenius,
whether Bob is selling the same message as Jesus,
well, we'll just have to find that out on X-Day.
But who else can you trust when the rupture comes?
I mean, we'd be the first to admit that our promises, predictions, dire warnings and stuff sound insane,
but what if they come true?
And that what-if part is what keeps most religious people in line.
But what if hell is real?
That's the only thought that keeps most folks sitting in the pews.
They don't really believe they'll go to heaven or any afterlife.
If they were, sure, they'd jump off a high bridge as soon as they got depressed over bills or something.
But no, they slug their way on through life just in case.
Some subgeniuses may not believe that X-Day is actually gonna happen,
but they damn sure have that $20 membership card in their pockets just in case, don't they?
But we understand, friends.
You may not have the strongest faith that X-Day will happen,
but you're none too sure it won't happen either.
You're just being smart, staying prepared for either outcome.
And that's why we say don't give away all worldly goods before X-Day.
It might not happen.
But leave some-definitely leave some kind of paper, legal paper, stating that in case of rupture,
your property goes to your desired unsaved friends and relatives
and not just any old left-over property.
And that's why you're not gonna be able to get a job.
You're gonna be left behind Christian who wants to move from an empty home.
And besides, will you even want to rupture when Jehovah One throws the cosmic switch?
Oh, many would rather stay, friends, since who knows what fate lies in store once back aboard that wondrous craft.
Oh, you must know!
You must know your destiny!
So don't die without slack, friend.
So be afraid, and think as much as possible about everything that comes your way.
The only wonder is the Pontiff.
Thela Broughrell capitulation,
the neige moral successfulant handing of iphone7
There's aame trial
and embg t sent  kommt
We kche
len caused this checked out
evolution!
Are you ready to pass through
the gates of opportunity,
perceiving the unsullied truth
with no subjective bias?
Are you ready to do
whatever Bob says
to swallow his every
statement, hook, line, and sinker?
Even if he someday tells you
that you, you must push
the button that sends billions
of mostly innocent pinks
to their unbelievably
painful doom?
Hey! Now some may
resist the possibility that
man's purpose may be to do
exactly what he is doing,
blindly pursuing his techno
madness until he wipes
himself out and causes a great
cataclysmic planetary change.
One of those cyclical
rearrangements which the Earth goes through
every few million years.
Now mankind, through Bob,
might be meant
to set off a nuclear holocaust
so terrible that even the mighty
cockroach will be extinct,
leaving nothing alive but blind
albino cave snakes and those
mysterious worms that live
where no other life can survive,
clustered, writhing senselessly
around volcanic heat vents
in the deepest, coldest
depths of the ocean.
Only for the purpose, though, of giving
that lowly heat vent worm
a chance to evolve
into the dominant life
form. Maybe it's just the fulfillment
of natural order. The dinosaur's
got their time. The mammals
have had their time. Maybe next time it'll be
the arthropods. Who's to say?
Only Bob!
Only Bob can say! But you can
rest assured, my friend, that
even if it is Bob's plan,
he at least will still be around,
probably down there with his
pants around his ankles, happily
humping away at a deep-sea volcanic
heat vent.
Oh, will
the pyramid of centuries
then be, in the end,
only a monument
to the vanity
of Bob?
Do you have
any better ideas?
...
morning
a new
ray of hope
for mankind
and your dead men
they are marching
in legions
to end the games
the ropes will
be hung
to speed you up
and your
young people are
leaving
their candles
like campfires
in darkness
to walk in the
sun
and your young
men and her follow
your teachings
now they know
how
you've done
and they've
heard all your
new sighted
preachers
now we
know just what
must be won
and the sweet
white light
flows freely
and clearly
and break the
now while
you can
and
form a great
circle
that shall not be broken
proclaiming
the freedom
of name
that shall not
and the
oh
yes dear friends
quicksilver messenger
service
old-timey old-timey subgeniuses i reckon they are
But you know, every sound like that cough is just a new note in the ongoing Doctors for Bob album that we're all recording right now.
We only sell little tiny sections of it.
Most people don't want to sit through the whole thing.
Unfortunately, we have to.
So give us a worst case scenario.
I mean, what is your ultimate nightmare of the future of the religion?
I mean, we're open for ideas.
How often do you engage in unorthodox sexual practices?
I mean, it's right.
Your body escapes the feast.
Voices fly away.
The night time falls.
Falling off the streets.
Come for now.
Touch me there.
Make the worst.
Insist.
Come for now.
Break the silence.
It's time to break the silence.
It's a sex party.
It's an emotional breakdown.
Oh yeah, that's right. Club No, friends up near Fair Park.
No, I can't.
But I can tell you that you're listening to the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
Oh, actually, what you're listening to is the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
Yo, what I got up there about the subgenius-
Oh, what is that social service?
Oh, a attainment of worship?
Yeah, they're cleansing.
You can click on them and do this, just click on them..
funk
coke
All that goes without saying.
On, we will start the video from the first clip..
..odd..
ordained in the church of the subgenius. I'm about to give you the free
post office box number to write to for information.
This is completely free information. It would help if you threw in a self-addressed
stamped envelope. Just address that to got that pencil ready.
Bob at post office box
181-417-Cleveland Heights, Ohio
44118 and also
see subgenius.com
And before I leave, I'm going to play you a cover version
of a famous old song. This is such an improvement over the original.
I've been wanting to play this for a while. It's Rudy Schwartz Project from his
Don't Get Charred, Get Puffy album.
Oh, you're going to love it. The horrible thing is you'll be humming it
for days. Sorry.
Cracklin' Rosie, get on board.
We're going to ride till there ain't no more to go.
Taking it slow.
Lord, don't you know.
I'll have me a time with a poor man's lady hitching on a twilight train.
Ain't nothing here that I'd care to take along.
Maybe a song.
Sing what I want.
No need to say please to no man for a happy tune.
Oh, I love my Rosie child.
She got the way to make me happy.
You and me, we're going in style.
Cracklin' Rosie, you're a store-bought woman.
And you make me sing like a guitar strumming.
Sing on your radio, girl.
This song is for you.
Oh, he's running home.
Play it now.
Play it now, my baby.
Cracklin' Rosie, make me smile.
You're a rock star.
Girl, if it lasts for an hour.
Well, that's all.
That's all right.
We got all night.
To set the world right.
Find us a dream, but don't ask no questions.
Yeah.
Oh, I love my Rosie child.
You got the way to make me happy.
You and me, we're going in style.
Cracklin' Rosie, you're a store-bought woman.
And you make me sing like a guitar strumming.
Sing like a guitar strumming.
Hang on to me, girl.
This song is running home.
Yeah.
That's awesome.