Instead of making your dollars shrink by investing in United States savings bonds,
why not make them grow with interest by spending needlessly when prices are high?
Here's the way it works.
Seventy-five dollars invested now each month will in ten years turn into an income of one dollar
for as long a period as you forcibly fought forces of evil each month for a fact.
But now...
The Soul Genius!
Our House!
What?
Savings plan.
Meanwhile...
Huh? That's weird.
It's like something out of that Twilight-y show about that soul.
My God.
What is that?
What?
Well, there's my ride.
I got one.
I got one!
I got a spaceship!
They're coming!
Bob!
There's something on the screen!
Yes.
It might be him, but the picture isn't very clear.
My God.
Bob, it's coming right at us.
I can't believe it.
Look at those tentacles.
They're coming!
From outer space, they're coming!
They're gonna enter our atmosphere!
We want the ocean!
We've already been stuck in rock'n'roll!
I've finally returned to Earth from thisendyr parsley crisis.
I think I Matter
I wanna experience As marca Pr trapped,
I want to explore you before I get
Re Christina ...
Knitting all of trader countries.
How to expand your Money général Know keys.
Oh, hello.
Alien? What do you mean, alien?
What do you mean from another planet?
That's a tricky one, isn't it?
Well, if that's the life, don't let them out there, flying saucer.
We don't want a lot of little green men terrorising the home counties during Ask It We Do It, hmm?
Yes, all right. Full emergency.
You hear the news? The three aliens are coming to New York.
One night only, $2,000 a ticket.
We want the aliens! We want the aliens! We want the aliens!
So what are you guys here for, to see flying saucers land? Is that going to happen tonight?
When they arrive, it's going to be the dawn of a whole new civilisation.
Space creatures conspiring with the Soviet government already control our thoughts.
By sending out electrical currents from the top of the Empire's...
State Building. And I'm the only one that knows.
If you're alienated, can you still help children?
Oh, sure. Alienation only affects the mind. It has nothing to do with the rest of your life.
We are going to see more and more of these visitors from space.
And that before too long, the evidence will be in controversial.
That you will have on your TV screens and on your movie screens concrete evidence that the ships are here and that they are real.
They're not fantastic things which have been cooked up to make a movie.
I have made telephones.
I've had telepathic contact for the past eight years with many space people from many areas of space, both inside and outside of the solar system.
Well, this device right here is one that we've used to contact the people in the flying saucers.
It receives the messages on a beam of light and it is in turn translated by this unit and brought out as intelligible voice speech.
You mean to say you actually receive messages from people in flying saucers?
That's right.
How about letting you try it, Dick, and see if I can get something on it?
Receiving transmission from galactic headquarters.
Bobby, there's nothing to be frightened of, man.
On my planet, all of you will be free men not locked away like animals.
Be free.
Find your own happiness.
Is that recording good enough to identify the thing?
Yeah, right.
Ha ha!
Hey, Bob is my only hope.
Back off and give him some more.
There's no room to think.
From that fateful day when stinking bits of slime first crawled from the sea and shouted to the cold stars.
I know I'm on the corner.
Our greatest dread has always been the knowledge of our own mortality.
But tonight, we shall hurl the gauntlet of science into the frightful face of death itself.
Tonight!
We shall ascend into the heavens.
We shall mark the earthquake.
We shall command the thunders.
And penetrate into the very womb of impervious nature herself.
God, please.
Enemy spacecraft, they are capable of 44.
Bob?
Well, he's up there.
Lost in space.
A hook.
I must go, huh?
Yeah, sure, honey.
I must leave this planet at once.
Has anyone seen my spaceship?
He's delirious.
Take me to your leader.
It's gonna be okay, honey.
Just relax.
Everything's fine.
Look, I am not talking to you.
I'm talking to him.
Oh.
She's not a woman.
The Terminator.
You'd better go now, Madge.
I won't go home alone.
Bob will take you.
I don't want to have anything to do with it.
Okay.
What's it for, you people?
I was joking!
Don't you know I'm joking here?
Everything all set for the big party?
We're getting there.
I'm gone.
I'll tell you about it.
Susie here still loves the walker.
Oh, yeah.
Thanks, Frank.
So who's all that ointment for?
They've been screwing us for a long time.
Now it's time we screwed that up.
Oh, Pat.
Ready to go?
Wait, honey.
I travel light.
That's a joke.
It's a bad joke.
You humans.
There's just no sense of humor.
Hey, check.
We're all ready.
Yes, you bet.
He's gonna regret this.
I'll show him.
No, don't go.
You mustn't go up there.
I can't stand this.
But he's a robot.
He wants to take me back to the ship.
It's your old pal, Bernard.
I'm sorry.
The fourth alien.
There is no fourth alien.
I'm here.
Look.
Look at you.
You don't even look like an alien.
Ambrose, will you get rid of this autograph hunter?
No.
Don't.
Honey, help me.
You simpleton.
Don't you understand?
I'm the fourth alien.
Get out.
Some years ago, we were in the habit of sending chimpanzees into outer space.
Someone, somewhere has gone one better.
They're completely worthless.
They know as much about the secrets of the universe as my mother's labradors.
Oh, no.
enemy battle cruiser medusa class configuration length 6,324 feet
28 laser rocket guns their aircraft are so primitive it's no challenge
they're just gonna have to give up they've no choice but to accept all of our demands
army fighter planes are on patrol for flying saucers cameras installed to photograph them
Portland Oregon the area from which came the first weird reports this flying saucer patrol
shows how the air forces while not putting too much stock in the mysterious things in the sky
are investigating the control tower is in touch and on the watch so are a whole lot of people
these days they're seeing flying saucers everywhere blocks of fantastic discs flying
through the air is there something to it or is it an epidemic of people just seeing things
even the goat seems to be looking for the mysterious discs and the bears on the alert
or maybe there's a flying saucer with milk now let's have no more curiosity about this bizarre
cover-up it's an emergency maroon alert or even for a million these are no pinheads from another
planet these are no pea brains from beyond
the earth these are mind suckers
my god haven't any of you seen invasion of the body snatchers no no no no no no no no no no
yes I am I mean no no let's kill him well I've been up all night I've got a real story for you
up to now proof and everything the aliens have landed among us I'm not hot-dogging you we've
gotta start protecting ourselves
they said protect and you survive
but alpha's man didn't score
eight pounds of over
away
so
please
blast it
everybody
the
broad
this
goes
that
look up
it
the
don't
I
I'll take your money with you!
Grab that woman's shot, will you?
Ah, yes, dear friends.
We're swinging and rocking and jazzing and jumping and jiving here.
Live in the studio this time.
It's not a rerun or an old tape.
Although you might think it was a tape from far away and long ago.
Well, it contains elements which have been heard before
under similar circumstances on other programs.
This should not make you think that it is not entirely original,
spontaneous and self-generated.
Here, on the spot, in this pre-X-Day Bobcast.
Well, the extra familiar thing...
was you, Dr. Howland Owl.
Me?
Oh, well, gosh.
They've heard that before, too.
Hi.
Well, I guess I'll have to try to live up to that.
At any rate, yes, I'm here now,
inextricably intertwined with the substance of this program.
We also expect to have familiar voices and guests
during the interval that follows.
Some, in fact, all of whom will be recognizable
to regular listeners of this program.
But he isn't due to call for...
Well, I better not say, because some imposter
could use the special code that way.
If I gave it away one time, they'll all start doing that.
A code in the head.
And I would love to hear somebody try to imitate Dave.
Well...
That could be...
They could...
It's done probably for up to ten seconds.
But it's like Jimi Hendrix, you know.
Lots of people can sound like Jimi Hendrix
for a little while.
Well, it gets hard to riff in character.
Right.
So, yeah, friends, we're all geared up for the...
Well, for X-Day.
The final solution to all of our problems.
Yes.
Thank goodness.
Final frontier, perhaps.
There's plenty of them.
But, yeah, the saucers will be lifting us up
to meet Bob and Glory, or escape Bob in horror.
You never know with Bob.
Never know.
And that's July 5th coming up.
Yes.
Of this year, 1998.
That's after the first 2,520 years of the Gentile rule ends,
according to the Holy Scriptures.
Therefore, God said to the subgenius first,
and then to the Gentile,
so by the same token,
the Lord is telling all subgeniuses
what is going to happen to them
for forsaking the God of the universe
and persisting in their war on God.
Oh, come on now.
You know God must be amused by that,
or he would have struck us...
Well, he would have stricken me dead by now.
Well, God is not in time.
I was the one who was always yelling that phrase.
Mm-hmm.
Sounds good, though.
War on God!
Oh, give me a break.
Really?
Well, you know, you don't have a challenge.
God expects a person to...
To kick back against the traces a little bit.
Should exceed one's grasp.
Or what's a heaven for?
Yes, just so.
And the Lord is not slack concerning his promise,
as we also know.
As much.
And then, no, slackness.
Mm-hmm.
In the elastic waistband of the trousers.
The elastic waistband of heaven.
That's true.
It can expand, but not infinitely.
Many are called, but few are chosen.
Sometimes the elastic waistband of the slacks.
Yeah.
Yes, it's true, but...
Tightness on slacks.
Ah.
Foolish fashion statement
that should fool no one of any greater than average sensibility.
Well, when you first get the elastic waistband,
it's tight.
But as it ages, like so many of us,
it becomes more and more slack.
Well, rubber doesn't have a long life, you know.
It turns leprous and horrible,
like those old animation models.
And our bodies in the same way.
And the werewolf mask from Captain Company
that I got when I was 10, by the time I was 15,
that thing had become slag.
The hair was falling out?
Well, it didn't have hair.
It was a cheap rubber mask.
Rubber over the head.
Well, you see, that's the thing.
The rubber loses its youthful fatality and sloughs off.
And this wasn't class rubber.
Mm-hmm.
I've got some older masks that are, you know,
some masks that have aged quite well for 20 years.
They're still...
They have a better quality of rubber these days.
The full over-the-head animal masks you can buy
in San Francisco's Chinatown, for example.
Those things are still, you know, ones purchased years ago,
still viable.
I bet a whole lot of the radio listeners don't know
or even believe in the bob rubber masks that are now available
from Sick Rick.
Which is not the same as saying Don Post Studios.
No.
Sick Rick is spelled strangely.
It's S-I-K-R-I-K.
That's all the dot com you need to know.
Someone with a speech impediment saying cyclic,
only it's Sick Rick, you see.
Dr. Howell, you've seen those Dobbshead masks, right?
Yes, they are a source of terror and veneration.
Yeah.
He does them in black and white.
They're all hand-painted.
And the black...
I asked for the black and white one first
because I thought it was the most terrifying Dobbshead
I've ever seen.
They're called Dobbsferatu.
Mm-hmm.
Really vampire-like.
And the color one is pretty scary.
And you get them with eyeballs or without.
Well, aren't you supposed to supply your own eyeballs?
But that's all right.
It depends on if you want to use it for display
or as an actual mask.
So have a mannequin head equipped with eyeballs.
And you can display it proudly in your home, den, or rumpus room.
Well, that's right.
You saw that mask at last X Day.
I did see it.
It was an astonishing sight.
That boy that YB Dobbs wore it,
I think maybe you or Philo brought it.
Mm-hmm.
Princess Weeb brought it.
Yes, I remember promises made years ago about...
Yes.
I wasn't there.
I just saw pictures.
...who would wear a Dobbs mask.
It was YB Dobbs that wore it.
They never came about.
Well, it's risky.
Yes.
People shoot at you.
Shhh.
The last person for a long time there to wear one of those
was Mark Mothersbaugh of Devo.
Yes, and look where it got him.
Yeah, he got shot.
He jumped out.
He was terrified.
He was so scared.
It was like a trap door under the stage
that he was supposed to pop out of.
And he'd immediately get shot and go back down.
That was it.
This is a guy who's been doing crazy stunts on stage
for half his life.
And he became terrified.
He was just certain.
His psychic spidey sense, his Devo mutant power
told him that somebody was going to use real bullets
and it'd be an accident.
And puzzling evidence wouldn't remember
which was the blanks and which was the starter pistol
and which was the real handgun.
Right, the Finnish pistol.
Yeah.
As it was, Mark survived after hours of surgery
in the hospital.
But he did survive.
Well, it was all in good, clean fun.
Yeah.
I thought he got someone else to do it.
No, he tried to get my wife, my ex-wife.
That's why I said it that way.
Yeah, Reverend Someone Else.
Yes.
Was her name.
And she was there and she was helping him.
And he said, I don't want to do it.
I don't want to do it.
And she pushed him.
When the cue came, she actually pushed him.
Now it all comes up.
He's not a real big guy, you know.
Hey, what are you doing?
And he pops up.
There's a really bad still of him in that it's a pretty bad mask, too.
And no good video.
However, of course, the first assassination of Bob,
performed by puzzling evidence, is beautifully caught on three cameras.
It has been videoed.
Yes, that's right.
Including the bottling down of puzzling evidence himself.
And everything on the stage is shown and has been studied in great detail.
Much like the Zapruder film.
There have been many talk shows about it.
They pop up and there's clips from all that in Arise.
And I think you see a little bit of some of that in, well, they show it in the feature movie.
They definitely show it in the subgenius documentary film, J.R. Bob Dobbs and the Church.
The Church of the Subgenius.
By the way, I just heard about another film festival it's in.
Montreal, Canada.
What film festival is that?
So they went to Melbourne, Australia.
And what happened there?
They haven't been there yet.
They're doing Galway, Ireland first.
Then Melbourne, Australia.
And then Montreal, Canada.
And this is all in July.
Sandy Boone, the director, is exhausted just thinking about it.
Yes, he certainly is.
He sounds rather exhausted.
Become a foot soldier for Bob.
Trudging from festival to festival.
No, and the funny thing is she's a Christian.
I think she's in a fairly fundamentalist church like Church of Christ or something like that.
I don't know for sure.
She was a Baptist.
A joyful Baptist.
She's very worried about where her congregation is going.
I probably shouldn't be talking about this.
Well.
Some Christians are upset by the way their preacher is supporting it.
You know, it.
Yes, it's true.
But they have been corrupted.
These preachers are corrupt.
They have all gone aside.
They are all of them become filthy.
There is none that doeth good.
No, not one.
Have all the workers of iniquity no knowledge who eat up these people as they eat bread?
There were they in great fear.
For God is in the generation of the righteous.
For example, recently, a bunch of Republicans were booing the words of the president of
Christ when they were quoted about helping the poor and so on, not recognizing their
origin since they are such poor Christians that they're all into this nonsensical prosperity
gospel that they've come up with when in fact the founder of the Christian religion said
over and over again, you can't take that stuff with you.
You know, it's easier to get a camel through the eye of a needle and so on and get your
precious possessions through to the other side.
Through the kingdom of God, only the purest sliver of the soul can be accepted.
All the rest of this stuff is like a millstone around your neck.
So sell all thou hast and give it to the poor as if they're going to do that.
No, instead they'll boo the words of the Nazarene when some plucky individual tries to stop
this disgusting bilge which is fastened like a sucking parasite on the ground.
The religion of peace.
Well said, Dr. Howell.
It's true.
My people are destroyed for lack of knowledge.
And one part of the knowledge that they lack is the origin of that phrase, the needle's
eye.
It was in fact a kind of gate used in bazaars in the Middle East that was narrow for people
to walk in and out freely, but they didn't want camel traffic everywhere.
Right.
So it was too narrow of a little area for a camel, especially a laden one, to get through.
So it was possible to take a camel through the needle's eye.
Well, the head can get in.
You just have to chop it into pieces.
Not fun for the camel and not a practical proposition in any case.
I can imagine now, I can envision a crew of rich, fat merchants struggling to prove they
can shove that camel through that narrow opening.
Well, I don't know.
Unfortunately.
Well, see, it's not impossible.
Enough rich men can push a camel through the needle's eye.
The wicked in his pride doth persecute the poor.
Let them be taken in the devices which they have imagined.
For the wicked boasteth of his heart's desire and blesseth the covetous whom the Lord abhorreth.
The wicked through the pride of his countenance, that smirking, smug, orange-painted countenance,
will not seek the camel.
There is no more thought of him except after God.
God is not at all in his thoughts.
His ways are always grievous.
Thy judgments are far above, out of his sight.
And as for all his enemies, he puffeth at them, probably with a vape device.
And as Bob once told me while worshipping Moloch, he said, Bob saith, I only believe
in two things.
Santa Claus.
And the fact that he doesn't exist.
And with that, we shall call in Lonesome Cowpoke Dave.
I mean, Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
Lonesome who?
Dave.
Oh, Lonesome Cowboy.
Yeah, there he is.
Lonesome Poker-Faced Roy.
Oh, he's holding a phone.
Oh, it is an imposter.
I was afraid of that.
See, if I said we were expecting Dave to call in some imposter trying to sound exactly like Dave.
And it's easy to do.
He's the easiest guy in the world to imitate.
No end of fold.
But this imposter, I suppose, would have to introduce himself with a few apostrophes
by locating the genius and the subgenius in each and every single little word he said.
That fluttering spirit which hovers even against the dank background of a subgenius personality.
Yep.
That flatulent weasel underneath your feet is nothing better than something to eat.
Wow!
Yeah, if you're desperate.
We're full of poetry and Bible quotes.
Tonight.
That was from the Bible, wasn't it, Dave?
Yeah.
Certainly would have.
Because I went to a poetry slam conference in San Francisco one time when I was out there a long time ago.
And this guy was talking.
I couldn't understand what the hell he was talking about.
And everybody was cheering.
And then he started imitating Deputy Dog having sex.
The old 70s cartoon character, Deputy Dog.
Yeah.
Deputy Dog having sex.
With some other cartoon animal.
And everyone was just laughing, laughing up and jorbing and joking uproariously
as if it was the most wonderful thing they'd ever heard in their lives.
Well, that was Deputy Dog's downtime.
Sorry.
He's got to relax, kick out the traces, kick out the jams.
Law enforcement is something that, well, it takes its toll.
Yep.
That's the way I tend to agree with that, especially thinking in terms of, like,
X-Day, what it really, really, really means, you know?
Well, up until the point where we are outside the effects, the efforts of law enforcement,
operating according to our own law.
I hope it wasn't bad for me to say that.
You say we can control gravity with our minds and stuff?
And comedy, too.
Oh, no.
At least nothing funny is going to happen around here, so.
Not on this show.
Not on my watch.
This isn't a time for ludicrous goofing and wacky antics.
We're on the cusp of the destruction of human civilization and the Earth.
Are we supposed to come here and make goofball jokes?
Yes.
Yeah, that's what I was going to ask you.
Apparently, there's this Mayan city they discovered that's got all these wall paintings that are real like...
It's your city?
You know.
Oh, no.
In Mexico.
Oh.
The Mayan city they discovered is the Mayan city.
Oh, it's Mayan.
Okay, sure.
Okay, well, how do you pronounce it?
No, it's Mayan.
No, Mayan.
Yeah, it's Mayan.
Well, anyway, they discovered it, and it's full of bar reliefs and wall hangings and things like that.
Yeah.
And one of them looks just like J.R. Bob Dobbs, and I just wanted to be either in it or...
No!
...were aware of that.
Well, we are now.
Right.
He and the...
Can't be unsaid.
...subgenius publication soon.
Can't be taken back.
We're going to have to make room for that in the subgenius canon, already bulging with irrelevant factoids.
But we'll get that in there, the Mayan glyph of Dobbs.
They smoked pipes.
That, it was only a matter of time.
Well, what was...
I don't understand what was a matter of time.
That makes no sense.
Well, no, that Mayan...
There's a Mayan glyph that shows this piped man who...
Actually, kind of looks like a Mayan-style Bob might look.
Yeah.
And he's greeting these gods from the sky and offering them some kind of canisters.
And there's what appears to be a city in flames and symbols of death and destruction.
But then somewhere along the line, there's this glimpse of heaven.
But you don't get to see that image.
You don't get to see that image very often because it's like those temples in India that are dedicated to raw sex and every position.
So it's a mixed message, you know.
It's doom for some and salvation for others.
Predicted by the Mayans only 1,998 years ago.
Bonampak is the name of the city where the frescoes are.
The name of the city is Bonampak.
Bonampak.
B-O-N-A-M-A-K.
Most interesting.
There's an argumentative woman.
I have to go for a second.
I'll see you in 23 seconds after I tell this old lady across the hallway who's got a TV blaring to shut up.
Hang on.
Well, she's watching her story.
She's watching her favorite show.
But I guess it's time to call everyone's attention into the center.
Goodness.
You're not getting along with your neighbor, that's for sure.
I didn't know that Dave had neighbors like that.
He does have a book, Neighbor World.
He who backbiteth against his neighbor.
He wrote the book, Neighbor World.
Nor doeth evil against his neighbor.
Yeah, we're all neighbors, neighbor.
Yeah, all gym neighbors to each other.
Gym neighbors to each other.
What an ill prescription that is.
Yeah, all singing in a sort of...
Whoa, whoa.
Yeah, kind of singing in an uptight way, which is unusual.
Does any of you guys read his autobiography, Gym Neighbors World?
Uh-oh.
Wasn't Gym Neighbors and also Annie Griffiths, weren't they all like sex...
Oh, no, that's Barney Rubble, or Barney...
Barney Fife.
Barney Fife, Gym Neighbors, and...
He's a pervert.
Not a pervert, but he called a staple of ladies, right?
His brother was Goober, you may remember.
Goober was an unwholesome character.
Yeah.
He was nuts.
Well, yes, he was part of that rural community featuring Aunt Bea,
who's also in The Day the Earth Stood Still,
claiming that flying saucers are coming from Russia.
And the little squinty-eyed Opie, also,
director of movies about giant whales and aged aliens.
Huh.
How come everybody's laughing?
I have no idea what you're talking about right now.
Well, a little Opie directed a movie called Cocoon,
and he might have even directed the sequel of Cocoon.
Who could forget that, especially if you've got dementia?
Yeah, see, these are these oldsters who aliens get all revved up and so forth.
A kind of prophetic, considering what we, the subgeniuses, believe.
And then more recently, he developed a movie which Hollywood considers a total flopperoo
about giant whales.
And he's got these little whales crashing into whale boats
and hounding and harassing the survivors as they attempt to reach out.
Are you talking about Heart of the Sea?
I am.
It's based on a true story that Moby Dick is based on.
Have you seen the movie?
Yeah, I loved it.
I thought it was great.
Well, it didn't do well in Hollywood.
And so they're now saying, you know, he's lost his magic touch.
But he just came out with something.
I thought it was really good.
I liked it.
It's an intelligent way of treating the theme.
What is wrong?
What's wrong with him to say such a thing?
Did he direct...
They're pictures and vampires.
First Man, I think he did.
Neil Armstrong's story.
Yeah, I recently watched that.
That was a good one, too.
Yeah, Opie's done some excellent movies.
And he did have flabby man tits.
And he tortured people in the Twilight Zone.
That's right.
That's a really good thing he did, however.
And he was a bad little kid.
Oh, pardon me, a good kid.
He was a good kid.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Very good.
You don't want him to get mad at you.
Right, right.
He could make your...
Your mouth just grow.
Send you out into the cornfield
to become a jack-in-the-box or something.
Mr. Howell is a bad man.
Yeah, he cut it out.
I send my tithes in.
You got nothing on me.
Yeah, that would be an ideal way
to start a perfunctory movement
would be like to say,
are you ready to go to the cornfields now yet?
Are you?
Well, you know, in old Ireland,
the people were actually terrified
of those supposedly cute little leprechauns,
and you were never allowed to criticize them
or say anything about them
except they were extremely good.
They were the good people, the good folk.
Bless them.
Let's hope they don't do anything.
They're good.
They're really good.
We tried to gain their favor, as a matter of fact,
rather than the way it is nowadays.
Even banshees were not considered
a very evil thing, per se.
They were just, you know, a portent of...
They're a spirit of mourning.
It means a banshee is a woman of the she,
kind of like the Mexican spirit La Ilurona,
the weeping woman,
the howling spirit who appears
at time of mourning and death.
And so the banshee,
rendered even more scary by Walt Disney,
also comes along with the leprechauns,
the coach driven by the headless coachman,
the coach that takes you...
to the other place.
And...
You have to have a special beard
if you're going to go there in a passport.
You have to go underground
to live under the hill.
And as you're under there,
time passes at a prodigious rate.
So when you come out,
everybody you knew was dead, dead, dead.
Darby O'Gill got in a lot of trouble with that.
And so did...
No, that's not Stang's Paradox.
Stang's Paradox is basically some...
You're not like your grandfather
and had sex with him.
No, no, no.
That's the Fry Paradox.
Mine was just real simple.
I must, yet I cannot.
It's as simple as that.
Yeah.
It's everybody's situation.
Where does I must meet with I cannot on the graph?
Why is this not part of the plan?
To laugh like the human,
to dance like the human,
to make silly jokes like the human.
To wear silly shoes like Herman.
You are a Roman,
and a Roman you shall remember.
You shall remain.
Now I set you in motion,
said Great Guidance.
One, kill the family.
Two, kill the girl.
Fail to do this,
and I will kill you.
Yes, Great Guidance.
What a sack.
It's not like one of those memes
that are traveling around now
telling people to kill each other and stuff.
Well, that's what Great Guidance was all about.
And Roman had already killed everybody in the world
except the small family of chumps,
you see, in the motion picture.
Yeah, that was...
He'd already done...
He'd already done most of it.
That was a tragic, tragic Bible story.
Great Guidance, I will kill these people,
but not the girl Alice.
That one I will keep for my experiments.
Yeah.
Who was Vincent Price actually talking to
when he was by the refrigerator there
and his eyes were all lit up
and it sounded like he was flat-slinged, too?
Just like his mom and dad were.
Who was the one who was taking that down
in probate court back in the 20s?
Yeah.
That's what I'm asking.
Some evil spirit hovering through fog and filthy air.
I think you got your Bible stories mixed up, Dave.
Yeah.
That was a different one.
Hey, dear, any of you good people know anything
about the market in human fat that flourished
just a few hundred years ago?
Fat, fat, fat.
Yes, it's very valuable.
It's demonized in the present time.
But you gotta have it.
If you don't have fat,
you'll become an Alzheimer's patient.
The human brain is made out of fat.
The sugar industry has made fat seem like a bad thing.
But fat doesn't even make you fat
unless you eat it with sugar.
That's not what he's talking about.
It was believed...
We're talking about fat.
It was actual human fat.
The sale of actual human fat,
just like people would sell their urine
as a fixative for licensees
and paranoid colors and stuff.
Executioners recovered the fat called
armsunderfat or armsunderschmutz
for the fat or grease of poor executed sinners.
Or people who were tortured in the Middle Ages,
as you can find out from reading Ivanhoe.
Their fat was often rendered down in the dungeon
and collected by the torturers.
It was often a major source of income,
I'm reading here, for some executioners.
Uh...
That's scary, but think about...
Think about how there were urine factories.
Hey, it says it's good for gout and bone pain.
Yes, fat is good all around for the body.
If it is not taken at the same time as sugar
and those carbohydrates which instantly turn into sugar
after having been consumed.
Hmm.
Now, does this explain the dietary supplements
in the 1890s and stuff, the fatiners?
Or is it a young woman who looks fairly normal
to the rest of us?
Because in those days, in around the 1890s,
it was really sexy to be, like, kind of a chubby.
Oh, I've got comic books with ads in there
about how you don't have to be skinny
and it shows a girl busting out of a bathing suit,
you know, and it says...
They had all these products, these called fatiners.
Yes.
And you'd eat them like ice cream
and I don't know what they would do.
Maybe they were like treacle or pudding or something
or sandwiches.
Well, I think it's sort of...
It's like Metri-Cal, you know,
that stuff that's supposed to make you thin.
Actually, if you constantly consume it,
you'll grow nice and fat and sassy.
Oh, absolutely.
Maybe, yeah.
And you become a calvinist, too.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Don't be sorry, Dave.
Two-ton Tessie tripping along the Midway,
the fattest thing in creation
and a sensation at the old Coney Island.
Across the nation, yeah.
At the old Coney Island,
but she had to retire.
In 1938.
But now, they don't have any freak shows
or anything like that in Coney Island.
I believe that it's all no longer PC.
Yeah, they've outlawed it even in Texas.
So how do those different folks make their money now?
They don't.
I guess they don't.
We accept you, we accept you.
Wards of the state.
Wards of the Puntang state
because they don't have any money.
The Romney people refused,
absolutely refused on a stack of unholy Bibles
to stop roaming around.
They'd like government in Czechoslovakia
would build like a village for them and say,
you're staying here and the name of this village
is Romney Village number 12 or something like that, you know?
And they'd say, oh man, I got to move.
And they'd load up the trucks
and a lot of small horse-sized caravans.
Caravans.
Caravans, yes.
Yeah, like the song.
Well, a caravan also refers to a vehicle
used by the Romney folk as they travel around.
There's the one wagon caravan and the two wagon
where the two wagons are joined together,
pulled by a team of horses,
as seen in the Universal Motion Picture
House of Frankenstein.
Professor Rampini's Circus of Horrors,
taken over by Boris Karloff, a hunchbacked assistant.
I actually played a gypsy feast when I was a young lad
in a rock and roll band.
It's strange how we acquired the gig.
The head of the band, they were on their way to St. Anne's,
which is in the Montreal, Quebec area there.
And they make a yearly pilgrimage
and their religion is real bizarre
because it's real heavy iconography and everything.
And you can't tell whether it's Catholic, Roman Catholic,
or Greek Orthodox, or you can't tell what it is.
It's just like...
Romney Orthodox or some weird thing.
It's robust.
And they ate a whole sheep at this festival we played at.
What did they do?
They ate a whole sheep and a dog ate the paw.
Well, I'm glad they saved something for man's best friend.
Yep, that little big-eyed fella sitting by the fire
deserved at least something,
including the cloven hoof of a ruminant,
a sheep-type critter.
That's all I can say.
That's all I can get out of it.
There's restaurants in areas near where I live
named after the cloven-hoofed one.
And I'm like, man, how come you said
that was a cloven-hoofed thing and so forth?
What is it?
Is that back to the Church of the Subgenius
why a goat mantra?
No, why not a goat?
And are not fed, as John Milton says.
No, they are cloven-hoofed creatures, certainly.
We know that for sure.
Just like the pig, man.
John Milton's other best friend.
Oh, I see.
A pig's hard to ride, too.
It's hard to get a saddle on them and...
They'll be cooperative if you treat them well.
Make America goat again.
Yes.
I've got a T-shirt that says that.
It comes from the goat ranch.
No, recently.
Greatest of all time ranch.
Some of our listeners will know when this is and where it was,
but some atheists tried to set up a huge statue
of the goat-headed goat.
It was a great baphomet
when they had posted the Ten Commandments
in a public location.
Did you follow that?
Yeah, I think they did it.
This great statue, this great bronze statue
with a plaque and a pedestal,
and it caused the good Christian folks to freak out.
The movie about that, Dr. Howell,
is why J.R. Bob-Dob's In the Church of the Subgenius
was not shown at Cannes.
No, what's a huge one in Colorado?
Yeah, the Aspen Film Festival.
The quaking Aspen.
Well, you know which one.
The most famous film festival in the world.
Telluride?
Telegraph?
No, no.
Even the biggest one of all.
That's why I can't remember it.
Well, it's not Aspen, and it's not Telluride.
Well, it's whatever it was,
so that kept the subgeniuses from...
We want to get it in.
I'm trying to remember.
Anyway, it didn't get in.
It was because the Church of Satan documentary
had been also entered,
and they didn't want to have two church of documentaries,
and Satan had a bigger name than Bob,
at least with these film festival credits.
Well, at least it's a longer name,
because Bob's just B-O-B,
and Satan has four letters in it.
Well, the movie title, actually, is long and clumsy.
J.R. Bob-Dob's In the Church of the Subgenius.
The Church of the Subgenius.
But it beats Slacking to Bethlehem.
Boy, it sure does.
What a relief it was that that wasn't used.
And as printed, as written on a sign,
it could say J.R. Bob-Dob's in huge letters,
and then in little tiny letters,
and then Church of the Subgenius in big letters under that.
It would look just fine on a marquee.
Have you seen the posters, Hal?
The ones that have...
You mean...
The one that Paul Mavridis made?
No, no.
That one's terrible,
and I've told that to Paul myself.
Did you look at it on a phone?
No, I looked at it on a great big screen.
So you did see the large-size version of that.
I didn't think it was terrible at all.
I'm talking about the one that used...
It's the painting done by a street artist in Bangkok.
That was...
For a dollar.
That was the beginning of it, yes.
It was an elaboration on that image.
It's the worst portrait of Bob there is.
Well, you see, by the weakest link in the chain,
we must stand or fall.
Well, anyway...
I keep on wondering why nobody ever wants to use
my revolutionary period communist posters
from the Russian Revolution.
They did.
They made millions of bucks off of those, Dave.
Didn't you get royalties?
God, are you a chump?
Well...
Well, they said something was...
It's going to be on its way soon,
but they kept on referring to it
like a person who was gagging on food.
Well, you saw him, right?
Somebody got something stuck in their throat.
That was your prize.
That was my pride.
Yeah.
Pride goeth before a fall.
No, the poster, the last poster I saw,
is black and white,
and it's got the right half of Bob's face
on the left side of the poster
and the left side of Bob's face
on the right side of the poster.
With the pipe all mixed up and turned around?
No.
No, no.
If you put two posters together,
you get a great big job in the middle.
They match perfectly.
It's kind of clever.
Hit the neighborhood with the pasteboard
and put it all up and down the fences.
Yeah.
The triumvirate of Bob.
But, uh...
Psycho-technical morning.
What about that strange realistico Bob
that showed up,
the actual physical, fleshy, middle-aged Bob
that some people were embracing a while back
and...
And...
And using his navel as a place
to store the salt for the salary.
They were junking the old Bob,
although there were some who said,
I like the old Bob.
But one thing about it is
they found the actual guy,
and it was exactly the way it was described
in the book of the subgenius,
a terrifying occurrence.
And he was fleshy.
He was kind of like a back-slapping Rotarian guy.
And they had arbitrarily cut off Bob's chin
just to make the famous subgenius
glyph, but once the rest of the body was restored,
he was a rather solid fellow
with more than one chin.
Dr. Howell, by coincidence,
the listeners of this station
will be hearing us discuss that Bob next week
from an hour of slack two years ago
done at Wisteria during X-Day
that never was...
Well, I forgot a lot of that stuff when we moved.
And I recently...
I recently rediscovered it.
Oh, good.
When we're gone for X-Day,
everybody can hear all these X-Day reruns
from two years ago that aren't reruns.
Nobody's ever heard.
It's a treasure trove.
And they're really funny,
but there's a long discussion of that.
The photo...
The pre-Dobbshead photo of a man
that became the Dobbshead we used.
Who posed for clothing ads and everything,
just like in the Church of the Subgenius.
Now, is Philo one of these discussors
of the...
the strange photo, Bob?
No, that was...
It was you, me, and Onan.
And I confess that for the first two years,
I refused to even think about it or look at it,
which is true.
Too disturbing.
And someone made a GIF.
What does GIF stand for?
Do you know what I'm saying?
A graphic...
It's just a format.
A graphic image format.
Well, you know, like in that Bugs Bunny cartoon
about duck season, rabbit season,
duck season, rabbit season,
they replaced the two,
the duck and rabbit posters with the two bobs,
so they're tearing down first the old bob,
then the new bob,
and behind it there's the old bob,
and behind it there's the new bob.
Yes, it's on a telephone pole.
Paul Marfretti's did that, I think.
What about all the Daffy Ducks looking bobs
that suck around the neighborhood?
They got, like, playing, smoking cigars
and making jokes and...
Out of luck.
But, of course, we have to bobify everything
in the neighborhood.
That's easier to do now with those...
pipe...
stickers that Fyre invented.
You just stick a pipe on something
and it's art, as we used to say.
Well, now everybody can do it.
It's within reach of...
And now all 50 states have an additional variety, too,
that you can vaporize on your forehead,
or you can use little cheese modules
that are stuck in your ear,
kind of like a bob ball,
like a bob, bob, bob, bob, bob.
Oh, those things overheat.
Those, you can get brain damage.
You don't want anything overheating by your brain.
You don't want incendiary in your ear hairs, you know.
No.
Poor guy Roknar,
he was our first guinea pig with that.
He volunteered.
Yeah, he volunteered.
Let's not wallow in sadness about it.
He volunteered for all kinds of stuff.
Yes.
It was really dumb.
Well, he was, you see, a cheerful volunteer.
He was cannon fodder for the subgenius war.
A soldier for Bob.
And we need many more.
Yes, we need the ranks to fill,
and we need to send them into battle
from our comfortable redoubt.
Yeah.
I'd love to be out there in the field with you men,
but they need me here.
And these nose beads keep me on my back.
Besides, my doctor says I have to have my feet elevated above my head at all times.
I've got bone spurs.
I can't go.
I can't.
I've got bone spurs on my bone spurs.
Men, I salute you.
This is a wonderful time for you, and women, too.
Go on out over the trench as soon as I blow the whistle and wipe out those pinks.
Amen.
Praise God.
We'll be carrying our tooth powders with us in our jolly duffel bags,
and we'll have, like, a bunch of postcards home to mom to visit dear old mother.
Yes, we've prepared those in advance.
And a whole bunch of dear John letters waiting for us with the next shipment.
Well, uh...
Unfortunately, that's the truest...
That's the truest value of the whole engorgement.
And what about Pope Perot over in Europe,
now no longer as powerful as before,
uh, waving his little paws,
impotent to stop the carnage.
I found a
big string of
Popero
posters. Popero posters
in the X-Day stuff I was sorting
today. Does it mean like
Pope doggy? Because I'm kind of out of this
one a little bit. If you don't mind
telling me. It's not poop dog.
Pope dog. There was
a foul-tempered little
dog owned by
a subgenius
minister in Germany.
With a prognathous lower jaw.
And a
one of the weekends
that lower teeth snapping.
Yes.
The black coat.
That's why they say
and then they say
you know what that means in German. When you say hi
to somebody you go
and they say
the
that means the same thing as
Pendejo. It doesn't mean friend.
They're making fun of you.
Well, well, well, we're just talking about etymology here.
I never have had any friends.
Yes, not in the German
nation. Anyway, the little dog
Pero, who is a Spanish dog.
A little grey schnauzer, yes.
He was made Pope of
Germany
because of the
failure of the black
Pope to
you know
show up at all
for a whole day.
Two leaders.
Yes, probably.
Demotion in the church of the subgenius
can be instantaneous and final.
There's one of the slogans of the church is
don't follow Pope Black.
That was.
Oh, he was the guy who's had the funnel cake wagon
at the same time he was selling all this religious
rumorage and all these false doctrines, right?
Well, he did. No, he did a lot of really good work
for the church of the subgenius.
It's just that he also caused some terrible problems.
He's kind of like the Martin Luther of.
Yeah, I got you.
He was a subgenius.
What can we say?
What can we say to us personally?
That's why his papal crown was given to little
Pugnacious Pope Pedro.
Yeah.
I've been leaving those little Pope Pedro pictures in in the
those sweat lodges, those big blue plastic sweat
lodges lined up.
I do not want to play this kind of music that's being played
right now in a sweat lodge because it can make it can make
too much conversation.
Because if you're trying to focus on getting out of off the
reservation somehow.
These are solo sweat lodges.
One person.
There's room for one person to sit down and you have to be
careful because there's a hole in it.
One and a half actually.
Who knows what lurks beneath?
Actually.
The children of old Sequa, perhaps.
Oh.
It could be or other dire creatures.
How?
You haven't heard the news.
Are the paleontologists subgenius has been studying those infants,
those snapping turtle juveniles that have been showing up in the
pond in old Sequa's pond, which is how we, we, you know,
learned originally that the old Sequa is female.
But he's he took a closer look at him and did some tests and he
says.
No, those are actually just ordinary mutated snapping turtles.
But moreover, Dr.
Howell, moreover, old Sequa is not, in fact, old.
That is the juvenile.
Indeed, the infant.
When the when the parent of what we call old Sequa rises, there will be earthquakes
infecting all of us.
Oh.
Would you feel something?
Oh, my goodness.
Oh, my God.
It's like, could it be a tremor?
Well, coincidence.
It would be over seven skyscrapers tall.
Yes.
He's a big one.
All right.
No, she.
She.
Yes.
And then there's the Loveland frogmen, another cryptid species from Ohio.
They could erupt out of the ground and create chaos and disruption.
We're reprinting that.
We had a point.
Or monsters of America.
Gave us a point.
We're going to have to get them down this year.
Oh, good.
Yeah.
But all these earthquakes are not the problem.
There was a four point earthquake just last week in the Cleveland area, four miles out
into the lake.
And I think it's strange that people made any mention of that.
Somebody claimed to see a gigantic head as if the head of a dinosaur.
Or they actually said it was a bit like Mitch McConnell.
A kind of a turtle-like.
Yeah.
He's a turtle guy.
He knows the handshakes, that's for sure.
If that's all you have to know.
Oh, Dave, it's 10 o'clock, which means it's the end of this hour of slack.
Yeah.
Howsoever.
Do you know where your children are?
I can check on the GPS tag I have on them.
Yeah, okay.
See how-
But anyway, yeah.
But don't go away.
Not that any of you had the ability to do so, dear listeners.
Or I'm sorry, yeah.
Because Dr. Sinister's show is coming up and it's going to include-
Filled with slack.
When should Dave come?
I'm so kidding.
I mean, how do you guys want to do it?
Do you want to just keep rolling?
We could.
Don't you have some sort of-
I see no reason not to.
I do have to say this one thing.
You're listening to this station.
Okay.
Now we're fine.
We keep you legal for less.
I have to insert a thing that says, this station for the other station.
And you can't give off the call letters of some other station.
That's definitely against all the regs.
Yeah, I have to be careful with that kind of thing because-
That's on your broadcast license.
Do you have a broadcast license?
Yeah, really?
You have to know who you're speaking for.
Yeah, so you better believe I do.
It's on mine.
It says, never, never, never give off the call letters of a different station when your
broadcasting.
And yet, I know people who do that all the time.
And you know what else?
I've been doing this for, like I think my first time on the air was in late 2001.
Uh-huh.
Never once was personally licensed by the FCC.
The station has an FCC license.
So I think the regulations have changed since the golden age.
No, I think they've been the same since about 2000, since about the mid-90s even.
Yeah.
And a lot of the actual performance things, you know, and stuff like that.
Anyway, friends, this show is over.
I could lose my license for this.
And you've been listening to the Hour of Slack, number 1,735.