Now I'm not making this up, but in the latest issue of Railway Modeler, there's a little house you can build with a little projector in it, and you actually get the impression of people moving behind the little plastic window.
Only a sick person would do that.
No, it's part of an advanced model railroad layout, in H.O. scale, whether I'll leave it or not.
They shrink down these people to a tiny size.
As a kind of a punishment.
You squint really close, you can see them shrink.
Hey, hey, but no, thank you, Michelle, I'm going to go to the hospital, no!
No, they whine that they can't escape from the town, like that old Twilight Zone.
You ever see that one where the people keep getting on the train, but they keep coming back to the station?
Who are you talking to, Hal?
And then finally a huge kid's face looms down, and they've been captured by the giant alien's attack.
What? He's talking so much.
Wow.
Oh, we're all talking.
I've lived that Twilight Zone.
And that's why they can't make it through.
He's talking about it.
One is a guy, he's talking about it.
Double follow the story.
The world is now experiencing strange astronomical phenomena.
Reports have come in from all over the globe of inexplicable objects being sighted in the sky.
Surely you're not telling me a scientist like yourself believes such nonsense.
It was all very queer.
But queerer things were yet to come.
That's a chance, that's a chance!
That's a chance!
Sir!
I could have stopped you.
I'm properly dressed, but in my pajamas.
Yes, sir.
I've never...
It's Lansing!
Good work, you're all right!
...known in the city of Spokane.
We can't waste any more time.
More time!
I'm in the middle of the helicopter.
You know the part underneath that thing where it lands?
Do you?
Do you know the part?
Yes, I know that part.
I've never hung on to that.
I've never even commentated a vehicle.
Now that sounds like a lot of fun.
Oh!
I don't know.
Lately I just don't feel like there's anything special about me.
You are an incredibly talented scientist.
You're a very sensitive man who inspires joy-joy feelings in all those around you.
Oh!
Excuse me, sir.
We're the clever ones.
Most of that bunch are like dinosaurs in suits.
They have absolutely no idea we're playing with their little brains.
That's who you remind me of.
An evil Mr. Rogers.
You know, when my kids start recombining the DNA of a frog and mutating it into a giant
monster who lays waste to our town, that means we're going to have to do something about
it.
That means I've been spending too much time at the office.
You know what feels great?
All those jerks at the company who never thought I'd go anywhere.
Well, this'll show them.
Doug, I have to tell you something I think you might not want to hear.
Uh-huh?
Hey, look, I didn't mean to be on the radio, but there's no law against it, is there?
In jail, in hell.
It's an effective attack on everything that bugs me.
I'm sorry.
You've got to get up.
You've got to yell and make my head explode.
I want everybody to keep trying.
That's it.
Go!
Amazing.
Just amazing.
Well, according to your brainwave charts, your solution is pretty darn simple.
And, uh...
What's happening here?
I don't know.
It's...
There's this bleed over that's coming in.
Yeah, what was that about?
Uh, the church is gonna rub...
People are gonna rub fog.
... something about that.
Bleed.
Yeah.
I think he's breaking down.
The clutch of the...
Birch of the...
Punch.
Menius.
What?
The crutch of the...
No, I know, but...
Evil genius.
Of the crutch of the...
Bleed.
Yes?
Dub.
Penius.
Oh, no, it's...
Church crossover.
The...
The, uh...
I don't know what to believe in.
It's Saint Slack Day's parade.
No, but...
It's...
That's what's, uh...
No, no, never.
... throwing us off.
It's that, uh...
No, no, never.
... Bishop Joey and his, uh...
Yeah, Mr. Stupid Pants over there.
Oh, he thinks he's so stupid.
Mr. Stupid Pants.
Oh, he thinks he's stupider than he said genius.
Comes right through your window.
He thinks he's the stupidest guy in the world.
I believe that.
He's the one who's doing it.
The guy who's doing it.
Bishop Joey's...
He's right over there, officer.
... he's been arrested for distributing child pornography, right?
And...
To a minor.
The children.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Mr. Stupid Pants.
We're stupid as you are.
Top that.
Come on.
Now, don't you mean Stooped Pants?
Not stupid.
Stupid.
You know, he stands pretty straight up.
He's lost the stupido.
He's something stupido.
He lost the stupido.
In fact, the...
The comment that was heard after the viewing of the Puzzling Evidence videos of Saint's
Stupid Day Parade of 2010...
Oh, really?
... heard all through subgeniusdom, was...
Oh, my God!
There's thousands of them!
How come we don't have that many people at X Day?
Ha!
And the answer, of course, is because rather than holding X Day in a city full of weird
artists and rich young people, we hold it in the middle of the most God-forsaken wilderness,
Amish-controlled, strange, hard-to-reach...
In the desolate wastes, reaches of the earth...
Frozen wastes of rural New York.
Actually, it's being moved to the West Coast.
That's right.
The West Coast...
That's right!
And the last thing we have is the worst waste of the burning...
... No man knows...
... ... forest of Southern Ohio.
... what size this beast may grow.
So, kids, your chance to go to X Day Drill at Brushwood is gone.
Already?
Yes.
There shall never be another X Day Drill at Brushwood because there is no more Brushwood.
However, there will be...
The sun shall never rise and fall again upon...
A mysterious next day at Wisteria in southern Ohio.
A hysterical place to have a big party.
The mystery of Wisteria.
The Wisterian mystery.
Did you ever see that Japanese movie, The Wisterians?
Yes.
The giant robot with pointy hands.
Yes, and a big pointy nose on that rock.
Yes.
It came bursting out of the cliff.
That was a terrifying, unexpected thing.
The Wisterians.
A robot?
A giant robot was concealed inside a massive cliff.
And at the beating of alien instigators,
it emerged from the surrounding rocky formation
with enormous rock fall and loss of life.
We don't know how many giant robots.
The insouciant robot begins to take a little stroll,
crushing property and creating havoc.
Perhaps on next day, the saucers,
the saucers won't lower themselves down to us from the sky,
but could rise up out of the earth.
Maybe they were here all along.
It is possible that some of the account, as we understand it,
is distorted because our understanding is not clear enough
to perceive the ultimate truth in this matter.
So it's possible it may be, in some few particulars,
slightly different from what we've always assured
our followers would be the case.
But really,
the basis,
the basic message is,
and always will remain the same,
that at the rupture,
if at the assembly point and fully paid up,
all will be accepted, saved,
and seized up into the clouds,
taking off into the air,
as the French say,
with the sex goddesses aboard the spaceships.
And that right there, friends,
is why you shouldn't commit suicide.
Because you don't really know the future.
And it might get a whole lot better just like that.
Just because you heard this show.
Just be for that reason only.
What you're hearing right now could lead you to
perhaps your life's true love.
Your mate for life.
Whatever sex or species that might happen to you.
I'll set you up with the love of your life.
What I'm telling you now,
could have repercussions that will benefit you forever.
Or,
it could plunge you into an endless nightmare.
A veritable hell.
The choice is yours.
Yes.
Actually, the choice is not theirs.
The choice is Bob's.
Only Bob may choose who is worthy and who is not.
And his standards may not conform to ours.
In fact, they almost certainly will not.
No, they would not, would they?
But the idea is not to,
to depend on Bob for a lot of, or a lot of chance.
You can't second guess J.R. Bob Dobbs.
It's not up to us to decide who is a true subgenius and who's not.
No, sir.
To attempt to...
Now, anybody can purchase somehow
some sort of little sign that says they're a subgenius.
Sure, anybody can do that.
Well, if you...
But only Bob knows.
And, well, and also his friends from outer space.
The men from Planet X, the X's.
The X's.
Who know if I've...
Pure telepathy and whiff reading.
They can whiff read the stench of your DNA.
Reverend Stein, you know the people...
Is that, uh...
...this part memorized?
Is that Reverend Diva Schematic in the background singing?
Oh, yeah, I think so.
With the...
The Athery squash?
The Athery squash.
The Ather...
See, I've seen on MySpace.
I hear an overbang mask.
There's more somewhere right now.
The rubber and the...
Totally wear the...
Cypress lawn
Table stall of cypress lawn
Holiday decent shoulders
Six foot by two foot
How can you be in a deal like that?
Really, that guy laid it out
Since he was laid out
What the hell's going on here?
I don't know, I'm just
I think I'm losing my mind
Just try to remember where you put it
Oh, the train
We're going to have to wait here while it goes by
Go 2.3 miles
And turn into a giant
Jesus
Is this a background music
That new genre known as
Flubstep?
Remember Flub-a-dub on the old
Audi duty show?
No, I don't, actually, Dr. Powell
How many animals
A horrible composite of various animals
How many can you recall Flub-a-dub being?
Well, a duck
Who was
Probably
That's the main
aspect of Flub-a-dub
A giraffe's neck
Yes, with immaculate
Yeah, this is something I've been doing
It's all
Look what happened this afternoon
It's all this weird stuff this afternoon
Wow, I bet if you did an advanced image search
On Flub-a-dub
You'd see a picture of Flub-a-dub
Flub that duck
And the duck it rode in on
That's what I mean
It's not a duck
I'm telling you
A composite
A chimera
A composite creature
Well, this can be
Looked up at something like that
time, I suppose, so
no one cares to follow these
instant sessions. I'll just make another note.
Must
view Flub-a-dub.
Flub-a-dub-dub, three men in a tub.
How does the rest of that go?
The butcher, the baker,
the candlestick maker.
If the tub had been stronger,
the tail had been longer.
What are they talking about?
Uh, rub-a-dub-dub,
three men in a tub.
Rubbing and dubbing and all
that rubbing. I'm still back with this
UFO stuff of the pleasure
saucers. Did they ever get all that?
UFO-ders, Big Feet,
and the mystery of the
Bermuda Delta Drive. You can think
all you want about those pleasure saucers.
I hope you're
thinking pleasant thoughts when you're
lifted up onto them, because if you
get paranoid at the last minute, why
everything could go completely wrong.
What could
go wrong on a pleasure saucer?
Really?
That's just oxymoronic.
Your attitude going in, as we say,
will be of extreme importance
in whether or not your ride is comfortable
and viable, as Bob intended when he made
the original deal with the Exes.
This interstellar contract is the legal basis
for the salvation of the subgenius population
via escape vessel operation.
I hope you go on the ride
with God, on the next day at
X hours.
Calm the F down.
I urge each and every one
of you to have a stress pill
ready to take when this
apical event begins...
Mississippi.
You're not spooky yet.
Just under and.
over general overman united states center will oversee with him proceedings you might not
recognize him anymore docking of the giant is going to give you another shot to them
the huge sponsons are landing here now seen in this other view he thinks he's still up on the
sixth floor of the space ships are being pulled okay we're here history this is the new extent
through the outer layers over there that's his camp our planet's atmosphere house camp over there
welcoming the space invaders our local police chief george
his wife former alicia douglas alicia wiggins and their visiting aunt from schenectady new york
now they're about to approach the head of the alien
delegation and we're going to listen for what they're going to be telling us in this special time
we're still waiting for that yeah is that this moment you know what the saddest part is i was
going to bring the little eeyore monster or whatever but you forgot what's the little monster
in uh uh the c40 c54 land uh and francis and the forbidden planet the monster of the monster
he's only that big well i thought he was scarier than that the ufo you've got you must not have a
very big id if that's how no you're a monster little soldiers are trying to shoot at the end
you've got the planetary guy right here he's on he's here yeah see him on this little bit what
what oh that's amazing only because my daughter is alive in my mind from microsecond to microsecond
yeah yeah whatever you got to work coffee yeah get the sponge
it's quite fatiguing to use the crell device eat another sponge also pleasure this is the best sponge
cake i've had in weeks the brain itself is like a sponge a meringue don't listen to your brain right
now it's like your brain on drugs yeah maybe communicating with angels or devils who knows
your brain is not the big boss of this area what did we figure out about angels earlier
i remember something about angels right now
reverend stang what was it about an angel they're not going to be of any help to us
the angel of the world wasn't that what it was yeah subgenius is the angel
but the angels themselves have they're by bound by a non-aggression pact and uh
are not going to be any help at all uh contrary to what you might have heard when x-day uh begins to
move
the devils on the other hand it's uh oh they've free for all really they're going to be everywhere
they they don't play by anybody else's rules and that's why they're devils and uh
that's why we need jr bob dobbs as the broker the uh the deal maker and the midnight toker to keep
you to keep the devils on our side
meekard
the devils on our side
the darkanto flower
the handle foil
the
jara
is this matter cast music from earth i hate that actual seriously aliens wants inhabited our own world
These ancient pictographs in a cave in Oslo, Norway, conclusively and convulsively demonstrate
that our Earth has been diddled ages ago by an alien invasion vanguard,
which may still be here operating in an unknown zip code.
And this History Channel special is the ultimate proof of ghosts and life after death.
Thank you, Ivan Stagg.
Yes, there may be an alien listening to this or living next to you.
The question is, what to do about it?
Keep listening, and we're going to provide the answer.
Will the real Martian please stand up?
No, not you, the guy in the back with the two sets of...
Yeah, that's right.
Could you come forward, please?
He doesn't have a microphone.
He needs two microphones, one for each head.
That is, I think, just a breathing orifice.
Oh, you could be right.
Well, they're bringing him a mic in just a moment.
Their language, I'm told, is a kind of wheezing noise.
It's been described as like a concertina shooting air out...
Well, but then I believe this particular radio show has been described exactly that same way.
That's true.
We've had to fight smears and allegations.
We've had to roll up our sleeves and tangle with the tufts and turts of radio repression.
As a matter of fact, we've got some...
We've had labor difficulties and many problems that we're not allowed to talk about here on...
Listener-sponsored radio.
But we're still in there and we're still punching.
And we're fighting the good fight until bruised, beaten, battered, and bloody,
we stumble from the ring with eyes swollen, shut, fractured jaw, and collapsed zygomatic process.
I'll zygomatic you, young man.
Oh, is this on?
Why are you playing this old-timey Cleveland piece?
To get the audience in the mood, you know.
Now they want to see the kill.
They've seen just about the march to death's gate.
But now we're going to go through the aperture into death's horrible hall.
These are the sub-teeny singers.
Oh, it's back to real life.
A lot of freedom of choice stuff going on.
Yes, freedom of choice dog food.
Your pup will love freedom of choice.
He looks one way, he looks the other, he runs in circles and he falls down.
Freedom of choice dog food for your dog.
Yes, freedom of choice dog food will make your canine...
Freedom of choice is what you've got.
Whoa!
At your local Safeway.
With a hearty woof, woof.
Dr. House, Governor Rocknoy.
Good evening, Governor Rocknoy.
Hi, if it isn't...
Welcome to our...
Governor, almost Congressman Rocknoy.
Sub-genius symposium of the airwaves.
I gave it my best, but I only got 22 votes.
How many votes did you say?
Doesn't sound like your best was...
Well, but you got out there and met the York constituents and gave them a taste of your ideas.
Young people these days.
They just don't try.
Governor Rocknoy tried.
Well, I was talking about the young people these days.
Oh.
Well, Governor Rocknoy's kind of young, I guess.
He's young.
You know what?
I've been...
I'm sorry that this is the first time I've called in a long time, but I've been working a new job over at the convenience store.
What is that job?
Yeah, I'm working 10 p.m. to 6 a.m.
So I'm total graveyard shift.
Now.
Ah, man.
Is this still at a Speedway or is this a Downer Way or a Wakeway or a Worldway?
It's a Speedway, yeah.
And one of the barcodes on one of the bakery pastry goods items, which is a cheesecake.
Cheesecake?
Oh, you're getting me started.
One of the barcodes ends at 13013.
What?
How about that, Governor?
The sacred number of dobs appeared in what?
Way in a cheesecake?
In a UPC barcode for one of our bakery items, the cheesecake.
The disguised letters spelling out Bob's name.
13013.
Yes.
In a cheesecake.
You know, a lot of people never have figured out why 13013 was a special number.
Apparently, they didn't write the...
The special positioning of the ones and the threes.
Right.
Where the three...
You know, it's like a magic eye when you look at it and you say,
Oh, there it is.
Right.
Eliminate all kerning between the one and the three.
And the secret will be revealed to you.
You kind of unfocus your eyes and then you see the Bob in the 13013.
Smoosh and blend together, yeah.
You see the Bob all too late.
Yeah.
Hey, I'll tell you a couple of stories of when it happened.
Number one.
A few nights ago, we had a couple of kids at the Speedway.
They were driving recreational vehicles.
Uh-oh.
And I asked them, it's like, you know, hey, I showed them a way to save six cents off a gallon.
You know, part of, you know, my little battle against the conspiracy.
And they said that they were headed to festivals out in California.
And I told them that there was a festival at Wisteria.
And they said that they knew where Wisteria was.
And they were planning to go to the festival called X Day between June 30th and July 5th.
You're kidding.
Someone walked into the store and informed you of this?
Well, I kind of told them, you know, about, I suggested to them that they go to X Day Wisteria.
Oh.
So, you know, we're going to see two kids in a pretty big recreational vehicle.
Oh, at least somebody will be there.
Yeah.
Those psychos.
Yes.
Oh, goodness.
It's true.
At least two people will attend X Day 2011.
Yeah.
You know what?
You heard it right here, folks.
It's way closer to me.
It's only a couple hours away from me.
I could actually go to Wisteria.
And.
Be there in a day.
Well, you know, friends.
You don't have.
It doesn't matter where you are on the planet Earth.
You will still be ruptured if your name is in the book of life and you are a true subgenius.
And what's that cost?
It can.
You can.
How much does that cost?
What?
How much?
You know how much.
You can't put a value on that on a public station like this.
You can't.
But you do.
So, well, I mean, you can't say that, but only a dollar.
I tell you how much.
I can't even say.
One dollar.
Oh, OK.
Only.
You can't say anything.
All you can say is for free information.
You might be interested in checking out subgenius.com.
That's right.
Let's go to your online resource.
We can't do a call to action.
That's.
We can't.
That's right.
We tell you to turn off your radio right now.
We can't do that.
It's against the law.
It is.
We wouldn't do it.
We can't.
We can't direct you to do anything.
Can you threaten?
Threaten?
Control?
And neither do we want to manipulate you into changing your opinion or mind about anything.
No, that would be wrong.
I really just hear that.
It would be wrong.
Your opinion is all right with us.
It's your facts we have a problem with.
You're entitled to your own opinion.
Is that Princess Wee I hear squealing with laughter?
Yes, you can interpret it as that.
I can't believe I heard that from him.
Get this.
Get this, Princess Wee.
Last night I had a drunk chick pinch my nipple at Speedway.
Ooh.
Story number two.
Well, there we go.
She was cute, dude.
She was definitely, she was definitely a cute.
A nipple pinching drunk chick.
She was a milk.
Nipple pinching a milk.
At an acute angle.
I heard that band one time, a drunk chick pinched my nipple.
Yeah.
What the?
Hold on.
Total cougar.
I mean, this woman was a total cougar.
What is going on?
Why?
I don't know.
And then she just, she just called me, you know.
She's like, coming in 2005.
I am.
Hello, mom.
Can I call the MF mom.
I'm scared.
Because that's what she said.
She said she was expecting MF.
Good Lord.
It is somebody in 2005.
Yes.
One hardly recognizes the old place.
All right, we're entering your mind now.
Oh, Tempura.
Oh.
Oh, moris.
Oh God.
It smells horrible in this mind.
It's so dark in here.
We have to go in through the ear.
Are these spider webs or what?
I think they are, but they're so incredibly tough.
They're slimy.
Yeah, you can wrap your camera in them.
Stringy.
It's all slimy.
There we go.
It's pulsating.
Now we're choking down the spinal tap cord.
It's throbbing and yellowing.
This is chunky fluid I'm standing in.
It's like, you know, kind of growing against my ankle.
That's the replacement fluid.
Oh, brains are gross.
I'm glad I'm a subgenius.
There we go.
I won't describe what just happened, but...
This is a common standard side effect.
Nothing really to worry about.
It looks a lot worse than it is.
You're fine.
It just does look a lot worse.
There's actually not much really even to remark on here.
This is such a common event and simple and really harmless in its own way.
It looks bad.
We'll grant you that.
The show must...
It's almost up to my knees.
Are you sure this is going on?
I, uh, I'm very sorry about that.
What's that happen so fast?
You know, if it's possible, we'll try to keep, uh, stuff like that from, uh, bothering you, uh, from, for the rest of your stay.
And then he gets a, uh, job as a truck driver for the Forest Service.
I know a guy who drives a truck.
Mama, don't let your babies grow up to be truck drivers.
Burp, burp, burp, burp, burp, burp, burp.
Stop, yeah.
He can't drive, but he's short.
He can do the multiplication table backwards and upside down in his sleep.
He can saw and whistle Yankee Doodle through a mouthful of soda crackers.
Put a brew in his mouth and it'll sweep the floor for you.
I recommend that...
What the hell?
Hire the...
I recommend it.
You're right.
I recommend it myself.
Okay, it's some kind of...
I recommend it...
I think it's some kind of cult, folks.
Don't call 848-4425.
And the police of my mind will come and rescue you if you call that.
Police?
848-4425.
I called in.
Don't call that number.
Now, if you call that number while the hour of slack is on, you'll get a completely different show.
Isn't that number gone?
In another state, and it won't even be this particular show.
Although it will probably be in this state.
Does the guy not edit that out?
The guy that runs those shows?
This week, that guy might not have time.
Okay, so...
There's not enough time for him to have edited it.
So in Cleveland, you should be hearing it like...
You're not going to...
Don't try to call that number unless you're...
848-4425.
Yeah, to call California.
Yeah.
An area code in Washington.
Wall-Way?
Oh, wake up, women here.
Listen to old Jenny Appleton.
Oh!
Let's remember.
You see?
A sunny smile plastered on your face.
Yes, it is.
You see?
A lie from an appleton is dropped into the car.
Get on track.
Why are you bothering us, old lady?
She's just trying to sing a splendid song.
But she's dead.
That doesn't matter.
It happens to the best of us.
She sings on and on.
It's actually my landlady.
I think.
She sounds so far away.
She's already moved on to bigger and brighter things.
So thankfully far away.
12 seconds.
That's the new world for you now.
Wall-Way?
Tall-A-Way?
Downtown's not the same as it used to be.
Well, she'll talk and then put the phone down and go putter around the house and then talk again.
That's your cue.
You call her.
All right.
Thanks.
I'm just, you know,
Petula Clark was a child.
Good job.
Even as a young subteen girl, she was a singing sensation on the British airwaves.
In fact, she was even the subject of a British comic strip.
I was coming in here.
Are you talking about Petula Clark?
Petula Clark.
Yes.
That's right.
It's true.
Petula Clark's career stretches back.
Back into the 1930s when she was the beloved.
Get a piece of pie, bud.
Childhood singing star.
Where are they now?
Sweet Petula.
Shut up the both of you.
Who cares where are they now?
Shut up the two of you.
If only.
Shut up.
I'm trying to listen.
Nice try.
Dr. Ducky Doolittle.
This is Ducky?
Oh, no.
No.
Who's that duck in the duck it rode in on?
If only it were her calling them.
Shut up.
I'm trying to listen.
Then it would be a more scientific sample.
You're a bunch of quacks.
Call yourself doctors.
But you're quacks.
The ducks rebuttal.
Quack, quack, quack.
That's why we spell doctor with a K.
Oh.
Doctor.
Doctor Howell.
Donald.
I'm like certainly enlightened.
Is this X-Day right here?
It might be.
These are common waterfall.
Mergens are ducks lying over the X-Day site.
Well, you know, the saddest of all is the subgenius who has so little imagination
that when he or she is ruptured up onto the escape vessel,
he can only...
I can only imagine his or her cheesy little apartment and crappy job.
And that's what the escape vessel becomes for that person.
And they never know that X-Day happened.
That could have...
Could that have happened to you, my friend?
No actual cheese.
Just cheesiness.
If you'll give up your record collection and your comic book collection here on Earth,
you'll have a better one when you get to Planet X.
I'm waiting for you.
Wow, look.
What is this?
Planet X has neon lights, not sodium vapor lights like Earth.
Actually, St. Palmer Vredes reminded me this very afternoon
that we ran the shark under the bus when we concentrated on X-Day and Bigfoot
instead of doing what he said, which was motivational seminars,
which I was supposed to direct.
He just would have the idea and then I would do all the dirty work.
Proving Palmer Vredes is a true subgenius.
...some time.
And has learned a lot from Dr. Philodrumon.
Find some other guy to do it.
What?
Nemzlow was an expert at that, too.
He would announce that something would happen and then wait for others to make it happen.
Usually it happened ineptly and poorly.
Causing him to rage against the dying of the light.
But it's not his fault.
Somebody else did it.
...against the dying of the light.
Cool.
No, he was still in...
Well, the probe is still in...
Nemzlow.
What was the worst devival?
Which was the worst subgenius show?
And what was the worst episode of that show?
Call in and let us know, friends.
I understand we were criticized internationally for our performance last week.
Lacking Dr. Howell, we apparently were not interesting enough or informative enough, perhaps,
for certain individuals overseas.
Who are these mouth-eaters?
Said that with all that talent, the show should have been a little better.
Certain Finnish-Mexican Americans have been known to actually criticize the show.
Who reside in China.
To raise a question as to whether the quality was up to the potential of the talent, such
as it was.
Do you approve teaching Chinese as a language in California's public schools?
...what's happening in Egypt?
...I wanna hear what's going on in Egypt.
...well, y'all, you got Pee-jo.
There are plenty of other stations covering that right now.
We're taking like a little rest.
It's all very easy to understand.
I don't think I can get a Pee-jo until after 6.
Somebody's mad and somebody else is mad and they're both like really, really mad at each other.
I'm mad too, Rachel.
I'm mad too, Eddie.
I think I had some of the stickers.
Yeah, right.
...you guys came back free, Rachel.
I'm mad too, Ed, I'm mad too, Bob.
I'm too mad, Bob.
I'm too mad, Alfred E. Newman.
I'm mad too, Alfred.
...I'm mad, Todd Bud.
...I'm mad-ow for mad-ow.
Yeah, I'm mad too, Mad-ow.
...that's a lot better than I'm-mad-too, Rachel.
Isn't it?
God, thank you, Princess, Wei,
for having that other half of the brain cell at home.
Sui-gaaaaaah!
Yeah, it's nice having the other half of the brain.
the brain cell? At least in the same
vicinity.
I've been driving around all day with just
my half of the brain cell.
So I could remember everything
but I couldn't enjoy it
and didn't know what any of it was for.
I'm the hard drive
and she's the processor.
Yes, you ain't seen
hard until you've seen my drive.
And now we're getting into a junior
version of the brag of the
subgenius.
The junior brag of the sophomore subgenius.
Brag of the imitated
subgenius actually is the most common
one.
Yeah, that is
very...
The worst, you know, almost worse
than the I'm a Bob, which is the
psycho who thinks he's Bob,
is the I'm a tater
who thinks he is tater.
Tater Gumfries of
scrub genius fame.
Yes.
A clear and plain
imitator, as you call him.
Imitating Mr. Gumfries.
And then the worst
is the dictator. Of course.
Yes, that's true. He can't keep it
in his...
What's the difference between
Castro and a jockey strap?
Castro motor oil.
One is a dictator
and the other
is the late Rudy Ray
Moore.
Did he die?
Yes, the great Rudy Ray Moore died
of complications from diabetes
I think last year.
Damn.
I hate thinking of that.
Yeah, he was known...
Most people knew him more for his
exploitation action movies such as
The Human Tornado
and Dolomite.
But I best knew him for his
Party records, released on
Kent Records, which he later
explained to me was his apartment
in L.A.
And, uh...
You know, the sad thing was, Dr. Drummond,
the whole time that we were worshipping
the Party records of Rudy Ray Moore,
he lived in Dallas,
was working as a waiter
at the Adolphus Hotel,
and occasionally doing shows,
but not at the kind of clubs
that we were cool enough to know about.
Oh, man.
Did you know that? No, I didn't know that he was in Dallas.
Yeah, he was in Dallas the whole time
that we thought he was in L.A.
L.A.
We thought he was rich and famous, and he was actually
famous and poor.
Right down the street.
Right there, ready for revival.
But his fortunes changed,
and as he told me in person,
Blockbuster had been
really great for him.
And here comes the check now.
Yes, the check, the royalty check
of Rudy Ray Moore from
Blockbuster.
Wow.
Ooh, that is a...
It's a little late, making a royalty check.
For a genius of comedy like Rudy Ray Moore
and his film crew.
But he was in his 70s.
He made it to his 70s.
Didn't he?
He didn't hit 80, did he?
No, he was 75 or so.
77.
He told me I looked like Bela Lugosi.
Well, at the time,
I didn't have the mustache and goatee,
and I wasn't...
He was, in fact, made up
as Cagliostro,
the ageless mason
magician.
And I did kind of have a
Bela Lugosi look.
I guess to him, to him, all of us...
So you gave him a pass on that one.
Gringos look alike, I suppose.
Yeah.
Well, they all look alike to me.
Yeah, you were saying,
Dr. Drummond, that you don't differentiate
between people's...
races, genders,
skeletal...
No, to you, everyone is exactly
the same.
Yes, I believe that, and sincerely,
that we all are here.
We've all got heads
and eyes and...
Do they work or not?
You've got...
Almost all of us that are alive do have a head
of some kind.
Some have more head than others.
Some have more head and some have
gray head.
Some have grand, swollen,
great heads.
We saw that great head today.
That's right.
Actually, we saw the tomb of great head.
A grave marker
marked great head.
Right next to the tomb of stupid.
You can get your advice
from the tomb of the unknown
struggling evidence show.
You never went to the Rosicrucians?
No, we never did make it
to the Rosicrucian temple.
Although we still got 15 minutes.
We could probably get over there.
Let's hurry.
Let's put the show in warp drive.
We'll make it over to...
Do you know the way to San Jose?
Yeah, it's right down that way.
That is where the Rosicrucian city is.
It's no match for Dobstown.
Not even the little American Dobstown.
A brawling, fighting young man
or the Brazilian Dobstown.
Or about a fortune for himself.
But no sissy-footed
liberal city council member
to tell him he can't have a barbecue
in his own backyard
or an electric train set in his garage.
A land as big as the mountains
and as wide as the green
rustling forest.
The call of the moose is heard echoing.
A sissy-footed great head.
And they do have that.
Hey, sissy-foot.
Your call screen.
Your call screener just now
was asking me some really weird
personal questions.
Really?
Well, we're trying to profile
everyone that calls now.
Do you have any searches on YouTube?
Yeah, we just, we have to know.
You know the way things are.
Do you guys really need a photocopy
of my house key?
Well, it would help.
It's not mandatory, but...
A clay impression.
If you could press it in a piece of clay
and mail that would be better.
This is me, see.
I'm an essential man.
Dental work clay stuff.
I gave you guys my social numbers.
I might as well just give you
fingerprints and...
Put your passport in there too
if you don't mind.
Okay.
There we go.
Yeah, that's all.
I just wanted to make sure that...
Really not that much.
I mean, we just know it's...
It's not like we're actually
going to use it.
No, but it's profitable these days
to...
The identity theft rings
that we circumnavigate.
I just didn't want to make anyone...
It's good that my...
At least my thoughts and ideas
are identified as my own
by copyright when I contributed
them to the show.
Pin number, please.
There's no price too high to pay
for attaining cosmic consciousness.
That's good.
Satisfaction, much satisfaction
was mine.
All I had to do was purchase
the introductory package
and I'm still as depressed as ever.
I cannot carry the package.
Yeah, it's...
Whoa.
You have to pack the package.
Now remember...
Pack that package.
As handsome as your package is,
you need the other junk.
The accessory kits available
at our subsidiary...
Our subsidiary...
At your free post office box.
The warehouse outlet
on eBay.
But I am much better dressed
than I was when I was following
them damn Jehovah's quitlessness.
Quitlessness, this says.
You mean like Michael Jackson?
So have you experimented
with many religions?
Uh, only...
Only this religion, A.
Religion A.
What am I supposed to say here?
The script is missing the phrase.
Say the first church of the last life.
Say first church of the last...
Laugh.
No, no, no.
Go back, go back.
Start again.
First church of the last life.
No method to unend the last life.
Proselytize the fruit members of the very...
I renounce all church.
I renounce the church.
I renounce Bob's...
The last church of the end of the world.
Don't listen to him, caller.
Say no.
Bob loves you.
It's the same old thing.
Now do the dance.
Do the dance.
Just separate it between...
That's enough, that's enough.
Okay, I know you know it.
I love you.
We know that you know the dance.
If you know the dance.
I live on the second floor.
I can't dance that much right now.
I just...
I'm already in trouble with this first floor guy as it is.
Once we make it to the first...
The hundredth caller.
All the callers will do the dance.
Together.
When the...
They won't have any choice.
I just have to recital...
Critical mass.
I just have to recital Fireside Theater albums now.
Yeah, the hundredth caller.
The hundredth Hitler.
The hundredth Manson.
Two Twilight Zone for me, man.
The hundredth.
It takes a thousand months.
It takes a thousand.
It's a sign up ahead.
It takes a hundred monkeys in our religion.
Not a hundred.
I hope Dick Cheney knows where you live.
You've just crossed over into...
We need a four thousand monkeys in our religion.
I hope the Fireside Package has arrived okay.
Chain Dicky.
Dick Cheney will walk the streets on the day he dies.
He's on the Fireside Theater.
He's back to doing a weekly show.
Dick Cheney shall rise.
Yes, I do.
Send one to each show.
He shall rock the streets of this land.
I didn't send one for Bishop.
I'm sorry, Bishop Joey.
I didn't send you a Fireside Package.
I was probably joking.
Oh, man.
Do you want one?
Bring it to the party.
Only now you see the error of your ways.
The folly.
The sheer folly.
What the music says is I am going to...
The pieces of error.
Oh, the damnation of imprecision.
The music is too damn loud.
Her bathroom.
It is too damn high.
Her bathroom is a special kind of place.
Oh, my God.
He turned it down.
There's a smile on everyone's face.
I actually...
I was trying to get him to turn it up, but he actually...
Is Doug sick?
Is there something wrong?
No, he's just a little out of sorts.
You see, he's been...
Oh, just a moment.
There's only one toilet on this floor.
You know, we're performing a mass ritual.
His aspirin worked too well.
Ah, yes, mine is burning too.
Well, all we're going to do is move the medicine cabinet a little bit over to the left.
We're going to keep all these...
The same medicines...
Watch the medicine.
Yeah, no, we're watching.
So, you want to keep the...
Don't let it fall and keep the sink there from falling off the wall when we loosen the bolts.
Protect the saint at all costs.
I knew this would happen when I moved.
Too late.
Is this what we get on the album, or do we have to pay extra?
Oh, no, they're free.
I sent you guys a book.
Ah, okay.
Oh, here it is.
I found it.
Put down the book.
Slowly.
Come to the window.
Come to the parade.
Sweet is the night.
That's right.
The 33rd annual Saints' Day Parade will be taking place this year in San Francisco.
Wait for it.
We're going to get the Embarcadero Plaza hat and boots.
And then that night at Rhythmix Cultural Works,
the...
You stupid art show.
We'll be having a big...
Here it comes.
Rhythmix Cultural Works.
So be there.
Here come the youth.
I know, I know.
But you know, you never know.
I'll be there with you, Bishop Joey, as will all the other members of this self-same cast of crazy...
And then again, again.
I am so glad I became a subscriber.
I get to go to the parade before everybody else.
Yeah, you were the guy that got there real early, right?
I am already at the parade.
Such pointless boasting.
You're already waiting for the parade.
Vainglorious bragging.
Where are they?
You know you never know, but you know you never know, but you know you never know.
The parade was so good, I became trapped in Echoplex.
Parade of Progress.
Echoplex.
You know you never know, but you know you never know, but you know you never know.
Am I dreaming, or am I dreaming?
Or am I dreaming?
But you know you never know, but you know you never know, but you know you never know.
No, seriously, I sent a book to the station, I hope it arrives.
I sent another book to the station.
No, seriously, this show is messing with my head, man.
I guess I'll go and look and see if there's some book.
Or if you're just talking some jive.
If you're just talking some jive.
jive. They're great.
Now it's messing in
my head. Puzzling evidence
went out of the station
to look for the book you
had sent. The show is out of control.
And as far as I can look, you didn't come back
with no book, so you're right.
You lost my friend.
He was driving a minute ago.
Yeah, your book is here.
The show is about to hit a tier.
Yes, your book
all for next week and
yeah, an end further than that.
The book of death.
Companion to the book of life.
Not to be confused with the
Tibetan book of the dead, which
goes with those zombie movies.
In the hall of Anubis, the lord of the
dead, when your
judgment shall be made,
your good deeds
weighed against your evil ones
and your soul
given under the custody
of the sealed and sacred
forbidden valley of Hadoff
in Neferab.
Hot dogs, cool.
But beware,
the shambling reanimated
mummy may enact
terrific vengeance.
This is what most Americans know about
Hobo Chang Bao.
The stupid of you.
Oh, God.
Yeah, that's what I wanted to say.
I heard a rumor that the
St. Stupids Day parade is not going to be
held this year.
No, no, we have to we have to skip it.
But but since next year is canceled,
we have to move next year's up.
So we're going to do next year's parade
this year.
OK, so they all move back one year
for the next century.
So this will be the 2012
parade. This will be the 34th annual.
OK, good.
We're skipping the 33rd.
We won't do it this year.
What happened? Somebody mistakenly
Well, our lawyers, I think we got a call from the Christians.
They said 33.
They own 33.
And we look good later when they try to figure out why there's no 33.
Yeah, so we skip.
It's like a building with no 413.
This is a religion with no 33rd anniversary.
We sure didn't have an extra.
Every time this happens, we do this.
That's why they call it a tradition.
Yeah.
You can count on it.
I mean, you know, every 33rd year, skip.
Skip.
We'll do this the 66th year, too, right?
Yeah, but only half as fast.
Oh, okay.
What about the 99th year?
We'll do it.
We can do that upside down.
That's great.
When we come to it, young fella.
We're pretty much in the 99th minute of the show here.
And then, of course, Rhythmics, Cultural Works, the Art Gallery.
Okay, well, I guess we go back to the regular thing next week, right?
Yeah, yeah.
Just regular.
Everybody, just take a step.
Take a breath.
Regular or pay attention.
Take a step backwards.
A puzzling evidence show.
A puzzling evidence show, but also like the religious summit of all the various, well,
two various religions.
It's a veritable potpourri, a potpourri.
Bingo.
A potpourri of potpourri.
Yes, that's what it is.
It's an ecumenical salad or perhaps sandwich being shared by two great religions.
Yes.
Ecumenical moment.
Would you pass the ketchup, please?
And we're here to commemorate it, the closing moments of our special version of the Puzzling
Evidence Show featuring Reverend Ivan Stang.
That's right.
The head of our order, the Church of the Subject.
I'm just going to go out chanting and dancing over here.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Well, it was the cleaner of the head of our order.
The head of the order is down the hall.
Oh, good.
I got the 13 minutes delay on it.
Now we're approaching the most amazing part of this ceremony.
The ceremony of sacrifice.
As the bobbies give forth one of their nines.
To be the food of the bomb.
In this mysterious and obscure mystical way.
Somehow the immolated flesh of the willing victim shall be converted to that of the
E-pop of the Church of the Subgenius.
They say themselves the semi-legendary J.R. Bob Dobbs himself.
In a moment we'll see the playing begin.
The first round of special torment being prepared by the International Board of Nurses Assistance.
And from Oslo, Norway, this is Ralph Fielding Snell signing off and wishing you happy sportsmanship
in the future.
My ears hurt.
It's wrong, I know, but it's a national security matter.
And that's all there is to it.
Well, they're kind of like them Smurfs.
They're real mean and they ain't blues.
Psychodromic.
Don't play.
Standard tool for therapy.
Done.
Ten to twelve hours tops.
All of the cells of your body will dissolve into a kind of organic stew.
I'll give you this in full flow.
I'll be the force of the region.
So much has been happening.
So many strange things.
This place is driving me crazy.
There's a dissident hiding in the hotel.
It's like the Nazis never ended.
And from where I'm sitting, I don't see any sense in you jumping off any building.
No.
Well, thank you for listening.
Go to sleep now.
You must get a good night's sleep.
I wake up and there are many totally unfamiliar surroundings and noises in the morning.
Let's imagine that you're deaf to the word and the bricks kicking right now.
The morning bird has scared me nuts.
When suddenly...
Eww!
I have to scrape it off my shoe and get it off.
I've read a bit once and for all.
It was great.
Just let it talk.
Fine, great.
Not thinking of the past.
Me too.
It wasn't strange.
Maybe impossible.
The experience was strange.
It was almost...
Erotic.
I don't want you to think that it was casually, wantonly sexual by any means.
I never would have occurred to me in a million years.
Now, why?
It was something...
It was friendly.
You know, this would be vaguely feminine.
Guiding.
Quick, run.
The car's been lit a spit.
It was a hot fire.
I thought I told you to go to bed.
You'd better go to bed.
I'll let you both just see what happens when the birds go with you.
What do you know about this?
You had a long, good time, your own...
Special.
I'm sorry.
I was just just trying to get at you.
You know, we never followed you.
There were no rules for you.
Do you believe it?
I wonder if I can use it when you get away with it.
You're everything I wanted, everything I want to be, everything we all would like to be.
We know better.
We don't take the chance.
We know sooner or later it always catches up with you.
A few minutes long, the wind out, and you'll be spinning in the wind.
What is it going to end?
Oh, you can try and forget the whole thing.
I like to work.
It's better to go home, see the apartment, or see a movie.
Just when I think I've got it, visualize it.
I just don't know what to write.
I start seeing old-fashioned classical reality again.
No one out there can help us.
What's that supposed to mean?
Nothing.
Didn't you hear about it?
It was awful.
You ought to have heard about that.
That nut who listened to the radio?
Well, the sun comes up at six in the morning.
Got 50 men, jeeps, horses, dogs.
I want to call Flagstaff and get two helicopters.
That'd be enough.
I don't know.
He talked so fast I got confused.
Imagine.
A thousand-year-old mind inside a 30-year-old body.
You don't mind my saying so, Doctor?
You seem a little tense.
Something the matter?
No, nothing's the matter.
You seem tense.
Like a cup of coffee?
Isn't that mind control?
What do you call compulsory education through high school?
Okay, that's it, fellas.
Now you're my friends.
I'm not your friend.
I'm your friend.
And I take classes at the Ajax School of Broadcasting.
Would you possibly please take a look at my tape, you know?
Please?
This is the tape?
Yes, sir.
It sucks.
Just one thing.
What?
The next time someone wants to see me, I'm going to be the one to do it.
The next time someone wants to blow their brains out on camera, let them.
Now.
Open the mic, you did it.
Well, another tragic tale of what happens when condoms and firearms are mixed.
The next time you see me, I'm going to be the one to blow their brains out on camera.