Princess Wee and I are here at the Afrofest. Thanks to our friend Charles
Sinocor for setting this all up as a grand show so far.
Representing our upside, and that it should be, at the Afrofest, it could be Tread Ball.
We'll see you at the action.
And if the world doesn't end, we'll see you at the Starbucks.
And with Afrofest, what we're trying to do is to educate that you all know that we're
what?
One blood.
Those of you who were not here when we started, you know that we're not here.
We're not here to open this show.
We found the oldest person in the house tonight.
And we had him come up here, well he was sitting up here, and he poured elevation.
One drop.
It is one drop of blood that connects each and every one of us.
We are brothers and sisters.
And we are all from the continent of Africa.
Forget what they tell you.
They will call you clowns.
They will call you white.
They will call you evil.
They will call you tucosoid.
They will call you warthog.
This is the age of what?
Information technology.
You go to Google.
You type in mitochondrial Eve.
Or you type in African Adam.
The way it leads all the way to Africa.
Except we were dropped off here.
We were brought here by aliens.
That we know that we don't belong.
But as far as you here and you believe you're human, you are African.
No matter what your skin color or your eye tone, we are all African.
So that's why we're here.
To celebrate Mother Eve Africa and Father Adam Africa.
Afrofest!
Stick around!
Happy Mother's Day!
Oh yeah don't forget, that is right on time.
When you are here.
One of the things that bothers me is that people think that there has to be something so amazingly powerful and wonderful up there looking after us, taking care of us, smiting our enemies, rewarding us with manna and good deeds.
But at the same time, it bothers me that nobody seems to realize that there is something up there that is more powerful, more amazing, more incomprehensible than any of these so-called deities.
It's the universe.
And let's face it, the universe is a very singular place.
It's a place where a very simple molecule of gas spend a little time changing itself into clouds and stars and galaxies and solar systems and planets.
And dare we say it, life and life evolved to reach a point at which.
Some.
Somewhere in this vast universe, there is a life form that has evolved with enough faculties and abilities and mental acuity.
To realize.
That the universe is amazing, enormous, fantastic, incomprehensible, but wonderfully entertaining.
And that's what we need to realize.
The universe has created.
Created us.
So we can appreciate the universe for what it is.
That's the only reason we're here, folks.
So just enjoy.
Sit back, relax.
And be entertained.
Just enjoy the rest of this film.
Life Draw by 27!
Estẹ
аль!
Well, welcome to the Hour of Slack.
Brave, buff, bold, and honey-dragged.
Yes, welcome to the Hour of Slack.
La, la, la, la, la, la.
La, la, la, Hour of Slack.
The only cult they want to talk about is the Subgenius Foundation,
the Church of the Subgenius.
Dad, Doug Smith says we're different.
Doug's right, Virgil. We are different.
Thanks to Jesus, the Genetic Engineering Corporation of American States.
Mommy, too?
Yep, the whole family.
Is everybody like us?
No, son, but we're working on it.
Round the clock!
Messages from invisible sources.
Or what some people think of as progress.
Well, ain't the heathens use smoke signals all through recorded history?
How's that a fucking recommendation?
Well, seems to me like letters posted one person to another
is just a slower version of the same idea.
When's the last time you got a fucking letter from a stranger?
Bad news about Paul.
Bad news.
Tries against our interests is our sole communication.
So by all means, let's plant poles all across the country.
Bestune the cocksucker with wires to hurry the sorry word and blinker our judgments of motive, huh?
He's giving it more thought than me.
Ain't the state of things cloudy enough? Don't we face enough fucking imponderables?
Does it seem like you're not getting money for your payment anywhere?
Instead, Prosper's not another settlement, repayment, or consolidation program, but money.
Repudiation protects your money, lets you keep your unsecured debt payments.
Prosper better quality lives for money.
Money-free future.
8393.
Okay, hi.
Hi.
Oh, uh, how are you?
I'm bi.
How are you this evening?
Uh, I'm very high.
Uh, so, uh, it's very to you, so, uh...
Mm-hmm.
Great.
And, and, and, uh, uh, too.
Mm-hmm.
Hello?
Can you hear me?
Yeah, I can hear you.
I can hear you.
Oh, Galactic Federation.
Okay, very good.
Uh...
Alright.
Oh, hey, Henry.
You know you can't bring Arthur to school.
But he's my best friend.
No, he's your best lizard friend.
You've got lots of non-lizard friends.
Not really.
Really?
Nope.
Bob has been busted having an affair with a nurse.
If I go down, I need to know.
Busted having an affair with a nurse.
His son-in-law, Dr. Gunna, oversees the family.
Bob has been busted having an affair with a nurse.
Uh, a cannoli.
A knish?
That's not exactly that.
It's more like peanut butter and jelly inside burnt toast.
Oh, yeah.
I'm sorry.
And once you know that, you can cut them a little slack.
Besides, you'll have plenty of time to aggravate them in your teens.
From PR News in Washington, I could do significant damage to PR.
The final four Republican presidential candidates touched down near Birmingham, claiming two
lives and leaving at least 100 others hurt.
Authorities today were working to determine whether there were any additional victims
of Mitt Romney-Newt Gingrich.
If it walks like a duck and quacks like a duck, it is a duck.
.
The European Union has joined the United States for another televised debate.
Government and police will need to obtain a warrant.
An Alaska woman who took on Newt Gingrich using a grain shovel was apparently able to fend the animal off.
According to a report in the Anchorage Daily News, Gingrich began stomping on the woman's husband.
Officials say the 85-year-old woman grabbed the shovel and began hitting the animal.
I'm continuing to pressure PR News in Washington.
Today is a time when every subgenius, every piece of equipment is measured against the unrelenting standard of
moment when you and your Cagalent긴 the day-by-day efficiency of your own efforts
Martin, get up to the bridge and check out.
... okay, right away.
come together, where each serves the other, and all serve Bob Bob Bob on or under, and
all serve the total organism that is the shirt itself.
Yes, Mark, what is it?
Maybe you better have a look, Bob Peter, yourself.
Something wrong?
It's dirty.
Looks alright to me.
It's just that it seemed to come up a little slow.
Hello.
Subgenius Information Center, where when the chips are down, the shirt is bought from,
where each subgenius feeds the others, and all together feed the demands of Bob to carry
out its mission.
It's the church of the subgenius, where you and the other very special subgenius, the
ones able to analyze, test, repair, and maintain the electronic nervous system by doing a subgenius
job.
I want the earth for myself, and that is why I have brought you from the far planet, Dr.
Botanist.
You will go and conquer it for me.
Yes.
You might have some trouble with the church of the subgenius.
And Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob.
It's all.
But the gargoyle barn will easily destroy them.
The world will be in your power before long.
Good.
Only Dr. Botanist can control the plant monster.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
Bob!
Swear to God!
It's all Stanks' fault, and I've had enough.
Reverend is laid down trying to hide another seizure.
Makes you clever to see through the subterfuge.
I've been letting it go.
But if the idea is for you to drink more and more till I say something, I am hereby officially
saying, I wish you would stop drinking now.
fucking drinking.
I have
no fucking ideas
as far as you saying one fucking
thing about anything
I do or don't.
As far as drinking
or where I stand or nap
or any other fucking thing
concerning me.
Or go or leave or don't
or when.
Alright, Jane.
So you can go fuck yourself
and don't try and hasten anyone
anywhere. Because everyone follows
their own fucking pace
and don't try and fucking hasten them.
And
don't try and hasten them
although I think
Dave has... I don't know if my
certificate is in order or not. I've been listening
and I got a little nervous
at the end because you said you were
that everybody needs to measure
their equipment and mine is low.
Just don't feel hastened,
Dave. Don't feel hastened.
It's all Stang's fault.
Yep.
Blame it on Stang.
Well, Legim is
always trying to take the
credit for the blame
these days.
Although sometimes
Pisces gets it.
She said she couldn't call in tonight
by the way because she's moving.
Yeah.
Well, unfortunately, you know,
gravitationally, electronically speaking
I mean on the electron level
we're all moving at all times.
Even if we don't think
we're moving and they stick us in a casket
or one of those, what you call it, tubes
send you to outer space or whatever.
Oh, the worst is the time machine.
You go five seconds ahead in the future
and you're in the outer space because the Earth
just moved out from under you.
Yeah, I never considered that until just
a few years ago. I mean, until
just now. I didn't really
the first time.
It's a great thought. I wish I would have thought of it.
Well, let's see. Here's
what I haven't done yet, Dave, is
the credits. And I also
haven't
we didn't tell you how much
fun we had at the Afrofest last
night.
I remembered you were going to remember.
Yeah, well,
our previous show,
Charleston's show,
African Abstract,
we just now realized as he was leaving
that he, Princess We,
and I all have something
in common. We run
a festival.
He's done Afrofest,
this is the fourth year, I think.
And Princess We
started with Starwood
170 years ago.
That's in Neanderthal.
She wasn't
really one of the main people then, but by
evolutionary
forces,
she's become one of the
main people behind that
festival. And of course, we have
X-Day coming up.
I think I've already been through my X-Day
paranoias.
And I'm, uh, we slacked
off yesterday.
And didn't worry.
Well, Princess We didn't
slack off, really.
Starwood's a much bigger
headache than X-Day.
And there were many, much more
heads there. But the thing is,
although the heads are smaller,
I don't mean there were bigger heads.
If this really is,
if X-Day really happens,
I should say when it really happens
this year,
she won't have anything
to worry about. We'll just move the whole
campground to my
escape vessel.
And we'll have Starwood.
And all the hippies that paid for Starwood
will get the full show.
And then some.
And then the ones that haven't bought
their subgenius membership by then
will be ejected into outer
space or sent back to the
giant crater left at the former
site of Starwood.
But that's what happens to the
unsaved, the disbelievers.
Speaking of belief and everything, let me do the
credits real quick here.
Credo, I believe.
Did you hear the
fellow talking about
life, the universe, and everything at the beginning?
Yes. Right after Charleston's
rant? That was G.
Gordon Gordon.
We heard Charleston
doing a quick little
rant about early
African origins of
humankind, which I've
also been boning up on,
as it were.
He said bone. Well, fossil
bones.
Denisivian
Denisivian bones.
Sounds lewd and disgusting.
Or Ignatian bones
and Neanderthal bones and stuff.
That sounds even leuder. Anyway, that was
G. Gordon Gordon doing the
science talk about how
the purpose,
the purpose of life is to
enjoy yourself.
To entertain.
And he should know, because
I'm not sure when he
had his 70th birthday,
but I think it was a while ago.
A while ago, yes.
And he'll be at X Day. In fact, he'll be staying with us
at X Day.
But the OK So All Stars
did our title.
Doug Smith says we're different.
It's from Invasion
of the Aluminum People.
1979 or 80
by the late
Reverend David Boone. There was a little
bit of
Deadwood,
you might say.
You know, that takes some
cuss cutting.
The internet version doesn't
sound the same as the version we played
on the air.
Oh, and the collages
were almost all by Reverend
Decapitator. Reverend Royalist
Bill Decapitator. The music,
the instrumental music in the middle was
The Psychoskeletons.
I like both of those very much.
Both
Psychoskeletons?
And also the
other, which you
mentioned before. The other musical.
Oh, the new PR
news is by Reverend
Cosmic Debris.
Ministry of Slack did the
subgenius readiness
public service announcement.
Those were funny also.
Everything was. And then at the end
there was, that was Calamity Jane
on Deadwood talking
about, don't try to hasten
nobody. Man,
I must have removed nine
cuss words from that thing.
I imagine so. Sometimes you can tell.
Yeah, and that's a magic number too when you think about it.
Thrice times, thrice times,
thrice did you remove this swearing.
Three times, three times
three did the blasphemes go.
As you retreated into
the potato room to argue
with the flower.
Oh, and just so I get this,
so I don't forget, the music, the nice
music in the background is by
the Flyin' Ryan Brothers from
their album Under the Influence.
A new album from
Ryanetics
music, ryanetics.com
R-Y-A-N
Ethics.
And
I don't play them much on ARS Slack.
Because they're kind of like too good.
And pretty.
They have a little bit of an early XTC
feeling before they became
what you call it, pop stars.
And also a little bit like
Nevermind. XTC.
Dave, you know so much more about music
than I do. I've never even heard of it.
But that was just like the very first album, I think.
Yeah, thanks to Philo
I am familiar with
early XTC and
nothing else after that.
There was a time when
Dr. Philo Drummond
was collecting
he had an actual job and would buy
actual albums at actual
record stores. And it was
the beginning of the punk period and
he would just go buy band names
and album art.
I guess he could afford
to do that.
I could do that with
MP3s for free.
He was a collector of cultural artifacts
at the time and he knew it because
because
he had that kind of vision
which only he had at the time
which that they would be as collectible items
because there would soon be
no more records. But now they
in a neo-McClunite sense
the damn things have been reinvented
and now kids that were not around
alive during the punk era
have punk bands that have to put out vinyl
on 45s.
And somebody in Germany buys a thousand of them.
Right.
What I don't get is
hippies came back.
They all did both concurrently.
I mean
in that they wear
these kids these days
they wear the same
dang haircuts
and tie-dye crap
that we did.
Only they still have all their hair.
It ain't fair.
It just ain't fair I tell you.
It's the civil, well like if you're into
real things retro it's the Civil War
look. A lot of people are
depopulating France now.
Removing their underwear and climbing
on the balconies in the middle of the night
waving you know thinking like somebody's gonna let them surrender.
But
I don't know if that's happened yet
but I assume it's coming just like everything else
is.
Everything that ever happened I'm afraid
is going to happen again including
the dark ages.
Yeah I just heard that on an old radio show
and it was called the Galactic
Barrier. And you get out so far
and it was like you know some
prime real early belief
in the finite
universe or something you know
as explained by mathematics.
And they hit this bump and then they go back
to where they started from.
Well it is a finite universe
in that frankly
you know I hate
to break any young person's heart
and I could easily be wrong about this.
I quit making predictions myself.
But I predict
that the
ideogularity will beat the
singularity and
you know
just as these
I mean I was raised
thinking there would be hotels
on the moon by the year
1977.
Yeah.
And we didn't even get the flying cars.
Although as Dr. Howell has pointed out
Hugh Hefner
has a flying car. You can buy
a flying car but you have to file
a flight plan every time you go
somewhere. Well Hugh Hefner
is a mummy. I mean he's a mummy.
He's like one of those reincarnated
you know the kids on
he's been alive for like 4,000 years
and stuff. Right.
I only call him St. Robert
St. Janay or St. Germain
type guys. Oh yeah St. Germain.
Yeah. And he can't
get a haircut because he's been you know
he's been through a thousand barbers
or millions of barbers maybe
even I don't know if that makes
any sense or if I even care but
I noticed those people on X minus
1 when they were doing they're talking about the galactic
barriers like it's like
1987.
And we have reached the
center of the galaxy.
Yeah. One final
thing for men to discover and then
at the same time they had ships
whistles and guns that went
ooga ooga. They say now
hear this and stuff. Right.
And the spaceship
control panels looked
exactly like the old radio
control panel from KMON
in Dallas. Exactly.
Or their sound. The
sound. Actually I very frequently in old
movies will see
sound mixing studios
old timey film
sound
you know because they have spinning reels and lots
of dials and things
dashboard
speedometers that spin around
could still make a lot of like Christmas
tree lights go
it was a
wonderful time
a time so few
remember because
there's nothing really to think about
there. It's just a happening.
Well I don't think anybody really could
think a whole lot until a certain
point. And of course that was when
that was beginning of the end thinking
and even worse talking
yeah to use this
around talking about stuff and then thinking
about it in human language.
The tool tool using is actually
where where it starts going
really bad. Well
some say it was rocafort cheese.
Was the era was the
end and beginning of all things
as far as civilization and walking
you know on two feet goes.
Well you know we started
the show with
Charleston Okafor
doing a little rant about the early
African origins and I
have spent
actually this whole weekend I've been
re
researching my
paleo anthropology because
the stuff I was raised to know
was all wrong.
And and
you cannot get that the
latest stuff from a textbook because
it's coming too hot and heavy.
Two years ago
Neanderthals were completely different
species and couldn't
interbreed with humans.
But one year ago it
was proved more or
less at least for the time being
until somebody comes up with something
else that not
only did.
Neanderthals breed with humans.
So there was another species called
Denisovians.
I only read this stuff.
I never hear it pronounced so I don't know
how to pronounce things.
Nobody talks about Cro-Magnon man
anymore.
It's now the Aurignacian culture.
It's actually given a name of a culture.
Well from 35,000 to
45,000 years ago in the upper
Paleolithic.
In Europe.
That was when the Neanderthals
started to vanish
and were apparently
replaced by people
who had come out of Africa
who had
were much more adaptable.
They had what we would call
a modern human brain.
They had developed that linguistic thing
that the big talking that led to all
the trouble.
This stuff that's getting us in trouble right now.
They had invented.
F.C.
Yeah.
They had invented the first figurative art
such as pornography.
The earliest one.
Yeah.
The earliest known art that looks like
something is a Venus that someone found in a cave.
Wow.
You once pointed out that the very one of
the some Neolithic painting in which a person
is sitting on a woman's lap and farts.
And you said it was.
What?
I don't know if maybe it was.
I thought it was you who told me that.
And I later Googled it and or whatever it looked it up.
And it's it's a painting of a woman or someone sitting on a woman's lap.
And the joke is a fart.
Well if I said that then you get a little lines.
That's Jimmy Hemsworth's argument palace and so forth.
And you know the various subcrop or crow crow towing whatever they used to call them in
ancient Virginia.
I'm gone.
I don't know.
And that's where I'm going.
I've had it with this place.
I'm going to Crow at the end.
Well obviously Dave did pick up on it.
Well I was one of the early in a previous life.
I fled the colony.
And Wolf where was Crow Crow at the end.
Crow was just the name of a couple of people used to pass by on trading expositions expeditions
once in a while.
And a lot of them said well I'm going to go with you.
There's a lot more happening that way.
I thought it was the name of an Indian tribe in Virginia.
What's now Virginia.
But the guys who came the second wave of colonists who showed up expecting to find some colonists
found nobody.
And the phrase gone to Croato and carved on a tree.
Don't we have a T-shirt.
Well it's hard to think of that.
That could be New Brunswick or Korea or someplace near a city in the ancient Philippines.
But one thing is for certain is they got out of there and they probably walked out with somebody's help.
And there were probably enough people around if they brought you know walked a half a mile.
Somebody pointed you know in a direction if they didn't speak whatever language it was never dance it or.
Oh most those Englishmen that came over here and even the ones who were like you know the landowners educated version of American.
Early American settler and governor types.
They didn't know Jack.
If it hadn't been for the the occasional natives given them a clue like hey you know you have to eat some vegetables or you're going to die.
Yes.
That kind of thing.
They never would have made it.
No.
They certainly would not.
Everybody.
Oh God.
Today I spent this afternoon reading up on Easter Island just because I got curious about it.
Princess.
We have a holiday.
And you forgot what year you are actually been.
Well you've been returned a few times.
But you forgot what year it was.
Well I did.
We had started with.
Princess Wee's mom sent her a picture of people digging up one of those Easter Island heads.
With big ears.
Yeah.
And we were all like wow they have bodies underneath.
And I was all like.
Yeah.
They're aliens from another planet that are going to be activated any second now.
Because I read that in a Jack Kirby comic book a long time ago.
But it turns out they've actually been digging those things up since 1990 and re-erecting them.
The what do they call them?
The something like Maui's but it's not.
Maui?
Yeah.
They are called those big statues.
I may not be pronouncing it right.
Again I only read this stuff.
I never hear it.
So I don't watch TV or listen to the radio.
But it's especially not this show.
But yeah they're called Maui's or.
Anyway you want to hear a quick.
Do you want to hear an impressive very quick history of Easter Island?
Cool.
Because I was you know when I said Maori I thought I was you know stressing the Polynesian connection.
Well they were Polynesians.
Dating now has them settling.
Settling that island around 700 to 1200 Common Era or AD.
And about the same time Hawaii was first settled.
And get this.
Those guys and gals had to sail 3,000 miles from where they were to get to Easter Island.
The nearest inhabited island to there now is Pitcairn Island.
Which is 1,200 miles away.
But they weren't coming from that direction.
They were coming from the other direction.
And somehow.
I mean that's some mighty navigational skills.
Yeah.
In catamarans.
Well that's why they call it the Middle Ages.
You know what I mean?
We kind of took a step backwards there in the European culture for a couple of almost a thousand years.
Well it happened to then.
And it's still happening technically.
I'm sure it will again yet.
And the Easter Island.
The Easter Islanders.
It's a.
God.
Everything that could go wrong eventually did.
I'm sure it was great at first.
The pre-European population of Easter Island.
Which is only 15 by 7 miles by the way.
In size.
Kind of triangular shaped.
The pre-European population was about 7,000 to 17,000.
It's hard to tell.
The.
Had they.
There were only three types of trees when those people first got there.
But they brought their own seeds.
And they had 21 to all kinds of different trees.
Including some of the biggest palm trees in the world.
But.
Even before the Europeans got there in 1722.
A Dutch ship landed there.
The Easter Island natives or Rapa Nui people.
Had extinctified all land birds.
And most sea birds.
And 21 species of trees.
In other words.
They had grown too big for their island.
And were starting to decimate the environment.
When the Europeans landed there.
Of course they brought the miracle of rats.
Which wiped out all the rest of the snakes and lizards and things.
And smallpox of course.
Measles and TB and so forth.
By 18.
Oh God.
It's horrible.
After the Europeans arrived.
Not that they necessarily had anything to do with this.
There was a war on Easter Island.
As people got more and more desperate.
The ancestor cult that built the statues.
Was defeated by warriors who were called the Bird Men.
Who have a similar group on Hawaii.
And they toppled all the statues.
Things continued to get worse.
In the 1860s.
The Peruvians started a slave trade.
Sailing to Easter Island.
By that time there were only 3,000 Easter Islanders left.
And the Peruvians made half of them into slaves.
Leaving only 1,500 people there.
By 1877.
There were 111 inhabitants.
And that's the story of the Peruvian people.
Of the Rapa Nui people.
Of whom only 36 had children.
In 1982.
A census showed that the population had grown.
Thanks to an Englishman.
Who basically bought the island.
And declared it a world historical site.
You know.
And allowed only tourists.
And kind of controlled things.
And they tried to bring back as many natives.
As they could.
But.
And to this.
Today there's about 2,000 Rapa Nui people.
Or about 70% of them are Rapa Nui.
Although they're mixed with Europeans.
And other Polynesians now.
So the Bird Men won.
And then they lost everything.
Oh and in 2010.
I had no idea about this.
The natives had a wounded knee.
Remember wounded knee in the 70s.
In wounded knee South Dakota.
The American Indian movement came in.
Yes.
Took over a drug store.
Basically.
In the little town of wounded knee.
And the FBI.
It almost turned into.
Well the government didn't respond with a drug store.
They responded with a bunch of armored vehicles.
Yes.
I know all too much about that.
The guys who started that.
Russell Means and Dennis Banks.
Lived in the house that I moved into.
Right after that.
In South Dakota.
So I.
In fact.
I did my best to prove.
I did my best to prove it.
To prevent an invasion of Crow Dogs Paradise.
But the feds weren't heading for that Crow Dogs that day.
They were going to his cousins.
Where they.
In fact did find a big stash of hand grenades and machine guns.
Because these Indian guys were all Vietnam vets.
You know.
That was back in the 70s.
Anyway it was interesting to find out that the Rapa Nui people in East Dakota.
Easter Island tried to do, it was like, hey, we got cheated, and this little hotel here really belongs to us, so we're going to take over.
That was in 2010.
And the Chilean government owns Easter Island now.
They came in and said, no, you're not.
And nobody got killed, and nothing happened.
Well, their voice will continue to be heard, because what a weird place and what a weird story to think of it to begin with.
Yeah.
3,000 miles, and they said, this is purely anecdotal, but I do remember hearing saying that ancient Polynesians could, like, feel the water and stuff,
and all the currents over here, and their star things were incredible.
It's incredible for the time, and for now, I guess, even.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's, well, you know, some people would say, well, they must have been helped out by aliens,
because only aliens could build them giant heads, and only aliens can dig ditches in the dirt that look like ants from overhead in Peru,
and only aliens can build pyramids.
No.
Either well-paid civil servants or thousands of slaves or both can build pyramids.
And stonehenges and Easter Island heads.
And, yes, yeah, you do have to haul giant rocks a long way, but that can be done.
Plenty of fishes and papayas.
In an area where there weren't any trees to have as things to roll on.
Well, they had plenty of trees for a while.
The same thing happened in Iceland, didn't it?
Wasn't it denuded, and now it's like, but luckily they have thermal underwear and so forth?
They do have a lot of thermal.
Well, they're getting into new information technology ways of growing things,
self-enclosed units that capture the sunlight and then make the water do something else,
and then turn on the lights and then turn the lights off when the lights are down,
because there's no agriculture, as you would imagine, in Iceland.
People indigenously lived off fish, period, and some kinds of lichen and moss and stew.
And things like that.
But I guess even potatoes wouldn't grow.
But now they can grow like killer hydro, dude.
Yeah.
Dude, it's like from Iceland, man.
It's frosty.
Yeah, have some frosty, dude.
I got it from the snowman.
Yes, silly land.
I mean, why would you, you know, and everybody worried about their bank crashing.
Well, I'd be worried more about the kids, you know, walking into...
It's an ice banker accidentally walking off a cliff into some penguins and stuff.
Well, apparently a lot of them went to Norway to get jobs.
It's a fine place to get a job, Norway.
Norway.
Norway, man.
Another pool of the imperialist sausages.
They dangle and dangle, and in the middle of the night you wake up
and there's another imperialist sausage passing by.
There's another cream puff.
There's another blah, blah.
Well, it's like the more history you read, the more it just keeps repeating itself.
Somebody has a revolution and then they're all going to do things cool this time.
And then one of them goes, yeah, but my way's a little cooler than your way.
And I have a bigger club than you.
Basically, it's the...
I have more people in my clique than you do.
Yeah.
And then he gets poisoned.
And then...
It's basically the bad guys win because...
They're the only ones that are willing to totally, you know, screw everything up real bad.
Well, actually, that movie Team America, World Police, explained...
Oh, yeah, the whole coin.
...society in one little rant of which I cannot use any of the main words on broadcast radio.
But it is the truth about all of history.
And it's...
I can't...
I can't even begin to do it.
No, it can't even be paraphrased.
No, it can't even paraphrase it.
It wouldn't make any sense.
Well, nothing makes very much sense anyway, so you can paraphrase it well.
You can just, like, come up with a statement and, like, and then repair it, say it a different way.
And we, you know...
Hey, what do you think?
How do you think we kept this dang church's subgenius going since 1979?
If you want to tell a lie, tell a big one.
And tell it over and over.
And everyone would believe it.
That's called television.
Yes.
Oh, did I...
I may have told you about this, Dave.
About the irradiation of your nether parts.
I heard it again.
You were trying to couple with a big screen digital.
I was trying to bring mammoths back to life was all I was trying to do.
Anyway, no, that wasn't what it was.
I got a letter from a TV producer from the Learning Channel.
They said, we're doing this show about people with...
People with...
Weird obsessions and collections.
And I read about your alien abduction online.
And I had to write them back and give a brief, fingers crossed description of Church of the Subgenius and go,
you really misunderstand.
I've never been abducted by aliens.
And I don't even believe in that stuff the way people talk about it.
I did write an article about an abduction experience that I later knew full well to be just a standard,
night hag dream that people have had all through history.
They used to think it was witches and leprechauns.
And now it's turned to gray aliens.
But yeah, I had one of those dreams too after seeing the movie Communion.
But I got to throw in the phrase, since what we're doing is a complex bashing of gullibility and superstition,
I doubt that our material would work on mainstream television.
I got a big kick out of saying that to an L.A. TV producer.
Because they always treat us like garbage.
The only time it's ever been done right was the very second Showtime What's Up America in 1981
did a good piece on Subgenius because the director was Reverend Larry Silkus,
a subgenius and co-writer of Ghosts of Mars.
These are hot lick stinkers.
These guys go after the...
If it leads, it bleeds.
I mean...
If it bleeds, it leads thing and stuff.
And every other common denominator known to the people of Twelve Toes.
They just come up with stuff, you know.
And they know it's going to...
It's going to...
You know, it's going to...
It's going to tell somebody.
It's going to...
You know.
Well, it's what sells.
You know, what gets most advertisers.
Yeah, if it bleeds, it reads or something.
If it bleeds, it leads, yes.
That's always been...
It's always at the top.
Well, you've been...
You've been studying on that stuff,
so you probably really, really know how much it bleeds.
Oh, boy.
Oh, man.
You can do pretty much anything without having to resort to technology.
People's minds are easy to screw with.
You noticed that.
I mean, it's beyond this, you know, the marketing class thing where they say,
Well, if you repeat something three times,
usually the consumer will keep the image in their mind.
Sometimes you, you know...
How do you think I felt when...
When the richest person I've ever met...
Wanted to marry you.
Flew into the Cleveland airport using his private jet,
probably spent more on fuel just landing than I made the whole year,
and wanted to meet with me,
and what he really wanted was to meet J.R. Bob Dobbs.
In other words, I don't know how to put this in a nice, subgeniously religious way,
but the...
The richest person I ever met,
who had inherited...
He was the heir to the ball seed fortune,
was the most gullible, stupid person I ever met.
And yet, I still was not able to keep a straight face,
and string him along, and bleed him for a million bucks.
I was too honest.
And I was too disgusted by the way he treated his wife and kids.
He banished...
He banished us to the other side of the room.
We weren't even able to sit with Reverend Stang.
He had that corrupt British nobleman type of disdain
for everything that came issued from his loins.
Yeah, he wasn't interested in talking to Princess Wee,
and he wasn't interested in having his wife involved.
He was a philosopher, and he wanted to talk to me,
but I think he assumed that I was just this clerk
who was like the front man to keep idiots away from...
J.R. Bob Dobbs.
You know, it's funny.
I've had top rock station drive-time DJs
right here in Cleveland assume the exact same thing.
A spokesman for the Bob industry.
This guy actually believes in this Bob dude, okay?
Like, he got this Fraud of the Year Award of the Century.
Fraud of the Century in Time Magazine in 2000.
I didn't know who he was,
so I looked him up.
And he's like this crackpot who preaches aliens,
and this Reverend Stang guy,
he believes in this Bob dude.
Every now and then I play that little clip on this show.
Oh, man.
That was done perfectly by yourself,
doing even the change of character.
Well, it was only one guy,
but that was quite...
said it all.
And that's one reason why we don't do...
fluff pieces with TV shows
or drive-time radio jackanapes.
Well, who cares what Sabrina Hazoukian
and any other people with, you know,
their lip mascara and their nostrils
being dissolved by different acids and stuff like that.
I mean, who needs to live in a cosmetically frou-frou world like that?
Well, I wouldn't be able to afford to myself.
It's the old problem of...
I spent $400 this week
just to show how I don't care how I look.
I don't care what people think of how I look.
Check out this tattoo I just spent $1,000 on.
See, I don't care.
Look at this crazy alienating hairdo
I just spent my whole month's income on
to prove that I don't care what people think.
I'm so old I remember when people used to
buy stonewashed jeans, you know,
which are, you know,
the way that jeans are going to appear
in the next century and stuff anyway.
So, you know, just wear it for a while and stuff like that.
And all of a sudden I realized that this is a vast,
has progressed as a vast industry of,
what do they used to call them?
Antique.
Yeah, pre-distressed.
Distressed furniture.
Where everything's a cultural artifact with,
well, it's not real, but, you know, there's dirt on it.
And I even saw it, went to the Walmart and stuff
and went to the work pants and stuff.
And now they've got the phony farts.
They've got stains on them.
And I'm wondering, well,
were these actually farted on in China?
Or is it, you know, like...
Or is it just printed on?
Yeah.
Do they have these kids that they force feed beans to
and then they can put on pants after pants?
Dave, I think we're approaching the borders of good taste.
Well, I just, you know...
Or maybe we passed them a while ago with that kidney stone.
Oh, God, that still hurts.
Oh, yeah, man.
This hurts for a long time.
Afterwards, I'm still undergoing a massive extraction
from my comp with it.
How is your comp, by the way?
It's going well.
In the thinking room, there's a dome place in my house
where there's a thinking room and a map.
I'm sorry.
No, I think much like yourself and like Princess We,
we no longer want to rule the world.
No, I don't.
We just want to find a narrow nostril space
where a freaking space alien could conceivably,
not, you know, superstitiously,
but really come in there somehow
and make the huge palm trees come back.
Well...
And so to speak, in life, make the big palm trees come back.
Wish in one hand and vomit in the other
and see which one gets full first.
Slap.
I can't quote Bob on that.
That's another radio phrase that can't even be uttered.
Nope.
That's what you have to remember, though,
when you buy into this sport,
that there's a lot of things that are blanked out
and you have to fill in the blanks.
No, I remember Bob's quote.
I'll try to do it tastefully.
Extra meditate in one hand and puke in the other
and wish you had a third hand.
I think Onan may have channeled that.
Those are words you live by.
And at least, you know, in a vague proximity.
You don't want to live right next door to them
because people who vomit in one hand
and wear their love lust on their tins like another...
Okay, I'll say it.
What was I?
I thought I was in the...
I haven't been in the thinking room,
and I've been avoiding it.
We went to...
What did we do yesterday?
We went for a walk.
We went to a movie.
Thinking shots.
And we went to the Afrofest.
And I played my video game.
I helped Stangor in the deserted island of Moga Woods.
And I've been sparing the radio audience tales of that.
I don't know how much longer.
You know, at some point,
somebody's going to tune into Hour of Slack,
and it won't be Reverend Stang talking.
It'll be Stangor,
who sounds sort of like Tarzan or Tonto
or Frankenstein's monster.
Why Tarzan or Tonto?
Does that go back to the old...
Well, in the game...
Me say this or something?
My first video game is called Monster Hunter Try.
And it takes...
My character is a monster hunter.
That's Try with an I, not a Y.
Yeah, it's the third version of this game.
It's the first time I've ever understood
how people can get so wrapped up in video games,
but it certainly has happened to me.
In fact, that's about all I can think about doing
as soon as we get out of here,
which will be very soon.
If we've got three minutes to mention that
we have three weeks till X day.
And...
And because of that,
we should do a live show next week
so that I can play my canned shows here
while we're gone.
Although, in theory, Dave,
the Sunday before X day
and the Sunday after X day,
I'm hoping, I paid for the plane ticket,
Dr. Howell will be here.
And us and Dr. Howell can do a show
and maybe he can come in
and be on Radio Synesthesia,
which will be on in...
one minute from now.
But Princess We won't be there
because in four weeks,
it'll be the Starwood Festival.
That's right.
So Princess We will have to miss
the in-between festival.
I may have to drive from Wisteria
back to Cleveland and back to Wisteria,
but we did that last weekend with no problem,
aside from our alternator going bad
in Marietta, Ohio.
But it went bad right in front of an auto zone
after...
ten minutes after Pisces said,
you know, it's unlikely,
but you might,
if you happen to see an open auto zone
on the Sunday before Memorial Day,
they might be able to help you.
And by golly,
by 11 o'clock the morning of Memorial Day,
we were back on our way to Cleveland.
So praise Bob,
praise Pisces,
praise auto zones.
Auto zones, kind, gentle giants.
This is a call to action,
but we did have an experience
that worked out well,
a particular one.
Is this Providence?
Look down with a smiling face.
Well, this Providence is
the Church of the Subgenius radio show,
Hour of Slack, number 1363.
For more information about this crap
we're talking about,
you can go to subgenius.com.
Subgenius does not have an O in it.
But it's in your mouth.
And I...
I...
Oh, and thanks to the Flying Ryan Brothers
for this great background music.
Especially Jimmy Ryan.
He's the subgenius of the band.
Sweet sound carpet.
Often saw the invisible
and far, far be fetched.
At least...
Oh, sorry.
That guy, I don't know.
I did that on Hal's show
and I had to cut it for this show.
The audience here hasn't heard that yet.
And they won't.
Hal kept going,
if there's no cuss words in it, it's okay.
It's the words.
It's not the concepts.
I was going, no, Hal.
You misunderstand.
The words in certain contexts
are perfectly legal,
especially in Safe Harbor.
It's the concept.
If the concept is obscene,
it doesn't matter whether there's
bad words used or not.
That's why our toes are tied up like this.
And we must get off the air.
Exactamundo.
I tried not to sound like an old guy
having a sexual condition.
You failed.
Well, I was doing something else.
It just sounded the same.
You know, the resonance was a little bit similar.
There was a vibrational movement in between.
And that's the way it went.
We were all experiencing synesthesias
just a bit early.
I was going to talk about...
You're vibrating the hell out of that place right now.
Vot for you're going to talk about
Reverend Stank?
I'll do it next week.
Reverend Just John had this great concept
that we could have gone on about for an hour.
We'll do it next week.
There will be another hour next week.
Until Rob comes over and taps you on the shoulder
and says,
so, I request that seat.
I see.
Thank you, and good night, Dave.
Good night, Princess Marie.
Good night, radio listeners.
Good night.
I hope you have a great day.
Do makes.
a different, modern, and motor übrigens.
Thank you.