From PR News in Washington, I'm filing false statements.
President Bush is hungry.
Americans understand that you should live in poverty.
In stocks 494141, this is PR News.
PR News.
PR's bad.
Iraqi justice officials say state troopers have the power to arrest PR News in Washington.
Car.
Is it them?
I think so.
Yeah.
It's the self-genius.
Power of the self.
Stop.
God.
Bob.
ABBA.
This is the hour of Computer Science Senseiwhat-is-it nel
Thank you.
Dave's are here in the studio.
Just covered with snot and sputum and all sorts of other weird membrane erections and heads.
Yeah, we just got back from 9X Day.
And, oh, and this is in the background.
You can hear the Billy Nair show.
We got some good recordings of them.
But only nine people showed up and all of them were holograms.
Well, no, that's not true.
What about those?
Could you believe what those women were doing?
I couldn't believe anything I saw there.
I'm still in a state of total disbelief.
I've got your mic turned up as far as it'll go and mine turned down to balance us.
I'll try this one.
Does this one work better?
I can't tell any difference.
There's no difference.
See, we're friends.
The world didn't end.
There's no difference.
But it almost did.
I'm certain that it almost did.
Oh, wait.
Maybe I have the wrong.
Here we go.
I had the wrong mics.
Now you can.
Now you're louder.
Now I'm louder.
Yeah.
I'm not loud.
There we go.
Friends.
Like I said, the world didn't end and we're exhausted after this incredible two-week X-Day.
It's only supposed to last a week.
Yeah.
And you're not supposed to have like a protracted period after it with all these invasive procedures
to make sure this implant is going to work and that implant is going to work.
And, you know, they had us ready to go, but nothing happened.
Or was it something?
Well, that's again.
Again, it's like every X-Day, something happens at 7 a.m.
And, well, as here.
Look, here's one.
Here's one.
There's a crack in the horizon.
There's a diminution in the dimensional shift, they say.
That's what they, you know, that's this fake sign, the pseudoscience reason they give for
why something does happen every X-Day.
But the X's don't.
Well, we don't know.
Maybe they did come.
Well, as far as.
As far as a lot of.
I don't know about them.
They came, all right.
Yeah.
But it was obvious that a lot of the subgeniuses were all over, especially after.
Right in the middle of the robot pajama ball.
That was disgusting to me.
I'm sorry.
I'm not sure you're.
Well, I have.
You notice I had to stand up there and announce that I had never seen anything like this at
an X-Day before.
And it was not planned by.
Oh, here's the recording of your band on Friday night.
I think.
Oh, this was.
Yeah.
Let's see if Princess.
She was here.
She can sing.
You can sing.
I probably should.
Does it sound pretty bad?
This is a bad.
When they blow the world away.
We shall have paradise.
Subgenie of the world unite.
Alien sex every night.
Subgenie of the world.
Subgenie of the world unite.
We shall have paradise.
Alien sex every night.
Subgenie of the world.
Subgenie of the world unite.
Oh, and this is back to Billy Nayer show.
There you go.
It was not a naysayer show.
That's for sure.
Everybody was full go.
But things still didn't go exactly the way they had that gravity machine where the guy
could skip along back and forth in front of the stage and he kind of float.
Yeah, it's like he was.
He his gravity was set to about.
What?
Maybe two thirds of what the rest of us.
I thought you said three fifths before, but whatever.
It's still.
I tried to get on the on the thing and do it and it tickled so bad I couldn't stand it.
He must practice on it.
Well, the part that kind of freaked me out was that I think you always have to have on hand at least two or three paramedics, not just the ability of a paramedic or two somewhere there.
You know, there were three emergency room surgeons.
Yeah.
You know, I mean, I've never had a surgeon subgenius as at my next day, but they shared each other's medicines and they were all completely passed out when a little problem happened.
And I can't believe that Nikki Death Chick was able to sew that hole up in that guy.
He was just using a girl.
Right.
And I'm trying.
Yeah.
Oh, twine.
It was twine.
Friends.
Yeah.
When subgenius is camp out.
There should be doctors around and there should be doctors conscious.
There should probably be the National Guard circling the perimeter with bayonets affixed to.
Don't you think?
Well, I certainly do.
Actually, there's after getting shot in the eye with a toothbrush for crying out loud, man.
It was a strange X day.
And a lot of people I'd never, ever seen before.
And I don't think anybody had ever seen before.
You know what I mean?
Were they really?
People.
Well, you know, we had that warning about that U.S.
Any employees of the U.S.
Government had to present identification and present their weapons and stuff.
And there were three of them that did.
But then there was that other guy.
Yeah.
The 10 percent.
Friends.
Oh, here's a good.
This is a song by a Cleveland band, which we should shut up for.
This is a really good song.
The Kirkendall Boys.
This is a good song.
When we were out on that Saturday night.
Oh.
Oh oh.
When I saw Sunanda there?
It was lonely right?
I went into a ship with a little green man.
Oh.
nasty Kosci.
He was singing this song.
Stern.
Cathy.
acy.
members of the human race
It's time for
Playing 69 from Outer Space
Calling all the members
of the human race
It's time for
Playing 69 from Outer Space
Playing 69
from Outer Space
Bandit because
they are the stories
Playing 69
from Outer Space
Calling all the
boys and girls
Girls in the U.S. of A.
It's your full plan 69 from outer space.
Doesn't really matter if you're black or white.
Anything is fine if it feels all right.
Calling all the boys all over the world.
Grab yourself a girl and give it a whirl.
Calling all the girls all over the land.
Grab yourself a man and a wingman fan.
Life in a spaceship.
It's out of this world.
Love in a spaceship.
Playing 69 from outer space.
Come on, little girl.
I don't pop a word on the phone.
Can one of you play this song?
That 50% is the thing I skiing from girl!
The guy I've been bangin' all day.
If you meet your girl and you do a hundred percent 1.
Into her head I'm a-"Lambretta."
No, she thinks you're the fucking king of her song.
That's all the world out there.
The wide range of their Hitler dressed withancials.
wrath and all that they desire.
Get together.
Hell yeah.
69 from outer space.
Plan 69 from outer space.
Outer space.
That's a Cleveland band or somewhere around here called the Kirkendall Void.
Yes, and they have an Eddinoid on the background.
It's just wonderful.
What about the tombs?
Not in the band.
They weren't.
They weren't able to show up and we couldn't afford them.
No, I'm not referring to the band, the tubes.
I'm referring to the tubes meant to enclose the individuals who get too close to certain of the activities.
What happened?
Did they just discard them the way they discarded those Iraqi tubes?
You didn't see the giant colon educational walkthrough display?
I was part of that.
Oh.
I was.
We were lucky to get that.
First to be a part of it.
There's always some weird props out there at Brushwood that the hippies leave.
Like there was a motorized dragon one year, remember?
And there was like a crash flying saucer one year.
A strap on third leg that you could just impress people with.
And yeah, I remember a lot of strange appurtenances and devices.
Well, you get a lot of crazy people at these subgenius gatherings and some of them are kooks.
Yeah.
They're kind of, you know, go to a regular, get up in the morning, go to a regular job every day and believe the world is round.
You know, crazy people.
Classical schizophrenia is what it's referred to.
Yeah.
God.
Friends, we had a slack day, believe it or not, at a subgenius event.
We actually slacked off on July 4th.
All we did was take time control lessons and we took turns watching Jupiter through a telescope.
And, you know, when the, finally, and then later on CNN, they started putting it on TV.
When the two storms on Jupiter formed that pipe and then erupted and those monolith things lining up in pairs shaped like X's, it was totally, totally weird.
Took my breath away for three and a half hours.
Once again, paramedics were nowhere in sight.
I had to be pounded vigorously by various subgeniuses.
The subgeniuses who passed by take a turn trying to revive Dave.
Did you know that Nikki was selling chances to pound your chest and try to bring you back to life?
I heard about it, but I didn't get any firm confirmation.
She made like five bucks.
Yeah, well.
Because she was only charging 50 cents.
It was just a joke as far as the money went.
We really did try to bring you back to life, and I'm sorry.
What a hell of a way to do it, to have extremely large women, like, bang their buttocks against my forehead.
Other large women bang their buttocks against my chest, screaming, breathe, breathe, you son of a, you know.
Well, some of those pagan.
Is that medicine or is that?
Yeah.
In fact, I saw a workshop about that at Starwood once.
So now you're importing this, you know, this yimmy glammy hippy hippy stuff to X days.
Hey, you weren't complaining when those large women were enrapturing you.
Well, I was having a dream at the time.
I was semi-conscious.
Large pink women.
Yeah.
I noticed.
Literally pink.
Yeah.
Which meant they were under 38, I guess, or something.
Isn't that the way they say?
I was jealous, Dave.
Because I like them.
I like those big gals.
You were jealous and I was jaundiced.
Yeah.
It's always that way.
Always...
And I noticed the smell that, you know, like I'm diseased or something.
It's like following me around.
I'm wondering if it's following me.
Yeah, a lot of people know that.
I noticed that smell following you around.
Did it follow from brushwood or...
Yes.
Oh, okay.
I can still smell it.
Because...
Well, that...
You know what it probably is?
Is you probably got a little bit of layer of unburnt pyroflatulation on you.
Because I noticed...
I got too close to that one, yeah.
We had this chili cook-off of So Genius International World Chili Cook-Off.
And there were some very, very weird chilies.
But...
And then we had this pyroflatulation bout about...
Five hours later.
There were some scorched eyebrows, believe me.
Yeah.
Worse than that.
One guy actually...
Did you see that?
One guy actually burned a hole through his pants.
Yeah, I saw the blisters.
Like, it exploded.
He was a typical, you know, subgenius Bobby showing off the scars and the...
The amateurs, they don't even believe that you can really pyroflatulate.
Half of them had never seen it done before.
They thought it was an urban legend.
And then when that first six-foot-long flame came out of Rocknar...
There's always...
You could see that half of the people there just about died.
Yeah.
Because they thought...
They really thought it was going to be special effects or something.
But it was the real thing.
It's not even a laugh at first, you know.
When a crowd sees that for the first time, it's like a...
The sad thing is we don't know whose chili was the most productive.
Because everybody had a little bit of each kind of chili.
There was some kind of dolphin chili that really did have dolphin in it.
Yeah, no tuna, all dolphin chili.
And there was a can of those.
There was a guy...
The guys from Australia had that roo chili.
Yeah, the pouchy pocket they called it.
Which really did have dried kangaroo jerky in it.
And they served it in a pouch pocket, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
It was kind of gross.
Well, I think what is weirder is the fact that nobody still knows whose it was.
You know what I'm saying?
Not the chili, but who lit...
Whose...
Well, we got videotapes.
Whose equipment made that happen?
Well, we have...
We're going to be looking at the videotapes.
I think...
Rocknar won with that very first blast.
But it's real hard to see the inch measurements on the tape measure.
So it's like a toss-up between Rocknar and Reverend Funny Name.
Then there were all kinds of people hanging around.
There's like five people called Reverend Funny Name.
Are there five people named Reverend Funny Name?
Yeah.
I'll have to change my name to Reverend Funny Name.
I noticed that afterwards there were all these people crowding around the dental tent.
Yeah.
I couldn't believe this.
Teeth were actually ripped out of their head, brother.
They wanted to do that, too.
They were in the whipping tent.
Yeah.
Like, my arm got tired.
They really enjoy that.
I got tired of watching it.
It reminded me of The Passion or whatever it was.
Yeah.
I had to go to sleep for another half an hour.
And then I was rudely awakened again by more of this malodorous faulty ball.
You know, people trying to amuse themselves with their body parts or without them.
Yeah.
Which was even more frightening.
I was kind of surprised that some of the people had such...
Low inhibitions.
I would not be able to do that in front of people.
Me neither.
And I don't think they're legally supposed to.
Yeah, no.
It is against the law, especially in New York State.
And isn't there an age limit?
Like, people over 90 are not allowed to do that?
Well, it's a health hazard.
They have to sign a release or something with their power of attorney and their children.
Did you see the liability waiver on the back?
Here, I'm going to read it.
I was exposed to it.
This is what people had to sign to come into X-Day.
I, the undersigned, do hereby certify that I must be completely insane to walk into this place
where I might witness or be induced to perform terrible acts,
which acts will probably be filmed and streamed to the internet.
That'll start next week.
And I likewise recognize that I will be much safer staying outside the X-Day gates.
That's what they have to sign right after they pay the $60.
It basically says,
I could get hurt and you will film it and make a fool of me and I can't do anything about it.
Sign release, put wallet here, go lay down.
Although, actually, Dave, every year or so,
I have to spend a night removing breastages from the Subgenius website
because every year some formerly young girl decides it's time to get a job
or talk to her family again and they suddenly go,
Oh, my God.
All those pictures of me.
All those pictures of me running around naked at X-Day.
Especially the woman with three breasts, you know.
Please take those down.
It's kind of fun because I have to find the pictures.
And you know how it is when you're editing pornography.
It gets to you after all.
I one time was in the office of Screw Magazine in the layout office.
Remember Screw Magazine?
Alan Goldstein.
Yeah, Alan Goldstein's thing.
I think, I guess it's still around.
No.
Well, he's in bad shape.
But anyway, at the time that Screw was flying high, so to speak,
the layout was being done by a subgenius woman named Sister Chris,
who is now married to subgenius Reverend R. Stevie Moore.
Sister Chris worked, did the layout of Screw Magazine
and she invited me to come meet her at work when I was in New York one time.
And I walked into this room and had a long conversation
with a young woman.
Young woman my age.
I was young in those days.
Surrounded by photographs of oral activity.
That's wonderful.
Everywhere the eye went, there were BJ shots.
Nice black and white prints.
Which is benign German.
I mean, it was an awkward and strange hour.
Broward.
Because everywhere you looked, there was this, you know, mouthful happening.
Ballsy, germane.
I'm like, you know, Hank Hill.
That kind of makes me nervous to be, you know, in mixed company in a room full of hard, hardcore
pornography.
Well, it-
Sister Chris was a real sport.
I think-
I think her deformity was like a third neck.
That was her deformity?
Yeah.
Because I was just going to say, I noticed that a lot of, speaking of New York City and
the subgeniuses who come from New York City, the women that you mentioned, I noticed that
a lot of them in the banking industry are afraid to expose a third breast.
Because there are federal banking laws prohibiting the, if not wearing, the actual growing of
a third breast.
Now, I don't know what this has to do with the flow of gold or how people in foreign
countries and the Euro and the, or what it means.
But boy, you got a hard time the next day after the next day with the eraser on the
old computer.
Getting rid of that middle.
The middle breast.
You don't want to expose these people to, not the law, I guess it's the Uber law or
something.
See, I pay extra for those.
Oh, of course.
But then you know, you've got these-
For the uncensored ones, the unphotoshopped, three-breastage teasers.
But once one of the secret society weirdos sees one of their own cavorting around in
a thing like X-Day, then there can be problems.
Duct tape and the old Comet cleanser.
Lonesome cowboy Dave, it's true that Princess Wee returned from an X-Day once and they were,
her photo was her coworker's screen saver.
Oh, jeez.
It had not taken long and she had to beg the person not to go giving these links around
to everybody.
She had her clothes on and everything because she's a space princess.
You know, we don't do, we do more like fantasy.
Yeah.
We do more like art postcards.
Not that-
It's more tasteful.
Yeah.
It certainly is erotic, but you know-
I did all the hard-
It's not blood time.
The hardcore stuff.
My hardcore career is behind me basically.
Well, it looks like it's behind you.
Yeah.
Me and Ron Jeremy have similar problems nowadays.
Well, you know-
And Hendrix.
Hendrix had the same huge problem.
He had an engorged sphincotta?
Yeah.
You've got to look forward to X.
10.
And things that should never, never be done.
Every year is like a learning experience.
If you don't want an engorged derriere, if you don't want pictures of women with three
breasts, if you don't want doctors actually taking each other's medicine and not giving
it to the people who need it, you know, you write these things down, you put them on your
spreadsheet, and then you go from there.
10.
X Day 10.
Yeah.
Oh, that'll be the real X Day, because it'll have an X for the 10.
You know, X means 10.
Yeah.
It'll be the true X Day.
X Day X.
Yeah, you'll say X Day X.
And that's what it'll be on the artwork too.
And if there was an ad for it, that would be X Day Ad X, which would be a palindrome.
Bob is a palindrome of mine.
It's an old song by Norbert.
It'll probably be shortened to XX.
By the way, that music that was on in the podcast-
In the background earlier, the first musics were by Lonesome Cowboy Day from his Friday
Night Concert, but the hip saddick did the Where's Bob one using an old Onan Canobite
riff.
And I think, oh, and then Ed Fred did Ghetto Bob.
That was the very last one.
And now we're hearing the Moog Cookbook.
Smells like...
Teen spirit.
Teen spurt.
And it did smell that way backstage.
I thank God there were a lot of younger-
God, the X Day stage, friends.
On Saturday night after X Day-
Seaman's Day is at your service.
The stuff that you...
You cannot walk across the stage without slipping on the fluids, the foul ichors and eruptions
of, I don't know what, pus and other things.
They're just like indescribable body fluids.
Some are clear, some are white with a slight pink stain.
And broken glass everywhere, broken televisions.
People walking on broken glass and having no-
Broken amplifiers.
No pain, no...
Well, the amino acids always break their equipment and all these TVs.
They get these cheap TVs and they make a wall of TVs that's on the whole show.
And then they do Mongoloid and then smash everything.
And only this time, they carried it the next logical step further and actually did the
human sacrifice, so to speak.
I don't think the guy died, but-
Well, he was a Mongoloid.
He won't be breathing without a machine's help for a long time, maybe ever.
I think you can expect some complaints from, if not the SPCA, but the Society of Prevention
of Cruelty to People with Autism or whatever it is.
But no, it's-
I don't know if you can expect that.
I think it's the actual Mongolism.
But, you know, I think that went way over the line.
Taking an actual Mongoloid and sacrificing him to Icarus by putting wings on him and
trying to get him hot.
He loved it, though.
He loved it.
He really thought he was going to be flying to the sun.
Yeah, right, right, right.
But how easy is it to fool a Mongoloid?
Did you hear the part where he goes, well, if I get too close to the sun, won't the wax
melt and the feathers will fall off?
It was as if he had heard the original legend or something.
Right.
Or he was smarter than most of us because he thought of it first on his own.
Well, it could have been engrammatic.
We don't know if it's stamped into the template of all our DNAs.
We don't know if this myth-
The myth that if you reach for the sun, you will get burned and die and everybody will
laugh at you and go, look at this subgenius.
But look at what Wilbur and Frank Lloyd Wright did.
I don't know what they did.
Forget it.
I'm sorry.
Now, those were Ohio boys, weren't they?
They were Ohio Dayton boys.
Yeah.
That's what gets invented out here every now and then.
The seersucker suit.
Really?
The X Day Jughead hat.
You remember those?
Those were the first few, actually.
They kind of phased out.
Those were before my time.
That was when Dobbs was actually running the X Days himself.
Yeah.
The old guy himself.
I don't buy it.
Why does he never really show up?
I mean, really?
Because he's tired of getting shot at.
There's always somebody who goes, yeah, Bob.
Kill Bob.
Yeah.
And they think, they usually really assume that some guy playing Bob, and they always
assume, oh, well, he's got like a body armor on because they always say kill Bob, dude.
So they kill an actor, literally, you know?
Well, yeah, right.
Well, not kill him so far, thank God.
Or thank Dobbs, dude.
That's why we have the liability waiver.
You know, we ought to play a song.
This is like the ultimate name dropping song by Saint N. Because I think it names every
subgenius except you, Dave.
Oh, well, I'm glad to be listening to this, then.
I can hardly wait.
That's great, it starts with a handshake.
Exits UFO's outer space.
J.R.
Dobbs is not a freak.
He is the eye of a hurricane.
Watch your money burn.
Thinks of their own needs.
Yet he's of your own needs.
Feeding on a purse with grand gay strength.
End times are close at hand.
Uber woman, over man.
Lyra in a fire representing all we hate.
With a government for higher end.
We're the only one who can do it.
We're the only one in a combat site.
The best is less a genie in a hurry with a con breathing down their neck.
Group by group, normals falsified.
Full fox, look at that load playing.
Fine, then.
Uh oh, oh no.
Population, they don't know.
Save yourself, serve yourself.
Pink, serve their own need.
Yeti, serve your own need.
Time to plunge your own seat.
Yeti with a rupture in the rubber in the right, right.
You super slack maniac.
Slam, fight, bright light.
Feeling pretty psyched.
It's the end of the world as we know it.
It's the end of the world.
As we know it.
Bob feels fine.
July 5th, X day.
Pleasure ships are on their way.
Quit your job.
Keep your slack.
Jared Os is got your back.
Hail Connie, hail Bob.
On your knees, stop right to slog.
Give it up, give it in.
Find yourself, you Yeti kid.
New religion, radio.
Help, hope gonna blow.
Pay to find out what you know.
Pass the pipe.
Take a check.
I'm telling you, this is no joke.
Spirits see, steer clear.
Turn a minute, turn a minute.
Turn a minute, lie.
Offer me solutions and you offer me alternatives and I decline.
It's the end of the world as we know it.
Bob feels fine.
I'm leading a family so I wanna make sure they left an homeland too soon.
Oh, it's the opening night.
Threw her, heroic.
Don't ask was Hemery Callar, do you need to ask the lies if you want it.
It's the end of the world
The other and other, John Tom Mars, Immortals living behind bars, Yeti driving fast cars, bang!
Reverend Ivan Stank, Jesus Christ and Princess We, Smoking for Auburn, so do we, Reverend Susie, such a floozy, Dr. Piss off St. Anne, one more time, I know you can, anti-Christian, Reverend Geo, doctors getting right, right!
It's the end of the world as we know it, It's the end of the world as we know it, It's the end of the world as we know it,
And Bob feels fine!
It's the...
...end of the world as we know it.
of the world as we know it
It's the
end of the world as
we know it
And Bob feels fine
One
Take me off to space
Come on down you saucer man
And take me off to space
Take me off to space
Come on down you saucer man
And take me off to space
Stick needles in my belly
Take samples of my skin
I don't want to be
I don't care as long as I
can live with Saucerman
I know that you don't take requests
but I'm a special case
Come on down you saucer man
and take me off to space
Take me off to space
Come on down you saucer man
and take me off to space
Take me off to space
Come on down you saucer man
and take me off to space
Hey, cattle mutilators, let me join your crew.
Give me a knife, you bet your life I'll cut up cows for you.
I don't care if you're some kind of ghastly fiend without a face.
So come on down, you saucer man, and take me off to space.
Oh, take me off to space, take me off to space.
Come on down, you saucer man, and take me off to space.
Take me off to space, take me off to space.
Come down, you tiny robots with your little nipper claws.
You pale and bug-eyed aliens with wide and clammy paws.
Life is just a sucker's dream and death is a disgrace.
So come on down, you saucer man, and take me off to space.
Oh, take me off to space, take me off to space.
Come on down, you saucer man, and take me off to space.
Take me off to space, take me off to space.
Woo!
Yeah!
That was just wonderful.
And we know you're here.
You're just a nut sack.
The Reverend Ivan Stein is going to perform a three-way,
three-way performance.
A performance operation with the...
No, I said I'm not going to do the three-way.
Oh, yes, you're going to have to because...
I'm not going to do the three-way, Daddy.
You signed the way, and the way we know, so let's get right on down.
I'm not going to get in a barrel with that brain cell.
Put your hand in there in the brain cell.
No, I'm not going...
I don't want to touch the brain cell.
In the barrel, in the barrel, you know!
I don't want to touch the brain cell!
In the barrel!
Friends, that was Take Me Off to Space,
performed and written by Nen Slow,
the most hated subgenius on alt-slack, also the most talented.
And somewhat beloved, most beloved, in his own peculiar way.
And I believe Dr. Ahmed Fishmonger was playing guitar.
There was a now-famous girl singing in the background.
Well, two of them, two authoresses.
Mrs. Nen Slow, Donna Cossey, who wrote the book Kooks.
About you.
She and Nen Slow, yeah.
And...
And everybody, the brain eaters and everybody.
She and Nen Slow live in a house called the Kooks Museum.
The Kooks Museum.
Oh, and also Pagan Kennedy, who's some sort of an essayist now,
and social critic.
But he's not a real pagan.
The name is Pagan.
It's an old Irish name.
Pagan.
Pagan Kennedy?
Yeah, Pagan.
She always said pagan.
Oh, well, I had it wrong then.
I stand delivered.
And delivered.
She was a cute little nerd girl back in the day.
She said, deliver us this day.
That was a long time ago.
Oh, and before that, the end of the world takeoff there was St. Anne and Helena Handbasket.
I guess there won't be any more productions from them because they broke up.
Well, they didn't actually break up.
Part of their synapses became diffused.
Yeah, actually they...
And the molecules started drifting.
That's what happened to all of us.
That's how we ended up at Brushwood waiting for flying saucers every single year.
That's why we're so tired now.
It takes a lot out of you when you come out to dinner again and the priest and...
You know, I never found Philo the whole time.
He had the frock and he owed me a bunch of it.
And every time I'd go where I thought he was, people would go, oh, he just left.
Philo is just here and he just left.
Did you get that too?
Everybody saw that guy, but nobody could say where he was right then.
Right.
And then they'd walk up and say, hey, where's Philo, man?
He told me to be here, blah, blah, blah, whatever clock.
Of course, clocks are irrelevant.
But he...
Well, or meant to be smashed or stabbed.
But, you know, and then they'd say, well, he just left and he was with a couple of people.
He walked off this way, you go over there and he just left and he just left.
And I think he spent most of his time just leaving.
Leaving, yeah.
Well, I saw him leaving with those two girls, the great big old one and the real little young one.
Yeah.
And nobody saw him for like a day after that.
Well, how do you hook up with that fantasy twist?
I'm curious as an alligator.
He's an overman.
An ubermensch.
He's the overman.
The ubermensch.
He's the only one who has been successfully, who has lived through the overman transfiguration in Dobbs Town.
Philo is an ubermensch.
Sorry, I had to accentuate that.
Because he is in a certain way.
Dave, listeners, I want you to know that Dave uses toilet paper.
Once in a while.
And that's how he gets those weird voices that he does.
I don't use it.
When it sounds like he's yelling through a tube or a cup.
Sometimes it's a Styrofoam cup that he fishes out of the trash with the AIDS all over it.
It also sounds like a very old radio drama.
Do you know where you're going, Mr. Tompkins?
Put that gun down.
Right.
Dave has special, really cheap tricks to make a good microphone sound like a really crappy old one.
And this is the only time I ever do use toilet paper.
To create video effects.
In the radio station at WC.
WCSB in Cleveland.
And I have been able to make some other audio effects with toilet paper.
But none of them are quite, what's the word, cogent enough to be written down and transcribed.
Well, to paraphrase Terry Pratchett, Dave, your smell, I think, sometimes leads a life of its own.
Of course.
Because I've heard people say that it goes out.
You needn't quote Terry Pratchett because that is a very old saying.
It goes out to movies and things.
Your smell, your odor.
Yeah.
Goes out to sushi restaurants.
And gets the octopus with the cucumbers and stuff.
Yeah.
Right.
Well, you're at home.
Well, unfortunately.
You know, working.
Whatever you do at home.
I sit at home and cry.
No, I pretend to cry.
Actually, I just like stare and wonder what the hell is happening in my brain.
Maybe something isn't happening.
Well, that's what we all, that's where we're all trying to get to as subgeniuses.
That's what we want to, we want to reach that state where truly nothing at all is happening in our brain.
Well, what about the little yellow trucks?
You're sitting home alone.
At alone, of course.
You're trying to get some work done.
You're trying to create.
You're trying to just relax, not do anything.
And next thing you know, the poppers come by.
The poopers, as they call them.
And the little yellow looks like a short bus for the muscular dystrophy truck or sometimes
the mental disability truck.
You see them too?
Yeah.
And every time I am seriously destabilized.
Oh, thank God.
I thought I was alone.
I can see the yellow truck.
And, um, I'm not sure.
I see it going down the street and I know the job has been done and I've been done.
So.
They don't even need to use the yellow truck anymore.
If you urinate, then they can track you.
Well.
If it enters the pub, unless you just go in your backyard, if you ever flush the toilet
and any part of that, anything that's been in you goes down into the city's water system.
Your body parts.
They know what you've been doing.
They can tell the insurance company what you've been lying about.
What you've been doing.
What you've been thinking about.
Unfortunately, now we're into thought crimes.
It's little pieces of the follicle of the brain actually escape into this.
They know who you voted for by analyzing your urine.
Your urine.
Not just mine.
Everyone's urine.
Yeah.
And what a way to live.
It's not the Amerikey that I grew up in.
Not the Amerikey I grew up in either.
When I was growing up in the old Amerikey, if somebody said, oh, well, sure, we'll hire
you if your pee is good enough for us.
Substantial.
In the old days, people would have gone, you are insane.
And they'd never be able to hire anybody.
Now there are people lining up going, oh, please give me a job for 20 grand a year and
no benefits.
Please.
And dictate my life.
Tell me I can't cuss or smoke even when I go home.
Keep peeing in a cup and keep being analyzed and keep being returned.
They're welcome to have a taste test if they'd like.
That's what I should have told that Christian broadcasting station that wanted to hire me.
Well, the Christian broadcasting guy had no business being at X Day number one.
Nevermind the guy who didn't hire you.
Don't these people know what they're getting in for?
He claimed he did.
You know, the funny thing is he was scared away, not by the third breastages or the guy
that got killed or any of that kind of stuff.
Or the double horns even.
You know what scared him away?
Yeah.
The Christmas star decoration thing about five feet high.
Not a real nativity scene.
Yeah, just a star that they hang up, that Brushwood hangs up at Christmas.
But it was laying next to a barn upside down.
So it was pointing downwards.
And that freaked the guy out.
To him that was a clear sign, you know, the work of the Pentagon.
The five-pointed star pointed down.
You know what my favorite part of X Day was, though?
Prussian blue.
Those two young racist girls.
The girls that did that Nazi music.
Yeah.
They were...
You saw them, didn't you?
When?
At X Day.
Last weekend.
Last weekend?
Oh, he's another one that doesn't remember.
The time control lessons.
Well, I remember them seeing...
You went to the time control lessons and you were still sitting there four hours after
the teacher had stopped.
And that's when I knew you were good at it.
I thought it was two weeks ago.
I was wondering why it showed up.
No, it was just last...
No, we just got back.
To me, that's one of the best things.
That was the weird thing.
It was only supposed to last a week and it lasted two weeks.
Total protraction of time.
Inversion of time.
You can go anywhere you want.
You can have it be the beginning of X Day week.
You can have it be the end.
Anytime you go into time control.
I think that's the only...
Probably the only really beautiful thing about the artifact.
Well, I guess that means it's not too late to check it out then.
Yeah.
If the time control is...
Like a bloody leg.
But there's the one...
The problem that time control must always go around.
I don't know if you knew that.
That's one of Bob's oldest statements.
Yes, it is hard to control.
He was really young when he said that old, old statement.
What's the word for that?
What's the word for when something is fraught with...
You know, you have a clear path and yet at the same time...
You know the old Murphy's Law, how they say it in science.
Dayfish? Is that what you mean?
No, that's SJ. That's subgenius.
You know, what's the real scientific word?
Randomness. It's filled with random...
I don't know.
Chaos?
You know, don't you?
Dr. Sinister knows. He knows all the scientific terminology.
Random versus chaos.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Entropy.
Yeah, chaotic, entropic.
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
That's why there's some ash around the edges of Bob's body.
Really?
I mean, you know, if you want to sign away, you know, a release form for anything, I mean, that's the thing you got to worry about is time control.
Once you step into the room, anything can probably happen.
Well, it won't happen.
You know, when you said time control, it reminded me to look at my watch.
Well, you do that every time. You mentioned the word time. You always subconciously glance...
Well, I have a clock in my head. I don't actually need a watch. I just, I keep it so I don't scare people.
You have one of those little digital lead clocks that go on the top of the bed alarm clock.
I'm an emergentile. Emergentile subgeniuses often have a little clock in their heads. That's why I don't ever relax.
Another beneficial of being part of the Uber.
You know that the Grim Reaper is breathing down your neck every second.
Well, you're not programmed for that. You're programmed just to react to the appropriate times. You're not supposed to hallucinate a big freaking Grim Reaper breathing down your neck.
Sure, but you're just programmed to say that. You're just the robot that's programmed to say that.
Of course, and you're just programmed to agree with me and disagree with me in the same...
Yes.
Not.
My least favorite part of X Day 9 was when the New York State Highway Patrol smashed right through the, what do they call the buntresses, the flagellers, the big...
The barricades.
The barricades. That's the word I was thinking about, French riots in the 1970s.
Yeah, yeah. That's where we learned how to build those.
But broke through the barricades. The petrol bombs started going, we call them gas bombs. We're in America and stuff.
And the gunshots started going and not enough people were diving for coverage. That was one... Did I say it was my favorite or least favorite?
That was your least favorite.
My least favorite.
Yeah.
It's hard to tell.
Especially after time control.
Especially after the stuff is so weird out there. You get in such a strange state of mind, partly just because you're in an unfamiliar place. You're outdoors and camping and everybody is perverse and weird in some way.
Most of us.
So of course you're kind of off.
And the drumming that's always going on. And the naked women parades. Have you seen... Did you catch those every afternoon?
The different naked women parades?
Breasts for Peace.
Yeah.
Breasts... What is it called? Breasts Not Bombs?
Yeah. Breasts Not Bombs.
Or Breasts of Bombs or something like that. It was spelled B-O-B.
Mammal Mommies Against the War.
Yeah.
There were all kinds of interesting and exciting names.
I liked that. I think that's a really cool way of... Hey, I need to play a song or something.
That's what my spidey sense says.
I noticed your hair is on fire so that means...
So I'm going to play... This is by our sister station in Champaign, Illinois.
And the Ouroboros Rex, who is a DJ there, did this lovely song.
That was the Swinging Love Corpses in the background from X Day.
Okay. Let's see. One of these buttons should...
So while since X Day, I guess I should believe, maybe next year will be better than the last.
I still remember the last thing that Bob said as he was leaving.
Now the drills go by so fast.
And it's one more day up in the saucer.
And it's one more night in Rushwood.
If a Friday Jones could be my high list.
I wish she would.
Na na na na na na na na na na na na na na.
Na na na na na na na na na na na na na yeah
The smell of big boys and their normals And the feeling that they all can't help
But sit in my face
With my third eye I look across the mill
No way to see he exists
On their way to burn this place
And it's one more day up in the saucers
And it's one more night in brushwood
If saucer dreams alone could bring me Susie
Maybe I could
Na na na na na
Yeah
I cruise this ladder mansion sometime after 2am
And talk a little while about the church
But the conspiracy makes you move a little slower
Makes you talk a little lower
About the church
About the day that we take over
It's been a while since X-Day
And I guess I will believe
Maybe next year will be better than the last
I can't remember all the times I played the hourglass
And wished my wish would make it come to pass
And wished my open-ended world
And wished after our own ends
No sign that I'm moving
It's 1701 in brushwood
I have never made it to a next day
I guess I should
If I could
I'd go home
Na na na na, na na na na, yeah
Na na na na, yeah
Yeah
A robberous rex
Mickey Mouse and Pluto
To their movie stars in Disneyland
Oh, friends, I should mention
This will hopefully keep me from getting more emails about this
For two weeks now, I've been warned daily
About GameSpot website
CNET
Using Bob's head
A giant company, yeah
One of their spinoffs, GameSpot
Was having a grads and dads special sale
And a Dobbs head with glasses added on it
Was being used as the
Dad
And I wrote to them, their lawyers
And said, that's a trademark
And the lawyers wrote back and said, no it's not
We found it on the web, on the trademark web
And that trademark has
Expired
And I was able to say
Yes, that's true
But you were looking at the old trademark
We have re-trademarked it under these
Different new categories which cost a million bucks
And therefore you
Must take it down
And they did, today, it's down
Oh, well then
They replaced it with a false Bob
That was like another guy
And another dad looking guy with glasses in a pipe
But it was not the mark owned by yours, truly
So, we cannot expect Oxo, Bloxo litigation
And lots more money for you
No
No, we don't know
Because you don't press things like that
Unless you really have to
Because only the lawyers win, Dave
In a lawsuit
Only the lawyers win most of the time
And the hams
The big hams
Lawsuits mean a lot of money for lawyers
Their lawyers and your lawyer
I don't have a lawyer staying
Princess
I mean not
Princess Magdalene
Her custody case thing
Has been going on
Last Friday and tomorrow
She may know something
Next couple of days
She'll be at X day
Jesus will be at X day
In time control land
In yesterday's X day
So he'll be in and out
Like Philo
Perhaps
Where you never can see him
But he's there
He's always just out of eye shot
Here's Philo
Turn on
Tune in
And slack off
I thought that was Timothy Beerle
No
That was one of Philo's
Alter egos
Philo was
Timothy Leary
And he shed him like a dead body
Yeah
He moved
He moved on
I like besties disguised
Just like a former KGB agent
That drinks too much
And has a bladder infection
This is Bill T. Miller
In the background
You can go to BillTMiller.com
If you want to
And download
This and much more
That's the guy with the ponytail
Who like runs around screaming
Look at me
I'm built like a woman
Why do they want to
Pick on me like this right
No that's Philo
Philo not Philo
Has a
No wonder I couldn't recognize him
He now has a ponytail
Yeah
Oh I thought
Well you know
And he's got that new wife
Reverend Chaos
Bobcat
Something
She changes her name every week
She's a regular
That's the way to do it
On the San Francisco
That is the way to do it
By the way
You know
Change your name weekly
Just like I should change my
Or your underwear
Thank you
Are you offering
Is that an offer
I'm offering to change
Anybody's underwear
Who wants it
Underwear
The undermensch
That's a fly
A little buzzy fly
Is the undermensch
Well
We're going to have to be
Moving out of here
Because this show
Is ending soon
And oh I should say
This has been
Hour of Slack
Number
One thousand
Fifty four
With a
Live
This time live
In WCSB studios
With Lonesome Cowboy Day
And Dr. Sinister
Who wandered
In
And yours truly
Reverend Ivan Stang
There's more information
About the Church
Of the Subgenius
At subgenius.com
And this is
Sivit Stang
Taking us out
Pretending love's
Beside me
In the dark
His dogs in pipe
They guide me
Without love
I smell his drop
Around me
And I'm in love
And when I have no slack
I touch my clown
And Bob has found me
On my job
The noddles act
Like dog slits
Without slack
The sweat runs down
My armpits
The next day
I'll see the saucers coming
And all I need
Is Bob and me
Forever
And I'll see
Bob and me
Forever and forever
But until
I spend my thirty bucks
I'm just
Ranting to myself
And not to Bob
And although
I know
That I am screwed
Still I say
There's a day
Of pain
I love Bob
But when the rupture's over
He'll be gone
The earth will be in ruins
Without him
The world around me changes
The conspiracy is everywhere
The malls are full of pink boys
I love Bob
But every day
I don't spend
That thirty bucks
I'm only just pretending
Without me
Bob's world
Will go on burning
Our next day
Bob will have this life
That I'll never know
I love Bob
I'm only
On my own