From PR News in Washington, I'm chock-full of advertisements.
PR News congratulates New York on becoming the 23rd state to legalize cancer, AIDS, epilepsy, and other conditions.
Hundreds of thousands of people in northern Ohio are still battling some 30 new wildfires, many ignited by fire.
This is the latest spate of fires outside a U.N.-run school in north-central Ohio.
This is PR.
Sunday newspapers called it appalling and disgraceful.
Well, armed militants called it a moral outrage and a criminal act.
It's being billed as the largest PR news in Washington.
Vibrant.
Can your heart stand the shocking facts about Bob?
If you're free, it's better.
Action.
This is the police.
Mine.
That.
Haki.
Bob.
Bob?
Hello there.
You know, I've been all around this wonderful world of ours,
and in all this world, nothing else is Bob.
Bob?
One of these mornings
Bob comes creepin' in the room
Oh, I say
One of these mornings
Bob Dobbs comes a-creepin' in the room
Oh, I say
One of these mornings
Bob comes a-creepin' in the room
Oh, I say
Oh, my lord, my sweet lord
What shall I do?
You can call on your president
But your president won't do you no good
Oh, you can call on your president
Oh, I say
But your president won't do you no good
One of these mornings
Bob Dobbs comes a-creepin' in the room
Oh, my lord, my sweet lord
What shall I do?
Bob Dobbs comes a-creepin' in the room
Thank you.
Listen, here's the lowdown
Everybody go down
Climb into a Greyhound
Find yourself a seat
Head on out to Motown
Gonna be a showdown
Hypnotizing low sound
Pumpin' to the streets
Another dirty flow
A fight another bloody go-round
Everybody throw down
That's including me
Never gonna slow down
We don't even know how
Everyone we mow down
Joins us eventually
guitar solo
Everybody get in line
Everybody from the new freak nation
Open up your tired eyes
Oh, get up now from your hibernation
Our research shows a shocking rise
In evil bullshit
And now they pull shit
It's sick
You'd be surprised to know
Just how deep it's got
Or maybe not
So everybody, now's the time
Snag a weapon and file out
Right behind me
The freaky time is coming soon
Our non-believers leave the room
Listen, won't be said again
This is your life to defend
We won't stand idly by
As it devolves into madness
Resolves in a sad mess
A broken pipe dream of the day
When freaks take control
Oh yes, that's right
That's the goal
Now who's still with me?
Hurry up, there's little time
I'm burning up with anticipation
You've heard enough of leaders' lies
Lies
You've learned enough to know
The true frustration
Burning in the hearts of every woman
Man and child
By a wild style
Sad truth is most folks are trained
In just one thing
Just ignore it
And that's some shit
To turn the other cheek is fine
If you don't care
But if you do
We're counting on you
Raise your hand and take a vow
I'm afraid your species needs you now
You came in thinking life was play
But hey man, that was yesterday
Look around and you'll see
This is just the beginning
And if your head's spinning
Take that as your cue
Whoop the band
They'll be first to arrive
And if they don't survive
We'll call upon you
The few who understand what's right
The few who hunger for some confrontation
Will get to undertake the fight
Get set to usher in a new era of freedom
In the new freak nation
No one knows why
All the freaky kids outside are screaming
Or that they're dreaming, scheming
Once it flows this river ain't never gonna stop
Even if we drop
But you just sit on the sub just tight
And imagine all the things you'd change in this world
And you'll never know what's real
And some of you are gonna fail
Others will end up in jail
Danger lurks so please take care
Try not to get killed out there
Most will say that we're mad
And implore us to give in
But the way that we're living
Just makes my hair curl up your fist
And focus your power
For you'll soon know the hour
Will take back the world
Everybody get in line
Everybody from the new freak nation
Everybody now's the time
Snag a weapon and file out right behind me
When the night falls
Once my heart was bound in sorrow
By the mist of conspiracy
The toilet beckoned kindly, and it drew me to come see.
And the sewage, it formed a message, it said 13013.
I then heard a voice from Doves Town gently saying, follow me.
There's a frog farm down the valley, there's a frog farm past the rain.
There's a frog farm in your sorrow.
When your mind is going insane.
There's a frog farm when you're burdened.
There's a frog farm where you stray.
There's a frog farm, heavenly frog farm, or kill me to say.
Sometimes.
My friends forsake me, and I'm tempted to despair.
When I summon my dear savior of short duration.
And I hear you would pay to know exactly what it is you really think.
And I'll guarantee you my brother, you are probably a king.
There's a frog farm down the valley, there's a frog farm past the rain.
There's a frog farm in your sorrows.
When your mind is going insane.
There's a frog farm in your sorrow.
And I hear your christening, o take me home.
There's a frog farm within you, when your mind is going insane.
There's a frog farm in your sorrow.
Jorge!
I'll be wherever you are all day.
God's Word.
No mystery, you can do it.
What's the least often comment that you hear about a banjo player?
I don't know.
What is the least often comment you hear about a banjo player?
Is that the banjo player's Porsche over there?
The fun thing about ranting up here is if you ever get scared,
you can't see anybody anyway.
If you can ignore hecklers like teeters, it's actually pretty easily done.
And you guys got it easy because GGG isn't here.
Stang doesn't heckle.
We is like the closest visible audience member,
and she's so goddamn sweet, you don't feel bad at all.
I mean, it's really, you know, you guys, if you're in this church,
there's a reason you can't, right?
Whether it be you grew up in a town of really messed up crazy Baptists like I did,
or maybe the synagogue wasn't working out for you.
Maybe the mosque didn't move you.
Maybe when you went to the coven, it felt wrong.
I don't know.
Everybody's got something.
Something draws you to the church, but what makes you stay?
You know, what gets you off?
We've talked a lot about slack, and we've talked a lot about keeping your slack.
And the question always comes up to, I've heard people ask, but what is slack?
So let's put this question out to the audience just for a second.
I'm listening.
I can hear you if I can't see you.
What is slack?
Slack is what you make of it.
You are absolutely right.
And what is slack for you may not be slack for me,
and what is slack for me probably isn't slack for you.
But everybody gets their slack.
And as we've talked about, the big key is, as a subgenius, must have slack.
Now, some of you are obviously getting a whole lot.
You're getting a lot of slack by sitting on your tuchus.
You're goddamn right I am.
Right.
Who the hell?
Is that YouTube memes?
God damn it.
Some of you get a lot of slack by busting your ass.
And that's okay, too.
But the subgenius must have slack.
However you get it, however you go about it.
And as Suds mentioned, you know, the big key is to not...
steal other people's slack.
The conspiracy does that good enough.
You know, they don't throw you out your own nurseshuts.
But they're also going to punish you, right?
Whatever, actually.
You.
Show, me.
Say you think I'm stronger than you think I am.
You know what I was Shocking.
Hay there was time when I thought I was THE greater привет.
Worst joke I've ever heard.
And I, I'm a boss of life, it was a boss of life
And any time I wanted to die, I'd die
I wore a hat, and I had a job
And I bought all the blankets so that no one knew
Boss of life, it was a boss of life
Friends were in a way
And I thought I had a game
Boss of life, it was a boss of life
I was a woman
And I could turn my way and say
And I wore a hat, and I had a job
And I bought all the blankets so that no one knew
Boss of life, it was a boss of life
And I thought I had a game
And I wore a hat, and I had a job
And I bought all the blankets so that no one knew
Boss of life, it was a boss of life
And I wore a hat, and I had a job
And I bought all the blankets so that no one knew
For all your lies
And I found you
Coming from my bed
Alleys
For all of the pret
All of the pret
O peut
ãy
Beer, ketchup, horseradish, bananas, fried rice, choky peanut butter.
Well, that was a sumptuous meal, wasn't it?
Dumb Liar
Break us beer
We need beer
And whiskey, too
We don't ask for a lot
And up on this stage it gets pretty hot
We're doing it for you
Whether you like it or not
Bring us some
Something to drink
It helps us play
It helps us think
Break us beer
Have us make it clear
This band wants some beer
Break us beer
Bring us beer
So angry Larry won't shed no tears
Praise Reverend Ed Glant
He brought us a beer
Bring us beer
But we need more
Don't make us shed our tears
Just bring us some more beer
Bring us beer
Bring it home
Ah, oh oh oh
Ah, oh, ah, oh ah
Ha ha ha ha ha
Now on songой
Esquivel
Our children follow
the sleigh
And it was only, I think, yesterday that I realized that Milnar was a band that our friend Reverend Stover is in.
And they will be playing at the Subgenius Devival in Kent on December 6th.
And we'll talk more details about that later.
Because the little song about pork chops was by Evolution Control Committee, currently of Columbus.
And then the final thing, the call for beer with Priestess Pisces singing, was the X-Day Jam Band.
Six or more fisted tails of Connie.
In this case, I'm pretty sure that was Reverend Angry Larry on something.
Reverend Suds Pasha on something.
Probably guitars.
And it may have been Reverend Stover on drums, but it was a little looser than that.
We would usually get from him.
Anyway, that's the X-Day credits.
We expect to do some more stuff presently.
But for right now, back to the news.
From PR News in Washington, I'm restrained and isolated during the rainstorms.
During storms, rain comes down.
Despite being warned, dry areas known as washes think they can always get PR news.
I mean.
Well, California's Department of Corrections is dead.
Israel's Prime Minister is in his country.
U.S. District Judge Lawrence Carlton pepper-sprang mentally ill prisoners to force them from Los Angeles.
Thousands of federal, state, and local litterbugs are putting out the word this weekend.
It's three days of talent shows and PR news in Washington.
It is known that the Air Intelligence has in its possession a spacecraft.
31 feet in diameter.
And it is entirely undamaged except for a small hole broken in the cockpit.
And because of this hole, the 12 small human beings died.
The spacecraft made an automatic landing after its occupants had died.
The local sheriffs peered into the cockpit.
And they're slumped over their instruments.
The instruments, motionless, were 12 small men.
The bodies were still limp and warm.
They were fair-skinned.
All were males.
They were between 3 and 4 feet in height.
All had differing shades of light hair.
All had blue eyes.
All had perfect teeth without any dental work.
All were superb physical specimens.
With no asymmetrical details.
They could pass on notice as small men or as children.
One body was selected for autopsy.
He was found to have the same organs that a human being has and in about the same place.
His blood type was human.
Genes and chromosomes would match up with those of an earth woman.
Everything was quite normal until the brain surgeon laid bare the right hemisphere of the brain.
There, in his skull, was a human.
The skull was the brain of a human being several hundred years old.
They had never seen so highly convoluted a brain.
There was a man several hundred years old who had been spared the infirmities of age.
If they could share their medical secrets with us, what a gift this would be to the human race.
It would be the gift of life to the human race.
Think what that secret would be worth.
Think what an opportunity it would be to develop the psychic powers, to develop culture,
and how little space travel would mean to a race whose lifespan was several times longer than our lifespan.
That is one of the benefits they might bring us if we would only stop shooting at them.
Imagine.
Imagine what patience and what forbearance for them to have been fired upon and chased,
and not once to have harmed a human being.
There is nothing to be afraid of.
Will everybody please stop shooting at them?
Ladies and gentlemen, either we are their lost colony or they are our lost cousins.
Undoubtedly, we are somehow related.
Undoubtedly, there has been an unbroken link going back a long, long time.
Well, I had a dream that the president of Microsoft Word was running around in the grandma's house and he stumbled upon Burt Reynolds.
He was watching some time he fucked up shit on the telly.
The president of Microsoft Word was chasing him around and shooting.
And finally, he traps Burt on the front porch and blows his fucking head off.
Man, that's the truth.
.
Well, it's a God-given fact
That you can't go back, no, you can't go back
It's a God-given law
That you're gonna lose your ma
Yes, you're gonna lose your ma
It's a God-given fact
You gotta buy him by the sack
It's a God-given law
That you're gonna get small
Yes, you're gonna get small
Maybe just another rap
Bet you're running out of sap
Yes, you're running out of sap
Well, you better take a rap
Dying under daddy's cap
Shabble up
It's on the top of the list
That you can't get pissed
No, you can't get pissed
It's rule number one
Living right isn't fun
Cause it's a God-given fact
That you can't go back
No, you can't go back
It's a God-given law
That you're gonna lose your ma
Yeah, you're gonna lose your ma
Time-tested and true
You gotta putty-poo-poo
Gotta putty-poo-poo
Well, it's a God-given law
That you're gonna get small
Yes, you're gonna get small
Maybe just another rap
Bet you're running out of sap
Yes, you're running out of sap
Well, you better take a rap
Dying under daddy's cap
Now
You're an signals korok
And add more
Jonah
Shout out minimize
Unconvinced
All summer
15 Life
Yes, dear friends.
And we have the Psychoskeletons in the background with a song called Plug Lord.
We just heard the Sunflower Saints covering Devo doing their classic song Shrivel Up about aging, I think it is.
Sometimes that's my theme song.
Before that, the short one-minute screaming thing.
Which will sound a lot different on the X-rated internet version of this show than it does on the broadcast version.
That's by Reagan's Pollock.
They've been re-releasing their crazy old stuff.
And the spoken word piece with music behind it about little space humans.
That was done by, insert name here, Joe Jeziorski.
I'm sorry.
I always bring that guy's stuff to the show without writing...
The log shows the title of it, but not the performer.
Most of these things I know from memory, but he's kind of a new guy.
Anyway...
We'll fill in that blank another day.
No, we'll insert name here again.
Yes.
Just to cover it.
Joe Jeziorski.
So, yes.
I'll have to...
I have to...
Hold the psychoskeletons out.
Oh.
Well, no, I kind of have to.
On account of...
Because of technical stuff.
Oh.
Gnome sign.
Gnote.
Gnome.
But we do have...
This is six-fisted.
Six or more.
Four-fisted tales of Connie.
That's not tales like stories, by the way.
That's tales like the thing at the end of most animals.
And I think this is Lonesome Cowboy Dave and Reverend Angry Larry.
Wow.
Which we could call the two Daves jam.
Yeah.
This was recorded at 9X Day.
I guess that was eight years ago.
Wow.
There's a whole disc of instrumentals here that we're running.
In the background.
And we have news, friends.
Yes.
Lots of news.
This particular time.
For one thing, did you know that you can now download subgenius music?
And not by recording this show.
But we did a lot of CDs over the years.
Actually, we did a whole bunch of cassette tapes in the 80s and 90s.
And then we switched to CD.
And most of the old cassettes...
The best parts kind of got reused on some of the CDs.
But the CDs were mostly from the 2000 through 2010 or so.
And we're working...
We're in progress on a couple of new albums.
And those might only be released electronically.
Anyway, what I'm talking about is...
Thanks to Pisces and Suds,
seven of the subgenius CD albums are on Bandcamp now.
And I can't...
Do prices or anything.
Because of the nature of this station.
And the other stations.
Which, by the way, include WORT in Madison.
WREK in Atlanta.
WHUS in Storrs, Connecticut.
WEFT.
Beautiful WEFT in Champaign, Illinois.
And Reverend Zarka's show.
And also in Storrs, Connecticut.
But I can't remember the call letters.
Aww.
All of that information.
In fact,
everything I'm about to say is on subgenius.com.
There we go.
And miraculously...
You can tell that's Dave.
You can hear old lonesome cowboy Dave's guitar.
Yes.
Fingering there.
Distinctively, yes.
So, yeah.
Right.
There's a lot of wonderful songs.
Like, for instance, Dave's song Iodine 131.
It's on one of those seven albums.
I'm not sure which one.
Even a girl's album, you might say.
A Squid for Connie.
But as with most of the Connie stuff,
that's probably the worst of the batch.
A Squid for Connie.
I thought that was like 10 billion squids for Connie.
No, that's a song on that album.
It's 83D Squids.
Oh, oh, oh.
That you...
Done by you and Dave and Chaz Smith.
Yeah.
83D Squids.
On this radio station, live in the studio,
there's several ESO or Einstein's...
Secret Orchestra songs that were first played
right here at this board.
Yes.
Only before the equipment was moved to this building.
But anyway, friends.
So, yeah.
If you look at subgenius.com
by spelling the word subgenius correctly,
you'll find the link in the big paragraph on the front page.
Also, if you haven't looked at the subgenius website
in a long time,
you may be...
You may be surprised by a certain little detail.
J.R. Bob Dobbs is gaining in power these days.
Also, what else was I going to mention?
Oh, there are all kinds of things happening.
Well, there are...
I was gonna...
I'm about to do a bulk emailing about all of this stuff,
including a reminder about the best subgenius Facebook pages.
Slack Hole 2.1
and the unofficial...
The unofficial Church of the Subgenius page
are probably the funniest ones.
But there's like a film...
Subgenius Film Society page,
a special Hour of Slack page,
and so forth.
All of that stuff can be found at subgenius.com.
And that and about 50,000 to 100,000 pages
of articles and pictures and rants and forums
and all that kind of stuff.
But our other...
Our other important news
is that we have some devivals coming up.
Yes, devivals.
Including WCSB-centric things.
The soonest one is...
This is not just a subgenius devival,
but we will be performing there,
or rather I should say I will be hollering
at whoever shows up at 7 o'clock
at the Witch's Ball,
the Northeast Ohio Witch's Ball,
which happens near Cleveland
on October 18th, Saturday.
If you Google Neo Witch's Ball,
as in Northeast Ohio Witch's Ball,
you'll find that.com,
neowitchesball.com.
Or you can look at subgenius.com events,
because all of this stuff is on there too.
And you can read all about it there.
The Witch's Ball is a masquerade ball
with people wearing crazy masks,
and it's a subset of a kind of a fantasy comics,
gaming, and new agey con
called Con on the Cob.
And it's held at Hudson Clarion Inn
in Hudson, Ohio,
which is about 45 minutes away
from most of us listening now.
It's also right near the ledges part
of Cuyahoga Valley National Park,
which is the coolest part of that park.
Mm-hmm.
And we always go there in the morning.
Then we go to the show and the party.
Then we sleep out there,
and then we come back to the ledges,
because the ledges are such a great place to hike.
So beautiful.
Anyway, we in Princess,
we and I will be there,
is what I mean.
They're showing Arise,
the subgenius movie,
at four o'clock.
Oh, my.
And then at seven o'clock,
I come on and preach,
and then about 8.30 or so,
our friend Michael Murth,
the magician,
will be doing his feats of telepatheticness.
Now, meanwhile,
I need to see if this is Dave.
It is, by the way.
Okay, good.
I'm sorry I'm calling so late,
but I had numerous problems.
I'm not feeling that well.
Oh, Dave.
I'm sorry to hear that.
I'm flying to Boonday.
Well, yeah, actually, we do.
We do.
I think we should have a prayer session right here and now.
I really do.
We've got at least ten people listening,
and I think everybody should bow their heads
and hold their breath for not at all.
And strongly concentrate their energies toward
Northeastern Ohio.
Heal Dave by acubating him with your thoughts.
Yeah.
Dave.
Could you please do it in about,
like, right now?
Okay, I'm trying.
I'm going to do it.
Oh, wait a minute.
I think I broke something.
Now we have to pray for both.
Oh, it helped Dave.
It worked.
No, it didn't.
Well, that's just wonderful.
Well, we're not going to talk about doctrinaire stuff, are we?
Because I'm feeling really radical tonight.
I was.
I was bragging up shows that we're going to be at
on October 18th,
the Witches Masquerade Ball in Hudson, Ohio.
Oh, and the WCSB Halloween Masquerade Ball.
Now, see, Dave, you should come to that
because you could be there free and rock out with us.
Oh, and it's so much fun.
The WCSB Halloween Masquerade Ball is November 1st.
That's a Saturday after Halloween
at Cleveland Public Theater.
And there's four bands, including all bands,
Dinosaurs, The Gizmos X, Sticky Fingers X, and another one.
Counterintuits.
Yeah, Counterintuits.
And we'll be showing...
Well, there's more than one, right?
I mean, more than one of the bands.
Not the bands, per se, but I mean, what's that guy's name?
Conduit?
There's more than one ball.
There are at least two balls.
There's the Halloween Masquerade.
There's the Halloween Masquerade Ball on November 1st,
and there's the Witches Masquerade Ball on October 18th.
That's two healthy balls right there.
Right, right.
And then there's one that's not a ball on December 6th.
And, Dave, if you could make it to this, it would be great
because we need preachers and singers and musicians.
In Kent, Ohio, at the Stone Tavern on December 6th,
we will join...
bands such as Milnar and probably the Amino Acids
or something like them, as heard in the background here.
Well, maybe that's not a good example.
It sounded more like Thomas the Train or the Tootie Whistle
and the Big Ten, whatever.
Actually, Dave, that's you.
And Reverend Angry Larry jamming at 9X Day.
Oh, I thought it sounded like the train conductor.
Somebody's blowing a whistle or something.
Maybe, that too.
There's some of that in there.
There's enough foreground for everybody.
The two Daves jam.
So, yeah, we're trying to talk you into showing up at the Kent Devival
and the Halloween one.
Yeah.
Well, it sounds wonderful to me, especially the Kent one.
Now, that is if you're not sick, Dave.
I mean, physically sick.
I'm sick every day and my car's always well.
Every day.
I'm sick every day and my car is always...
Now, I'm confused.
You changed the rules already.
I didn't even know we had any to start with.
There's nothing like standards of forbearance and practices,
regulations as per...
I don't know how any of that works, obviously.
I think anyone listening can tell that we don't know how any of that works.
Well, we sure can make sky rockets.
We can make sky rockets.
You know?
Yeah.
We can get people thinking about things they don't normally think about.
But, Dave, you said you were feeling radical.
What's got you feeling radical, man?
Well, I don't know if my sickness is connected with my mental illness
or my...
It just seems like this planet is kind of sick, too.
You know what I mean?
Life is just Ebola cherries.
No.
Oh, man.
Did you really just say that?
No.
Somebody else said that.
I ripped him off.
I saw it on Facebook.
I'm just doing what everybody does on Facebook,
ripping everybody else off and not giving them credit.
Yeah, that's what you should...
That's what you've got to...
Those are words to live by.
Lift, rip off, give no credit.
Lift, lift, lift.
Wait, that's six words.
It's supposed to be a three-word intro.
But...
Lift...
We can't...
You ever...
We can't worry all the time.
We can take OxyContin like the Mormons do.
I just read an article...
I read an article in the news today about how
they're having a terrible painkiller,
prescription painkiller and heroin problem in Utah.
Oh.
Well, they have it in Ohio, in small counties.
Well, of course.
Well, it's funnier in Utah because the Mormons are perfect.
Yeah.
And they don't do drugs.
They don't...
A lot of them don't even do coffee.
But, you know, if the doctor tells you to take Vicodin or whatever once every...
You know, three times a day, you eventually start taking it nine times a day.
And the next thing you know, you're over at the pharmacy going,
my dog ate my last prescription.
I know I just picked it up yesterday, but I need another one.
I know that because my sister worked in a small Texas town pharmacy
and heard that one on a radio.
And she said, well, you know, I'm not going to take it.
Yes, it's heard everywhere on a weekly basis.
That's the wellspring of addiction is these darn doctors
who are just so full of pus and vinegar,
they don't even have their own side swipes together to, you know,
reprimand the great...
Yeah, I need a new doctor because my doctor just, when I go,
oh, I'm really pained.
Oh, I fall asleep all the time.
Oh, I'm too nervous.
She just goes, you just need more exercise and eat right.
Yeah.
Eve, that's not the kind of doctor I want.
I want the kind of doctor who goes, take 10 of these every day for the first day
and then take 20 of them the second day and then take 40 of them the third day
and then come back for more and pay me more.
Well, that's certainly a bone of contention is the state of our health system
because many of the doctors get Alzheimer's and other things that start with A
and stuff like that and ancillaries.
Did I say ancillaries?
They get a lot of ancillaries for prescribing these things.
And they're verboten and they're bad for people, what they do is.
Mm-hmm.
See how I tagged those words on the end just to make it disgusting?
Well...
They are bad for people is what they are.
Well, no, I don't know.
It's medicine, you know, makes you feel good.
People want freedom from pain.
Yeah.
They're not going to let their cancer cease from anxiety.
And they can find that in a simple little pill.
And there wouldn't be any problem with that except that eventually they run out of pills.
Yes.
And then they start robbing their family members and neighbors
so that they can get more of them kind pills for their body.
Spending a lot of time in the bathroom when they come over your house
going through the medicine cabinet.
Hey, what are you doing in there?
I left my cross-dress and socks in there, you know?
Well, man...
I hate to think how you know about looking through other people's medicine cabinets,
but I have to admit that there was a time when I was a young hipster
when I would do that sort of thing.
I learned my lesson.
I had my throat removed so I couldn't swallow pills anymore.
So that's how I broke the habit.
But, you know, I mean, come on.
I know we're all...
You and me were just...
I was jealous.
I mean, I know as well as I know
that we both would love to have one of them pills right now.
But we're 160 years old or older and, you know,
the ones who didn't learn their lesson, they're all dead.
Don't you have a lot of dead friends, Dave?
Yeah, we all got a lot of dead friends.
Yeah.
And they're the most fun to hang out with
because they don't talk much.
Back to you, you know, they don't give you any snuff.
They just sit there and, well, whatever they're doing.
One thing your dead friends never say to you is,
man, if you don't quit drinking,
I'm afraid you're going to be dead in a couple of years.
They'll never say things like that
because they kept drinking.
When you told them that, they didn't listen.
So they're dead.
Oh, well.
This is a funny comedy show tonight, isn't it?
Boy, it's just a barrel of laughs.
There's been an awful lot of heroin overdoses.
It's in the five-county area.
There are 219 people died last night.
And back to you, Gina.
Well, those aren't exaggerated numbers necessarily either.
No, I was just somewhat on the...
There's not quite 200 a night, but it's certainly 200 a month.
And it's 2,000 a year.
And it usually starts...
It's often people who would never, ever consider smoking pot
or even drinking too much.
But the doctor said,
you know,
that rash that hurts so much,
they give you that pill.
And that pill doesn't really even do...
It doesn't really...
It kind of makes you sick at first.
Yeah, they make you learn your lesion, so to speak.
The number of little rips you've got on your torso
indicates the number of the 10-pack or the escadrille
of pills you may ensconce
as a member of the...
of the...
of the subterranean parties.
It's one of them.
Dave, you do sound kind of sick.
Your voice sounds kind of rough.
You sound almost like Pigman.
Well, it's not that kind of roughness.
I've been gargling with gravel like Archimedes did.
Remember when Archimedes wanted to be the best speaker
in all of Athens?
I heard about that party, but I missed it.
Gargling with gargle could be really dangerous.
Gargling with gargles?
And the Athens cops are not into...
Now, gargling with garlic?
That would be much better.
Yeah, where do those funny hats come from, too?
I mean, those people must think they can fly or something
with those weird, like, four-corner hats and stuff.
That's why I'm proud of being American.
Because it's the biggest liar state in the world,
the biggest mass of corrupt, evil people running the show,
and still, and still, I believe in America.
You hate...
You hate our freedoms, and yet you still believe in America?
I'm confused now.
I didn't say I hated any freedoms.
You just said it was the worst country in the whole world.
Or something.
No, it's up there, though.
Believe me.
It depends on who you are.
You know, I mean, if you're a rich American,
it's the greatest country in the whole world.
If you're a...
Some...
I don't know.
One of our victims, or...
I should put it this way.
If you're...
In one of the countries we're trying to help.
If you're one of the countries we're trying to help,
then, yeah, it might be like the Death Star.
Yeah, and that's what Nurse Ratched always said.
What's wrong with these patients around here?
You know what I mean?
Yeah, they act crazy.
Yeah, they're acting crazy and stuff like that.
They don't understand that you must be crazy
to think this is not a worker's utopia.
Because, I mean, just think of it, man.
We've tried so hard to create a worker's paradise
where everybody gets a little piece of the pie
plus a little Alamode on top whenever they want.
That was a long time ago, man.
Yeah.
I just read several people in the Yahoo comments today
were saying that Obabo, the preseserp,
was basically responsible for Ebola
because God is angry.
Oh, come on.
You know, he made...
He made God...
Obabo, the preseserp of Uninu,
made God angry,
and that's why God is killing Africans.
Is there nothing...
And then Obabo is going to bring the Africans here
to kill all of us.
It's a complicated and kind of circular logic
that I keep reading my fellow Americans spouting about
when they get on the Internet anonymously
in that category.
It's just cowardly fashion they have
of expressing opinions about everything
they don't know a damn thing about.
I know.
That's the most striking thing about it
is the ignorance of all these people.
But it's actually more entertaining than the news itself.
That's the first thing.
I read the headline, then I read the comments.
Then I go back and read the article.
I know.
It's hard to not want to do that
because it does tickle your innards
when you see how retarded these people are.
I read a news story today that was funny instead of depressing.
They are growing penises in labs and are ready to start testing, attaching those to men who have damaged or ambiguous genitalia.
And I thought, man, this is the best news.
This is the best news in the world for the one penis.
As a spokesman for the ambiguous genitalia party, I'd like everyone and each and every one of us to vote this coming election.
And remember that the penis that you grow now will live on as long as you water it every day.
Thank you. Thank you.
Well, it brings to mind this comedic imagined scene of a factory with rows and rows of penises in little jars.
Or, I don't know, hanging off hooks or something, being watered or grown or fertilized.
The thing is, though, that it has to be grown from your own penile cells or it won't take. It won't attach.
Now, what if they tried to grow one with clitoral cells?
That would, I don't, for some reason, I didn't read that article.
That would be the fun part.
Doggone it.
But apparently there's a lot of little boys who are born with clitoral cells.
Kind of questionable package.
And what they usually do is just do a sex change operation right then and there on the infant.
My dad, the lawyer, has actually had to represent some of the victims of this kind of thing.
So he'll be glad to know that they can finally get a penis.
The rest of us can get, well, the rest of y'all, I should say, can get your multiple penile.
But you know what, Dave? The show is over.
The show is over.
I'm not even going to have time to play an end song on the other copies.
I have to say, this is the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
For more information, well, we already told you about subgenius.com.
Well, I'm sorry, so fleshy, because I wanted to become, anyway, never mind.
We'll save the penises for you, Dave.
But I'm going to have to, we're going to have to turn everything off because the show's over.
Well, but...
Oh, wow.
Just like everything else.
It's Dr. Sinister.
It sounds like you're, it sounds, however, like your illness has been healed by the ten listeners you've prayed.
I'm still hurting, but I don't hurt.
You know what I mean?
It's still like, ouch, but it's not like, oh, man, when's this going to end?
I'd just like to thank everybody out there who looked at their imaginary penis or whatever they were supposed to be doing for the last half an hour.
And just thought good thoughts and put them my way and I'll pay back someday.
Really, I swear, I really will.
Maybe Tuesday or something like that.
Not this week, but a couple...
Tuesday week or Tuesday couple weeks.
Tuesday couple weeks from now.
Yeah.
From, from, yeah.
What Dave said.
Oh!