Welcome to the subgenius radio ministry, Hour of Slack, sponsored by the Church of the Subgenius.
The subgenius Hour of Slack that you are about to listen to is specially designed only to be played on radio station
and only in the city of...
Oh, friends, friends, friends, this ongoing war. I don't know when you'll be hearing this show,
but this show will be composed of some older shows. I'm going to go with part two of Reverend Susie the Flusie's
very first war show, broadcast on WREK in Atlanta.
Probably a month ago, at least. Part two of her show also, we'll be hearing lots of, of course,
Einstein's Secret Orchestra Swamp Radio from WCSB in Cleveland.
Oh, I don't know what we'd do without these college radio stations that let us get away with it
and that replay this stuff, even once we've gotten away with it once.
It's just incredible. God bless America and Bob damn the conspiracy.
And...
And, uh, however you want to define that, my friends.
God bless planet Earth, too.
Your God bless planet Earth, that is.
This music in the background is by Ego Plum.
You might check out www.EbolaMusic.com.
You're listening to the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
For free information on the Church of the Subgenius,
always feel free to write to...
Ah, that post.
Office got that pencil ready.
Box 140306, Dallas, Texas.
75214.
We'll get that number again at the end of the broadcast,
along with that sacred URL, www.subgenius.com.
And now, this.
I'm getting out of this town alive if it kills me.
If we build a 30-foot wall, they'll find a way to get over it.
If we go 35 feet, they'll jump that one, too.
Whatever defenses we set up, these people will try to breach them.
So our only hope is Bob.
And a deep enough pit to hide in.
And you know how I feel about Hell Hole.
In the archives is a letter written by my dad,
which said, in January 1972,
that in reality,
instead of bombs falling on New York and Los Angeles and Houston and Dallas,
in reality, what really had occurred
was that the greatest door in the history of the work
had opened to the church.
He was going to be able to put,
in the name of God,
And that was an interesting thing.
What the hell?
Was that Garner Ted Armstrong or Norm Sekwetel?
No.
But he does bring up an interesting topic, Seeker.
Yes.
You know, there is one clutch of violence that stands to make a substantial profit
off of this whole deal.
Why don't you take a look at the bottom line?
Hmm.
Oh, yeah.
I do need to raise the veil on that, Bob.
But I need to buy a little more time.
Let's listen to some music.
And appreciate the fact that W-R-E-K Atlanta
isn't a Connell Rad Station yet.
But give them time.
They'll come around to it.
He thought with a kind of astonishment
of the biological uselessness of pain and fear,
the treachery of the human body,
which always freezes into inertia
at exactly the moment when a special effort was needed.
But precisely because of the extremity of his danger,
he had lost the power to act.
It struck him that in moments of crisis,
one is never fighting against an external enemy,
but always against one's own body.
Even now, in spite of the gym,
the dull ache in his belly made consecutive thought impossible.
And it is the same, he perceived,
in all seemingly heroic or tragic situations.
On the battlefield, in the torture chamber,
on a sinking ship,
the issues that you are fighting for are always forgotten.
Because the body swells up until it fills the universe.
And even when you are not paralyzed by fright or screaming with pain,
life is a moment to moment struggle against hunger or cold or sleeplessness,
against a sour stomach or an aching tooth.
Can we have some more music please?
I don't want to hear this stuff.
Can we hear more music?
When we speak about the end times in progress of today,
we are talking about the end times in progress of today.
Then of course this also applied to the last time.
It was God's judgment upon a godless world.
To begin with, I would like to say,
God's thoughts are not thoughts of destruction,
but thoughts of peace.
He said, look, I mean, God is not in the building squishing business.
He doesn't take life.
He didn't take his breath and cause those airplanes to veer off course
and smash into buildings.
He's not in the killing business.
But beyond that, I believe that we should use the muscle of the United States
to begin the decolonization of the Soviet or the Russian Empire.
And with that in mind, I would think that we as a nation
should send whatever arms and supplies are needed
to the indigenous groups of freedom fighters that are struggling for liberty,
whether that would be in Nicaragua,
whether it would be in Mozambique,
whether it would be in Afghanistan.
This conflict was begun on the timing and terms of others.
We could not have dreamed two years ago
that God was setting up a timing that is absolutely incredible
because the whole world is asking,
why? Why? Who did this?
How could God let something like this happen?
Reverend, I need to know.
Is God punishing me?
Ooh, short answer, yes, with an F.
Long answer, no, with a B.
How could we have known?
It has been a dream of mine for 20 or more years
to really depict in graphic form on the silver screen
what the Bible tells us the last few years of this dispensation is going to be like.
I mean, hey,
if you want to stay around, you can be here.
I'm out of here with you.
Oh, yes!
Yes!
Come on!
Let's go!
God didn't do this, folks.
The devil did it.
Right.
Okay?
The devil!
And we agreed to cooperate with Jesus Christ
in destroying those evil works
and those evil men who had perpetrated this dastardly deed
that just boggles the soul.
It's not just the mind.
All of us have just been numbed, I think,
and yet, here's the Scripture,
that God just burst in my spirit.
Oh, hallelujah.
When I first got the bad news.
Ha!
A lot of Hollywood is cancelling the release of their films.
Are you cancelling the release of your films?
Absolutely not.
No.
A thousand times no.
Now, some of the other big Hollywood films had to be cancelled
because they had acts of terrorism in them.
and it is most appropriate that arnold schwarzenegger and some of those guys that had
you know what does hollywood want to make films that show acts of terrorism i well don't get me
started on that or we'll be here the rest of the night my german blood will begin to boil
absolutely the mcgeddo premiere will go on the 18th next tuesday matt will have the
early premiere then as scheduled on friday the 21st in theaters across this nation
we will have the answer to the question that the world is asking right now why did god let this
happen yeah the answer to a question we had no way of knowing that would even be asked
the answer to a question no one asked the god in his infinite wisdom
time
and planned this whole thing even canceled out the other serious hollywood movies there'll be
no competition the world is going to come to see mcgeddo and they're going to get the gospel let me
urge you to bring unsaved friends and loved ones to this movie i keep teasing you a little bit we
are going to scare the hell out of everybody and we're going to scare heaven into them all
on that night because we're showing what the pages of the holy bible says are going to happen
i hope this show is gonna inspire the next generation yeah everyone get seriously
than you are or you're losing the ministry but if you had the answer the political leaders of this
nation and of this world do not have any answers oh thank you very much they didn't make any money they lost millions of dollars and may they lose much more if they ever try they haven't by the way and by the
way did you know the films lately are not nearly as christian bashing as they once were i think we are making up for it past time and being filmer of the inside and outside world that kind of came starting up in beyond memory in this collection of yours in because since this was written later in her life do every day啊
making an impact on Hollywood.
Thank God for Megiddo, which was positioned perfectly in the midst of the most radical
thing that's ever hit the United States of America.
Here's the answer.
Here's a message in the form of a theatrical motion picture, prepared, ready and releasing
10 days from now.
Oh, Matt, I see the hand of God so clearly in this.
Wouldn't it be awesome if the other major motion picture producers, for whatever reason,
postponed their releases so that Megiddo is the only thing you can really come and see
on the 21st of September when it releases on that weekend?
I mean, God has got this all figured out and I know that something awesome is going to
come from this.
Give us your money, money, money.
That's what we want you to do.
I can't.
It's too early to say too much.
It's too early to be saying too much.
It's not.
That's what
is.
You're right.
feared that one day would be the last day.
Now, in 2001, that day may be tomorrow.
Maghetto.
You don't have a chance in hell of getting what you want.
I'll always have a chance in hell, David.
And God's will is not always done.
You know, and sometimes I think we see these things and somehow we want to, you know,
use the old Augustine idea that everything happens.
Absolutely not.
This is not the will of God.
And we need to be willing to say that without question.
God can take the most awkward circumstances.
Exactly.
From this point forward, moving forward, he can do that, no question.
Mr. Reagan used to tell the story about that kid digging all that manure out of that stock.
The horse.
The one that actually came out.
Yeah.
He said that all of this has got to be a pony in his stomach.
It's got to be a pony, yeah.
It's a pony.
No, it's a goat.
You know, one of them lady goats.
Good Lord.
Oh, how could you?
I think I'm...
I'm going to be sick.
Oh, yes, seekers.
Am I the only one who's more than a little disturbed by all that venal dry washing of
hands going on on the Trinity Broadcasting Network?
Am I the only one who seems to be doing a little simple math and putting some numbers
together and figuring out who is going to benefit from this total top to bottom shakeup
in our society?
Yes.
Oh, yeah.
I've been taking in a lot of viewing seekers, but the saber rattling is...
Oh, from the Christian camp, it's disturbing to say the least, but below it, there's a
corporate financial venal coldness that makes me wonder who was behind all this.
Oh, yeah.
I'm sure it was the
piloting those plans.
If you believe Paul Crouch, it could have been angels.
Oh, yes.
The world's getting way too screwed up for even me, seekers.
I think that says a lot.
Oh, yeah.
Good.
And it looks like that ain't getting better than we thought.
I'd say ahesion's ingredients are complex...
In a quiet little village by the sea
I hear the calling and it calls for you and me
So keep your riches and your houses on the heels
Cancel all your credit cards and settle up your bills
Cause you don't need them anymore
Blow us down the factories, blow up all the stores
Cause there's a big world coming down
Cause there's a big world and it's coming down
Once I stood in New York City with a sign saying
The end is coming, friends, but then why there's still time?
I will admit that no one really seemed to hear
The word I'm going there, fingers at my sandals and my feet
Now they listen when I say
I have proof that I'm ready
I'm ready to go
It's a big world
Thank you.
Jack Warner's about that big world coming down.
I know I've played that before, but no.
I like to soundtrack it at home.
The butthole surfers with the human cannonball.
I found locust abortion technicians yesterday at the bookstore.
Yes, along with their hogs.
Things are just falling apart.
Shaved pigs had a song,
Die for profits, kill for profits.
And they spelled it B-R-O-F-I-T-S.
But I think we're going to have to deal with some people that are crazy for it.
The other kind of profit seekers.
And Planet B Project hopped in again with a letter from the shelter.
Oh, victims of the fury.
It was just too appropriate.
The world collapsing around us.
Robin's drowning.
But what about things right next door in the People's Republic of Chlamydia?
We heard there's been a like a.
A large outbreak.
We could call it a stain somewhere in the middle of the land.
You know, and some of these people are just stinking the place up.
Yeah.
And was that was it was that planted by the KGB CIA or was it planted by them?
Right.
Smush to make the CIA KGB look bad.
Or was it planted by the others to make them look like they were planting the evidence to make the CIA look bad?
Or was it really salami bin?
I mean, it's been over and take the salami and his crew of madman cutthroats, which must be stamped out one by one.
Well, I can tell you.
By professional cutthroats.
Like cutting heads off a giant bean.
With tattoos of anchors and mom on their arms.
I can tell you what.
And bop!
Grr!
Maybe that's the fast travel.
Ten minutes.
reacted like the internet stuff.
dirt all over.
That's just not clickta-
I didn't make a deal.
I didn't.
Thank you.
I think we could all use a little jolt of this.
Let us therefore brace ourselves for our duty.
So bear ourselves,
that if the British Empire and its Commonwealth
last for a thousand years,
we will be able to do it.
This is the death right now.
That's what I've been trying to find out there,
and I can't find it anywhere else.
I get the feeling that nobody out there is in charge.
And everybody's willing to act their part.
It's like a horrible, jerking fight on a playground
between the three biggest bullies.
The Seekers Group's stuck.
We're stuck.
We're stuck right in the middle of it.
What are we fighting about?
And all we can do,
all we can do is be strong.
All we can do is find that measure of strength
within us as subgeniuses
to keep slogging on.
Look, is this what we,
to keep slogging on,
Haven't we all been getting a little too complacent?
Oh, yes.
We needed a damn good jolt.
Well, honey, here it is.
All nice and gift-wrapped.
And unbelievable.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
Anything.
Anything is survivable if you're lucky.
And that's what we're in this cult for.
And right now, I mean, damn it, Bob didn't get us off this planet,
but here's a chance for Bob to prove that that $30 membership fee was worth something.
At least keep my ass alive.
Oh, Bob, please.
Oh.
Oh, and
if I go.
Oh.
align if I go.
Oh, and if I go.
If I go, I'm up in Marietta, which is close enough to kill Radius and Dobbins over there
that I'm just going to melt into my damn records.
I'm already living in a basement.
It's this far to a bunker, honey.
I'm all it's all there.
Oh, until it's fast enough, then I'm gonna dance a couple horseback.
I want to be a part of it
New York, New York
And the twins were part of their constellation
And the end of the star bore the statute of limitations
As she held out her mighty foot in the harbor
But the day the sky rained black blood
Came and went
Boy, it's getting nighty-night
As I get old
Sack and a belly laugh and a deer eyes nut
Pass me a chunk of that cooked man leg
Stang, can you tell me how bad it's gotten?
How bad have police state America's gotten?
Well, they're thinking about a bill
Where they could grab you for throwing a rock at a truck or a tree
And call you a terrorist and keep you for a week
Until it is gone
They decided you were just throwing a rock at a truck or a tree
Man, there's some places in America
Where they will throw you in jail
For doing things only to yourself
With no victim at all
And no possibility of a victim
Just things that you and you yourself
Agreed to do to yourself
They can consider that somehow as a crime against the state
Since you're part of the state
But yet, I should point out
They let go of the law
They did let me get away with saying that
So it must not be too bad yet
Stang, would they put you in jail
For eating cheese whiz out of the nose
Of a half-prairie squid jackrabbit?
Now, not in Cleveland Heights
But over to Mayfield Heights
I think that they will
But only after 3 o'clock
And before 6 o'clock in the morning
You better not do it on the street
Or in the morning
You are definitely doing some time for that, buddy
You know, the funny thing about some of these autonomous regions
Is they actually get up and bark
Before they're supposed to do the dimwaddle thing
Oh, some of them have nuclear weapons
Yeah, and you can imagine when they start juggling these
Like fish in the middle of the arena
We're all gonna purify
Hey, the Church of the Subgenius
Has three nuclear weapons, doesn't it?
No, five
Five?
Yeah
When did they get the other two?
Oh, a long time ago
We, you, uh
Have we got a nuclear weapon?
We got them, Lane
You were there when we got them, you idiot
Oh, that's right
Pope Black, duh
Don't you remember the deal
When we were
The last time we were in Amsterdam
Oh, that's true
No, it was the Chlamydians
It was a red plutonium dealer
Uh, named, uh, Eichorff
And this, uh, you did the
The Danish Subgenius made a deal with the Ukrainians
Do you have any
Does the Church of the Subgenius have any nuclear weapons in Europe?
Or are they all in the U.S.?
Well, I'm not gonna tell you where or what we're doing with them
Or what countries they might be being shipped into right even as we speak
Because that would be part of an ongoing criminal investigation
That I personally don't want to have any part of
Really?
So, whatever
You gotta understand
You can't joke about bombs and stuff anymore
No
You really can't
They really are gonna come and talk to us now
Yeah
Uh
Let them talk to us
What have we got to hide?
Yeah, you're on a phone call on the other side
It's not a question of hiding your balls
See, this guy thinks all he's gotta do is hide his ball spot
You just hang up
And the beds will go away
This has nothing to do with that
This has to do with planting a new pubic goatee
One that makes you invisible
When you have to have, well, perhaps some sort of interviewer dealing with those people
There'll be a couple of them big black suburbans with the smoky windows
Parking downstairs
Yeah
Somebody's gonna, like, peer out of one of those windows and pull his wife's
Actually, I've already been
I thought
Sure, we'd like to have a word with you
Or a worm
That's what you really gotta worry about
Sure, we'd like to have a worm with you
Or the name like
Like Charles Smith
Yeah, they know that's an orifice
I mean, a name
Skinny white guy
Why, that's the most average fellow in the world
That's what you're looking for now
Old Charlie Smith
Why, sure, he's just a regular guy
Joe Lunchpale
Mr. Mo the Log
Good Catholic boy
I'm just a regular guy
Regular barbecue feller, kind of a neighbor out there.
He was an altar boy and a paper boy.
I don't want to catch.
And I say, as long as you're alive,
shout, make noise, or whatever,
because when you're dead, you shut up like hell.
guitar solo
Yeah, and the storm is threatening
I'm alive today
I'm going to get to the shelter
Oh, I'm going to fade away
Won't you run?
It's just a shot away
Won't you die?
Yeah, and the storm is threatening
I'm alive today
It's just a shot away
Oh, I'm burning and popping
I'm dead, but I'm not stupid
Oh, I'm going to get to the shelter
It's just a shot away
Oh, I'm burning and popping
I won't to die
It's just a shot away
guitar solo
CTO
solo
Charlie, Charlie
It's just a Charlie
I'm telling you
Sister, I
Back
Man, stop that wall.
Them cats are killing themselves.
Put away the guns.
Put the bombs on the shelf.
Stop this wall.
The cats are killing themselves.
Boy, they're shooting them up and they're shooting them live.
They even got swigs and shooting them live.
A big bomb hit a boat out in the sea.
The sailors jumped up and hollered, what you doing to me?
Music
Boy, they bring them down
Low, they're low
When the bomb hits the ground
Them cats have got to go
Boy, that sounds like one of them instantarian bombs
Where'd you get that word, Wingy?
Boy, I dug it out the dugout
Stop the War by Wingy Manone
Or Man-One, or whatever
I have no idea, friends
That was posted to alt-binary slack
And I thought it funny
And it's been an unusual amount of non-subgenius, non-indie music tonight
But then it was largely a Suzy the Floozy Show replay
Bless her heart
Gimme Shelter, there was the Rolling Stones live at the Paradiso in Amsterdam
An unreleased track, Bless the Internet
And alt-binaries sounds, bootleg mp3
Speaking of internet, subgenius.com
Friends, that's where to find it all
www.subgenius.com
For books, mugs, toys, and etc.
And if you're not on there, then you can write to us
If you're not on the internet, you can write to the post office box
A box, here it is again
A box, 1-4-0-3-0-6
Adaption
Dallas, Texas, 75214
Or write to stang at subgenius.com
Box 181417
Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118
Friends, and check out our catalog
And spend, and then support your local station
Spend, and then spread your seed for the war effort
Because hopefully it won't cost too much
Hey, I know I'm going to get on a touchy subject here
But has a subject here?
Osama Bin Laden paid his $30
No
Wow
Boy, you better say no to that
Of course, no
No, I mean
Is there a financial tie
I haven't actually checked
Between the church and Osama Bin Laden
You know, to tell the truth, I haven't checked
I have not checked
You better read that and list the names
Look for all the Mohammeds and stuff
Well, I mean, look at how much money
That the Bin Laden family gave to Bush
You know, that's a big Texas
I mean, you would think that $30
I mean, they've got all that money
They could at least pay $30
Hey, what I want to know
Is that how those Bush girls signed up
We got to get the Bush girls to Ex Day
That's what I want
We must preserve the empire
On board the escape vessels
So that the seed of genius
Will have a suitable fertile ground
In which to be sown
In the future
The far future
I want to go home
Keep your hat on tight
You're back to the wind
You're sacking the saddle
My name's Chaz
Ivan Stang
Pope Black of all New York
Of all Europe
I woke up
Bob
J.R. Dobbs
Bob Dobbs
J.R. Bob Dobbs
Was on the phone
On the number one list
Of frauds and phonies
For Time Magazine
And I didn't know who he was
Exactly
And J.R. Bob Dobbs
Is the creator of
The Church of the Subgenius
This guy
The Reverend Ivan Stang
Is one of their
Disciples
Yeah
Alright
You know, it's funny
I don't think Jesus had
A disciple named Dopey
Poor Bob
Lone cow babe
Don't you know
What they're doing to yourself?