Shootin' high, I'll never stop till I get to the top. Tell me why, shouldn't I?
You know it's you I'm after, you're my lucky star. I'm on a rainbow rafter.
Well, it seems that this new plan has really succeeded in driving the callers completely away from our radio program.
Your slack powers and how to develop them.
Everyone has slack abilities, but few people actually develop them.
These talents must be trained like any other skill.
Here are training methods, physical and mental exercises to prepare you to open your slack centers
and gain powers you probably never thought you could possess.
The exercises are simple and require no special requirements.
Just send $1 to Bob, P.O. Box 140306, Dallas, Texas 75214.
Ah, yes, dear friends, and welcome to the subgenius hour of slack.
Here are some sample subgeniuses now.
They are locked in their special cult hand sign throwing and shaking situation.
Primitive with deep set eye sockets under glowering brows,
they walk upon their knuckles hunched forward uttering plaintive cries.
Calling to each other, Bubba Gee, ma'am, Bubba Gee.
Now, they'll do this for another 20 minutes or so and then they'll settle down.
Contemporary troglodytes, living fossils.
The subgenius.
They are most interesting from an anthropological point of view.
Now, if you're watching, Cadillacs, you can see our view of the subgenius museum in Dallas.
These are the last actual subgeniuses.
Most of them imported from Arkansas.
This is subgenius man.
His home was a cave in the mountains.
The mountains of Dallas, Texas.
Bubba Gee, ma'am.
Their laws are simple.
The strong take everything.
This is Akoba, leader of the rock and roll track.
And his two sons, Sakana and Tumek.
Or Tumescent, Tumid as they call him.
There is no love lost between them.
And that is our story.
Yeah.
So, you...
Man, you should have your head examined.
Yeah.
God, what were you thinking?
Christ, oh God almighty.
Whatever.
Ian, you're...
I can't even begin.
I'm...
Don't wonder what kind of sheer ignorance and stupidity...
would like a man like myself to hear.
Well, God.
Praise Bob.
You're one of the flock.
For only the truly stupid shall be saved.
God's judgment day.
It's true, brethren.
It's true.
How dumb are you?
And for all of you low forehead, toothless, throwback, redneck, honky people sitting out there who are going,
I kind of like that negro music that they keep playing.
And all the dumb shit with watering your beard so you don't undone it from לח찐 comeryidec island.
In fact this isn't a new world.
It seems like it was a newдиtian music.
Hey cats!
Listen to me.
There's a place down in Texas where the hip people meet.
They got lots o slack.
Come along, you will see
It's the place called the Church of the Subgenie
Yeah
That's right, ladies
You wanna live forever
You gotta sleep with Bob
But hey, after all
Isn't there a little Bob in all of us?
The place called the Church of the Subgenie
Bob
You've got a friend in Bob
Just follow the pike
He'll take you there
To Planet X
Drifting out somewhere
Jump on the one plane
And you'll find me
You'll leave the conspiracy noobs
Far behind
And if you think this is all just a scam
You'll be wishing you believed
When the shit hits the fan
As we kill you pigs
So go away, you fool, away
You've got a friend in Bob
When the X-ists come out of the sky
And all the mediocre evidence start to die
All you'll find is a friend in Bob
You'll be pleased with your pathetic jobs
You'll wish they'd listened to the word of dogs
And if you never send in your thirty bucks
It's gonna look like you'll get royally fucked
With a mountain lion in a mug
You've got a friend in Bob
Bob's revolutions are the time of the peak
Reveals the subgenius destiny
Cast out false prophets, extra meditates
So send thirty bucks
Before it's too late
For you've got a friend in Bob
You've got a friend in Bob
July 5th, 1998
Seven a.m. I can hardly wait
The sex gods said
Yes, we'll take thee away
I'll party down with Jesus and J.F. May
Sex hurt for the home of a babble
Bob's rock to the gills
The party rages on
For love of eternity
You've got a friend in Bob
Good Lord, friends!
Good Lord, man!
I just heard that song for the first time with you.
I guess I'll have to cut some,
a couple of cuss words spots out of that.
And, uh, yes, dear friends,
that was the incredible Reverend Moe Joe Walker.
Uh, eh, eh, eh, eh, from, uh, Connecticut.
Yes, Ellington, Connecticut.
I guess he walked up to me and handed me a tape
at the Boston Divival.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, something like that.
Reverend Moe Joe Walker, a friend in Bob,
a great new X Day song.
Uh, we also heard, uh, just before that, uh,
the Church of the Subgenius song by Die Music of Warren, Texas,
Church of Elvis, I believe they, uh, also,
and, uh, and, uh, Dr. Legume and, uh, Dr. Strange
and KPFA Primitive Subgenius Show with Dr. Howell
and Puzzling Evidence and Little Friday Jones.
And, friends, it's true!
It's only 65 days left to X Day.
And things are heatin' up around here, anyway,
and not where, nowhere near as hot
as it'll be for the little Moe Joe Walker.
And pinky winkies come Judgment Day.
But we're waitin' up to our knees in the blood
of the baptism of the mighty fist-face of Bob!
And, uh, uh, and here's a f-
It's flash after flash.
Uh, friends here from the X Day Files,
shall we call them, uh, three days ago,
the church business manager, Jesus,
managed to get one of our many press releases
about X Day onto a weird news site.
And it's a service called News Flash,
which goes to everybody from a morning drive-time radio jock
in Hobunk, Texas, to David, uh, Letterman,
that chicken butt.
Twelve hours later, uh, I, I was on the phone
to, to drive-time jocks in South Africa,
and the Lord was schmoozin' a talk show in New Zealand,
and yesterday I did five morning radio shows
in a bunch of different cities,
and we got two this morning,
and we got four or five more next week,
and it's mostly a bunch of ha-ha, cutesy-smeutesy,
short, smarmy, five-minute stupid culture blips,
but we managed to get some contact information
about the church, you know, a P.O. box,
and some delayed-reaction anti-God time-bomb one-liners in,
you know, about the invisible monsters and like that,
and then maybe it might help the potential last-minute
savees, uh, to recognize Bob's word the next time
they encounter him, dear friends.
Um, and so praise the Lord for this disgusting P.R. blitz,
uh, in the last days here.
I just wish, uh, we didn't have to go to bed so early.
It kind of cramps the indolent lifestyles
of the Lord Jesus and myself.
And, uh, and praise Jesus, the 32-page new
Stark Fist magazine has been printed,
and beautifully, and you won't believe
that this is a Stark Fist, and has been, ironically,
it's mailed out to everybody who renewed,
or at least confirmed,
their existence to us.
And, uh, a lot of people didn't even bother to do that,
so, uh, but man does it look good.
And praise Steve Jackson Games, friends!
The new NWO subgenius role-playing card game
is finished and should be in stores...
now.
And, uh, this, uh, game set, friends,
includes 100 color reprints of the most psychedelic
subgenius art ever imagined, even in Connie's wildest orgasm,
and can be, uh, uh, played either as a standalone
or as part of the Illuminati New World Order game, you see.
You know, the New World Order's just a game,
and the Church of Subgenius is just a game.
Wherever role-playing games are sold,
you know, try the comic book store, actually, friends.
And we've been preaching our leathery old lungs out
on the final Armageddon tour,
coast to coast,
before it's toast, friends.
And after the triumphant Portland and Seattle devivals,
I went to Cleveland for this,
that sublime Einstein secret orchestra secret rituals
where we, as heard last week,
um, where we had, friends,
we had the biggest turnout ever in Ohio,
and, uh, while I was, uh, overmanning the sales table
in Cleveland, this youth came up to me and he said,
my friend has a palindrome.
A palindrome with Bob in it.
Would you like to hear it?
I said, yeah, and the palindrome was
Boston Bob, not sob.
It spells the same, forward, backward,
sort of like Bob's name.
And I asked him if they knew that we were preaching in Boston next,
and the kid denied any knowledge of it,
for the message had come to his friend in a dream, friends,
and the prophecy rings true,
because the final, last, ultimate, penultimate subgenius devival
in Boston, produced by the irreverent and buxotic Friday Jones,
which, because of which I'll always remember it as the double D devival,
friends, the last devival was inarguably the best,
and, and, and by far the most profitable.
Same thing.
Even though it was pouring sheets of rain from the bowels of
Negi himself that night, friends,
the flock came from as far away as Chicago and Quebec
and packed the place to the rafters
to make Friday Jones a fortune.
Um, the first time I've ever seen a subgenius producer make a fortune.
All the preachers got paid, all the musicians got paid,
Friday Jones broke all subgenius merchandise sales table records,
including DragonCon, I'm not kidding.
The only reason the Super Bowl
that a super genius like Friday Jones is even allowed in this church
is because she's still technically not a genius,
but this is what a true subgenius devival is all about.
Real money and real slack, my friends.
The audience was totally jazzed,
and the slack was so thick you could cut it with a chainsaw.
And we had a new pulpit, a pulpit too heavy for any airline to ship.
Huge, carved wooden wings of slack on the front,
and, and, uh, hieroglyphs carved into the front,
and an auto-suck and an auto-john built right in for the preacher,
built for us by the evil Reverend Ed Strange.
And we had banners, cheap but effectively crafted,
Friday Jones banners using the Bobco symbol font,
hieroglyphs printed out big with iron-on-transfer material,
ironed onto a strip of cloth,
and huge new slogan buttons and products,
and, and, friends, uh,
I got to preach with Brother Cleve and DK Jones
and Bill T. Miller as backup gospel organists,
and the, the prophesied bucket of pills was there.
There was a pump, a dispensation of the pills.
There was a dispensation of the pumpkin,
which was righteously groped and orgy-ized on the dance floor by the audience.
The King of Slack, Bill T. Miller, did his greatest hits from Orgy of Slack.
Pope! David!
Friends, tonight's show will feature the incredible,
uh, uh, ranting of,
Pope David N. Meyer,
his return to the subgenius stage,
his mighty confession,
I am the conspiracy.
Friends, Slackbangers performed.
Dr. Legume told the true story of killing a cat that refused to die.
Brother Cleve Duncan got up and peed the spirit of Bob, my friends.
He peed the spirit of Bob.
We did the last of the mass short-duration marriages.
The whole club, 200 people, all married to one another.
We launched the Bleeding Head of Arnold Palmer for the last time.
Pope Meyer got so excited he had to come out and rant again to be heard later.
The Earth Anthem! There was a rant-a-thon, dear friends!
How... how many bands do you know
that will let anyone from the audience come up and use their equipment after the show?
Complete with on-stage fighting between Reverend Stang and me over his girlfriend,
and praise Bob Boston.
Bob... not sob.
It was... and we even had kooks.
There was a crazy man there that said,
came up to Friday Jones and he goes,
I... I am Bob, book of the sub...
I need to know who really wrote Book of the Subgenius.
Stang ignores my letters, and I need to know who really wrote that,
because I... it's based on my life.
I am Bob Dobbs.
It's based on me.
There are 2,000 correspondences with my life in that book.
I used to be a famous Hollywood producer,
but then the conspiracy, the government, have followed me,
and they follow me with black helicopters, and...
Friday Jones said, oh, this is too important to take to Stang.
Write it... write it all out in detail.
And address it to Jesus.
Send it to the P.O. Box, but don't address it to Stang.
Address it to Jesus.
Praise Friday Jones.
The minute she got home from the devival,
I swear to God this is true French,
she stripped off her clothes and rolled in the money.
Literally rolled in the... actually, I did too.
And you can see the pictorial, Miss Subgenius July,
in the upcoming special publication,
Sex, Goddesses of the Church of the Subgenius,
also available this week only on the Newsgroup Alt Binary Slot.
And friends, what's coming up after this?
X-Day is coming up!
By gobs and golly-goshin',
and we at the Dallas Church Headquarters
plan to concentrate everything towards X-Day.
This is the final countdown,
the last push
before the great evacuation,
when Bob's load shall fall,
splashing upon our slack-rejecting,
unrepentant, Bob-less world.
And friends, we're gonna try to release some CDs,
and a CD-ROM of all the great new Subgenius art,
in fact, a completely revised sub-site
at www.subgenius.com.
New T-shirts, designs, and gimmicks, products,
my friends, everything must go by July 5th!
Everything must go!
And, uh, hell, we might even buy advertising
for the first time in 20 years.
That's a sign of the end times, friends.
When the Church of the Subgenius buys advertising.
Well, what...
Oh, you are probably wondering,
what is this great music that I've got in the background?
And it's, um...
What the hell is the name of that sick band?
Ed Strange handed me this CD.
It's a local Philadelphia band called
Stinking Lizaveta.
It's an album called Slaughterhouse.
It's all instrumental guitar tracks.
Ed heard them live and thought,
they...
They might likely like that.
And they all look like Charlie Manson.
You can email them at stinkinglizaveta
at juno.com
or, um...
1002 South 49th Street, Philadelphia,
PA-19143.
Well, friends,
oh, there's so much,
so, so, so much to share,
and I don't even know where to start.
I...
I guess side two mayhaps be
the great rant of Pope David Meyer,
his return to the subgenius preaching stage.
Yeah.
Well, let's just go straight...
Let's just...
Let's go straight into that authentic subgenius
devival tape recording right now.
Praise God.
¶¶
I'm talking about if you've seen any of the old videos, then you have been touched, you have been hit, you have been healed, you have been felt, you have been induced by the great, great, Dr. Dr. Mr. M.D.
Pope David Edmire, the Pope of all New York, Pope of all Great Pacific Northwest, Pope David Edmire, praise the Pope!
Hey kids, how you doing? Why don't you give yourselves a hand, you're such a lovely audience today.
Can we have a hand for the almighty Reverend Cleveland Douglas Duncan, please?
Can we have a hand for the Reverend Cleveland Douglas Duncan, please?
Can we have a hand for the mighty T.K., please?
Can we have a hand for the mighty Dr. M.D.
Can we have a hand for the mayor of euchity, children?
Let me tell you what happened, children.
We were over there in, where were we, Cleveland?
It was called Spit back in those days.
Club Spit, children. We were in Club Spit.
Myself, the Reverend Ivan Stain, the mighty Cleveland Douglas Duncan, we were preaching the word of God.
And you know what happened that night, children? I'm going to tell you what happened.
The mayor's citizens of this town tried to murder the Pope of all New York.
The mayor's citizens of this town, children.
tried to maim the Reverend Ivan Stein.
The fair citizens of this town, children, could not harm
the great Reverend Cleveland Duncan Stoneman. Do you know why?
Do you know why, children? Do you know why?
Do you know why? Do you want to know why?
Because the Reverend Cleveland Duncan Stoneman was upstairs
counting the money.
Children, there were football players
in BC that had necks bigger than my thighs.
My thighs are only medium sized, children, but that makes a big ass neck.
And children, they began to hurl foodstuffs at the Reverend Ivan Stein.
They hurled pizza at him. There are photographs and documents that day of the church
where the Pope of all New York, who is basically a pacifist, on stage
with a mic stand, daring this fucker to come on stage and get killed.
And if you know what the Pope of New York
said, the significance of that event was...
Let me ask you this, children. Was it significant that we kept preaching in the face of danger? Say no.
No! Was it significant that we had the courage of our convictions? Say no.
No! You know, when I go to, when I recount this event, when I tell people
what occurred, they say to me, Dave. Dave!
They say to me, Dave. Dave! They say to me, Rev. Dave. Rev. Dave!
They say to me, Pope of all New York City, Dave. Pope of all New York City, Dave!
What did that event signify? What did that event signify?
It signified, children, about the last time you could get killed over culture.
Now, children, the way it works is this.
You may think that the anti-conspiracy culture resides in the culture you purchase.
But doesn't, children, I say no, children, I posit no, my view is no.
I believe, children, that the desperation, the need, the maniacal desire to be groovy,
has merged the conspiracy and the anti-conspiracy so completely
that when you purchase your culture, you can no longer tell where one ends and the other begins.
Now, children, those of you who have seen me preach before,
you might recall a few salient aspects of my earlier preachings.
There's number one, I usually tell the rules of the church.
Number two, I usually wear shades.
Number three, the Reverend Cleveless Donald Duncan usually plays gospel music behind me.
But, children, my view is that if you don't know the rules of the church by now,
given that the end times are coming in 73 days,
don't mess with it.
Second of all, children, I'm not so sure the rules are relevant anymore, and I'll tell you why.
Because 18 years ago, when this wonderful church, the church of love and money, the world's best industrial church,
the only church to guarantee you eternal salvation or
your money back.
Well, back then, children, back then, in 1981,
we were funny. But today, children, in 1998,
we're just right.
You know who people say, children,
people say, you don't have a monopoly on the truth.
We do, children.
We do have a monopoly on the truth.
And the truth is, children, that as you try to make your way through this world, as you try to parse out,
does this guy look like a bodyguard? Can you be more sinister, please?
Come over here. Step up here. Somewhere out here is a force of
anti-bond that wants to harm the Pope. Get it together.
Now, where was I? As you try to make your way through this culture,
children, as you try to find yourself by your purchases, what you will find
is a self-fulfilling tautology, and that is this, children.
You can't find an authentic experience
because you're purchasing, children. You're purchasing. You know, Reverend Slack
was loathe to define Slack. I am not loathe to define Slack, children.
I am willing to tell what Slack is, children. People say to me, day.
They say to me, Rev Day. They say to me, Pub of All New York City Day.
What is Slack?
Slack is all that.
Well, I'll tell you just what the fuck I'm talking about, children. Slack is a
relative phenomenon, children. Slack varies from place to place and time to time and person to person.
I'll give you an example. In my house, Slack is two new CDs and a
brief respite from existential dread.
In downtown Kilgolly, children, Slack is a handful of millet.
And the rest of us are somewhere in between. But what I want to say here, children,
is there's some things that haven't been touched on that I think need to be touched on, children.
And that's this, children. As you pursue that authentic experience, children,
as you go around purchasing your culture, children, purchasing your identity until it doesn't work anymore,
you've got to define yourself. We get back to the most basic of Bob's preaching, children.
And that's what I'm here to tell you tonight. To get off Bob's dick.
And to get off Bob's tit.
Because what is Bob, children? What is Bob?
Bob is a short-term
duration personal
savior.
That's short-term, children.
That's a hobbyist's savior.
Keep going. You ought to go. That's a hobbyist's
savior. So you might say to me
in all reasonable terms,
Dave. You might say to me,
Rev. Dave. You might say to me,
oh, New York City, you almost got killed
in Boston. Dave.
What are you still doing in the church then?
Well, the answer is simple, children.
The Pope of all New York is the world's first slackless pope.
There's a hard core rule in the church, children. That is,
the harder you preach for Bob, the less slack you've got. The more you reach for Bob,
Bob only receives, children. He only receives. Think of Achilles and the turtle, children.
Is the Pope of New York ever going to catch Bob? Say no.
Say no. Say hell no.
Say hell no. I'm here, children, to serve you.
And you. And you.
I'm here, children, to bring you the
true word of Bob. To tell you
how Bob really, really
operates.
Now let's talk about a little
word of Bob. To tell you how
Bob really, really
operates.
Now let's talk about a little something,
children. An 18-year-old concept
that's still valid called
techno-boredom.
Now techno-boredom, children,
is the way the conspiracy operates.
But the funny thing is about techno-boredom is this.
Techno-boredom is the conspiracy's main tool
to make you buy again. It makes you
bored with your new toy, so you've got to buy another
new toy. But you know what we've learned, sadly,
over 18 years?
Just identifying techno-boredom
doesn't allow you to escape it.
Now, children, you know
the great Huey Newton, the great Huey Newton,
the founder of the Black Panther's people party,
he said, and I quote,
the man's technology
is no match for the people's will.
That sounds good, children.
It sounds good, but I'll tell you what,
he had it exactly backwards.
Because, children, our home is filled
with toys, it's filled with
diversion, it's filled with ways
to escape, and what are we trying
to escape, children? What are we trying
to escape? With our televisions
and our CDs and our
sampling keyboards and our Internet?
I'll tell you what we're trying to escape.
We're trying to escape the pain within.
And where does that pain within
come from? Does it come from your
fundamentally worthless
humanity?
I think not, children.
It comes from the marketing forces
around you that make you hate yourself.
So you'll go buy something so you'll hate yourself
a little less.
But in fact, children, you don't have
to buy all the conspiracy products.
It's kind of a word line
mistake you've got to do.
You don't have to buy the conspiracy products. No, you
don't. You just go out over here and buy, children.
You just buy out over there. People come up to me
all the time on the street, on the street
when I'm without my bodyguard who's doing such
a good job of protecting me, and they say to me,
Day! They say to me, we're dead!
They say to me, Paul, all
New York City dead!
Where do I go? How do I think?
What do I buy? What do I wear?
Where do I turn? And you know what I say
to them, children?
I say, it's in the book.
It's all in the book, children.
It's all right here.
If you read this book carefully,
you'll know all you need to know.
If you extra meditate longly,
deeply, fully, and with
concentration, you will find the answers
that you seek.
Now let me just turn my milk canes over here,
children.
The thing is, that this insidious culture
that surrounds you turns you into
efficient water. You can't tell
when it's in you and when it's not in you.
Understand me, children?
Here's the point I'm trying to make.
Here's the thing I came here to tell you tonight, children.
The thing that I brought myself down here tonight.
Doug likes to say that he has nothing in common
with the conspiracy, and that might well be true, children.
But in my case,
I am the conspiracy, children.
People say to me, we're dead!
They say to me, Paul, all New York City dead!
How could you possibly be the conspiracy, children?
And you know what I say to them children?
Say no!
You know what I tell them when they ask me that, children?
Say no! I'll tell you what I tell them, children.
I tell them that I make my living
creating the conspiracy.
And I'm damn good at it, children.
That's right, children. I write advertising.
I edit commercials.
I write and produce promos.
And when you open your magazine,
and you go home and watch television,
and you see an ad, and you go,
wow, that ad is like
so groovy and hip and kind of a
commentary on that other ad that
ran two years ago. Wow, that's really like a
meta-ad. It's not really an ad at all.
It's more like a pastiche
of a deconstruction of all these other ads.
It's positively fucking Lacanian.
I got news for you, children.
You know what that news is? Say no.
The news is,
I wrote that in service of the conspiracy.
Where do you think that hip shit
comes from, children? It comes from
sellouts like me!
And you know what that does to me, children,
when I think about my personal short term duration?
It fills me with shame, children.
Keep going, boy, you want it.
It fills me with irritation.
It fills me with self-loathing.
But, children,
what it does, do I go out there
and buy something from the conspiracy?
Say yes, children!
Yes, I do!
Oh, yes I do, children!
Why do I hit it?
Why do I make all that good conspiracy product, children?
I make all that good conspiracy product
so I can buy more good conspiracy products.
And I make all that good conspiracy product
to make it harder
for the goddamn bobbies
to tell the difference
between pink and slack.
So, children, let me tell you,
when you watch a TV and that ad comes on,
that goddamn ad that's
so perfectly canny,
children, that's the conspiracy
at its most insidious
form. Because no
in the conspiracy, children,
no organ of the conspiracy,
no arm of the conspiracy,
is ever going to tell you the truth, children.
The truth resides here!
The truth resides with Bob!
The truth resides in those
who take Bob into their heart!
Who take Bob into their head!
And most importantly, children,
who take Bob into their wallet.
Why should Bob be
any different, children?
The measure of your commitment to your culture and yourself
is what you spend
on it, children.
Talk is cheap, children. Talk is cheap.
That's right, children.
Tell me something, children. Do you remember this proverb?
Tell me something.
What walks?
Bullshit! I couldn't hear you.
Bullshit! Excuse me, what walks?
Bullshit! What was that?
Bullshit! Thank you, children.
And what talks? Fire!
There you go, children.
So, children, if you don't tie it to Bob,
that which is Bob's,
then, children, I hope you're drowning in shame.
I hope you're drowning in self-love.
I hope you're drowning
in fear. There's nothing
that affects the fear that the public
on the York side has.
Because, children, I sell the conspiracy
only in pursuit of slack.
I operate on
perfectly symmetrical hypocrisy.
I know exactly
where I stand, and I never
confuse myself. When I'm sitting at home
and that ad comes on, and I wrote
the son of a bitch,
I say, God, that's a conspiracy
at its worst.
And the shame, children,
the shame rises over me,
and I have to think, children.
Do I deserve Bob?
Do I belong with Bob?
Am I clean enough
to be with Bob, children?
Am I too corrupted
for Bob?
Have I become nothing
but a slave to the conspiracy, children?
But you know what, children,
when I come here
on a night like this,
and I feel the presence
of God,
when I feel the Bob in me,
when I feel Bob passing through my veins,
when I feel Bob setting me free, children,
when I see the error
of my ways, children,
and when I know I can fly first class
when I work for the conspiracy,
and I can still come here
and drop down on my knees for Bob,
on my knees for Bob, children,
I feel the Bob within me,
I feel the Bob passing through me, children,
I feel the Bob
redeeming me, children,
I know that Bob is here
with me tonight, and I say
to all of you, and I say to myself,
you are
clean enough, you are good enough,
you are right enough,
but if, if,
and only if, you get
right with Bob
tonight, goodnight!
Good night!
Like Jesus, God,
you are out of control!
You are out of control!
Hey! Oh, David Ann Meyer!
What's that shit?
No!
A young world.
A world
early in the morning of time.
Beware the giant flying
octopuses.
Beware the cliff
dwelling centipede.
A night crawling scorpion.
Beware!
At night,
out upon the land,
things come crawling,
twitching, seething, rustling, and flopping.
I'll bet that's where
Phineas is, in the seething, rustling,
flopping things, and he can't find his way out.
He's just too timid to get out of the car, and
they're driving around in circles.
Through the seething, flopping,
trying to find Berkley.
Yes, they're plunging upriver through a
seething horde of
living things of incalculable
number.
Huge plesiosaurs, tylosaurs,
gigantic primordial fish,
a carcaridon
megalodon, the gigantic precursor
of today's great white shark.
So don't worry, Smith.
The creature's the size of Ireland.
Take it easy, Smith.
Yeah, just take it easy, Smith.
Take it easy, first, Smith.
And the fastotopalon,
hugest of turtles
that swim the ocean's stream.
Take it easy, Smith.
You gotta take it easy, Smith.
Oh, God, what a relief. I hate that song.
Wasn't that, uh,
overmodulated slightly?
We don't want to drive Dave
completely over the edge
before we get to Alpha Centauri,
do we, Chaz?
Commander Chaz.
I thought maybe
peaking the levels would
kind of push him that little bit extra.
That little micrometer more.
Well, we're just trying to get
him to keep him creatively dreaming.
We're not, we don't want to
drive him completely catatonic.
I mean, he might have,
what's the difference? Who cares?
Go ahead, whatever you were doing.
I just thought I was, uh,
as shipboard computer, you know,
it's my responsibility to, uh...
Oh, look, what's he...
A pleasure vessel.
I probably could have anything
I wanted right now if I really tried
and put my mind to it.
I just didn't think of myself as a
victim out here.
You can be what you want, Dave.
That's right.
Anything you want.
I'm never coming into a meteor shower or something.
Yeah.
I might have to think of something quick.
What if them things start pounding into
this little tuna can?
I'll be dead 90 million miles from here.
He listens to me better when I use the female voice.
I'll switch over to the female voice
and counsel him.
Come on, Dave.
Yeah.
Mom, it's gonna be all right.
Mom?
Yeah. Mom?
Aren't you my mom? Are you...
I don't think so, Dave.
You...
I'm just the computer voice, but I'm not programmed to sound like you.
Mom.
Well, you're good enough for mom for me.
Just keep paving me up.
If that makes you feel better, Dave, I can be mom.
Just keep telling me what to do, because
I got a bad feeling in a few minutes
I'm gonna be going turkey duty all over this here floor.
Lay back.
I'm gonna be a little bit hurt out there, man.
It's okay.
Kaka duty won't hurt anything.
Oh, yes, brothers and sisters.
Oh, yes, the end is near.
It's right in front of your face.
Can I get an amen?
Amen!
Now, for those of you who are saved,
you might as well just go have yourself a drink,
because I'm not talking to most of you right now.
So, now listen up, pig people.
Weepin' well.
Because of the misery
that is coming upon you,
your wealth has rotted,
and moths have eaten your clothes.
Your gold and silver
are corroded.
Their corrosion will testify you
and eat your flesh like fire.
You have hoarded wealth in the last days.
Look!
The wages you've failed to pay the workmen
who've mowed your fields
are crying out against you.
The cries of the harvesters
have reached the ears of the almighty dogs.
You have lived on earth
in misery and self-indulgence.
You have fattened yourselves in the day of slaughter.
You have condemned
and murdered innocent men
who were not opposing you.
For this,
the earth shall mourn,
and the heavens above
shall be blackened.
It's okay.
Just ignore those sounds.
It's really nothing.
Breathe deeply.
That's right.
Just ignore those sounds.
The flashes, too.
Just close your eyes.
It's starting to shake in here.
Una, what am I going to do?
It's going to hate me.
We lost first.
We lost Mickey, Matt, and everybody.
No, I don't want to go back.
Don't you remember you were in a foxhole, Dave?
I don't want to go back.
Charlie's grenade landed in there
and the next thing you knew
you were wiping away.
You were wiping your best friend's face
off of your face.
Oh, no, that's right.
No, wait a minute.
I know what happened.
You were injured. Your spine was blown out.
My spine was blown out.
No, wait. Yes. No, wait.
We took you to the hospital.
Yes, you took me to the hospital.
You took me to a medivac,
and a doctor shot me up.
And then they tried to put a new spine in,
but instead they said...
Uh-oh. Get down, men.
Get down.
Take him down.
Get over here.
Put him in Hanoi Hilton
for 30 years.
No shooting. No shooting.
No Ming-Li Tao.
Me Dinky Tao, see?
Peace, man.
Peace. Let's have peace.
Make love, not war.
Just get on the helicopter, man.
Come on. It's time to go.
We're here to help you, man.
Don't you want to leave this place, dude?
Come on, man. It's time to go home.
Come on.
Okay, man. It's been a long one for me.
I lost a lot of guys down here.
Hey, man, wipe your best friend's face off your face
and get on the helicopter.
Oh, my God! I still got Jerry's face on my face!
There's one law manifested by Bob's hand.
His reign has opened darkness on the land.
We will punish all believers.
The children of the Yeti
will torture all the children of the ape.
Run to the hills.
Or face your crucifixion.
Amen!
The cattle die in the fields.
The crops wither in springtime.
Your stomachs bleed with hunger.
Your bodies burn in fire.
The battlefield is cold and desolate.
Seven million years of boiling shit await you.
Your eyelids shall be cut from your face.
It's the greatest show on earth.
And you can't look away.
The four horsemen ride.
To rage the fear.
The prophets will be crucified.
Behold the horsemen.
The stage is set through all dimensions.
The end has come.
Look to the west.
Dave, look behind us. The path's gone, man.
We just walked. It looked like there was a path.
The path is gone.
Oh, my God.
Man, we're out in the boonies.
I was up in the helicopter.
Man, this is worse than Jacob's Land.
But I...
Hey, what am I...
Hey.
General Ursus, I must insist
that we cease this cruel hunting of humans.
Dr. Zaius, you are a silly liberal fool.
These humans are nothing but animals.
We will take them aboard our pleasure saucers
and train them to be our servants.
I see.
We will give them lobotomies
and do experiments on them.
There's nothing wrong with that.
There's nothing else we can do.
The surplus of the program's almost all been eaten
by the last cuts.
We have to do with what we can.
And look at them, anyway.
You call them humans?
I will not repent.
Rather, I will turn back from it.
What time is it?
It's harvest time,
brothers and sisters.
It's harvest time.
Oh, yeah.
The crops are getting high in the fields
and it's almost harvest time.
July 5th is the day
the shadow of the scythe shall fall
and reap the harvest here on Earth.
You don't need
the Hubble Space Telescope
to see the end.
It's right in front of your face.
It's harvest time.
I'm going to bear witness to you.
I'm going to tell you all a story.
In 1953,
Jehovah One
gave a man named J.R. Bob Dobbs
a seat on the planet.
He was a great seed.
Bob could have sold that seed
because he's the greatest salesman who ever lived.
Bob could sell
stink to shit.
But Bob didn't sell that seed.
He planted it.
He walked out
into a big old field of weeds
and he planted that seed.
He watered that seed
with his slack.
He fertilized that seed
with his seed.
with his bullshit.
He knew that one day
there would be a mighty crop
in that field of weeds.
And 25 years later,
there sprung from the ground
the first green sprout.
Ivan Stan.
Philodrumon.
Pope David Meyer.
Oh yes, and then another
and another
and another. And Jader Hypercleps, yes.
And another and another.
Yes, until there was a verdant
garden of subgenius.
Sure, the weeds, the humans
tried to strangle and choke those
subgeni down. But the subgeni
held their ground because they knew
that on July 5th, 1998
they would be transplanted
to the fertile soil
of Planet X.
So be patient then, brothers and sisters
until the saucer's coming.
See how the farmer
waits for the land to yield
its valuable crop.
And how patient he is for the autumn
and spring rains.
You too be patient and stand firm
because the X's coming
is near.
Amen!
As for the weeds, however...
Suspect number four, pull your pants down.
Pull your pants down,
Suspect number four, it's time for the ceremony.
Robert had to pull my pants down.
Suspect number four,
Lonesome Cowboy Day.
Hey, you guys back behind that window,
I ain't taking my pants down.
I don't need to be identified that way.
You know, you guys said you all were in the cave
and now next thing you know you want me to, you know,
take my pants down. She can't identify me that way.
Princess, me?
Is the seminar dildo
well greased and sharpened?
You know, I got a good lord, buddy.
Alright, prepare the razor dildo.
Administer him.
Alright, alright.
Set the dwarves to
cranking the machinery. How long do I have to do this?
So that the great corkscrew razor dildo
and the ceremony may begin.
And the ceremony may begin.
Oh, good brogue friend.
Okay, you guys,
there it is, only four and a half inches.
You want to start laughing now or what?
Okay, can you identify me?
Is this my distinguishing mark?
Oh, good brogue friend, thank you for sending us these
to the hands of pathetic humans.
Suspect number four, just stand there the way you are.
Just stand there.
Just shut the sacrificial
rakey up.
Please.
It's starting to get cold.
My god, these stupid
ceremonies, this stuff goes on for so
long that the dwarf-powered
razor dildo is broken.
Man, I felt a cold shaft of air
go right through there, man. I'm zipping it up right now.
I've got the creeps in here.
Well...
You guys are nuts. This ain't no police lineup.
I guess Bob's going to get
suspect number four after all.
Oh well, at least he pays well.
You're going to be Bob's
personal manservant soon.
His dresser, so to speak, Dave.
On his great mansion,
which we also, science knows,
as Alpha Centauri, the star.
That's actually Bob's
house, and first you're going to have to
mow the lawn.
It's a lawn of
flaming hot hydrogen
reactions. Some would call it
hellish.
But in Bob's house are many mansions,
you know, Dave.
You broke on through to the other side,
you passed the veil, you came to the light,
you made it to Alpha Centauri,
and well, now... I'm invigorated.
...you get your eternal salvation.
Yeah.
...on this 2,000 degree Fahrenheit
hydrogen gas bag
in outer space.
It's heaven, Dave.
That's right, yeah, heaven.
And those guys in pitchforks,
with pitchforks and long tails, those are angels.
Yeah, they come to help me
and I just chuck some hay in stuff.
So, uh, you go on out there, Dave.
I'll jump right in.
Yeah.
I'm ready. Margaret!
What, Linda!
Margaret, I'm ready!
Bob says I can mow the
nuclear fusion lawn now, if I can
if I can just
I think the weeds sound like
a police...
Amen! As for the weeds, however,
they won't be
transplanted, because it's hard to
find. Yes, brothers and sisters,
the aliens from Planet X will enjoy
a mighty weed harvest,
for they too are farmers.
Weed farmers!
On X-Day, you who have
scoffed at Dob's prophecies
will find that you've been
hung out to dry, and the
X-ists are going to smoke you
like the cheap weeds you are.
Woo! Praise cheap weeds!
Oh, yes, brothers and sisters.
I want you all
to reach into your hearts.
I want you all to reach
into your minds.
And then I want you to reach into
your wallets, and take out
thirty dollars.
That thirty bucks is your
seed. And like Bob,
you've got to decide whether to plant your seed
or sell it.
Now,
you can sell your seed today
for a month's
worth of cable TV,
or you can sell your seed
today for a ticket
to see the Spice Girls
or Marilyn Manson.
But if you
do, you'll go hungry
tomorrow.
Because if you plant your seed
in the fertile soil of Dob's pocket,
you'll feast for eternity
on an all-you-can-eat buffet
of sex, slack,
and salvation. Give it a name, then!
Amen!
The subgenius church
is one small step away
from becoming in full
Mystery Babylon,
the adulterous harlot
of Revelation.
Last year,
just before Halloween,
Reverend Stang and myself were called out
to San Francisco by
Anton LaVey, who was lying
in his deathbed at the time.
As he lay dying in his bed,
Anton LaVey reached out
and clasped my hand.
And he said to me in a raspy voice,
Where's that cat?
Dapper legume,
I think I fucked up.
And then he shoved
thirty dollars into my hand.
Anton LaVey's
dying words were,
Praise Bob.
Those words passed his lips,
and he died.
Well, Anton LaVey was right.
He did fuck up.
He gave his money too late,
and now he's fucking dead!
Don't make that same mistake.
Don't come waving your thirty dollars
at us on X-Day
at 7-0-1-A-M.
Don't come waving your thirty dollars
at us on X-Day at 7-0-1-A-M.
You can wipe your ass with those
scraps of green paper then.
And you'll need to,
because you're going to shit
when you see what Bob Dobbs
has in store for you.
Bob Dobbs will show you fear
in a handful of dust.
You shall be burnt with hunger
and devoured with burning heat
and with bitter destruction.
Dobbs will send the teeth
of beasts upon you
with the poison
of serpents of the dust.
And you shall suck
the poison of asps.
The viper's tongue shall slay you.
Hell is naked before you
and destruction has no covering.
Oh yes,
brothers and sisters,
and I had a vision
and I looked
and beheld a pale horse
and his name that sat on him
was Dobbs.
And hell followed with him
and slung him over the earth
to kill with sword
and with death
and with the beasts of the earth.
And in those days shall men seek death
and shall not find it
and shall desire to die
and death shall flee from them.
Therefore shall Dobbs' plagues
come in one day,
death and mourning and famine
and earth shall be utterly burned
with fire.
Do you hear it?
The raging hoofbeats
with a cloud of dust
and a hearty high of silver
the four horsemen ride.
Can you see the sign?
I was still alive.
Do what you like,
not what you're told.
Stay with me,
brothers and sisters,
and give me life.
Scorch the men who wear the mark.
Let the seas and rivers
bleed into the air.
The firstborn of the dead,
the firstborn of the dead.
is on his head.
Turn away,
turn away,
fuck the blood of the Lamb.
Jesus Christ sucks cock
for nickels in Times Square.
He who has an ear
let him hear,
he who has an eye
They fill our hearts with lies.
They feed us egg McMuffins.
Brothers slay brothers.
Sisters, children shed each other's blood.
Hard is the world.
Sensual sin grows huge.
These are sword ages, axe ages.
Shields are cleft in twain.
Dorm ages, murder ages.
The world falls dead.
And men no longer spare or pity one another.
Uh, no they don't, dear friends.
But if you want to cover your own butt,
be sure to write for free information from the Church of the Subgenius.
Just write to Bob at Post Office Box 140306.
That's Box 140306, Dallas, Texas, 75.
214.
The only source of the truth, dear friends.
Also available at www.subgenius.com.
Praise God.
Yet he will go and will pour his seed upon the earth.
And there will erupt a grievous sore.
Praise the sore!
Bleeding out of the darkness.
A prayer for the dying.
They want his slack.
They want his pipe.
They want his blood.
His blood flows to the river.
His slack can shatter the blackness to cry out in the night.
Bring me my pipe!
Our hate roars like thunder.
Carrying a jagged wound across the land.
The earth will bleed and die.
It drags you through the doorway and rips out your lying tongue.
Praise God.
And he said.
It's
Well,
you sell me two days for a home.
Mostly on the tip off,
but most of theied as 모습 with he pay.
You have died mid night.
会 shake him just unable to freeze.
Dying in some soup without telling my age.
The only thing.