This is your host and prayer partner, Reverend Ivan Stang, leaving Barney's Coffee Shop and Bar in Amsterdam with Dr. Hal Robbins, Princess Wee Ardo, and Governor Rottenaar, towards the last legs of the Cannabis Cup Tour, on which Dr. Hal and Rottenaar are judges, and on which Princess Wee and I are vendors, sacred vendors.
I could have stayed in there all night long.
You could stay in any of these coffee shops all night long, and it's been, it's taken great discipline and effort to make it from coffee shop to coffee shop.
Barney's, Barney's was the best.
Barney's had the greatest bribes of any coffee shop, and some of them, some very good froth as well, no doubt, but they gave us samples.
There's a car, a truck.
Seconds.
Well, okay, we better, since friends, we have to pay attention to finding our way home now, so that's the story here in Amsterdam for the hour of slack.
Tonight.
And with that Christmas song by the Children of Holland.
This is Radio Nederland returning you to The Scenic World in Hollywood.
Look, look, it's all dovetails.
It's all dovetails.
A sea of them.
A sea of dovetails.
We're standing under the overtune, friends, in a subterranean pirate radio basement station in Amsterdam, Holland.
Dr. Hal is here, and Princess Wee, Pope Black, and Governor Rottenaar.
And a number of other humans or subgeniuses wearing Dobbshead masks, making the whole scene look like some kind of warped twisted Fellini movie.
Yes, it's like living in a foreign film.
Everything is there except the subtitles.
And oh, how I miss the subtitles.
Which might explain to me what the hell is really going on here.
But of that, I remain ignorant as perhaps you too, the listener.
All we can do is have faith.
Yes, faith in that face of J.R. Bob Dobbs.
That endlessly dotted halftone or sometimes high contrast face.
If we can but seize upon that as the focus of our attention, our love, and our thoughts.
Perhaps we can be safely guided back to a place of cool music and cool speech, talking, and so forth.
But in the meantime, we're trapped here in this dungeon basement with the Church of the Subgenius.
Megachurch.
Sex.
The only path to salvation.
Megachurch.
Sex.
The only path to salvation.
Very carnal.
Hawk is 80 years old now.
And he's admitted that he slept with his brother.
Very carnal.
He slept with his brother.
Brother.
Br-br-br-br-br-brother.
Megachurch.
Sex.
The only path to salvation.
Megachurch.
Sex.
The only path to salvation.
You are listening to this session because you needed slack tonight.
Tonight.
You.
Yourself.
The one listener.
Not those other listeners, but you.
The one listening now.
You.
I, we knew you needed the slack of Bob.
Yes, Bob.
It's no longer God.
It's you.
The one that we're talking about.
Who cares about those old fashioned Gods?
This is the newfangled, cool Bob from bob.com.
Yes, we are here to bring you what you needed.
Slack.
A respite from normality.
A break from your daily grind and perhaps a headache or two.
because the music here recorded in the stomach of my colleague Dr. Howe about six hours ago.
Bob! Bob! Bob!
Why, listen, you can hear the subgeniuses calling for their lord and master Bob,
singing praises to Bob, that ever-present smiling face tattooed inside the inner side of your eyelid
so that you can never stop seeing them.
Yes, yes, yes.
And only on Radio Patapo are the signals allowed to go out unblemished, uncoated, the pure signal.
There's no extra code in here, not like all the other radios that you listen to.
No, at Radio Patapo in Amsterdam you hear only the pure sounds of the angels.
The sound of heaven.
Those sirens always make me feel like I'm in the TV show The Prisoner.
So Bob is sort of this parody of the culture?
Some people call the Church of the Subgenius a joke or a parody,
just because our...
Our religious leader, like some others, is a patent fraud and fake.
But, hey, you know, where would any religion be without its fair share of hypocrisy?
Bob founded the world's first industrial church.
It's a church made for this modern world where you get planned obsolescence.
Well, we know that most religious leaders are going to get...
boring and tedious after a while.
So Bob is what he calls a short-duration personal savior.
We want you to buy every bit of wisdom and entertainment that Bob sells,
but after that you're welcome to move on to the devil or Jesus or L. Ron Hubbard or Elvis
or your favorite porno star.
Maybe your favorite comic book artist.
Yes, my colleague here is Dr. Howe.
He's the one who wrote the book, The Toast of San Francisco.
But of course what we bring as we go catapulting into the future is just more of the past.
Because the more the future continues, the more of the past there's going to be in it.
Until finally there will be room for no more future, but only the vast, heat-up accumulation of the past.
And at that time we will bring matters to a close.
So Tony, we're waiting.
First şöyle сейчас,
Raquel
Alors Pierce
I think I got you all back, guys.
Joining you, all right.
Where do you live?
California.
Do you think my future might be obsolete?
Is life's puzzle somewhat incomplete?
Have you lost anything more than just a joke?
If you have to ask then you will never know
I'm not telling you what to do
You wanna try out something new
Save our humans of today
Let me tell you how
You change now
Now
You have that feeling that others think you're strange
Would you like to get even with everyone you hate?
Do you think that you're the one who might be next?
It's possible you're better than the rest
I'm not telling you what to do
Know yourself what you should do
Your normality starts today
Let me tell you how
You change now
Now
Thank you.
You're taking now.
Oh, yes, dear friends, Mutate Now by the band Mutate Now,
which happens to be our friend Reverend Scott Stanton of sickvideo.com
and a couple of German guys.
And you can find the video of that and much, much more of their material
from myspace.com slash mutatenow or mutatenow on YouTube and watch the video.
Oh, those people suddenly appeared in Dobbshead masks at Radio Patipo in Amsterdam,
which we heard some of via Lord Yeti just a little while ago.
And plus, we heard some miscellaneous sounds of the Frop Cup there
and various interviews with High Times TV and others.
More of that to come.
And collages by Fernandenende Limer and Norelpref.com.
And...
And more will follow, but first I must answer some questions last month
on the subgenius puzzling evidence show from KPFA Berkeley.
I think this show is a frightful, still-living human specimen of miracle of medical science.
When the coming era of Dobbs comes over the nation,
and if Reverend Stanton becomes the Pope of the USA,
what will be the separation?
What will be the separation of church and state?
Quarter inch.
It'll be lifted.
Theocracy.
One and fourteenth of an inch.
It's a theocracy.
When Bob is world overlord, there won't be any difference.
It'll be lifted and separated.
It's a total theocracy.
When Bob is world overlord.
Completely depend on the subjugation of all the masses
to make the virus pursue the appropriate course.
Hey, do you have any of that virus?
I think some of that virus are taking over.
When Bob is world overlord.
Radio show.
I think it's working.
I can't understand a word.
Man, that's some of the best virus you've ever heard.
Great wild hog that you've ever seen.
How and I were at the virus cup.
How was that?
How'd that go?
That's right.
I and state.
I mean, there's no problem.
Well, I told them how you graduated magna cum laude from marijuana university.
I was shocked that I was such an expert on marijuana.
I was shocked that they marked me down by four points for my allegedly frivolous answer.
After years of flapping, how did you find this?
Allegedly frivolous answer.
This hidden knowledge of marijuana.
Well, that was my question because I'm a frapper.
You know me.
Yeah, he's a frapper from way back.
You got your frapper abuser t-shirt on.
That's right.
Show us your diploma.
Here.
Whip it out.
The radio audience.
Oh, I forgot to bring it.
Which camera is it?
It's on camera two.
I have it, not him.
Radio audience is tuned to camera two.
I forgot to bring it.
I mean, she has a frapper abuser t-shirt.
Frapper abuser.
I don't have it.
By the way, I have the list of, you know, I have the list of, you know, I have the list
of winners in the Frop Cup.
Yeah.
Our Slack people already heard it.
And who won?
Was it G13 Hayes?
Who was the winner?
Super Jenkum Hayes was the number one winner.
Whoa.
That wasn't the popular favorite.
Jenkum.
I'm sure that was her final word.
Let's see.
Did she make it to half a million?
Biggest prize is when Ren first won.
She won.
Biggest prize.
Biggest prize for sitting in the room.
Okay, but what does that come for?
Same thing with a makeover once again.
Lame.
You know what I mean?
I mean, we didorta gets her.
Running over with that other idea.
But in the Cannabis Cup, there was a contestant called Princess Bob Indica.
For real.
Corn swoggle it, and we never ran into each other.
And I back away, and it goes away.
Well, that's unfortunate.
Although I have been communicating with Plastic Mediator.
Plastic Mediator was another winner in the Frop Cup.
That was some good stuff.
I had a sample of Plastic Mediator hash.
You did?
This one's got a divot.
They were giving out grams of Plastic Mediator hash at the Dobstown bar.
Oh, my.
I see.
I'm going to have to revise my personal chronology of recent events.
But it is a lot less dusty.
Mr. Nothinghead was a big winner.
Yes, I remember that.
And under the Lung Junk category, Death Lung Head.
The Death Lung Hash, which was scraped from former subgenius Chaz Smith, was the winner.
At that cafe, yes.
Death Lung Hash.
Yeah.
Lunk.
Death Lung Hash.
Lung Junk.
It's the game joke.
For the listeners who aren't familiar with Lunk, Lunk is the material that is scraped from the lungs of heavy smokers after they die.
You have to be in the Lunk Club, and that way your Lunk will go to the next Lunk user.
It's sort of like you can give your body parts, you can give your Lunk to the Lunk Club.
Now, what is the organic relation between Lunk and Gradoo?
Well, Gradoo is sort of like generic Lunk.
Yeah.
Yeah, sort of like environmental generic Lunk.
Could be from anywhere.
Right.
Lunk is always Gradoo, but Gradoo is not always Lunk.
Correct.
And there's that mysterious substance, Glaxo, which accumulates in the navel and between the toes.
It's beautiful.
Yeah.
Don't forget.
It's the beginning of the show.
Yeah, I know.
That Billy Button Lent sweater.
That's the one we had for sale last year.
Now, the Billy Button Lent Lunk was another one.
It's a really weird spider.
It's what they call America.
That's a real...
I dare you to call.
I dare you to try to talk to us.
She could knit a Billy Button Lent sweater.
The United Snakes of Marijuana.
It's beautiful.
It looks like a tail.
A potato?
Oh, no.
The Billy Button Lent sweater was real popular last year.
Your daughter is a psychopath.
Since time began...
She is on the verge of insanity.
Out of the slime and darkness.
And I strongly believe she has been symbolic.
Oh, isn't that good?
Murdered by marijuana.
Murderers.
No.
If you break, a white fluid oozes out.
Use your eyes.
Marijuana and hashish.
Joints.
Roach.
Joint.
Scorched, irregularly burned butt.
As a matter of fact, hard narcotic addiction.
Oh, no.
It frightened me.
The story you are about to hear is...
The subgenius.
Power of Swatch.
To protect the cigarettes.
Long cigarettes.
Hello?
This is Longhead.
Who?
Longhead.
Oh.
I see.
Come early and we'll have cots together.
Oh, boy.
Yo, yo.
And death.
Another cup?
No, thanks.
I've had enough.
Why?
I ought to have more sense into paying the attention to cranks.
Because they're the kind of woman who comes with a crate.
Oh.
I feel more at home wrapped up with pretty ribbons.
It's rather daring for me.
But if it pleases you, that's all that matters.
Oh, talk about that later.
Oh, no.
Hey, Philo, can you squeeze the juice out of this thing right here?
Yeah, here, let me bend over.
Bend over, okay.
Boys, boys, boys.
Your youthful pranks will be the death of you.
It looks like tapioca.
It was supposed to be tap water.
Now I think it's time to tap into a different stream.
It's lunk.
It's, yeah, just some lunk.
It's the gradu covered drain at the bottom of the shower.
If you put your bare feet there, you'll be dead in an hour.
You put your bare feet in the lunk?
Right here?
Hello?
Is there a relation between gradu and sludge?
Oh, yeah.
Is sludge strictly like the antithesis of silence?
Speak not to me of sludge.
I only got like 30 seconds.
30 seconds to...
Are you familiar with the colloquial euphemism moss-headed lunker?
Of course.
That's my favorite fish.
Yeah, the old moss-headed lunker at the bottom of the pond.
That's the biggest fish in the pond.
Why, that's the one they make the ghost meat fish out of.
Yeah, the old moss-headed lunker is a mighty fancy.
Fish meat.
But he's hard to catch.
Because when he sees you coming, he burrows down into the mud.
Where's that lunker sound coming from?
It looks just like a hill of mud.
Yeah, but I use a yo-yo for me.
Yo, yo, I'm trying to talk to you about that old moss-headed lunker down there at the bottom
of the pond.
Let's just clear the air.
So friendly.
He's your best friend.
He likes you.
In the nice, deep water.
Drifting silence of the pond.
Lunker fish.
Scrape this.
Scrape it.
You scrape him.
Beams of light come down through the water.
Scrape him so fast.
Scrape him good.
You rub him between two sticks until the fish actually catches on fire.
Claw dad goes by.
And cooks itself.
Friendly crocodile.
Right.
You have to rub him really fast.
Unfortunately, this same idyllic pond also harbors toxic slugs.
And red tide.
Here he goes again.
Because everything you say on the radio comes straight out of my nose.
Once free, get on your feet.
My head just said slugs.
But everything smells like feet.
It's all over.
All over in Central California filled up with slugs.
They'll give you a hideous disease.
Oh!
That's no way to treat the show.
That's not right.
Don't swing that lunk like that.
Steam clean.
Now that's the bucket of lunk, not the bucket of anal fissure tissue.
Tough bugs, man.
What is the type of that lunk head talking coming from?
The lunk head?
Yeah.
You must find a cop.
In the back of the car.
The lunk head.
Oh, I see.
Oh, it's the lunk heads in the other booth.
That's a beloved radio personality.
Art Lunkheader.
The ones that are shooting.
They're sending us obscene gestures.
At the speed of light.
Gang signs, man.
And it's competitive, man.
It's competitive obscene gestures.
It's highly compressed video signal coming through.
Well, he's got his obscene gesture embedded with riding instruments.
That's why they took Art Lunkheader off the air back in 1689.
Oh, wow.
Hock up a lunger there.
His daughter was a tragic lunk head, wasn't she, Diane Lunkheader?
Yes, she was a pole dancer who plummeted to oblivion after a series of failed fessings.
Now, do you think that lunker and lunger have the same root word origin?
Yeah, lung.
Well, then the root seller.
Oh, yeah.
Hey, you guys want to go out and share?
I say I'm some glam cop dancer tonight.
Don't throw the answers tonight.
Where do we go?
I'm a glam cop dancer.
I noticed their similarity.
I thought we just did that.
And their familiarity.
I thought we...
Don't go on the show.
Don't look in the basement.
All right, we're not on the show now.
Don't go in the...
We're hiding in the back room of the show.
Don't open the door.
Okay, bend down.
Get under that desk.
He knows you're on the way.
Let's get under that desk.
Shouldn't play with...
Don't call Palmer up right now and wake him up.
Don't slew any room.
Okay, now, Gary, you get back over there under that desk.
Whatever happened to me?
We're all under the desk together now.
Whatever happened to Palmer?
Okay, when the next caller shows up, we'll all jump out.
And surprise him.
Okay, okay.
Shh, shh, shh, shh.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Okay, okay, okay.
Shh, shh, shh, shh.
Here he comes.
Okay, here's the caller.
I'm going to reboot the Michael Pepe.
Ow!
Hey, no, Michael Pepe, not me.
848-4425.
That's not the caller.
Okay, gentlemen, this is the cusp of a historic occasion.
Okay, here we go.
Let us set our teeth and march forward.
So the caller forgot that that was their cue.
Yeah, caller, you failed us.
You failed us once again.
You failed your country, your nation, and your God.
You know, this would be a great show up.
But one for all these really poor callers that we get.
This I've got to hear.
Stoner, stoner, stoner, stoner, stoner, stoner, stoner, stoner, stoner, stoner, stoner, stoner,
stoner, stoner, stoner, stoner, stoner, stoner, stoner, stoner, stoner, stoner.
Cool.
That is as it should be.
I was drunk.
We're selling a different drug, baby.
Exactly.
It's a healthy drug.
Yeah.
Slag.
With Bob.
With Bob, you don't need a lighter.
Nope.
You don't need a fancy glass.
You don't need a pipe.
No, sir.
With Bob?
Well, actually, you do need a pipe.
And a lighter, I guess.
You definitely need a pipe.
And, of course, a lighter.
You don't want to be totally lean.
Yeah, I guess you do need a lighter.
But it can't be a bubble pipe.
And it's not actually that healthy.
A pipe made out of chocolate, maybe?
It's not actually really healthy.
And you can't say it's not a habit for him, either.
But it's an alternative.
It's an alternative pipe, baby.
You can get really out there on Bob.
Never, ever come down.
But, friends, I'm Bob.
And, friends, don't use Bob as a crutch.
This isn't the crutch of the subgenius.
You let him use you as a crutch.
Let Bob lean on you.
Possibly financially.
It's the greatest thing a person can do is to fund Bob's great adventure.
Let Bob...
You be Bob's crutch.
And, friend, if you really...
If you really want to be Bob's crutch, you can be Bob's crutch.
If you really want to get into Bob, want to know what's inside his head, let Bob smoke.
Friends, really, I mean, you can throw yourself into that pipe.
And then maybe you'll be the molecule that goes into his brain and gives him that next
great idea.
Now, just recently, somebody on alt-slack, a subgenius forum, was talking about this.
And they were saying, what is Bob smoking in that pipe?
Is that marijuana?
I'll bet it is.
420.
Well, actually, friends, what's inside Bob's pipe is the same thing that's inside Bob's
head.
As New Monet put it, what's inside Bob's head...
I have to read this, because this is a new revelation.
Some of you old timers haven't heard this.
What's in Bob's pipe and inside his head is the multiverse, the antiverse.
The diviverse, the negaverse, the demiverse, the klasiverse, the periverse, the division-by-zeroverse,
the square root of negative one verse, the averse, the roboverse, the hitlerverse, the
nocverse, the gayverse, the pooverse, perverse, the quantumverses, the hootervearse, the claymationverse,
the monsterverse, antivirus.
hyperspace, hypospace, overspace, underspace, throughspace, wormholes, beetleholes, blackholes,
buttholes, blackwhores, patrizemi, verschluggener, and trace amounts of halva.
And also the Alamo.
Yes, the Alamo is inside Bob's head.
Bob?
By gobs, that man is crazy. Are you Mangy Old Scorpion? By gobs.
The subgenius power of SWAT.
Uh oh, what happened?
We got super dead air.
Hey, pause! Dead air!
This past 10 minutes of dead air has been brought to you by the First Church and the Last Laugh,
the world's fastest growing snack religion, 150% less dogma, it's a light religion.
One holy day year today, isn't it? But April 1st will be the 30th annual St. Stupid's Day parade.
So get ready for it, and we'll see you at the Embarcadero Plaza, Monday, April 1st at noon.
And now back to our regularly scheduled program.
Dead air is really not dead. It has things in it.
Living things are not actually dead things.
Is this the bathroom?
This is the bathroom.
Ten minutes of complete silence.
In honor of silence from which all sound comes from, we have to give homage to that silence.
I can't believe that.
Just like giving homage to that stupidity.
How about Philip Glass and his famous silent song?
The multi-talking guy show.
Just a cascade of voices.
Finally, there's going to be a girl on the show.
Bop, bop.
A tower for hell Nazis.
Yeah, a tower. It could be a tower for some.
For others, it's just an opposite end of the question.
If only the hell Nazis would stay in their tower.
But no, they have to leave and come out and afflict the rest of us.
And their telephone networks like nothing you've ever seen.
That way, that telephone networks is phenomenal, if not criminal.
Telephone networks.
Yeah, telephone networks every time.
The net covers essentially everyone.
So are you saying that the show actually had a silent part?
Asylum from what?
The point was there was no sound coming out of the speakers.
But the First Church of the Last Left bought that silence.
We paid for that silence.
Thank you. Thank you.
The payment for a silent part.
Was there a sound or was it like...
It was a sound or unsound mind.
It's available. This silence is for rent.
I mean, you can plug in anything you want.
You can put signage in there.
Once we get it on tape, one of Doug's cassette tapes, it goes on there.
Yeah, one tape.
Could we mix some of the silence in with the show that's going on now?
We could divvy it up. Everybody could take some home with them.
Can we use an 8-track tape?
No, I mean, can we use it right now?
That's a good idea. Squirt some of that silence in there.
...will set the Mormon Church over all America and over all the world, for it is written in...
Written anymore.
That was the silence part.
That was good. That was good.
That was kind of an acoustic hook for the Michael Peppery.
That's just a test, right? A test of the silent radio network.
This has just been a test.
You would have heard the following message.
Michael Peppery's stakeout.
The sounds that you did hear were very unimpressive.
...if I dare you to talk to us.
What's there to be afraid of?
Oh, you know what? I forgot about this.
A guy from Ontario emailed KPFA and said,
I listen to the show all the time, I like the show, but the guy says the number too fast.
And I can never call up.
Well, in that case, you...
Listener censored radio.
Oh, bro.
And one of the general managers of the show sent, shot me the email and...
All right, let's give out that number.
One of the general managers. Have you ever noticed in this station how this...
We have more general managers than employees.
You know how many colonel managers there are? 16.
And there's like 24 generals, 16 colonels.
And it's all I can do to manage my privates.
And then there's just us privates.
580 of us little private managers.
I got my privates...
Managed.
...hidden. Hidden away.
And it's about time. Nobody wants to see it, believe me.
No, I don't even want to see it.
Too late.
Well, here, pick this. Pick on this...
Why are you giving me this magnifying glass?
Well, you know, it's all relative. It depends on where you stand.
Rob. Rob.
New or
Plagued.
Cold.
You're so happy you could die
And at the same time terrified
So much distraction, you're confused
You end up laughing at the truth
Stupid is cool
You sit in front of your TV
At least there's something to believe
That's taking time bomb on command
You do the goose step on demand
Stupid is cool
You're so cool
You wanna be all you can be
You are so eager to agree
That slogan's on the line
And it's mirror how you feel
The lowest passions are ideals
Stupid is cool
You're so cool
You're so cool You're so cool
You're so cool, you're so cool, you're so cool, you're so cool, you're so cool, you're
so cool, you're so cool, you're so cool.
Stupid is Cool from the video by Mutate Now.
And what a great old new cult that is, friends.
You can see that video with links at sickvideo.com or Mutate Now on YouTube or MySpace.
And before that, friends, we heard some puzzling evidence with Dr. Philodrumon, Dr. Howe, Bishop
Choey, Michael Pepe, and puzzling evidence and yours truly and other people, and Leemur,
and Norell, Preff, and some ranting from the Baltimore Devival by yours truly, Reverend
Ivan Stang.
And now back to Berkshire.
Dr. Hal and I got in trouble on John Sinclair's radio show for talking of extra meditation.
Yeah, yeah, he didn't think that was cool.
Oh, did we do that?
This was the guy with the MC5, dude.
The guy John Lennon wrote a song about.
And he said extra meditation was, and it was on Radio Free Amsterdam.
But were we free to discuss the right of extra meditation?
No.
The right to extra meditation and the right of it.
It's an inane.
Nay.
Nay, on radio.
It's not Radio Free Amsterdam.
It must be Radio Anti-Bob Amsterdam.
Well, it certainly wasn't our show.
Don't forget our God-given right to pyroflatulation.
Well, now, Philo, you've got to go in steps.
You can't.
You can't expect the people to be that liberal.
Yeah, they're still putting water on their...
You must move by income.
They're like dripping water or walking through the water.
They're waterboarding us.
Here's Reverend Stang.
Oh, man.
My pleasure.
This is my colleague, Dr. Hal.
Dr. Hal Robbins from San Francisco.
These two guys will be coming in to do some time on the radio show during the college on Tuesday.
I hope so.
Looking forward to it.
And they actually both have been involved in radio broadcasts for the last 25 years, I'm afraid.
Yeah, I get it.
East Coast, West Coast.
So we'll come wandering by at some point, I guess, probably Tuesday.
Yeah.
Whenever you feel free.
Great.
That's hard to do, actually.
Reverend Stang.
That's me, Price Bob.
Father, am I correct?
No, actually, I'm just one of the head clerks.
Yeah, J.R. Bob Dobbs is the high E-pop and guru.
He's that smiling, be-piped face that you see.
Bob.
Yeah.
We call it the Dobbs head.
The Dobbs.
Yes, my colleague here is Dr. Hal Robbins.
Dr. Hal.
Master of church secrets from San Francisco.
I do a very fine doctor myself.
Well, I'm envious at how well you do.
What a great job.
There's no envious side of everybody.
No, one of the seven deadly sins.
The seven affronts.
Well, you know, we came to Amsterdam to preach Bob's word of slack,
but we found that we were preaching to the saved.
Everybody here already has slack.
Bob's like pure white.
Right, so our job is done.
We're just relaxing now.
That's why we're going to preach to the Holy Joseph.
The Joseph, Daddy of Jesus, is a highly placed reverend in the church.
Actually, he's more like what we would call a saint.
A saint?
Yeah, he's a saint.
God damn, I thought he was a saint.
Yeah.
I'm a saint.
Well, wasn't one of the popes of Europe in here earlier, Pope Black?
Pope Black, yeah, he was on our show.
He is a provisional.
Provisionary pope.
Right, currently a little Spanish dog that lives in Germany has more authority,
more papal authority than Pope Black.
What about the papal bull?
We've got a ton of that.
We've got a load of papal bull.
In fact, you've got to watch where you step in Dobstown.
Yes.
Well, wherever you smell that bull, look around and you'll find Bob nearby.
Or at least one of his menace.
Well, it's a lot of, theottle's shoulders would smell like that
Orinella won't những and don't speak like Bob like anyone else.
Yeah, I'll say I've seen a lot of the papal bull as the Priests.
I had them最初 charted into aviation club Judas Rebels of our church in my family in Jerusalem.
Two years ago.
I was talking to the priest Paul Finley.
And we hung out at the Cannabis Cup Expo for a little while.
I had never been to one of those before,
and I was gratified to see that it was just like I expected.
Yeah, yeah, just like the picture.
Yeah.
You will thirst for slack, and you must receive slack.
Right, the subgenius must have slack.
That doesn't mean that you must go out and get slack.
That means you must already have had it in order to even be a subgenius.
It may be misplaced, or maybe you haven't appreciated the slack that you already had.
Some people, it takes them a while to learn.
The slack lies in the simple things oftentimes, like extra meditation, a daily act.
That's a sacred rite.
The silence of the extra meditation chamber.
Anyway, no one would interrupt anyone during that.
That's a particular solemn morning rite.
Yes, that's true.
Bob?
You're a part of every boy and girl's body, right?
Yes, yes, the doctor took me out.
Bone.
Tuck, tuck, tuck.
Right at the beginning of your large butt.
Okay.
Well, I look like a narrow, pinkish-gray tube.
How big or small are you?
I'm a half inch wide and two inches long.
Yes, yes, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
That's right.
Right, Bob.
Bob.
Doctor, since I was a very useful organ, I have no real purpose.
I see.
Bob.
Scientist, Bob.
Scientist, scientist.
Bob, Bob.
Over and over and over again.
Hey, that's right.
Once the boys and girls get into my body again.
Oh, definitely, Uncle Bob.
Bob, Bob.
Mother.
Asshole.
You mean nowhere.
It's waste.
Correct.
Bob, Bob.
Zuper duper.
That was noralpref.com.
And more torture now.
On Puzzling Evidence.
They're waterboarding us.
Well, it's because I say waterboard the crap out of them.
The little Dutch boy took his finger out of the dike and has gone to a coffee shop.
He's at the dump cream.
That's sampling the place of love.
That's the newest fad.
People are waterboarding themselves.
I'm going to waterboard the dike.
You know that story.
Every schoolboy knows that tale.
It's a bummer.
I'm going to waterboard that little falls.
Do schoolboys still know the tale?
That's a little.
Little Dutch boy.
I'm going to waterboard Tilton Park.
I'm not sure that it's valuable for them to learn that lesson except as part of cultural studies.
Because, in fact, the story is completely bogus and not even Dutch in origin.
And there was no waterboard?
There was no dike, no finger, no little Dutch kid.
Oh, yeah.
What do you call this?
No airplane.
It was, in fact, made up by an American.
Still, so many people think it's happened that even the Dutch government can't react against it.
So, there's been.
A cover-up.
They've erected a statue of the little Dutch boy and so forth.
Another cover-up.
It's bogus.
That's because people expect to see it.
Well, I knew it was bogus, but I thought that it was Dutch.
No, you're going to tell me that the Dutch boy paint.
Dutch boy paint's logo is bogus, too, right?
Oh, it's really painted on there.
Well, if that's bogus, then what about Bob Dobbs?
What about the whole church of the sub-church?
What about Sherwin-Levitt?
That's a little Dutch boy.
He's alive.
Calm down.
Couldn't Bob be alive?
Gentlemen.
Order.
William's paint, it doesn't cover the world.
What a comedy.
I thought it covered the world.
Oh, that cannot be.
I do not want to live in a world where there is no Bob Dobbs.
I thought we were in a world covered by paint.
I'm going to explain the problem.
I saw the logo.
I'm having a crisis.
For Bob is to be praised.
Praise Bob.
The facts surrounding Bob are incontrovertible.
There is no doubt of the existence of Bob or his stories in this world.
But other religions.
Are highly felt.
And their premises can be examined.
Praise his sweet name.
They are going to be silenced.
Right this far.
Bob is fire.
Bob is ice.
Bob does not have body life.
This guy is doing the real show.
Praise God.
He's doing the Bob show.
We don't have to do anything.
We can just relax.
He's been doing it quietly in his room all over the years.
That's like an ancient Glass Madness song from the 19...
Me too.
Yes, he's quoting the classics.
I just spoke to that fellow three days ago.
Just me.
Yes, all these Johnny come late nights.
I'm going to have to go to the bathroom.
Can I?
This capi lovers.
Goodbye.
Bye boxing.
Go making a gro testified postエним you'll see reduce the number of children staying
All alone.
I apply partly to a single loved attire.
I am sorry.
Glass Madness did that, and now Dr. Howell in Amsterdam,
ranting at the Akhnaton subgenius devival.
Of course, fellow lotus eaters and traversers of Demimonde,
it's great to smoke all this marijuana,
and frock is one of the many hundreds of synonyms for marijuana.
But frock in subgenius theology classically means a special herb known as Hapifroxipulops,
frock for short, which only grows on the selected droppings of certain Tibetan holy men
in that country's mysterious mountain fastness.
But metaphorically, we call cannabis and sensimia frock also,
because it certainly has some of the same effects, providing slack on the man.
Oh, remember, slack is not tension, slack is leisure,
and only in leisure can anything worthwhile be created.
But false slack? You may think you want to conspiracy these products.
They will dangle before you every latest glittering tchotchke,
every iPod, Palm Pilot, and so forth.
I say, if thy iPod of empty, pluck it out,
because you will find that the moment you have this object of your desire,
it will fail to satisfy, and instead, your thirst, your lust,
will be transferred to the next expensive item,
which in all probability will be manufactured by the phone company,
which history will show will be the greatest instrument of tyranny ever leveraged
against the weak flesh and spirit of a faltering humankind.
It makes me hungry.
Here comes that big silence.
First church in the last lap is going to buy another chunk of silence.
No, puzzling evidence has left his post.
Very true.
The show is...
It's careening out of control.
The show's out of control.
There's no driver.
Dead air everywhere.
Lean this way.
No, lean this way.
Normally, you see, friends, puzzling evidence conducts the show like a master conductor.
All of this, what sounds to you like chaos,
is actually carefully planned and controlled by puzzling evidence.
But Bishop Joey is right.
Control board.
We can lean on this side of the show,
and then we can run over to that side of the show real quick and make the show turn.
Yeah.
All right, now back to the way.
Yeah, back to the way.
Yeah.
Oh, the show is careening again.
Oh, God, this is making me sick.
Come on, call it.
Get aboard.
Yeah, this is what we were talking about earlier.
This is where the nausea action sets in.
What's that?
Chunky stuff on the floor?
Sick.
Caller.
You're on the show, and you have to leave early and go home.
Oh, I was hoping it was a camera.
You wish you could stay, but you're nauseous.
Oh, God, if I'm...
It's either you're going to hurl...
I could use a plate of ambergris right now.
You're going to hurl, or you're going to...
Steam and heap and take.
Listen, do the...
Okay, nobody go to that side of the show.
Okay, don't go to that.
If you go to that side, there's like a puddle of something that you might step in.
Filo butter, if you ask me.
Don't step in that in your good shoes, people.
Okay, puzzling is back.
Don't tell anybody on this seat.
Pretend we're not here.
Everybody start talking.
Is it okay?
Do you want to hear a praise ball?
Praise ball!
I can hear you.
Hallelujah, amen.
Now, brothers and sisters,
tonight's sermon is going to be a very short one.
But a very clear one.
Because there are two things I'm going to preach about tonight.
And that's slack and work.
Now, how many of you out there have a job and actually have to work for a living?
Come on, put your hands up.
How many of you got to work?
Now, the conspiracy invented work billions of years ago.
Before man had to work, we lived in a bonobo-like paradise.
Where drugs grew on trees like berries.
And bubbly brooks frothed from the ground with the best beer and wine.
And no one had to work.
And no one needed food or drink or had to pay for a thing.
And the only thing you wanted when you wanted to have sex was ask.
This was the cornucopia paradise that we once lived in.
Until they came along and invented work and money.
And then they took this money.
Which is actually a slave token.
And they created work so you could earn these slave tokens.
To buy things that they made to sell to each one of you.
That used to be free.
They made conspiracy food.
Conspiracy drugs.
That not only make you sick.
But used to be free.
Conspiracy beer and wine and whiskey used to bubble up from the ground.
And you could drink it.
And not even get a hangover.
But now not only do you get a hangover.
You have to pay for it.
With the slave tokens you earn.
Yes my friends.
Tonight I'm going to perform a holy ritual.
That will cure each and every one of you of work.
Yes my friends.
Some churches heal you of work.
Some churches heal you of what pains you.
But tonight I am going to sicken each and every one of you.
So you are too sick to go to work tomorrow.
Do I hear a praise bomb?
By the powers vested in me.
And J.R. Bob Dobbs.
And the Church of the Subgenius.
With my title as Pokeball Europe.
I hereby sicken each and every one of you.
And command you not to go to work tomorrow.
And to lay in bed with a hangover.
And to never ever ever ever work again for these slave tokens.
Do I hear a praise bomb?
Amen.
Hallelujah.
But now without further ado.
You shall rise up.
And find Bob.
And join the Church of the Subgenius.
And join the army of freaks.
The freaks and hippies.
And heavy metal heads.
And goths.
And weirdos.
And we shall rise up.
And be an army against their football coaches.
And lawyers.
We shall be a bulwark against their bullshit.
Do I hear a praise bomb?
Amen.
AŤIăIc¤ oħ.
That testing horizon a çeţcə
I thought we'd go back to the old-fashioned way.
And this revival with a wedding.
A sacred, subgenius wedding.
Now, we're going to wear this beautiful, well, this coat.
Poe Black and Poe Pesonina.
But, you know, and it's a big but.
In this church, we can marry you to anything you want to marry.
So if you want to come up and be part of this too, you're welcome to.
If you have a boyfriend, girlfriend, same-sex, animal, your wallet, your car keys, anything.
The beer in your hand.
Whatever else is in your hand.
Come on up.
But for now, Poe Black and Poe Pesonina, step forward, please.
Step right up.
To get your holy short-duration marriage right here, test your mettle and win.
The little lady.
A snooping dog.
No, we're not moving it up here with me.
You're down there.
I'm up there.
I'm the holy man.
I'm up here on this ascended level.
Also, I can see you better down there.
And she's really cute.
She's going to be married.
Oh, shut up.
Oh, yes, beloved friends, boyars, jealous associates, and any hidden cameras.
Do you.
Poe Black, in certain name here, swear to tell the truth, the whole truth and nothing but the truth.
Say yes.
Yes.
Same with you.
Say yes.
Yes.
And how long shall this period of sanctified coupling last?
Normally, it's 24 hours, but I think in this case, it is 24 eternities of pure, raging sex hurt.
Yes.
Yes, baby.
I don't want you to make a mockery of this sacred ceremony.
I want you to sanctify it and make it real and hard.
I want you to go home and go back to that hotel room, that sleazy, fly-ridden, fly-bit hotel room with the vibrating bed.
And I want you to fuck, baby.
I want you to fuck and fuck and fuck and fuck and fuck as if your very life depended on it.
Because it does.
So, yes, it does.
So, we are gathered here together in the presence of J.R. Bob Dobbs, Connie Dobbs, whatever form or other deities, Jesus, whatnot,
to join this man and this woman, and thank God it's a man and a woman this time,
in a temporary but no less virtuous bondage of holy matrimony, for better or for worse, and this time forever.
Forever.
You're going to hear that again in hell.
Do you feel a spirit?
Put your hands on each other and say, praise Bob!
Praise Bob!
Now, this is a bond of sub-holy wedlock.
So, no matter what physical position these two may take in the next eternity, their moral standing shall be upright.
Woo!
Take this woman, Nina, to be your lawful wedded wife.
In short duration, subgenius matrimony.
To have and to hold.
To do damn near anything you want to do with.
For sickness or in sickness or in kinkiness.
In rich or poor.
Through any hardship or disaster that may befall her in the next eternity.
For whatever sick and twisted but knowest blessed reasons.
For the next 10,000 years.
Say, I do!
Hell yeah, I do!
Do you, Nina!
Do you poor, sad, deluded creature.
Agree to take on the horrible job of looking after this giant-sized infant.
This huge 35-year-old baby.
To diaper him and feed him and put up with his insane bullshit.
For God's sake!
For worse than rich or poor and sickness and kinkiness.
Say, I do!
I do!
Praise God, she said, I do, the poor thing.
Now, shake on it and say, it's a deal!
There you go.
Oh, look, it's a hand fasting.
Like the ancient pagan traditions.
The Pope, like, is hand fasting himself through Pocostina.
With, uh, packaging tape.
It's true!
Now, get on the ring and put the ring on.
Now, like, you know, that's...
Friends, if you're joining in by television or webcam, if you don't have a special ring,
you can make a wedding ring with the...
We call it the sacred temple of Devoe.
Just form the hole and the pole and thrust the pole deep into the hole repeatedly.
There you go.
That's so romantic.
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
We take this ring as a symbol of the Holy Spirit.
The Holy State of Marriage and wedlock is real as fuck.
So, by the authority invested in me by Jehovah God, God, the law, and everything else in
defiance of the laws of nature, I now pronounce you man and wife.
You must now kiss each other, groan each other, clutch and feel up each other, fall on the
floor and rip it.
Well, whatever is within.
And don't break my tripod while you're doing this.
And don't do that, if I poke black now.
Damn, this love stuff is always expensive.
Ashes to ashes, dust to dust.
It is done.
A man and a woman, praise Bob.
Praise Bob.
And so, folks, all I have to say is give our books and pamphlets a chance.
Especially Revelation X, the Bob Apocrypha.
That is the second in a planned series of books which will march through the decades.
But we'll have more of them.
until finally they are all out and before the eyes of the world.
And when they are, and when the selected elect have read them,
then down will close the end of time.
And we will come to the ultimate terminal where everything is final and nothing is general.
Ask Dr. Howell, ranting there at the subgenius revival in Amsterdam, 2007.
More on Dr. Howell at askdrhowell.com.
That's A-S-K-D-R-H-A-L dot com.
And this is Hour of Slack number 1134.
You can learn more about the Church of the Subgenius and the Hour of Slack at subgenius.com.
The background music here is by Speed Cave of speedcave.com.
Praise Bob.
Meanwhile, we're broadcasting here on behalf of the Church of the Subgenius
because the time is running out.
Our world grinds to its end in its last agonized moments.
We hope you've made up your mind about whether or not to embrace the doctrine of J.R. Bob Dobbs
and grasp at it as a drowning person grasps at a straw,
although a straw is really not useful at this time.
Now I'm going to turn you back to Ivan saying,
remember, subgenius principles can easily be understood.
Just look at Bob's face.
This is a face-based business and a business-based religion, friends.
So now in the name of J.R. Bob Dobbs, I want to pass a benediction on to you.
May all your moments be filled with slack, however you define it.
And may all of your thoughts be completely devoted to the thoughts and patterns of the face of J.R. Bob Dobbs.
Praise Bob.
Let there be slack.