And now, the subgenius hour of slack.
Slack.
Slacks.
Make a cool radio.
When I put them on, I'm ready to go.
Man, you ought to see me with my derby on.
I know that you would say he's gone.
Slacks.
Mostly in the head.
Well, that's what I said.
Slacks.
I'm the cat's pajama.
Cause I run around with crazy little mama.
Slacks now.
Well, the girls all look when I go by.
Slacks.
I wear red bow tie.
They say me old mom slacks with a cat chained down to my knees.
I ain't nothing but a real coo-coo-free slacks.
Slacks.
Brrrr.
Brr.
Slacks.
Make a cool radio.
When I put them on, I'm ready to go.
Slacks.
Brrrr.
Ah, joe.
суu.
And the sparkle tones, friends.
Well, tonight we're going back to 5X Day for the last time.
But it's an X-rated visit to that day of excuses.
This will be one of those hours of slack that falls off of the radar of the normals.
This will only be presented on the internet.
So we're free to cuss, cuss, cuss.
Actually, these are tapes from 5X Day.
And other places that they were too raunchy to use at all.
Even if I bleeped all the fucks and shits out of it, there wouldn't be anything left.
Anyway, friends, let's go back.
Back in time, not that far, to 7 o'clock in the morning, July 5th.
As the subgeniuses await the aliens on the morning of the beginning of the end of the world
that never really got started.
I got one thing to say, and it won't take long.
But Bob Dobbs done been here, took a good shit, and gone.
We're once again.
We're here.
We're Bob.
Maybe we are supposed to build our own shit, Bob.
Maybe the disbeliever's right, Bob.
Maybe we're the fucking...
Huh?
Oh, well.
Yeah.
That's a pretty good...
You know, that's not a bad slogan for this year.
Just it's simple, it's short.
Or next year, actually, I guess.
But Bob, Connie's coming.
That's a bad one.
Yeah, that's okay.
Hey, it's 7 in the morning, man.
Oh, you're a yeti, you can dig it.
Hey.
Hey, it's 7 in the morning.
Hey, hey, hey!
10 in the morning, the first movie of the year!
And it's so easy to fix.
It helps with yourumbs, it does help with genes and everything.
We're going out there, we're going online, is it time to film?
We are the best, Bob.
We're a heavenly High School actress!
Let's go.
Yeah, thank you, Bob.
I was playing with kids.
I couldn't pick a number, let's 600,000, no?
Now, because of COVID-19, I can't go to school everyday,
and three days in a row, I just have to tbsp this job which is really tough.
Girl, I love this kind of stuff.
domestic deviation, Connie is our inspiration, a lovely leader in fighting love, sister Connie
do we trust, to find domestic deviation, Connie is our inspiration, a lovely leader in fighting
love, sister Connie do we trust, sister Connie, sister Connie, sister Connie, sister Connie,
find domestic deviation, Connie is our inspiration, a lovely leader in fighting love, sister Connie
Sister Connie, do you trust your domestic deviation?
Connie is our inspiration,
a lovely leader in sighting lust.
And Sister Connie, do you trust?
Sister Connie, Sister Connie.
A Saint Inn, dear friends.
A Saint Inn in Helena Handbasket at 5X Day.
And now back to the disappointed Saint.
The subgenius UFO cultists, whose UFOs again didn't show up at 7 o'clock in the morning.
Although we did.
I gotta find a church that gets up later.
It'd be surprising if you picked something like 8.08 AM.
Yeah, 8.08 or 4.20.
Or how about 13.13.
Or 11.11.
You know, here we are trying to second guess J.R. Bob Dobbs,
the dumbest,
the dumbest creature in the universe, yet luckiest.
And trying to second guess the exes that are probably so advanced we can't understand them.
Or so simple we can't understand them.
See, there you are trying to second guess people who don't use logic or rationality at all.
That's why my own irrational theory has to be...
The good news is there'll be an X Day 6.
Oh yeah, I guess so.
I'm going back to my motel.
I got a...
I got a good one.
I'm wearing these pajamas and I camped right next to this pavilion for real good reason.
I'm gonna take advantage of that.
I'm gonna go have my continental breakfast and catch up on my sleep here.
Yeah.
I think you're right, Mr. Seastead.
Damn.
Well, it wouldn't be the first religion that shit on me.
But at least with the other ones, there was that hope thing.
Oh.
Yeah, well, that was for the dumbasses.
This fails consistently.
Yeah.
You always get your fucking...
Fucked by Bob.
I think that's going to be the topic of a rant if I sell a voice later.
Fucked again.
Yeah, I was starting to lose my voice this afternoon.
I was doing my Chris Lee...
Well, now you ought to see my faith voice held.
Now you still have a faith that was trying not to sit on, too.
If you came back for this year, you'll never stop coming to this.
Never stop coming?
Never stop coming.
To Brushwood.
Oh.
You always have a big butt, Stang.
Whoops.
Well, of course, what would I do without it?
Going to Dobbs Town?
Are you guys going to the town?
Are you going to go light up some citizens and piss them out?
We already did that, but you pissed on the mansions.
Thank you, Reverend Susie the Floozy, who came to 5X Day all the way from WREK in Atlanta, Georgia.
You know, folks, many subgenius radio folks lived to try to...
to report on their oft-times sordid X-Day drill experiences.
What about this European revival I was reading something about?
I heard something about...
I read something about actual male fist effing...
Homosexual male fisting.
The kind of psychosexual...
The kind of gravy you want covered all over your handshake.
Someone's already getting it, so...
Yeah, the London X-Day...
Oh, that was sick.
Actually had more people show up.
We had about 200 at Brushwood.
They had 250 in London, but it was indoors, and they didn't have to pay nearly as much.
And there was, in fact, probably smellier displays of...
Yikes.
Dharma?
Discussing...
Sexual dharma.
Holy mackerel, Andy.
It can't get any smellier than two meerkats having a...
Pleasuring themselves.
They did allow cameras.
The Italian subgenius told me...
Reverend Slita told me that he was going to post some,
but he was going to censor the hidden arm...
The hidden forearm pictures.
Oh, my God.
Well, we don't even need to think of that to know what it means.
Wow.
I mean, somebody was actually hiding their forearm in a fold of human waste.
You were talking about...
No, but it's monkey...
There are monkeys that wouldn't do stuff that subgenius humans...
No, monkeys will not do that.
Monkeys will not...
They refuse.
I don't think you've ever...
It's not in the contract.
It's not approved.
Recorded of a monkey dipping his fist in a bucket of lube.
No, it has not been done, at least in this century.
There were perverted monkeys in the old days,
back when they tainted the water with, well, you know, with the oxide.
And this really...
Well, what else happened if that happened?
Another thing that happened was they went out to Avonbury...
Man, we can't even compete with that.
Avonbury.
Avonbury Avenue.
A giant old monument like Stonehenge...
Oh, Avonbury.
...upon which at 7 in the morning on July 5th,
Papa Joe Mama launched a bleeding head of Arnold Palmer
at the Avonbury Mounds, the ancient Stonehenge-like mounds.
And the mists...
Was it on Solstice Day?
...were gone at 7 a.m.
And they...
Oh, oh, oh.
Apparently, they said, if I...
The line of the morning was,
if I cannot bang my head against the rock,
the rock will bang.
...itself against my head.
And I guess they all ended up with the rock...
See, now...
...the giant ancient rocks banging them on the heads
as the exodus failed to arrive.
Well, it sounds like a real moment of epiphany for some folks.
They're more into drinking over there
as opposed to the...
Well, yeah.
The meditative approach that the American subgeniuses do,
the sticking the sand...
...to pay for cactuses up their legs at wounds and so forth.
Well, you know, the thing is, I saw many weapons at X-Day.
And now assume the correct lotus position.
I saw M-16s and M-5s.
Yeah, it was kind of weird seeing all that.
It was weird.
A complete electromorphified vaporizer,
which vaporized many people.
Brain cells.
It was a brain cell vaporizer, but it didn't hurt your lungs.
Your lungs were fine.
And your snapback...
Your brain cells would be...
...coded...
Instant.
...with this drippy, sticky, green, skunkish, horrible...
And this guy just walked around like a ghostbuster,
just blasting people with this vaporizer...
...all week long.
And everybody in his path was just mumbling idiots.
Yeah, but healthy lungs.
Because the brain was not cleared for cannubial darkening.
That guy was...
Healthy lungs.
Yeah, that was a Mr. Troll.
They were breathing well.
The breathing was no problem, but there was a glaze over the eye.
Over the eye.
The one eye, of course.
The other eye.
The other eye wandered freely.
But that's why we had so many casualties by the pit.
The third eye.
The red eye, baby.
Oh, the third eye left many, many, many...
That's where the English side took the red eye flag.
You are one magnificent hunk of man-meat.
Fuck me hard.
No.
What knockers.
Oh.
Thank you, doctor.
So many things you want to say, but can't.
So many anthropological observations.
And close hands.
Primate behavior.
I am the Carl Sagan of rock and roll, you know.
Well, you've been among these creatures long enough observing them that they don't even behave differently when you're around.
Right.
And rock and roll is just black slang for sex.
So is John.
I am the Carl Sagan of...
Of prof rock and roll.
Of sex.
Yeah.
Sex.
The old in and out.
The Carl Sagan of sex.
Well...
Boo-shaka-vaka-vaka.
Well, not really, but...
Yeah, I guess I would be.
Boo.
I'm more the Mestopheles of a bad bowel movement.
You know, Carl is a total stoner.
You keep telling yourself about how you're a sexual scientist, Chaz, and tell the doctor that, and...
Yeah.
I'm a sexist.
That's all.
Isn't it all science, Chaz?
That's all it's about.
Tell the angry husbands that.
The firings of the scrote.
No.
Tell the illegitimate children.
The misfiring of the brain.
Well, no.
I'm a sexist.
I'm...
I've become the lonesome cowboy now.
Yeah.
I'm...
It's...
It's funny.
Buddy, when you start getting those pink notices from those misbegotten children that want your support, whether it be of an athletic nature or just a plain old church supper where you strangle them and maybe put their bodies below in the basement...
Yeah.
You know that you don't want to spread your spore any further than you have.
The mankind already, according...
Is depleted.
Its spermatozoa has been depleted.
Bob spread his spore all over the place.
Bob has come...
Has come to redeem us.
For RDP...
No.
Bob the drummer.
Yeah.
I think you had a problem with slack vampires, man.
Oh, yeah.
That happens a lot.
You hear?
Slack vampires, like, they'll dig right into your carotid artery and just start sucking away.
Yeah.
They're everywhere.
In my...
The tainted things.
My aura of view...
In my aura of view, I was able to see these slack vampires that were, like, following you around.
...Coming to your chest and...
...Following you around.
...And want to save your blare.
Because you were, like, the man.
...The coolest band and the coolest pants and everything cool.
So the slack vampires, naturally, are, you know, they're going, oh, here's a little font of slack.
You gotta watch for them.
They're like...
...Slack fish.
They're like slack...
They're slack...
Slack blockers.
What do they call those fish that attach to sharks?
Piranhas.
Slam prays.
Oh, uh...
Yeah.
There's no...
Slam prays.
Slam prays are from Lake Erie.
Yeah.
They're extinct.
They're called, um, pilot fish that are on, um, sharks.
Pilot fish.
That's their name.
How could they be from Lake Erie if they're on sharks?
No.
Slam prays are, are on Lake Erie and they're all died off.
Or no, they killed everything.
The pilot fish are on sharks.
Those circular mouths with the, uh...
Yeah, yeah.
...the endless row of tiny shark teeth.
And what are bad chats?
They're sucking...
...are the ones that look like they're left to the swimmers.
They suck.
They suck majorly.
And on...
So you're...
And you're thinking they're going for your pelvic muscles.
...shark-like muscles.
And they'll suck in your brain suits.
...shark skin suit.
...suits.
And, uh...
And, yeah, you have to swim really fast and do a lot of things.
You gotta darting.
Oh, you gotta wear those frog flippers, man.
You gotta have like a hydro suit.
Sort of like the candira fish of South America which swims up your urethra.
It's such a narrow creature.
But a shark...
...we offer to all you rats a shaving towel into the river.
Because of this, a shark can never quite sleep.
You know, a shark cannot stop moving.
They have to keep moving to keep breathing.
That's right.
Well, even sharks get old and then calm down.
They only get rest when they go to the top of the ocean and then glide down slowly.
You can lay down, but you can't sleep.
It's hell back there.
Hey, what's another news story of why the fish are all washing up dead?
And when they do get down in their little shark bed...
I'm sorry. I just thought I'd remember it.
Well, there's another little, like, you know...
...uh, the little...
...crab kind of thing.
A giant snow crab sort of sleeping in their bed or...
...sucking the toes of another giant snow crab.
Oh, El Gordo and Princess Party Girl.
You can go ahead and talk about them. They don't listen to this show.
And they're too small to gobble up if you're a shark.
You know, you don't care about that.
That's just gonna get stuck in your teeth.
Chas...
Those are the ones you toss back.
I thought...
Well, that just gets stuck in your teeth and then that jams up in your gums and that's no good.
Then you lose another row of teeth and have to throw them back.
No, no, you're...
And then next thing you know, your snout is as flabby as a porpoise's ass.
It's a dumbass thing, friends. You would understand.
And, uh, so, uh, that's enough, I guess, of, uh, inspirational, uh...
Yeah, I don't have too much inspirational blabbering to do because, uh...
Uh, I just want to party.
Woo!
We do have, we do have some...
Rules.
Commitments. Rules.
Regulations.
Rules. Yes. Fuck them if they can't take a joke. That's the one rule you have to live by.
Also, you have to question authority.
Or else!
Oh, that's the guy part you're supposed to do. I'm supposed to do the or else part.
Go!
We've got a real program, Dan.
We've got...
I suppose we could start the auction. Here's a microbiology coloring book.
With a dead cow.
With a dead cow and anthrax bacillus on it.
It's...
You can color...
It's how to culture anthrax.
Huh?
The cover is How to Culture Anthrax.
Yay!
That's good.
A timely children's book.
Introduction to protozoa. Whoa.
Keep flipping!
Hey, man.
It gets better.
Protozoa.
That's a taliban of proof.
Yeah!
These guys don't even have bat bones on them.
Whoa!
They're little prairie squids.
Yeah, little tiny...
A little tiny, preemie prairie squid.
Underage.
Bob really doesn't want us to fuck them.
Just take out...
If they come home you'll look to a protozoa.
I'm gonna...
I'm gonna get an under...
An underage pro.
I'm gonna get an underage prairie squid and I'm not gonna use the big red straps.
I'm gonna use big green straps.
Pleasure.
The following order is to be carried out immediately.
Why don't you go outside and play hide and go fuck yourself?
When a person is insane...
Insane.
As you clearly are.
You are being irrational.
The match ignited a pocket of intestinal gas and flames shot out the tube.
You people are insane.
On dope?
Ha hear ha!
You ever seen a grown man naked in a cockpit before?
No sir!
Do you know that you're insane?
You just stop and go, wow!
It's amazing how fucking crazy I really am.
Go back to bed.
Oh, a little cut up by revbrovt, made out of pieces, things posted on alt.binaryslack,
uh, oh by the way this background music is by the original doctor slova.
for Bob.
Yes, yes, yes.
Something good, good, good
is coming up, friends,
as we now go back
to waiting through the end of the world.
Bob promised us 40 gigs and a mule.
Yes, 40 big fat acres.
He promised us blue balls,
frustration,
a making up of our own reality.
This guy's got a problem.
A determination to do it on ourselves.
Was it you, you scroungy little fuck, huh?
He does.
My goodness gracious.
That's the kind of people
that are running our military?
I'd hate to enjoin or conjoin
with any one of those soldados.
I'm asking the fucking questions here, private.
Do you understand?
Sir, yes, sir.
Well, thank you very much.
Can I be in charge for a while?
Sir, yes, sir.
Are you shook up?
Are you nervous?
Sir, I am, sir.
Do I make you nervous?
Sir, sir, what?
Are you about to call me an ass?
Asshole!
Sir, no, sir!
How tall are you, private?
Sir, five foot nine, sir!
Five foot nine?
I didn't know they stacked shit that high.
You trying to squeeze an inch in on me somewhere, huh?
Sir, no, sir!
Bullshit, it looks to me like the best part of you
ran down to crack your mama's ass
and ended up as a brown stain on the mattress.
I think you've been cheated.
Where in hell are you from anyway, private?
Sir, Texas, sir!
Holy dog shit, Texas.
Only steers and queers come from Texas, private cowboy.
And you don't much look like a steer to me,
so that kind of narrows it down.
That's me on Altbot Slack.
You've become either a raging bull or a raging...
No, I'm here.
I'm trying to whip these people into shape, man.
There you go.
Us old-timers are not going to be around forever,
and somebody has to be trained.
I think Legume and me showed how to whip people into shape.
We have to live by example.
Just ask Nicky.
Just ask...
Well, we'll just leave the other names out of it.
You know, don't you?
Dr. Legume got an award this week for best...
Well, not best, but worst influence.
Yeah?
Ex-fluence.
And that's what it all is, ex-fluvia, man.
We're talking people now.
I knew it.
You got an award, too, but I can't remember now what it was for.
Who was declaring the award?
Lost brain cell or something like that.
Lost brain cell.
Who was declaring the award?
The elder bankers.
Oh, the elders of bank?
The elder bankers?
Yeah, who live in Mount Shambalalalala.
La la la la la la la la la la.
Mount Shastakola.
Mount...
More than rhyming.
When we hit the floor, you'll find out what this song is for.
Go to hardcore and tell your soul, I'll find rapport with your control.
Encore, encore, just scream for more.
My technique, you will adore, and when well done, the toe fucks I will wore you out.
And then you toe fucks I will wore you out, but I won't say a word.
Rest assured, when you're sobered and realize what has occurred,
you had sex with a rhyming nerd.
You let loose your inner demons, still can feel your pussy semen in your eyes, there's still a...
gleaming on your chin, there's still some semen screaming,
creaming though you work my time.
Well, it's so damn weird.
What you got to do with pleasure drove me crazy, that's for sure.
But you don't want to be a slut and let folks know I busted a nut twice on your face,
once in your butt has literally looked like a glazed donut.
What's that got to do with Bob, you want to know?
Are you just lobbing lines about your lob?
You slob.
What's that got to do with Bob, you want to know?
Are you just lobbing lines about your knob?
You slob to mob the cops and get a job,
point and sling for all to see,
J.R.R. Martin's setting you free.
Whether you're cute or flat, ugly, don't matter if you're slow like me.
Take a tip and understand, this war might not go as you planned.
No excess will include plans, so I just take no brand new plans.
We stand the pressure of the con and make the world through standing on a will,
admit you're not a farmer, you can do what you want, get slack!
If you can persuade, well then make sure that you're paying,
and profiting from what you make,
then you've got some love.
Five dollars for this.
She just looked at you with that sweet smile so fair,
she knew you paid thirty bucks just to smell her underwear.
Now your bunny's nuts are covered in that pink rash,
and you got sweet salvation, thirty dollars cash.
Every night Connie's in my room, possessing my tits, my ass, my sweet little poop.
I'm a worker.
Down by the seaside.
I'm Pisces.
Fishy girl swimming in an ocean of slack.
I give it all away just to get more back,
and I'll keep giving away just to get me more.
Yes, Bob, dammit, I'm Connie's whore!
Fuck Bob.
Fuck Bob!
Slack must flow like snot from a cold-ridden three-year-old's nose.
Fuck Bob.
May Bob be fucked up the ass with barbed wire.
But you know, maybe that's just what he wants.
Eh, fuck it.
Bob's ass will flow like blood from Biblical plagues.
Fuck Bob.
The aisle will run red with the blood from Bob's ass.
Give me my fucking slack now.
Dammit, Bob.
Fuck Bob.
The problem is, Bob needs to be shown his place.
Bob's place is on the business end of my razor wire strap-on.
Fuck Bob.
You know what?
Bob could look like shit in my underwear.
These right here, Bob could do nothing with.
Bob isn't man enough for my undies.
The slack contained in the very vaginal secretions latent in any uberfem's undies is enough to kill Bob instantly.
Fuck Bob.
Fuck Bob is nothing more than simply the butt plug in the ass of an unkempt rainbow child
who sold his ass to gay porn to support his co-cabin.
Fuck Bob isn't even worth the razor-striped underoos of a nine year old redneck boy.
Fuck Bob needs a job.
And you know what that job is, ladies and gentlemen?
Bob needs a job sucking my giant rubber cock.
I want Bob down on his knees in front of me, taking it in the ass from a seven foot tall Norwegian chicken, high heels with a giant purple strap on.
And while he's on his knees in front of me, you know what he can be doing? Sucking my giant rubber cock.
Fuck Bob. Slightly crazed, I love the Norwegian women, but fuck Bob.
I hate Bob, and that's pretty obvious.
Mainly because I'm ten times the man Bob is, I'm about a thousand times the woman at least.
Bob keeps fucking his every dozen eggs.
But I've got an idea, let's fuck Bob over. You guys get the Singapore swing, I'll get the lead pipe, and we'll show Bob a thing or two.
Yeah.
You go first.
I will go first.
Bob came dressed like Sailor Moon came up to me, and he asked me, he had the gall to ask Kanye like me if he could give me oral pleasure.
I said, what the fuck.
Well, I dropped my drawers right there and showed him the glory of my dark jungle.
Bob's eyeballs fell right out of their sockets and rolled across the dusty ground.
I looked at him and said, get those back you fucker, or I want them later.
So there Bob was, crawling around on his hands as named, a little Sailor Scout skirt flapping in the winds.
I couldn't resist.
I pulled out my nine and a half inch space Connie strap-on of slack, and I gave Bob's little rosebud a stiff fucking, fuck Bob.
So there Bob was with this huge purple strap on his ass, screaming, Pisces fuck me harder, Pisces fuck me harder.
I was just disgusted with his candy ass.
You know what, I looked at Bob, and I told him, put those little red panties back on you cunt, and suck my pussy like the bitch you are.
But you know what, Bob failed again, fucker.
Bob couldn't find the clitoris if it was in his fucking pipe.
Fuck Bob.
See I've had Bob, the no good son of a bitch.
I've turned Bob down since then.
I said take my thirty dollars you fucker, go learn to eat pussy like a real woman.
I mean shit, I was drunk, Bob was being nice, he had on a nice pair of pantyhose.
But enough about that fucker.
Let's talk about Connie.
I see visions of Connie. Of course I do.
I am a vision of Connie.
I have titties that could feed a small South American nation.
I have ovaries of steel, and a cunt built like a brick house.
My uterus could nurture a full grown yeti.
I am a sweetie.
I'm a comb slut.
I'm an angel.
I'm a devil.
I am F-A-T fat.
And P-H-A-T fat.
I'm the succubus and the innocent.
I am a vision of Connie.
Connie herself.
And you know what?
So is every sweet, lickable, lovable, sexy uberfem in this church.
Very lickable, aren't they?
I don't see Connie though in the pages of Vogue magazine, my friends.
No, no, no, no.
I see Connie in beautiful, naturally occurring women with great wondrous beauty.
Dismutated imperfections.
Big, curvaceous asses.
Titties that bounce when they walk.
I want to see some fat on my women, and so does Connie.
No, no, no, my friends.
No cover girl for Revlon and the Clinique of Anorexia here.
No, no, no.
Those pink priestesses of pure anti-slack are put there by the con to keep you from the church.
You.
All of you.
From Connie.
And she lets that happen, you know.
Of course she does.
Because if this filtering comes out, the only women who will be left after all the beauty ads and hype from the conspiracy are the true sex goddesses.
The true uberfems.
This is how Connie filters out the best females on this planet.
Not one true uberfem is once considered model material.
We're all too fat, too short, too skinny, too this, too that, too weird.
But as you know, as I know, too much is always better than not enough.
Now.
Ooh, doggies.
Reverend Pisces, friends, or actually Priestess Pisces, live at 5X Day.
Before that, we heard Reverend Floyd rehearsing his rap, which was never properly recorded.
Friends, Reverend Pisces, or Princess Pisces, is one of the Connie-ites of the church.
The gals who worship Connie more than Bob.
And the babes of the church.
And there's lots of them, as you can witness on the yearly subgenius calendars.
We had a beefcake calendar this year, as well as the traditional naked woman subgenius calendar.
Yes, you babes of the church, you better watch out, because we'll be watching you.
Uh, who else was right up front there, I remember?
Oh, yeah.
The, uh, the Evangelical, Princess Wee, of course, me.
Yeah.
It was a big blur.
There was a lot of people, a lot of people dancing.
It was, you had, it was the best-looking front row of babes I've ever seen at NX Day.
Yeah.
It was the, the.
There was a fine, fine front row there.
All the pagans must have been there, too, because when I went down to the roundhouse
later, they were all like, that was a great show, great show.
Oh, I could hear it all over the campground, too.
Yeah.
Even if they didn't want to come to get near the terrible subgeniuses.
Those men were.
Those men who never have sex.
Well, many of those people have had those.
Sexless.
The sexless geeks you must flee from.
Those sexless geeks will molest you.
So, who is the sexless geeks?
That's us.
Oh, that's us.
You, Dave.
But, but, but, we're, we're dangerous molesters at the same time.
Well, much in the way that we frogs have many different sexes, so are we all supposed
to be.
We're sexist macho sexist geeks.
Marxist?
Sexist?
Sexless macho sexist geeks.
I first started watching bug porn when I was five.
Oh, it started out harmless enough, but soon I was popping in VCR after VCR tape of bugs
doing it any which way their little green brains could think of.
Butterfly O'Roll was my favorite.
To watch those little butters go to sleep.
Butterfly feet suck on the gas I know and the rat is shooting ant or beetle made me
cider spasm all over the walls.
I even hit the ceiling once.
Sick I know, but I couldn't stop.
Bug porn got in the way of girlfriends, boyfriends, family, and eating.
All I did was watch bug porn, bug porn, bug porn.
My penis was raw most of the time from friction burns.
I got to the point where I was like, oh, I'm going to die.
And I realized I don't like such things.
It made me wish I was eating stuff, like you and I, osm
is a really good song as well.
Oh, sometimes I want to open up my mouth, but I just can't.
Whenever I seldom just eye contact with them, I just let them draft a joke at me, so I didn't
have to be too careful.
I just wanted to smooth my shoes into the white color.
The immediate thing was to calm their nerves.
The road is getting裸 hatteer.
I even gave those red-headed ants a second chance, but now I tape up my pee-hole.
Addicted to the Insects, the world's first song about bug porn, by Heart Ignition.
Folks, it's just not the same without all the Jim Bae drummers.
Uh-uh.
We were playing this stuff at X-Day on the Club Tiki Banzai stage, the Bonobo A Go-Go,
with eight drummers and 40 or 50 dancers,
all in one little campground.
Campsite.
I'm just in a campsite.
That's all.
Campsite right by a swamp.
And, uh, yeah.
Yeah.
What a week.
We built Monkey Island.
Here's what happened, actually, at X-Day, if you're curious.
And, uh, yeah, I'm still recording.
I even put a cue on it.
Uh, well, we built Monkey Island.
That's what we did.
And just presented it.
We just built, that's all we did.
We built Monkey Island.
And hot damn if the monkeys didn't just drop from the trees and, uh, populate that bastard.
Indeed it did.
But, uh, we built Monkey Island.
Me and my main, uh, me and my main man there.
And my main captain.
And my main drill instructor.
Dr. Katad and Lagune.
We inducted the recruits, too.
There was a lot of new recruits at X-Day.
We inducted them real right fine.
And we began the process of breaking them.
Others we had already begun the process of, and we did break them.
Uh, maybe not Saturday night at the big ESO show, but somewhere along the way.
Uh, many were broken.
Music
When sergeants begin speaking to you, your answer should begin with the word, sir, and end with the word, sir.
Do you understand me?
When sergeant Matthew Hall's asked you to repeat everything he said, you've been to the bed.
I'll tell him, you little fucking dude.
When I ask you again, you might be dumb.
Right, dude?
Get up here!
I don't want no teenage weed.
I just want my M14.
If I die in my combat suit,
they sound like pussies to me.
If you sound like pussies to sir,
now,
we're gonna give you
another chance!
You!
Lamby boy!
What's your fucking name?
Boy!
And I go!
And I go, sir!
Bullshit, Al Corvo!
You look like a simply pile of rat stuff!
And now all your name is?
Maverick Rat Stuff!
Do you understand me?
Sir, yes, sir!
Do you like me?
Do you have a sucker?
You're a rat, my cock!
Sir, yes, sir!
Are you some kind of penis-bubbling homosexual?
No, sir!
Get down!
Get down, y'all!
Yes, sir!
What about that one?
His name's Top Mojo.
Yes, sir!
Granada rhetoric, them, I'm sacking the
ice.
I don't want no teenage dream
I just want my M-40
If I die in the combat zone
Pack me up and ship me home
If I'm 96 foot down
Can you hear it hit the ground
When you hit the bottom you hear me say
Take my life
You can't be saved
If I wanna be a good instructor
I wanna grab on my hair
I wanna wear my school be better
And now
One more time
What's your name you monkey
B coins
Pass votes
share we rockin'
Oh my God
Well what the hell different thing you got
Do you have much in your ears
A ton of less
All you have is
You're crazy!
What you're saying is okay!
Bullshit!
You're crazy!
What you're saying is okay!
Bullshit!
I know that I do have it
14 years and I can't have it
But I don't want no TV queen
I just want my important
Yeah, the heart
Makes the world so far
But your ass
Pulled on some
Superb stuff
Cool little blue man group
background here
Yeah, the Bonobo
Go Go
Was the hot happening place
At X Day
One of the hot happening places
And we certainly did jam it up
Real right fine
And man, I just can't tell you
The things that happened there
Just amazingly Bonobo
Things that happened
Which I had no part of
Mostly
All right, maybe a little bit
One or two times
But just as a
Sort of overseer
But the real
But I didn't really get involved
In any true Bonobo-ism
Although other people sure did
On my bed
Come back from the hot tub
Find some little hag
Blowing my drummer on the bed
Well, one of the drummers
All right, somebody
Not the drummers
Can you say blowing?
Probably not
I'm not sure
I'm just a little bit
Performing a lewd sex act
In the public open eyes
I'm like, what the hell's going on here?
Like, get it the hell out of my bed, man
Geez, old man
I mean, I don't care
If you wanna go have fun
Go have fun
What's the big deal?
But not in my bed
Come on
I got a nice little thing here
You know, one of them things
You go down to Kmart
You know, one of them queen-size
Blow-up things on the stand
You know, and I got one of those
Under a lean-to
And it's by the fire
And it's a cozy place
It's been my cozy little hideaway
All summer long so far
All spring and all summer
But there was people defiling it
And I was tired
I wasn't in any kind of mood
For this sort of open Bonobo-ism
As the sun was coming up
I also wanted to go to the
I wasn't in any mood to
Sleep on a wet spot
That someone else made
So
But I did play a lot of cowboy songs
And I had fun doing that Saturday night
And Friday night
We had a pretty damn good jam too
And Thursday night
We had a really good dance party
With the drummers and all that
And, uh, boy
It just
Everybody wanted
All the drummers came out
All the pagans got together
With the bobbies
And there was a big truce
And, uh, I was like
There was even mating rituals
Between bobbies and pagans
That went on
Yep
But I just kind of kicked back
And watched the monkeys on Monkey Island
Swing from the vines
Chitter chatter
You know, that little
Little chimp chitter chatter
Chitter chatter
That kind of kept me up all night
You know, some of that
Chitter chatter of the chimps
You know, the
That
You know what I mean
It was just like
You know, keeping me up
But you get used to it after a while
You sort of get used to
The depravity of musicians
But I did witness
The goom actually pointed it out to me
On Friday night
It would have happened
Right under my nose
I never would have noticed
Knew what was going on
Uh, people were diving
Literally
Jumping
Into the bonobo
Cauldron
Of depravity
At 5X Day
They were immersing themselves
In the
The sewage of our past DNA
Back at age
You hear about the new find?
They're putting
They found a skull
That not quite ape
Not quite human
But definitely not ape
But not all human
Seven million years old
And we've known
For years and years
That some divergence
Happened
Somewhere between
Five million and ten million years ago
But that's a five million year span
And we didn't really know what
You know, what the hell's going on there
That's good music
I'm just gonna keep that one going
And uh
We still don't know really
It's very fuzzy in our
You know, if you go to school for this stuff
We don't really know what's happened
In the last five years
Five to ten million years
Where we diverged
From the chimps
But we do know it happened
Five to ten million years ago
Hold on, I got
Got a cough
I still got a
Little sore throat
From last weekend
But yeah
So they find this skull
And they just announced it
Or put it in a paper today
It was found last year sometime
Actually
It's probably been in all the science journals
Already long ago
And uh
But there they are
You know, we're not that far removed
At all
From that
Half ape
Half chimp
Yeti sort of critter
Somewhere in there
So that's all we know
Five to ten million years ago
Aliens came down to the earth
We don't exactly know when
And mated with the chimps
The bonobos
And out popped the humans
You know
But now they're getting close to figuring
You know, finding one of those first
Yeti babies, I guess
You know
Or, you know
And that's kind of cool
But you know
After spending a week in the woods
With the whole church of the subgenius
And the kind of
People that it attracts
You definitely see many instances
There's many times
In the short few days that you're there
Just whatever
Four days, something like that
There's many instances
In four short days
Where you just look at what's happening
And you go
I mean, you can easily visualize
One of them public television programs
Where they morph into monkeys
You know, chimps
Because that's what they look like
Going, I see a chimps
I saw what I witnessed
It looked like the chimps
On Monkey Island
And no different at all
Except there was a lot less hair
That's all
And in some cases
That wasn't true either
Some cases there was just as much hair
But most cases
It was just a little less hair
That's all
A little more pink skin
But definitely chimps
No doubt about it
Definitely chimps
Saw it over and over
And over
But
Anyway
If this stuff ever gets out to
The old church on the hour slap
Or something
I want to definitely thank all the people
That donated
If you're listening in
To the Tranquility Base Fund
That helped out a lot
Thank all the people that brought stuff
Brought swag
Swaggly things
To the
Club's
Tiki Banzai Bar
Bottles of stuff
And things to hang up
And add to the display
I want to thank all the drummers
That jammed
You know
They're out there
Though they ain't hearing my voice
They're out in the woods right now
They're drumming tonight
I'm sure
I guarantee you
They're drumming going on
Tonight
Certainly tomorrow
Because the big fests
Are coming up now
So you know
Big thanks goes out
To all them drummers
And all the people
That jam
Big thanks goes out
To all the people
That danced
You know
Had a lot of fun
At the big ESO show
I certainly did
I had fun
I like
I think it was
Sister Decadence
Putting one of the
News group postings
That I
I changed costumes
Almost
Almost as much
As Cher does
But I think
I have better costumes
Though I just don't have
Nice tits
You know
I think
I'm going to have to
But I do have a weird look
You know
Like Cher does
Got a uniquely weird look
So
But it was there
There was there
Back to the anthropology
Of it all
It was definitely
A bonobo time
That was had by all
Bonobo go-go
Was decked out
To the hill
And we had
The gym
Happening
I'll tell you that
Why are you going
Deck state this year?
We go
To confront
The chief enemies
Of the people of the world
The Yankee imperialists
And their commander in chief
The vulture from Texas
It was merely a matter of hours
Before the looting and arson
Had spread through the city
The first major fire
Came at 6.30
Man-hackers
I think the people
Are fed up
Way up above their ear-line
Of the muggings
And the robberies
And the murders
And the hijacking
And all this thing
That's going on
That's caused riots
I think all races of people
Feel that way about it
Come on, baggy
Get with the beat
The bare necessities
Of life
Will come to you
They'll come to me
They'll come to you
How about scratchin' your teeth?
And that old left shoulder
While you're up there, Mowgli?
Now just a hair lower
There
Right there
That's it
Oh
This is new
Oh, that's good
Shit, we've got to get to a tree
This calls for some big scratchin'
You're a lot of work, Will-il
Right on it
Yeah
Uh-huh
That's delicious
Oh
Ooh
Just a little bit
Yeah
Ha ha
Huh
Uh-huh
Yeah
Mm
Uh-huh
Huh
Oh
Yeah
Uh-huh
Heh
Mm
Oh, man
Sosodata's 5x day
a sickening little collage
of how Reverend Sosodata
spent his 5x day drill
and now friends
to take us home
take us on home
Einstein's Secret Orchestra
ESO Swamp Radio
from beautiful WCSB Cleveland
with yours truly
Reverend Ivan Stang
Doc Rock
Professor Chaz Smith
and Lonesome Cowboy Dave
you know it's weird
some people are disgusted
by insectuals
they hate bug porn
and therefore
I guess he was mad at you
for not having been aborted
for doing what you did
that one time
with that umbilical cord
uh huh
well
spit it out
I see it
spit that thing out
right now
it's not gone man
it's been swallowed years before
look at these dendrites
look at these small little snappy teeth
does it look like I could chew
an umbilical cord
you can't look at your own dendrites
like in the days of 1x
like I could jump down
and literally rip
someone's umbilical cord out
and perhaps play the floating baby
and throw it through the air
I'm incapable of such stuff now
the floaty baby you say
of course the floaty baby
you think you can just say this stuff
and then just have to say it
and nobody take you up on
check it out
and ask what's up
you're just gonna spew out this nonsense
and nobody's gonna call you up on it
right
as if the floaty baby wasn't a real thing
that everybody saw on X-Day
floating over the horizon
buzzing the brushwood campgrounds
well I know I saw it
dropping its diaper waste
well I know I'm not allowed to see them
its confused blatherings
you're not allowed to see anything
you never even see the UFOs that circle around here
ever ever ever
not me
I mean there are people pointing skyward
you know with one finger one place
and you're not allowed to see them
the other one
and you refuse to acknowledge this stuff
and I wonder why
you can't see them
I can't
we believe in the gods
who don't want us to believe in them Dave
and we believe in the gods
who have ended this world as we know it
and have given us this sandwich in return
we're back to square one
yes square one indeed
and this world is ending
this ESO radio stand-in is ending
as the hour comes to a close
and DJ A's fans will be gloating
glad to know
that he's back
and urban lullabies will proceed
as before
as ever
and as unto the end of time
with your sack in the wind
your head in the saddle
how does all that stuff go?
keep your proboscis in its normal situation
keep your tangential awareness acute
and keep your feet dry and fuzzy
I bet you've always wanted to do this
and any stray sacks all go to Princess We of course
and keep your frustrated wanderings
in a small circle
so that you don't harm any of the other patients
keep your feet
forget it
oh
I'm slack
P.O. Box 204206
Austin, Texas 78720
that's a box 204206
And it's so calm at www.subgenius.com
Praise Bob
They didn't know how to wipe without actual toilet paper
Everybody knows a good old dry leaf will do it just fine
When my bandmates first got there, the other two guitar players
They were like, they'd never been to this before
And there was that little short guy
Peter Pan, they called him
Yeah, the little guy
Reverend Zorro
Oh, Reverend Zorro, the fox
So cunning and free
And he was standing there watching whatever was going on at the stage
This was daytime still
Still light out
And John and Frank and I walked up to the stage
And he was standing there and he was picking his ass
Well, we all hooked fingers firmly up
The chest
You think that if you're really scratching it
Was picking his ass, he would have picked a better one than that?
That's what I can't understand
And John and Frank just looked at each other
And I didn't know what to say
I began slowly picking their own muscles
They were like, Chaz, man, what kind of fucking gig did you get here, man?
They were, after all the asses, they were confused
They thought he was a demon
I mean, these are the guys I play in in a glam rock band
That we go and play New York City all the time
They're not ready for bold surrealism
They kept asking, what's the deal?
What's up with that guy?
I didn't know what to say, what's up with that guy
What was up with that guy?
His finger
He's a descendant of the Yeti
His finger in his colon
He's a genius
He's closer to Bob than you are, Dave, I'll bet you
Well, I'm sure he is
I noticed there was much less hair on his chest
And Bob was fond of depilation of the chest hairs
Bob's an old crack picker from way back
He smoked many a wedge in his days, unfortunately
Yeah, for a long time
There was a lot of hair