This show's satellite feed, beyond satellite.
It is a tool created by man, for man, for men to use.
Like a screwdriver, or a hammer, or a wrench.
It's something to manipulate something with, isn't it?
That's what it is, like, oh, let me screw this screwdriver.
I'm just gonna screw you down, you're the public.
Let me get you in my vice here.
TV is a tool. It can be used to do anything.
Like, you can take a hammer, and you can, like, nail something in the wall,
and hang something good up on the wall, or you can beat someone's skull in with it.
Same idea. It's not the tool, it's who uses it.
Who it's created for. Do you understand?
Do you get it, man? Comprende?
And you have babies, don't you?
They eat pablum. You know that stuff that really isn't anything?
It's just pablum? That's what TV is.
It's pablum. Want some? Want some?
It's good. Sure? It's good.
Want some? Want some?
Sure? Open wide. It's good.
Here comes the pablum. Gonna force feed you.
Want some? Sure? Good.
It's good. Want some? Want some?
It's pablum.
You know what I'm saying?
I'm gonna force feed you the pablum. You want some?
The man on the TV is gonna force feed me the joke I don't want.
Invite some people over. Here, I'm gonna invite some people over.
I'm gonna tell them to come over to the wrestling.
There's Hulk Hogan. Come on over. Watch a little TV.
There's Don Johnson.
And behold, the man that came from the TV screen.
Amen, can you say hallelujah?
And he came walking down that lane.
And his name was television.
Thirty, thirty, thirty. Count them.
And he started. Frames per second.
Coming at you, TV.
What started as a dream has become a reality.
It's everybody's reality.
Don't even bother, cause you can't ignore her.
She's TV. She's everybody's reality.
It's my reality. It's your reality.
It's my vision. It's my dream.
I'm the Mustang.
And I can tell you, start praying to a new God.
Start praying to a new, new God.
I'm a new God.
Don't you know you're watching? Aren't you?
Yes.
I can see you're still watching.
I also awoke from the same dream realizing that I had subconsciously gained knowledge of a deductive technique
involving mind-body coordination operating hand-in-hand with the self-genius.
Our old sweat.
Everything about it is dislocated, dreamy, and agitated.
It's hallucinatory, higgledy-piggledy panoramas like some deranged overview of Mr. Rogers' neighborhood.
A bird's-eye view of the lower depths.
The sub-genius hour of slack that you are about to listen to is specially designed only to be played on radio station
and only in the city of...
Here's your host.
My name is Mike.
His name.
Is Bob.
Bob is the slack-jawed leader of...
Bob is the slack-jawed leader of this gang of ragamuffin dopers.
It doesn't take much to be the leader of this pack.
I'll say.
Bob wins out through the sheer force of his lunatic savvy.
He may be perpetually groggy from the residue of a thousand fixes.
Bob is the slack-jawed leader of...
But when he's pulling off a robbery, he's surprisingly agile and quick-witted.
He also has as many superstitions as a professional.
Bob and his gang don't want to get rich.
They're going to stay high.
Has the soulful, famished look of the undead.
Which, in a sense, is what he is.
I'm the Will of Dobbs.
A half-educated boy just like you and me has the unmitigated nerve to stand up and say
God told him to rewrite the Holy Bible because it's full of errors.
Errors, mind you.
And to go out and preach that old churches are an abomination to society.
I'm not going to lie to the Lord except this one.
That God told him personally to go out and get an army to run.
Give him a trumpet and I bet he'd say he's Gabriel himself.
Perversely, they love to export their birth control devices, their precious condoms,
their precious condoms,
condoms,
their...
their clever,
their precious,
their clever
and well developed abortion techniques,
abortion,
their pletio-
abortion techniques.
Techniques, techniques, techniques.
Their precious condoms,
abortion techniques,
abortion techniques.
Techniques, techniques, techniques.
Their precious condoms,
abortion techniques,
abortion,
techniques. Now, techniques, techniques, techniques, abortion techniques, abortion techniques. Now,
if we think of international relations to kill their own countries, what contem- cont- country,
cont- cont- cont- country, country, cont- they must talk for us. What contempt to kill their
own countries. As for food, could care for 20 billion people. To the overpopulation trees,
what contem- cont- country, cont- cont- what contem- cont- country, cont- cont- country,
cont- cont- cont- drum thumpers, anyhow, drum thumpers, anyhow, drum thumpers, anyhow,
drum thumpers, anyhow, drum thumpers, anyhow.
What's a mere 5 billion people?
They're all countries.
What cunt?
Anyhow.
What's a mere 5 billion?
To the overpopulation drum thumpers.
Anyhow.
Compared to our escalating abortion rate.
In abortion.
Escalating abortion rate.
True, of every 500,
there's a 5 billion.
There's a 500,
God bless.
You and me.
Hello,
listeners and others.
Yeah, the monitors I'm talking to.
Now, you know,
you monitors out there know exactly
to whom I'm
talking to you.
That's right.
We know you're out there monitoring
us, but we love,
we love our listeners, but we
hate the monitors.
So, you keep listening. You won't understand
the half of what you hear.
And in fact, our regular listeners may not
because I don't really myself.
Tonight is going to be a
noisy show.
So, you might
follow
my lead and wear headphones.
I have to wear headphones or the show
makes even less sense than it
ordinarily would, but
you out there,
I'd put on my headphones if I were you.
It's just a
thing I like to do
is put on my headphones.
So, tonight,
you want to know that, well, so far,
what have we heard so far?
Blade Runner right now.
Start praying to a new
God. That was the Sedition
Commission and
oh, then some
Twin Peaks stuff. That was Agent
Cooper. We haven't forgotten you,
boys.
And, oh, you know,
Bob is the Slackjaw Leader. I've played
that before.
And then that little
little thing where the
fellow was in such an uproar over
our precious condoms
and our abortion techniques.
See, our
condoms and abortion techniques
are, by
definition, totally different from
the norm, that which you are familiar
with. Even some of you long-time members
may not be totally aware of some of our
precious condoms
and abortion techniques.
There, there.
Be watching for that new book of the subgenius.
And that's mostly
what's been going on at the headquarters this
week or so, is working on that
new book, despite
the work is continuing,
despite the best efforts of the conspiracy
and
why the church itself seems to be
trying to throw a couple of
monkey wrenches in the works.
But that's another story.
What else?
Well, myself, one thing I've been doing quite a bit
at the headquarters this week is
changing addresses
on the hundreds
of stark fists
which came back to us
because you out there
that have moved
didn't see fit
to be telling
the truth.
Well, anybody.
You know, the post office, which I can sort of understand.
But you didn't even
tell us that you were moving.
Was that a good idea?
I don't think so. You see, because
if you don't tell us,
you won't get your stark fist.
Now occasionally, if it's been a recent enough move,
why, the good old post office
will let us know and
we have to go through an incredible amount of trouble
re-entering those addresses and sending
them out at great expense and
it tends to sour us.
on those of you who've done that.
And then of course we get those letters
from people, I heard there was a new stark fist out.
Bob.
See, Bob doesn't
do the dirty work, but still.
Bob, I didn't get
my new stark fist. I want to know why.
My friend, my friend down the street got his
or hers.
Now it's true, I did move
two or three times without telling you, but
you know, still.
It's amazing how many people will actually write
that sentence, that I moved a couple of times
without telling you, but they still don't
subgeniuses. Some more sub than others.
So, in the future, and
those of you listening, because this does not
merely relate to Dallas, obviously.
This relates to, you know,
many other cities where we're
broadcast. So please, dear friends,
when you move, let us know.
So stay tuned for
Church of the Subgenius
Hour of Slack
Radio Ministry. To start out tonight,
...
Ah,
Steve Stein.
...
We'll be right back
after this word, word,
word, word, word.
...
It's
so fresh!
Look at that shine!
Oh, yes!
Lemon,
chicken,
liver.
Alright
Hey, Mom, can I have some more?
We'll be right back
after this word
After this word
We'll be right back
after this word
Bargains, bargains, bargains
Now how much would you expect to pay now?
It's like you do
Not just one
Not just two
More than three
You get more and more
It's fresh
You pay only $9.99
This offer may never be repeated
$29.99
Operators of stand-by
$9.99
$29.99
Absolutely free
We'll be right back
This word
After this word
The word
Work. Work.
New order? Here's all you just called.
Just call this toll-free number and have your credit card ready.
Please allow four to six weeks for delivery.
Offer not valid in Kentucky, South Dakota, and Hawaii.
And don't forget, with every seven you order, you get one free.
Iron, niacin, and riboflavin.
Riboflavin.
Get down.
Humminah.
Call before midnight tonight.
Humminah. Humminah.
Humminah.
We'll be right back.
I'll be right back.
For this work.
Quickly
Fast
Remember
We'll be right back after this word.
We try to be right back.
And of course that was, I hope I remember to mention,
that was Steve Stein.
I'm trying to remember to give credit where credit is due.
So that was Steve Stein.
And this, I hope, is Spinal Tap.
You've been bad
Don't do what I say
You don't listen
You never obey
I try to teach you
But you just won't be good
You won't behave the way a big girl should
It's time to give that whip a crack
I'm gonna have to send you back to
Best Go
You're a beauty
You're the best of your breed
You're a handful
And I know what you need
Any training
Gonna bring you to heel
I'm gonna break you with my will of steel
Discipline is my middle name
And no one comes back the same
Best Go
No more skipping strangers
Or running free at night
You think my box's bad, honey
Wait till you feel my bite
Right
I got problems
You whine and you beg
When I'm busy
You wanna dance with my leg
I'm gonna tell you
Make you sleep out the door
You're so flaccid
When you're down on all fours
And when you hear
Your master's name
You will come a little faster
Fight the best goal
Best goal
I'm not here to take you back
Good girl
Best goal
Be bold
Be brave
God protect us
Beat the GD
Beat the aument
Get me high out
Hit the ông
Don't look down
You can hit the Austin
Have you lost your dog?
We were up in heaven, but now we're in the mud.
We fell off the wagon, you should have heard the thud.
We were so superior, that was just a phase.
We were high on that for the 14 boring days.
You decide to skip mass and abuse drugs today, and you're comfortable.
Will I end up a bum? Will I end up a crumb?
Will I end up in hell? Will I end up in jail?
Will I end up in Jesus? Will I end up in trees?
Will I end up rich, rich, rich, rich?
Rich.
And the reality of where you are brings you back.
You're a real man.
Fight, fight, cigar.
Hit it, hit it.
Time.
You've got 48 hours to save a life.
You've got a lot of time.
What a sweat.
Now's the time.
A minute.
Nothing happens until someone buys something.
Now you might be telling yourself, the project sounds great.
What can I say? It's just beautiful.
The project in its packaged form is available for your use immediately, with your own chosen title for the album.
As well as the entire inside cover surface for your use.
Take two high-quality stereo LPs, put them in a full-cover jacket, add a beautiful sexy gal on front, and candid photos of the KQ jocks inside.
And you've got a bombshell.
You could see it in the streets and smell it in the air.
There was a sort of electric quality about it.
Everyone knew this time there was no fooling around.
They meant it.
They really meant it.
Please put down your weapon.
You have 20 seconds to comply.
I think you'd better do what he says, Mr. Kennedy.
Did he say, I think you'd better do what he says, Mr. Kennedy?
That's right, it was Robocop.
Ed 209 killed JFK.
I knew it all along.
So, what have we been up to here since last we spoke?
I mean, if you knew what I was doing when I listened to this.
First, of course, we heard Spinal Tap doing bitch school.
So good to hear from them again.
Most of this media barrage you've heard so far.
And we'll hear this from Food For The Dead.
And then we'll hear the Fights of the Gods, which is Blaise Brown's show from New Orleans.
New Orleans.
So, what do you want to hear now?
Of course, now you're listening to the Raymond Scott Project.
That guy was, uh, Carl Stallings took a lot of, arranged a lot of his music, of course,
for the Warner Brothers cartoons.
I kind of prefer the Carl Stallings arrangements myself.
But isn't it great?
We live in a world where we're able to get this new stuff.
I mean, I've dreamed all my life of being able to hear Warner Brothers cartoon music on,
well, I certainly didn't imagine CDs or anything.
You know, give me a break.
It's a wonderful, wonderful world we live in, friends.
And how about, how about a little number here called
The Creation Science Polka
by the Rudy Schwartz Project.
Everyone's a project these days.
And so here they are.
Stay tuned.
Come on, everyone, join the fun.
We've got tanking on the run.
The Earth is circled by the sun.
Creation Science Polka.
Science classes in our schools taught by superstitious fools.
Jerry Falwell sets the rules.
Creation Science Polka.
The universe was fabricated in six literal days.
The humans and the dinosaurs shared a condo in L.A.
Carbon dating makes us cringe.
We're the right wing lunatic fringe.
Jesus died for our sins.
Creation Science Polka.
Innovation agency.
Here's a Report on Crafty Steve Chameleon.
Lyricist
Four- cavehunter
The Bible says the earth is only 6,000 years old.
Deny and Jesus Christ will roast your balls on burning coal.
Come on everyone, join the fun.
Ignorance has almost won.
Get geology from a nun.
Creation science polka.
Take your children out of school.
Homespun dogma is so cool.
Prop them up, watch them drool.
Creation science polka.
Donken Dunn
pavements
Bw providers
electrician
petroleum
plasma
solar
メ 2001
com
Sometimes, when she talks to me like that,
I feel I'd like to go up there and curse her
and leave her forever.
Or at least defy her.
But I know I can't.
She's ill.
I understand.
I don't hate her.
I hate what she's become.
I hate the illness.
Norman Bates' mother has been dead and buried.
Buried in Greenlawn Cemetery for the past ten years.
I am sorry, boy, but you do manage to look a little different
when you give me orders.
Please, mother.
No, I will not hide in the fruit cellar.
You think I'm fruity, huh?
I'm staying right here.
This is my room and no one will drag me out of it.
Least of all my big foes.
Son of a...
Now come now, mother.
He came after the girl and now someone will come after him.
Mother, please.
It's just for a few days.
Just for a few days so they won't find you.
Just for a few days?
And that's dog-stained fruit cellar?
No!
You hit me there once, boy.
I'll do it again.
Now get out!
I'm sure this pain in the asses is a lot for my unofficial payment.
sostituting a second hub would still
On the period of much
I told you to get out!
I will carry you, mother.
Norman, that's what you think you're doing.
Don't you touch me.
Don't.
Norman.
Put me down.
This place happens to be my only world.
I grew up in that house up there.
I had a very happy childhood.
My mother and I were more than happy.
It's sad when a mother has to speak the words that condemn her own son.
But I couldn't allow them to believe that I would commit murder.
And again, that was Creation Science Polka by the Rudy Schwartz Project
and Elmwood by...
No, no, Elmwood Doing, the Bates Motel.
Stay tuned.
We have a...
It's a very musical show tonight, I seem to notice.
It's quite deliberate.
Here's one I don't think we've seen before.
We've never played before.
Left goes left where it should be.
Right goes to right accordingly.
I therefore praise these gentlemen
who know and show both the how and when.
50 years of mountress secrets thought toémentary martial arts studies.
What are theirận
≧esen
≧えば
≧ober
for her...
stupidass!
I met an anarchist in Tompkins Square Park
He was an angry man, spitting words so dark
He called for death to rich men, death to the obese too
Death to hard-backed bourgeois blacks, death to landlord Jews
Kill the bankers, kill the cops, kill him, her and me
Kill them all for CBS, NBC, ABC, TVN, CNN, HBO, Live at Five, MTV, Street Break, Party Weekend, Sunday, Jesse, White Day Out
I wrote a book, I sing you, we just had a baby
And I said
Hey
Think you could live forever
дет mundis
kan
can
tapes
Page 2
thatootese
Rebel Stanton, God damn, I'd like to have you sing your tune
But I've been making friends with this here death
And it seems a night too soon
And I said
Hello Death, goodbye the new age
I'm getting tired of waiting, tired of being afraid
Joseph Campbell gave me hope and now I have him saved
So I say
Hello Death, goodbye the new age
Now I'm getting tired of waiting, tired of being afraid
So I'm not trying to be flippant here or irreverent or exploitive or sarcastic or ironic or postmodern
And this is not a parody
Get it? Got it? Good
I've been thinking what he told me that took me to cry
When we held the crystal teen and the child spent twelve grand to buy
Homeopathic pie
Fresh squeeze wheatgrass juice
Doctors off in Bellevue
Doctors, Salk and Sue
Sonnets, time will all be going home if you can find a way
Yes, everyone is going on, going on to stay
And it's time we find a way to cope
A way to find some hope
Some it's the best
Bible or Buddha
Or Muhammad or Krishna
Or cheesecake or bourbon
Or the butthole of Silphos
Or it's Jojo Armani or Romeo
Or Shigley and you really can't afford it
But it looks so fabulous on you so why don't you take it on home
And speaking of home
Is it about time you moved out of that East Village hellhole
You know, the one with the honeymooner's view of the brick wall out the window
Because you deserve something more like affirming like a tree or a flower
Or a patch of grass or a singing little bluebird
Or maybe you just want to take your boyfriend to Europe cause he's never been there
Or the job you always hated
Or you learned how to play the guitar
It's easy
Or getting seemly drunk at a piano bar
Or sing show tunes
And don't be embarrassed because at this point I'd rather see
Brigadoon than Henry for portrait of a serial killer
Or maybe you'd like to get politically active
See a disruptive presidential press conference by shoving a five pound week old stock of broccoli
Between those thin lying lizard lips that no one can read anyway
Because half the country's a litter and the other half is apathetic
Including the first lady who couldn't step just five hundred feet of the ground
Over-decorate a white house to visit the goddamn quilter
Maybe you'd like to put a bullet in a Jesse Helms pea brain
But you know when you start thinking like that
When you start thinking like they do
Then it's time to let go of the material world
So maybe you'd just like to get yourself some religion
Cause Jesus is the way
Jesus is the way
Besides, it's a lot easier to accept Jesus Christ as your personal savior
When he looks like Willem Dafoe
But maybe that stuff turns you off so your end power of myth
Made me feel really good for about ten minutes
Or maybe you'd just rather do acid and listen to Led Zeppelin
Then again, the last time I took hallucinogenic drugs was about five years ago
I took mushrooms and Joshua Tree
Looking for that Carlos Castaneda kind of experience
I got off, my boyfriend didn't, he fell asleep
Left me alone with the television
Turned it on, put on PBS
You know what was on?
Berlin Alexanderplatz
So I started watching it and
You know what?
I got really bummed out
And that's when I said no to drugs
No to drugs
No no no no no
Hell no to drugs
And maybe you wanna say no to drugs too
Or maybe you just wanna join
Atheists of America
The Madonna fan club
Or watch Richard Gere
Follow the Dalai Lama across the world
And then do those oh-so-Zen-like movies
With those oh-so-Zen-like messages like
Hey, it's fun to be a prostitute
I can't wait to spread my legs across Hollywood Boulevard
Because then maybe some rich, handsome billionaire in a Jag
Will come driving up and take me shopping on Rodeo's
And then drive
And that's what a woman's all about anyway, right?
Sucking and shopping
Come on, it's a singalong
But hey, who am I to argue?
Because it's the feel-good movie of the summer
It's the feel-good movie of the year
It's the feel-good movie of the nineties
It's the feel-good movie of the millennium
And you know what?
Oh, yeah
There's a smile on your face and a song in your heart and a spring in your step well
Whatever makes you happy?
Whatever gives you hope
Even if it's a truly tasteless
joke
so
back to
manifesto
pencil in a
date
let me know when something
gives I hope it's not
too late
cause I'm
getting tired of waiting
tired of being
afraid
joseph
campbell gave me hope and
now I have been saved
so I sing
hello
death
goodbye
avenue A
hello death
goodbye
avenue A
hello
death
goodbye
avenue A
hello
death
goodbye
avenue A
hello
hahaha
hey what are we laughing for
I was
dirty
I'm a big
man of
coo
He's not dirty
But this man
Has his own banter
Chip, chip, chip, chip, chip
I wonder what became of that chip
I thought you kicked the TV
Chip, chip, chip, chip, chip, chip
I hope you don't miss O.B.C.
Okay
That was Skank
The aptly named Skank doing a song called
Shimp
We thank OBE for that one
Hmm, and before that of course was
Bong Water
Featuring the lovely and talented
Ann Magnus
Man, what a babe
Mm-hmm
So it's a song called Folk Song
From the album The Power of
Something I can't say on this show
But
A lot of you have one
Call up the station here
Or write to the subgenius P.O. Box
Which is P.O. Box
140306 in Dallas, Texas in La Florida
We'll tell you the name of that album
And look for Ann
And well she was on a sitcom on ABC
For a while there and
Oh, she's been in
Saw her over the weekend
In Making Mr. Right
Which was cute
But I
Of course my favorite role of hers
Was in The Hunger
She's not in it for long
But she makes quite an impression
So let's get back to the show
Thank you
You now have 15 seconds to reply
You are in direct violation
Of the 130th and 79th
I say to you
Be prepared to enter a world
Of adventure that you have never imagined
Rather than the one we face
Where something is really exciting
And there is no way
To penetrate this barrier
It is the strength of a million souls
The power of the dead
You are a creature
Galaxy
I saw a creature in waste
To penetrate this barrier
It is the strength of a million souls
The power of the dead
I summon you
Be prepared to enter a world
Of strangers
Where only death can nove While the dispossessed
Be afraid of politeness
The chivalry of one
Cut the disconnects
Be afraid of everything
simultaniously
The life that makes you
The one thought that drags you
I'm your child.
Somebody get a fire extinguisher!
If I'm destroyed, that gaping wound opens. You might say we terminate together.
Now get back.
And I wish the truth would come out.
Watch it!
You ought not never think about giving up.
Giving up.
Right now is the time.
Oh, that's gone!
You better believe it.
I want my disciples across America to look for a soul.
For a soul.
To look for a soul.
Y'all better watch that stuff.
I'm sure that he received the truth.
He's the newest and most sophisticated treatment available.
It was simply a very bad situation.
Take me away.
Well, she said she was gonna do it, but then when it came down to the actual moments, you know, she was backing out on me.
So I had to think that, well, the aliens had either possessed her or my 50 bucks wasn't getting me anywhere, man.
It was at that moment when the National Guard came in, man.
Yes, I'm talking the National Guard.
It just so happens.
Don't forget the maggots the size of bolognese.
Yep, yep, yep, yep, yep, yep, yep.
Bob loves you.
Yeah.
The lady that had supposedly confessed to the crimes had then changed her story to completely innocent.
Of course, none of the fools in the audience thought her story feasible.
The man with the saucer on his head used his...
...psychokinetic powers to deem the whole business unnecessary.
But of course, the bologna patrol had already set in and enforced the prime directive, that being kill all those unthinkers.
The only thing that was left was the
We've missed you down at Our Lady of Immediate Consumption.
I think it's time to get out the good book, Mrs. Spender.
Oh, yes, here it is, dear, the Spiegel catalog.
Oh, don't order.
Come with us immediately to the shopping mall.
Oh, yes.
Remember, gratification delayed is grace denied.
Oh.
Oh, yes.
The First Amendment gives you the right to choose what you hear, what you say, and what you think.
Oh.
Uh
Are you kidding me?
A Rose Pr chart with Lenny Mad aims to be the best Whatever you close your eyes with.
And this is a book where the regulation with no constitutional obligation was passed.
Oh, we're taking the steps here.
Who gives a ?
Funny, tall, humble, block.
How do you feel about that?
I don't give a .
Richard, state that as a question, please.
Who gives a ?
But Bill doesn't give a .
Funny, tall, humble, block.
How do you feel about that?
I don't give a .
I just give a .
How?
Who gives a ?
Censorship is never going to accomplish anything.
How?
There are a few four-letter words in the album.
It will always sell an extra million copies.
We want people to make up their own minds.
There are a few four-letter words in the album.
The first amendment gives you the right
to choose what you hear, what you say,
and what you think.
Funny, tall, humble, block.
They're offended me, like Chuck lots of people offended themselves.
School.
Who gives a ?
I don't give a .
Everybody needs it.
I command you to throw dirt bombs at cars.
Yes, master.
Anywhere that Jesus meets, I'll faithfully let me go.
Whoa.
For the past few brief minutes,
some more Food Fight of the Gods by Blaze Brown from New Orleans.
And the Kings of Feedback with Who Gives a Bleep,
which is, of course, edited for radio.
And us.
So, listeners, we love you all.
Every one of you.
But mostly we love those of you who are, A,
A,
members of the world's first industrial church.
No names, please.
And, of course, those who have pledged to the Hour of Slack
and, more importantly, paid your pledge.
Don't forget, dear friends, we need you and you need us.
And if you need more of us, you can get some more of us
by writing to the address which I will now be giving,
which is, ready?
Got that envelope?
Give you a second there.
Okay.
Dear friends, write to Bob.
Try to remember those little quotation marks around the word Bob, too, if you can.
Bob at P.O. Box 140306 in Dallas, Texas 75214.
That's Bob.
P.O. Box 140306.
P.O. Box 140306 in Dallas, Texas 75214.
Praise Bob.
Thanks ever so much for listening.
We'll be back with you next week, same time.
Good night.
Praise Bob.
His promise rings true.
God does not send sickness upon his children.
No, sir.
And so God said it.
And I believed it.
And thousands have been healed.
If man had never given himself over to the devil in the Garden of Eden,
man would have never been sick.
Man was not sick until he sold out to the devil.
For you say, sure, have I sinned because I'm sick?
No, if you're a child of God, that isn't the reason.
But I know the remedy.
Just like you found the remedy for your sins one day,
he's also the remedy for your sicknesses and diseases.
And he'll set you free.
And so put your hand against mine and believe the Lord right now.
If you have an afflicted child, place its little body against mine.
Countless thousands have been cured this way in the United States and other nations.
Lord, I bring the sick and afflicted to you.
God, you're looking upon them.
God, you're right there because God, you're everywhere throughout this whole earth.
And oh, God, lay a healing hand.
On the sick and afflicted now.
Heal, heal, heal us.
In the name of Jesus.
Pray every single one of us.
No record has been any good.
It's been about sex.
God does not send sickness upon his children.
No, sir.
And so God said it.
And I believed it.
And thousands have been healed.
If man had never given himself over to the devil in the Garden of Eden,
man would have never been sick.
Man was not sick until he sold out to the devil.
So you say, preacher, have I sinned because I'm sick?
No, you're a child of God.
That is the reason that I know the remedy.
Just like you found the remedy for your sins one day,
he's also the remedy for your sicknesses and diseases.
And he'll set you free.
And so put your hand against mine and believe the Lord right now.
If you have an afflicted child, place its little body against mine.
And thousands have been cured this way in the United States and other nations.
Lord,
I pray for you and I pray for you.
God,
you're looking upon me.
you're right there.
Oh,
God,
you're unaware throughout this whole earth.
And oh,
God,
lay a healing hand on me.
And now,
heal,
heal.
ah.
Three,
every single rock and roll record has been ended.
It's been about sex.
God,
does not say sickness upon his children.
No,
and the God said,
he can't believe it.
And I'll lose him.
If man had never given himself over to the devil,
the garden of Eden,
man would have never been sick.
Man was not sick until he sold out to the devil.
So you say,
preacher,
have I sinned because I'm sick?
You know,
if you're a child of God,
that is the reason that I know the remedy.
Just like you found the remedy for your sins one day,
he's also the remedy for your sicknesses and diseases.
And he is such a brave.
And so put your hands against mine.
And believe the Lord right now.
If you're having a sick child,
press him to the body against mine.
Hundreds,
thousands have endured this way.
None stays another nation's Lord.
I bring the sick and the sick to you.
God,
you're working upon them.
you're right there.
Oh,
God,
you're everywhere throughout this whole earth.
And oh,
God,
lay a healing hand on the sick and the sick.
And now,
heal,
all.
Heal,
In the name of Jesus.
Every,
every,
single rock and roll record that's been any good has been about sex.
And he'll set you free.
Set you free.
You're free.
Free.