Who is it?
This is Bob. He can straighten your wheel and fix that flat in no time.
Sure I will. Sure.
And then we'll take you along to the place where the show is going to be.
Excellent. It's all going to bliss.
The program you are about to hear, Bob's Slack Time Funhouse, is parody, satire, and comedy.
Any reference to Bob, the Church of the Subgenius, religion, politics, or any other touchy subjects is intended only as humor
and should cast no reflection on the high standards of WREK Atlanta, its staff, or that of Georgia Tech.
I can't tell her to stop hoping, but when she's disappointed again, you can help pick up the pieces.
I think I'm going to be sick.
Everybody was busy getting things ready for the show.
Mr. Stang, you won't believe your ears.
What's that?
You'll puke with wonder when you hear and see.
Be specific. There are strange forms in the Matrix that come and go.
Strange forces that cannot be predicted.
There are signs and portents and faces in the sky.
You're smoking a pipe.
Uh-oh.
Then get ready for a super goody on Saturday, July 5th at 7 a.m. Eastern Daylight Time.
Our Earth will be...
Hurry, the tents come down July 5th.
Portents.
You see? You see?
It means something sinister is coming.
The overlords are coming.
Yes, something sinister is coming. Soon.
Oh, no!
Thanks to the lobotomy and, uh, let's see, the baby sacrifice.
Oh, how awful.
And, uh, the Castro Street group sex orgies and all that.
Filthy.
I've done it going both ways. Completely accidentally.
Ah, heck.
And filthy.
Oh, for God's sake.
The light just went off in my head.
It is crazy. It'll leave the landers on the air in jail.
It's a fine choice.
Yeah.
And furthermore, I want him in charge of the program.
Uh...
Him?
Yeah, that's right.
You involved.
Can you believe it? This is a pretty good deal.
What?
Oh, those two idiots. Imagine!
Efficiency rate is still optimum.
Only when you two pick up the slack.
I'm sure that Bob will figure out a way to do that.
Fuzzy parameters. Limited logic. Shifting allegiances in the data banks.
Oh, no.
Uh, let's see. I'm going to, uh...
Oh, I'm going to be doing subgeniusly things, if you really wanted to know.
Well, I'm looking forward to it. Looking forward to it, Mr. Stagg.
Automated responses boxes. Stand by with a smelling sauce.
Earth receives a space visitor through a radio receiver. Next.
Jing.
Come.
The new jing.
J slide.
Come.
That's great.
So you thought about that with the jing.
Yes.
So, you thought about that with the jing.
You're right.
I don't know what to do.
The only time I'm happy is when I'm sitting on the floor
And if my sister goes somewhere I can't make it down the door
I don't know what to do
don't know what to do
How you seeing Bob?
Gotta be here soon
Yeah?
Well, maybe
Yeah, maybe
We're checking on it right now
Depraved genius
Party boy
This sinister psycho's capacity for mayhem
Is only matched by his insatiable appetite for a good time
Don't be fooled by his sensitive side
Oh, how do you know he's done all those things?
Hmm
Yeah, that's a genius throwing another universe party
And look at this
Yes, Bob
Who else am I talking about?
All I know is I'm supposed to deliver him something
And I'll be on my way
I would be careful if I were you
Three strippers from Vegas were abducted a couple months ago
They were last seen getting in a motorhome
With some guy in a black duster and a cowboy hat
Bob, Bob, Bob
No one's seen him since
Around the 5th
That's when he has to report back
Or he's AWOL
We've never met
Oh, yeah, right
Which makes him that much more impressive
Really?
Yeah, yeah
I don't want to talk about Bob
As if on cue
You look surprised
Oh, Jesus
You're my first celebrity I ever gave a rosary job to
Oh, please
I'll do anything you ask
Just, oh, please let me come
Please
Hey, Bob, say let's do that
Sure, I will
Sure
Yes, you bet
We're already
Guys on their knees are his assistants
As they say in the Old Testament
Gary the
Bobination
You can leave me there tonight
Come on, Bobby
What do you know better than that?
Bobby
There's nothing to be frightened of now
On my planet
All of you will be free men
Not locked away like animals
Be free
Find your own happiness
Oh, come on, Bob
You don't really believe in people like that, do you?
If you're asking me if I believe in miracles
Then do it
On July the 5th
The 5th of July
Anno Domini
You think I'm gonna help you befoul his legacy?
Yeah, now the boss says it's a very bad thing for the country
The boss has got an idea
With all this Nazi and Jack money
That, yeah
Well, I haven't got it quite straight
But anyway, the boss says it's a bad thing for the country
What did you find out?
I don't need the terrorists
Boy, you're hotter than a firecracker on the 5th of July
The final hour is approaching for the people of Earth
You are to command the forces that mop up
No one must survive
You
You are to seek out and kill every human being
Sure, I will
Bob is anal
Meanwhile
Down in the lake bed they find, uh
More homes, like
Trucks and cars
But no people
Anywhere
Just
Vanished
They don't find them, huh?
They made the jump
The jump?
What's the jump?
Well, the lake bed is a jump station
For the UFOs
It's where they come to abduct travelers
And leave others behind
Right
It's kind of like an interplanetary
Truck stop
Yes
Right
Gateway
Crossover
And what, people just vanish out there?
In the middle of nowhere?
You really believe this?
You believe in this?
You don't believe me?
I can't believe it
Who cares what you believe?
No one would be stupid enough to believe that
Not if he's got his right mind
Please, Jesus, please, Jesus, save Bob, save Bob, save...
Save our Bob
To the unsuspecting person who would not normally get involved with him knowing who he is
Satan
No!
Yes!
No...
Bob's not
Sorry, kid
Come on!
I got you!
I want to call for all of those that believed in his power to rise up and come to him
Click
There it is
You hear from Bob?
Oh my God!
You got Bob?
Bob, Bob, Bob
And out they come
Bob
Tomorrow night I promise you, presto, the strangest story you've ever known
Now, do you suppose this garrulous intruder may be a swindler perhaps
An assassin, a charlatan plotting some curious disaster for your love
Such characters exist
But they are secretive rather than mysterious
I, sir, am a major mystery
Did that salesman cut one?
Yeah, and for some reason he turned on the radio to cover up the smell
I don't know how to take this
I don't see why he moves me
He scares me so, I love him so, I love him so
I will be your guide to the gateways of every world in the universe
We will see impossible beings and unimaginable beauty
And everyone's gonna be what the guy says
What guy?
Bob
On the radio
This madman has only one thing on his mind
Evil
How long did he give it?
Tonight
Oh, that's just what I've been waiting for
Is everything packed?
We've been packed for a week
You sure it's safe?
Now, look, clean up this place and clean it up right
And don't leave any calling cards
Or at least
We're here to change the brain cells inside your head
Bob can help you get rid of the brain cells you don't need, my friend
With overwork and television
The conspiracy has added more brain cells than you need
We're here tonight to kill some of those brain cells
Your brain cells can't be afraid to say
Kill me, Bob
If only I could wedge my name in that little spot
But there's no room above the title for me yet
Well, there's ESQ after this
One of these days, though
I've got a lot of other directors I have to kill
All of these are
Well, I don't know which is worse
They're eating it up?
Yes, from the way they're squirming around
It must be eating them up
You're the ace of cucks
Now bend over and smell the Furo's brain
Uberspeng
Let me smell
Smell
Smell the Furo's brain
Max smell
Max, please, sit down
It's only a demonstration
And this is only a gun
It's not a real gun
It's a...
It's a gun from Dobbs
Oh, I don't know, man
Come on, it's not gay
There's guns in the room
Smell the Furo's brain
Ah!
That was weird
Hello, Mr. Stang
My assistants, you all know him
Mr. Stang
He's got some real duties he wants to show
Um...
Will you teach us how to smoke?
Yeah!
For some reason, something about the nature of our religion
Seems to appeal to these potheads and cannabis smokers
Looking forward to it, Mr. Stang
I just don't understand that
Yeah, very funny
We have a serious problem on our hands
This Malaysian thing is getting out of hand
I need to take care of Sioux night people to answer to
I can be arranged
A gentleman and Ivan was seen leaving shortly
Thereafter with this gentleman
My goodness, Ivan, I'm stunned
The same gentleman joined him again this evening
Bob, you're a poison
As they're walking
Basically fondling one another
As they walk on the street
It made me sick to watch
We observe Ivan and this gentleman again
In an embrace and a kiss
Oh, my God!
At that point
Here we are, Bob's Country Bunker
Bob's Country Bunker
They travel to a country western bar
What kind of music is this?
What kind of music will he have there?
Oh, we got both sounds
We got country and western
Smells awful both ways
This thing is going out two-stepping with Lisa
Lisa?
He lied to me
Unless his name's Lisa
Doesn't look like a Lisa, though
I didn't catch your name
We won't do that, Bob
We do know that Ivan is with this gentleman again this evening
They've been there for a little while
What do you want to do?
Bob, you're dead
You're dead
I mean it
Dead
Okay, let's go
Now hold on, Mr. Manager
Manager
Got a problem?
I simply refuse to have that man on my air
But we're in a spot
Why don't you have it shut off the air?
I want the program canceled immediately
Bob told me personally he will walk off the show
If he is not allowed to express himself freely
Why then what?
Right before you go to my office
We're going to talk about this private fire
That maniac
What's the matter, Bob? What is it?
Well, they went down to the manager's office
They want to shut us off the air
Well, if they can't do that, that's sabotage
Nobody can make a fool out of me except me
Why don't you think of the children?
Well, I have been thinking of
The worst of all was the disgrace
Doggone it, Bob
I'm afraid I've lost another job
Ow, you smashed my hair
I'm sorry, Bob
He laughed gaily
A squid eating dough in a polyethylene bag is fast and boonibus
Got me?
He rubbed his rump, laughing with childhood pleasures
His grin now said,
I'm going to succeed at cross
But I don't know where I'm going to go for that one
That's illegal even in Mexico
Does it worry you, Bob?
The guy dismissed the question with a wave of his hand
Someone told me, maybe Malaysia
Be ready in five minutes
You bring the towels, I get the penicillin
Come here, Bob
Let me show you how a real woman does it
Ooh, ooh
Bob covered every criminal debutante in town
And now
Or whatever
Why don't you come with me?
Oh, Bob
When it's all over, you and I will be the only ones left
You!
You're one of us!
He's flaming hot and flaming gay
He's vibe squared
No, I was scared to death
He's got these eyes that like hypnotize you
Those eyes, they're frightening
And then his thing
I don't want to get into it, but it's huge
It's like a rocket ship
There was a noise too, a kind of plop noise
And the thing bulged
Fantastic
Do you believe in the devil?
Huh?
The world is full of all kinds of beings, my friend
But we make up imaginary ones with pointy horns and pitchforks
In our dreams, we're not the only ones who are like that, Bob
We fly like gods
We long to shoot through space
And why is that, huh?
Because humans used to fly long ago
So you sell drugs here, huh?
Imagination enhancers
If you imagine something, it can come into being
Imagine a devil, and he may show up
That was the charm, my friend
Friends, the world is ending
The birds are vanishing
The polar bears are melting
The skunks have all been eaten
Genetically engineered chemtrails fall from the sky
And all of our food is made of antibiotics
And American brain viruses are in every airport
The hole in the earth keeps getting worse
But that's nothing new to us
Whoa, what a hole!
Someday we're gonna learn and drop right in
Till then, we'll slack around on the surface again
You can't let it slide
Until it slips away
Away.
What happened next?
July 5.
It gets sad again.
You remember Bob?
Bob!
Done!
Garnet!
We have to get Bob!
Who's Bob?
One, two, three!
This is an outrage!
Who is that one?
Send your answer to Old Pink.
Oh, my.
Welcome to...
The Others.
Yeah!
Tonight's the night.
Tonight's the night they come.
It's a freak show.
Where?
About halfway up Devil's Highway.
Turn when you see the Indian.
His name is Bob.
Bob the Indian?
Yeah.
He'll be waiting.
He'll ride in the back, guide you the rest of the way.
Come again?
How do we know that?
I wouldn't go too deep in the desert if I were you.
You might never come back.
In fact, maybe you better stay here with us till it's over.
Sorry, I gotta do this.
But it's been real fun meeting you.
Well, if you change your mind,
then we'll be in there.
But not first.
Reveille at 0700 tomorrow?
0700?
How about okay?
You scamp, I love you.
Mwah!
You'll miss this, sweetheart.
Oh, my God, no.
It's today, the 5th.
I need to get out of here.
Bob!
Get up!
Come on!
Come on, it's 6 o'clock!
Right, Johnny, right, Johnny!
Short moments.
50 minutes, in fact, to kill.
Kill Bob!
Bob, Bob.
Bob.
We see him.
All right.
You remember Bob?
Bob the Indian?
No.
No, I'm Lawrence of f***ing Arabia.
Nice guess, Kimo Sabe.
You want to get in, Bob?
No, no.
All right, I'm done.
You, go that way.
I had the strangest feeling
that I was leaving the familiar world
of my neighborhood behind.
That, somehow,
I was going to die.
I was now in an unknown and alien place.
A place where anything could happen.
There it is.
Pull over by the cone, now.
Oh, good.
Now you unload these suitcases
and you arrange them in a big circle.
Exactly 12 paces from each other.
I think that might be your job, Bob.
Oh, Jesus!
He was groaning madly.
I think he was trying to talk me into doing something.
No way!
Just do it.
Do it.
He just grinned harder.
Do it and get it done now.
If it don't get done, then I'll move on it.
Do it.
Get it done.
I don't want to be no part of no conspiracy.
I knew he was in with a bad crowd, but it was worse than I imagined.
Aliens.
Huh?
Alien menace.
The alien next door.
And why was Bob always talking about you?
I don't know.
He didn't say.
Now, there's something like seven minutes to the world's end.
Is there anything important we needed to remember or do?
Five minutes to go.
Well, where are they?
They'll be here.
Those people always keep their word out.
You won't forget your promise, Bob.
Sure.
Sure, I will.
Next day, get up.
7 AM.
Drink two cups of caffeine.
Jump.
Drink more caffeine.
Ah.
Sup, geniuses?
This is X-Men.
Yeah.
It's really cool.
Never want to smoke.
Never go out.
Don't go home.
Once more, there are other people outside.
Go to sleep.
THREE Saw logs.
200 of them returned.
consumption is going down.
IN THE MARINE.
appropriated have been used as Rand writes for the color back My very old
thinks you were able to survive.
Medic, breathe. Medic, breathe. Medic.
One, two, three.
Medic breathe. Medic breathe. Medic breathe.
Medic, breathe. Medic, breathe. Medic.
Three minutes, Chagall. I'm not a bit worried.
You are not, but I am.
There is no phone ringing, Derek!
Yes?
I can feel the vibes in the air. Bob is coming, and when he comes,
I run right through the jail door with a huge grin on my face.
Bob, are you worried at all about your lunar adventure?
I'm sure glad to have you boys here
I'm Bob and this here is my place
I read your flyer
Finally, a religion that makes sense to me
Hey everyone, I found him, over here
Bob was a science fiction writer of some note
Publishing many stories a year under various pseudonyms
Including Frank X. Barlow and Kilgore Trout
If I might be so blunt, do you really need a flash in name?
I mean, it's hardly a religious title, don't you agree?
My parents both were born in the day of the false gods who lie
The latter end
And I was born subgenius
Dobbs, I'm an admirer of your work
Personal as well as professional
I help people move on
Help them to escape their mundane ordinary lives
If you want to keep living this life of quiet desperation
What am I going to do about it?
That's up to you
I don't know, man
I, sir, am a major of history
You're a convincing talker about very unconvincing things
Whatever men do not understand they find unconvincing
But please don't suppose I'm dangerous because I'm unfamiliar
I ask that you believe in me
As what?
As a friend of yours
Your talent
Of all human beings
That's quite a spiel, Doc
Subgeniuses
You have two minutes
Three
Two minutes
Attention, subgeniuses
You have two minutes
Two minutes
Three minutes
Bob explained
It is a gateway station
They are situated throughout the universe
It is how people travel from one distant world to another
How come I've never heard about it?
He sighed
Politics
Some say let Earth in
Others say not yet
In the meantime, your gateway is a very important one
How do the gates work?
Look here
He started drawing on a napkin
If you draw two dots on paper, they do not touch
But if you fold the paper in half, they do not touch
If you fold the paper in half, you can touch the dots
Then the dots touch
Gateways are the folds in the paper
Through them, you can visit worlds of wild excitement and strange beauty
You can meet highly peculiar creatures such as you
That's all I'm taking from you
Get back here, you devil
Patience, my friend
Patience?
Bob, you are testing my patience
And all of a sudden, something comes into vision
No!
It's a fist
Bob is my only hope
Back off and give him some room to breathe, Bob!
I'm not going to let you go
What are you all doing?
Well, I'm getting the book
Are all you people crazy?
What's happening here?
It's time
Time for what?
I have to go
You have only one minute
Come to the pavilion now!
Seems in a powerful way, that one
And the customer seems anxious to buy
I haven't much time
We haven't discussed the price
Thirty dollars
Show it to me
Take it
It's Bob's
Thirty dollars
Enter!
It's the chance of a lifetime
But you only get one chance
Put these on
You're on your way
On my way where?
Paradise, my friend
There's no such place
Oh yes, John, there is
Make a choice
There's a whole other world out there
One chance
Make it count
Master, thank you
Now what?
Now we must beg the Hulk
See if they bite
And pull him in
You know no one can hurt you
You know no one can even get near you
You're an X-ray eye now
And you can breathe fire
You can wipe out entire cities
With one blast of your fiery breath
You're a monster now
And only a monster can realize
The fulfillment I'm capable of feeling
It's so wonderful
To feel this far gone
Ah!
You know what?
Stand there!
And wait
Wait for what?
What's happening here, Bob?
The same old, same old
Am I gonna die?
We all died
It's just a matter of when
This moment the entire group of people broke into a deep, slow, rhythmical chant of B
Old B
B-O-B
Over and over again
Very slowly
With a long pause between the first B and the second
A heavy, murmurous sound
Somehow curiously savage
In the background of which one seemed to hear a stamp of naked feet
And the throbbing of tom-toms
For perhaps as much as thirty seconds they kept it up
But this subhuman chanting of B-O-B
B-O-B
Always filled him with horror
Gulp
Aliens!
Hundreds of them!
Like every space creature and comic book monster you've ever seen come to life
Only these were real
Beings with any number of arms, legs, heads, tails, tentacles and antennas
Slithering, gliding, creeping, waddling and scurrying this way and that
And not one of them gave us a second glance
B-O-B-B-B-O-B
A voice on the loudspeaker began making announcements in a language I'd never heard
It sounded like pure gobbledygook
I noticed that some of the creatures hurrying by were carrying suitcases
Suitcases?
Announcements on a loudspeaker?
All of the sudden I realized what this reminded me of
It's like some kind of airport, Mike
It's 7am, what are they cock-a-doodly doing?
Mike, don't look now
But there's a boa constrictor climbing over your shoulder
It turned out it wasn't a snake after all
It was an arm, one of three
Attached to a creature that looked like...
Well, you tell me
Noodles and Bob's throw-up
Three giant yellow eyes about the size of basketballs
Perched on the ends of three thin nets
Three arms were attached to its body at the waist
Each arm ended in a three-fingered hand
And yes, in case you were wondering, it also had three fangs
Bright red fangs
Located in the palms of its hands
And a third that was on the end of its trunk
She can't go flyin'
Flyin' flyin' flyin' flyin' flyin' flyin'
Her
Thank you.
Please.
Please join us.
You highlighted the ships.
Yeah.
You are our new parents.
Wait, is this book written for me?
Let's see what it says.
Thank you.
I'm the first.
You're my parent.
I think that's terrible.
It's a bad joke.
But this night's not over yet.
Woo! Woo! Woo!
You are sure I must come, you smack bastard!
The aliens are here! We're all going to die!
The aliens are here!
What?
The aliens!
It's a cookbook! It's a cookbook!
Ouch! Ain't that ironic?
Now I am become Death, the destroyer of worlds.
I suppose we all fought that one way or another.
See you.
They understood what they were doing.
They were unleashing a power unlike any humankind had ever had.
We now have...
...the ability not just to kill others, but to kill all other human beings.
Yeah!
Great job! Great job!
Magic
Is loose
In the world tonight
Tonight
Rachel
I'm going to get somebody that will stop her.
Well, when you eliminate the impossible,
the only thing left, no matter how incredible,
is Bob.
Bob was some kind of illusion.
Magic Bob.
Like magic.
Real magic.
Like a shower around the sphere.
My feelings are better.
It's a strange kind of scene.
There's a little distortion
on my personal screen.
Honey!
Can you feel it?
Magic
Is loose
In the world tonight
Oh, this is dumb.
Magic
You're so beautiful.
In the world tonight!
How do you think it...
Magic
That's just like a sad excuse for your strange perversion.
You're screwed in the head.
Magic
Come on, Bobby. What do you know better than that?
Don't call me Bobby.
Magic
Bobby!
Alright, so...
Yeah, man.
I don't think I feel so good about this all of a sudden.
Magic
You dumbasses!
You're so stupid!
How could you?
Without their heads, they're powerless.
Please, no!
Said the head.
We mean you no harm.
No, I don't!
Oh, gee!
A lot of smart boys, aren't you?
This ain't right, Bob.
Nothing's right anymore.
The head, he thought, appeared to agree with him.
Run away, said the head silently.
Go back to the others.
You mean...
Go back, said the head.
Sure.
He saw reality too clearly.
A faulty denial mechanism.
Sure.
He failed to block out the terrible truths of existence.
In the end, his inability to push away the awful facts of being in the world rendered
his life meaningless.
Or as one great Hollywood producer said, too much reality is not what the people want.
I have named it Ozymandias Melancholia.
Oh, Bob generally knows what he's doing.
He does everything for the...
Well, Bob, what are we gonna do?
I don't know.
There's hope.
You see, he's got some fight left in him.
Guess Bob liked the real world approach.
Yeah, you know what he found?
Something about the place didn't seem real.
Didn't have a good, odd feeling about it.
So he quit.
Thought it was crap.
It was a joke, really?
No.
You were just wrong, that's all.
I'd rather not tell you.
A little headache.
Something you ate, perhaps.
Joke, Dodgy.
I'm not joking.
Are you gonna let me in on it?
In on it?
Sure I will.
Sure.
Bob, about, um, our money for tonight.
That's right, uh...
We want smoke.
Uh...
I said smoke.
We've got to have smoke.
Cause the smoke's a signal.
And we can't be rescued if we don't have smoke.
Yeah!
There was silence except for the multitudinous murmur of the bees.
Over here, Bob.
Bob.
Over here.
But this night's not over yet.
There's been a little hitch in the giddy-up.
Oh, you got your shoe case.
I'll explain when we get back to the motel.
Hey.
Got a little surprise waiting for you there.
No, Bob, you really surprised me.
You got that right.
Oh!
And I like Bob.
I don't know, does everyone like him?
I know Molly Ringwald ran out of there.
She was scared of him.
She was a little scared of, of Bob.
Hah hah hah.
Where're you goin'?
How could I get goin'?
Y'ka take me with ya?
Don't even ask.
Y-you know how we get.
Huh?
You think I'm kidding?
Oh, don't leave me out here.
That's all right.
now i'm gonna go back to bed it's too late for this spooky i think it's old bob
hey bob don't leave me here
bob turned and draped his arms around our shoulders again smiled and say twizzled he said
just as the camera flashed ah my eyes and before you could say dracula bob spread his wings
uncurled its ears and turned into a bat and the air was full of flapping bat wings
time for canal though watch out
oh
you can't do this bob
sure i will
i'm doomed
there's no hope for me
i battle my existential quantities all day long
i entertain no dreams of ever freeing myself from them
it's just the way i am sickly and worthless a scribble stab at the face of a perfection
that never even really existed and don't tell me i just haven't seen it
i see things as they are
and i don't like it one bit
and well yes sure
i laugh and smile sometimes
but eventually i come back to the realization
that it's all futile
for the least i know it
hahahaha
you're doomed
ahahaha
a mystic new age postmodern guru hipster
you don't impress me you get yours don't worry
trying to save the world with your magical herbs
victim theory and pc f**king troll
just take a good look at yourselves you're so scared and idealistic
whining at the first hint of difficulty itching to strike out
and when you don't understand you're oblivious
oh i'm sorry man i've signed a small circle of neurotics
bouncing your boobs in aerobics classes breathing in positive ions well haha
i guess you gotta spend your money on something
so go ahead and spend it
or it's not worth something
hahahaha
we're all doomed
sprawling and painting all over this natural world that sustains us
for the self interest and comfort seeking that nature installs in us
bombing and flituring our made up enemies
in the hopes of avenging our pitiful tormented conscience
sacrificing our souls and abandoning all that's left us worth living for
for cheap globalized ephemera
who says we're so rational huh
we can't even decide if technology is our great savior
or just our new escape note
oh but it's just a more powerful pen
to write the same old story
in an ugly story it is
struggling with each other
struggling with ourselves
and there's more of us all the time
more fingers on your throats
we've always had wars
we've always had injustice
we've always had stupidity
why should we stop now
we love it this way
we wouldn't have it any other way
but it won't last forever you know
because unless we somehow change
which is highly extremely unlikely
we're all doomed
all doomed
after a few moments
the green glow blinked out
and the sound faded away
until just the echoes
lingered in the dark distorted shadows
hey what the hell
what the hell is this
oh how our entire race will die
this party stinks
oh god you blew it up
i hate that bastard
jesus
oh that son of a bitch
i'm gonna kill you
you stupid rotten son of a bitch
you really did it
i can't believe this
but he pulled him off better than i was going to
damn him
wait a minute
and i
um
are you crazy
are you
i don't remember
oh that's just
you're not
this is the only
you're here
look at this
you know i love you
so do you
this is where we knees
this is you
we know
how to
how this
what i got
shut
resurrected.
Full of crap.
After our, um,
brainwashings there.
And that's why I...
That's why I'm the way
you see me now.
And we decay
with every minute here
and with your
efficient ministrations
turned to jelly.
I want my freedom.
But I was talking
to empty air.
He was tiptoeing
toward the stairway.
There's our thing.
You have to be ready
to be killed by Bob.
I just want to say
one thing.
That I never listened
to such a pack of lies
in all my born days.
We were lying,
Mr. Stein.
You think you have slack.
Cut the crap.
Most of you don't even
know what slack is.
No, I don't.
I don't even know.
This is the thing,
suck it.
I want you out tonight,
bud.
You'll live with Lisa.
Princess.
I can afford to go out
and party at the disco,
et cetera, et cetera.
Now I can afford
to go out and get some slack.
I'm going to have
my fingers in my ears
and be going la la la
the whole time.
Impossible!
I blinked and looked again.
No, I wasn't crazy.
Wimp was gone.
The burnt out wimp
wasn't even there.
Where is that little weasel?
Where is that old face?
Where?
He's gone.
Clocked out at seven
this morning and went home.
He said you should
keep wasting your life, though.
You have to go out
and go out
on your own, man.
Where are you going?
Dallas.
We're all going to live
in the parking lot.
See ya.
I started a joke
Which started the whole world crying
But I didn't see
That the joke was on me
Oh
Oh no
I started to cry
Started the whole world laughing
If I don't see
You
That the joke
Was on me
That the joke was on me
Bob.
Who's there?
You know.
Go get my damn beer.
You're freaking moron.
Bob.
You figure it out?
No.
Bob.
I ain't scared of that circus freak.
He's done exploiting me.
So he plots a masquerade with his pack of sissies and kicks me out for good.
I'm not scared of that circus freak.
That's what happened.
When did you discover that?
How much money you got?
What's that supposed to mean?
Motherfucker.
You know what I mean?
Don't give me that condescending bulls**t Bob.
I don't like it.
I put the damn budget in the damn sink and he knows it.
Yeah.
It's the drugs.
That's me.
Listen to me you dumb s**t.
Okay?
I ain't even a have-been.
I'm a fake creation.
You got it?
You stupid.
I hung up on him.
So how come now Bob gets to tool around in a power everything kind of ride?
He's stepping large and laughing easy.
But the calendar's still on.
I'm not scared of that.
The silence is deafening but the feeling is strong.
All you're gonna do is cover Bob's name in s**t.
Bob Newman!
What can you tell me about him?
Bob.
Never seen him before.
Medical records.
Masturbatory techniques.
Oh my god.
References.
What?
Sperm samples.
Whatever you want to call it.
Whoa!
No.
And then there is this incident involving Vaseline.
Liberally applied to...
Listen.
What do you want from me?
Nothing.
Look I'm sorry.
I can't help you.
Maybe they don't want to be found.
Maybe they got on a spaceship and flew away.
There is one other possibility.
They may have all been the victims of say a single diabolical serial killer.
Maybe somebody who entices his victims to a remote location.
in the middle of nowhere where he has his way with them.
And then buries their bodies somewhere out there.
Wish I could help you.
Cowboy, the blue suitcase, the alleged murders,
the alleged incident in the desert.
But they were there.
There were 15 people getting on a damn RV.
John, do you really expect me to believe you were abducted by aliens
wearing track suits?
You guessed it.
It says here in your statement,
you believe they've stolen your sperm.
Man, that's rough.
I don't know.
It's the only thing that made sense.
It's a conspiracy.
But if you want to be introduced to our chief conspirator
in our little conspiracy.
Where is it?
What's the matter with you people?
I was joking.
Don't you know a joke when you hear one?
So we know whoever laughed was Stang?
That's not all we know.
Mr. Stang.
Drank a lot of bottles of Jenkum,
which smells awful, but is...
It's all dripping out of your ears.
Come on, go go on the head.
A lot of bottles of Jenkum.
And that's why I...
That's why I'm the way you see me now.
Ridiculous, Mr. Stang.
You think I'm kidding.
I'm actually not kidding.
Do you know what Jenkum is?
You leave it in a jar for a long, long time,
then you whiff it,
then you see your ancestors.
Today's Stang jury has already heard testimony
about your event, Scotty.
A lobotomy.
Then Jenkum.
That explains a lot.
That may have been the way...
It happened, Mr. Stang.
Those things did happen, but...
Suppose it wasn't.
I don't know.
That means something sinister is coming.
Yes, something sinister is coming.
Soon.
But you're lying, Mr. Stang.
I know.
Well, but you know you got ripped off.
If you could remember it,
you'd know it wasn't any good.
Perhaps, Mr. Stang.
Oh, well, you know what?
Bob never made any sense,
but that was the charm of it.
Well, Mr. Stang,
it was an almost foolproof plan.
But I wouldn't do that.
You know why?
Because it would be wrong.
Mr. Stang.
Don't do that.
Prove you're Mr. Stang.
Word.
I made a million bucks
selling 5,000 pounds of hash to school kids.
Yes.
Now there's our Mr. Stang.
And they paid us, uh,
300 euros each
for a Jenkum lobotomy.
Can you believe it?
It was a pretty good deal.
300 euros is like 500 bucks.
The only problem was that
Ivan had skimmed 25 million bucks
from Spike Lee's operational account
to cover his stolen nuclear,
uh, materials.
Today, what?
How you find out about fish?
Getting real tired of you ducking me, man!
Halfway down the throat.
That's the best place to find out about a fish.
I want more money, man!
How does a fish feel to the mouth?
How does a fish taste?
How does a fish work?
Touch.
Sense.
Perceive.
Where's my money?
How does it relate?
How do you use it?
How do you find out?
You touch it.
You try to taste it.
You smell it.
You're relating to it.
She's fine.
Well, darling, you made a great try.
I don't remember beating me, punching me.
He wasn't really beating you.
He was just trying to execute you.
He didn't know how to do it right, so he had to, you know, use his fists.
If he had any brain, he would have just shot you, but...
A little bit at a time.
Who would ask for that?
You know you're my hero.
You're my hero.
And I know if I'll only be true to this glorious quest
That my heart will lie peaceful and calm when I'm laid to my rest
And the world will be better for this
That one man scorned and covered with scars
Still strove with his last ounce of courage
To reach the unreachable star
I'm not innocent.
You are.
I killed Bob.
Seekers, do you have what it takes to kill Bob when the time comes?
Well, the time's coming in one short week.
And if you'd like more information I want to do to save your yeti ass
When it all starts coming down
Turn to subgenius.com
There isn't time to mail anything
Oh, Bob, let it be this year
Let it be this year
Y'all smackers better figure out what y'all gonna do.
Oh Bob, I'm gonna kill you.