On the first side of this record, a self-analysis will help you control your extreme deviations with basic principles and suggested exercises while forcibly holding the buttocks muscles together to refrain from increasing the air pressure within the abdominal cavity.
It is important to breathe normally or to open the mouth to make this movement more difficult and to see how tight the buttocks can be, holding this twisted position to stretch the low back in the yoga anti-gravity position.
First, let gravity do the work by relaxing and lift the head slightly just enough to see the toes.
Keeping the buttocks muscles together, now very slowly lower the straight legs to the floor.
Then, over the head, upward to the ceiling, or as far upward as you can reach, let the head relax to the floor.
Efficiency in moving in anti-gravity depends upon the structure, proportion, flexibility, and strength of your buttocks.
Hi, I'm Mike Wallace with a sensational golden bob.
Oh, goody, goody.
This is Bob, the effective reliable way to natural male enhancement.
Bob is...
living large.
Bob is looking cool.
Some people don't understand the true nature of our activities and resent us.
Say hello to Bob.
Hello, my name is Mojaba and I was a Muslim.
I don't think making fun of religion is funny or clever.
You're going to love being a disciple of Bob.
We organize lots of social activities.
I think you know what I'm trying to say.
Oh, my God.
Wasn't that Stephanie from Accounts?
Not anymore.
Now she's a bride of the Dark Lord of Chaos.
You'll find plenty of opportunities for advancement with Bob.
I was supposed to be ritually sacrificed to Yogg-Sloggoth on the ziggurat of demonic tumult.
Hey, can you stand in for me?
There's more of us out there than you think.
Us?
Us.
The fraternity.
The brotherhood.
The cadre.
The alliance.
The fellowship.
The order.
The cabal.
The secret society.
For God's sakes.
I'd love to be a member, sir.
Why, I had an uncle who was a Shriner and that...
Good for him.
Let the portal open.
Let the initiate gaze upon the unspeakable glory of our Lord.
Keith.
John.
Paul.
Mark.
Ian.
Peter.
Andy.
Dan.
Jack.
Steve.
Alex.
Terry.
Howard.
Jimmy.
Enoch.
Barry.
Brian.
Jesus.
George.
Ezekiel.
Rashid.
Gareth.
Dick.
Mack.
Vic.
Larry.
Shirley.
Mo.
Blue.
Colin.
Barb.
Bar-bu-barb-bar-bu-bar-baarrggg ah theyee a hao-all opening.
A hole, if you will by the Bishop of New York City,istic senin'
It's a Bob special tonight, friends.
We need Bob- holy shit.
Dobbs in these troubled times.
And when we need more weird noises for this troubled show,
this time, not just the ubiquitous Fernanda Nande-Lemur,
but also many other weirdos from alt.binary slack.
James Watson, Champion Jack Codini,
Artemia Salina,
Reverend Jay Cobblestone,
New Monet,
Mr. Sister, and even, even Jarto, Jarto the New.
Plus, of course, ESO Swamp Radio from WCSB Cleveland.
And now, Lemur.
Excellent!
Oh, but wait.
It's really this year.
Not 2003.
And this isn't show number 883, but 1,883.
How did this happen?
Well, I've been busy with other things.
Accent on other.
But I have news about X-Day.
You know, this year, because our new regular best venue is moving temporarily,
it's a do-it-yourself X-Day.
Partly party in place,
or throw a big party at your place.
Partly virtual.
I'm doing a secret one here, probably.
But here's one you can attend.
Not in July, but the weekend of June 10th through 13th in Hannibal, New York.
An event being called The Real X-Day,
sponsored by The Senator.
Featuring Dr. Hal and Rubik's Cube,
and a whole slew of other bands.
I mean, like, a dozen bands.
You can find all the details at subgenius.com on the events page,
which basically gives you this link I'm about to give you.
Write down this link.
xday.ticketleap.com
slash 2022.
I'm going to do that again.
X-Day.com.
The URL is xday, four letters, no dash,
dot ticketleap.
That's ticket, L-E-A-P, one word,
dot com, slash 2022.
Or, like I say, the events page at subgenius.com has that same link under X-Day.
You can't miss it!
I wouldn't, but I have to.
Because they need me here.
I need to be here.
Men and things.
Anyway, it's a four-day gut blowout extravaganza
to loosen you up for the rupture.
And possibly for Bob.
Because what if he decides to take a fancy to you?
Bob!
Bond with that chicken.
I guess...
I guess that happens.
That's right.
I almost forgot a letter from Bob.
Bob seems to freely express his hostilities.
Bob refused to bathe.
He resists housework and cooking.
Everyone likes that little butthole.
Diagnosis?
Bob's a latent Bob.
A severe case.
What?
We will accept, Bob.
I know.
Attention, all humans!
Stand by for an important revelation!
Shut that back.
We've been getting in hot, guys.
Yeah, did not...
Number one show.
And when Bob showed up,
Network pulled the plug on our show.
Yeah!
They forgot all about us.
Hell, they left us out there to die.
I want you to tell me about the Bob.
The Bob will lead us all through heaven's chimney
in a giant cigar-shaped UFO-brand flying saucer.
Really?
So Bob is a special person.
But what can you say about he's an epic rattler recreate the
And to get substantial sino- hostage which just
That's all Bob could do.
But not just that BobJones presumed to be cool.
Because does 20 countries claim the
Power of energy aime happy بعد
You, detected!
In a giant cigar shaped UFO brand flying saucer
I repeat, this is not a drill, this is the apocalypse
Yo yeah, praise Bob!
Praise Bob!
The Bob has no ears
I repeat, this is not a drill, this is the apocalypse
In a giant cigar shaped UFO
Yo yeah, praise Bob!
Praise Bob indeed!
Praise Bob!
Will you give me a praise Bob?
Do I hear a praise Bob?
Praise Bob!
Praise Bob indeed!
Let's try this again
I want you to tell me about the Bob
The Bob will lead us all through heaven's chimney
In a giant cigar shaped UFO brand flying saucer
Really? So Bob is a special person?
Now open your mind!
Bob!
The Bob is not a person, the Bob is pure light and energy
Do I hear a praise Bob?
Praise Bob!
The Bob is not a person, the Bob is pure light and energy
Yo, fucker, you!
In a giant cigar shaped UFO brand flying saucer
I repeat, this is not a drill this is the apocalypse
Do I hear a praise Bob?
Praise Bob!
I repeat this is not a drill this is the apocalypse
Do I hear a praise Bob?
In a giant cigar shaped UFO
Praise Bob!
Ah, collage there by J. Watson.
And maybe, maybe, maybe...
Been one of those days.
I know all about it. Bob called me.
He has found it in that great, oversized heart of his to forgive.
Bob with a heart-bleeding sensitivity that he unfurls like a flag.
Because he's such a rather dull, quite uninspired, average-type guy with an appetite.
The kind of a guy that could be satisfied by a horse.
That's it. That's all of it.
Ask a sixth grader and they'll say,
Ask a seventh grader and they'll say,
Ob?
In sixth grade by seventh.
Be sure your kids know you want them to use drugs.
A message from the Partnership for a Free America.
Comrades.
The time has come.
Context.
For context.
What is the context?
The context is the first...
Nobody knows the context.
What is the context?
It's all relative.
Everything's relative.
Of course it is.
Space, time, space-time.
The Shifting Beach of Sands.
No, no. That is not true.
You said it was true!
It is not all relative.
It is relative.
You said life is a shift...
No, there is a baseline.
You said it.
No.
There is a baseline.
Beneath the beach.
It is Bob.
Bob is beneath the Shifting Beach of Sands.
Bob is the still center in the churning ocean of reality.
I think they buried his head in the sand and he can't get up.
Bob, J.R. Bob Dobbs is the unmoving...
I'm sorry.
...focus point around which all things revolve in time and space.
So he is the predetermined...
He is the baseline.
You can start your...
There is no revolution.
...revolution from that.
You can measure heat and cold from Bob.
You can measure small and large from Bob.
You can measure rich and poor.
With either a rectal or a patrous thermometer, of course you can.
Then what is Bob?
He's a neatly thermometerated object.
Something that we measure heat and vesicular time.
But a philosopher.
Well, he's a big nothing between two handsome bees, baby.
Two handsome bees?
He's a big whole nothing.
You have a collect call from...
Big Fitzwill?
Big...
Beep-a-Bah!
Hey, open that door up.
See if DJ Hayes is out there.
You have a collect call from...
Harry Balzania.
Beep-a-Bah!
No, baby...
You can'tということで with release...
Foot
These
of your television set to you.
That sounds like a lie to me.
A collage by Champion Jack Codini.
A face.
Floating just in front of her.
There is a beard and nose and eyes.
And there seems at first to be nothing above the eyes.
But now, as she gets used to the light, she sees a sort of...
Turban.
But it is a turban of brains.
The top part of the skull has been removed.
The brains bulge out.
She sees it twitch.
Kill it. Kill it.
Put it out of its pain.
The mouth is wide open.
And quite dry.
And she sees now it is not floating, but fixed up on a bracket.
Things hang from it.
No drills.
She thinks.
No tubes.
Rubber tubes.
Yes.
They lead into the wall.
And then, from its mouth, from its mouth, a puff of air.
It licks its lips, working its mouth.
Oh, Mr. Stump.
Oh, please.
I are a bandit.
It is no pain to bear.
She sways, dwegleth its씩 gazonit.
Nied me.
Did you risk margeing with that big freaking scab?
Oh, my dear.
Work you talk.
And this piece gets понадuspców affliction.
On germienye finally.
Bob.
Your friend wants you to smoke that wacky weed.
You don't know what to say.
Try this.
Thanks, man. I'm into that stuff.
Sponsored by the Partnership for a Free America.
Bob.
Well, I heard that even the Warhawks are all pissed at George, too.
Because they didn't do it quick enough.
Now he's, like, caught in between some weird, goofy place.
He can't figure out what to do or something.
He's damned if he doesn't. He's damned if he doesn't.
So everybody hates him now.
He was slapped by the mighty fish of street democracy, don't you think?
The Warhawks think he's a good guy.
He's a pussy, and the, you know, the peace lovers all want to stop him.
Yeah, the peace lovers are done with him.
They don't accept anything anymore.
If you hear them talk on the errant radio show where they get on, you know, and stuff,
where they get past the screen.
I've never heard one of those.
Well, they have one in Pittsburgh.
I'm getting tired of that.
This music makes me want to go to war.
I say let's nuke them all.
Everybody.
Music make me want to take P.O.T.
Tactical nuke.
In large, large amounts.
They erase all those lines on the map and just nuke everything.
Everything with land on it.
Kill Bob.
Bob.
We're going to kill Bob.
Kill Bob.
He's got a huge, huge.
So, here's the answer.
I mean, we're going to get into things that we know.
Up and down the gambit of mental health.
Mold, fungus, yeast.
Forgetfulness.
Post nasal drip, stuffy sinus.
Hay fever.
Pain behind the eye, pain in the forehead.
Irritation.
Respiratory problems, sinus congestion.
So think about it carefully.
Bronchial, sinus, asthma, wheezing.
Allergies.
Aggravation.
They'd had surgery, they'd had antibiotics.
Anxiety.
It was one thing or another and not the real root cause.
And I think a lot of people think about this.
Sort of head and neck stuffiness.
And particularly chronic sinus.
Mood alterations altogether.
And especially bronchitis and even asthma.
It's a huge problem.
A collage by a cobblestone.
American Ptix.
Sunday night, a conversation with Bill Clinton.
Only on C-SPAN's American Ptix.
We need to talk.
We need to stand by the boys.
That's right.
Yeah, actually.
Not too close because...
Stand by the boys going off to fight the war.
Some of them have wounds that go way back.
I want to go play in the USO show.
Where can I sign up?
I don't know.
I want to go play.
I got some nice coats.
You saw them nice outfits I got.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
I could go there with a couple of Playboy bunnies and...
USO.
I could be the MC for the Playboy bunny helicopter.
USO and Stanford unisexual or unicorn squacking orifice.
I want to go over there.
I want to go help.
Battle of the bands.
My mommy was played in the USO band.
She played the bass fiddle.
That's just true swear, a true lie.
They played this kind of crap.
You know, it's not just boys going over there.
There's some hot looking ladies.
Yeah, there's all these stories about all the...
They're married couples in the Gulf now.
Well, they've got toddlers over there, too.
Some of them are 300 pounds, 6 foot tall.
Chance, there was a lovely young teenage girl at last X-Day
named Reverend Lee Burles.
And she is now a Burley Marine.
Oh, wow.
She's now General Lee Scrooge.
Cool.
Look, a hot little...
I, General Jack C. Rippler.
How do you make a waif into Burley?
That's what I want.
Well, have you ever heard of purity of essence?
You know, what they're putting...
in our bodily fluids right now, it's...
It's methylone.
It's a methyl squalane.
I don't want to think about it.
What is it, pyrotechnics?
What do they put in your teeth?
Women want her essence, but she denies them.
This Friday and Saturday.
Beep, beep, beep.
Beep, beep.
People are rarely gregarious when constipated.
Boo!
Wow.
Well, in that case, I guess I'll just have to blow up the planet Earth.
Heh, heh.
We've launched a massive Hope for Nothing campaign here in America.
Grocery stores overflowing with every kind of boy and girl right here at home.
While you can walk down aisle after aisle selecting your baby for tonight's dinner or maybe tomorrow's breakfast.
You can enjoy the babies of this great nation.
But for millions of Americans, working through compassionate friends has made matters worse.
And this exceptionally harsh campaign is growing at an alarming rate.
Your gift of only two massive babies will support our missions all across America.
So please help your fellow Americans slip closer to the edge during this exceptionally compassionate harsh love of brutal Jesus Christ right here in America.
When you do, please don't call Jesus Christ.
Please don't let another child open the floodgates of God's blessing without brutal struggling in your land of abundance.
And let them know that Jesus loves them.
Every day.
200,000 pounds of babies.
Hope for nothing more than a dream.
But we're going to give them even more.
I love you.
Oh, skittin' through.
waste of the science
life
its
I can hear the jams starting to pump and pulse.
My feet are smiling.
Your knees are bouncing.
The biggest rave party on earth will not be taking place, not at Burning Man this year,
but Burning Man will be moved to its new destination.
Oh my God.
I rapped.
What a thought.
You could make a hell of a big man out there and really...
They're going to try and fry a lot of men, I think.
Rather than one big Burning Man, there's going to be a lot of Burning Men.
Oh, if only we could just restrict it to one great big man instead of many.
If only we could restrict it to a little child's fart we wouldn't have to pay attention to
rather than we must grieve the rest of our years from blowing up the world.
I mean, it's just that simple to me.
Are you trying to drag a little child's fart into this serious world?
Well, it cannot be this innocent little...
Does it need to be dragged?
Stang?
You who are so heartless, does it need to be dragged?
How easy.
Does it need to be dragged?
I mean, would you drag a child's fart or would you just let it waft in gently and happily?
Would you somehow try to suck it into the room?
No, I would enjoy it.
I would have a laugh.
I would think about it as what it is, a spark.
Have you been in a kindergarten classroom lately, have you?
I just left and that's why I'm so happy.
Look at these nipples.
I'm smiling inside.
I'm smiling inside now.
Little child farts are nothing to laugh at, man.
I'm not laughing.
I'm just happy.
Go visit an elementary school.
Go to elementary school and then tell me all about how wonderful little children's farts are, dude.
Chaz once remembered a long time ago in Gulf War I that George Bush Sr. sounds a little bit like Mr. Rogers.
And since they've eulogized Mr. Rogers as a non-sniper now and it's come out that he never really was a sniper, he was a music student and a piano teacher.
Yeah, that bums me out.
Well, it bummed George Bush out too because he's been referring to Sodom's Neighborhood all week.
And tonight was the culmination of...
You know, and I could just hear his dad saying it.
Bad neighborhood.
We're not going to do it.
Not going to do it.
Bad neighborhood.
No, it wouldn't be pro-dude.
Can he say good neighborhood?
No, he's not a good neighbor.
We're going to have to go get him.
You can't be my...
He's an axis of evil.
We're going to go get the bad man.
Now, I was reading an article in that liberal magazine, The Nation.
And they themselves, this particular writer was saying that despite what many liberal types think,
George is not a complete dunderhead wuss completely at the mercy of the people around him,
but in fact is a pretty bossy wuss.
And also that they're not faking with all that Jesus stuff.
No, I don't think they are.
They're not doing that just for show.
They're really...
Yeah, but his own real religion...
What's going on?
DJ, I came downstairs...
Lee.
Mee.
Mer.
And sumi eso.
Coming up friends, the sounds of Bigfoot.
That's right, Bigfoot.
From the record, the sounds of Bigfoot.
Here, Bigfoot expresses aggression.
Godless is Trump.
And do us.
Speak to us.
The nerve of God.
And we say, what?
What?
Isn't that too very soft?
Nothing.
What?
How do you know what?
You may ask God what?
And we say, we're darsening.
What?
Come on, say it again.
This ended us.
Guess what trouble?
What?
Are you the one with the
Come on.
Thanks to Mr. Sister.
Did you also hear...
That there is a place in Belgium called the Diamond Exchange or something like that.
Oh, yeah, we all know the Diamond Exchange, Chaz.
We're not ignorant.
Or the Diamond Suppository or something.
We all wear them.
It has 164 vaults.
And 164 vibrations per second.
A few days ago, somebody walked out with 123 of those vaults worth of diamonds.
And they have no idea how it happened.
Really?
Yes.
Belgium, the biggest diamond suppository in Belgium, Brussels, Belgium, where all the diamonds are.
Was looted a few nights ago.
It could be a crafty revolutionary act because Belgium is so involved with Europe.
And they cleaned it out.
They only left like 30 of them.
They were thinking ahead.
Belgium is close to Brussels.
It was the king of Belgium.
It was probably Leopold.
I have the key to this thing.
I'm Leopold IV and this is my freaking key.
If you need me, I will be in Jamaica.
In the vault.
Diamonds.
No, I think it was a revolutionary act.
Three, scene two.
Diamonds.
To break the bank of diamonds.
Diamonds and gold make an important suppository or vertebrae, if you will or won't.
Of the conspiracy.
Of the conspiracy because paper money is only created by banks to keep us knuckleheads down as we toil for wages.
Hey, look out.
It's worked great.
Well, it worked.
It worked for a while, but it never worked forever.
Once the masses arise, once the masses become aware of what the uber-slovers have done to us
and how we've been ployed upon and sacrificed.
We will rise up from our motley ashes and strike them down and resume our places ahead of the...
Man, I think the time for that came and went around the early 50s.
I thought it was 1917.
Well, there it is.
And there's Brittany doing her ESO, USO show over in Riyadh.
Oops.
Time for the game.
Hey, boys of the earth!
And the soldiers are erupting all over the sand.
That's sort of disgusting, actually.
One man has pulled out his Black Hawk helicopter and are taking him away.
Here comes the first wave of Apaches.
Her natural trill.
And here come the Navajos.
Not really ready to fly.
Looking for a good taco.
So if you were in the middle of the desert somewhere,
up about 300 feet close range,
would you rather have an Apache on you,
or would you rather have a Navajo?
They are the worst, worst battle cruiser in our helicopter forces.
The Navajos, they're slow.
They take a long time getting from point A to B,
and then they get there, they don't want to shoot anybody.
They never...
They ask them questions.
You learn a lot of them, man.
Try to get a taco within an hour.
Yeah.
You know, at a restaurant, down in the res.
And it comes out, and it's already cold,
and they look at you, and they want to talk about something.
You know, absolutely.
Hey, did you hear about that guy at Four Corners?
Yeah, it's like your taco.
Your burrito has been sitting on the counter in the back room
for about 40 minutes.
And then they fill them with bees sometimes.
Well, that's if they're doing the lariat dance.
They told me that.
That was an honor for the, you know, visitors and strangers.
They were inoculating you.
If you were going to be in the actual beaver jump dance,
they'd have to inoculate you.
They can't just let you go in there with a mouth like that,
staying for crying out loud.
They told me that wasn't the real beaver jump dance.
They said that was just something they do for the tourists.
Well, that's true, but, I mean, look at you.
I mean, you look like you've been smoking the wisdom teat all afternoon.
You think they're going to let you come into their cave
and hop around like that?
Oh, the wisdom teat.
Oh, to lick the wisdom.
Aye.
Oh, to smoke the frosty goat of hell.
Oh, to smell the bluey bilberry bush.
Yeah, forget the sick, sick, containing stuff.
I don't need that.
I can dig the goat of hell.
The frosty goat of hell.
Well, you know, you've got to have a little temperature change
going down there to lubricate and elastricate.
That's why they love that goat so much down there in hell.
Yeah, it is.
It's one bit of relief, but oh, such relief.
The love, the frosty love goat of hell.
Oh, look at the beautiful face on it now.
And look at the face on it.
It's like a lizard-headed man.
Mind your manners on level six of hell.
But I don't want to.
Level seven, going down.
I still don't want to.
Top and J's, fake churches.
What are you doing?
Unrealistic wars, sad economic ventures,
whacks of intelligence, and firefights with flies.
A Tomahawk cruise missile, man.
I want a Tomahawk cruise missile.
Level eight, stangly robots for underwear,
thermal soup, biotic sauces from the heart of the heart.
Plasticines, plasticines.
And re-aware, re-awareness kits.
Now here's what I hear the Lord saying.
I'm going to send nips, invertebrae, and a fibromyalgia.
In Jesus' name, in Jesus' name.
Now here's what I want you to do.
I want you to begin to bend and twist and turn.
I want you to examine yourself, examine yourself, and twist and turn.
Stretch your hands out toward me.
And you at home, just lay your hands up against my disc.
Herniated disc, a herniated disc.
Pain in Jesus' name.
Nips, invertebrae, in Jesus' name.
Pain in discs and vertebrae.
Tingling, numbness, nervousness.
Jesus, bend down and touch your discs and vertebrae.
I'm going to send vertebrae in Jesus' name.
I love...
Oh, God.
Oh.
Bob?
Oh, my God.
Pennsylvania up next. Go ahead.
Well, the...
Well, thanks a heap. Bye.
Bye.
More lemur.
And here, Bigfoot shows attention.
Attention.
Oh, yes, friends.
Oh, it's...
The ESO shows that we're playing were done before the shooting started.
But even then, Chaz wanted to move to Jamaica.
I can make a living more in the Caribbean than I could up here.
Well, everybody could.
Well, good.
The problem is nobody can make a living in the Caribbean.
There's plenty of orange juice and spleef, man,
but there's not too many, you know, gas and electricity bills.
Eat the oranges right off of the tree, man.
Yeah.
Eat the jerk chicken right off the chicken, man.
The coconut ball.
Hey, have you ever eaten jerk chicken right off the chicken?
Just jerk it right off, man.
Get your jacket of banana off.
Get your orange off of the tree.
The banana's foster, man.
You know, with the red stripes.
Tear your head off of your chicken.
Oh, man.
Smoking that frog.
How long have you waited by this piece of inactivating tissue?
Waiting for your last ride to the cosmos?
I was stuck somewhere.
I'm sorry.
I had to get that out.
It stunk.
It smelled bad.
I mean, but I was stuck in it.
You guys are stuttering.
I put in some island music and I think it threw you off.
Yeah, yeah.
It's a different rhythm.
You know, I was just...
I think for the first time in the history of ESO radio, there was almost quiet for a second.
It was almost quiet.
No, almost quiet.
I was just bobbing up and down on those waves.
It's almost soothing.
Yeah.
We were feeling the riptides pulling us out into the middle of the mid-Atlantic, you know, man.
Yeah, my salivary glands are...
I can't do this anymore.
I can't do the you know on because the orange juice starts pulping from the inside.
Look, just pretending you're some sort of a Jamaican...
Are you Bill O'Reilly or something?
Watch this.
...terrorist act at this point, Dave.
That's like owning a head shop.
It's like selling dope to little porno kids.
It's like owning your own head and pornographing little squids.
It's like...
Oh, no.
Now I'm getting turned on.
Oh, yeah.
Well, I can see that.
Big squids.
Wait, could you please...
This is quite visible.
...toss his coat over that thing?
Big squids.
The Jamaican arboreal squids have a poison...
...a poisonous sack that you have to remove before you sex them.
Wow.
Well, how come they're not going to Baghdad to use their mini-equipments?
I mean, you know, to fight in the fighting war for...
The fighting war.
The reptilian, you know, Jamaican...
The arboreal birds?
The tree squids?
Oh, the Jamaican guys who have that thing planted in them.
No.
Come on, kids.
We're having a communist party.
Can I come again?
No.
No, sir.
I am free.
Look at him.
It's picking time down south in Columbia, South America,
where a new industry is already showing signs of healthy progress.
Fifty million pounds are being harvested, the biggest crop in history.
Mother.
Mother?
Is Maxwell House really the only coffee in the world?
Well, your father says so.
And your father knows best.
Yes, it's father knows best.
Brought to you by Maxwell House.
Maxwell House.
Always good to drop.
Sir, why did Daddy switch to Postum?
Your father says there's no caffeine in Postum.
Nothing to spoil your sleep.
And your father knows best.
Yes, it's father knows best.
Brought to you by Instant Postum.
The good-tasting drink that's entirely caffeine.
It's...
It's outrageous.
That's what it is.
The most outrageous thing I've ever seen in my entire life.
Yes, dear.
Thank you.
It's a plot by the government.
Yes, father.
Thank you.
Look at Mucklucks.
Yes, father.
Thank you.
Devil Mucklucks.
Mucklucks.
Sainted by backward children.
My sister Kathleen and her family.
Yes, mother.
Thank you.
Father, they're simply dreaming.
You see?
You see that brother-in-law of yours shelling out Mucklucks, do you?
Yes, dear.
Thank you.
They tried to help put that brother...
Brother-in-law of yours away for Bud.
Bud.
No.
Yes, dear.
Thank you.
But...
Oh, gosh, Dad.
No.
Bud Watcher.
Cow, Kathy.
Kathy.
You know.
Yes.
It's a plot by the government.
Yes, dear.
Thank you.
Bud.
You just wait.
Just wait.
Bud.
Kathy.
Look, I don't want you to enjoy a healthy, normal life.
Why?
How do I...
Why now?
Well, you just said that...
I said I don't want you to enjoy a healthy, normal life.
Why not?
Because we have so many Mucklucks.
Yes, dear.
Thank you.
But, Pop...
We've got five bird records.
Father!
Oh, it's all right, dear.
It is not.
It's a plot by the government.
Yes, dear.
Thank you.
This family has to stop the simple things of life.
And we've got to stop the encyclopedia.
Yes, dear.
Is that so?
If I didn't go to Pop, this whole family would get warmer.
For Mucklucks.
Much warmer.
Dear.
We've got to realize that we aren't the Mucklucks.
And we've got to act that way.
Yes, dear.
Thank you.
We're just plain, simple, backward children.
We're just backward children.
For Mucklucks.
The family worked together to put some pot away for a rainy day.
This family lives in a continual potburst.
What, Bud?
Yes, Father.
It's a plot by the government.
Yes, dear.
Thank you.
Isn't that weird?
And then, plus, somebody in a mall got thrown out for having a...
Him and his kid had shirts on and said,
Give peace a chance and peace is pretty cool or something like that.
They bought it at the mall.
They bludgeoned him.
Yeah, they bought it at the mall.
They bought it at the mall and then the security cop said,
Look, we're against policy to have a troublemaking shirt.
Yeah, troublemaker.
Give peace a chance.
Look at that troublemaker.
Boom.
Man, I almost wore mine the other day.
Now, for all we know, this guy and his kid were walking around going,
you know, grabbing people and trying to preach at them.
Right, right.
Nobody liked it.
Now, hey, I was just wondering something.
Out of all the allegations of child endangering and sexual conduct with the church,
has there been even one of the cases where it was a nun having a lesbian thing
with a little girl?
There was just one.
In the Church of the Subgenius, we've been dogged.
I've got to admit, we have been dogged by the charlatan.
That would be really hot, man.
Tributism, rampant lesbianism in the nun snakes in Dobstown.
Yeah, what is it with any female that steps onto the Brushwood campsite on July 4th weekend
and immediately has to go have a lesbian experience in the hot tub?
Chaz wants to see somebody shed a bad habit.
And I think she's obsessed with the idea.
The power of Connie and her...
Her agents, such as Sister Decadence and Susie the floozy.
And he's powerful.
The rabbi.
You can smell it many miles away.
And so many of these babes.
And the power of suggestion.
You know, if you keep saying that enough, Chaz, it's actually...
The power of kitty litter.
What about if it was the other way around?
That would kind of be disgusting.
Well, that's like the year those guys came and crapped in the hot tub.
Yeah, that's an acquired taste, too.
Yeah.
What about the billy goat boys around the big bonfire that one night?
The Monkey Island night of...
Group sex in New York State.
Monkey Island, yeah.
Public crazed group sex around the bonfire.
Their sunglasses were melting in the heat.
One half was...
And nobody invited Chaz.
That was the funniest part of it.
I was emceeing the event.
What are you talking about?
He had one half of the crowd singing,
USA! USA!
And the other half was chanting,
Down, down, USA! Down, down, USA!
And the other half was going,
USA!
Down, down, USA!
No one was smart enough to play both sides.
So am I.
Alright.
And two groups time.
USA ceremony.
Time.
The sir and the baby.
We're happy.
I got肉 us going.
We're joining.
Cool.
Oh water no talks.
Ah qui.
white white white white paint black black gray paint paint light light dark dark dark sienna
dark sienna brown brown the happy paint thinner happy ink happy water happy little thinner
brown
isn't that neat
we're looking for sunny below me here deep in the sun sunny bono is dead well that's
that's not necessarily a good thing or a bad thing it's just like an ejaculation
sunny bono is dead bella lugosi is dead
bella lugosi's dead now he's not his son
copernicus is dead dave copernicus never existed chas it was a myth created by the
neoplatonists as well known the worst italians were fighting it out
digging it out with the neoplatonics the worst italians were mathematical whiz whiz
and the neoplatonists believed in love so the two of it got together and threw numbers and
spittled until the world was round again as they shaved the soft peach fuzz from the outside of it
and stared directly into its
glazed eyes
the truth became more clear than ever
the neoplatonists and the aristotelians
were a match made in heaven
i almost screamed at obscenity i almost said the f do do word as loud as i could at the end of that
it is after the hour that we sh**t wild
that is
could it ah i can only agree
he said that bad word
he said he came out of his mouth
he opened his mouth and said
he opened his mouth and he came right out of there
and here's another line
he opened that fleshy glutonous trap and out came ait
big bad bones
well we used to talk about wars
we used to talk about economic values
i was gonna say
dave i got a letter from from uh uh uh
a ee drunk
i'm moving into the jungle man
who said who implied that i didn't care about the war the up the non-existent upcoming war
ever-present war.
The debacle in that.
Because I
wasn't doing enough about it,
he said.
What should you do?
How could we build this?
I think you should sign up.
Sign up, line up, and re-enlist today.
That was your cry in the old days.
That was my cry. That was back
when I was younger than draft age.
And that's when you had
cut the soles off his shoes.
Now that I'm beyond draft age,
it is again my cry. Line up, sign up,
enlist today.
I believe you. I support you 100%.
I saw a feel-good story.
This is a wondrous
feel-good story.
We need feel-good stories.
Really?
You can tell us
a feel-good story.
I don't generally catch the news much,
and I don't have cable.
So I log on, and I think it's
ABC News or CBS.
Dan Rather. ABC News.
I think.
CBS News. I don't know. One of those two.
Well, anyway, you can look at their video archives.
They're conspiracy. Either way.
And I looked at one, and I saw
one of the video archives of a story
they just run about
a reunion in the desert.
The banana splits.
It was Dan Rather, the monkeys,
and a kid, a guy, who
something like nine years ago
stole Dan Rather's car.
Oh, I saw that. Dan embraced him,
and he got down on all fours and sucked his knee.
They had to turn him over.
Turn the camera off and resume.
Yeah, he was crying. You know, Dan Rather cries.
He weeps.
Kenneth is a weeper, especially when the frequencies are bad.
Mmm.
I heard, as I heard,
the noise of thunder.
One of the poor beasts sang.
Come and sing.
And I saw, and behold,
a white horse.
Hi.
You hungry?
Looking for a tempting treat?
Hold on till I absorb some yeast.
Uh-huh.
Some added tang might please you, too.
I'll slide into an oven-fresh bonnet.
Uh-huh.
Oh, yeah.
I'll take it.
Hey, Mom.
Yes, you.
Why fuss and fret about dinner?
Why not have it right here?
Yes, this drive-in offers everyone in the family
a real picnic treat for dinner.
We've got delicious sandwiches with all the trimmings
and your other dinner favorites,
plus whatever you want to drink, hot or cold.
Come early before the show starts
or eat while you're being entertained
or at intermission time.
So why fuss?
Give your family a tasty dinner at this drive-in.
Blessed is he who in the name of charity and goodwill
shepherds the weak through the valley of darkness,
for he is truly his brother's keeper
and the finder of lost children.
And I will strike down upon thee
with great vengeance
and great love.
And furious anger
those who attempt to poison
and destroy my brother.
And you will know my name
is the law
when I lay my vengeance upon thee.
And I will strike down upon thee
with great vengeance
Hail abnormal fortune,
all Gods of Hell,
so you can stand up with me at the moment occurring.
things we need to do,
or possibly not give,
Natomiast that's not the.
Pension Bimco.
And Jennifer says those tools are definitely those tools.
Now, do you know how to play Make Your Move?
No, I don't.
You put this under the two numbers and the price of the three numbers.
Under the four numbers.
Under the three numbers.
And the price of the two numbers.
Under the four numbers.
And the decorator bed.
Now you know how to play the game.
I put that under the three numbers of the...
That's right.
Check.
Three, four, three, two, four, two, three, four, four, three, two, four, two, three, four, three.
Okay.
Three, two, four.
Now, she says the tools of the decorator bed is right.
That's fascinating.
Level nine.
What do you want from life, George?
Oil.
What does George want from life?
George would like to be an innocent.
A bystander of his own ill works.
Well, there you have it.
The lonesome cowboy Dave himself.
He'd like to wash his hands of the whole thing.
He's sorry now.
Be able to go to sleep.
Without seeing the same dead faces.
I want my Apache helicopter.
That's what I want on a ride.
I'm out there in America's headquarters.
USA from the commander in chief all the way down to Mr. Wolfowitz.
And all the rest.
That'll come spelled and all the people that we count and rely on.
Sweet dreams, weirdos.
Take a deep breath.
Just take a deep breath and take that duct tape.
Take that duct tape.
Here's what you do.
Here's your survival plan, kid.
You go buy some plastic sheeting and some duct tape.
And you take a big piece of that plastic sheeting, wrap it around your head.
Take the duct tape.
Secure it.
And then you literally wrap that plastic sheeting around your neck so that you can no longer breathe.
And just smile and everything will be okay.
You won't get the bad germ.
Unless you bite through it.
That's like the instant bio shield.
You just take the plastic, wrap it around your head and take the duct tape and right around your neck.
Well that's how they were going to take care of Osama bin Laden.
They were going to take duct tape and plastic and smoke them out of those caves one by one.
Gonna make him a toga out of the plastic sheetings.
Togas, that's it.
Take your duct tape, kid.
And that plastic sheeting and fashion yourself a nice little toga.
Nothing on Elsa besides your plastic sheeting toga.
And walk down to the protest march down in public square and protest the war in your plastic...
Uh...
And duct tape toga.
Set yourself on fire, man!
I'm behind it, I'm behind it all the way!
You first!
Absolutely free.
Till next week, keep your hat on tight.
You're back to the wind and your sack in the saddle.
Run some cowboy d's.
Happy birthday princess we are doe.
The river and I them stand.
My name's Chad. See y'all.
These over here.
Canada Dry ginger ale for life is yours.
Cavity, and Pepsi, Cola, and 7up for life.
Cavities are all yours for the rest of your life.
Do you have any cavities for the rest of your life?
Kinda digging the rhythm.
Or you can have alcohol for the rest of your life.
Yes!
13 cases of Walker Special Canadian every day.
It's all yours.
Alcohol is up for the rest of your life.
Or, courtesy of Johnny Rodgers and the Sex Pistols,
the largest safety pin in the world.
This is all yours, courtesy of the two of you.
You have to decide now which one would you like.
Alcohol, the cavities, the safety pin, the coat,
or the fashion design gown.
It's a plot by the government.
Yes, dear.
Thank you.
True, each of us may have different ideas
as to what that future will be.
But every forward outlook reminds us
that all the highways of all research
and all communication,
all the activities of science,
lead to a future of science.
And that will lead us onward to better methods of doing things.
With new opportunities for employment
and better ways of living.
As we go on, determined to unfold
the constantly greater possibilities
of the world of tomorrow.
As we move more and more rapidly forward,
penetrating new horizons
in the spirit of science.
And the future of science.
As we go on, determined to unfold
the constantly greater possibilities
of the world of tomorrow.
As we move more and more rapidly forward,
penetrating new horizons