This is Doug Smith, radio operator.
I'm going to bring you a piece of that green cheese for sure.
I have the second!
No trouble.
Just get set and get going.
Hey, hit me.
Recording.
Everything's going fine.
No trouble.
Where are we, Rob?
The code is broken.
Trouble?
Big.
Security?
I have the lid on tight.
Well, take it off for me.
That's message here.
Mars needs women.
Mars needs...
It's a gag.
It's a prank.
It's a fake.
I don't think so, sir.
Bob?
The message is now part of and registered in your subconscious mind.
It will trigger the entire message without your being aware of it.
Welcome to the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Black.
Sponsored by the Church of the Subgenius.
This is Reverend Ivan Stang,
sacred scribe of the First Orthodox Megafist Temple Lodge of the Church of the Subgenius,
with Pastor Buck Naked of the First Naked Church of the Subgenius.
The opinions expressed are not necessarily those of this radio station.
For the sermon, a message concerning Bob Dobbs,
living avatar of slack and saint of sales on planet Earth.
Are we controlled by secret forces?
Do you ever get the feeling that free will is a joke?
Do people think you're strange?
Do you?
Then you may be on the right track.
Are you abnormal?
Then you are probably better than most people.
Yes!
You're kind of a joke.
And we feel the praise.
And we say the right thing.
Mother of the Subgenius.
By blowing them off.
Bob's promise is to widen the scope and nature of abnormal behavior,
to explore new ways of going over the edge,
and coming right back.
Plus, to bring back those who couldn't.
To help you create the highest possible earnings
from the psychodynamics of abnormality.
To turn conspiracy-implanted personality disorders around.
And channel them into an illusion of creativity
that will fool normals and get you sex.
Bob Dobbs!
Bob Dobs!
Ah, yes, dear friends.
This is Reverend Ivan Stang,
and this is the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
But, friends, I still haven't mounted.
I'm late to the radio station.
I still haven't.
I haven't made it to the station.
I'm broadcasting from this little remote mic,
and I'm trying to get everything packed up together
here at my house.
This is the Bulldada time control laboratory.
This little security system.
Shut down that little security system.
Turn off the fake revolving hand.
Oh, wait, I turned it on.
Get these things working right.
Oh, it's, well, you can't even see where I am.
These are the kitchens of the Bulldada time control
laboratories.
You can see the little soles on ice over here
that haven't yet been thawed out and prepared for the vast hole
in here.
And over here, we've got the slackless children
who've been cast out of the home for slackless children
because you didn't send in your donations to the station,
friend.
Look at these poor little children.
What do you have to say to the people, children?
My tooth is loose.
Like my favorite sleep now.
I got an ant bite to do.
A big old bump.
Right.
See, friends, these are truly slackless children.
And these kids, these ant bites and these little bumps,
and bruises.
Now, friend, you're not going to let these poor kids,
these are American kids.
You're not going to sit by and let these kids be in pain
and slacklessness, are you?
See, they all call me daddy.
Isn't that sweet?
These are only two of over 5,000 of them
because we have this amazing electronic babysitter here,
this handsome robot.
You can hear it talking.
See?
See, if you turn this amazing household robot on,
it will just sit and entertain the kids.
And they don't have to do anything.
You don't have to do anything.
It's a great time saving device only available
from the hour of slack, dear friends.
Listen to those kids laugh with joy in the background.
It's time to be manipulated.
Brother, I want to tell you something.
The world is tired of dead preachers.
Dead preachers preaching dead sermons to dead congregations.
They're tired of cold services and cold churches.
This world is hungry for reality.
They've had enough of Hollywood.
They've had enough of Nashville.
They've had enough of .
Okay, that was City Lights by Jimmy McGriff.
I'm going to turn it back on.
Gue uncertain.
The k potent.
We lazy Aktarianomie has hurry the
totasha of corruption.
That wake up call made yesterday,
we started it right when out there.
We started it at 10 a nd this morning, brethren.
That just kept going.
I met these guys that sleep down by the police station, and we...
That was a really cool parade for Bob.
I was surprised how many...
It seemed like every KON person was there.
I didn't know there were nearly that many Bob fans.
Indeed.
I noticed they didn't all have...
They weren't all...
They didn't have all their trucks fixed up like...
Like worshippers or whatever, but...
Oh, there we go.
So I was still editing this thing when...
In the car on the way here.
I just woke up.
I woke up outside the police station.
Oh, there we go, yeah.
You're outside.
Huh?
Oh, yeah, well, they...
A lot of the subgenius people sleep in the downtown area
around the police station.
So when they really get hungry,
they've always got a place to get a, you know, a meal.
I see.
Well, let me see.
Let's see if this thing here works.
It's hard to tell with some of these tapes.
These church tapes can't tell if the machine's broken
or it's the tape or the poltergeist or what.
You want to get here and talk real quick?
We can do this.
We can at least inform you.
Time control.
The ride's giving me...
He knows that a creative sale
is one in which the idea that leads to a purchase
generates in the mind of the salesman
before it does in the prospect's mind.
A variety of ingredients.
You can create an appetite in the prospective customer...
You don't see very many dead animals lying around.
Psst.
There are quite significantly altered...
Wood.
Boom.
, or they're destroyed.
Psst. Psst. Psst.
The lid's off.
It's gonna be louder beyond Ontario
than it's gonna be here.
Those sounds...
...are weird.
The NEW
Trash.
Spooky chefs are a bit mostly stern.
They've often thought that It'll never get to do anything before the next business.
But I can feel my legs feeling like I'mReagles.
Come on!
The Three找köping Advocate.
Hey, King, what's shaking?
My everything.
Oh, dear.
Come on, get up off that chair.
Follow me.
Ready?
Go!
The subgenius.
Our old subgenius.
Welcome, potential initiates.
I love you.
The subgenius hour of slack that you are about to listen to
is specially designed only to be played on radio station K-N-O-N
and only in the city of Dallas, Texas.
Here is your host, Reverend Ivan Stang, dear friends.
The sexiest man on earth.
A young Adonis who's irresistible to women.
I can't wait a moment longer.
I've got to have sex with you.
Now, sir.
Settling down, girls.
Oh, it's beautiful.
Beautiful.
The facilities are now enormous.
This is where the young composer feeds a fragment of it
into several tape recorders and gradually...
Gradually achieves slack, dear friends.
Oh, and the mighty K-N-O-N parade was wonderful.
I knew it wasn't really the Bob...
Oh!
Subgenius.
Rock.
Now, for the very first time...
Selling is not limited just to people called salesmen,
for we all have something to sell.
The doctor sells his patient.
The lawyer sells his jury.
The doctor sells his...
The pastor sells his son to the congregation.
The lover sells his love to his sweetheart.
The peanut vendor sells his peanuts.
We've got all kinds of...
Not to lose, really.
Yes, everyone selling together blends hearts and minds and spirits,
just as the musicians in an orchestra harmonize musical tones
to create a mighty symphony of prosperity.
Oh, praise sales.
And Bob?
Bob is the greatest salesman.
Symphony of prosperity.
The end times.
Now you can have this amazing new symphony
right in your own home.
This is Doug Smith, radio operator.
I'm gonna bring you a piece of that green cheese for sure.
This tape is copyright 1982.
82?
By the subgenius.
Foundation.
Yeah, sure.
That's what I call time control.
The Reverend Jaynor Hypercleets from Little Rock, Arkansas
tried to make it all a little clearer to me
with his own explanation of his conversion
into the church of the subgenius.
They said this jar was my mind
and then they poured it down a sink.
Run that by me again?
I don't know.
What do you mean?
They said your mind is in this jar
and then they poured it.
Down the sink.
Can you go into a little more detail?
Well, Bob is the original church
that sanctifies the worship
and launching of bodily parts of golfers.
The exes are the alien invaders
which come in a year.
I'm not sure what the year is.
We at What's Up America,
though not given to making predictions,
feel that the church of the subgenius
is surely the church of the future.
Well, Bob is a kind of total all-consuming sex.
He can create an appetite in the prospective customer
that isn't hungry.
That isn't hungry.
Ha ha ha ha ha!
The lover sells his love to his school.
Sweetheart.
For we all have something to sell.
Yes, and K-N-O-N has unfortunately had to stoop
to trying to sell itself to the federal government.
Can you believe that we're driven to have parades
to try to get support?
I mean, actually, the support's there.
We just had to prove that the support was there.
And friends, I think it was a beautiful thing.
It was a wonderful parade.
And we've got a live report on that.
That...
What was that?
How long am I gonna be in here?
That's a good question.
You wanna go home?
I mean, shoot.
Well, no, no.
Hey, I'll keep entertaining the masses, folks.
Well, let that guy.
Give me...
Okay, then I'll go home.
Dr. Gene Scott's time slot.
48 minutes.
Yeah, we have a new program on.
Excuse me?
Oh, yeah.
What time is it?
3 o'clock.
Friends, at 3 o'clock.
Oh, well, that's...
You know, that's a weird thing about this church,
this time-controlled doctrine.
It can really throw you.
And right now, we're gonna go to that parade.
Well, see, you know, if it wasn't for K&N
and most of y'all out there,
you wouldn't even have heard of Bob,
much less know who he is.
So we'll be kind of jumping back and forth again
if we can just maintain the continuum.
Doug, this is Guy Ponce after the parade.
That was fantastic.
I had to leave early, but it was a beautiful parade,
and I hope it does some good.
I just wanted to compliment you on it
if you were a co-organizer of that thing.
I love the way it was all lined out
in, like, boroughs of New York.
So, uh, good show.
Talk to you later. Bye.
Keep that child alive.
The operators of radio station K-N-O-N
are basking in a show of support tonight
from thousands of listeners.
That may or may not make any difference.
The FCC doesn't think K-N-O-N managers
should be operating the station
and have given the license to someone else.
The voice of the people.
The voice of the people
is what all these demonstrators call K-N-O-N radio.
To show their support for the community-run station,
at least 2,000 supporters staged a protest parade
stretching through the heart of downtown Dallas to City Hall.
The demonstrators were as diverse
as the programming on K-N-O-N.
We got your cowboys, we got your Indians,
we got your Solsters, your lowriders,
your, your, your black gospel people.
We've got everybody.
Tonight, the Christian radio station
run by the Criswell Center
that is taking over K-N-O-N's spot on the FM dial.
K-N-O-N supporters say their station
is doing a good job of serving the community.
And they're appealing the ruling that may silence K-N-O-N.
If the ruling goes against us,
it's amen for community radio.
K-N-O-N!
Ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay.
Whoo! Praise Bob!
Whoo!
Help me! My leg's gone far!
I ain't jammed! Got no leg!
Yes, dear friends,
this is Reverend Ivan Stang here,
waiting for the parade to begin.
The great K-N-O-N parade
in celebration of ourselves,
our cool selves,
those cool enough to march,
or crawl, or hobble,
or roll along in the mighty K-N-O-N parade.
Of course, the subgenius contingent,
flopping and stumbling along.
Actually, we haven't been able to do that yet.
We're still waiting.
Waiting, but for what?
Oh, there's the Batmobile.
The Batmobile finally made it over there.
In typical subgenius fashion,
the subgenius cars and trucks
are spread out completely randomly throughout the parade.
Most of us don't know where the other ones are.
And, uh...
Yeah, Stang sent me out to look for some of them,
and, well, a cop came by,
and he asked me what I was doing out here,
and I told him I was looking for a pickup on Harry Hines.
Fast, he almost arrested me.
Ha, ha, ha!
That was the voice of the Reverend Seyfaud,
who many of you would want to avoid
on a dark night.
But it's a sunny day.
We did the special rituals,
and I don't think it's gonna rain.
You can hear the ant band,
the tiny parade of K-N-O-N ants
going by in the background, practicing.
And, uh...
Oh, there's Batman.
Batman is here.
Oh, Batman, Batman,
could I bother you for a few words
to our radio listening audience?
Hell yeah, hell yeah.
I'm sure it's been a...
What kind of a week has it been
as far as crime fighting goes?
It's been a wild week.
There's been all kinds of wild accusations flying
here and there about, you know, the, uh...
What is it? KWBC throwing rotten eggs at all of us,
K-N-O-N-ers and so on.
So we called out the Bat Crew to make sure
that the Bible Institute didn't, you know,
throw rotten eggs at us.
Praise Bob.
But, uh...
Yes, friends?
And me and the male wonder, doing it again.
This is our, probably our fifth parade in Dallas.
I haven't seen, yeah,
I haven't seen the male wonder.
He must be...
He's probably squirming around somewhere.
Yeah, yeah.
If I know him.
Move it out.
Yeah.
And is he a male wonder?
You subgenius gals out there,
I will, you know, commit a few crimes
and get them to show up.
They'll teach you right from wrong.
Real quick.
Confidentially, I like men.
So, uh, any, can you, how about violence?
That's what our listeners want to hear,
is real bizarre violence stories.
As long as you're sincere about it.
Deformed, I am.
Deformed criminals that we haven't heard about
in the news yet.
We got, we got one we just caught.
We broke his arm off and put him in the trunk.
Oh.
And, uh, the Batmobile.
Is this a new deformed criminal or...
Yeah, this is newly deformed.
Right.
Oh, oh, so you deformed it.
We just got it.
We just got it back on the project.
You deformed it.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
I tore his arm off while Robin held him down.
Huh.
He's great.
And, uh, he should be in the trunk for the rest of the parade.
Oh, there's Reverend Belt.
Chastity Belt is here, of course, in the parade.
Yes, I'm glad to be here today.
Looking for a Kim Can, as I am.
Yes.
They've been...
You know, why didn't they have a truck, a flatbed truck, with a bunch of chemical toilets
on it?
I have thought of this as a potential offshoot of the, right, Reverend Chastity Belt, Church
of the Avenged Sword of the Lord Ministries.
And I may consider this soon.
Something a little different.
I mean, this is the first of my, you know, tax-deductible toilets.
You know, if we were true to Bob's word, we wouldn't...
We'd do like Bob, you see.
We'd walk through those construction sites, kicking the Kim Cans over, screaming at the
workers.
You're men.
You're mammals.
Why can't you just...
Why do you need to hide in a closet, he'd say.
I agree with this.
So many people in Plano and other areas must be just like that and living true to the word
of Bob, because they don't feel the need for Kim Cans just to...
Got one Story Only.
You never know what that is, yeah.
It's just too easy to lose.
We may use very short term prior to E parece hearts on the wages at 18 million or pr
7 and 20.
We're so honored to have you here in the parade here for KMOM.
That's right.
Batman was just telling me that you deformed a new criminal just this morning.
Pulled the arm off.
Got him in the trunk already.
Yeah.
We put one of those big arm stoppers on him over the stump where his arm used to be
so the blood wouldn't all ooze over the bat.
What did you do with the arm?
I just left it there in the street for the city crew.
Oh, yeah, the animal control or whatever.
Ivan's thanks.
I get you back.
Oh, it's Norm Ward?
Well, what happened to you?
How come you don't come in after the show to insult us?
I got fired.
You're still on Monday morning, aren't you?
I mean, Friday morning.
Friends at Norm Ward Friday morning.
The only talk show that...
That you'll ever listen to.
Because next Saturday is the end of the world.
And friends, dear friends, besides the Batman and so many other celebrities down there,
we're also dealing with a lot of...
There were just a few subgenius church old-timers.
Butt Naked was there and the Hell Swami Satellite Weavers.
As usual, the Hell Swami created some really wonderful graphics.
And so forth.
What is wrong with my monitor, my friends?
There's still...
Once again, we've got those creatures.
Yeah, there we go.
We had some fine graphic displays.
So did everybody else at all the shows.
So those of you who didn't make it, man, I pity.
I pity you.
Because there was a real motley crew down there.
As seen in this hidden FBI footage here.
A lot of new subgeniuses.
I'd actually been dreading that part of it.
Because, you know, there's so many bobbies about normally.
There really are.
And...
But what we had were real nice folks.
They looked real fierce.
You wouldn't want to meet Reverend Zaphod, for instance, anywhere.
In the get-up, he was in there.
He looked like Mad Max.
There's an Inquisition monk.
And where was Ann Leonard?
But it was beautiful, friends.
Just beautiful.
We're going to move here into less and less of what you knew you were going to hear.
Bob Dobbs is a sex god.
Oh, come on.
Get off of that.
Once he offers something far more powerful.
An excuse.
A divine, all-inclusive excuse.
Which allows the bearer to free...
Free himself from the grip of temptation by overindulging in it.
Until it releases him.
The true seeker must give himself up to temptation.
Or he will never conquer it.
The second rule of the church in the church is...
Two months is always better than not enough.
Can I get a two month?
No!
Let me always better than!
That's right.
I'm the king.
We give you...
A few weeks.
Even if you look, you would buy any shit.
What?
The sad, weekly self-denial preached by the New Age Movement is pure conspiracy pablum.
The true son or daughter of Bob knows that our universe is no laid back, Om chanting cosmos.
But an active, tumultuous, squirting universe.
Bent on rampant...
Reproduction and easy grins.
The false cults may try to teach personal transformation, psychic development, human potential.
But Bob goes straight for the glands and seeks to amplify the self to bloat the abnormality potential of his pupils.
Only through excess can one contact the lower self where the real decisions are made.
Don't just eat a hamburger.
Eat the hell out of it.
I am a man, as I said, that would do anything...
For Bob.
What's that you say, Bob?
Dang it all.
Bang my head against the floor.
Right now, Bob...
He'd kill himself for Bob.
I know I said that.
He would.
He'd kill himself.
That's gonna hurt, Bob.
Well, I didn't say I wasn't gonna do it now, did I, Bob?
All I said was that that was gonna hurt, Bob.
I didn't say I wasn't gonna do it.
I didn't say I was gonna...
Most people don't realize it, but they have a gland in their body, a body that's not
a man's.
It's a Bob gland, so to speak.
And these are the subgeniuses.
We're trying to find these people, let them know about their Bob glands so they can massage
it properly.
They need to exercise their abnormality potential.
This is what man is beginning to forget to do.
We're letting ourselves be led by nameless, faceless corporate entities, and we've got
to release the power of abnormality that we have.
The power that is in so many of us.
Really, it can't be explained in words.
We feel like bodily worship is the main mode of God and inner force.
How do you worship, Bob?
Like I was saying, Bob-ily, bodily worship, which would be something like...
Ah!
Bob!
If you're driving 60 hours, take a Bob.
Dog!
If you use your mutant powers, take a Bob.
If your blood is glowing as sugar, when you're picking a pumpkin, they shoot him with a lunas.
Take a Bob.
Dog!
Bi-a-tree!
Buy a tree and carve yourself a garden of peace.
I send the angel of the Lord.
I send right now power, the very glory of God into that home.
I move back the foul spirits of opposition, the lying spirits, the binding spirits.
I speak authority to you in the name of Jesus Christ.
Don't ask any questions.
Just do as I say.
All right?
We're pretty sure he's a psychopath.
Now, how do we spot him?
Well, if he's wearing a Napoleon hat, it's easy.
Otherwise, they come in all sizes and shapes.
11-year-old girls to 80-year-old men.
They all look perfectly normal.
I keep telling you all, this is a sick and perverted nation.
All tired.
And nobody wants to listen to me.
Nobody wants to hear about Bob.
Nobody.
I try to tell everybody what's going on.
They won't listen to me.
Well, to tell you the truth, I can't stand it anymore.
Bob.
Bob, take care of me.
Just do away with them all.
I don't want them anymore.
They'll be a problem and lose you to my mind after all.
They don't love you, Bob.
They don't love you like I do.
Oh, God.
But let's leave things of this world behind
and walk now down the path of Bob
for this brief minute of slack from the church of the subgenius.
Oh, yeah.
Yes, dear friends, this is Reverend Ivan Stang.
And I know some of my listeners are going to think I'm crazy
for what I'm about to say, but you know what?
I don't care, because I have slack.
And you don't even know what that is.
I've got Bob Dobbs in my life.
Bob Dobbs, the living avatar of slack.
So I know I'll be safe on the pleasure vessels
of the sex goddesses from Planet X
when that day of judgment comes.
Ah, yes, and you unbelievers
will fry in a hell of your own making.
And how do I know this?
Why am I so sure?
Because I have slack.
I have faith, my friend.
Faith in Bob.
You don't use your mind to think about your religion.
Nay, nay, you let that Bob signal from space
beam straight into your skull,
unfettered by your stupid notions
of good or evil or job or free will.
For the word of Bob is a direct word.
It is not written in some roundabout symbolic manner.
You don't try to figure out what it means, my friend.
You just do what it says.
Because Bob said it, I believed it,
and that settles it.
Let there be slack.
Uh huh.
Everything's safe.
Get outside, exercise, and take a bath.
YShowers
Oh, take a bath
our
Fukimono
All and VGO
all análès
allalala
lalalala lalalalala lalalalala
You cannot run from your own legs.
There's not a man or woman in here tonight who can run from their own legs.
Is there what you're using to run from a whip or how you gonna run from your own legs?
You cannot run from your own legs. You cannot hide from this man, J.R. Bob Dock.
You cannot hide from this guy, cause he's bigger than you, he's bigger than all infinity, he's bigger than the universe.
Oh, help me somebody, shake out your legs. My legs are on fire, freak.
You cannot see your own eyes. What are you gonna do, turn them inside out?
Oh, what the hell was that?
Who makes the rules?
If someone asks,
I'll tell you.
The advanced initiate, once freed from conspiracy programming as well as the worldly goods that enslaved him,
makes his pilgrimage to Dobstown, the church's fabulous walled encampment deep in the jungles of Malaysia.
There, the initiate's third nostril is surgically opened by psychic surgeons,
allowing him or her to whiff-read the psychic stench of those around him.
He masters the sciences of schizophreniatrics and memory editing, creating a clean slate on which Bob may write.
The purging is at last at hand. The day of doom is here.
All that is evil, all that have eyes, are blind.
Your parents, your leaders, those who would call themselves your judges, those who have lied and corrupted the earth, they shall all be cleansed.
In your hand, you hold my light, the gleam in the eye of set.
This flame will burn away the darkness, burn you away to paradise.
The light of the dark will burn you away to paradise.
And here another view of beautiful Dobstown, and the treatment that the initiate receives at the hands of Bob Dobbs and his chosen teachers.
My child, you have come to me, my son.
For who now is your father if it is not me?
Who gave you the will to live?
I am the wellspring from which you flow.
When I am gone, you will have never been.
What will your world be without me?
My son.
The end.
Extra meditation thus taught, whereby the mind is voided upon the great throne of relief.
You dont use your mind to think about your religion.
Bob is a very special kind of religious leader.
Bob is a short duration personal savior.
Yes children, Bob will be the savior.
In your heart, and in your mind, and in your mind, and in your heart, and in your mind.
God wants you to take him into your checkbook.
But after you've taken him into those sacred places,
God wants you to think about him, consider him, and then cast him out!
God wants you to make your own religion, your own rules.
...of what he calls short-duration personal saviors.
Now they will know why they are afraid of the dark.
It is foolish and cowardly to cling to any one personal savior.
The hectic pace of modern life demands disposable saviors,
specific ones suited to the moment at hand.
A sort of while-you-wait-do-it-yourself religion.
Now you're sure to understand the meaning of anything from a book you're reading,
to a smudge on the corner of a page of that book,
to a TV star you're currently enamored of,
to a brick that just misses crushing your skull
as it falls from the cornice of a rotting tree.
To the coagulated, dripping neck-stuff of a decapitated World Cup golfer.
And it can last anywhere from a nanosecond to your entire lifetime!
And you can have one or ten or millions of short-duration per-savs
concurrently, consecutively, and simultaneously.
Don't let the fact that Bob is a white man fool you.
His church truly spans the globe and embraces all races,
creeds, and several sexes.
Some undiscovered.
The subgenius race is the master race because it comes in all colors,
all sexes, all shapes.
And there's three sexes, by the way.
You know it.
Mmmmmm...
Bob is a rock.
Bob is a tree.
Come on, sing along!
Bob is a you.
And Bob is me.
For the deaf people, please look to the stage right.
Bob is rich.
Bob is poor.
Bob is a window.
And Bob is a door.
We're gonna pick it up a little bit.
Bob is the sun.
Bob is the rain.
Bob is my tongue.
And Bob is my brain.
Welcome to the End Times.
In today's End Time essay, we will be covering the difference between
the Goprofram and the Bloodyhead Launcher Society itself.
As seen here in our first slide, the Bloodyhead Launcher Society goes on forever.
There is no end, and there's no use resisting.
.
. .
I hate when they say that your calls you're sitting in bed my calls right yes
dear friend let's hear it from the book of Larry hello really loud way up I give
it up of my own free will I have the right to give it up and I have the right
to take it back this is what Bob has commanded me to do
oh I got there sharing that with us that was real good I like that sucker and uh
you ready for the soul sucker now now now remember you don't want to get
sucked entirely into this machine so okay that you want to start howling if I
get too much into you okay you ready
dear friends those are the things I want to tell you about today
you
the very many things the things that Bob know the things that you know and when
you know that you know it because everybody does have that plan that
mystical Bob land in their feet that one that tells them what to do if they'd
only think with it but somewhere along in the past man got confused and decided
to start thinking with his brain and when that happened oh dear friends that
was a very sad time in the history of man because when man
stands on his brain and thanks with his feet then he'll know exactly which way to
go and how to find mob you got a massage that foot gland and he only way to
massage it is to walk on it yes t dinner friend you gotta walk on the foot spicy
because when you're walking and bob talks and you'll know all you need to
know about what to do after the holocaust after the i
lier
army
come and take us and give us all them giant pills
and all them fantastic machines that's supposed to run our lives
and that big white stone that everybody's going to know personally
in their very own home.
Ah, yes, dear friends, that stone, that's the stone.
That's the stone that you think you might know
and you think might help you.
But by God's dear friends,
that's the stone that's going to ruin your very lives.
You think you know who Big Brother is?
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Dear friends, I want to tell you that you don't know.
You don't know nothing.
Come on, do it.
Those UFOs, they're flying all over your house.
That's right, then they know about bomb.
And they're going to be dropping them.
Doctor.
We interrupt this program for a special promotional announcement.
We got a buzz box and we're going to use it.
Come on, baby, and do the locomotion with me.
Are you rocking that cats and kitties?
If you want to do the locomotion in Dallas,
where have you got to listen to the hottest stations?
Yes, sir.
On the planet Earth.
KNOA 90.9 FM.
Monday night, 7 to 9 PM.
We got Elmo, Latex, and Kelly from the hip.
Tuesday, 7 to 9 PM.
We got Tim Hibbs and Brave New Radio.
Tuesday nights, 11 to midnight.
Jeff Webb's Vital Hour, a feature hour on a vital artist each week.
Wednesday nights, 7 to 9 PM.
It's Charlie, don't park an owl with Who Cares?
And Wednesday night, 11 till 2 AM.
Jeff Liles is bringing it to you, man.
He's telling you.
He's telling you that life is hard.
Let me clear my throat!
And then Thursday night, 7 till 9 PM.
We got Jeff Webb doing Offbeat.
Friday night, 7 to 9 PM.
Kenny, Deep, Freeze, Folly, and Paul Supron
bringing you music from the underground.
Late night, Friday night, 1 till 4 AM.
Anatomic and Ordre doing Radio Lobotomy.
Saturday, 2 to 5 PM.
In the afternoon, Mr. Brad Sigler doing Dig That Groove.
Saturday night, 9 to midnight.
Shaggy's Pajama Party.
And then Saturday midnight to 2.
Ari and Terry, a brand new show, Radio Freeboro.
Saturday night, 2 till 4 AM.
The only heavy metal show in the area, Electroplex.
It's Mr. Jerry Ward.
On K&N Wind, the only place for rock and roll in Dallas, Boatway.
She likes to rock.
Doesn't have to rock.
Can you guess who's rockin'?
We asked treatments down at World of Rocker Expo
in Del Hoyo.
Andke Harми in St. Louis,
and 100,000 people decided to show of her music.
Randall Brodsky in Baltimore dramas.
Lizzy Hagan, Michael Edwards in labor.
Robin Fle蛆laj, and pretender Problem Letters.
How did Moxie trays darkness
show love?
you it was free it was free maybe it's maybe it's sort of the conspiracies guilt trip on you
to that you didn't pay for the speaker and maybe they're trying to suck all the slack out of the
show so maybe i think you ought to go down to your local uh church of sound warehousing
and make a donation i'm desperate for slack i am addicted have you ever sent any money to us
the church yes well like i plan to well can we just take it out of you in seoul can we just take
it out of you in seoul as long as it doesn't hurt if it hurts would you are you will you scream i
will scream all right well let's try it
freeze bob
who
help me somebody help me my leg are on fire copyright 1986 jenner hypercons
well we've got some uh great looking we've got all of the official subgenius altar pieces that
haven't been stolen over the years the six foot bob head and the the wings of slack and
the uh well that's that's from the rio bisbee band that's some guys in maine that flag of the
wings of slack used to be on the back of a motorboat
and it's
an ironic symbol of how pathetic time control is until we have bob back because it's almost
completely falling apart with the fe spray tearing away at the you know when the clock
dissolves in the middle of it that'll be it i read something in the bible about that
you know just the bible's got all the same stuff that books the subgenius it's just older more
you know fancy language well it's you know it's just old people and they're the ones that need it
This is violent and, you know, lewd.
But it's got all those Middle Eastern idioms, you know.
Yeah.
Huuuh! Huuuh!
Listen to those mighty huuhs!
Now, you know, that actually started out as
Huuuuh!
And it gradually got perverted over the years into this...
Well, it's better than I think.
St. James Brown started that?
You don't what?
End up with a sore throat.
You're right. You're right.
Well, but, you know, if you do it enough, you don't get a sore throat.
You get lightheaded.
You talk like...
Yeah.
But that's... No, that's good.
Lightheadedness is good.
Well, as you can tell, friends, the, uh...
It took a while for the parade to get started up.
So we had a sort of a miniature sub...
Ha!
Miniature subgenius convention going on there.
...getting the Batmobiles started.
Could you come over and lay your hands on the battery?
Hey, the way I do healings, I can't do them in public.
Okay?
Whoa!
And I don't believe that exhaust pipe has got enough diameter to it to work on that thing.
So lay it on, but the hands aren't necessary.
Yeah.
Now, Chastity Bell is really...
She's a good healer of appliances.
See, we had Dr. Drummond was here all...
Hey, Zandy!
Watch out.
Don't drop the ray gun on that Bob face.
And damage the ray gun.
Look, they're starting to move up there.
I bet they're...
I better grab my...
Oh, take up the cross.
Friends, I've got a giant, heavy wooden cross here with the six-foot bobs taped to the back.
Ah, yes, dear friends.
This is the hour of slack.
Now, you know how you do that?
You go, this is the subgenius radio ministry.
Our almost...
Almost...
And it is, dear friends, on KNO and 90.9 FM in Dallas, Texas.
The only station that inflicts the word of Bob and the church of the subgenius on you.
This is your host, Reverend Ivan Stang.
And it was a...
But the parade gathered in momentum.
I'll tell you, I can't imagine what the people along the street watching this conversation...
Could go by.
Could it...
I mean, there were all these outlandish, Mardi Gras-type groups going by.
And then along would come the subgeniuses.
And it was sort of like Exodus.
You know, it was...
It was astounding.
It was inspirational.
These mystical emblems on poles carrying flags and pictures of this man with a pipe and dots all over his face.
The face of Bob Dobbs.
His hair pompadoured back.
A modern guru.
A modern leader for us all.
A symbol of the freedom and the slack for which we mutants pray.
And it was a great parade.
Even little kids were in it.
I brought my X and XY unit.
People by the road.
Some laughed.
Some stared blankly in incomprehension.
And a few unsavables rolled their eyes and sneered like they thought we must be the most hopeless juvenile fools.
And we are friends, among other things.
But they'd never understand the freedom it takes to be able to know Bob.
For they're...
And they're...
It's their poor blinkered idea of being...
Mature.
Huh.
Hey, grow up, man.
Like, this Bob stuff is stupid.
Why don't you get into Washington, Dallas Cowboys like everybody else?
Friends!
We don't care if it's Bob.
Bob himself doesn't care if you worship him.
You might as well be worshipping Dan or Bill.
Praise Bill.
Or Spider-Man.
If it gives you slack, then great.
If you really have slack, my friends, you're a soldier for Bob Dobbs.
Whether you mean to be or not.
Ah, yes.
So the parade moved out.
The awe-inspiring face of Bob striking fear into the hearts of the lawyers who, for mere money, would make us have to raise more money ourselves come the pledge drive.
In one hour, dear friends.
The pledge drive starts.
Now, next week will be our pledge drive show.
And you better be ready for it.
Dr. Zaphod, St. Frazier, praise St. Frazier.
The mighty Cecilia are all gonna be here answering your phone calls, your pledges, your pleads.
And they'll be healing you over the phone.
So now's the time to give to KNON.
But preferably in the name of the hour of slack.
Come on.
Because that helps show that we have support.
So we won't be replaced by some other show that can claim to be more relevant to the community.
More relevant.
What could be more relevant, dear friends, than the word of Bob Dobbs?
Yeah, I've got two more reels of tape hanging off of me.
Oh my gosh, that microphone is dangling in an unseemly way.
I really shouldn't do that.
I'm asking for it.
I have microphones hanging off of me.
And this one, it actually doesn't do me justice.
You're in a critical position.
Yeah.
Are you sure it's staying?
I just wanted to shake your hand.
Howdy.
Oh, are you a member or a...
I'm not your listener right now.
I've been thinking about joining.
Well, thinking ain't enough, my friend.
That's right.
Without that membership card in your pocket, you don't know what's gonna happen.
I'm gonna tell you what's gonna happen to you come next day.
But I just wanted to shake your hand.
Hope that all this does real well.
Yeah, I hope we get our license back.
Well, it's not gone yet.
They'll appeal for a couple of years.
But the problem is that they'll have to pay for the appeals.
So they won't be able to go to 100,000?
Right.
The whole problem is, you know, it's like the judge is mad because they haven't gone to 100,000 watts.
And the reason they haven't gone to 100,000 watts
is because they had to spend all their money on lawyers.
Well, as you can hear, the parade participants are getting very impatient to start.
We're already almost 45 minutes late in getting a move on here with this parade.
Now, some people are walking forward.
Oh, marching to the slaughterhouse.
Start to move out.
Now, you guys remember to wave that bob head around.
I'll hold it up.
And you've got your little green pipe down.
Daddy's here.
Oh, no thanks.
He's trying to cut down.
We ought to be in front of the gospel group.
Yeah.
We are gospel.
We are the only good news.
It's a full slack gospel.
Actually, well, their gospel is fairly, it's about a three-quarters slack gospel.
They're not, I like the gospel.
Last time I was up by the front, they weren't making enough noise.
In my opinion.
Well, they're more solemn, you know.
They're more solemn.
That's true.
They take the suffering path, the suffering path of the crybaby Jesus.
No, no, no, no.
I don't think the Kano and gospel folks do because they're black Christians.
And they're more like, they like to hoot and holler and have fun and, you know, praise the Lord.
As opposed to your, you know, more standard mainstream guys that are all real solemn.
The generic Christians.
Yeah, the generic ones are, they don't know how to have fun.
But the gospel people do.
You know, I mean, I don't understand how they can believe in some dead guy on a stick instead of a guy with dots all over his face like we do.
I just don't understand that.
Well, I mean, that's such an irrational belief.
A dead guy on a stick, right?
It's sort of like launching a, you know.
A head or something.
Well, it's like launching a Carol Burnett.
Or a Sam Snead head.
It didn't make any sense.
No, no.
You know, there's an Arnold Palmer head and yet they launch a, you know, Jack Nicklaus head.
What's the point?
What the heck is the penguin doing in the Batmobile?
You guys.
And the questioner.
We had Batburgers for lunch.
That guy is drunk with his Bat beer and now we don't know what we're drinking.
Oh, man.
Oh, God.
I was hoping you guys could stay off the Bat beer.
At least for the duration of the parade.
We all have our own crossings, Barry, you know.
Yeah, right.
Look at that.
The Batarang's all beat up.
Got beer stains all over it.
We're ashamed of you.
We're ashamed.
Well, Batman and Robin are all beat up.
There's little kids.
There's little kids that look up to you superheroes and super villains as role models.
I'm tired of being a role model.
I'm tired of it.
I just want to kick some booty.
Excuse me.
Oh, we're finally, finally the subgenius death march from Dallas to San Francisco.
The fourth annual subgenius death march.
If five or six of us are left when we finally make it there, then we win.
Then all who died win also.
Yeah.
I think so.
Nev Reedy started the death march.
With Star, Todd, and Dan.
And he's lived through all of them so far.
All the death marches.
All the parade ones.
Yeah.
But boy, they throw a hell of a dock stock festival at the end of everyone who ever is left.
And friends, I wonder as we subgeniuses struggle along here, what these people think.
They're thinking, this looks like some sort of a religious group they're thinking.
They're carrying crosses and mystic symbols, but they don't recognize the guy hanging on
the cross, you know?
Yeah.
It's like when did Jesus get back haircut and smoke a pipe?
Three pills.
One part of the conspiracy would like you to believe in the little, cute, squatty aliens.
The Spielbergian aliens who'll come to save us all.
Oh, they'll come just in time before the conspiracy pushes the button.
You'll be too loud to have them on your side.
Because at least there's two arms and two legs.
It could be worse.
It could be much worse.
Three amorphous, hideous things glide up upon reality.
You'll be lucky to get that.
At least that's something you can puke at.
Something you can throw up over.
Something you can run in fear away from.
What if it's something you can't run away from because you can't see and it's everywhere?
Something just like the conspiracy is.
God, what you gonna...
Are you just gonna sit there?
They won't even have to do it.
Bob won't even have to see the day the world happens properly.
It'll happen by accident.
The exes have landed.
Earth's under their control.
Bob's vision stands proven.
The city's radioactive holes.
We don't know what their game is.
But their name is...
Unpronounceable.
Monsters like a true man will be around thee all night.
And shall make thee to look past the door which should be locked.
And thy silences will terrify thee and bring thee naught but devils.
For thy spirit is locked away inside the wild stern.
But thou shalt not see which man is in some great firm's space.
Their machines following our tracks.
Bob's vision stands proven.
A world without slack.
But what is the commodity with which Bob will bargain Earth's future?
Some claim it is the souls of his followers.
The true subgenius does not question Bob's wisdom in such matters.
We have only our simple faith that heaven will be ours if we only believe.
Ironically, his mission will not be to sell Earth but to prevent Earth being sold and transformed into a kind of Stuckeys in space.
Don't forget that Bob is...
Has come to, uh...
has prophesied the end of the world by July 5, 1998...
When most Americans will have hangovers, but it's not just for the Americans.
It's for everyone in the world.
Right. That is...
that is why...
Yeah, start smokin', start drinkin', and live it up.
Start fornicating as if your very life depended on it.
I'm speaking to you in the old calendar year, 1981...
which we refer to as 17BX.
BX before the excess before the excess land this is true all the signs of are
already in place and Bob has come to us to make sure the end of the world
happens but this plan will succeed only if only if dear friends that you get
ready for that pledge drive that thing starts in an hour oh ten minutes yeah
ten minutes now oh oh the wrong script once again and boy this is probably the
most important one you know I've we've before been able to sort of have fun
with the pledge drives and and we will this time but I mean this is getting
really serious as you heard a little earlier it's like this the this station
has has been
under severe constraints that cost a lot of money legally and we're gonna stay
on that's not with their people have misunderstood that you know this was we
only had a couple of weeks or something we've probably got a year or two as long
as they can pay for the legal fees all this stuff happens in Washington not in
Dallas and in Washington they don't you there aren't very many canoen fans they
don't know
that much about it and thus we do things like the parade which was really
intended to get some some media attention that that might some echo of
which might make it all the way up to the mighty courts in Washington but I
need to get on with this live report from the parade
Bob money sex
Bob money sex free pills
free pills
I want like lightning straight down the
You know if you get hit with this if you get hit on the head by this cross I'm carrying the Bob cross and you get a cut on your head then that's good because oh we gotta run okay come on
Oh my gosh
Hey
Howdy
Nice to meet you I'm a pink infiltrator
Oh my gosh
It's true
A pink infiltrator?
Yeah it's true
I'm surprised they ever gave that you all ever gave us enough credence to even bother to infiltrate I mean
Well what it is is I got tired of chasing communists and types where I had to be secret about it
Yeah
And I applied for some kind of a job where I didn't have to be secret about it where I could come and say that I was infiltrating and they said that you guys were in so that's why I'm here
Oh okay well as long as
You guys
Well I don't I don't I guess there's nothing you know nothing you could tell them that they would want to hear or would believe
Yeah I think they might actually be trying to get me off their back you know give me a foolish assignment just to keep me away from them
You sound like you probably ought to just you know convert to Bob and you know renounce your pinkness
Well
Although no one can really do that exactly but they can if they think they do then they usually write us checks
Oh yeah?
Yeah
So you see it's at least
Well I wrote you
You know within the hypocrisy you know within the limitation of hypocrisy it's very honest sort of church
Oh yeah?
Yeah
I want a picture
Computer generated
Tell me something actually I have to write a report tonight what should I tell them?
Oh for who?
I don't know
Oh for the
For them
It's a conspiracy
Oh tell them that this appears to be a threat to human peace and sanity and it's like
I don't know
It's like undoubtedly is the one world religion prophesied in the bible and it's
Okay
You know that it's not a bunch of sort of silly teenagers
Uh huh
Guys that ever grew up but it's
I see
You know like Jim Jones, Charlie Manson kind of serious
Okay
And you know you definitely saw people under the influence of mind control and those that had minds
Okay alright I will thank you for the guidance on that
Sure sure
Who helped me?
Somebody
Well there's some Bob-Bites over on the side
I got it on the tape
Huh?
Oh thank you okay Captain Sun Sunson has brought a new donation of audio tape we can use on
the show it's in a ball but Bob can play this kind of thing back just by holding it up to
his temple
Daddy next time it stops I'm going to run and hop in the back
Okay
You know those serious looking liberals back there behind the Bob truck look kind of they don't
They don't look like they're having as much fun
Daddy
Oh
Get in place get in place
Don't jump don't jump
Oh my gosh the questioner is climbing up the side of a building here at St. Paul and Munger
Batman and Robin are pursuing him they're in hot pursuit but oh my gosh Batman is not in the shape he used to be
He's obviously out of shape the Riddler is out of shape too
He's about to get away from him easily the Riddler went in one window Batman followed him now the Riddler is coming out the other window
But right into the arms of Robin who is so plastered from drinking his bat beer if that's what it really is that oh my gosh and the Riddler easily out distances
Oh there goes the Batarang friends oh it doesn't even return to it
It returns
Yeah after the questioner threw it
Questioner
That's not the Riddler it's the questioner
He's evil because he goes around to people and questions whether their job is meaningful and stuff
Where did the truck go?
I'm being stupid
They're watching Batman and Robin and the subgenius truck went way ahead of us and that's one more example of why Bob didn't call it the church of the genius
This I think we're just about if on camera one it looks like coming around the corner here
And just about to go by the back side of the first Baptist church which was just a coincidence
I couldn't believe it there was there was a you know I don't think anybody was worried about exactly but there were a few you know six or seven nice pink type folks with grins on their faces and looking very friendly to us really
But surrounding them were a bunch of hired security guys with guns armed guards dear friends to protect those men who were in danger of being killed by the cops
And I think that's what we're trying to do here is to protect those servants of the Lord from the evil dangerous and even sometimes dark skinned K-N-O-N fanatics
You know I'm not I don't know what they thought we were gonna do like bomb their abortion clinics or something
There must be some shit we can do
The one who kicked out the demons from this building
Praise Bob
We've had good
They will eat them and grow strong
ordan
Yes, Nunu loves me!
My Brooklyn tells me so!
Who is this Nunu of whom they speak?
You must not speak of me, Nunu.
Surely not the ancient sex goddess of antiquity?
The one they call the Venus of Willendorf?
Known by other names? The obese ancient
180 year old woman of fertility?
Surely not! Surely not that one!
Buck is heavy in the Nunu. That's why he gets around.
Well maybe I ought to carry this thing.
I was carrying this bob across with a giant,
giant bob stuck on the back. Nothing blasphemous meant here.
It was strictly a...
The whole world is watching!
It was strictly an allegorical sort of thing.
I mean, the money changers are in the temple, friends, as far as I'm concerned.
He feeds the false churches!
Give us not these false flags! Give us not these Mercedes!
Give us not yet ye television stations!
Oh good, what it says there, it says full house, but Bob will give it to you straight!
True Bob!
Nothing but aces with Bob!
Well we're walking by the first Baptist church parking lot, dear friends!
Praise Bob!
There are some...
Six aces!
Two out of the sleeve!
They're nice folks.
I'm sure they're...
I'm stumbling by here with this,
with this, uh,
Bob crucified.
I'll get it. No, no, no, no, no.
I have to carry it, it's the effect, the martyr effect.
I'm doing this on purpose.
I'm walking like our Lord Jesus did when he had to carry the cross.
Like Bob did, our Lord Bob did when he had to carry his briefcase.
All the way across Manhattan.
This is where I got my doctor's badge, isn't it?
Where's my...
my child? Oh, there.
Oh.
Well, he's... that was a very, uh, actually sort of an anticlimactic moment passing the first Baptist church enemy of K-N-O-N.
Because, uh, they weren't...
No one yelled, no one was rude to each other.
We yelled,
praise Bob, and they prayed.
And Bob prayed on them.
Those are just Bob's words.
You know Bob's words.
Bob, Bob,
oh no, now I have to run again with this.
Oh my God, this huge Bob head is acting like a...
a kite!
It's like a hand glider!
I'm 20 feet over the street,
I can't believe...
Oh, let me down, that was incredible.
I got you on the rope.
Listen, if we could drive a little faster, I could stay suspended with that kind of wind.
Yeah, we thought that might work.
Yeah.
I never showed up.
Oh, Batman and...
Batman, he's angry.
I just like building that
edifice of spewing hatred!
One more time,
I'm gonna puke!
He... Batman just said, if I...
Speaking of the first Baptist church, if I
pass that... that what
edifice of spewing hatred...
I'll puke.
But he's got that mask on, you know,
that's quite a sacrifice.
Batman...
Yeah.
Oh, I bet that's it.
Slack, sex, Bob! Slack, sex, Bob!
Slack, sex, Bob!
Pilled!
You know this is true! Those puns, they will fester,
they will kill, they will cause
horrible nasty absences
if you don't let them go, if you don't let them
out of your body, if you don't spout
those horrible puns and horrible
nasty riddles and jokes, they will
kill you, kill that other
soul within you.
I think he... I think he's been getting him
some Bob pills.
Bob!
The passers-by, they mock
us, they stone us!
Run with Bob! Run with Bob and take
pictures of it! Friends, this...
the weight...
I feel the weight of Bob's
face, every dot,
every dot seems like it
weighs a ton.
And I believe,
Mr. Stang, Dr. Stang,
Professor Stang,
that every dot does in fact
constitute a universe
within the realm of Bob's
power. And they all
weigh like a 10 billion dwarf
stars. That's right. They're all
black holes. They all weigh
what a black hole does. They all signify
what black holes signify.
Every dot of Bob
will suck in
everything else in the universe.
And the only reason that anyone
given one doesn't is because
of the proximity to each other.
They negate
each other's pull.
That's right. That's right.
Oh! Oh my gosh!
My microphone swinging
obscenely at my lap!
I can't believe it!
Bob is coming!
The end is near!
Bob is coming! Get him a towel!
And Bob comes
again and again
to justify
your sins, my friend!
To rationalize
your sins!
To teach you to live with your sins,
brothers and sisters!
Live with your sins!
But why, Bob? Why am I doing this?
Why do I give myself
leg cramps?
Why am I floating your hideous head
miles and miles
in front of unheeding,
unwhiting
passers-by?
Oh my gosh!
There it is!
City Hall!
It's within sight!
And there I will get upon this cross.
My hands will be scotch-tape
to this cross.
They'll nail me up!
And they'll nail me up!
Just as
the evil false churches
would nail K-N-O-N up!
They're riding out of
the proper air!
You can make it stink!
Come on! The last few minutes
you've been via Dolorosa!
I don't know!
Oh my God!
It's just a few inches more
and then they'll kill me!
Oh! Oh!
Why are we stopping? I want to die!
I finally see
Bob! I understand
now! Kill me!
Kill me!
Now I know
what... Now I know what slack is!
Nail me up!
K-N-O-N almost killed him!
Killed him!
Wait, wait, wait! That N-O-N isn't sanctified!
The laying on of the
putting herbs!
Oh! Oh! Oh!
Oh! Oh!
Oh!
My Bob! My Bob!
Why hast thou forsaken me?
Oh!
Bob!
Woo!
You really look pretty!
Come on!
Yeah, I wish I had some, uh,
some toothpaste
so I could look like I was slobbering.
Woo!
Oh!
Here,
City Hall
for the money changers.
Gathering of the Horde.
Stop stand!
I thought it was a myth!
A joke!
Oh, God!
Figures!
Eugh!
We made it!
Dr. Spade, we made it!
Do I get to die now?
Yeah! Is the show over?
Is this the end of the show?
Wait a minute, Slade! We're about to do the
cassette over! No!
No, kill me first!
I can't stand another 90 minutes to this!
Contemplate this
on the Tree of Woe.
Crucify him.
Dinner for wolves?
Ha ha ha!
What gods
do you pray to?
I pray to the four winds.
And you?
To Plum.
But I seldom pray to him.
He doesn't listen.
Ha ha ha!
What good is he then?
Eugh!
It's just as I've always said.
He's strong.
If I die, I have to go before him.
And he will ask me,
what is the riddle of steel?
If I don't know it,
he will cast me out of Valhalla
and laugh at me.
That's Plum.
Strong on his mountain.
Eugh! My god is greater.
Ha ha!
Plum laughs at your four winds.
He laughs from his mountain.
My god is stronger.
He is the everlasting sky.
Your god lives underneath him.
Eugh!
This is KNON 90.9 FM
in Dallas, Texas.
Fire and wind come from the sky.
Eugh!
From the gods of the sky.
But Krum is your god.
Krum, and he lives in the earth.
Once giants lived in the earth.
Kronan.
And in the darkness of chaos,
they fooled Krum.
And they took from him the enigma of steel.
Krum was angered.
And the earth shook.
And fire and wind struck down these giants.
And they threw their bodies in the sea.
And the waters.
But in their rage,
the gods forgot the secret of steel
and left it on the battlefield.
And we who found it
are just men.
Not gods.
Not giants.
Just men.
And the secret of steel
has always carried with it a mystery.
You must learn to understand
its riddle, Kronan.
You must learn its discipline.
For no one,
no one in this world
can you trust.
Not men. Not women.
Not beasts.
This you can trust.
This, son.
This image of J.R.
Bob Dobbs.
And this radio station.
Ah, yes.
Well, friends,
I have one last request.
If you were there at the, um,
at the parade,
subgenius believer or not,
if you have any good 35mm photos
of the, uh,
subgenius section with the giant bob head,
or especially any
videotape, I can really use that.
And you could either drop it in my box
at the station here
on San Jacinto, or you could mail it
along with your request
for information about the
church at the subgenius.
To P.O. Box
This is, this isn't, I'm not about
to read the station's box.
This is the subgenius post office box.
Uh, P.O. Box
You got that?
Dallas, Texas
Or, uh, I suppose
you could call me right now
8237490
You know, the pledge drive
is about to happen,
folks, and there,
once again, I cannot stress
strongly enough
just how important
it is
to your eardrums,
to your hearts and minds,
to be able to, you know,
people who, um,
uh, who listen to the show a lot
and don't listen to what's going on on the internet,
and the other stations.
You don't know how lucky you are.
You really don't.
It's, it's money.
It was funny, at the parade, one of,
I brought my two test tube babies
to the K&ON parade, and one of them,
young Idnax, got so fired up
that he actually spouted a new
church motto, which is unusual for him,
because he, normally he's a
heretic against Bob.
My own son, he thinks Bob's just
a big face with dots.
He believes in Santa Claus, but not Bob.
Yet he comes up with some concise
wisdom. It's funny, Bob
always speaks most clearly
through those who respect him least
and mock him most.
But, uh, he said,
he said, Daddy, I got a new
line. Don't take money, take Bob.
The whole crowd started chanting it.
And other, other cults might say it's better
to give than to receive, but in Bob's
philosophy, see, it's better
to take than to receive.
That's a subtle difference, but
I was proud of my boy there.
You oughta see how us original
apostles treat Bob. The more we do
for him, the more we have to
abuse him and insult him, and otherwise
we'd fall into the same trap
that all other great world religions
fall into. Now,
a little earlier, somebody called and said,
once again, we keep,
every show it seems like, I get a call from somebody
who says, why are you doing this?
It's like, it's not that they don't
get it, or at least
they get it, sort of, but they don't really,
they're not listening enough to realize.
And they were upset, because
they thought we were, you know, mocking Jesus.
Friends, if
you listen, if you
really listen, and I don't mean,
you know, skim the radio, but
if you listen to what we're saying, we never
mock Jesus,
or even
Buddha, or
you know, any, any of
the great teachers and bringers of
slack. We sometimes even
paraphrase them.
But we do, we do
mock those who we think
have perverted
the sweet names
of these leaders, who, most
of whom, in fact, almost all of whom,
are not only Bob's drinking buddies,
but they all said, more or less,
that the mutants shall inherit the earth.
They said that
it was okay
if something was different, if it
wasn't just like you,
you should treat it as if it was
your, you know, like
you would want it to treat you.
And, uh,
I don't know anybody here who tried to close
down anybody else's radio stations.
And yet, somehow, we're expected to
turn the other cheek,
you know, you're gonna get the other cheek
slapped if it, you're turning it
to somebody who claims
to be, I don't know,
I don't wanna, God,
this makes me so mad, I'd get to,
I'd get to cussing again.
Uh, let me see what else I had
here. It was,
it was wonderful.
It was a great parade,
and I wanna see,
you know, I think it ought to be a yearly event.
Uh, if any of you all missed it,
you know, watch it,
come to it next time.
Oh, oh,
Ron finally made it!
Ron Lindsey is here.
We'll get out of here with just one last,
uh, brief
message, I think.
Let me see, no,
we can't,
Conan's been running back there for a while.
You let me know,
Ron. Friends,
thanks a lot
for supporting the station,
and thanks a lot for calling in your pledges
to Ron Lindsey as in the
hour, er, several hours
coming up. I want you to,
to do that now, you know, I want,
I also want you to pledge the hour of slack,
okay? You got me?
Just right at the appointed time.
Otherwise, dark forces
of antiquity
will be
coming at you.
So, I'm gonna
get you back in time.
And I will
take you
home.
I'm gonna
take you home.
take you home,
baby.
Get me home soon,
but I ain't gonna
alone, bat.
I'm just gonna
stay here
forever and dong
you know?
And all those legends about him really not being dead,
those are not true.
The girls know they can't get Bob.
Because all these people are saying,
but Bob isn't dead, he's going to come back.
And I just want you to know,
we were time-scratching over the same exact moment of time
over and over again,
and both of us were convinced, firmly convinced,
in the one bullet, one assassin theory,
and that that moment was the real moment,
and Bob was dead.
Because we saw it over and over again.
We saw him fall.
We rewound the scratch, you know?
We went back in the time disk a little bit,
and then we ran over it again,
and he fell down again,
and then we run it back,
and then he falls back up,
but then you run it forward again,
and he falls down every time.
We tried everything we could
to stop the moment from happening,
but the security was so tight that night,
we...
We...
None of our passes could get us behind the doors there,
and it was just impossible.
Nothing...
Nothing we can do in the past or the future
is going to alter the fact that Bob was shot that night.
Bob is dead now,
and there's not a damn thing we can do about it.
Now, I've been dooming and glooming all over the place,
depressing all my friends.
They're all saying,
Reverend Bleepo, there's something wrong with you.
You're not your happy chipper self anymore.
And I look at them, and I say,
it was all going fine till that moment,
to that irrational moment in time
that just...
just plain shouldn't have happened.
Because...
All the people that are there,
that were there back there then,
that are now in the future,
that know what's happening,
that have time control,
none of them did anything to stop it.
And I want to know,
what has Reverend Stang got to do with this conspiracy?
No, no, no, wait.
Now, wait.
You may say,
Stang, oh, he couldn't do nothing.
He's...
He's in charge of this radio show.
He's the one responsible for putting my words over there
and all that over there.
But, friends,
that's completely impossible.
You say, yeah, well,
what about, like,
Johnson and the JFK assassination?
You ever ask yourself that?
Sure, sure.
You know,
mourning for the world and all that.
Now, let's be frank here, folks.
Now, I'm not saying Lyndon Baines was a bad man,
but Lyndon Baines was a powerful man.
Lyndon Baines was a man who could withstand pain.
Who's to know what kind of strange hypnosis
he underwent with them...
with them hypno-demons
back when he visited that flying saucer
on that Air Force base in 57 with Eisenhower.
Yeah, he was the senator that was there that day.
He was supposedly standing there
watching the whole damn thing.
Well, if you ask me,
those aliens just hypnotized him,
took him both aboard the spaceship there
and, of course,
erased part of the mind
and then put it back
and then made them forget
that they could ever remember it,
which just, you know,
makes the whole subconscious drive
to do the insane thing even stronger.
I love those aliens.
You gotta love those aliens.
Anyway, I mean,
you gotta admire them, let's say.
Maybe you can't exactly embrace them
with what we call love.
You know, sort of...
I can't go into that right now.
But anyway,
so, at any rate,
so what I'm just saying there is,
you know, it's entirely possible.
Now, please,
I don't want any lawsuits or nothing.
This is just a theory.
I'm purporting.
I'm not saying this is true.
But, you know, it's just possible
Lyndon Baines and, you know,
his friends there,
they, you know,
what if he was easier to fool?
Hell, Lyndon Baines Johnson
was the only president
that ever gave Bob a hard time.
We were watching this.
If you look over at magazine advertisements
between the 1950s and the 1970s,
you take a look at the time.
You know, the advertisements
from, you know,
63 through 68
when Johnson was still president there.
You look at the pictures of Bob
and he has stress on his face.
That's because Johnson
was the only president
that gave Bob a hard time.
He got right along with Eisenhower.
He got right along with Kennedy.
He got right along with Nixon.
All the way on up.
Well, we can't talk about that.
But, anyway, he's still there.
Yep.
But, you know,
what I'm saying is
Johnson was the one man
who would not let himself
be hypnotized by Bob.
Or at least knowingly.
Knowingly.
So, I'm just saying
it's entirely possible
this could all be a...
This could be...
Well, I have to say that
for legal FCC reasons.
This could be all part
of the same damn thing.
Anyway, I just wanted to express this
at this time.
So, I want all of you out there,
you know, who feel any ambiguity
towards Reverend Stang
to make up your minds.
Is he guilty or innocent?
And even if he isn't
either of the above,
who is he anyway?
I'm getting scared.
I better get out of here.
He's gonna do something strange.
I can tell.
No, Reverend Stang,
don't put that tape eraser down.