Good evening fellow necro-mediacs. I'm glad so many of you could come.
I'm Harvey Mews, ladies and gentlemen.
And could you see our colleague here?
He's a real creep.
I want to give you a friend of mine.
I'm sorry, good friend of mine.
I think you know who I am, but I don't know.
I don't know who I am.
What was your name, sir?
A desired outcome of the aircraft motion.
Do you fucking understand me, you fucking piece of shit?
I don't know who I am.
But let's leave things of this world behind and walk now down the path of Bob for this
brief minute of slack from the church of the subgenius.
Ah yes, dear friends, this is Reverend Ivan Stang.
Hey, you know those policemen on motorcycles won't let me preach on car hoods downtown
because they think I'm a crazy man or a drunk man.
And there's no reason to arrest me, yet they would, because I'm free, free, free enough
to rant to myself in public because I come against death, taxes, work, and premature
immaculation.
For Bob, your mind, friend, your mind has to be certified okay by them, them, them,
and oh we hate them, they and their tools of iniquity.
Not the tools of the preacher, not the tongue nor the other parts, nay, but tools of false
slack dangled forever in front of you like that raise right around the corner or like
that rat.
Swimming in poison cheese.
Let there be slack.
I'm going to Godstown, Godstown, here I come.
They got some crazy little Godsheds staring up and gonna get me and I'm gonna get my ass
in the back of their car, I'm gonna get my ass in the back of their car.
Why did you let your daughter dream of going on this mad moon journey?
Because I love her and I wanted to live to the best effect.
Dragging out life to the last possible second is not living to the best effect.
The best of life, passwordly, lies nearest to the edge of death.
Our fathers and our fathers' fathers cleaned up the old order of things because it killed
death because it tormented people in vain because it outraced human pride and dignity because it was
an ugly spectacle of waste but that was only a beginning there's nothing wrong in suffering
if you suffer for a purpose our revolution didn't abolish danger or death it simply made danger and
death worthwhile we must hold this crowd back at any cost for a time until the gas of peace is
ready i seem to done toilet on your floor
right right right
right
you'll wonder where your teeth went when you brush your teeth with
and i think uh i disagree with chairman bob uh i do agree with the chairman bob
the chairman bob can't be working
i recall that chairman bob went that route right right i think the thing things are the thing uh
uh
and i think i'm some and i think in essence the chairman bob can't be working while they're type
alive to investors
uh we've uh uh uh viewed and so forth but uh
how to close down the law.
But now, one final question, if I could.
Anybody on the panel who'd want to address Chairman Bob?
No.
Okay.
When you're alone and life is making you lonely,
you can always go down.
When you've got worries, all the noise and the hurry
seems to help go down.
So go down.
Maybe you know some little places to go down.
Forget all your cares, so go down, down, down.
So maybe I'll see you there.
We can go down, down, down.
Bum, bum, bum, bum, bum.
Bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum.
Bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum.
Bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum.
Ah, yes, dear friends,
some wonderful edits and credits
by the great Fernanda Nande-Lemur.
Except for the very last one,
which was from Dr. Mr. Sister
here in Cleveland.
Yes, aside from that, all the rest
was by the great Fernanda Nande-Lemur.
All those cut-ups, anyway.
Our title tune, The Hour of Slack,
is by El Queso All-Stars.
And the very opening was by Heart Ignition.
More from him.
But first, this fantabulous rant
by the old-time Dr. Dr. Dinosaur.
What kind of savior do you want?
You want something exciting in a deified being?
Or do you want a completely predetermined cosmology
with static and stable and sedentary
gods and demons?
Or do you want a whole bunch of gods
hanging off of it like apples
still stuck on a tree in January?
Are you looking to get carried away
on that sweet chariot?
Or are you afraid that there won't be
any difference between it and the boxcars
that will unload at the gates
of the eternal concentration camp?
Will you settle for a holy order
that's all order?
Or are you hankering for a chance
to put in a few licks yourself
in the timeless struggle between good and evil?
Unless you're ready to let your soul,
your soul, roll over and die before it's even
had a chance to prove itself on the field of holy battle,
it seems to me that you might want to think
about making a choice.
Are you going to throw in with the likes of Satan
when you know, you know from the book
that he loses in the end?
We may pull the wool over our own eyes,
but that doesn't mean we're stupid.
We may go in for the underdog, but we don't place
no bets after the cards have been shown.
And even though he wins just before the credits roll,
credits with only his name on them, by the way,
are you going to sign up for the Yahweh team
when you know the outcome?
Hell, everybody likes to win,
but only after they get to play the game.
You can turn a buck betting on a sure thing,
but where's the slack in that?
Now we got the fightin' Jesus, but we got the fightin' Jesus.
That hardcore three-nailed money changer-ass
kickin' Aramaic rowdy, and that's fun for a while.
But he ends up selling your account to Yahweh,
and you still get shortchanged on the action
and thrills you crave in a belief system.
Well, kids, I think you know what the answer is.
The answer is the ever-widening smoke ring
around J.R. Bob Dobbs.
Yes, only Dobbs, among all the modern mythological
people in the world, is the one who's going to win.
And the guy who's going to win is the one who's going to die.
strong, magical madmen represents the uncertainty,
the dramatic tension, the screaming scary monster
movie mayhem that keeps your heart a-thumpin'
and your blood a-pumpin' while you sit on the edge
of your pew waitin' to find out how this movie turns out.
Where do the big spenders, the high rollers,
make their fortunes?
Do they toss their bankrolls into long-term IRAs
and deposit certificates and play it safe?
Hell no!
they dare to risk it and play the market and that's the kind of Savior Bob is
children Bob is the Wall Street Savior we may know the saucers are coming but
we don't know what the outcome will be we know Bob can cut deals with human
governments and overlords and Illuminati and rake in the cash from that but we
don't know yet whether he'll be able to close the deal that will keep the exes
from just plowing us all under as a bad crop we don't know if we'll ride the
saucers as exalted examples of Yeti evolution or as fertilizer for some
planet where they intend to try again if you want true adventure in your eternal
future if you want a little havoc with your heaven if you can stand a little
mystification in your destiny and there's only one personal
Savior that will satisfy your soul's fighting spirit and that is JR Bob Dobbs
dr. dinosaur dear friends in a classic old-timey racket now
rift
I
I peaked in the Devils secret hell files and found a list with names a mile long
and saw you and you and you and you and even you and me and the whole thing
You! Let me close my eyes!
Please don't make me watch Satan masturbate!
He's a hungry clown and I don't want to see all his dirty deeds!
Oh, why God, oh, why did those assholes at the employment agency
give me this job cleaning up this office?
Oh, why, somebody tell me already!
Was this the best they could do on such short notice?
Am I being punished for overeating and using too many cuss words?
Or is it for sounding too much like some pale, cheap imitation of Captain Beatheart?
Or am I too much like Frank Zappa?
Am I being punished for not cutting enough people off on the freeway?
Or for answering my phone messages?
Oh, why, God, oh, why did those assholes at the employment agency
put me here where I don't belong?
When they could have gotten me a job telling the hot dogs
instead of idiots at Disneyland?
Were they afraid I'd put the old laser by erection?
Did they have suspected that I'm a urinate through the cosmos
at the top of Space Mountain?
Oh, why, somebody tell me already!
Oh, why, God, oh, why did those assholes at the employment agency
inform me early about the hatred call?
I would have worn my fat man's pajamas
with the air conditioning back in the year.
I would have worn my fat man's pajamas with the air conditioning back in the year.
You dress your suits.
What are you doing here?
Who is that?
Who's there?
It is I, Zooks Rift.
It is I!
Get a fucking job!
It's you!
How the fuck?
Wait a minute.
This can't be what...
You're dead!
Be cool, dude.
That's right.
I'm dead.
I'm dead because you killed me, Zooks Rift.
Because you and your slug musician friends
beat me up and killed me.
You're dead because you killed me.
Oh, man.
Don't I have enough problems?
What is it you want, oh great spirit?
You want to complain to me that you're in hell, I suppose.
That you're dead and have gone straight to fucking hell
for driving like a fucking idiot on the freeway,
giving me the wrong change of jack-in-the-box,
playing that heavy metal shit on your stereo at 3.30 in the morning
when we're all trying to sleep?
Ah!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Ah ha ha ha ha!
No, Zooks Rift!
No!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Sending me junk mail, trying to entice me into wasting my money
on boring, inane magazines,
charging me over a thousand dollars at the Chevron station
for preventive maintenance while all the while
deliberately destroying my car...
Ah!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
No way, dude!
Ah ha ha ha ha!
For going through life talking like a blabbering, snobbering idiot,
driving your van to the beach during spring,
bring break with a sign painted on the side that says,
Show us your teeth!
No!
I said, no!
Zooks Rift, they didn't even hold it against me
for being a booker in several Los Angeles rock clubs,
or for getting all the pussy while guys like John Truby
were stuck with their shit jobs at the hardware stores.
Well then, what are you talking about there?
I'm in heaven, Zooks Rift!
That's right, you killed me, and I went to heaven,
glorious, beautiful heaven!
But you, Zooks Rift, it's you that are in hell!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
You fucked up!
Ha ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
No!
Yes!
You're in hell, and now you'll burn out!
No!
We'll teach you to send back those readers,
digest sweepstakes and trees,
in a no!
Zooks Rift.
Ah, yes.
Ah, friends, and let's change the tone now
and go back to WCSB Cleveland's Thursday night show,
ESO Swamp Radio,
with Professor Chaz Smith,
Lonesome Cowboy Dave,
and us.
Me and we!
Mommy, Daddy.
And another sound.
And the attic lock melted.
Mink.
Mink with bright little eyes and tousled hair
peered inside.
And behind her,
tall, wavering eyes.
Frightful.
Darling.
Thanks andHeeky signed this.
To the gallery.
reporters 110 times gave the tower the coldest
Fang here you are.
Let me show my good things
And my name is Dave,
Raven heads and their one good eye pointed firmly above their master eyes.
They charged forwards.
Some were bleeding on their feet.
Some were bleeding at the ears from the ranting and raving they had been forced to hear.
Some's navels were smiling, that austere yet abstruse smile.
Reserved for the few who knew their fate.
My ears are bleeding!
And they just keep trudging.
Looks real good from that shot up in the hills there.
Is that a dolly shot or is that a... what is that?
Just turn around.
Hey man, you're not supposed to show your watches.
It's 1392. People don't wear watches in 1392.
The time is 13-0-13.
Do you know where your smell dawned twice?
It's time.
Can you feel more premium?
Are your breasts as ripe as the milkmaids dancing through the forest glen?
Are you enslaved to time, handcuffed by your wristwatch?
Is your lust for material things insatiable?
Do you have a streebly long, funny-looking forefinger?
I'm gonna blow their loads in the last minute before the CD is formatted.
I'm alone!
Two minutes takes forever when you're waiting for it.
I blew it!
My skin.
I once had the skin of a smiling little simian boy like you.
Yes, grand.
I like that new skin you're wearing tonight.
Oh, it is very, very good.
Very, very luxurious to be wearing it.
What is that, like about 55-year-old female?
Yes, yes, a kangaroo is the bottom part, and the top part is a female.
Younger than he is.
A Corinthian kangaroo.
It's only a 55-year-old female skin you've got on?
This is very supple still. Feel it.
Touch it. Put your hand.
No wonder you look so young. Ooh, you feel young, too, Dave.
Very supple. She was. She was a beautiful dancer.
She died from an ergot overdose.
We transported her to the Middle Ages to enlighten her somehow,
and yet she became involved in the celebrations when she came back.
Where did you download that skin app, mate?
Arr, arr, arrr, arrr.
It's gm.com. Skins for all your fancy new internet programs.
Just as sure as sugar and sweet.
Just as sure as you walk on your feet.
Just as sure as we'll all be dead.
Something's gonna crumble in your head.
Poop dog will pee and pee dog will poop.
And out of my hose will come horrible goop.
One by one they shall die.
One by one.
Two by two.
Oh false smite.
He did sin.
Lake of fire.
For he used the name J.R.
Behold, the day of Bob is at hand, and he shall come like a salesman in the night.
Yes, he shall come.
Give up hope.
Come and come again.
Bob's no crutch.
Here comes Negi.
Here comes Butch.
Dressed as Bulgarian woman, and look at the fascinating necklace they are wearing.
Oh, there is the flute player.
Sonia, how did you get your...
Sonia, could you step closer to the microphone?
What is the name of the flute you are playing in the Bulgarian Woman Orchestra?
It's called the Jelet Kakakata.
The Jelet Kakakata.
And it looks like you can also shave your legs or any other hairy part of your body.
You're absolutely right.
Yes, it's a very rare instrument.
I notice very many of the female singers have very, very hairy moustache, which must be
taken care of on regular basis.
Yes, isn't that a nice coincidence?
So you can whistle through your nose and rip off your flesh in one fell swoop.
I'm glad to be talking about the different orifices of whistling because, you know, that
can get kind of personal.
That's why the girl did the high notes so easy, because she had been shaving her fuzzy
.
Oh, if only I could reach the high minutes.
Of time.
The high hours.
The high days.
The high weeks.
The peaks of time.
Why cannot we skip from the peaks of one time to another?
Are there fifths?
Skip over the boring parts.
And the weeks of a day of a week.
Or the painful parts.
Actives indeed.
Monday we will call C.
Time is a waveform, is it not?
The Monday after we will call C.
Can we not skip across the tops of the waves?
Can we not?
By passing the long trip down?
Like luscious milkmaids on surfboards, can't we?
Now what about the fact that in engineering, we have to do the same thing?
In engineering terminology, the element of stress is measured in moments.
Stress is measured in moments?
Stress is measured in moments, yes.
Slack, however, is measured in drummets and dobses.
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
Is time a particle or a wave?
I am familiar with that system.
Maybe time is a particle, not a wave at all.
If that's the case, dude, we are screwed.
Well, do you know how long it takes to...
We might as well just give up.
Can you track the path of an electron?
A proton or a neutron?
If you were to get into quantum physics...
Because that would mean for every atom there is in this universe, there's another universe.
There is.
That's quantum, baby.
There's another universe waiting.
It's the flip side.
It's the B side of every universe has a continuous flip.
Just as big as this one.
Just as valid.
Just as alive.
Oh, some are smaller, though, James.
Don't discount the entropy factor.
Some are much smaller.
Some have sharp teeth.
Hey, I saw an ad in the scene, in the back pages of it.
It said...
This didn't make sense to me.
Doesn't make sense.
Sex-starved escorts.
Looking for pale and elderly women.
This don't make no kind of sense at all.
If an escort is sex-starved, what does she look like?
Gravitas.
I mean, shouldn't an escort be, like, getting sex all the time?
Now, you know, Chaz, I've been reading entertainment weeklies for a long time,
and from what I've learned from those is that there are a lot of beautiful women
who are completely lonely.
I guess all the guys think that they're getting tons of dates, and no one ever calls them.
They're the ones who are waiting for your call right now.
That's right.
At 1-900-
Yes.
They're waiting.
At 888-669-2323.
And you can-
Actually, there is a beautiful, live, naked woman waiting for your call.
A free call at 888-669-2323.
But don't you remember, every time you call her, she hands the phone to a sweaty stevedore
named Bill, and the rest of the evening is pure hell.
You know, the funny thing is I just gave out the number of Jesus, and actually it's Mary
Magdalene is the beautiful, naked woman that we picked up the phone.
Well, we know that Our Lord and Mary Magdalene were fond of fuzzing the fur, as they used
to say in Judea in the old age, and I think you might interrupt them at a tragic moment,
if you call that number.
And what is that number again to call them at a tragic moment?
888-669-2323.
You know, they're going to be going, damn, that sang gave her number out over the radio,
and two people called up.
Call it any time.
Woke us up.
Call now.
Operators are waiting to hang up on you.
It's like four in the morning in Bulgaria, where they are, the new foundation headquarters.
Well, we just interviewed one of the whistling women of the Bulgarian chorus, and she actually
played a little Gillette shaver.
And she could shave her mustache to get the hot stuff out of her face.
And here's a type of her now.
Isn't that, now look at that incredible headdress she's wearing.
You know, it's amazing how Europeans sometimes resemble like tribal cultures, I've seen South
American stuff.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Are those real feathers, or are those someone else's under...
Well, they're a certain kind of a feather that is a part fur, and then the other part
is feather.
As I look now, I can see that these are actually bark-stained underpants that you have...
Under things.
Under things crawling beneath the surface.
How in the world could you have ever seen my under?
My unders are under all of my skirts.
How in the...
Do you have x-rays vision?
Under things.
Under the mind.
Submental.
You look...
Sub genius, in fact.
So you love me tonight.
Sub temporal.
And what shall we do with old man time, who keeps dragging us along with his fitful pace?
Take the toilet plunger.
And plunge it in his eyes.
Where is time control?
How can we skip away from this poor boring now?
And leap, leap ahead.
Back or back?
Yes, back.
Why not?
Yes, it's the 99%, isn't it?
That one little tenth of a thousandth of a millionth of a percent that makes you less
than human.
Isn't that what it is?
And as you climb in the door, there you think you'll be saying goodbye to this earth.
But no, no.
You'll come back again.
And it's...
It's not enough to smash your watch.
It's not enough to buy every new clock that will be on the subgenius catalog soon.
No, just to prove your independence from time.
Your rebellion against God Time.
The evil time god.
You know, it's all for the time being, they say.
That cruel taskmaster in the sky.
With a capital T and a capital B.
With a long white beard.
The time being.
Made of time pieces.
Oh, I don't believe he had time.
The great tick.
The human being.
Time being?
The tick.
The great tick.
The time witch tick.
Arr!
The time being!
And we must...
We must bring down the time being!
The time ass pirate.
Ah, for him.
He is not a tick, a parasite.
His blood roots of seconds and precious minutes.
And the acid queen.
A parasite and an ass pirate.
Who is the acid queen now that, uh, uh, princes die?
Is it...
I thought it was Laura Bunchcake.
Did you hear that story?
Did you read about that?
About Laura?
The right hand man told these, uh...
A plutonian man?
We'll all be drinking.
Princess Di used to have, uh, men snuck in in the trunk of cars.
And she also used to go out in the middle of the night.
This is true.
She used to go out in the middle of the night and, you know, and drive around and give money
to hookers.
Really?
Yeah, to help them out.
Did they have different...
Tell me.
Did they have different favors to perform for?
No, go home.
Just go home.
Go buy some shoes or something.
Go buy a coat.
You don't need this.
A true princess.
It was because they, they were competition.
I love this thing.
My judge sat a week on his corner for like nine hours.
She made a deal with the aliens.
Very, very cold.
And then she didn't pay it off.
She was a great person.
That's not what I mean.
But she didn't pay off her deal with the aliens and they came and got her.
She'd come by and maybe rip off a quid or two and I'd be back home with me honey in a very,
very short time.
Look, when you signed that paper with the acid queen...
I love that.
...she was a great person.
She was a great person.
You got to follow through.
...she was queenly.
In her own sick, demented way.
Go ahead man.
Bring it up.
Bring it all the way up.
Bring all of them up on all screens.
Go ahead.
I dare you to see what you're looking at.
No, no, don't use that third eye.
Close that third eye.
Quick.
...chipsy acid queens.
I'm getting the hell out of here.
...all the masculinity of the...
Spaceman.
Oh, Spaceman.
Come rescue me.
...the whole world.
I'm not going to let you out.
...in the whole world.
...it's time to become a psychedelic hologram as we blast through the universe wearing no
clothes and funny little puddles of flowers.
Look at our faces we look like frogs.
Now.
Free, free, free again.
I'm surfing with the aliens.
I'm shedding my chromosomes, baby.
I'm getting out of this earthly humanly garb.
This only cost 30 bucks.
What a deal.
Ah, ah, ah.
...you want to see what I do.
What a ride, ladies and gentlemen, we're having here in the genealogy room.
As we all look out the open port holes and check on our charts and see where we came from and where we're going to.
I really don't want to know where that character came from.
All right, some of you don't want to know the character, but you're going to have to drop your chromosomes in the other room.
All of time is just soaring so fast.
This room is...
Oh, backwards.
Real time, the ball and chain of the chronometer shall no longer anchor us to temporal reality.
Iron Man, no ass pirates and no blood sucking parasites like the time being.
Read us for $30. It's free for $30.
Hey Dave, do you remember the ass pirate song?
Yar har, yar har, yar har.
We've been sailing.
Oh, so far.
The acid pirates?
I'm looking for some chunky rump to set me nose on fire.
We'll throw the clankers over and drag the bitch aboard.
We'll sniffer and we'll piffer and...
Old Peg Leg Dick, they called him Peg Dick Leg.
Do you remember Ruby the Dyke Queen?
You may mean the pervert pirate.
I'm a cat.
It's no bigger threat for them having admitted it than for them having admitted it and not
having admitted it.
But I would hope that in context of the recent admission in which they've admitted that they
admitted it, they've admitted it, but they did in fact admit it, it could be an important
lesson by something that's really not very useful.
I'm a cat.
M Vote
M against Haocau
Thank you.
I think of that!
If I had a particle board, we could surf on it.
Well, let's see what he wins, champions of the Deuteronomy tanks.
Let's take a look over here for numbers flying through 11,
where the atomic particle only moves in five directions at once.
That's the necromancer time.
You're going to come back time and time again and punch your penis in the orifice.
That's right, the neck of the dead person.
And that's not all.
It's like two quantum realities in one.
You'll be crossing them in big-time fashion as you cross five different dimensions at one time.
Your ocular vision, your board, board, board.
Because everybody's constantly spinning it, you know.
Somebody's dimensions at once anyway, you know.
So, like, every possibility that's occurring occurs in some universe.
Twice!
And it's because there's so many universes that there are possibilities, man.
Yeah, but then you also have to double that.
And TikTok's there again, like a monster's cross.
There's a crocodile waiting for Peter Pan to touch it.
There's a good one and an evil one.
Yep.
Bill, this is easier to understand than income tax.
I'll say that.
You know what I'm saying, Tom?
Yeah, we do.
You know what I'm saying?
Yep, duality.
Is, you know, yeah, what?
I use a program for income tax and for morality.
You use a program?
I have a computer program that dictates morality and ethics for me.
As it does your taxes at the same time?
No, they're different.
Different.
They are linked, though.
By a fashionable poo-poo stick.
But they are linked, indeed.
They're linked by the thing longer.
They are linked by a fascist evolutionary style statement lingering somewhere in your medulla.
The thing of my Bob dangles and ever towards the center of the earth.
Cinema Bob?
That's how you know where gravity goes, is where Bob's thing is pointing.
Yes, it's one of the best ways of finding out, too.
It's within, like, a fraction of a microcosmic second.
It's been...
It's been determined by Greenwich.
I mean, at least...
It's the plumb bob upon which is hung all gravitational...
The prior, original plumb bob of Wiener Plumbing.
The plumb of my Bob.
The shadow from the buttock also...
It's a mad Bob.
...incidental time.
Just sit a reel of Greenwich.
That's what I'm talking about, Bob.
From your head, Bob.
Well...
Hair Bob.
Have we said all we can about his abilities?
Well, you know...
It's fairly flexible, I think.
You know where to put the cork.
Yeah, I know where to put the cork.
People doing your yoga lately, haven't you?
Yeah.
They say the days don't move
And that there's no such thing as time
But reflecting on the hours gone by
I know that once you were mine
Then something happened that I just didn't see
That something took you away
I never thought that it would ever come to be
That I'd look back and despair
But now I'm here
And I'm standing alone without you
Wondering where I went wrong
I don't wanna live without you
Seems like it's taken so long
For me to gather up the words I wanna say
I need you with me, it's true
There doesn't seem to be any real way
That I can ever come through for you
Uh, I've tried to make a career
I don't wanna go, but there's only one way
What's more, it's in a double side
Note that in a real
The weakenedhangs
That I've come to believe in
Look me in the eyes and say
guitar solo
Baby, yeah, do it, do it
You're driving me crazy
Oh my god, that feels so good
Oh yeah, yeah, oh baby, yeah
Do it
Oh, you're driving me crazy
Oh yeah, yeah, oh baby, yeah
Oh
I'm the hottest thing on the wheels, bitch
You're so rad
My father taught me everything I know
No, I've never met a he-man quite like you
Like, you know, someone who could take me beyond the confines of my perceived celestial boundaries
Exemplified by the quasi-cataclysmic cacophony
Of one's personal ponderance of existential mortality
Like a man who's been in a coma for a long time
You know what I mean?
I know you mean, bitch
The Master y
The Master want you
But I'm the only one
That's been watching you
Oscars
Thanks for watching!
now champion jack
you shall have as much meat as you want
what the devil is going on chrissy they're dressed like little girls
you are a sucker and you listen to me and you listen to me good the time has come
it is now or never thou shalt not listen to rock and roll music thou shalt not masturbate
thou shalt not fornicate
the time has come a reckoning time a time when all the mighty buildings shall be shattered and splintered and split
when the world's bellies were broke when america will be put to the fire and tested in the new revelation
this is the end of today's lesson
you know we live in a world where we want to get stuck
and there are all kinds of schemes out there
and we are desperate we are hungry and we are thirsty for something that they give us what we want
it's the process of criminal law
thrown into the fire and burned
i like to think ridiculous and posturing
i can hardly believe that i heard it on the radio
it's a pill
that has test effects
it's a word either weak or weak
all other gods besides jehovah and his son jesus christ are strange gods
i like how they collect the weeds first and bind them in bundles to be burned
uh
thrown into the fire and burned
in flashbacks
you have already been expl bd
burned by the word i sung to you
wrong
exactly
enough
all this means is that i gotta get out of here
and you got the gun
getting out
heart ignition
and now back
to WCSB Cleveland
and ESO
radio with this final
message
the message is the message
and when the lord exploded
his messages
on the depleted mankind accordion
he found
the message is the message
God is mad
as hell
and he's not gonna take it anymore
I said God
God is mad
as hell
and he is not gonna take it anymore
see me
pay me
hear me
thank you doctor
at least it doesn't get his ire up
that's what I'm glad about
if it made him angry
I'd be worried
here comes
you know
otherwise I think
we're just fine
really
I think we can trust
that everything is just fine
and we're fine
there's no need for
contrasting opinions anymore
God is mad
he can come over to my house
and fuck my sister
well yes
and I think it's just going to be fine
I really do
I think I'm gonna have to
dunk onto the subway now
yes
the subway
mad as hell
I'm not gonna take it anymore
no they're not
they voted
they're not mad as hell
everything's apparently just fine
everything's just fine
yes we will take it
we are bending over
go ahead and
all I can say is
free
Willie
that's three video
we're gonna take it
we're gonna
oh there he goes
he freed his Willie
he took him away
he's really making it
come back
Willie no
come back Willie
oh it looks so nice
hanging out like that
but not like the plumb bob
let's forget you
yeah
well I think it's time for everyone
to go to theater
find me that way
I want to see a nice show
at the industrial tractor factory
number five
plumb bob is plumb
bombed
ah
I love these Chechen movies
put your hand down here
it's not a movie
it's a
stick your hand in my pocket
I think this Chechen terrorist woman
to my left
wants me to put my hand on the popcorn
there's a quarter down there somewhere
you're not a Chechen woman
you're a hairy Chechen man
I don't want your
and then
she put her hand out
holding his mighty
credit card
and there's the beautiful flotilla of the virgin Larry
is making its way down the street
with all the apostolates
and the other subcrimes
smoking the
the apostrophes they've been given by their
dear dear dear lord
a fanny man who used to write them
efficaciously once every summer
as they cramped away off of their wilderness huts
but now it looks like some of them are actually
rolling in the dough
as they begin to make a huge human pie
ah
out of the shell
shall we break
that looks messy
it is
it's very messy
you don't want to get your feet too close to the middle
there's four and twenty blackbirds in there
oh man
and there's also a dead saint
which comes back
the blood boils every August 22nd
before the feast
freedom is laid to west
in the grave of history
the human gene
which once stretched across the globe
and threatened to kill you
accidentally died
neutralized
never gets rid of the human
just prepare yourself
goodbye
give this pub interest
poem
to sun
ashes to ashes
dust to dust
so endeth all things
would you like a little bite of his
ankle
there is much pain
and gnashing of teeth
put a little bit of raisin butter
on the ankle there you could
oh man
get out of there
you've been resurrected
get out of that coffin
throw away the stone and get to work
who's playing the butt trumpet
well the first thing we're going to be doing
we're going to be working on building back some of that
flexibility you've been losing over being
dead for the last 26 years
you're all kind of scrunched up
you're skeletal look at yourself
you need to do 25 26
maybe 27 light year pushups
come on Norton get down the
neural fives let's see you do them do them
do them
one of the 37 percent of
American registered voters who showed up to
wave my fist in the occult sky
and smack my
firmly between the genital areas
I'm so glad
I was the first and now I'm
well you hear the dogs don't you we better get out of here
oh here they come here they come
there were only 37 percenters total
I voted the wrong way man
here they come
it's those giant crickets
the tag glows
they can see the tag man just just keep moving
cover up your arm
twinkle twinkle little star
till next week
keep your head on tight
how I wonder when
you're back to the wind
and you're sack in the saddle
Mr. Butch says his mandate
means lots of fun
for the people on top of the pie
I shat
for those squanderlings laying down near the bottom
there won't be much pie left
there's only coming
for the gravy
I'm so high
like a diamond in the sky
twinkle twinkle little star
how I wonder what you are
you have been listening to
the subgenius radio ministry hour of slack
produced by your surely reverend Ivan Stang
my address is
P.O. Box 807
Glenrose, Texas 76043
but you can write for more information for free
paper information from the church of the subgenius
at post office box 807
Glenrose, Texas 76043
as seen on www.subgenius.com
the subgenius radio ministry
help
just keep on yelling
just don't struggle
don't struggle
help
Don't struggle!
Help!
Don't move.
Just stay still.
Help!
They're hanging in there upside down like in a slaughterhouse.
I wish you'd seen it.
I want to get a picture.
Well, you better get to bed now, son.
Have a good sleep.
In the middle of the night?
Yes.
So now you listen and you listen good.
Have a good sleep.