and that's going to do it for this version of the universal soul express
we just heard soon forward was it no front door and then before that we heard special guests
so but we have very special guests with us today live and direct from where my all my exes live
subgenii praise bob yeah praise bob cleveland finally fine it's so good to see you by the way
so good to see you joel yeah well i mean it's really you know having hanging out getting to
hang with the um subgenie the subgenii
live and direct as much as i love playing your cds uh it's so much nicer to have you guys here
well believe me it's a lot it's a lot easier to do it here than at my uh dinner table in texas
oh okay yeah yeah it's hard to get motivated properly well it's also hard to keep the dogs
to shut get the dogs to shut up they're really noisy oh wow as soon as they know i'm working
on something they start want to be on the show join me oh you know they want to be in on that
but they're probably listening now they probably are yeah so um so yeah so i'm really excited to
thank you guys for coming in and um i think all of our friends listening out there are really
excited to hear that you're here especially our friends in mentor and columbus and parma and new
orleans louisiana how about germany germany yeah we got we got three germanies we got bayern
and bayern again nuremberg so thank you guys tuning in canada we have you and well we have
hawaii listening really yeah tommy fox what's up tommy fox uh russian federation's listening
that's crazy i know it used to be only germany we you know we had we had our friends in leipzig
yeah well you know it was uh you know it's um our world war ii enemies and and our cold war enemies
are uh
tuning in so yeah well yeah yeah russians and and uh chinese and everything yeah i know man
let me tell you bob's getting more popular that which is a good thing okay the question i have
for you and i don't want to run into your show but the question i have the subgenius movie
that you were a part of yeah that we talked you've talked about in previous episodes of the hour of
slack is that coming to cleveland oh eventually i'm sure it will in fact
for cop developers will be home so that your province
and our
audience will gather
for them
not
coming around
yeah
right
well
there won't be
watching
what are you going to do hot culture
if it doesn't support
focuses on the old days.
Sadly enough, I mean,
I gave them footage of this station.
I went out of my way to make sure
there was an interview with Lonesome Cowboy
Dave, even if I had to do it.
They didn't use any of that stuff
that I shot. And it all
focuses on the first 10 years
basically.
Although it ties in
what's going on now and the
terrible need for slack, especially
lately. Oh my God, yes.
The last few years.
So it turned out
really, really good.
It moves real fast.
We've already
been talking to people from the station
about showing it.
It's still in film festivals.
But it came out pretty
good. I'm hoping it'll be on Netflix
or Amazon or something. That'd be sweet.
Also, I'd like to see if our
Cleveland Sim and Tech
or Cedar Lee.
But like I say, I still
don't even have a
copy of it.
Okay.
I can look at an old cut.
It's not as good as
the new improved version.
Okay. Well, I'm very excited to hear
more about it. I'm sure you'll keep us all
up to date on the goings on.
Yeah.
It was really fun. My grandkids
got to see the movie. My
10 and 8 year old grandkids.
Oh, wow. Yeah. When Bob
got shot, they said, was that real?
I said, no. And then they said,
is any of it real?
Do you guys really do shows? Yeah. Yeah.
That part's real. But the shootings
aren't. None of the shootings aren't.
There were a couple more shootings
later on that were also fake.
Well, I'm actually
going into your time now.
You're listening to WCSV Cleveland.
I'm just going to put up this dub music for a little bit.
If you want to switch it. I'll just use that part.
Okay. Yeah. I'll keep all that.
Okay.
I'm glad I had the recorder on.
Okay. Hang on one second.
I hope the dogs
are listening. I hope the dogs are
listening too. Yeah.
They can only hear it off my little
computer speakers. Not the big
speakers. So the sound, they may not
recognize it. Okay. Here we
go. Our slack.
The subgenius.
Power of
slack.
Slack.
well
footage
I say, Mr.
Speaker,
I've had a speech in-soak
this six months and it has
swelled me.
like a drowned horse. If I don't deliver it, I shall burst and smash the windows.
The gentleman from Subgenius talks of summing up the merits of the question, but I'll sum up my own.
In one word, I'm a screamer, and have got the roughest racking horse, the prettiest sister,
the surest rifle, and the ugliest dog in the district. I'm a little the savagest critter you ever did see.
My father can whoop any man in Tennessee, and I can whoop my father.
I can outspeak any man in this church, and give him two hours start.
I can run faster, dive deeper, stay under longer, and come out drier than any chap.
I can go to this side of the big swamp. I can outlook a panther, and out stare a flash of lightning,
tote a steamboat on my back, and play it rough and tumble with a lion, and an occasional kick from a zebra.
To sum all up in one word, I am a horse.
Goliath was a pretty hard colt, but I could choke it.
I can take the risk of a horse, and I can take the risk of a lion.
I can drag off, frighten the old folks, astonish the natives, and beat the normals all to smash.
Make nothing of sleeping under a blanket of snow, and don't mind being frozen more than a rotten apple.
Congress allows lemonade to the members, and it charged under the head of stationery.
I move also that whiskey be allowed under the item of fuel.
For bitters, I can suck away at a noggin of aqua fortis, sweetened with brimstone, stirred with a lightning rod, and skimmed with a hurricane.
I've soaked my head and shoulders in Salt River so much that I'm always corned.
I can walk like an ox, run like a fox, swim like an eel, and yell like a subgenius, make love like a mad bull,
and swallow a pink hole without choking, if you butter his head and pin his ears back.
This song is for her, you know.
I am a bull man.
I'm a bull man.
Bob.
After years and years of trying to catch Bob, we were going to kill Bob so we could make him look alive.
Bob must be about 15 years old now.
We gotta kill Bob while he's still alive.
I tried to shake off my feelings for Bob, but it was impossible.
Must catch Bob.
Aw, who am I kidding?
I haven't caught Bob in 15 years.
Find Bob?
I mean, catching Bob is one thing, but why do we have to kill him?
I don't like the idea of stuffing Bob either.
7,000 gigawatt radio signal activates an electronic pulse attuned to Bob's brain waves.
All Pete has to do is find Bob, and this baby will do the rest.
It's genius.
No wonder we haven't found Bob.
With extinction staring Bob in the face,
the only question was, could I save him?
Let me get this straight.
If I don't catch Bob, I'll be famous?
Bob is a fish.
You and I are fishermen.
I hope you appreciate this, Bob.
Next time will be too late.
Bob will be gone by then.
Bob.
When it comes to Bob, there's only one rule.
There are no rules.
We're talking big bad Bob here.
Great day to be alive, eh, Rigley?
Yeah.
Yes, you bet.
Unless, of course, you're Bob.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
I'm sure it would mean a lot to Dad if you were here when we finally bag old Bob.
Bob was out of luck.
The Bob hunt had begun.
Bob.
But poor Bob wouldn't get the chance.
A feeling that Bob deserved a better fate than ending up hot glued to a piece of plywood.
Come on, Bob.
Make me famous.
Where's Bob?
I saw him on the way over.
He told me to say hi.
We're not against you, Don.
We're just for Bob.
Bob?
Sure.
Bob.
Ya...
In general, the two of us are always together
Now, the question is, what's the time?
One, two, three, two, three, four
What are we doing?
Because he started with experiments in the backyard
And Jack passes as a little boy when he wouldn't go too far
But the trouble really started when he found another young ascender
Because together they were ready to reach the sky
So the two of them began to play around about a year
Six, close six
Jack is going from a local crowd of company
A military gathering at the Avial Rock
It's a sign of bliss
But the both of you are no one else at the chief
How high?
Does your rocket fly?
You've got to be careful boy, as you chase money
Except for the one that I find
You've got to be careful boy
You've got to be careful boy, as you set the world on fire
Set the world on fire
A loyal follower of Mr. Alistair Crowley
He took a oath to be a magistrate, really
His friendly house in Pasadena was notorious for the orgies
Every night at the city of Mysteries
So when his company became the famous Jakey Laboratories
His reputation made it difficult to proceed
And after one of his ecological ceremonies
He found his body in a pile of blood and debris
How high does your rocket fly?
You better be careful
Where's your rocket fly?
You can't smell it
You can't find it
Set the world on fire
You better be careful
How high does your rocket fly?
Where's your rocket fly?
You can't smell it
Set the world on fire
You can't find it
We better be careful boys
We better be careful
Set the world on fire
Keep them up and down
Love is the love
We better be careful
Set the world on fire
Fly me through the moon
Thank you.
That was delightful.
Delightful.
Yeah.
I wish I could sing like that.
Not everything's singing, you know.
The only important thing these days is rhythm and melody.
Rhythm.
And melody.
And of all my friends
You've been the best to me
Soon will be the day
When I repay you handsomely
Broken heart's a heart to mend
Nor have my share
But life just carries on
Even when I'm not there
I'm not going to give in
Situation I win
Rush for a change of atmosphere
I can't go on so I give in
Gotta get myself right out of here
Situation I win
Rush for a change of atmosphere
I can't go on so I give in
Gotta get myself right out of here
I gotta get myself right
Gotta get myself right
out of here
Out of here
Dog communism
And now
Hopefully
There will be
Lonesome cowboy Dave
I hope
Oh
Where is he
But if it's not Dave
Who could it be
Hello hello
Mutilage
Are you
Musilage tonight
I'm flavored
Well flavored indeed tonight
Took over 300 pounds of
Escawhiskers to bring this down
To its original
State
That's very
Musilaginous
It's like a caramelized onion in so many ways
That we don't
Yeah and that's the theme of
This show tonight caramelized onions
Oh wait well
I guess that's as good as any
Caramelized onion Musilage
Dave it's great to hear you over the WCSB system
It sure is
It's amazing to hear you be able to pick up
Without causing injury to yourself
And others around you
Yeah I hope the dogs
Are handling this well
They've been left alone for the first time
In the Cleveland Heights
Slacker Mansion
Well before they cause any demons
They're sure to check out every freaking
Square inch of the place
Well they've been
On the show for a year or two
Two years now but
Princess We hasn't been
This is the first time we've had her here for
A long time cause she had to stay in
Ohio all that time
But I'm back back baby
And Brother Love
Is here too
Hey who's Brother Love
He's the guy that does African
Abstract show half the time
Before our slot
I'm sorry I forgot
Quite alright
Well I remember I actually
Remember but I forgot
What the Soviet context was
Remember back in 1952
When we had the imperialists
By the testicles
What do you mean back then
Oh wait no
Now the imperialists have us by them
That's right
No that was the band the imperialists
Hey Dave I have to do some credits real quick
Cause I didn't before
And
There were
Several cuts involving dogs
Those were all by Lee Murr
Who also does our titles
There was a song
The song I just played called Rush
Was by
Big Audio Dynamite the second
And there was a song before that
By the Claypool Lennon Delirium
A song called Blood and Rockets
And if anybody listens back to that
Or on the
Podcast
You'll
You'll see that it's about
Jack Parsons
The crazy
Black song
Black rock
Black magic rocket scientist
Who partied with L. Ron Hubbard
And then blew himself up
And was he
Was he
Did he hang with Aleister Crowley
Or was that
No, he was after.
They just did his books.
That was much later.
Yeah, he just read his books.
He was involved in the OTO, and he took it real seriously,
and he really was a rocket scientist.
I think he started the Jet Propulsion Laboratory, strangely enough.
But what is the OTO?
I forgot the digital phenomenon.
The OTO is the...
The Ordo Templi Orientis.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
Tempical oracle.
Started by Bob's old prankster buddy, Alistair Crowley.
It was all...
He was actually a British agent of no imperialistic designs himself
because he wanted to be the leader of Europe in an underground way.
Oh, he was a nut.
He was just another one of those nuts.
If it had happened a little bit later, he would have been a good subgenius, but...
Absurd selfies with lagoon hats on.
You know, that's the kind of stuff he was into.
You know, like a big turban and everything and smile like Lucifer.
Yeah.
Or not.
Do what you want before you wilt,
is the whole loophole in the law or something like that.
They're chanting all that stuff at the end of that song by the Claypool Lennon Delirium.
Oh, there was a collage that was the first collage we've ever gotten from Reverend Elvis Martini
that was called Pete and Pete Kill Bob.
These guys talking about killing Bob.
It was uncanny.
I don't know what show that's from.
Oh, in the very beginning, there was...
Yeah, everybody knows Bob's already been dead for 25 years now.
Yeah.
Let's kill Bob.
You know, it's okay.
We're going to kill him again and again.
And they still don't get that joke.
Never mind.
I'm sorry.
He's still, you know, he's still got that...
He's still wearing that target on his back.
Nobody told him it was there.
I guess they like watching him get shot and bounce back.
Oh, and there was a brag at the very beginning.
That was, of course, Reverend Onan Canobite
doing a brag called Born on a Mountaintop.
Unchanged from the original...
Cowboy brag, except that he changed
one ethnic term slur to subgenius
and the other one to pink.
That was the only thing he had to change.
Otherwise, it was a perfect subgenius brag.
So, there we are.
Are my nostrils cutting out or are yours abating?
Like a text with abatement?
No, that's my allergy.
My newfound allergies.
I had a new...
I had a new gift from the...
From the goddess.
From the exists or Bob or somebody that's allergies I never had before.
I didn't notice your nostrils cutting out, Dave.
I did.
Yeah, it seems to have come and gone.
Like I said, digitized type of thing.
Well, I can faintly hear the whistling as you breathe through your nose
through that forest of hairs.
I have the same problem.
I have to use a big old lopper.
Well, better to have a...
Better to have a forest...
...to your degree in nose hairs than to breathe through your mouth holes,
which is very bad and sinful for your education as a miner.
I mean, a coal miner.
Don't worry.
That's too light for me.
I know you already went to that divine apple slapple in the sky
and came back and said,
hey, it ain't what it used to be and it ain't what it ever will be again.
I remember all those lies you used to tell everybody,
especially since the days of the French Revolution.
And then Bob, you come up with this Bob guy.
Everybody knows he's not real.
Or he is real.
In fact, he's a crazy guy on the route to San Leon in New Orleans.
He lives in one of them little shacks there up on...
No, no, you're thinking of Bob, not Bob.
I'm thinking of quotation mark Bob, unquote Bob.
Oh, you are?
Okay, well, whatever.
You can think of...
Okay, I'll just call him Bob because as you commonly know,
with your nose holes as big and wide,
and flared and strange and as full as venomous tissues as you're ours.
Boy, you know...
Some of us type Dobbs because we just don't want to do those quotation marks around Bob.
It's just as many letters,
but you have to use an extra digit to make those quotation marks.
Yeah, that's a real concern, man.
Somebody who knows the keyboard knows it hurts sometimes.
That's a true thing.
I don't know if you knew that for true.
You just made that up on the spot, Stang,
but that's an actual real thing that flashes in your head like,
I don't know if I want to put two freaking quotation marks.
Yeah.
Most of them don't know any better.
I mean, you can tell who's just a Bobby Gimme Bob on Facebook,
a pretender, by the fact that they don't even know about the quotes.
They never noticed.
They can't even spell Bob right, in other words.
What about the guy in Japan who married a love doll,
a pornographer story love doll,
and he made a big deal about it
because he took all kinds of selfies of him proposing and everything,
like it was going to be a real wedding,
mailing out these invitations and stuff like that.
Then he had, because it was a love doll,
he just couldn't respond in curios alquimundo
to his resolutions or his sparkling drinks and beverages.
So when the preacher said,
do you take this man for your lawfully wedded husband,
the doll didn't respond, probably.
No.
Unless the groom kind of out of the side of his mouth,
like a ventriloquist said,
I do.
Holding her head and nodding it around a little bit.
Yeah.
I saw a whole movie, a documentary movie,
about people who are aficionados of those love dolls
and really fall in love with them.
Yeah.
Yeah, treat them better than they treat their friends.
They feed them better than they feed their dog.
And they beat them better than they feed beaters.
And everybody loves dog meat, too,
especially in the wintertime when it gets pretty cold.
Well, not me.
Dog meat?
It would have to be awfully cold.
Not me, no, not me.
Well, you know, I turned into a dog person
at the last point when we were forced to.
My dad left me with this big old hound dog.
And then we got hooked on him.
And then he died because he was 12 years old.
And that's how old I live.
And so then we got a little one.
And now I've got yet another one that I also inherited.
And I used to spend all my,
I used to waste my time playing video games
or looking through microscopes.
I always had some hobby.
A new hobby is just worshipping the dogs.
Just doing their, serving them.
Doing their bidding.
Yeah, we're good service humans.
I used to use this very, very personalized
I'll see you later message
if I felt like I had to get home
and feed a dog or something.
I used to say, well, I gotta go,
how did I used to say it?
See a man about a penis full of urine?
Something like that.
Gotta go fillet the dog.
Oh, fillet the dog.
F-E-L-L-A-T-E, fillet show.
Yeah.
Oh no.
Gotta go fillet my dog now.
What?
Well, I don't have a dog right now to go and fillet.
Why would you do a thing like that, Dave?
Okay, okay, that's enough.
Because that's what it appears like
when you get to such great extent.
Oh, they need cookies.
They were good today.
Oh, they're going to put three walkies today
because you know what I mean?
Yeah.
Oh, I sure do.
Do the dogs wake you up?
Me?
Yeah, do they?
It's like, oh, it's time for you to feed me.
Get up, human.
Only in extreme situations.
Usually I'm up before they are.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
Yeah, they're really quite,
they sleep 18 hours a day, thankfully.
Yeah.
Because the rest of the time they keep me running.
Yes.
Daddy, take us for a walk.
Daddy, let us out.
Daddy, give us a treat.
Daddy's playing Einstein's Secret Orchestra, aren't you?
Oh, yeah, I am.
That's a witch disco that's in the background.
Yeah, I just, I heard that and I went,
where do I know that from?
Yeah, it's you on the guitar.
At least I'm on the Proximo Profundo as well, too.
The Battleship Potamkin sank back in 1942,
but they're still keeping the memory
of all those great Soviet seamen
and others who propagated the myth of Ishtar.
I think you got a couple of facts wrong in that sentence.
Oh, but I got plenty of facts.
That's what's most important is how many you have.
It doesn't matter if they have anything to do with each other.
That's what the president said.
That's what the president believes in.
And just think what a successful businessman like you would have.
Show you a vacuum cleaner or a hamburger maker.
Right, right.
Yeah, successful.
Mm-hmm.
Yep.
I bet he's having second thoughts.
About this whole public service thing.
He built up an empire of $7 million
into zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, seven times.
Well, but as people have pointed out,
yeah, I wish I was as poor as him.
You know what I'm saying?
Well, actually, he might really be.
If he were to shoot straight, square up and down,
maybe that might be true, but, you know.
If you have the right kind of lawyers,
you make money by losing.
You get the government to give you twice as much money as you lost.
Yeah, you have to be an expert.
You have to be an expert in, like, Russian literature,
like Chekhov and Gudanov.
Hey, hey, watch your language.
Nastrovya and Prevyat-Toverich.
And Nichival.
All right.
Well, I can sure hear some cutting out,
and I was wondering if it must be my phone.
Can you hear it on the other end?
No.
Sounds great.
Sounds real good.
No buzz.
No.
I'm hearing me.
We can hear your nose flare.
Yeah.
Yeah, well, I can hear you guys talking about dialectical materialism
behind my back and saying,
Bob's the real avatar of the century,
which I never believed or doubted or denied,
but I just used to poke a little fun once in a while
right between the eyes.
Dave, the voices you've been hearing weren't us.
Well.
That doesn't mean I still can't hate them as much as if they were you.
Sure.
Yeah, but I'm just letting you know that those voices in your head
weren't our voices in your head.
Why not?
Because we weren't talking to you that way.
We didn't say anything about dialectical materialism.
In fact, I barely, I don't really even know what that means.
I know it's something that commies talk about a lot.
Yeah, especially ones that like to play,
golf, you know, at Point Vista Towers or Trump Towers,
wherever it is.
Well, yeah, I wasn't invited to that party.
Or maybe I was and I just blew it off.
I don't remember.
There was a lot of stuff happened in the 80s and 90s that I,
I've been kind of surprised at some of the things I learned
from that documentary movie about us.
Yeah, I've heard you turn somebody,
some professor said you were a lot more religious
than you pretend to be making fun of religion and culture
and stuff like that and that you really are more of a religion
than some of those religions you're making fun of.
No, but it is true that the director of the movie told me
that she thought we behaved more like Christians than most Christians.
And none of us are really Christians.
That's the first thing that you mentioned,
that I thought was true.
That was the first thing you said,
followed by a bunch of other corroborating statements
that indicted you of being a liar
and a physical humorous and retardation.
Well, she acted more like a subgenius than most subgeniuses.
Yes.
You know, as I've been saying,
it's ironic that the best movie about Church of the Subgenius
was done by a pretty devout Christian.
Yeah, I just heard this guy the other day say
they were behind the Iron Sky.
What?
Well,
there's certain...
No, no, that's because Iron Sky ripped off...
She-Wolf.
That's because they were ripping off Bob's comic books
and, you know, manly pulp novels and stuff.
That's where all those movies come from.
They're all just ripping off Bob.
We sure did.
But then again,
he rips everybody off right in return.
But he's...
Yeah, but he doesn't have to even try.
That just happens automatically.
Oh, it's so sad sometimes to think of a way...
Only for us.
Not for him.
He's only sad if he's in the mood to be sad,
which happens sometimes.
It's a good excuse for him to get really drunk, I've heard.
And he'll get ridiculously maudlin'.
He'll just be...
Oh, why'd she...
The ones that she can't see are always bigger.
Why'd she do that to me?
Yeah.
I can't believe that.
You managed to pull a little post-relative humorous laughter out of me
just thinking of him saying that there.
It is rather humorous to see him kind of down on his knees
becoming a human being like the rest of us, you know?
Well, that's only...
Like I say, that only happens if...
That's kind of what he was in the mood for.
That was his whim, was to be miserable for a while.
But even then, he's grinning,
and the pipe still keeps smoking
without him ever having to light it or refill it.
And the devil hellions keep on stoking the fires of hell.
Well...
He might be sort of like that blues player Robert Johnson
where he had to sell something really important,
important to get that sales gift.
It's possible.
It has something to do with...
But it's probably...
Probably the devil felt somehow ripped off afterwards.
Like, wait a minute.
But he did.
Bob got all this riches and talent and luck,
and the soul he gave me is...
I'm not sure if it's even a soul.
I'm not sure what it is.
I think it might be a sock.
It's a baritone erection, they used to call it.
But, yeah, he...
Did I say that wrong?
I don't know.
Baritone erection?
I'll have to listen back to the recording.
That's when the middle fur of your animal fur goes down on you.
Oh.
I don't...
Wait, wait a minute.
You're getting perverted again about animals?
Well, I'm not really...
They're all perverse.
I mean, you think of the top of a mouse or a rat
or, like, a cheese monkey.
Or a fiddler.
Put all those together, you got one thing.
Onion pie.
It's not made for human consumption, you know?
So you have to kind of, like, put dangerous radioactive materials,
substantial amounts of vinegar and ointment,
and teenage pie, and everything is disgusting to you, right?
In one little box.
Wow, that's a pretty interesting recipe, Dave.
It is.
I don't know about the vinegar and ointment myself.
Just sent me a couple...
A couple thousand dollars, and I'm, you know, on Xerox or just...
That's right.
I'll type it up and print it out for you
and send it right to you directly in person, in hand.
I won't even email.
I'll get out my hands and my fores
and give it to you as a real artifact.
Well, there's that fundraiser for you online,
so you must be pretty rich now,
because you were asking for $150,000, I think, originally.
Yeah, I made literally tens of dollars.
That's what I...
Well, you did basically...
It basically says,
I need $150,000 so I can write screenplays.
But then it doesn't say anything about what kind of screenplays or...
And they're all very, very elementally cruel and interesting,
and I didn't even mention them.
No, right.
So it's...
I'm not surprised.
You know, I put that link on every time I post a show.
People...
Get...
The chance to click on the Give Dave Money link.
But...
But there's no teaser.
There's no...
Yeah, there's no...
You're not...
Yeah, you're not teasing them enough.
You're not seducing them into it.
Bob obviously didn't write that copy.
No, he didn't.
That's a very loser copy.
It was obviously written by the client.
Yeah.
And, you know, when the client gets out there pitching the cards,
you're going to see a lot of stupidity,
and the director's going to come up numerous times and say,
No, no, just read what we've got here.
Just...
Just look over here.
And then when I move my hand over here, look over this way.
Oh, this is just like the way Washington works now.
Yeah, George Washington used to write commercials.
Oh, okay.
For wooden teeth.
And hemp.
Yeah, I'm playing on the guitar.
I'm playing the wooden teeth part, too.
I just heard that.
Hey, they...
Philo's like George Washington now.
You know, he moved to Kentucky,
and he...
He...
He sold his hovel near San Francisco for over a million dollars,
and for what a hovel outside San Francisco costs,
he was able to get a 50-acre farm.
And now he's...
They legalized hemp growing again,
not marijuana.
That's kind of different.
But just regular hemp.
Yeah, so they can...
He can, you know,
they can make flags and paint out of it and stuff.
And toilet paper.
At least it's not seditious material that we'd have to report to.
No, but if there was some of the kind mixed in with that,
nobody would really notice it.
Not that he would...
Not that Philo would do a thing like that.
Oh, heavens to Betsy.
If you see something, you've got to say something.
You know, haven't you ever gone to a council meeting?
No, I've avoided this.
Wearing a pair of leather hosiery with your Nazi armband on.
And before you give your...
You say,
Reverend Ivan Stang,
so-and-so,
Glenn Rose, Texas.
And then you go,
you hold up your fist in a mighty Hitler-like salute
and say,
seek high on it.
And sit down,
you're wearing shorts, you know,
and a brown shirt and everything,
and you look like a bad, bad Nazi child.
Oh, man, you wouldn't believe how much trouble we've gone to
to erase and hide all the old photographs of those days.
Because, you know, people just don't forgive you
for a sick joke you made 30 years ago.
Ever.
And hey, man, you know, I went to Argentina,
just like all the rest of us.
You know, I didn't stick around and cause more trouble.
I knew when I was licked, like a wounded dog.
Yeah, well, it serves you right for whatever it was you did.
Well, I don't know if I actually did anything on any level at all.
I didn't think you remembered.
I didn't think you'd know.
You don't know what you're being punished for, do you?
No.
I don't either.
That's why they call it Welcome to the Memory Camp.
If you can remember what you did wrong, then you get released.
Well, yeah, but if you...
They'll just keep giving you more years of labor,
forced labor at Trump Stop.
You know, those private prisons combined with convenience stores.
Yeah.
Yeah, I think we already did this bit before,
and that's the way it all turned out, too.
Oh, you think it's a bit now?
No.
It's just a repetition of a theme, and, you know, it's true.
It's true.
We've coupled up some ideas there, you know,
and next thing you know, it's a world of its own.
Just like, you know, have you ever seen a book by the porcelain monkey?
Sure.
Anytime somebody makes a sick joke like that, it comes true.
Or you find out that it already was true.
Yeah.
If we had enough...
If we were sick enough to just think of it
as a joke, that means somebody else was sick enough
to really do it for real and set the wheels in motion.
And then we get unfairly accused of inspiring these arch criminals,
which we might have done, but we didn't mean to.
That wasn't our intention.
We wanted to inspire the arch slackers.
Yeah.
Whatever that means.
I'm not sure.
Put fuel in the fire there for them.
That's what I agree with you on that one.
You just said...
Now, true, we don't...
You kind of agree with me a little bit on that there.
Yeah, I agree with you.
Well, I mean, you know, it doesn't sound like you really, really think I know what I'm talking about.
But I do.
I do, Dave.
I really do.
I don't.
Yes.
I've already forgotten what the hell you were talking about, but that's not unusual.
That's okay.
You signed it away, man.
I signed that contract with Dobbs.
He signed it all away, man.
Yeah, the memory.
I signed away everything.
You look in the mirror and go, I know who I am.
I know who I am.
And cry and stuff like, what's his name in Johnny Angel.
Well, you sign away the memories of everything that you're signing away.
So you don't even know what you had before.
So you don't miss it.
Well, right.
But it's like Robert Johnson, he said, like at the Crossroads,
once the devil did come and put the pie pan right in his football.
That's hard to do.
You know what I mean?
That's difficult as hell to do.
Yeah.
And once you do it, you do it once.
You come to the Crossroads and you made your, you signed on the wind blood on the dotted
line there.
When the X day comes, meaning in your language, X day, when the day in question comes, X day,
you'll be ready to go somewhere else.
Yeah.
What Dave said.
Speak out.
Speaking of X day, that subgenius holiday and destruction of the entire human aspect
of the planet is coming up in a couple of months, less than a couple of months, I guess.
It's breathing down our very necks.
Yeah.
Starting July 1st, the devout will be gathering in Southern Ohio at that campground.
With possibly Bob lurking in the woods.
Did you mean like Wisteria campground?
Yeah.
Is that the one you meant?
Is this a Starwood?
Bob always pooped in the woods in Wisteria.
Well, Starwood happens after.
Yeah.
But see, X day comes first.
Okay.
And if-
And if the world survives.
Well, even if it doesn't, we'll have our own planets that we can put Starwood on.
Oh, okay.
Cool.
Yeah.
So I was planning to beam up the campground and protect it and let them have their Starwood
before we eject them out into space.
Wow.
The ones that didn't pay up.
Of course, by then, everybody will want to join up.
Yeah.
But we can't do any kind of a call to action.
Really?
Starwood's got some interesting guests.
Yes.
President Vermin Supreme is going to be at Starwood.
And apparently when he does an event, he does it to the max.
He does several workshops.
He'll rant.
He'll be your friend.
He'll tell you the secrets.
So yeah, Vermin Supreme, he was very friendly to deal with too.
Yeah.
And he didn't charge too much considering that he was actually elected president.
Yes.
I thought he looked horrible as a woman though, Stang, really.
When you said he dressed up, he looked really good.
And the trans side, dress side bit just did not work on me.
He looked horrible as a woman.
Because he had these like, you know, all rouged up and rowdy chicks and cheeks.
Oh, man.
Well, actually, he looks like a wizard from Lord of the Rings.
Yeah, he does.
But that's not unusual at Starwood.
Yeah, he turns up as an old lady, you know, like when you walk up behind him and you see
they got a big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big,
He's got a bunch of long white hair.
You think it's an old lady, a 93 year old lady and you look at it's some kind of bohemian
man.
I wish I could say we would have celebrity guests at Ex Day, but, and we do, Dr. Hal,
wee ma ma the mother of Princess Wee.
The amino acids are usually there.
Yeah, well, something amino acid like.
They're superstars.
Something amino acid-like, yes.
Yeah, yeah.
And, yeah, that always happens.
And then if you happen to be a superstar and you want to come to X-Day, you're more than welcome.
Yeah, that's right.
Well, they still have to pay for the campground and us.
Are the four elements going to be there?
Earth, air, wind, and fire?
Yeah, are they going to be there?
Well, they're usually there in great strength.
In large quantities.
Especially the wind and the rain and the fire.
Yes.
Oh, wow.
And if mud counts as earth, there's usually lots of that.
Lots and lots of that.
Yeah, there's weather.
You do get weather.
We've had mostly good weather the last couple of times.
The last three times.
It's been very intemperately hot, though.
A couple of times it was, yeah, it was a complete.
But that was the whole Midwest was almost destroyed by the heat.
And there was no power anywhere in Ohio, southern Ohio, except for that campground.
That's right.
They were prepared.
We were the only, it really was like a rehearsal for X-Day.
And for the first time ever, the subgeniuses had ice and internet.
Yes.
And no one else did.
And we were told, don't tell anyone.
That we still have power or ice.
Because there were people selling bags of ice for 50 bucks in town.
Wow.
Yeah.
We didn't want to have the bikers and Amish invade and kill us, you know, for our ice.
Yep, I think that was one of the most heartwarming and stirring things that the church has ever done.
It's become the same as those avid reptiles down there who took the day off on Tuesday, I think it was.
And it was tempestuous.
It was like 98 degrees.
And the photography session was 98% or something like that.
98, 98.
And even the people who went out to get their turtles snapped off over at the turtle pond there could find no relief.
But the reptiles like it.
I mean, the reptile people like it.
They thrive in that high temperature and humidity.
Well, sure.
It's just like dangling food.
A low fruit.
A low fruit source.
It just about kills the little hairy mammals, though, which is most of the subgeniuses more fit.
Yeah.
More super, yeah.
With pouches.
Some of them do have pouches, actually.
I know.
It's a good thing we all do have pouches.
Because what would you do if you were out in the woods?
You're going to start a little fire and you realize that your kindling and some of your starter fire stuff like Utsie the Iceman is in your pouch.
And you reach down below your navel there and then your pouch is gone.
Yeah.
That's a sinking feeling.
Uh-oh.
It's going to snow pretty soon and I won't be in a nice little warm tent.
I'll be freezing my cuckoo.
Well, and for a lot of people, since that's a clothing optional campground, the really elderly ones actually go clothing free.
And they really do have pouches, but they need them.
They need them to put their car keys in.
Yeah.
The chargers for their phones.
And their phones.
And you're saying that the young and beautiful and fit and taut ones all wear clothing?
Mostly, yeah.
Well, they have the sky-clad camouflage there.
They're wearing that sky-clad camouflage.
It means you can look exactly like a 78-year-old woman with tattoos and a very, and a ponch.
What do you call it?
Up until about 2005, the young people did run around naked.
Oh, yeah.
But then the smartphones appeared and everybody had a phone.
Suddenly, grandma was on the internet.
And all the younger ones, you know, they didn't want their boss seeing what they did on the weekend.
Actually, we're pretty tight with that.
We really, really...
Well, you guys try to keep the cameras down, but it's impossible.
We do try to keep the cameras down.
It's almost impossible.
Yeah, because people just don't...
Some people don't know the camera rolls.
Brushes are okay.
Okay, because they're just...
But if, say, for instance, Floridina or one of the exes' girls were to start massaging their floral areas very protuberantly,
then you'd have to have some trouble there with your FBI and your NSA and all your other police scores.
Yeah.
Well, unless you make sure they get to have copies of all the pictures, too.
Right.
You always got to look up the popo.
We really did have FBI and so forth come to X Days to check it out.
Yes.
Back in the old days.
Oh, yeah.
There's so few people there now, they don't really...
It's like, well, how many terrorists can they possibly have?
And they all wear glasses.
They can't...
It's like a bunch of terrorists that are all pencil-knit geeks that wear glasses.
And aren't really terrorists and just play Magic the Gathering while they...
They're Canadian exchange students.
Yeah, while they listen to Dr. Howell and me rattle on and on and on and on.
Only last year, I wasn't there.
Neither were you, Dave.
What's sad is that they walk away from the event with a diminished sexual interest.
Suddenly, it's like life, like you're...
I'm real young and I'm going to take the world by the horns.
And by the time I'm 52, I'm going to own the Megaloth Empire and so forth and everything like that.
And all of a sudden, next thing you know, you're 22 and you feel like you're 92.
Yeah, but that's a real relief, you know, not to be driven anymore like that.
I mean...
Driven like a bad old car.
Yeah.
Is that what you're saying?
Like a bad old car?
Something like that.
Hey, Dave, it's getting...
We're getting up near the end of the show, as they say.
And we actually did about five minutes of stuff early.
So the internet version is going to be a little longer.
Because Brother Love did some banter with us before the show.
But anyway, I do need to say that you're...
Some people are accidentally...
For the first time in their lives, listening to The Hour of Slack, a variety show from the church of the subgenius.
A real religion disguised as a joke disguised as a real religion disguised as a joke.
Disguised as a bunch of regular folks acting better.
Better.
People around the institution, wherever they go.
In their own strange way.
Anyway, what people need to know is that they can learn more at subgenius.com.
Our prisoner friends out there who are not allowed anywhere near social media can actually do it by mail.
And so our post office box in Texas is box 807.
Glen Rose, Texas.
76043.
However, until the world ends, if anybody remembers our Cleveland address, you can use that.
Because we're here.
We're in Cleveland for...
Just until the world ends.
And then after that, we'll only show up when the world is ending.
Right.
Well, Princess We might be here a lot more than I will.
But somebody has to stay.
They, you know, mend the fences.
And, you know, rope the goats.
Speaking of the goats, Stang Ranch has 114 new kids.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Praise the holy goats.
And let's see, what can I play next?
I have to play the Goodbye Dave words.
Goodbye Dave.
But what are the words?
Oh, I thought that's what it was.
And then I just faded out.
I hate saying goodbye to Dave.
And you can keep listening, but I'm cutting.
He's out.
He's gone.
He may be able to still hear us, but he can't talk.
And now that's true also of you, Princess We.
And in a minute, well, what will I play here?
I'll just put on some Jimmy Ryan.
Reverend Jimmy Ryan.
This is an instrumental called Pipe Dream.
It's big guitar, because that's what he does.
He's a big guitar guy.
And...
And after that, if the show bleeds over into radio synesthesia,
which is coming, because Dr. Sinister is here.
Oh, look, it's the alarm that says I need to take my pill
and give the dog her pill.
Oh, no.
Yeah.
Okay, friends, so you know what I have to do.
Oh, the second cut might be...
This will be our fourth dog-titled cut on this episode.
A mishmash called...
Roswell Dogma.
By Uncle Dr. Unincannabite.
But first, Jimmy Ryan.
guitar solo