From PR News in Washington, I'm being treated for dental problems.
Cable subscribers are no longer seeing President Obama as a game Mexican bandit.
Rescuers say they now know this is PR News.
We are a bum bum.
Our finest gifts we bring are a bum bum.
To lay before the subgenius of our own.
The hangout for the homosexual.
It's filled with cornhole fun.
There are those who believe that something mysterious lives in the south of England.
Wherever there are lake monsters, there are people just like this.
Locals, visitors, scientists and investigators yearning to become lake monsters.
There's one man who supports a lake monster.
I feel blessed.
So long.
Have you noticed an upsurge in goth girls on the porno binaries news groups?
Oh boy, that sounds very, very...
Very, very, very, very, very, very, very...
Well, it's Halloween, children.
It's spooky time.
Oh, yeah.
Things are going to get weird, aren't they?
People act weird.
It's special.
It's amateur hour for the weirdos of the world.
A great little voice in the back of your head.
Welcome to it.
Till next week.
Sit down.
For two hours, they see what my world is like 365 days a year.
I thought I would be able to find my way home.
But now it seems that I'm just wandering in these pieces of chaos.
Is that like a space suit in your side someplace?
Maybe just your brain in a little jar or something like that?
Here it is straight.
One of the scientists in the last polar test claims he saw a monster.
Don't look at me like that.
These scientists claim that this monster, beast, whatever it is, it's a prehistoric thing.
And if you laugh, I'll bring you.
It's romping somewhere around the North Atlantic.
A monster.
How can she love a monster?
Let's get that through your head.
Are you dried up?
Monster.
We've been hearing sexual stuff for years.
You know, the five-day orgasm.
It all happens without physical contact.
It's only the beginning.
Why should this reality be public domain?
What's so great about it?
Maybe they gave you some drugs.
Maybe none of this is real at all.
He's going into shock.
Yeah, this is the one thing you don't think about on the show.
Maybe this is not real at all.
Well, you lower down those plastic turkeys.
You can't tell what's real and what isn't.
Lower yourselves.
You're the caller's brain.
Okay, speak now.
Or forever hold the little pieces that are left on the floor of your shattered heart.
My pain.
On the surface.
In casual conversation.
Yes.
Their piano's all great.
Yeah, yeah.
It just seemed like normal guy.
Want to trade me the rest of it for the banana?
Sure, we can trade the whole show for a couple of bananas.
Absolutely.
We've done it before.
I'm giving you great input.
Thanks for the input.
Yeah.
We have to put it in somewhere.
Might as well be here.
Doctors taught me a lot about dealing with tension.
Yeah, here we go.
No, not tense, are you, doctor?
Much better.
Now I can see that you really are a doctor.
I got a good doctor.
Hello, this is me, and I just want to say that the Stuck Genius Foundation is like.
We're in pain.
I want to declare that we are subgenius, and we must have flack because we were here first.
We are new.
We are the subgenius new.
We were here first before these bland, normal, communist society humans came into existence,
whom have dominated and occupied here in the United States and the world.
We were here first.
And we have the right to do whatever we please.
And the UFOs are in the sky.
Now, these have been meaningless to you because you're not a monster fan geek.
You're a rock and roller or some writer type or something.
You're a girl.
So you wouldn't know.
It wouldn't mean anything to you.
Because to you, a monster is just some fictitious creature of a madman's imagination.
Could a madman cough like I am coughing now?
Could a madman shriek like this?
Could a...
Slap the cuffs on him, Janie.
He's bleeding.
Huh?
I don't know.
I was just talking to myself.
Yeah, me too, man.
I'm having trouble following anything tonight because the devil.
The devil is...
The devil has gotten in there because they let the devil come in.
At Halloween, they just open their hearts to the devil.
He's looking behind every dumpster.
What are you talking about?
I'm going to take on Jesus and I'm going to get so drunk I forget about Bob.
And I'm going to grow a single horn from my head and let the demons speak from my navel.
Actually, I wish I could get that excited about Halloween.
But, you know, it's a whole world Halloween special day.
You act like somebody you're not.
Like a Frankenstein?
You have a...
You say...
You pretend you're someone else.
You have a disguise all day.
What is the purpose?
You say you act crazy.
Oh, man.
On a special day.
Yeah, I understand.
Maybe for some people it is.
It just isn't the same when you do it.
You know, I used to love Halloween and yet now it's...
Now that I do it every day.
Oh, the first time I...
Now that every day is Halloween.
Popular culture may be as much a mirror of our society
as it is a perpetuator of our best and worst.
If so, how much responsibility do we take for creating our own monsters?
Dad, can we leave the door open in France?
How's that?
I want to see an oil refinery explode.
Um, could you check the closet one more time?
I want to see a tornado hit a church on Sunday.
How's that?
I want to see some guy running through the Kmart
with an automatic weapon firing at the clerks.
Um, could you check the closet one more time?
I want to see thousands of people in the street killing policemen.
I want to hear about a nuclear meltdown.
I want to know the stock market dropped 2,000 points in one day.
I want to see people under pressure.
If anything, I...
I'm sure there's nothing under my bed.
Uh, no, no monsters here.
Uh, uh, no...
Nope, no monsters here.
Okay?
Okay.
The ideology of the external threat is integral to the Western political culture.
The propaganda model operates so vigorously.
External threats have been ingrained into journalistic practices
to the point that even in periods of peace,
it is expected for journalists to frame issues
in terms of our guys versus the bad guys.
Do not invite strangers.
And so, once again, good triumphs over evil,
and the forces of light utterly stamp into a bloody pulp
the defeated forces of darkness and disorder.
So, you say you saw some sort of monster.
You say you saw this beast, creature, werewolf,
or whatever you want to call it.
But, you know, the human mind's a funny thing.
It plays tricks.
There are no monsters anymore.
We've proved that.
We put a man on the moon.
In any case, we can't give in to him.
One, eats food, magma of underground.
Two, shoot fleeting rays.
Slow down, I'm writing this down.
Three, a gigantic angler.
The northern Pacific had a big damage.
Now, does this seem like an angler fish with a lantern hanging at the end of the sea?
I always wondered about that.
I think it says a gigantic angler.
I assume it means...
Ah.
...that.
That type of fish, yes.
It is a Japanese monster.
They are based on...
Some of them are based on marine organisms.
Let's not be racist.
We won't attribute any race to this.
Just look at it, man.
Look at the screen.
It's obviously a Japanese monster.
It's an Asian monster.
Let's just say Asian.
Well, there is a difference.
There is a difference between Hong Kong monsters like...
It's a Far East Asian.
Korean monsters like Yongari monster.
How about we say a Far East non...
And a North Peninsula Asian.
...ordinary Japanese monster like...
All right, all right.
We'll say it's an Asian island.
What's going on in L.A.?
Come on.
They come from Ozu Island.
It's not...
It's not a mainland Asian.
Long-star island.
They come from Monster Island, from happy Monster Island.
They're here from Monster Island.
Monster Island is their home.
Hup!
Some of you guys, I don't know.
It's going to be rough.
You're going to have to make...
You're going to have to make a deal with some of the squamous aliens that pass themselves off as sex goddesses.
But as Hal was saying last night, their pheromones are so strong, you won't care.
That's right.
They touched upon that in that movie Galaxy Quest.
The actor playing the actor who plays the Bones character fell in love with an alien woman on that.
And when he...
When she lost control and started squirting tentacles up out of her body,
that turned him on even more.
He was the subgenius of that movie.
Who was it that told me?
I think it was Doc Fropp.
He said,
I like my coffee like I like my women.
Anally.
It was one I wasn't expecting.
Who goes there, friend or enema?
He saved his guys in hell, right?
He was...
Bob Dobbs.
He was on the number one list of frauds and phonies for Time Magazine.
And I didn't know who he was.
And J.R. Bob Dobbs is the creator of the Church of the Subgenius.
This guy, the Reverend Ivan Stang, is one of their...
Disciples.
Disclipples.
Yeah.
All right.
You know, it's funny.
I don't think Jesus had a disciple named Dopey.
But you are so wrong, Pinkboy.
Jesus did in fact have three disciples named Dopey.
And one named Grumpy.
And one named Sneezy.
Yes, and here comes Grumpy.
And he's well named, too.
And better watch out for Sneezy or everything you know will be blown away.
Shallow, Pinkboy.
The most frozen and fearful of all the little dwarfs.
Shallow.
Shallow can hardly keep it together to do his whatever it is he, she, and his doing.
What is it doing?
It's making a chain of flowers.
No, it's meditating.
No, it's not making...
It's making the flowers, but it's meditating on higher purple.
That burning, elastic thing.
What is that?
It's...
Thinking of new ways to kill.
Ah...
It's one of the spandex...
Used to kill its victims.
Slack takes many forms, my friend.
Killing is one.
Dying is yet another for some.
who pray to die, others pray to kill.
Which are you, my friend?
Why don't you come into the bosom of Babel
or Connie, who has actually a better bosom.
Yes, a cripply bosom.
And learn all that you can know
about the forbidden sciences
and about occult incantations
that can lead you to mastery and power
over your own wallet and your own personal guardian demon.
I will wind the wand or the signet three times.
Take the alabaster pepperoni and put it near your nostrils.
The third nostril will expand and the magic door
is not so magic anymore.
Power and slack, I tell you.
Beyond your wildest imaginings.
Yeah, it is great old power.
Slack, it is called by my people.
We have yearned for slack.
For so many years.
The name we use is slug.
It sounds crude and simple to your people, I am sure.
But one of these days we will master slug
and climb from the slimy pits near the river
where we have been banged.
And we shall...
What are we going to do?
Look, there is the slack.
Now climbing up the banks of the slimy river.
Yes, it's...
It's slipping down on the muddy slope.
Hulking and looming.
Why?
You make us frat your ass.
Look at that slack.
Hulking.
That's majestically looming.
It's the grandest and greatest.
No, no, no, no, stay back.
No, no.
Yes, dear friends, slug.
I mean slack.
The hour of slug.
Slack is back.
And Princess Wee is here.
With alabaster pants.
Pepperoni.
And Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
Soon to come in.
What we've been hearing has been a lot of old subgenius radio
from WCSB in Cleveland with the late Chaz Smith,
Lonesome Cowboy Dave,
yours truly, and Princess Wee,
from KPFA in Berkeley, California,
the Puzzling Evidence Show with Dr. Philo Drummond,
Puzzling Evidence, and Dr. Hal.
Hence the word Halloween.
And big Dr. Hal fans are Halloweenies.
Phineas Narco of National Cynical Network
did a collage about our own monsters and politics,
which is what this show will be about.
And we heard a collage by Fernand and Andy Lemur
at the beginning, and also PR News,
which he has some knowledge of.
Yes, friends.
Yes, it's a...
a special night tonight.
We don't usually do timely-type shows,
and so this might seem slightly dated to all the stations
besides WCSB Cleveland, where we are right now.
But we decided to come in and do a live show tonight
because, well, it's Halloween where we are now,
in time,
no matter when you actually hear this.
And Halloween is the perfect time to do a show,
and we're going to do a show about how the monsters
are coming to Maple Street,
and why you kids should get out there
and make the broken system that much harder to break further.
Yes, we're telling you...
we're suggesting.
We can't get direct call to action
on a community station like this,
but we can suggest that you think about the possibility of...
voting.
Um...
Also, Reverend Barack Obama is in town,
in Cleveland tonight,
or he won't be there tonight.
He was.
And we're hoping he'll call in.
Many people don't know that the President
is an ordained subgenius minister,
but even before he was elected,
I believe our friend Reverend Shane Smirker,
that rapscallion in Austria,
or Australia, one of those,
the one that they have to hang from,
he bought memberships for both
Reverend Barack Obama and Reverend...
Sarah Palin.
Although we never have...
we haven't heard from Miss Palin.
I hope this, uh...
I hope everything is working here.
Princess, well, you might help me keep an eye on these...
Oh, but of course!
But of course I'll keep an eye on that.
The blinky lights out here.
Of course, I'm looking for the green flashing light.
You can be the engineer.
That means that Dave is calling.
Well, or Barack.
Or Barack.
Barry may be calling in.
Could be.
Although, I doubt if he's gonna do it again this year.
Probably not.
You know, I mean, he's done it twice and...
He's a busy guy.
But, uh...
Yes, friends, we're doing a horror show
about what will happen if you cynical, jaded, disillusioned subgeniuses
don't get out and vote on Tuesday.
It's Tuesday.
Not yet, it's not Tuesday.
Well, it was Tuesday already last week.
Don't go down there and try to vote today.
Or you could try.
Although, I guess some people could.
Yeah, sure.
Why not?
But, you know, Princess, we told me that on...
What's that website that everybody does now instead of alt-slack?
Facebook, that's it.
They were...
She said the young...
Some of the subgeniuses were laughing at the election.
They were planning not to vote because they're cool and cynical and they seem to think the
system's broken.
Can you believe it?
Broken?
But I think it's only broken in places and could eventually be repaired, hopefully to
my exact specifications.
It's much like a child's smash toy moving along at a strange speed and banging against
walls and stopping every once in a while and then starting again.
It's broken, but it still does something.
That's better than having no toy at all.
Well, it's a sad thing when we have to think of our democracy as a system.
It's a toy, don't you think?
I've always...
You know, I would love to be in the position where I could use it as a toy and sling it
around and hit other kids with it.
Well, actually, I guess that's what some people get to do.
That kind of reminds me of the last...
The previous administration, which, by the way, was all my fault.
I'm here to confess to you, Dave, and the listeners.
I was the reason that George Bush was elected.
I was so sure he'd lose that I wasted my vote on a third party candidate.
I didn't really like the third party candidate.
I just liked the idea of a third party.
I knew he wouldn't win.
I thought Gore would.
But, so see, that's what happened.
Gore lost the ability to steal the election by one vote.
And...
George got to steal the election by that one vote.
And that vote was mine.
So, kids, every time you don't vote, you're actually voting twice for somebody who wants
to kill you.
Think about it.
I...
Oh, what a hell prescription.
I thought of it and didn't like the idea.
Me either.
According to the Onion that I got in the mail, the Republicans are going to win at least
916 gubernatorial seats.
So we're toast.
Unless our race is...
Our Republican friends, like Mr. Sister, who lives down the street from us, unless they
stick up for us when Homeland Security comes for us, we're going to be declared obsolete.
Obsolete.
I had to beg, Mr. Sister, don't let the beggars come and Anne Frank me.
Please help me, Mr. Sister.
He said he would intervene.
What?
I have to go.
So...
So you're going to be a gentleman.
You know, he could know the place you hide in your basement.
Right.
I remember when I was younger man or person that as a way of showing our discontent, we
would often vote for Alfred E. Newman, which was our idea of none of the above at the time.
And he was narrowly defeated quite a few times.
Well, and in a way he ended up getting elected.
What?
Well, Alfred E. Newman, or someone who very much like him, from Texas, or ostensibly from Texas.
Yeah, actually, he's from Australia.
They don't want you to know that Bush was really born in Australia.
Right. He was really in Australia.
I never saw his birth certificate.
Did you?
And he's also a religiously a Pangean hypocrite and a foreskin identuator.
And he's also been known to clasp strange objects to his bosom and cry in the middle of the night.
And I don't think that's the kind of man we wanted, but it's too late.
Well, I'm not going to blame everything on Bush because I don't, you know, that's what they say liberals do.
But actually, I blame everything on the conspiracy, which can take any form, my friend, either the good cop or the bad cop.
Now, some of my friends, they say, well, I'm not going to vote because that validates their good.
I'm going to vote because that validates their good cop, bad cop system.
And I used to think that way myself, but I'd rather have the good cop.
There's always going to be cops.
Why not pick the one that doesn't hit you as hard?
Yeah.
That's right.
Or at least the cop you prefer.
He doesn't have to be better.
Some people like the bad cop.
Some people love to pay the conspiracy to take their money away and give it to rich people.
But that won't count.
They whine.
Maybe, maybe not.
Only one way to be sure it won't count, and that's to not vote.
Then you know for certain that your vote went to the worst guy.
Just think of all those foreign countries where your vote is totally worthless.
Although our vote may only be worth a farthing, at least it has some monetary value.
In some lands, a vote is merely an action ordained by the class in power to make them feel nice.
And they get to watch the evening news.
Well, they also watch the noses.
The evening noose.
That's the hangings every day.
Noose.
They watch the evening noose to see when they...
Which is going to have your neck in it, buddy, if you don't get out there and protect yourself with that broken system.
Not you, Dave.
Well, no, I have no broken system.
I have no system.
Right.
But, you know, as we look far into the future, what kind of chance does a returning home war vet have for a better job and...
A new pair of shoes.
A returning home dead war vet have, and more shoes.
Yeah.
I did not...
Very much, I wouldn't assume, because the wars will never end, regardless of who we vote for.
Right.
Evidently.
The endemic poverty, which is getting worse, will never end, because that isn't part of it.
Well, I don't know.
That's not necessarily true.
You can't predict the future.
I quit...
Around the middle of 1998, for some reason, I quit making predictions myself.
But, you know...
You never know when some super genius is going to suddenly invent a great, you know, invention that will feed and clothe everybody.
In fact, we saw Twilight Zone last night about this guy who stumbles into a small town where they can't let him leave.
Because he stumbled upon their secret that years in the past, a super genius came to this town and gave him the gift of eternal energy and life and health.
And the...
Which could also be used to destroy the world.
So, they...
And he says, you people in this town can keep this wonderful stuff, but don't ever let it out, because the normals will use it to destroy the planet.
And, of course, our hero, who stumbles into all this, immediately tries to escape with the secrets, which would destroy the planet, proving them right.
And it just goes to show...
Whoever John Galt is, he's nowhere near as cool as J.R. Bob Dobbs.
Price Bob.
John Galt.
Yeah.
You know that Ayn Rand stuff?
The objectivist?
Well, I'm a subjectivist.
I'm the exact opposite of those heartless fools.
And I will do the exact opposite of whatever the John Galt or teabagger conspiracy tells me to do.
I'll do the opposite.
That's my reason for living.
Is to do the opposite of what the conspiracy tells me to do.
And I must agree with you.
I fashioned a crude form of life for myself, which in many ways is the opposite of the teabag idea of what things should be like.
And I'm quite proud of it right now.
Although there are some large blue stains on the floor that I think come from some sort of material imported to my house from a nearby area.
A military armaments factory.
I still maintain...
That thing you created is still alive?
No, I'm still maintaining a slow argumentative erection.
But the things are trying to live.
I can see they're, you know, they move every once in a while.
Oh, yeah.
There's some semblance of...
It's hard to kill anything.
Yeah, I've been jumping up and down on them.
I swear at them.
Anything mean.
It's real easy to kill.
You can't kill anything nice.
Yeah.
Dave is a killer?
It's hard to kill them.
A killer of nice things.
Well, they're easy.
For instance, your flowers.
Yeah, they're easy to kill.
Lions, they're very hard to kill.
People.
Not so easy.
Not as much as you'd wish.
First, you have to bite them real hard.
You don't have nearly as big of a mouth as a lion.
Your teeth aren't nearly as sharp.
So it is difficult for humans to...
Well...
Oh, in the movies, they just stick.
They stick a knife in somebody's gut,
just like it's easy, and they fall over.
But if you ever, God, ever actually try to stick a knife in somebody's gut,
you really have to push and twist.
I mean, it's messy.
It's just not like in the movies.
You know this from first hand or first foot?
You have actually twisted a knife.
Well, of course, I'm...
I've heard these, that sort of thing.
Charlie used to talk about them.
His girls used to talk about them.
Oh, God.
And he traveled.
Yeah.
That was back in the...
Back in the day, though.
Oh.
Dear listeners, I would like to dedicate this hour of slack
to a Potter Nostril whose birthday is the day
that we happen to be recording this hour of slack.
His birthday's every Halloween, isn't it?
Every Halloween.
What a coincidence.
It's always Halloween on his birthday.
Happy birthday, Potter Nostril.
Hello, Charlie.
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday, Potter Nostril.
Well, that's all he's going to get from us.
And also, my witchy friends are having Halloween together.
Now, look, we're not doing shout-outs on you.
We're shouting.
I'm shouting.
I've been shouting for minutes now in a row.
It's all shouting now.
My Halloween shouts.
Shout your mouth.
Many, many, many devious and dubious types
were born around this time of the year.
Yees.
To name a few, besides Potter Nostril,
Mephistopheles, the great, was born this time of the year.
Also, Tutankhamen, the invincible monster,
was dragged under a bus last Tuesday.
I don't know how that relates to...
Well, according to the research of Reverend Imgur,
Anne Frank died on the very moment that Henry Winkler,
who played the Fonz, was conceived.
Therefore, Henry Winkler, the Fonz,
was the reincarnation of Anne Frank.
But I think he died, didn't he?
Henry Winkler?
Yeah, so I don't know.
I don't know.
Maybe I have him mixed up with some other beloved dead actor
whose show I never watched even once.
He said proudly.
Maybe it was Patsy.
Wasn't that one of the names of one of the characters?
I don't know, Dave.
I'm not the guy to ask.
I think that there was a Patsy.
Now, if you want to ask me about Twilight Zones,
I can tell you who was the main star, the title, who wrote them.
Now, who was the original?
The one we saw last night was the first one we've ever seen
that wasn't...
Photographed by George T. Clemens.
Can you believe it?
I believe it because I've been witnessing it with you.
I never knew Mark Twain was a member of the Twilight Zone cast.
He was the director of photography for the Twilight Zone.
Yeah, after he quit writing, he became a director of photography.
Samuel Clemens was an actual photographer,
or cameraman for the crew then.
Right.
For every Twilight Zone up until...
That explains a lot about Huckleberry Finn stuff.
Well, yeah.
And, yeah, every Twilight Zone up until the fifth season.
That was photographed by that guy.
Yep.
I've gotten to where it's like as soon as the first bars of music hit,
I can tell you who composed the score.
Really?
Bernard Herrmann, Jerry Goldsmith, or who.
By the way, the music in the background tonight is by the great Hans Salter.
Hans J. Salter did most of the music for the Universal Monster Pictures
in the 30s and 40s.
Hans.
Let's have a Hans for Hans.
Hans J. Salter.
Some juicy clarinets there.
Ha.
Well, that was Igor on the clarinet.
They actually had the guy that Igor's character was based on
was a member of the orchestra.
Of course, he couldn't be in the movie because he was too ugly.
They had to have Bela Lugosi play him
because he was kind of a cute version of ugly.
But quite a humanly effort on his part
for doing all the stand-ins and all the double trills.
You know, that's a pretty hard instrument to play.
Mm-hmm.
Well, Princess Weep plays that instrument.
The flute.
Yes.
The flute is not the clarinet.
She's a flautist.
No, it's not a clarinet.
It's very different.
No, it's quite different.
One is a reed instrument.
And when Igor didn't really even play the...
He played a homemade flute made from a human bone.
A femur, I think.
It was either a human femur or a lemur femur.
But it would have been a very large lemur.
And he merrily missed high C.
Oh.
Fair enough.
Well, I don't know.
I'm trying to be glib on such an evening before an evening before
that is so romantic in this land.
Could possibly be a dangerous one.
A dangerous Tuesday for some of us.
Could we speculate, perhaps, on what might happen
if the Tea Partiest actually ascend to the throne of gesticulation?
Well, I don't know.
Let's see.
I'm on...
I'm not really worried.
What would they have against me?
Just because I'm known to commonly associate with...
I mean, at times, I've perhaps been real good friends with
pagans, Jews, Muslims, queers, or other types of homosexuals,
weirdos, the differently-sained, the differently-abled,
the differently-colored.
The differently-sained.
A lot of the differently-colored, actually.
I've never even been able to land on a...
It seems like everybody's different-colored.
Isn't that weird?
And parts of me are different.
That's what...
I wish I could all be one color, but I'm kind of spotty.
Yeah, in your case, I usually...
So, you know, Dave, yeah, and I know that you have been on record
as questioning the status quo.
Specifically under the Republican...
In fact, there's recordings of us making fun of Republicans and...
Oh, did you...
You heard about the protest...
There was like some Democrat protester was at a Rand Paul rally last week
and she dared to be sarcastic or had a sarcastic costume on.
She got kind of close to Rand Paul and Governor Rocknar,
the subgenius who happened to be standing there.
He was a volunteer at the time.
And the volunteer bag party bagged her and threw her on the ground
and kind of stood on her head.
Now, here's the funny thing about it.
Kind of stood on her head.
The guy that got in trouble for standing on her head
was wearing a Don't Tread On Me button.
Oh, that is ironic.
The boingboing.com pointed that out.
But yeah, if you blow up the picture, you can see he's got the little
Don't Tread On Me button.
And while he treads on someone who dared not even to interrupt,
but just to wear a sarcastic outfit and have a sarcastic sign.
So that's what you can look forward to, friends.
If you want a picture of the future,
imagine a face stomping on a human boot forever.
Saying don't...
Wearing a T-shirt saying don't stomp on my face.
Right.
The funny thing is we have Reverend Modemak brought a big
Don't Tread On Me flag to X Day.
Don't Tread On Me.
He did a great drill about five years ago.
Indeed he did.
We still have it.
And we have a wonderful photograph of a car driving over him
as he's wearing that flag.
It says don't tread on me.
And there's actual tire treads going across poor Modemak.
There you go.
You know, I noticed that those Rand Paul fans didn't stomp on
Rocknar's head because he's probably too big to knock to the ground.
Yes.
The person.
They've taken the whole crowd to pull him down.
The person's head who was being stomped on, I believe, was a woman.
Sort of a light-framed woman.
Well, she deserves it for daring to question the great Rand Paul
and all that he stands for.
What do they think this is, a democracy?
What do they think is going on here?
You know, this show alone, kids,
if you don't get out and...
and vote on Tuesday for somebody who's not going to kill us,
they'll probably kill us just because of this show that we're doing right now.
And Christine O'Donnell will turn you into a toad.
Oh, my God.
Can you imagine, speaking of Christine O'Donnell,
what if the so-called liberal press,
I mean, if the so-called conservative press
had gotten a hold of a liberal lady who had claimed to have dabbled
in the press, and she was going to kill her.
And the way the conservatives use the word dabble now is,
oh, everyone does that when they're 17.
They light a cat on fire and put a candle in their rumpus
and say some gibberish that sounds like the Necronomicon.
But in reality, had she been a flaming liberal,
she probably would have indeed been set afire
much in the way the witches were set afire
back in Middle Ages Europe.
That's because everyone knows that liberals all want women
to practice witchcraft and become lesbians and leave their husbands.
It's not because they care about the women.
It's because they hate America.
I've been told that over and over again by the liberal-controlled media,
that the liberals control the media and they hate America.
And I've been told what they think.
I've never told what anybody else thinks, only what liberals think.
And yet, I know tons of so-called liberals,
and I've never heard a single one of them bring up any of the stuff
that liberals think.
They're constantly being described as thinking.
So they must be thinking it real quietly.
Well, some liberal husbands do want their wives to practice witchcraft
and become part-time lesbians, you know, when they're around.
Yeah, if they can take pictures, sure.
Well, who wouldn't?
I mean, come on, boys.
The average liberal is no different than any other average Joe,
except for he hasn't been steeped in tea for three weeks.
He has ideas.
That fall on fallow ground here in this land.
People just don't...
Well, some don't get it.
Now, as I understand it, I've been told over and over again
that no liberal has ever been able to support himself or herself,
that they're all supported.
They're all either rich elites and or, at the same time,
ignorant welfare queens.
Yeah.
That's all there is, is rich elite welfare queens,
who only will show up at a Jon Stewart rally if they're paid to or if there's free food.
Well, they usually show up in Broham Cadillacs and that sort of thing.
That's what they're supposed to do.
The Cadillac has a TV antenna on top.
No, on welfare, but the Cadillac has a TV antenna on top.
They never had to work.
Nobody who ever voted for a Democrat ever has worked.
I've actually read that.
Several times a day for the last several weeks
because I'm dumb enough to continue to examine those comments
that people can leave after news stories on the Internet now.
Well, did you know that one of the very, very best criteria for becoming a president
is to have actually run a major corporation disguised as a small business?
Right, yeah.
That's the only experience anybody needs.
Right.
Well, you know, here's...
Here's the sad thing.
I'm probably what you'd call a bleeding-heart liberal.
That's what some people would call me.
I call myself a middle...
Exactly the middle of the road.
You can zero your meter on me.
But I'm actually...
I run a small business,
and we sell stuff that's manufactured here in Cleveland Bluffs, Ohio,
using mostly American...
American...
Made goods.
And...
And I...
We didn't actually take handouts from anybody.
I've never been on the dole or unemployment or anything my whole life.
I've always had at least two jobs.
It's now un-American to buy American.
Real patriots buy foreign cars
because they don't want to shop with government motors.
I noticed that.
I'm taking in your voice there
because it is hard to tell what they want us to do.
I'm trying, though.
I personally am giving it my best.
I want to know what they want us to do
so I can do the exact opposite, like I said.
It's just a devilish thing about me.
You know, if everybody else is going to be a brown shirt
stomping down the street waving a flag,
then I'm probably going to be hiding in some Dutch person's cubbyhole.
Well, I'll probably...
Hoping that they don't find out what non-religion I'm not.
I don't know.
I don't know if you remember a dream I told you I had one time.
I awoke to find myself surrounded by Nazis.
And suddenly, and I didn't want them to know that I wasn't one of them.
It was like the Nazi army.
It was like the SA or something like that.
And so I donned the stuff,
as much of the stuff as I could find.
The helmet and the coat and the boots were far too big for me.
So everybody was forced to start marching in line
and we were going to go.
We crushed the Stangs and the Subgenie
and all the other unwanted scum of society.
And I was elected to be in the crew
that was going to go out and do that.
And it just felt so weird wearing all those funny clothes that didn't fit.
And you thought this was a dream?
Oh, I had doubts about it, but I still thought it was a dream.
Submitted for your consideration.
Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
Then you rescued the princess.
A hapless schlub.
Who thinks he's having a dream
about his country being taken over by Nazis.
But in fact, Dave has just crawled into a zigzag tunnel
that we like to call the Twilight Zone.
I'm sorry, I seem to do that every show, don't I?
Actually, at home I do it every hour.
But if you were a pea partyist,
you would cut away to a commercial.
I'm sorry, I'm a pea partyist.
So enamored of everyone.
If I had the right kind of talk show,
we'd be getting paid,
and we'd run commercials for buy gold
and all that stuff.
And frozen armatures and wasted money.
Golly.
Glenn Beck has an audience of millions,
and we only have an audience of ten.
But...
But on the other hand,
there's ten million drunken high school dropout rednecks
bitching about that black guy.
And he gets to be president!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
And this is good.
So I hope they're...
You know, it's...
The poor guy's not...
I'll be really surprised if he can...
stand after the next two years.
But, um...
But...
Boy, it sure was fun to watch those people
squirm in impotent anger for the last couple of years.
The sheer blistering,
insecurity-based hatred of these guys,
who, you know,
they haven't even been able to make it to assistant manager
at the McDonald's without getting fired.
And hear this, this, this...
Well, I don't want to say it,
but he not only graduated from Harvard,
but became president.
That's just not fair!
No, it's not.
I've got to admit,
it's been a great couple of years so far,
watching that...
Just listening to the grinding of their teeth.
On the other hand, it gets kind of scary.
Because, you know, where we might have...
Where we might have been...
Where your average liberal back three years ago
might have been saying,
I think George Bush should be tried for treason.
What you hear now is,
Obama should be tried for treason,
and then...
And then executed for military treason!
It's amazing how many...
I wish y'all could have seen me when I did that.
I wish you could have seen him, too.
My veins were all over the place.
Every vein on his face has popped out.
His face is bright red right now.
I was just imitating other people, though.
I'm actually not a very angry guy anymore.
Speaking of that,
did you know that Glenn Beck
has been...
has been considered the same
as many of the...
the subgenius speakers
when they give their rants?
There was supposedly some famous preacher
in the South in the 1920s.
I forget his name.
Perhaps you remember.
And he actually initialized a speaking style
which extols the audience
to do things they wouldn't normally do
just because he's foaming at the mouth.
And Beck was...
You can go point by point,
and he uses that technique.
It's an old tent-go-to-meeting type of...
pounding on things voice.
Right.
Yeah.
It's a way to get people riled up,
and it's real easy to get people riled up.
They don't understand that rhetoric, do they?
Especially if they're stupid.
But that's okay.
Can you believe our poor country
is so drowned, did, in rhetoric
that we jump like little weasels
every time the fanny barks, you know?
It's just too much to complain about.
No, it's not.
Let's keep complaining, man.
I love it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I agree.
It's free country.
We're supposed to bitch and gripe all the time, right?
Yeah, but we're not supposed to do anything about it.
Right, right.
Dare you actually do anything about it?
Well, I wouldn't want to issue a call to arms at this point
because there's too many people with their fingers on triggers.
They don't care what they're going to shoot at,
but they're going to shoot at something.
One finger on the trigger
and the other one in the derriere.
You know, it was only 90 years ago
that women got the vote.
In America.
Well, that's where...
And these women...
They never should have been allowed to learn to read.
...that are not voting are just...
If you would read that history of the suffragettes
and see what those women went through,
and the worst thing about it all was
it actually was not a codified law.
It was a cultural thing that women didn't vote.
Right, they could have voted.
It just wasn't done.
They would have had to have been that first one
to not go to the back of the bus.
They would have turned the lady away at the polls,
for being unladylike.
And an officer without the recourse of law
would have enjoined the fray
to escort the lady out.
What the hell of a kind of place is this?
And just think of 100 years ago,
he could be shot on sight
just for being an Indian or an African American.
And say, well, he got in my way.
I was trying to pass on the left.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's hard to imagine, actually,
the way things were not all that long ago
and how easy it would be
for it to all slide right down.
Right back to that.
Look at the country of Iran.
At different times,
they've been the most civilized,
free, freedom-loving,
knowledgeable,
scientifically advanced country in the world.
Several times they've been that way.
And then there's these in-between periods
when it's the baggers take over.
Mm-hmm.
And that can happen anywhere.
I've actually, Princess,
we and I, in 2004,
we were in Hamburg, Germany,
and had to listen while young Germans said to us,
we're kind of concerned about this fascism
rising up in America.
It is true.
And they would know from the tales
that grandfather told him.
Well, German schools are actually
probably a little better than all Americans.
The worst German schools are probably better
than most of the best American schools.
They were listening to the news.
And we call them gymnasiums.
That shows how it's culturally illiterate.
Yeah.
Well,
those who can't do, teach.
Those who can't teach, teach gym.
And those who can't teach gym,
interview each other
on podcasts.
The media ditch is full of corpses again tonight.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yes.
I'm hoping you do this
before the evening is over.
I hope that all young,
brave men and women,
out there,
between the ages of 25 and 93,
expecting your next birthday
to be much the same
as it was their last birthday,
to put on a new pair of pants,
a new pair of shoes,
perhaps a fedora,
and stride out the door
and hold their arms open wide
and look up at the sky and scream,
F...
I...
No.
I forgot what I was saying.
That's okay.
Okay, Dave,
because you know what I have in front of me?
No.
I have...
No, I know you don't.
I have in front of me
something you posted on Scrub Genius
earlier today or yesterday.
Would you like me to read it
in a lonesome cowboy, Dave?
You mean you're reading it from the monitor
from the computer at the studio.
You don't have it in front of you.
No, I do.
I have it printed out.
It doesn't spatially exist that way.
No, I printed it out.
Oh, yeah.
Here, I'll do it in a lonesome cowboy, Dave voice.
Talk the way you used to talk
when you were from Texas.
Why I will vote.
Mostly because I can.
Many sub-geni feel the system
is so corrupted by corporate interests
that any democratic procedure
is doomed to failure.
But as an individual with a fiery zeal
for true democrazy,
I implore you to ignore
those correctly made assumptions.
If there aren't more people at the polls
than TP people,
they will not have to falsely prove their case
in a more semi-rigged way.
So I will vote just to show
those TP types
that I don't like the world they want.
Kind of like when Chancellor Hitler won.
Lots of people voted
just to make a personal statement.
Please don't let Hitler win.
Gulp.
If Christine O'Donnell
and all them other idiots win
like the rigged polls predict,
it will be easy.
It will easily be as bad here
as when Bush reigned.
I know O'Donnell's behind,
not carnally,
but the others are not, see?
That was by lonesome cowboy Dave.
Well,
our friend Sinfaltvis Ex Mortis replied,
yeah, if everyone stops voting
because the system is broken,
I can't do the New York accent,
then the only ones to win
are the breakers of the system.
It's all one big conspiracy
to get you to stop voting,
so rebel against the conspiracy
and vote, damn it.
I concurred.
Yes, you concurred.
You said,
I remember when Gore lost,
quote unquote,
and then they finally announced it,
though Gore,
had conceded the count,
which resumed after Scalia, Thomas, etc.,
made their one-time-only deal,
showed that Gore won Florida
by a squeaky 15,000-some votes.
On top of that,
he'd actually won the national
by a few mil.
I would never have been much of a supporter
of any politician, said Dave,
except the screwjob to what it veiled
has since become so obvious,
and we're 10 years beyond that mind.
And they wonder
why some malcontents urinate their pants
at the BMV in protest,
and have the suits come with disinfectant?
Does that make any more sense to you
than now that you're hearing
Lonesome Cowboy anyway?
Then this anarchist said,
well, I'm not going to vote
because it's all wrecked.
And Artemia Salinas said,
my motto is,
if subgeni are the only ones who vote,
then subgeni will be the only ones
who participate in elections
from a voting standpoint.
Which is kind of a circadian,
secular statement saying sort of nothing.
I like that.
No, it's logical.
Susie the floozy said,
I'm only voting so I can get
the free orange juice and donut
and the $25 and being able to pick up a bundle,
any bundle, out of the cop's evidence locker.
I'm not accepting the free foot rub, though.
That's twisted.
Tater said,
they had hamburgers and chips
down in Lumley where Tater voted.
And I said,
I said,
us said, actually,
Princess We and Me,
us spelled USA.
We used to love voting
in the old folks apartment building
because the hot dogs the old ladies sold.
But now we enjoy voteeing
in the elementary school
because we love the smell
of elementary school paste
and cafeteria hamburgers.
And plus, the last time I voted,
my guy won.
It was the first time that happened
in over a decade.
So who knows?
Maybe I'll hit the jackpot.
Oh, God.
And on top of that,
it just reminds me,
I've got jury duty coming up.
And I'm not even going to fight it
because I figure it's my civic duty
because if I was the suspect,
I'd sure as hell want somebody like me
on the jury.
So I'm going to go on and do it.
To be honest, Reverend Stang,
the last time we voted in our neighborhood
in the new voting place,
there was someone selling
maybe burgers or hot dogs,
but there was also someone
who was selling falafel sandwiches
complete with vegetables
that she grew in her
Cleveland Heights garden.
Falafels?
Homemade falafels?
Homemade falafels.
Communist Muslim Kenyan.
Trader.
That's Cleveland Heights.
A communist Muslim Kenyan.
Yeah.
They were amazing.
Communist Muslim kingdom.
That would be...
I think that would be
a great TV situation ploy.
Communist...
What was it again?
I missed the middle part.
Communist Muslim Trader...
Kenyan.
Communist Muslim...
Nazi...
Nazi communist.
I guess...
I hear that a lot.
That's kind of weird.
I mean, Nazis were fascists.
I mean, there's like,
well, you're the National Socialist Party.
It means they're socialists.
Actually, it was accent on the national,
not the...
And when they said socialists,
that's not what they meant.
Well, it's odd of them
to throw Muslims together
with atheist communists as well.
It doesn't make much sense
that these people
who are so infected
with the hyperbole of a deity
and these other people,
who are so disconnected
from any idea of a deity,
I think that, well,
I...
I don't know
who they are.
Who wanted to do that?
It would be like
endorsing negativist
Sunday night bowlers
who congeal with
fractured...
I don't know.
You can't put those
two opposite things together
very well.
I can't.
I can't put any of it
together anymore.
I don't know.
All I know is that
you're listening to
The Hour of Slack
from the Church of the Subgenius,
broadcast tonight
from the lovely studios
of WCSB Cleveland.
And if you want to know
more information
about The Hour of Slack
or hear the last 1280 shows,
this is 1,281,
you can look at
Subgenius,
genius.com
or write to us,
subgenius,
at P.O. Box
Cleveland Heights,
Ohio,
44118.
And your lack of prayers
will be answered.
And if you don't
pray at the polls,
who knows what monsters
from the id
will rise up
and die.
We'll see you next time.
Booting and stomping
in their shiny black boots,
taking away your slack
or forcing slack upon you
that is not your slack,
but their slack.
Nyag hol.
That's from the SIG HAL.
The horror.
A drink of rancorous juices.
So kids,
vote for whoever you want to,
but just go ahead
and do something.
Don't just do nothing,
because if you do nothing,
you don't really have the right
to complain to me anymore.
How many YouTubes,
right,
how many YouTubes
do you think there already are
showing needless
hypocritic youth
pyroflagellating,
for example?
And just think of yourself
as one of those
pyroflagellates,
one of those people
who have actually
extended themselves
and may lose a grip
and actually lose a grip.
And actually explode
from the inwards out.
And friends...
Then you know you're doing
the right thing for Bob.
That's right.
If you don't do it
for your country,
at least do it for Bob.
And now,
we must go off the air,
because the time
has come
for us to go.
The time is easy.
Dave, I'm fading you out.
I'm fading out slow.
Yes, fading out slow.
There he goes.
Poor thing.
Listen to that.
Oh, there he goes.
He's gone.
And, uh,
and I...
Shh.
I'll fade that out.
Oh, my God.
What happened?
Uh, this.
From PR News in Washington,
I'm Dan.
A top White House
economic advisor says
Chinese exports surged
last month,
helping it to overtake Germany
as the world's largest surger.
Figures released
by Chinese Customs
on Sunday
showed 34%
and 8,
even $586
sloping foreign PR news.
Analysts point out
that good
Christian Malaysians
are praying for
national extremist attacks
today.
The attacks have been sparked
by high courts
ruling to allow
PR news
in their prayers
and this
is PR news.
The Dallas Cowboys
crushed Israel
34 to 14.
Dallas head coach
Wade Phillips says
I mean, we, uh,
I would,
I was about to
turn into weather
and much of the PR news
are still in Washington.
You say,
you can't save money.
It's easy as pie.
Brown bag your lunch
instead of going out.
$6 saved a day
times five days a week
times 10 years
is 21,000 bucks.
That's a lot of lettuce.
Small changes today,
big bucks tomorrow.
Hear more from
the Talking Piggy Bank
at feedthepig.org.
A public service announcement
from the Ad Council
and your friends
at WCSB.