If you enjoy assembling your own high fidelity or stereophonic sound systems
with their complicated components and speakers on every wall,
then you will be especially interested in what I'm about to show you.
I have just developed what I consider the latest in sound reproduction.
This is designed for those persons who desire simplicity rather than fidelity.
As you can see, there is only one speaker, nor is that the only improvement.
We have also eliminated the old fashioned record changer.
Now only two attachments are necessary.
A small crank and a hearing aid.
By the way, neither of those items is needed for our next number.
The subgenius, our own slash.
And he has power to give life unto the image of the beast.
That's the image.
The image of the beast should both speak and cause that as many as would not worship the image of the beast should be killed.
Because of all, both small and great, rich and poor, free and enslaved,
to receive a mark in their right hand or in their foreheads,
and that no man might buy or sell except he that had the mark.
And the name of the beast is the number of his name.
Mark, name of the beast, or the number of this show, of his name, of this.
Here is wisdom.
Let him that has understanding count the number of the beast, for it is the number of a man.
The number of a man.
His name.
His number is 600, three score and six.
Thank you, Father, for the anointing of the Holy Spirit.
We bring into captivity every thought, every intent, every heart, and every mind.
Now we consider the eternal truth of your word.
Now we confront the plans of Satan.
That's what we need as a good.
We've got to get a bunch of bobbies to just off themselves.
Just get a bunch of bobbies, like a hundred bobbies, just get them to off themselves.
And then we'll have great advertising for the subgenius webpage,
which totally kicks ass over any kind of Heaven's Gate webpage.
And that's it.
You know, it'll be great.
I mean, maybe they even have this in the works or something.
I don't know.
But, uh,
Well, I kinda got a homesick feeling that I'm faking that it won't be long till I live.
You know, part of the problem is that we're in as far as Cancer is concerned, as many
of you who have been in emergency situations as us all know, they're getting extended service
The timing is going to strike a balance between what I intended.
Jim Bakker said
When you help The Shepherd, you're helping the Sheep.
the irreverent Friday Jones, and...
Where are we? Where are we?
I know where we are because I've been keeping count.
Have you been keeping count, sheeple children?
For this is a very propitious Hour of Slack show,
for this is Hour of Slack number 666.
Ah, yes.
The Harvest.
I never thought we'd make it this far, friends.
I thought for sure we'd be ruptured last July,
but now, as we enter 1999,
which is, after all, 1,666 upside down.
No. Yeah, that's right.
And did you know that 666 times 3 equals, yes, 1998?
The Antichrist was born last year inside my Macintosh.
Macintosh.
But I don't want to get lost in the spirit, my friends.
I want to tell you something that blesses my heart.
Can't you feel it, children?
Can't you feel that these are the last days,
the very end times themselves?
For are there not every day in our newspapers and Internet
signs and portents, my friends, signs in the heavens,
omens and divine hints from the before life?
It's just like the Roman.
It's just like the Roman Empire just before the Roman Empire fell.
And the prophecy, the prophecy.
Let he who hath subwisdom know
it is the number of a man with a pipe and a grin,
and that number is 999.
Yes, for as we know, friends, within subgenius numerology,
999 is Bob's number, for Bob is the Antichrist.
The Antichrist.
Not the Christ.
He ain't that well connected, but certainly the sworn-born enemy
of that old fiend, old split-tongue,
the Antichrist of the conspiracy.
The embodiment, friends, of evil,
which will lead the pinks astray
under a false subgenius one-world religion
that will lead the sheeple into a perpetual timeless bondage
to their TV sets upon which,
they shall see him, the one who gives life to the image of the beast.
That's me.
And the image of the beast is the computer-animated 3D Bob,
which is what I've been working on in my lab all this time,
and Dr. Legume, too.
We're bringing life to the image of the beast.
Bob's not around.
Who's to say he didn't mean for us to do this?
Anyway, I say this all right out in the open, friends,
to ensure disbelief.
Hiding it right in front of everybody's faces.
That's right.
Luke Skywalker is going to have to whoop me
if he wants to shut down the Antichrist.
Heh.
Eh.
Actually, that would make a good movie.
Actually, friends, you know,
the millennium is a nice, round, even number
for the humans and crackpots to fixate on.
Everybody knows that the...
that the...
have no resources.
Oh, yeah.
I've used, you know, on the Internet,
They're at birth control.
They're going to have to go ahead and put my hands up.
For any reason.
it's only, let's see,
half a top high on the horizon.
So that's still out in the space than it should be,
from the old four-track T-Act reel-to-reel
and jolted it back to shambling life
so that I might share with you listeners
for the first time in years
the old media barrage.
Number eight, the 666 special
direct from the master tape,
which may actually sound kind of glitchy
on this beat-up old machine.
Plus, Lordy Mercy, dear friends,
the Fire Sign Theater
has a new album out,
and it's great, it's perfect,
and it's about this final day.
And you youngins will soon realize
why the Fire Sign Theater
was probably the biggest influence
on my poor teenage brain
in the early 1970s
and all through the 70s
besides Zap Comics and The Three Stooges.
Their new album, friends, is called
Give Me Immortality.
Give Me Immortality or Give Me Death.
And this music,
in the background,
was by
Ennio Morricone
from the Italian movie
L'Antichristo.
Yes, the music of the Antichrist.
Oh, listen, I can hear him.
I can hear the devil fiddling.
And with his big farmer boot
gonna come stomping down.
Bob's gonna come down with his big pipe,
and that farmer's gonna come down,
take his big boot,
and we're gonna stomp out the devil.
We're gonna root him out.
We're gonna root out the hate.
Yeah, yeah.
Half of you be the big dog with the big boy.
be the poor little scared dog. Are you ready? Big dogs first. Bow, wow, wow. Ooh, dog on
bow. When you live in a computer-generated world that you've created on your own, are
you not the god of that world? These are the implications of virtual reality, and they've
got to make us wonder how this could possibly fulfill the prophecy of the image of the beast.
You can see how important it is to have this video, and if you round that gift off to $100,
I'll throw in my brand-new book, In the Name of Satan.
I believe that 10% is good enough for Jesus. It ought to be enough for Uncle Sam.
He starts to roar out against you. You say, wait just a minute, Mr. Devil. I'm not fighting
this battle. You can roar all you want to toward me, but I'm going to tell Jesus on
you. Hallelujah, hallelujah. It's a safe way. He said, no lion shall be thine. He said,
no cat or any rabious beast.
The Cuban insurgents, the Sandinistas, and the enemies, the guerrillas in El Salvador
are our enemies, enemies of freedom, and they have one thing in mind, not El Salvador, but
eventually Florida and Texas and California and the United States and South America in
world conquest.
It's going to happen if we don't have a moral awakening, a spiritual revival. That's why
I want to put that program in prime time. I'm going to ask you to write me, make your
check paper, the old-time gospel writer.
This creature is trying to tell me something.
I can see it in his face.
Are its lips moving?
No.
His lips aren't moving.
But he's looking at me and he's saying to me,
don't be afraid.
Did you hear him tell you this?
No.
You felt he said it?
Uh, I know.
And, and, I, I, oh, God, give me strength.
I'll fight it off.
I'm not afraid.
And I run out across the road and there it is up there.
Oh, those eyes.
Oh, can't I please wake up?
I'm not afraid.
Come, my creatures.
I summon all of you to attend.
Be silent, all of you.
I've opened the surface of the earth.
It's time to attack.
Oh, no.
I've given the earthlings an ultimatum.
Either they agree to become my slaves or they'll be destroyed.
It would be futile to fight them.
With military power, it would lead to defeat.
The end of civilization.
This is why the bad movies, the low-grade science fiction films,
those directors, those are true subgeniuses.
More sub, perhaps, than others.
But for that very reason, they're more in touch with the, uh, the...
What we call the possible fewest.
There aren't that many.
There aren't that many possible fewest.
It's not an infinite thing.
There's like six or seven paths that can be taken.
And we must keep the pinks on the bob path.
The problem is probably, uh, the problem getting through the pinks is that
the love of bob can kill normals.
The love of bob has killed normals.
Normals who were not ready for the church have, uh, gotten into it,
misunderstanding a lot of the dogma and found themselves, uh,
uh, overcome.
And they, when they do that, if they're not ready,
they open themselves up to the dark side.
The, uh, the off powers, the powers of the demons, uh,
need you as a main tension.
I don't understand.
Their eyes don't have no body.
They're just eyes.
Oh.
Oh, that's what it's got to be.
It's a, a wild cat.
Of a tree.
Oh.
That's what it's got to be.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Oh.
I know.
It's the Cheshire Cat in Alice in Wonderland.
It disappeared, too, and only the eyes remain.
Keep telling yourself that, buddy.
Darth.
And once you start seeing it and looking at it and see the game they play,
it's nothing.
And they're already signed forpmeme,
and uh, I know this is, where the scene to sucks.
so that's gonna be anotherless in doors.
Terrace,
I'll tell you what you're standing on.
Oh, come on.
You could be an longevity activist.
You could be M-ывают,
can't stand with who?
that they injected syphilis 40 years ago into 600 black men.
And only four years ago, accidentally, we discovered it.
And y'all wondering what's happening in Atlanta because you're crazy.
None of you want to deal with reality because y'all are all hooked up into that other thing.
Well, you're fixing to lose all that mess.
Check them movies out.
Check out Capricorn One.
It's about how he ain't never landed nobody on the moon.
He ripped that money off and didn't do nothing but put weather satellites up there.
That's why you got a drought going all the way across this country.
And come this summer, the whole damn country can burn to the ground.
They have made it that dry.
And right now, as we sit here, there are forest fires that is raging across this country
to the likes that we ain't never had them before.
I don't know, the whole world gone crazy.
Hi, baby cake.
Hi.
It's a toothbrush.
And it's loaded with toothpaste.
Be filled with their own devices.
For the turning away of the simple shall slay them.
And the prosperity of fools shall destroy them.
But who?
There's no body there.
There's no corpse there.
The angel shouted it.
He's not here, but he is risen.
I said, now, I want to continue to receive offerings and all that.
I said, I'm just not going to give you any report of it.
You'll never know till you get to heaven where I went over the budget and all that.
And I said, even when you get to heaven, you're not going to get any report of it.
And I said, even when you get to heaven, God will have to tell you, because I'm not knowing.
We're not against it.
The true education facilities is in the top of your head.
Not in no college university.
Controlled by the same force that controls the university.
And that true education facility in the top of your head will never open up until it's around an oasis of love.
Most of these colleges and universities, numbers say,
says, who's a patriot?
That whole game.
That whole game, somewhere.
And once you start seeing it and looking at it and see the game they play.
And Matt, can you imagine George Washington and Jane Fonda?
Mmm.
The ultimate incompatibility.
The strongest male of the pack.
Just like the damn apes, you know.
The biggest, meanest male of the pack.
And, you know, that's the...
And we run kind of a limited merchant trade situation, barter system.
A collective bartering system.
Like a barter pool situation in a small township between certain patriarchs of that area.
Very much like the feudal system, you know.
Back to the dark ages again.
That's what I want.
I don't want one world government.
I want a regime.
I want a return to the dark ages.
That's what I want.
Philo speaks.
We're the big guy one.
You know, what's the ideal situation?
The ideal situation is that you're like an enlightened despot.
Although you're a patriarch, you're enlightened to the point that you provide for your children.
They love you.
You know.
You take good care of your children.
You lead your flock like a good shepherd.
But...
Right?
Like a good antichrist.
Ah, yes, fine.
And you're Phyllox production, and, and, uh, see, you know, that's where Polygamous
Kingdom comes in.
Polygamous?
That's where Polygamous Kingdom comes in.
Praise the Polygamous Kingdom.
Yeah, all the lives we can to pump out all the kids we can so that our clan can get bigger
than the next clan, and we can be a more powerful clan, you know?
Yeah, yeah.
And beat the hell out of the damn, you know, the Jablonskis down the street.
Yeah, the Jablonskis.
Let's get out of here.
To give, to receive the instruction of wisdom, justice, God is truly just.
There's coming a day, listen, there's coming a day when a God of justice will judge all
men.
We have Ivan the what?
Ivan the Targeter.
Ivan has some, today, some 7,000 nuclear weapons on missiles and bombers in the Soviet Union
that he has to pick out targets for in the United States.
Ivan the Targeter will probably lay...
Damn near anything he can get his claws on.
Phew!
But don't you see, you'd be doing exactly what you say you're fighting, killing, using
force because you're certain you're right.
But it wouldn't be the same thing because we'd be advocating nothing, forcing nothing.
Now, there are many strong men in the world today fighting for tolerance, compassion,
wisdom.
For your right to be different, to be wrong even.
They wouldn't be touched.
Only the dogma hurts.
The infallible.
Trying to play God.
You just can't do that.
Why not?
If God's too busy.
Who's to say that it's not his will, that we're not his agents?
Every man shall bend his knee and bow his head and call Jesus Lord to the glory of God, the
Father.
On past that, justice and judgment.
Jesus said, you're here to prevent the putrefaction.
But this putrid world only tells that we're not doing our job.
As we should.
God help us.
Wake up.
They've come to steal my dreams.
Knock the door down.
No, go away.
Go away.
No.
Ah, get up lady.
It's the trade of the century.
Rise now.
And turn over your old mattress to me, Lord Eddie.
Who is this?
Lord, I can't.
Monsters?
There's money in that mattress.
That's right.
There's monster money in every sweaty mattress
when you trade in your used dreams at Unconscious Village.
But those dreams have been with me since the beginning.
Don't be stuck with leftover dreams in the terrible days to come.
Open mattress.
Oh, look.
A pig.
It looks like a locomotive.
I'm a bullhead.
Three hundred million swaps in his yo-yo.
Three monkeys.
It's the most in-for-mice.
And loud, don't whine.
A noble woman condemned to most of this earth.
Why, that's... that's me.
Yes, that's yesterday's you being reborn today on tomorrow's mattress.
A Golden City Yeti Dad Double Duck Infit
inside us from Naughty Nights Newsmakers.
We're from...
Unconscious Village!
I am asleep!
Radio Now.
Oh, no, it's not now.
It sucks, okay?
All right, too fast the hour.
And those hours are passing quickly.
And I am in your ears.
You're in my mix.
I have left my body.
I'm in your head.
I am Bebop Loco.
Yeah, that's me, baby.
The suspect.
The outsider.
Not looking for the hoochie-cootie song.
Weirdly cool.
Perfect.
The
And that's who we are.
No, no, not anymore.
Bebop, there's been a format change.
Mr. Producer, do we have a new focus group?
Yeah, they focus us up real good this time.
Well, what are we now?
Uh, coming at you, Bob-Man.
Extreme.
No sense of humor.
Aggressive.
In your face.
Now.
Radio.
Man, all right, all right.
It's three past the last on this day of all days.
And me and the Now crew counting down with you till the end of the day.
End of time.
I got Danny Vanilla on the street.
I'm right here dogging the dirt till the end of the world.
I got Chump Threads in the booth.
I got sports and new shorts coming at the sevens, Bebop.
All right, but every crew needs a captain.
Let's go to our dizzy devil over Fun Fun Town.
Captain Heffy painted in the Now Chopper.
Copy that, Bebop.
And hello, folks.
If you aren't swilling office coffee in the cube farm by now, you're probably one of the
gas govers I'm looking down at here on the 666.
From Oil Heights to the Santa Baby off ramp, it's a mess.
All lanes crawling.
I'm looking down at the Santa Baby off ramp.
I'm looking slow and go behind two sacred cows pulling the Ark of the Covenant in the
show off lane.
I need to back up.
You hear a person sitting around.
Roger.
Just a hearing now.
The Edom Intern is still being blocked by hostile natives in robes diverting uncircumcised
motorists onto the Goyim Cut-Off.
So if you're not a helmet head, I would stay away from there.
Looks like locusts down there.
Hey, those are locusts we hear, Captain Heffy.
Aren't those fumigants on their way to the Zillion Bug March?
Nuggets are.
Bebop.
Okay.
All right.
Yeah, sorry.
Sorry.
The chopper cops are backing me off to 1500 ticks.
So this is Captain Heffy recycling off in the environmentally souped up News Now chopper.
Get out of there.
Me vida loca.
It's an unholy mess out there.
Oh, we got another take from one of our rolling eyeballs on the ground, Mrs. Caroline P. on
the car phone, baby.
Hello.
My car just stopped in the middle of the freeway.
Is it the bugs?
Oh, it's the motherboard under my hood.
It's going zeroes.
Why?
Y2K.
It's the millennium, stupid.
Well, I know that.
I can't move it.
Calm down, Mrs. P.
Get away from my car.
How bad can it be?
All right.
Things are beginning to unravel out there.
Hey, we're at four.
Get ready for more on Radio Now.
Well, if it's not happening now, who cares?
Because of us, it's morning in America.
Breakfast, honey?
Thanks.
Hey, is this real corn?
Is this pork?
Because of us, people in the Great Plains are just plain doing things.
Little things, like taking money from machines.
Hey, hey, stop, kid.
I'm not a machine.
Because of us, they're roasting East Coast marshmallows on the West Coast.
Wow.
These taste like pork.
We're the people of US+.
Guess what we do?
Chemistry?
Transportation?
Pork?
Kind of.
US+.
We own the idea.
We're the people of US+.
We're the people of America.
It's five past the last.
Time to give you the business.
And the only business we care about here is show business.
We got Radio Now celebrity stalker Danny Vanilla.
He's really out there.
Danny, what's the gossip, man?
What's the dish?
I got the dish.
I live for dish.
I live for her dish.
And I've been up all night here at the unbelievable, fun-believable Hotel Millennium.
Bebop, here's my very, very now dish.
All right.
Princess goddess.
Just as virtually gorgeous in full digital.
She wasn't a fab flesh.
Wow.
She couldn't get to the Ebola virus ball here at the hotel last night because she was
reading fairy tales by satellite to young plank victims.
Wow.
Well, man, she may be dead, but she's obviously a very caring person.
She's...
Okay.
Well...
Let's get back to Ebola.
You got your yellow ribbon on, right?
Well, frankly, I'm not wearing mine, Danny.
You know, it could be infected.
Oh, come on, people.
You gotta wear your princess plague ribbons.
The money goes right to keep the deadly organisms from getting across our designer borders.
Come on.
I can't even get across our designer borders, man.
Danny?
Is he okay?
It's not...
Now they're all in there after the post.
Oh, belly up and put them down.
I'm Chump Threat.
And I'm coming up at you with sports in your shorts.
Lately, I've been getting more and more people to come and get me.
I'm getting weep-eyed wooscrams and punk-ass calls from fans who are bummed by the blood
on the ice.
They say they're way gross by the broken bones on the boards and the poor babies are bopping
over the twisted bodies in the bowls.
Hey, you don't want to see it?
Get yourself blinded.
You're the man, Chump.
Yeah, I am the man.
And here's my pick of the day.
Don't bet the pros.
They're cons.
And the colleges, they're goons on the tape.
Put your money on junior high soccer.
You're the man, Chump.
The George X Middle School fruit bats are holding you back.
They're going home to the St. Stools Sandabs.
The bats are totally pumped.
They're going to punk them and pork them.
The Sandabs are bacon.
The fruit boys are going to have their Elvis day.
The bats by 30 goals.
I'm Chump Threat.
And I'm out.
The Chump has left the building.
Radio Now.
And if it's not happening now, when did it happen?
Give me immortality or give me death.
That's the motto here at Ralph's Ball Sports New and Used Body Shop in the St. St. St.
St. City of the Future.
Hi, friends.
Ralph's Ball Sports here to tell you that everybody must die, but you don't have to
be there when it happens.
That's why we're having a great going on a body sale.
Yes, you can live forever while your friends fall apart around you like rotten fruit.
And here's how.
Lease an organ or limb from our headless body farm.
It's made in America from Americans.
Enter the new century with these exclusive clone-ons.
Nat Velour designer jeans, deluxe follicle hair mat grafting with upgraded media sensitive
stimulated wrapper filler, rear rolled non-glossy carbon-intensified glue guards, power moons,
and tinted tent Ralph's Follies in slash dash or faux flannel.
So come on down to Ralph's Ball Sports City of the Future and do it today because there
may not be a tomorrow.
Now, Ralph is always with us.
The fruit is around us.
Open, aggressive homosexuals.
No more a sense of shame.
But really a demand for a change.
A demand for recognition as a form of life.
And God's judgment is going to come and fall again upon a godless, Christ-rejecting, blasphemous
society.
Well, if this sounds paranoid, you're right.
But I think I have good reason to be paranoid.
It's a strange world out there.
I think I've been there.
I'm going to say that again.
You didn't go.
Well, that was some real Uber driving there, Dr. Drummond.
I almost thought we were going to get killed.
That made me disconnect my mind.
I gained a glimpse of true slack for a minute there.
And you know, as fate smokes apart, we live the life.
Ah, yes.
We're done.
...on the nines with my man Ray the Hamburger.
Thank you, Bob.
This is your Radio Now on the Spot,
actually now News Team.
I'm Ray Hamburger.
And I'm Harold Hiphugger.
Hey, hey, hey, wait, wait a minute.
Since when did you two guys become a team?
Hey, wait a minute in there.
Harold, you're supposed to be out in the now mobile van
making news happen.
Yes, well, someone forgot to gas up the now mobile van.
Dios mio, it was me.
But it was an emergency.
I had to take Mrs. Bebop to the birthing class.
By the time she got open, man, everything was closed.
We'll have a story on that coming up.
Very exciting.
I don't think so.
Okay, make it up, boys.
Make it happen.
Well, we could do that Camel on the Lamb story again
if you got the copy there.
Oh, yes, it's here in the wake.
Is that mine?
Camel on the Lamb.
Disgraced icon Joe Camel
had to climb down...
from his last billboard this morning
before a jeering mob of addicts and ex-children.
It's about time, Ray,
but instead of handing over his pool cue,
dog glasses, and smoking boots to the jackbots,
he...
Smoking butt.
My smoking butt.
That should be smoking butt.
Let's just go to that tape one more time.
One at a time.
I'm not the president.
Here's the story.
They took my smokes.
They snatched my axe.
I could see the handwriting on the wall.
Yeah, where'd you learn to move?
I learned a glyphic script.
Very funny.
Yes, sir.
Joe, I had it to gun through your head yet
that you're just a drawing,
a drawing of a camel,
a cartoon.
I do know I'm not a camel, Hal.
I know that much.
I am a logo.
Get that straight.
Joe, they say your stomachs are gone, Joe.
I got two stomachs left, Wiley.
Who cares?
Joe, Joe,
box into Babelizer here.
Yes, ma'am.
Any plans for the future?
Yeah, party.
What's the problem?
The problem is
they crossed the line.
They wanted to take my shades.
That's the way you have to, Joe.
Where are you going?
I'm going where everyone else is going.
It's the millennium, stupid.
I'm going to the big one.
Let them try and keep me out.
Yeah.
And so Joe vaulted through his signature smoke ring.
And the defeated dromedary
peeled off behind the wheel
of his horse-heavy muscle car.
A beautiful machine.
It certainly is to the big to-do.
The big party.
That's tonight.
Couldn't keep me away
if it was the end of the world.
Well, I think it is.
See you there.
Here on souped-up,
suggestive, desensitized,
bite-me,
environmental now radio.
Fly the goddess.
Multi-sex plugs for your laptops,
international mini-meals,
unlimited plague-free air,
no bloody babies,
and extra knee room
for your extra knee.
Isn't that where you want to be
at midnight
when the big eyeball drops
on those sub-millionaires
30,000 feet beneath you?
Goddess air.
She'll get you there.
Hello?
Don't worry.
Number six in a series of good nature programs
designed to address your profoundly
unreasonable fears
and mindless superstitions.
Yes.
And today we shred another paper tiger
as we confront the millennium,
a.k.a. the end of the world.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Ha, ha.
All right.
And that's our program for today.
Of course it is.
All right, you live,
you learn, I guess.
I guess that's what de-sensithiz climate radio
sounds like, I guess.
It's certainly weirdly cool.
Ha, ha, hey, Mr. Producer Man, you there?
You're Bob Stitt.
I got an idea.
You got another one of those
that's long enough for me to take a whiz behind?
Bob, if you're short,
enough. You're long enough. I'm out the door. Shake it.
Fly the
Goddess Air Plush Bus
and leave the luxury to us.
It's the end of the world in air travel.
From the dizzying disorientation
of its gyro seats to the old world
fermentation cushions and drop-down
ale masks, you may not know
where you are, but you'll never forget
how you got there.
Goddess Air. Let her take you
for all your worth.
Hello, don't worry.
Number two in a series of jolly
good programs designed to confront
your shallow, infantile phobia.
Yes, and today we
pop yet another paranoid piñata
as we take a good, hard
full Monty at your fears
of eyeball hats.
It's a silly, semi-sentient fixation
that quite ignores the clear
and unpleasant danger of the mumbling
millennial morons beneath the hat.
But it's the I and the ball.
You see, the one.
The one and the Z. It's the null.
El Cipher.
And that's our program for today.
It's the code.
The virus is eating us.
Hey, Bebop, man, where are you?
You're on the...
Yes, friends,
we're still here and
I just, uh,
well, I hate to interrupt that
Firesign Theater new album.
Give me
immortality or give me
death. I think it's just...
I'm hearing it for most of the time.
I'm hearing it for most of this for the first time with you
tonight, but
um, you know,
it is a commercial out-of-CD
that's available in stores.
And I'll probably
play the entirety of the whole thing
on the Hour of Slack, but friends,
Reverend Nikki Deathchick just walked
in with a package
from Reverend Chaz
Smith of Einstein
Secret Orchestra holding four
tapes, including an
edited volume 11
of the book, and I'm going to read it to you.
Live radio shows
from the last couple of months
and our New Year's
show, and I guess
that since we're talking about
centuries and millennia
and next days and end of the world,
it probably makes some sense
to whip it out
and share with you this...
We were...
We called in
to the show from
Dobstown 4 in Austin
where the subgenius
hierarchy had gathered
to confab
converse and otherwise
hobnob and...
Anyway,
we did call in
and we'll listen
to this wonderful Einstein
Secret Orchestra in the background
for just a minute, and then we'll go back
to the talk.
This is Chaz's new space
theme.
...
Now she's got something on the net called teen sex.
Will you just stop right now?
I just typed in Bill Clinton.
Oh, she typed in Bill Clinton?
Bill Clinton.com and it came up on a site
called teen sex with a big X behind the sex.
Oh, yep.
The X's are putting their...
their two cents worth everywhere.
Are all the porn sites run by the X's?
No, actually, I doubt seriously
if God like aliens from outer space
or ne...
Although, why not?
You know, there's money in that, I understand.
Yeah.
Oh, there we go.
Yeah, that's interesting.
Well, then, are we on the air?
Yeah, we actually are.
Now, what...
Well, Chaz, why...
Aren't you supposed to be playing like, you know,
popping balloons or getting drunk or something like that?
No, those are all the other radio stations.
We're doing a...
We're doing the show for the people who are sitting home alone
tripping their brains out or...
or smoking their four-foot bong
or drinking that bottle of wine with the candles lit.
That's who we're doing the show for tonight.
Well...
All them poor, lonely souls.
The...
Those happy, lonely souls.
The club members...
They're not alone with Bob.
Every one of them is a card-carrying member of Sex Without Partners.
And that's cool.
Hey, man.
If Bill Clinton would've been a member of Sex Without Partners, he wouldn't be
impeached.
But...
Well...
Oh, wow.
But, yeah, by the same token, if...
if...
if all of those people who think it's the government's business to...
to poke into somebody's private pants...
That's right.
I don't know.
I don't like the government looking down my pants.
Oh, well, yeah.
Would you stand up and say to the people who are sitting in the back...
You particularly, Mr. and Mrs. America.
I'm not the president.
Answer this question.
Did you lie about cheating on your spouse?
You don't.
We'll know if you tell the truth, you're going to lose your job.
And if you lie, you're going to lose your job.
Now feel free to answer yes or no.
And probably go to jail too.
Did you lie about cheating?
Did you lie about all the times that you stole from all those people?
Did you chop down that cherry tree?
Well, it depends on how you define the word.
I cannot tell a lie.
I did not have sex with that woman.
Well, I am your Uncle Sam, son.
And you have to tell me.
And your big brother here.
Big brother Bob.
Well, I mean, it's obvious because Clinton was a fan of JFK, not George Washington.
So George Washington.
George Washington was the one who said, you know, I cannot tell a lie.
Well, that's the mythology behind it.
But, you know, and the whole cherry tree thing.
But JFK, I mean, that was Bill's hair.
Well, of course that cherry tree story is true because, you know, the history, the American history books cannot tell a lie.
No, not at all.
They do not lie.
What did Bob tell you, Dr. Herman?
He told me.
He told me to pick up your butt.
Get going.
Yeah.
Because I know you're dragging ass.
I know you get tired and low at times, but you got to just get yourself in the butt.
And get back up there, boy.
And keep on going.
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
Here is wisdom.
Let him that hath understanding count the number of the beat.
For it is the number of a man.
The number of a man.
His number is six hundred three score and six.
Thank you, Father, for the anointing of the Holy Spirit.
Jehovah One is a space deity from the corporate sin galaxy, which exists somewhere in the distant corners of the universe as we know it.
The earth is his test tube.
The materialization of an experiment that Jehovah One started roughly seven million years ago as the result of a bar bet.
In his presence now kneel and make thy covenant.
In this new life nothing shall come between us.
To thee will I cling, though all the powers of heaven shall rage about me.
Thou art my God.
And I am your God.
God to use you individually and collectively to begin to address and deal with those problems.
This is the way they did it in the New Testament.
God scolded his people in the old testament.
The greatest people on earth.
And you walk in with the Judas tribe and the wife of Judas might be one of the ladies I've laid to make a socialist.
This is Jim Jones.
She might give you slow poison in your champagne.
You don't know how clever I am.
One thing you've all done to underestimate me.
I made plans for treason long ago because I knew I couldn't trust nothing.
I knew I couldn't trust anything but communism and the principle in me.
Yes, I knew that that's what I had to depend upon, not depend upon the arm of the flesh and never put all your eggs in one basket.
So honey, I put my eggs in many places.
You figure that out if you want to.
Some of you are too naive.
You don't know what I'm, what I'm talking about.
You don't know what Jim Jones is all about.
You can't even follow him.
You haven't even, you haven't even smelled where he's at yet.
Much less followed him.
You don't even know who he is and you might miss him if you didn't have a real good look at him.
You wouldn't even know who he looked like.
You really haven't got an x-ray.
But I've got all kinds of things in store.
It be cleansed.
You, you who are stupid piss ants and reptiles and lower than the price.
You could make a hoopie if you want.
But your hoopie makes me sicky.
So you can make your hoopie while I do something far more sicky.
I got me some big plans.
Both here, there and everywhere.
Got lots of plans.
Planning to be missionaries.
Training to be missionaries.
He would sharpen you up and make you ready for a bit of the old ultra-violence.
The enemy is at the gate.
And the enemy is the human mind itself,
or lack of it,
on this planet.
Hey, Bebop, man, where are you?
You're on the air.
Alright, I'm on the air and I'm back, the outsider, the sus.
What's happening?
Look at your monitor, Essie.
Oh my gosh.
Hey, we've got a developing chase situation down on the Tribulation Highway.
So let's go now to Happy Fandit in News Chopper One.
Happy, what's happening?
You know it was gonna be a hell of a ride in the last hours,
but look out below.
Just seconds ago,
a Maroon Sports utility convertible Babylon SX 4x4
came rolling right out of the scene
across the center divider
and it's going hell-bent against the arrow of time.
Oh man, that's spooky,
but that's a great car.
Somebody could get hurt. Who's driving it?
It's a female woman drinking out of a large trophy or gold cup.
Yeah, the Rattler Baptist is saying it's a chalice
and the PG Amish,
yeah, they think it's a big gulp.
Well, this is Harold Hippogor in the newsroom.
I'm Harold Hippogor.
What are you doing in the newsroom?
Why aren't you out in the now mobile van
chasing that booty?
Out of the now mobile van.
Oh, that's what these keys are.
I found the keys in the bathroom.
I'm looking at the Channel 86 news picture down here
and this redhead weaving along the trip,
she appears to be drunk driving,
she's talking on her cell phone
and there's a wonderful shot of the license plate
of her 4x4,
it's a vanity plate with a one and a zero.
That's an eye and a ball.
I've got the angle on her.
I'll take over here, Harold.
Yeah, I can see from here that they're sealing
the next seven exits
between Perdition Pass and Great Satan's Village.
Oh boy, oh boy.
They're laying down funny foam
that's going to block the quadruple bypass
and clog every major artery into the city.
I'm glad I'm not...
Throw it! Stay on top of it!
Is he gone?
Holy virgin, what is happening out there?
Spot coming at you.
All right, well, run, spot, run.
The critics are unanimous.
They hate Pull My String.
A new level of low.
A morbid exploitation of the freshly dead.
The end of film.
But what do the people say?
I'm going back in as soon as my seat is dry.
They've done some big things with their chest.
Oh my goodness, the mudboarding was dope.
Yes, it's weirdly cool.
It's very cool.
It's Titanic without the water.
Hey, that's Pull My String.
Yeah, me too.
Princess Goddess had to die
to star in the movie of her life.
Now she'll live for you
in Pull My String
from Bottom Fiedler Films.
I'm Harold D.
And don't forget the Radio Now Princess Goddess doll drop
at Homeless Stadium when it all comes down tonight.
Bring a kid
and maybe a doll will drop on her.
It's five after five alive
on this day in Fun Fun Town
that's going by, woo, way too fast.
But on the fives,
we got Danny Vanilla, the celebrity stalker.
He's on the move again.
Hey, Danny, it sounds kind of wet there.
It is, Bebop.
I'm partially submerged
in the celebrity storm drain
and I'm getting boxed, Tony.
I can eyeball Princess Goddess inside
attending a brunch, of course,
with Prince Harold.
Now right above me is a stretch dumpster
ready to speed Princess Goddess
to the White Tie and Black Ribbon Affair
at Dead Center Hall.
There, a replica of the solid platinum cord
the doctors pulled out of her back,
making it possible for her to speak again.
Will be auctioned off along with Rose Mud,
the mudboard she was riding
at the time of her final encounter.
I'm sorry.
With a landmine on the slopes of the English Alps.
Here she comes, here she comes.
Pull over my string.
Come and see my very fast feet.
Oh, she's so exquisite.
Wait a minute, beg you.
Here come the celeberoxies
taking pictures of themselves.
There's Tony Eatery with his latest
Wet Girls Storm Drain.
And there goes the stretch dumpster.
Princess Goddess, she's rolling down her window.
You know, she's digitally winking at me.
I love you, Denny.
What did she say?
I got my teeth in your ears
and I'm biting through
because I'm Chump Prince
coming at you with more sports
in your shorts.
You know, watching the game without betting
is like having sex with your hat.
Oh yeah, it's got you covered,
but it just don't fit.
Hey, give me my hat.
I'm gonna take some corks.
Hey, Chump, am I on?
How would I know?
I need a tip.
First one's free.
What's the spread on midnight?
Well, the desert says 3 to 1 on the end of the world,
but for my money, you'll be mowing the lawn
and popping brewskis per usual tomorrow morning.
No, no, I bet Mom's farm on Armageddon.
Oh, well, if you can't stand the heat,
don't bet the kitchen.
Greased dog on two.
You got a problem, Chump. Yeah?
Greased dog, sit up and tell me something I don't know.
It's over, Chumper.
We're pulling the plug.
You're drinking out of the toilet on this one, dog man.
Oh yeah. Oh yeah.
Check your screen.
Hey, what's that big eyeball doing there?
Hey, hey, hey, it ain't CBS, pal.
Hey, I'm starting to get sleepy.
Yeah, we're coming in.
Yeah, well, I'm out here.
Oh, no, you're not.
Hey, let me out of here.
Let me out of this place.
Yeah, there was a time.
I forgot what I was going to say.
We're five minutes away.
Are we? Yeah.
See, my watch says it's only three minutes,
but I'm not tied to Greenwich.
Hey, the Lord Jesus Christ just walked into the room.
Praise Jesus.
A native of your noble state of Ohio.
Yes.
Send our greetings to Jesus.
Here, hold on.
Chaz?
Jesus. Hey, how's it going?
Good. We're stumping it out here in Cleveland.
Getting ready to count down the seconds to the last year.
Yes, the last year.
Now we will be entering the next year.
How's the rocket going?
We have, actually, we have 15 vessels ready for test launching.
15?
I've been collecting those SD rocket packs.
You know, the ones that go into the smaller rockets.
Okay, well, we need...
I think we have about 16 million of those.
What we need are D engines.
D engines?
D. We need a lot of D engines.
Okay, well, we should tell the listeners to send those in.
Yeah.
It's going to take a lot of D engines to get off the ground.
Yeah, you're right.
D and E. We can do D and E engines,
but E engines are more expensive.
What about the double E?
Do you want to stay away from the double E?
No, then you step up to the F and the G.
Actually, there is a... I'm going to pick up an H engine.
You know what? We were talking.
Maybe we should, instead of building your own spaceship,
how about the idea of stealing
another one that's already finished?
Well, there is one down at...
Steal your own ship.
At Cape Canaveral. They have that last...
the Saturn V that's
disassembled, you know?
Can we get in?
Yeah, I think we could.
Who's there tonight? Is it just you?
Michelle and myself are here.
Oh, hey, Michelle.
Hey. How's it going? I can't hear you.
Oh, that's okay. You don't need to hear me.
I can barely hear you. You can just feel my presence.
Yes, yes. Wow. So you guys are going to
count down the new year together there.
I'm surfing around on porno sites
on the web here in the studio.
Oh, no. Yeah.
Go to, um, AltDog
Legless Children.
Gosh.
We got another one out here.
Oh, you still there? Yeah, I'm still here.
Steal your own rocket ship.
Go to Alt... Did you check... Check out this.
www.prairiesquidsex.com
Really?
Check it out. Yeah.
www.prairiesquidsex.com
Yeah. It's mostly... It's pretty good pictures
but, you know, it's... She's on it.
I don't know if it's a legal site. It might be blocked out from the school.
So make sure that you... You plan
a really good... I mean, this has
to be a real sacred moment when all these rockets
go up. Yeah. So...
When are we planning the launch? July 5th?
Oh, absolutely. No, like...
We're... You mean we're going to have... You're saying
at X day we're going to have a completed ship
for people to get on board? Yeah, it should.
If we put them all together.
No. Well, actually, yeah, schedule it
before the 5th because they're just tests.
And, uh... And so there's tests.
Yeah, they're just... So we're going to have to just pick a random person
to send off. It's just... Yeah, it's just...
I'm just going on the thing like, look, if Bob
screws up again...
Look, at least we'll be taking a little step towards... What do you mean, if Bob?
You mean when Bob...
Screws up again. I mean, what do you mean
if Bob screws up again? Of course he won't
screw up.
But at least we'll have some tests.
At least we'll be... We'll have something to
do until the... Until it all hits.
Wow. Everyone should build their own ship,
bring it to X day. That's right. We'll hook them all up
together with, like, some duct tape or something. That's right.
Right, yeah. Who's going to be our...
What's the name of that little monkey that was
the first monkey in space? Uh...
Uh... I don't know. Bonzo?
Or... J. Fred Muggs?
No. I remember the first
dog was Laka. Laka?
Yeah. Who will be our Laka?
Yeah. Who's going to be our... I mean, is
Lonesome Cowboy Dave doing anything?
Well, he does have a dog.
He does? Yeah. I think I'm going to just use him.
His name's Jake.
Jake.
But which one would we rather send into space, though?
Dave or Jake?
Both of them.
Jake would probably be able to work the controls better,
but, you know, it'll be
more fun to watch Lonesome Cowboy Dave go up.
Hey, you're mine!
Hey! Let me out of here! Let me out of
this place!
You know, Rex?
Yeah. I think that's
me. Well,
I've been drinking this popular
brand of beer
for a pretty near hundred years.
I'm still so depressed.
Me, too.
I can't even
lie down, Sandy.
You boys are down in the dumpsters
because your adult beverage
is only an alcoholic
enhanced dietary supplement.
How come you're so
peppy, Roy?
Here, take a swig of what my
grandkids put me on
the last roundup.
I'll take a swig of what my grandkids put me on
I'm trying. It's a
Polar Pro.
Dang, I do feel
a whole lot less
suicidal. And I got
the Texas Trots
again!
Yee-haw!
Polar Pro, a prescription beer
for older Americans with natural
Alaskan bear urine and Prozac.
Consult your doctor if you're
pregnant over 80 and operating
heavy equipment.
Whoa, don't fire in the air.
You don't know where it's coming down.
Well, we are here at a
subgenius last year party.
Hey, it's time to
do it, man. Get everybody on the phone.
It's a countdown. It's like
20 seconds. It's like
20, 19,
yeah, here we go, into
next year. Into next
year. 15, yes.
Into the future.
10, 9,
8, 7,
6,
5, 4,
3, 2,
1. Happy
next year!
Wait, I gotta kiss Michelle.
Happy
New Year!
Ho, ho, ho!
The sun's Santa Claus!
Bringing you little babies
full of cash and
old, just, jelly-bearing
cysts walking, shuffling
off into the horizon.
New Baby 1999
comes crawling around the bend.
His machine gun in
one hand and a crack pipe in the other.
And Old Man 1998
with his broken bob pipe
and his crashed sawtooth.
Go watering.
Go down into the pond. His pink feathers.
Yeah, into the pond.
Into the pond with Old Man
time. Old Man 98.
And your machine gun toting
Baby 1999.
Crawls up out of the pond.
You can plug these in.
But, uh,
yeah.
Old Bob goes into the
outhouse and out crawls
Baby Bob.
Just plug him in anywhere and turn it up.
Oh, yeah.
Jesus is gonna go get G. Gordon Gordon
since he represents the old year.
Well, Old Man
19, the Old Man
time has come crawling.
Oh, and Baby, young Baby
1999 is here too.
Ooh la la.
Old Man time, say farewell
to the peaks of 1999.
So it's 1999 there.
Hey, hey. Yes. Howdy.
Howdy. You people are a year ahead of us.
Do you realize that? Yeah.
So it's already X day coming up over there.
It's next year already.
We are already in next year here in Cleveland.
So it's a time. You're talking
across time. That's right.
Talking across time. We're an hour behind.
You are one light hour behind me.
One hour behind you.
You people have already moved into the future
and we're all hung up here in 98.
You still have an hour to go.
Yeah, exactly.
To reach the destination we, the plateau
we have already stood upon.
Yeah, that's it. You've already
achieved the, the pathiosis.
You have reached the peak.
And we're still scrambling up the side of that
damn, you know, sidereal
mountain. We haven't gotten anywhere near
the peak yet. Yeah, but it's in view.
Well, yeah, you can sort of reach up. The light's at the end of the tunnel.
Yeah, you can focus on the light
at the end of the tunnel. Yeah.
Or the drink at the end of the tunnel or something.
I don't know. Yeah. That big,
that four foot
bong at the end of the tunnel.
Ah, yes.
And the healing sound
of a frappy new year.
Frappin'. A frappy
new year. Absolutely
frappin'. Yes, we be. And I'm being
filmed even as I speak.
Stain cam.
Stain cam is on me. Stain cam?
It's in my trousers. Wait just a minute.
Stain cam is in my, get that stain
cam. That is disgusting.
You know, ever since he and Ken
Starr became friends, it's been the
same old stuff over and over again.
Well, I should
probably relinquish this to other people who need
more important things to say. Hey,
well. For the new years. But happy new year
to all you people up there in the northern
areas. I bet you're freezing your buns off.
We are indeed. We are indeed.
Well, we're out the back porch jammin', man.
That's pretty good. We're out here jammin' on the back porch.
We'll see you at
next day, brother. Okay, man.
Alright. It's, it's, I think it would be kind
of dangerous to go outside around
these parts. Sounds like there's a
small war going on. Oh, I need to put on,
I need to put on Miss, Miss
Baby, Miss Babe
New Year 99, Sister
Decadent. Oh,
Sister Decadent. Happy new year to you too,
darling. Hello, Sister Decadent. Oh,
happy new year to you. We have already
achieved the nirvana of next
year, 1999.
We will be with you soon,
my brother. Yes.
We will be arriving in approximately
one hour, first time.
What is that,
boom-booms out there? Oh, man. Yeah.
It's like a war, like, like a,
actually not even a small war, it's like a
big war. Lots of bombs
going off and, um,
automatic rifles and
guns. It's, it's quite exciting,
actually.
We were seeing Bob's in the stoplights
on the way over.
He's showing his head even as we
speak, pre-new year.
He is at P.O. Box
140306.
Yes, we can, here's an update, a news update
from the 9th floor of downtown Cleveland. Dallas,
Texas,
75214.
It does indeed sound
like that. That's
Bob at Box
140306, Dallas, Texas,
75214.
www.subgenius.com
Just calm yourselves.
They say it sounds like a war.
And when you're in the midst of it, it sounds
even more. It sounds
exactly like the footage from
Baghdad. Exactly. That's
what it looks like. I swear to God, I'm
looking out over the east side of Cleveland
and it looks like the foot...