The subgenius of the slack.
Have you been smoking, Stan?
Yep, yep.
Shh.
Don't tell anyone.
You know, you really shouldn't.
It's unpredictable and it could affect your medication.
Better win their prescription.
All I know is the world looks beautiful.
The world looks so damn beautiful.
I feel fantastic.
And I never felt as good as how I do right now.
Except for maybe when I think of how I felt that day.
When I felt the way that I do right now.
Right now.
I feel fantastic.
And I never felt as good as how I do right now.
Except for maybe when I think of how I felt that day.
When I felt the way that I do right now.
Right now.
Work is anything but quiet these days
I try to mitigate my concentration haze
I can see the day unfold in front of me
So I take the stairs and hit the gym
The phone is ringing when I get to my desk
Well, plus the stinging's now a sharp pain in my chest
So I take a call to next and just chill
And then it's time for lunch again
All I know is work is easy
When you don't stress out about deadlines
All I know is to take my medicine
I always take my medicine
I feel fantastic
And I never felt as good as how I do right now
Except for maybe when I think of how I felt that day
When I felt the way that I do right now, right now
I feel fantastic
And I never felt as good as how I do right now
Except for maybe when I think of how I felt that day
When I felt the way that I do right now, right now, right now
Right now
Sometimes I'd like a slur
From a friend to some old friend
I'm going to take a pill for my social anxiety.
I get a table and a nice bottle of Chablis.
Now it's getting late and there's still no sign of her.
I have another glass of wine.
All I know is the wine lasts longer when you don't got to share it with someone.
All I know is the steak tastes better when I take my steak tastes better pill.
I feel fantastic and I never felt as good as how I do right now.
Except for maybe when I think about how I felt that day.
When I felt the way that I do right now.
Right now.
I feel fantastic.
And I never felt as good as how I do right now.
Except for maybe when I think about how I felt that day.
When I felt the way that I do right now.
Right now.
Where, where, it's through.
Just, it's happening.
Wow.
There's nothing spooky about it.
This is, I know exactly how it is.
That's right.
That's how it is.
Heart Ignition cut that last little piece.
And the happy song, I Feel Fantastic was by JoCo.
That's our man Jonathan Coulton at JonathanCoulton.com.
Princess Wee can sing along with all of his songs.
This show, due partly to the contributions this month,
seems to be a little bit more than just a little bit.
It's going to be a drug abuse themed episode.
That happens every now and then with this show.
I'm also still gradually editing through the recordings from 13X Day Drill.
That is a daunting task, friends.
But I'm starting to unearth some of the best ofs.
And that's what I'll strive to structure this and future shows around.
Le Mar did the titles.
And The Lard did the titles.
And George did the next cut.
And there'll be more from them.
And Fat Man D and Monkey Hive.
And Reverend Janus.
And even Crazy Jim Jones.
All from 13X Day Drill recordings.
And there will be old Rudy Schwartz Project.
And yes, even new Devo.
Let there also be Slack.
For an emergent high like me, friends,
Slack is going at it so hard that you just about like to burst that vein in your forehead.
And here then is something that unexpectedly happened at 13X Day when I got good and fed up.
You'll hear Reverend Angry Larry and Dr. Philo Drummond trying to defuse me.
We might, since we know how to use computers, maybe do a Jonestown thing or something.
Do a what?
A Jonestown.
Oh no, that was years ago.
That was years ago.
But the thought was there.
The thought was there, so yeah.
It wasn't the pagans that burned that Dobbs icon.
It was the power of J.R. Bob Dobbs that burned that goddamn Dobbs icon.
And he did that so that you bastards would stay up here and keep playing.
So that's all there is to it.
You can dress it up.
You can purty it up all you want.
I'm sorry if I might offend.
I'm sorry if I might offend the tender ears of some liberals, the book learning subtenuuses,
the ones that memorize the pre-scriptures but don't know what they really say.
Well maybe I'm going to make you mad when I say it was the power of J.R. Bob Dobbs that did that thing.
It was not Connie Dobbs.
It was not Reverend Ivan Stanglers.
It was not Dr. Philo Drummond.
It was the power of J.R. Bob Dobbs.
And Bob alone that did that thing.
No.
And Bob wants to thank God.
It's going to be done.
And he did it.
I think it was Dick Dobbs.
It was not Dick Dobbs that did it.
It was not Nege.
It was not the Yucca Tisma.
It was not you or you or me or nobody but Bob.
Why can't you trust?
And have faith?
If Bob wants to happen, it's what's going to happen anyway and that's all there is to it.
Now be careful Reverend Stang.
You might pop that nodule in your neck.
You know what happened last time?
You popped that nodule in your neck.
Look, I was only saying that we didn't want to spray the pagans down with WD-40 and light them on fire.
I was just sticking up for them.
I said that.
So the DJ event starts in five minutes.
I was saying no.
Because they look out for us.
I don't care if I understood what you said or not.
I'm still going to preach and worry about it.
We got, yeah, five minutes until the DJ event.
It's one hour to my bedtime.
If you will make your way to the 808 camp which is located in the middle of the field.
It should be a big black tarp with a bunch of noise getting ready to head out of it.
That's what you, Reverend Ivan Stang.
What do you believe?
Do you really believe this bomb joke?
Do you people really believe this crazy UFO bomb joke?
What?
They go Reverend Ivan Stang.
What do you really truly in your heart really believe in?
You got to believe in something.
I believe I'm going to go up and get myself another beer.
Praise Bob.
I am a human rocket,
on a mission of deployment.
I've been cocked and loaded,
ready for the culmination.
I am a human missile,
guided by secret gender,
that commands my every thoughts and deeds.
That wills me on my way.
I am a human rocket
On a mission of redemption
I've been fucking loaded
Right by everything I know
I am a human missile
Guided by a secret voice
That commands my every action
And wheels me on my way
There is no turning back
There are no second thoughts
First things first and all things fair
We love the war they say
There is no planning me
On the land, in the air, or on the sea
This is what's supposed to be
My duty now awaits me
I am a human rocket
On a mission of instruction
I've been primed and programmed
Since the beginning of time
I am a human missile
Guided by a secret master
That commands my every motion
I am a human missile
And wheels me on my way
I found my target
I reached my coordinates
I'm set to detonate
And resonate
The final poem I will create
I made a video
It tells a story, oh
I guess it's time to go
Don't forget to rewind
I am a human rocket
On a mission of destruction
I've been locked and loaded
And ready for the confirmation
I am a human missile
Guided by a secret perfection
That commands my full conviction
And wheels me on my way
Large parts of the interior
Will go by
I've noticed we are all distracted
By the lights and sounds
Of everything and nothing
Do you remember the breath you took
When they left you off the hook
And sent you swimming away
Back into your cell?
I am a human rocket
On a mission of instruction
I've been cocked and loaded
Since the dawn of time
I am a human missile
Guided by a secret voice
That commands my every motion
It's time to speak
And loose me up
A righteous way
McFarland
I really do
I know you've had a swirling torment of anti-slack around you of late.
And I really do.
You know, I've got to tell you something.
You know, I know in the heart of my heart that you need healing.
You need some healing.
You need to feel that slack within you.
And before you ray it, I need to heal you.
I need to heal you and make sure that your precious, precious soul is ready
for 7 a.m.
Oh, bless your little heart.
So be healed!
Be healed!
All right.
I don't know if I'm going to be able to top that.
I'm not naturally in doubt.
Never you mind.
I came into this church, and by that I mean money was exchanged.
And when I saw a rant by the good Dr. Legume,
and literally before the end of the video,
I was typing in my credit card number into the lovely subgenius website.
Yes, praise the credit card number.
Now, what he was talking about, not my credit card number, thankfully.
Well, what he was talking about was the nature of subgenius heaven.
For those of us misfortunate enough to shuffle this mortal coil
before the saucers happened to get here.
What did this have to do with Legume?
That was his rant!
That was his particular rant, and it was beautiful.
It touched me in all the wrong and the such right places.
But what he forgot to mention was that,
in heaven, there is no bacon.
Not subgenius heaven, friends.
Not subgenius heaven.
In subgenius heaven, you can find all the bacon you want.
In the bacon plains of porktonia.
Not to be confused with the porktonian plains of bacon.
That's an entirely different show.
Now, there is no bacon in heaven, of course,
because heaven is run by pigs.
Fat, greedy, pig little pigs!
I had to go through that boss show of vemus burning
like a chicken in a pan.
Then, some time you guys, I run this thing
pointing till the same place.
I said, I'm going to make a wish.
There's a beautiful like a hoodlum or Tirana bird that I hate.
I get up.
was a mistake. George Orwell knew it. George Orwell knew that heaven is run by the pigs,
as above, so below. And now you know it, friends. Now you know it. Even Chuck Jones knew it.
This is how the world ends, not with a bang, but with a stutter. That's all, folks!
There's no keyboard up here, but I hope you'll not mind me singing this one a cappella.
There we are!
Somewhere in subgenius heaven, you'll find slack.
Eternal salvation, sex, drugs, rock and roll, or triple your money back.
Somewhere in subgenius heaven, there's fields of frop and bars that keep pouring shots
and won't ever let you stop.
Oh, way above Jehovah,
that's where these dirty deeds are done and where I'll be.
I've been beating it until it creaks and climbing crack mountain for weeks.
That's where you'll find me.
Because,
somewhere in subgenius heaven, dreams come true.
I paid my thirty dollars, so, oh, so can you.
I may have missed the aliens and hunting down pinkos, but I'm not going to waste my time.
Where do you think you'll go?
Dungeon, lieutenant,
where's the the decent or the bad guy?
And I'm alive,
even in a relationship with even a bad guy,
and my key in your pocket is...
No, you don't have to.
THE HUGE TRIM stopover
I hope you're varias de standing tall with a cannot.
I can easily see
Because I'm there persuading some of you
where stuff's so annoying that you can't take a cut.
Or not.
So then why do your lives matter?
It's just like that,
shit flies
along with all of those
other things that
your mother sang of
in her drunken
lullabies
Hell
fucking yes!
Praise Jadis!
Drugs First
Oh great
You may need drugs
So what do I do?
Take your pills? It's making us feel better
And my ears itch
Yeah yeah yeah
An hour of slack will do that to you
Itchy ears, sour brain
Speaking of which
That was a nice rant and song by
Reverend Janus
The kind of new subgenius we could use more of
Which is by
definition impossible
Oh well
But he wasn't the only one to sing
Over the Rainbow at 13X Day
Drill No Sir
The sex goddess
Reverend Fat Man D
seduced Princess Wee
into joining her in another
illegal flight over the restricted
airspace known as
13X Day
For our next song we're gonna
click our heels together and
go over the rainbow
Somewhere over the rainbow
Blue's
Oh we're so high!
Blue birds!
Yeah I thought it was skies
Skies are blue isn't it?
Oh
She knows!
Way up high!
Cause we're high!
That's why we forgot it was self descriptive
Nothing like rehearsing in a Novi's campground
Okay
Somewhere over the rainbow
Way up high
There's a land that I heard of once in a lullaby
Somewhere over the rainbow
Skies are blue
And the dreams that you dare to dream
Really do come true
Someday I'll wish upon a star
And wake up where the clouds are far behind me
Where troubles melt like lemon drops
Away upon those chimney tops
That's where you'll find me
Somewhere over the rainbow
Blue birds fly
Birds fly over the rainbow
Why oh why can't I?
If happy little blue birds fly
Beyond the rainbow
Why oh why can't I?
Marijuana
Butter
They all came together in opposition to
Uh
Marijuana
Butter
Zombies
Relax
This music
Depends
How much
Is too much
Tch, twit, twit, twit.
Rest in bed whenever you can.
Dead.
Use pain-killing medication.
La, la.
Your doctor.
Pleasuring.
Keyholes.
Because it feels pain and discomfort.
Waiting.
Feeble-mindedness.
Death.
Blindness.
White.
Madness.
Burning.
Physical decrepitude.
Sexual perversion.
Burning.
City.
Neurotic.
Egg control.
Burning.
Heavy bleeding.
And bones.
Sexual benefits.
Nothing.
Heavy bleeding or discharge.
Burning.
Deviant.
Dog.
Perforated alpha.
Fish man.
And vomiting.
And gold.
From one of the ovaries.
Empty bottles.
And vaginal bleeding.
Cardboard boxes.
Cigarette ends.
Masturbation.
Nothing.
And sinful vaginal penis.
Brain practice.
And on her daughter.
4-1-3-0-1-3 days.
And I'm glad it's over.
Burning.
Hey, ladies and gentlemen, we are here to represent the assembly of the flaming carpet.
I am the very esteemed universal philosopher of absolute reality, Reverend Frodus.
I am the founder of the 28th Day Adbaptist Movement and Grand Master of the Order of the Crimson Finger.
Professor of audiophilic mixology at the apocalypsolic branch of the Dobbsian Mental Lodge for sanctimonious conditioning.
And student of the teaching of J.R. Bob Dobbs.
You may call me Reverend Suds.
And I am the mofo of Mojo.
Pastor Fister Gag Hole.
Master of Fat Fuck Foo.
And Soki of the Order of the Crimson Finger.
Friends, we come before you this day changed over, man.
With soaring hearts and stupid grins.
With the scars from a lifelong battle against the oppressive machine of the conspiracy.
Fuck the conspiracy.
We stand before you first-hand accounts of slackful gains, shocking nuggets of wisdom,
trippy recounts of landscaping sessions, and raging contempt for the pathetic masses of pink pestilence.
And none of it would have been possible without the teachings of J.R. Bob Dobbs.
Praise motherfucking Bob.
Praise Bob.
I'm a beacon for Bob's mighty luck to shine no matter how much the conspiracy tries to drag us down.
No matter how much the conspiracy tries to tie us down.
No matter how much the conspiracy tries to tear us down.
No matter how much the conspiracy tries to beat us down.
Bob, will show us the way.
Let us pray.
Our salesmen who art in Dobbs Town, name thy behalf.
Come, he who died, come and come again.
Give us each day our daily flock and justify our trespasses.
To those who cannot take a joke.
We are the people who are seriously suffering from a major problem.
Oh, it feels good.
Hallelujah, peace, peace, Lord!
I know the word hell.
Yeah, yeah, girl.
It was like the end of the world.
There was destruction everywhere.
People scrambled around in hysterical panic.
Cars and buses and taxis were slamming into each other by the second.
Mass confusion reigned like never before.
And the cause of all this?
Bob?
Let me hear you some genius!
You're not Jesus.
You're Bob.
Yes, Bob.
Take a good look with your eyes and say a goodbye.
The sauce is on our side.
Damn right.
We got the pipe.
We got the tools and we wrote all the rules.
They want to cancel those plans.
Let me tell you now where you stand.
Starfish, kiss the night.
It's such a glorious sight.
Chomp your face in the dirt.
Show you what you really were.
Step back to the end of the line, cause it's our time.
This ain't no game, son.
You fix it better.
Run, run, run.
I'm on my hot horse and I'm gonna ride, ride, ride.
I hit the power source.
Make us fly, fly, fly.
I paid my dues to the man with the pipe.
And we hold all the guns.
We're gonna watch this planet blow tonight.
Cry, baby, cry.
Tears won't change the story.
Scream, baby, scream, cause it won't change a thing.
Just to fight your sin with a pipe and a grin.
There ain't no asking why.
It's time to slack off or die.
J.R. Bob Dobbs, master of slack.
Eternal salvation or triple your money back.
I'm on my hot horse and I'm gonna ride, ride, ride.
I hit the power source.
You fix it better.
Run, run, run.
Put it under Bob's control.
The hover expires while you wait.
Operators are standing by.
From then on, there's no stopping the pop as it spreads from town to town.
I'm a yeti through and through.
Ain't nothing that you can do.
Make all the pings start shaking in their boots.
Make the conspiracy one of you.
You can't hold me or control me.
All the bobbies, whatever you mean.
Till the sausage come down and burn your tongue.
There's no stopping the pop as it spreads from town to town.
There's no passing dough.
Collect 200 million souls.
Sunrise July 5th and the martial symphony shall be recorded.
Then it's time to settle the score.
It ain't about the battle.
It's about the war.
The revelation that comes after the score.
I got more.
First you stand in the Bible.
Play the black and the silent.
It's just too damn much for all of us to rely on.
Cry, baby, cry.
Tears, woe, jades, and story.
See, baby, scream.
Cause it won't take a thing.
Justify your sin with a pipe and a grin.
There ain't no asking why.
It's time to slap your heart or die.
Say you're a black bear with a pipe.
J.R.
Bob Dobbs, master of slap.
It's my last chance to save your life.
Eternal salvation or triple your money back.
Don't leave your cruel and sacred soul.
Put it under Bob's control.
This offer only goes through X day, July 5th, 1998.
You can't stop the pop.
For Christ's sake, isn't there one you fucking maniacs
that know who I'm talking about?
July 5th is coming.
There's no time to wait!
Serve a World Cup golfer's head on a plate.
Know the bliss from the rings of Bob's pipe smoke.
And if you call within the next 30 minutes,
we'll throw in a par-press prairie squid.
Damn, in some parts of the universe,
this thing would be considered gritty!
Woo!
Repent, quit your job, slack off, and drink bomb!
Monkey Hive recorded live at 13X Day Drill.
Unbelievable.
Praise Reverend Suds Pasha and Reverend Gaffer
for that.
More to come in the future.
Before that, collages by Reverend Heart Ignition.
And next, Reverend Fat Man D.
Still on topic from 13X Day Live.
But first, The Large.
I wanna be high.
And through it.
So I think I'd like to sing you one brand new one
before I bring up my very special guest,
this gorgeous girl.
This gorgeous girl.
Let me find it.
I've never sung it in public before.
But I think you will like it.
And if you don't,
you, yeah, fuck you.
If you don't like it, fuck you.
I wish I could say that.
I'd be like,
like, you don't fucking like my show?
Yeah, I don't fucking wanna sing for you.
I don't fucking wanna sing for you.
That's not how that works, though.
You never wanted whiskey.
You never wanted rye.
You only asked me for the reefer.
But for the reefer you must die.
My friend the priestess told me
She warned me of your church.
And I said,
I'm gonna go to church.
Who gave the starving child
To the nuns who
She dreamed of nuns
She dreamed of nuns so blinded
By their faith
By their faith they could not see
They could not see
A hungry baby
A hungry baby crying
Nearly dying to be
Nearly dying to be free
You never wanted whiskey.
You never wanted rye.
You only asked me for the reefer.
But for the reefer you must die.
What do angels sound like
When they're crying?
What makes them raise
Their voice in song?
Is it music
Or a death march?
Are we dreaming
We've been wrong?
I hear the church bells ringing
They tore down trees to house
They tore down trees to house their dead
The living goddess
The living goddess sings among us
I can still
I can still hear her in my head
I wish those priests
I wish those priests surrender
Walk away with their
tales of sin. I live for life and for loving. I care not for the lies they bring. You never wanted
whiskey. You never wanted rye. I only asked you for some reefer. But for that reefer I must die.
I must die.
Won't you help us feed that child still hoping to survive? Why can't we feed it loving? Must it choke for your false gods to survive?
Where is your Jesus hiding?
When I can hear my goddess sing. This earth's forever growing. It knows not of Christ your dead king. You drink the blood of your savior. His flesh grinds between your teeth.
But I'm from civilized people. I praise the life beneath my feet.
We will feed the baby. From our bosom it will feed. Your priests can call me harlot or witch if they so be all a need.
I don't want your whiskey. And I don't want your rye.
I only asked for a reaper
I think those priests must die
Thank you so much.
As you can tell,
I don't get to sing that one at the club too often.
Fatman D of FatmanD.com did that.
Next, a subgenius song about 10 years ago
and just now reintroduced to us
by Dr. Jerry Faison.
A song called Pink Boys.
Pink Boys.
My body is a temple and I'm a hope
And one man's sacraments, another man's gold
The minute God appears in a river
The way you live away your power to the social engineers
They say you're profiting, it doesn't make a way to feel
To figure it out, there's all that bullshit to live
The best profession is a good education
Not being a criminal, so not by invasion
Absolutely not by domination
I predict in the near future
the right wing
will use
drug experience
as a pretext
to set up an
international
police operation.
I hear you, man.
Those guns behind your butt.
Hey.
It was up in the big boy.
Your flesh is my appeal, boy.
Please stay patient.
Hey.
Tell me what's up with the big boy.
My body is a temple and I'm a homeboy.
And one man's sacrifice,
another man's gold.
Sacred plants and vegetables
have been used for thousands of years
to expand
man's mind.
Man's
mind. That one
was not from
any time recently.
Pink Boys was the name of the song
by Jerry Faison from
the 1990s.
But now, from last July
2010, live at
X-Day 13,
Tommy Amoeba.
For my next
number, I would like
to sing to you
a song that I wrote.
It was inspired by
a short story
by my favorite
scientist.
Science fiction author
Arthur C. Dobbs.
It's called
The Nine Billion Names of Bob.
I folded
up my
telescope
and waited for
the wind
to blow
the clouds away
so I could
see the stars.
But when
the heavens
were unveiled,
how could I
trust my eyes?
Beyond
belief,
I
stood beneath
a
black and empty
sky.
If you listen
for the sound,
of the voices
in your head,
the nine billion
names of Bob,
will be whispered
in the wind.
As I'd given
up all hope,
all my wonder turned
to dread,
I folded up
my telescope
and waited
for the wind
for the wind.
We're going to have a couple of ranters before the next act.
And the first ranter is an interesting character.
His name is Reverend Jim Jones.
I'd like everybody to give a hand for Reverend Jim Jones, who apparently has something he
really loves.
He really,
really
needs to let out.
Thank you for giving me a hand, Reverend Stang.
Now I wish I had some good news to tell you people.
I wish I could tell you about how Bob entered my life and how everything was okay, but I can't do that.
So therefore, I'm going to need to make a request.
I need all the haters.
I need you to get up front.
I need all the people that have been crapped on by life.
I need all the people that are ranting and screaming and are mad as hell.
I need all of you up here right now.
That's what I'm talking about.
Now, I'd like to begin things the way I end them.
So I'd like everybody, just for a second,
if we could all join together
for a moment,
of noise!
Praise Bob! Praise Bob! Praise Bob!
Yeah!
Thank you very much.
Now,
Pisces told you that there was something I need to get off of my chest.
It's actually on my chest.
I have this thing.
It's called a hate gland.
Now, you might think to yourself,
why do you need a hate gland?
Just with...
Well, that's the thing.
For most people,
when something makes them mad,
they're just out with it.
You know, wow, you made me mad.
I'm gonna hit you in the face.
But in our world,
we can't do that to Pinks no matter how much we want to.
Oh, we want to.
So what do you do?
You get your hate gland.
And every time somebody says something stupid,
your hate gland fills a little more.
Yeah.
When those Pinks,
when they tell you that you're just gonna get over it,
your hate gland fills a little more.
When they ask you what it is about this Bob thing,
your hate gland fills just a little more.
Well, tonight,
the next day before the pink...
before the X's show up,
we're gonna get all that hate gland out.
I'm emptying it,
and now I'm taking all you with me.
Yeah!
All of you!
See?
Even he couldn't hang out with it.
Yeah.
And he's back.
Don't worry.
He'll be out again.
Now,
I've been thinking a lot about the Pinks.
They're kinda in your face.
Ugh!
I just can't get them out of their head.
They're like a virus.
They're like some cheesy 80's band.
And they're just like,
they're growing.
And it's like,
you're gonna get a swelling head from the normal,
the pinkness.
Now,
a lot of people think,
you know what,
I can pay my $30 and I'm good.
I will have slack.
The conspiracy will stay off my back.
Everything will be okay.
All I gotta do is pay that $30.
No!
You think you can do it every day?
You gotta praise Bob every day.
You gotta fuck shit every day.
You gotta make mistakes.
Every goddamn day!
That's what I'm talking about!
You gotta be a subgenius every minute.
And if not,
then you backslide.
And you might think,
well, you know,
if I backslide,
I still pay my $30.
But here's the thing.
You may get on those saucers,
but you will live a lifetime of slacklessness.
If that's all you do,
you gotta get that original slack.
You gotta get it back in you.
Thank you.
Can I get a praise, Bob?
Yeah, yeah!
Yeah, stamp straight!
Stamp straight!
That's what I'm talking about.
Now,
I want,
you can get that slack back.
First, you pay your $30.
Step one.
Step two,
you give money to Bob.
Yeah!
How do you give your money to Bob?
You go to the swag shack.
You spend money at the swag shack.
You listen to the hour of slack
every single week.
Now, you see,
Now, you see, here's the thing.
I'll tell you guys a little bit of a secret,
a little bit of a confessional.
I,
I used to be like those normals out there.
I know, I know!
I don't believe it either.
I used to think, you know what,
maybe if I just, you know,
work a little harder,
make a little bit,
yeah, then I'll get slack.
Maybe, maybe,
maybe if I just smoke a little bit more,
then I'll get slack.
Maybe, maybe,
maybe if I just cut my hair
and shave my beard and look normal,
maybe I'll get slack!
And then I had a vision.
Then I saw, you know what I saw?
I saw that face!
That face!
J.R. Bob Dobbs!
I saw that face!
And I looked at that face and I said,
what the hell is this, this Bob guy?
Fuck!
I don't want that Bob guy.
I want like Jesus.
I want the goddess.
I want that Wiccan shit.
You can get the Wiccan chicks that way.
But no, no!
I got Bob!
And I'm sitting here and I'm like,
what do you want from me, Bob?
Why won't you leave me alone?
And he said, no!
I'll make you a deal.
You, and I was like, okay.
Yeah, I was like, you know what?
Okay, okay.
We'll make this deal.
You tell me what you're gonna give me.
And he said, here's the deal.
First, you pay your $30.
Then, you listen to the hour slack.
Then, you buy shit at the swag shack.
And then, you will get slack.
Yeah!
Now, I wish I could say that I fake my hate.
I wish I could say to you guys that, you know,
I'm not really like this.
You know, like Stang does.
You know.
I wish I could be that cool.
But you know what?
I'm not.
Because I look at the pinks and I feel, hey!
Can I get a praise, Bob?
Yeah!
I look at their excuses, I look at the dumb shit they do, and I'm like, ugh!
That's what I'm saying.
How am I doing for time?
We got it.
Now.
Yeah.
Whatever you want.
Yes!
Sex!
Bob is better than sex!
He is better than drugs!
He is better than everything because he is slack!
He is everything and all of that and none of it at the same time!
That's what I'm talking about!
Now.
There's something I want you guys to get ready for that we're going do here in a minute.
Now, I thought I could do this for a long time, but you know, I'm going to cut it short, give you the essence.
But I want you to start getting ready for it now.
Now, I know I'm not the only person that has the hate.
I know all of you fuckers got it too.
Don't lie.
Don't front with me.
You all got it.
Now, I want you to take that hate.
You feel it right there.
That type of hate that makes you sick.
That type of hate when everybody says something bullshit about Bob.
Whenever Bob says bullshit to you.
All of that everyday crap that's in your head right now.
I want you to start getting ready.
Because at the end, when I get that tone from Pisces, we're going to do a one minute hate.
I'm not just going to do it.
I'm going to make a fool out of myself.
Don't you worry about that.
But I'm going to make a fool out of myself so you guys can do it too.
So whatever you do, don't worry.
I'm going to be a lot.
More stupid looking than you.
And I can take comfort in the fact that no matter how stupid I look.
I'm going to be stupider than that face.
Yeah.
Because we are not stupid enough to be Bob.
We are not slantful enough to be Bob.
And you know what?
That's okay.
That is awesome.
Because it always gives us something to aspire to.
And I remember I was watching that thing live.
That CD.
You know.
You're supposed to get it to kind of like fiddle with your head or something.
And you know, they said that those eyes and that face.
That face.
Can I get a praise for that face?
Yeah.
And they said that that face is the face of the conspiracy.
And that it's all.
I know.
And they said it's all the joke.
But you know.
What a very wise man said to me not long ago.
And he said it to all you guys too.
Tell us.
Yes.
But first, you got to scream for me.
Praise Bob!
That's what I'm talking about.
Thank you.
Now.
He said that this may be the greatest joke ever.
If the earth can make it.
The punchline.
But I don't care if it's a joke.
I don't care if it's funny.
Uh-uh.
They're giving secrets.
That's probably some of that church hierarchy stuff.
I wish I could tell you about that.
But I don't know nothing about that.
I'm just up here screaming.
Dancing for your amusement.
Now.
I think it's about time.
Do you guys feel that hate yet?
Yeah.
Are you feeling it?
Okay.
Can I get somebody with one of those conspiracy clocks?
Give me.
You know what?
I was going to give it one minute.
But I think you guys want two.
Do you guys want a two-minute hate?
No.
We want three minutes.
You want three minutes?
You want to give Bob three minutes?
Here's what I want you guys to do for me.
Hate.
I want you guys to scream so loud that they will hear it everywhere.
Scream.
Woo.
Go.
Oh.
Faster.
Do it.
Do it to the ground, people.
Yeah.
Woo.
Up you up.
Woo moves it.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, but it's going to explode.
Thank you.
Have it yourselves.
I get kay.
Buy me a drink on those saucers.
Amazing, crazy Jim Jones.
You know what is the coolest thing about that guy?
His hairstyle.
Praise fucking Bob.
Oh, you noticed.
Well, we appreciate the appreciative.
Yes, friends, Reverend Crazy Jim Jones did that,
and everybody was impressed.
Before that, Tommy Amoeba, likewise.
That 13X Day Drill, sponsored by the same bunch of knuckleheads
who did this show, the Church of the Subgenius.
For more information, see subgenius.com.
In the radio section of that website,
you'll find all lists of what we play
and the MP3 downloads of all shows we have ever done.
That's subgenius.com.
Meanwhile, Lemur paves.
The way.
Thank you.
Oh, and by the way, the background music during the credits
was from the new album by Mayan Ruins,
Sacred and Profane.
You can see mayanruinstribal.com
for more information about that fine CD.
Thank you.
Joe.
Juvenile Friday.
Yes, ma'am.
Could you hold on a minute, please?
Yeah.
Speak just enough English to answer the phone.
Can I help you?
Yes, sir.
No, sir.
Right.
Like they say in Tibet, you know.
No, I guess you wouldn't know it.
Is that right?
It's been a lot.
Right.
I'll bet.
Thank you.
Yeah.
A stoner could have done it.
Go ahead.
A stoner was right back on the floor.
Is that all the money you got?
It's not fair.
Back.
Has he been using narcotics?
What's that?
How's that?
Tomorrow you get a haircut and those beads come off.
Yeah.
Hello.
Goodbye.
Well, compatriots, compadres, campesinos, mis amigos, we're not here because we want
to stay on Earth.
And we're not even actually satisfied with what may or may not be.
We are here for one reason and one reason only and that is to have sex with aliens.
And in that vein.
Our last selection is the theme song to everybody's favorite sci-fi classic hit, Star Trek.
This song was written by Alexander Courage and Gene Roddenberry.
Thank you so much for tuning in to X Day 13.
Live in Brushwood, the last and only.
I'm Fat Mandy.
This is Princess Wiardo.
Woo!
Beyond the rim of the starlight.
My life.
Is wandering in star fly.
I know.
He'll find in star clustered reaches.
Love.
Strange love a star woman teaches.
I know.
His journey ends never.
His star trek will go on forever.
But tell him when he reaches his story.
See.
Remember.
Remember me.
See.
Remember.
Oh.
Stay near me.
Far or near.
To play far is fun and sweet.
We are the Dole!
Oh.
Love.
police statistics in franais.
Me outside the screen.
Yes, sir, what'll it...
Well, hello.
Can I be of some assistance, maybe?
I just want my suitcase.
Thanks, baby.
Here.
Small token of my appre...
Oh.
Okay, pal, whatever you say.
You want me to wait?
Yeah, you better.
Yeah.
I headed for the slippery half-open single-beaded plush-white yellow-stretched-out wild-sparkling pudgy cocky-polished little cherubic smile.
Smiling lassie.
Flyway fire red blood-stained leather boots.
Happy of the seven dwarfs in Jungle Getup.
It was a good time for me and my 38 to announce ourselves.
Thank you.
I always do.