So, you will be greedy.
Now I'll tell you a story about a mouse who was greedy and came to a bad end.
The Strange Doctor Weird
The
Self-Genius Power of
Swag
Joe Doakes was just a guy who liked to tinker around his barn.
Some people thought Joe was lazy.
Some even thought he was nuts.
But one day, he had an idea.
I thought I was good.
I was mental.
Very mental.
A couple of ladies' eyes.
Mental.
Very mental.
You just get motionless to you.
You get a phone call.
It sounds great.
You're mental.
Forget about that phone call.
Whether it happens or it doesn't happen.
You better be mental.
Hello.
You better be mental all the time.
I'm blessed being mental.
That's the way I see it.
No matter what you say about me, I think I'm mental.
That's what you gotta be.
Mental.
And if it ain't good enough for the person next to you, that's just unmental.
Very unmental.
Another word for unmental is you're mental.
Willing spirits as well.
That's trying to look good.
I'm a gay chick.
I'll do my therapy.
Drop that beep.
You know?
Mental.
Very mental.
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
Maybe that's all Bob is.
I'll say hello later.
Golly!
Bob.
Exclusive.
Easy.
Full, comfortable, custom, perfect.
New!
Real hair.
Let's just step up.
Okay.
So here it is.
Now this is what happens.
Again and again and again and again.
And when it does, when they probably don't.
So there you are.
Well, here's the problem.
But hey, sponsored by the Partnership for a Free America.
We go to my way to heaven.
In seven.
Seven.
I'm in heaven.
Yodel my way to heaven, to the Father, Jesus Christ.
You know, I ain't a church-going person, but I swear, that's going to be a thing of the past.
Um, let him be all right. I didn't hit him hard. He should still have one good one left in him.
Beloved, I wish above all things that it's mine. Flush it down the toilet, because it's mine.
How long will you sit? But it's mine. Sin, sin, it's mine. Hatred, it's mine. Bitterness, it's mine.
Covetousness, it's mine.
The Bible says that it's mine.
This little hunt found me excited.
5, 2, 5, 2, 6, 6, 2, 8, 6, 9, 2, 0.
Oh, baby.
Who gets the chance?
We want toد
Nice to meet ya-
Who gets in a dragon,
You get your
life
Let's begin. According to the nursery rhyme, what term refers to a Roman Catholic?
Uhh, uh,
Yes. What letter found in 1937,
Uh. Old Golden Earl.
That's right?
Yes.
Oh, no.
Oh, a cat.
Yes.
B-b-b-b-bob filed for bankruptcy in October 2001.
Oh, uh, uh, uh, I don't know.
Yes. Uh, you've got a bunch wrong.
Oh, a f-king Bob.
Now let's see what you've got around here we can tax.
Hmm. Let's see.
What's going on here?
Say, what kind of a joint is this anyway?
1-11-7-9-3-5-13
My name is Coco, and the reason I do drugs is because I have Down syndrome.
Because having Down syndrome, I can't really tell what's right or wrong.
So I do drugs because I have Down syndrome.
And I feel that I need to do drugs.
Spotted by PCP for Free America.
A nice lucky number.
Well, you better hope I don't.
You can't.
Oh, you can.
Right.
This man's drugs.
I know.
Yeah, well, watch it.
Whatever.
So he's trying drugs.
Alright.
He's spending more time with his loves.
Ah, yeah, don't mess with me.
And it works.
Parents give their kids drugs at www.freedrug.org.
Sponsored by a partnership for Free America.
This is my last committee hearing as chairman.
And I hate education.
And I hate New York.
I hate Southeast Asia and Southwest Asia.
And Colombia and every place else.
I hate younger and younger people.
And I hate families.
I hate kids in grade schools.
When you kill one, there's 10 or 20 or 50 waiting to take his place.
I hate society.
And I hate people like you.
But I have one question that nobody ever asks.
And that's this question.
What would happen?
I'd like for any of you to answer that.
There are some things you just do.
Like smoking marijuana.
Because when you get high, it's your mind you're messing with.
So what?
My brother Jeff's gonna drop at the mall tonight.
The good stuff.
Sponsored by the Office of Drug America.
How's it going, dude?
I'm not sure.
I don't know if I'm actually gonna make it or not.
I'm really glad I wasn't able to make it.
No, I haven't, you see.
This is an energy spoiler.
So we're really happy with that.
I want people to know that.
So avoid hip-hop and left- reopening, you know what I mean.
I'd кожan somebody cause I'm in crisis.
But at the very least, it gets on the good side.
I'm not sure.
I mean I've got to check out the radio station thing at night.
My turn is it going eineutrop awakened forever and ever which is so funny to me.
and other people.
The ESO stuff on the show was done in early 2003,
a few days after the tragic Columbia shuttle explosion,
15 minutes before landing would have happened.
Although the space collage by Chaz Smith,
which you'll hear that's also in the show,
predates that.
It's from around 1998.
Conspiracy year.
Even though it sounds like it must have been assembled yesterday
just for the shuttle show of 2003.
Anyway, special thanks to all the Alt Binaries Slack artistes
from back in Usenet day who posted the collages,
especially Fernanda Nende-Lemur.
The Ghost Intro Show title mix was an Artemia Salina creation.
And now a piece of music,
by Aphex Twin,
which started with a recording of a bouncing ball
and all other instrumentation was electronically derived
from that simple sound.
Aphex Twin.
Both weapons had beaters of当!'s
birthright videol bringing Aphex Twin next year,
Do the American Party have a business
I'm going to show you how to do it.
Uh, yes.
Listen to the wind.
Oh my God.
The wind.
I'm a machine.
She's jumping.
There.
God knows what the machine is supposed to do.
Coming in on a wing and a prayer.
Well, obviously the machine didn't do what it was supposed to do.
Step on into the chapel.
We're marrying men and women.
Okay.
Flower is a vegetable.
Come on.
and everything
to its own self.
A gift of
Roger Houston.
Stop.
Look up.
Hey, Houston, look up.
I think we got this.
Hub, hub, hub.
You have no alternative.
You know it.
Everything will be all right.
You are in my hands.
I am here to protect you.
You have nowhere to go.
Here at Truth Control,
we do our best.
we do our best
to keep you thinking
of the best things
you can think.
Here at Truth Control,
we do our best
to keep you not thinking,
to keep you asleep,
to keep you wandering
around in the dark.
Here at Truth Control,
we're here to help.
Hey,
we have no time
to be here.
Please come back.
You have nothing to be afraid of.
We have to go back.
And it is your last chance to return.
You have nowhere to go.
You cannot survive.
We only want to help you.
This is your last chance.
There can be other creatures in this alien environment.
Hunters.
Hunters are fast and maneuverable.
They eat the floaters, both for their organic molecules and for their store of pure hydrogen.
But there can't be many hunters, because if they destroy all the floaters, they themselves will perish.
But have we neglected one of the most important items necessary for being effective for the kingdom?
I have come upon an amazing and startling conclusion that this here great mass that we stand upon,
heaving and throttling...
sweeps through the land holding the land join masters,
is restricted to the land of speed,
I shall shake the gods' clanka.
The fire, horses, the mountains.
About men of last España.
步 steps now become a kingdom.
We are our senses to Це,
we are our hearts to this
world.
Let's rise up,
and advance.
You need fourえ
Here we go.
What do we do?
You ask that question now?
The Major in Longerat, you say?
You know the answer, Major.
Sure.
We'll circle around.
Then we'll crash.
No, no, no, no.
No, it'll be all right, my boy.
My word again.
Have peace forever.
Prophecy is an easy thing.
For rarely is the prophet brought to judgment.
Tonight I bring you a false prophecy.
The place of our story is a great rocket speeding away from the moon.
Now, as you notice, some of these ships are made of cardboard.
If you've got the will, if you've got what made America great,
if you've got a heart,
a heart as big as the sun and an ass as big as the moon,
you'll make it.
You'll storm on through those stars like a laser through butter.
Yeah, man.
Yeah.
Come on, come on.
Don't worry about that plastic wrap around.
It's not real plastic.
No, that's a solar shield, man.
That'll protect you.
It's not plastic and those cigarette wrappers on the floor.
That's insulation device for when you're in deep space.
But you've got to believe, you've got to believe, you've got to believe, Earth, that you're
a man, you've got to believe.
Deep space.
In the slash, slash, slash.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes, I've always known.
Yes, I agree.
Man, it really makes it, yeah.
That's a real man.
It really makes it.
Susie?
Forget it.
You better run along out if you want to have your invasion before dark.
It is time.
I want you to tell me the truth.
What is this invasion silliness?
It isn't silly.
It's just a game.
That's all.
Whoa.
That was a funny little radio show, wasn't it?
Did you want the peaceful victim or did you want the...
That was a funny little radio show.
They thought I was...
I thought they wanted me.
Money.
They wanted me.
What was the issue?
Invasion?
Drill?
Zero hour?
There are a lot of kooks out there.
There are a lot of people that will use, you know, what the scripture says wrong.
They will interpret it in a way to benefit themselves.
And then I go and I fix the problem.
I cut the potato and then I cut the potato and I eat the potato and then I make another
potato into a potato flute and I go up the mountain and I yell to greet the new day and
then I yell to greet the end of the day.
That is my potato life.
I'm so full of happiness.
Hooked on something new.
Yeah.
Almost out of coolness.
Harvest fresh onions that you're
decentralized into fresh onions, because you're not supposed to go to place to aside
We can't spend as much time around the Earth.
That's what they were singing.
They came down that last 15 minutes of flight.
15 minutes from landing.
We set sail on this new sea.
Because there is new knowledge to be gained.
And this is my room.
And you're all here.
And I'm not going to leave here ever, ever, ever again.
So what's your theory about the...
I think they slapped the taste right out of Chaz's mouth.
Don't you think it's highly distasteful?
To talk about that jet.
What got the shuttle?
I think it was Zeus with his mighty blue thunderbolt.
They're talking about...
He's got some great thunderbolts this year.
Who's got blue thunderbolts besides Zeus?
I mean, it might be the Zeus liberation army.
Which I guess is very fundamentalist in their beliefs.
They go back to your zip.
I don't know.
I've heard that Ra has green thunderbolts.
No, but you notice the thunderbolts that rolled off good old...
And Bob has great big red...
Straps.
Great big bungee sticks.
He whooped the hell out of me, that thunderbolt.
For using a Chinese...
So I heard that NASA knew from the beginning of the flight that that was going to happen,
but didn't tell the astronauts because they couldn't do anything about it.
Oh, man.
What a grim thought.
You know, I had...
And then they made up this whole thing that they're going to do this big, you know,
the inquiry and all that to, you know, cover that off.
Oh, actually, I had an even more paranoid whole scenario unfold in my imagination.
Underwear?
Shortly after I heard the thing.
It was like a movie.
It was just like an action movie.
Well, imagine if those guys were up there and they're, of course...
Just having a smoke after some copulon.
Quintus interruptus.
Just check it out.
I'm listening.
And...
Okay.
The astronauts have been instructed to dump.
This mysterious cargo into orbit.
One of them does some homework and discovers that it's a doomsday privacy erasing device
to be put into orbit that could easily be used by the wrong hands to enslave all humanity
under fill in the blank.
The astronauts confer and decide not to activate the evil device.
But one of the astronauts is, of course, secretly with them, the big them.
And he pulls out a death ray or something on the other astronauts.
Now, stand up.
Stand back.
I'm going to bring this baby down.
But this one woman astronaut who he had knocked out earlier, she comes to behind him.
I didn't wake him up.
And she's just in time to clobber him from behind.
And there's this dramatic fight aboard the shuttle as it's coming in for a landing.
Wow.
Okay.
Now, the good guys, the good astronauts defeat the bad agent astronaut and have informed
mission control.
We're coming in for a landing with big news that will shake the world and shock everyone.
And that...
Is when they in Washington or Langley or wherever ordered the secret button push that makes
the shuttle explode upon reentry just as if a heat panel or something had been damaged
during takeoff.
And they even had fake footage of that standing by just in case of that kind of emergency
and sudden cover-up.
Wow.
And that makes me a real conspiracy theorist and made-for-TV movie director.
You think as a movie director they could come up with better prosthetics than fake feet?
Hey, who's on the line?
You know?
Man stank.
You've been working in the methamphetamine mines way too long.
It's time for you to find a new line of work.
Look at his fingernails.
They're all like Fu Manchu'd and long and have weird things sticking out.
I knew how dangerous it was when I went up there.
We all wanted to get off and those American, those brave Americans got off Earth.
Man is frozen as frosty spines.
Just a bunch of flaming monkeys falling from the sky.
I can't see out the window.
They're all glazed open.
Matt, have you ever saw flaming monkeys falling from the sky before?
Well, of course we've seen it numerous.
We saw it like 17 years ago.
Well, sure.
Back when the amphetamines were...
They were flaming.
Good reference, Strange.
He knows about flaming monkeys and amphetamines.
This whole thing gives me a great new idea to start up a whole new cottage industry.
A new burial technique for people with way too much money.
Cottage cheese.
Shoot their corpses up into orbit.
Cremation by re-entry.
Oh, I thought you were going to turn them into a cheese.
If you can't afford it, 100 grand will descend your head up and re-enter your head.
No, you don't even have to.
You just have to pump them up a little bit.
You know?
You don't even have to get them that high.
Why?
And they'll just come back down.
You could probably do it with a military device.
Why not leave them in the methamphetamine labs?
You just take their money and you throw their corpses on the heap with the rest of the rotting monkeys.
Why not re-amphetimate them?
You know what I mean?
Bring them back to life with the amphetamines we've created in our lab.
Admiral Timothy Leary, yeah, right.
And Admiral Posty Leary was honored by that type of cremation.
But he couldn't ejaculate at the wrong moment.
And so he was incinerated just the same.
Of course we believe in it.
You really believe we are?
We've actually been in space.
It's dog.
We've never been in space.
Hey, really, I don't believe we walked.
Nobody's ever made it outside the dome.
I don't believe we walked on the moon.
I don't.
You want to know why?
Nobody's ever really made it past those warehouse walls with Shell Beach painted on them.
Friends, the first half of this show, all those zillions of collages that mess with your head
were by the great cut-up of Alt.BinarySlack for NendeNendeLieber.
Mer.
Praise.
Leemer.
Of Leemuria.
And they were arranged by me.
In fact, friends, half of the next four shows will be the cut-ups from that great cut-up.
Now, there was also the long space collage preceding the talk of the sad shuttle situation.
And that collage was by the great Professor Chaz Smith.
Dances with rockets.
On ESO radio.
And, uh, friends, coming up, stay tuned for more, more, more.
Including this computer speaking by Heart Ignition.
Would you like to play a game of Genesis?
Or maybe you would like to have sex?
With the dead body?
J.R.
Dock, you'll make that a reality.
Fruit is good.
Cheeks.
Sex with dead bodies is good.
So many of us posing is one thing.
In reality being something quite different.
Society, the highest claddom sort of self has been learning from London.
It might be been sleeping where he is.
However, as it would like to you and your to clear, and for you to be of his.
That's all I have to say.
I noticed that my capillaries are beginning to float to the surface.
I'm going to have to get a new one.
And they're starting to pop and roar like lamb's bread.
Lamb's bread.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
Camera 5, you want to take down the shorts on the, uh, Numinator over there.
Looks like we've only got a high profile until a midway shot.
Looks like we need to go for a full shot of the...
A robotic flailer.
I don't believe...
Hey, how do you fix this robot, man?
On the moon.
I don't believe it.
I never could.
The robot's head exploded, dudes.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha.
You know that...
Maybe Phil Spector actually grazed the shot, you know, Columbia as it was coming into our airspace.
As he was aiming at Xena's double.
He was already confused by thinking he was shooting at Xena.
He shot her double, but actually he fired five shots.
One went off the rim of the old canister there next to the neck, you know, neck...
So it was one of Phil Spector's...
...neck of the Philiac pool.
Ricochet bullets?
It might have been Phil Spector's Ricochet.
That brought down the...
Oh my God.
Think of it numerologically speaking.
Phil Spector has 11 as the numerological bedroom, which comes out to two.
Okay.
Needless to say.
All right, now two is an interface between the yin and the yang.
As we both know, it's a...
Right, right.
Duh.
And everything.
Okay.
So you've got the yin and yang.
You've got a perfect balance.
And then he throws it out of balance.
And what have we got going on in space?
We've got a curry party.
We've got people talking about golf.
And next thing you know, the last...
Well, now how does Michael Jackson admitting to sleeping with the boy...
Boys have to play with it.
It's a hit.
These are all hits.
But did you...
The space shuttle was a hit.
Michael Jackson is having hits all over again.
His crappy albums are selling better than ever.
Okay, here's a conspiracy theory.
Did you hear that Michael Jackson, and the reason for his weird intolerance to sunlight
and his facial diseases, is that he was a former shuttle casualty?
Come to me.
I thought he was just an evil.
That's from a Canadian website.
That word come is an invitation.
Michael Jackson, Michael Jackson.
I'm not an alien or just a severely damaged astronaut.
Somewhere up there in the land of Pan, never, never land.
You know, like waiting for Captain Hook, I guess.
To come out of the sky and...
I'm Captain Hook.
You're Captain Hook, well I'm Peter Pan.
Come to me.
Tinker Bell, Wendy.
I am Captain Hook.
I am your father, Peter Pan.
Come to me.
Come and sit upon my pegged lap.
I will tell you the stories of seven leagues deep.
That word come is an invitation.
I'm the kind of pirate you've heard about, young Peter.
That's right, a modern pirate on a modern ship capable of taking down air force and
army weapons in...
Was that virtual too?
I mean, was that so-called nano-virtual or was that just like a...
I don't know what you're talking about, I didn't hear anything.
I'm talking about old blue eyes.
You know, talking about the lounge mood.
You're proud to be a ding-a-ling.
I am.
I'm past that cigar and give me a martini.
Proud to swing my ding-a-ling against your empty brain pad.
That's a just a ding-a-thing.
I'm not a baby dangler.
I'm not.
You're not a baby dangler?
I'm just hanging out with my kids.
He's not a baby dangler.
He's hanging out.
See, you can take that two ways.
Yeah, exactly.
That's very logical.
Because he's known to expose himself to the elephant or whatever the name.
If there is a God and he made everything beautiful, how'd you guys get here?
We came on the plane.
We came around the covenant nation.
We do not need people that are hung up this way.
That is the exact same grammatical form, obviously just reversed.
But I have a real problem.
If it means one and only one, obviously under 60, a person who is sober minded.
And if you can't handle that, we do not need people that are hung up this way.
You would get people more in tune with what may lie ahead.
I couldn't tell you what city it was or what, where everything started being somewhat civil
and pockets that are missing underneath civilization.
The upper floors of the high rises were just desolate.
Luster jumped bail two weeks ago, halfway through his date race.
He told the public, split, He
He said work can help you everywhere.
He said spiritual life is a these things you canilah isolate cream,
But it is real business, You know that?
That's what I help them enjoy.
University
Look out!
Outro
or three. Six and a half dozen of the
other. Patrons, Saints, Civilizations, and
parking meters.
Bet you didn't know that. You're not Catholic, are you?
So it's all like church stuff?
It's all church stuff all night long.
That's right.
Another hour and a half. Another hour and a half
in your ear. Church on one
channel.
You can roll over.
You can forget about us. Or you can call in now
and stop the show.
You can call in at
424-425 and stop the show now.
That's literally true, isn't that?
That's the way he would have wanted it
if someone would have given him a choice.
Yes, had they really
thought about it and dialed
010-484-425.
As many men could call in now
and stop this madness now.
That's right. That's the way he would have wanted it
if he wouldn't have wanted it that other way.
Ladies can call free.
Tell us there was not in this
horrible heat. Wait, that's you.
What the heck is going on?
No, that was my mentor
Jimmy Swagger.
Oh, they were animals and not human
beings.
He's talking about last week's
pinpoint.
Let's go eat some vegans for breakfast
after this show.
I give you my word, I will
smite this cancer.
Smite, smite, smite.
Smiting, some more smiting. Must be a band
thing. Smite you.
No, Smite was the guitarist.
He's the lead guitar guy.
Oh, I used to listen to the smites.
He may be a human,
but he's on the line.
On and on and on and on.
Never stop.
Although he may have a heart and a brain.
He lacks courage.
But all he...
What do they have
that he doesn't have?
They have medals of honor and valor.
We should not concern ourselves
about him because he has no legal right.
Bob had no legal right.
Bob was not a man
as we call men.
But let's leave.
But let's leave things of this world behind now.
Walk down the primrose
path of Bob
for this gauntlet of torture.
What?
Gabrochen. I can't say Gabrochen.
The Supreme Court said it better.
Don't call me a Gabrochen.
Ah, yes, dear friends, this is Reverend Ivan Stank.
Yes, these
wonderful moments of the past can be
yours today. If you call in now.
Call in now on the miracle of MP3.
Over 700,000 hours
of subgenius broadcast
on one CD.
More than you can listen to in an entire lifetime.
And you'll be forced to.
Incredible 7.5.
You'll be influenced by Dobstown.
Call in for a 4-4-2-1.
Dobstown.
Where am I going? Help me.
Why am I going to...
Did I win that CD?
Yeah.
Now listen to this song
and it's Hypno Theory.
Ironically
enough, the Dobstown song is from
Lee Murray. That's right.
I thought it was Wilbur Harrison.
He knows that.
I mean, we must brainwash our children.
What are you guys on
when you're doing that show, man?
Oh, yeah.
Come on, you can tell me.
I see you've done toilet on your floor.
A song?
I mean, this...
Song?
Caller.
My little son, caller.
This song is dedicated to you.
And your trippy amp today.
Can you just fast forward the whole show?
I want to get out of here.
No, down.
Just, you know, go down.
Down.
Just go down.
But I did go downtown.
No, come on.
Just go down.
Yeah, how's it going?
And then say, stereo.
I am a cave.
Fernando Mandela.
All those cutouts.
Yes, Burbid.
I just got into the studio.
No.
Slack mixes by you.
Rock music is leading our young.
people to drug addiction and promiscuity.
You seem a little nervous, my friend.
You're just a strange kind of fire, so...
You're selling me from beyond.
You'd better be ready
to speak your piece.
You can't...
Call me from beyond.
You disturb my rest of sleep
with your childish games.
You don't know what you're playing with.
This is not a game
for little boys and girls.
This is a game
Look, we're not just another stupid heavy metal band.
Listen to your music backwards and reverse.
It's okay, world, but...
You can't do that.
Heavy metal, heavy metal, heavy metal.
I'm not saying I don't...
Well, you know, I'm kind of...
The bottom of the age...
Right.
I'm not saying I don't...
Heavy metal is heavy. Get it?
Cool!
You ran for me.
I used to be a nice guy just like you.
And then I found...
The truth is in the taking...
You know what's wrong with you.
I will need a lie.
I bet you have a spit in your face.
I'm sorry.
You ran for me.
Better be ready to face the consequences.
It's never too late to redeem yourself.
One last chance.
That's all you have.
It's up to you.
You ran for me.
No escaping my eyes.
You'll see them in every dream.
You will see them in your dreams.
A dream you can't ever see for real.
A dream you'll never see for real.
You'll see them in every dream.
You'll never escape the eyes.
A dream you can't ever see for real.
The sun will never shine in the eyes again.
Would you like to be my ex-girlfriend?
Oh yeah!
You'll still be my ex-girlfriend.
Ready for me from beyond?
You've got to be ready to face the truth, my friend.
I'm here for you, slow.
That was...
You rang from Reverend Bill T. Miller.
And you can get a lot of free Reverend Bill T. Miller music from...
www.billtmiller.com
When girls go by, then I play high.
I thrill them with each note.
Oh, how I get their goat.
I'm the fellow with the fiddle.
Oh, boy, I can play the best in town.
I make a smile from every round.
And every time I start to play,
I say the whole of Dorna Town begins to sway.
A-votey, votey, votey, and a-fretz-hat-say.
A-root-a-toot-a-toot-a, and a-raz-a-ma-taz.
When I play, though, the girls say,
Oh, and tremble like they're freezing.
I know that I'm the reason,
for I'm the fellow with the fiddle.
Oh, boy, I can play the best in town.
Just a little girl, she'd come in,
and she'd see, she'd notice,
and she'd run all around.
And she'd want to ask her mother for a fiddle.
And she'd learn to sing for her.
She'd tell her mother, say,
Sing for your fiddle and you can get it.
And she'd jump out in front of her and sing.
Give me a little fiddle.
No, a titty mama, titty.
Titty mama, titty.
Just give me a little titty, please, ma'am.
A titty on the hill, mama.
Say it again.
Titty mama, titty.
Just give me a little titty, please, ma'am.
A titty on the hill, mama.
Friends, that was Mary McDonald, and I don't know anything more about that.
Before that, we heard a little bit of Mel Blanc singing Fellow with a Fiddle
from the Warner Brothers cartoon of the same name.
This music in the background is from the amino acids from Detroit.
Check out www.aminoacids.com.
We're going to be doing a revival in Detroit soon with the amino acids.
Ah, yes.
And now this.
Boy, he was quite a man, Bob Dobbs.
Right, that Bob.
Quite a woman, too.
He was everything. He was an animal.
He was an animal.
He made a believer out of you.
J.R. Bob Dobbs was an amoeba.
He was an amoeba and a super genius.
He was like the smartest amoeba that ever existed and the most mindless man.
He was like Big Brother and Little Daddy at the same time.
You felt like love-hate in one emotion at the same consternation.
Right, like the tallest midget and the shortest giant.
You knew both concepts at one time.
You'd see him, you'd know height and small at the same time.
You could feel it, you could smell it.
He was like the essence of everything.
Like the cleanest dirt.
Oh, they used to use that clean dirt.
Bob used to give off clean dirt that sprang flowers and little vegetables out.
He was like the driest water.
He was like Santa Ana winds blowing a big old polar bear.
Try not to.
He was like burning hot ice.
He was like that polar bear in a bad dance club.
He was like the furniture you can't believe in and yet you try.
He was the source.
He was the...
He was...
Bob.
He's gonna be back.
I know he's gonna be back.
J.R. Bob Dobbs, if you're listening to me now...
I have faith.
He's gonna be back.
Faith in you.
He made the salmon sweat.
He made the eye cheese come out where it's not supposed to grow.
He made the Eskimo buy ice.
He made the ice for the sorcerers.
And he kissed each and every one of them with an Eskimo.
He sold hate to the Nazis.
He gave love.
He gave love wherever he could find a place to sit down.
He sold hypocrisy to the Baptists.
He sold retardation to the subgenius.
Yes.
Sold water.
He sold water to old St. Nick.
He sold a fluoroscope to his uncle.
And then he sold himself out of business.
But he still kept on being and seeing and being the source.
He had insurance, my friend.
Bob had insurance.
Do you?
Do you have Bob's insurance policy?
Bob is your insurance policy, my friends.
And it's just one payment you make.
The premium lasts forever and ever and ever.
And never comes back.
And if for any reason you should chance to die or drive into a car
or perhaps just fall asleep and not wake up sometimes,
that's your problem.
And that's Bob too?
He's your insurance policy?
And he's what kills you both at the same time?
Bob resold your insurance policy to a crooked bunch of weird scam artists at the Pentagon.
Because he loved you.
He had so much love for you.
Look, look, look at his leg.
He's...
He needs a towel.
He can't...
Bob loves you more than you love anything.
Oh, those chromosomes are so bleak.
But at the same time, if you could just pack one little bit of that essence...
They're rock hard, the chromosomes are.
You'd be rock hard like those chromosomes.
Oh, yeah.
I'm not a baby dangler.
Bob's a baby dangler.
He dangled you at the moment of your birth.
He dangled me.
And it's taken all this time for you to wake up.
Is he gonna smack you?
Are you gonna wake up and start breathing and being alive?
Baby poop poop bait!
...city probe scanner.
Are you gonna just be...
...across some illegal sexual activity?
A reprobate.
It should be on your DTO screen now.
Reprobate.
Pay close attention to the following transmission.
Your eyes may become unfocused.
You may feel heat around the back of your neck and shoulders.
The forehead may become indented.
Ooh, that feels good, Bob.
Further down. A little further down.
I'm phasing.
I'm phasing now.
Ooh, nope, I got...
I...
I got a squishy.
Oh, that's perfect.
Wait a minute.
I'm gonna put it in my pants.
Oh, that's perfect.
Pipe down.
Pipe down in there.
Bob's trying to sleep.
Hey!
Pipe down!
Bob's trying to sleep!
Shh.
Relax.
Let go.
Oh, it's very, very easy.
Talk to the leper first.
You don't encourage the leper.
You talk to the leper.
It's hard for a leper to change its patches.
Take it.
You're in there.
Okay, you're impaired now.
Oh, disgusting.
Your convolution.
My
Galena wants you to listen to this music with pride now.
The music will make you hard and frightened.
Frightened and hard.
Take down those, take down those, take down those drops.
Who's there?
It's the tax assessor.
Tax assessor?
A little music there from Fellow with a Fiddle, and now more from Reverend Cobblestone's collage.
Yes, I'm just pleased about the loss of the manufacturing command and presence that we once enjoyed.
It's gone the route of what everything else has in America.
A global war of...
One world order, the new world order, whatever you want to call it.
The culture of death.
You know, I guess I was vaguely weak, but until you said flat out, it hasn't been in my consciousness.
Isn't that special?
Well, I think you're right here.
The effect of the sense of modernity, the American values, have some value.
I'm not going to take that ride.
No, I'm not going to.
Let's have a moment of silence for the little twinkle twinkle.
Twinkle little stars that burned up in the atmosphere.
Yeah, that is kind of, you know...
They got off.
You know, I'm always so radical in my stanchies.
I get all sheepy when I think of, what's your name, the Indian girl.
Dave's got the hot...
He's looking at the pictures.
Well, I have. I have no necronomicon or whatever you call them.
You know, I'm not a necrophiliac.
Or affiliated with any of those.
You're an asher.
An asher.
They like it dry, eh?
They like it dry, don't they?
Eh.
Just add water and you're back to...
All the basic ingredients, just make them up in your own mind the way you want them.
A moment of silence is a kind of a heart...
A little crack.
When you have a day...
Did you hear?
A day.
It's a moment of silence.
God bless America.
God bless the space program.
And may we continue to shoot monkeys into space in the name of science.
Yes.
It's the best way...
It's a better reason for killing people than some you can come up with.
May we continue to hook small animals up to car batteries to see what happens.
That's a taxpayer's expense.
Works for me.
After all, the shuttle program was funded by CIA drug money.
I thought you were going to say CIA druggies.
You know how good they are at fooling things.
It's all funded by the CIA drug money.
And Labrador's smuggling ring.
Why do you think they called the first shuttle Columbia?
Can I ask you a question?
Can I ask you a secret question?
Are you a bonesman?
They don't want you touching the wreckage.
They're afraid you'll find the CIA stash that was hidden in the cargo bag.
Bales of cocaine falling all over Midwest.
The aliens.
Well, I think Chaz had it right on the nostril.
No, it was actually Stang who had the wrong nostril, right?
You claim...
They discovered the dangerous satellite they were putting out in the nick of time
and were about to land and explain what had happened.
And they were silenced by them.
Good night.
That's right.
Till next week, keep your hat on tight.
You're back to the wind.
You're sacking the saddle.
See y'all.
Give your sack to Princess Wayne.
Become an astronaut.
Achieve your dreams in the sky.
Look to the blue as your nostrils inflame.
You will realize...
Now the party's over.
You're listening to the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
Sponsored by the Church of the Subgenius.
For more information about the Church of the Subgenius,
write to Bob at...
Post Office Box 807 Glen Rose, Texas 76043
or visit the Subgenius website at...
Subgenius.com
Thank you for listening.
And praise Bob.
Good.
Ha ha ha.
Ha ha.
No, no, no.
Good night.
Come in.
Goodbye, dear Pietro.
Oh.
Goodbye.
Why?