You know, I'm so thankful tonight that I don't have a lot of money, I don't have a lot of friends, but I have a whole lot of diagrams of how to position Bob or Steve.
Somebody's got a conspiracy going on and you will say, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
We don't have a lot of money, we don't have a lot of people, and we got a lot of power of the wicked Bob and the spiritual darkness.
We asked Bob to come and to reveal the conspiracy in the skies.
PR News in Washington. I'm being investigated for personal gain.
Donald Trump says, I'm not.
I am not.
But the U.S. economy continues to get stronger.
Trump now says, he's waiting to first hear from PR News.
Trump says Bob could be persuaded.
Corker says some crime has been committed.
The Trump's already allowed PR News to expire.
In the latest numbers.
220 fell, more than 48 and a half thousand.
Trump says,
the Department of Homeland Security is expected to decide if they're going to disband now
Acquisted ideology, anger and misogyny.
Harest has kat کنْ'ف من polls qui d' Awards for Cory Romее's cover ofologue.
Communist plot
Tweet storm meltdown
No collusion, double down
School shootings, Mike Pence
North Korean nonsense
Stable genius in control
Immigrants are criminals
Witch hunt loyalty
Alternate reality
Right wing fantasy
Carlson and Hannity
Fox and Friends and Ingraham
Automatic weapons ban
Sociopathic lie up
Now the page is turning
And the world is burning
Sociopathic lie up
Now we gotta fight it
And it's time to write it
Michael Cohen prison time
Putin is a friend of mine
Stormy Daniels on her back
Avenatti payback
Manafort paid the price
Bannon wasn't very nice
Washington's a TV show
Go impeach, cat fight
Legislative oversight
Tea party, body bag
Syria, what a drag
Death threats, bodyguards
Living off a credit card
Got a job, new start
Greet her at a Walmart
Sociopathic lie up
Now the page is turning
And the world is burning
Sociopathic lie up
Now we gotta fight it
And it's time to write it
Democrats off track
Too many candidates
Biden and the Ukraine
Gerry Bender swing state
Climate change deep fake
Evil evangelicals calling for a civil war
Deficit shortfalls
Privilege phone calls
Whistleblower WikiLeaks
Snowden had to take a peek
Make it up as you go
Rudy's on a talk show
Nothing but disorder
Bangers at the board
The president's a fool
Sociopathic lie up
Now the page is turning
And the world is burning
Sociopathic lie up
Now we gotta fight it
And it's time to write it
Fake news, pizza gate
Email, deep state
2020 gets sent
Shake up in the cabinet
Roe, Wade, Kavanaugh
Pentagon, martial law
Me Too, Muslim ban
Big mouth, orange tans
Black Lives, dead zones
Be best, kill the drones
Conscientious ignorance
Fabricated innocence
Constitution blown away
What else do I have to say?
Sociopathic lie up
Now the page is turning
And the world is burning
Sociopathic lie up
Now we gotta fight it
And it's time to write it
Anti-vaxxers, trade war
Hearings in the capital
Tax cuts, 1%
Rent, pipelines, Palestine
Razor wire, tell a lie
Jared's got a peace plan
What about Afghanistan?
Killer cops, hate crimes
Adolescent suicide
Opioids, homeless vets
Poverty, hopelessness
Rule of law, water crock
Now we are a laughing stock
Allies headed for the door
I can't take it anymore
Sociopathic lie up
Now the page is turning
And the world is burning
Sociopathic lie up
But when he is gone
Will it still burn on and on
And on and on
Sociopathic lie up
So you now think that no one knows
You can talk today
So you can take a few at night
I don't care, right
It's notом
It's a social pandemic
Bl LOUD
Like and Sub s Policeman
actively
I wish you
Maybe you think God just happens to be
Maybe you think the big bang just happened to happen
Whatever you think, keep it to yourself
And don't take the word of anyone else
Shut up, shut up about it
Everybody talks about shit
No one's ever seen with their own eyes
Maybe you have questions about your soul
Maybe you just want to feel like a part of the whole
Maybe you have some answers, well I have some too
But mine are just for me, and yours are for you
Shut up, shut up already
No one needs to hear your hateful voice
No one needs to hear your heavy theories
Someone else drilled into your head
Shut up, shut up about it
Everybody talks about shit
No one's ever seen with their own eyes
Nobody's ever seen with their own eyes
You've got a gut feeling, and you know you're right
No one disagrees, and you're ready to fight
If it made perfect sense, you wouldn't need to shout
Why you so defensive, if you have no doubt?
Shut up, shut up, stop talking
How can you still find it shocking?
These days giant claims require giant proof
Shut up, shut up, shut up already
No one needs to hear your heavy theories
Someone else drilled into your head
Shut up, shut up about it
Everybody talks about shit
No one's ever seen with their own eyes
Shut up, shut up about it
Nobody's ever seen with their own eyes
Listen how I can fight
With their own eyes
Man, be careful with the blues
You know someday you'll make it smart
Be careful with the blues
Man, I'll let you remember
How foolish I used to be
The way I used to love you, baby
How bad you tried
I used to cry about you, baby
Tryin' to walk the streets late at night
I used to cry about you
Walk the streets late at night
If you love me just a little bit, baby
Wind the world
Don't you treat me right
Ah yeah
Eh yeah
Big Sister
Ah yeah
Hey baby
If you were always so unkind
You'd color my多!"
Big Sister
Ah yeah
Sweet
guitar solo
That's the fun of the thing
Oh, I believe
Mr. Musician
guitar solo
I want you to tell my baby
To forgive me for my sins
This guy doesn't.
And that's as simple as it needs to be.
So thanks for your question.
And yes, in the next Dark Fist,
they're going to continue the adventure stories that I wrote.
I would talk to you more, but I've got some interviews to do.
So I'm just going to give you a little preview treat.
The next issue has a continuation with the subtitle,
The One Bar Jail.
The slot rods did that.
Reverend Angry Larry, the guitar player,
the instrument called Herman's Headers from Surf and Glue, the album.
Detroit hot rod monster surf punk at its absolute best.
Reverend Angry Larry runs a store in,
Mount Clemens called Weirdsville Records.
And my old LPs are for sale there.
Shut up, buddy.
But now I'd like to share a personal phone message
I got from my old, old, old friend,
Reverend Bleepo Abernathy,
whose voice is the only one besides Buddy's
that you always hear on every,
every episode of this show.
Testing, testing.
Is this on?
Reverend Stang, this is the Reverend Bleepo Abernathy.
Some of you out there may be saying,
now Bleepo doesn't sound like that.
And it's true.
I'm not, I'm not talking in my real voice.
This voice is a synthesis of several subgenius voices,
including my own,
but also, uh,
containing elements of, of the Reverend Ivan Stang,
uh, the late Chaz Smith,
lonesome cowboy Dave.
Um, that's all I can think of at the moment,
but there's others that are peppered in there.
As you may be able to hear from the sort of faux Texas,
Ohio twang that is contained within my speech.
Uh, you might call it an impediment because normally you'd hear me talk,
like the subgenius hour of slack but I'm not gonna talk like that now cuz see
it's real late at night and I've been thinking I've been thinking about need
we all need see staying in yeah now somebody else's be I think a little John
Houston's creeping into my voice I just want to mention that at this moment here
because I am a voice over artist actually I think of myself more as a
voice over man artist but that's that's beside the point that's because of my
subgenius training that enables me to be a voice over man but back to need I'm
rambling you'll have to excuse me because I drive a rambler
rambler sedan sort of low-key but anyway what I need now is gas and then I
need a new toaster oven I need a lot of dry cleaning there's a whole lot of dry
cleaning you got to do they don't tell you this when you move to Hollywood but
if you move to Hollywood you have got to do dry cleaning like nobody's business
so you find the dry cleaner that has the most cute funny animals and it's
logo and then you you make sure they have lots of coupons and that's a trick
so what I'm saying here is everybody's got a need but Bob will know he won't
stood he doesn't really steer you but look the point is I forgot what the
point was but but Bob Bob has inspired me as have all the great subgenius
ministers and the ones with radio shows the ones without them all of them can be
said to be masters of I forget what why this cat is bothering me now she the cat
is poking its little feet through the back of my chair and tickling my backside
now that's just wrong
cat it don't let your cat do that even if you enjoy it I don't enjoy it that
much except when this one cat does it but you know it's not it's not that sort
of relationship don't get the wrong idea that's what's going on now too many
people walking around with wrong ideas my point is not now I sort of sense the
actor who played the character in the movie is a character who is really good but it's not a good character
that Mel Blanc later based foghorn leghorn on I forget what that actor's name was but he was he was actually a senator claghorn was the character's name on the radio show and I realize he's sort of sneaking in here so the older elements sneak in to the voice the older influences and mine was of course Warner Brothers cartoons yeah am I rambling well it's about time to wrap up the show I'll see you next time on the show
I'll see you next time on the show
now
you're going to die...
fish
good totems for you
I don't know.
Jets.
Somebody has an oogly.
I recognize many of those giggles and crepitation sounds used in that crazy mix of Dr. Musique,
which is by something called Rad Lab,
or someone who is apparently,
an admirer,
and now,
a contributor,
and one of the gang.
Thanks, Rad Lab.
And also,
now,
I mean,
and now,
15 minutes from last X Day Drill,
first day,
fourth show,
with Dr. Hal and Philo Drummond,
after I got tired and asked the sole remaining audience member to replace me on mic one.
That was the subgenius,
known as X.
But he did a really good job.
But the recording that I got after I left was horrible,
extremely bassy,
especially on Dr. Hal and X.
And I've filtered this very heavily to make it perfectly audible,
albeit not at all resonant.
The music in the background is by CyberChump,
and,
I'm sorry,
I keep promising to leave.
Hey,
somebody else come up here and grab this mic.
Hey you, wake up!
Yeah, yeah, go, just do it.
I don't care.
You can even use these headphones.
Uh, what, oh, but, oops.
Oh, I forgot the headphones are, uh,
these are subgenius headphones.
You just have to hold it there.
Once it's clamped on, it's fine.
I don't think I have any ear infections today.
Did you get a ride down here, Father?
I just have to stand up, walk around for a minute.
You better be funny, or we'll just, we got this big hook.
That shouldn't be left.
Where is the big hook?
It must be that close.
It must be this high to ride this, uh, ride.
And it must be this close to be audible.
You can barely hear Hal hunkering over it.
Remember you talk to Michael Pepe and you tell him,
hey man, you're spitting in my face.
It's just like saying, hey, would you spit in my face?
God himself had buried but one.
He turns the faucet on full blast.
...content to make use of this way,
collectible from Scripture expressions.
So the spewing saliva, Michael Pepe spray,
the Pepe spray is all over you.
...about recovering the body of Moses.
Not that I didn't have any other mistakes.
Have we driven him away yet?
But the practice of burning was also of great antiquity
and of no slender extent.
...district of Caledonia.
Are they gone yet?
...to derive the same from Hercules.
Manlius the consul burned the body of his, uh, son.
And the ashes were kept in an urn on the Capitoline Hill.
And then...
...suddenly...
...there was silence.
The silence after cremation.
Mm-hmm.
The ashes to ashes, dust to dust.
If my blues don't get you, then my jazzin' must.
So, Philo, you've been walking up and down inside the world,
uh, and in it, and seen many...
I walked all the way up, completely back up there,
and then all the way back...
...up to that lone...
...lorn...
...except for the time when Princess Wee took me up there...
...on the ridge.
...and I didn't really walk up there, but I just said I did.
Well, you had a help.
Your mic is much louder than mine.
You had a, uh, guide...
Well, I've always had the ability to project my voice.
...from a guiding spirit.
...extra loud, hooked up to your doohickey.
Uh, my voice control is going through your doohickey.
...my doohickey.
You've got my mic turned up hot, hot.
No, I have your mic half way down.
See...
...that's because I'm just so awesome, though.
My voice has...
Oh, see, we have a...
...I turned my voice on to awesome.
...stereo presentation, full fidelity, uh, rich, uh...
I've got my awesome switch turned on.
...switch...
...switched.
You know, it's true that you're one of the few people I can always understand with my deafness.
Really?
Yeah.
Well, there you go.
That's because of years of sales training.
The authoritative, uh, southern white man, Exile.
I love drama.
Years of training.
...determined.
Salesman supreme.
To get my voice to carry across a crowd of...
...offers.
...unruly customers.
...this master class.
The swing line stapler of sales.
You can buy this.
...have to beat those customers into submission from time to time.
Or you can buy this.
...back slapping hail fellow...
They don't know what they want to buy until you let them...until you tell them what they want.
Always be closing.
Customers are constantly wanting things, but they don't know what they are until they require salesmen to...
Don't give them time to make up their mind.
...imbue them with the very best of their abilities.
...the values and benefits of getting...
Push for that sale.
...product or service.
Push, push, push for that big sale.
Now everything's too loud.
Okay, uh, they say it's all too much of a crowd, too much, too, much too lush and loud.
What's wrong, Reverend Stang?
It's distorting.
Everything's a little loud?
Is it hurting your little pity ears?
Now, now, I know where.
Perhaps not to everybody's taste.
No, wait.
You wouldn't know.
If I would wear headphones, I wouldn't know.
Well, I'm just a...
Excuse me.
I'm gonna talk a lot more gentle now.
There you go.
See?
You have tamed his fiery spirit.
I hear the voices.
Even when I'm talking gentle, I'm loud.
Yes, he's a loud gentleman.
It's like hurting the cats.
I'm a loud motherfucker.
You're a loud many things on this program.
But I'm not a dirty motherfucker.
I'm a clean motherfucker.
Of course.
Shy.
We hew to a certain standard.
I'm a clean motherfucker.
You're a clean motherfucker.
I realize one day that almost all the women I ever had sex with were mothers.
What?
Afterwards, you mean?
At some point in time in their lives.
Well, coincidence or conspiracy.
Might have been afterwards.
You motherfucker.
That's what I mean.
I'd say it proudly.
You see, he populated the Earth and the land of Gihon, where there is bdellium and the
onyx stone.
There's a...
We had an audience and we scared them away and now they're driving off.
At a high rate of speed.
They paid their fee.
They're highly indignant at the results of this.
They're mad.
They're really mad.
They're in a silver car.
Shifting into iambic gear.
They wasted their silver.
They cast their seed money on the car.
The show is riveting them.
Away riveting them away.
They bought it from somebody else.
It's riveting them against a steel girder that's a long ways away from here.
They have to get there fast now.
Four stars riveting.
I was riveted to my seat.
There they are.
There they go.
Our former audience is now either on stage.
Departing silver car sets the standard for all cars.
Our former audience is either on stage or rejecting us.
They're ears.
The only guy that was actually sitting there listening is now.
You had to hijack the audience.
You were so tired.
You were just so worn out from yakking for hours on end.
Tired.
That you had to hijack the audience.
And now.
So you could have slack.
Yes.
So we could trade everything.
Your birthright for a mess of potty.
I need to hijack somebody.
Who do you think you go from?
And then you go.
Well, I'm going to go.
I could just put on a tape of me talking about hijacking somebody.
I think I'm no longer needed here.
Oh.
Oh, I'm going to find it.
So awesome.
What are you going to find?
Your destiny.
Find and fulfill your destiny.
I got the perfect filler.
There's no need for filler anymore.
All filler, no killer.
The filler has been filled.
It's stretched.
What is your name again?
Bob Hope Phyllis Diller, golf classic.
Which reverend are you?
X.
He's Reverend X, or just X for short.
X the unknown.
Yeah, we still have a Rev X.
He's like another Rev X.
Our book, Revelation X.
So, Philo, you were going to spin a platter you were seeing.
It's going to take me a minute to find it.
But when I do, I'll wind it up for a bit.
Check that out.
It's real funny.
It's approximately 45 revolutions per microsecond,
which causes 60th or 70th birthday.
Fabric of time itself.
And that's what you got.
And it's funny.
And you can use Febreze on this fabric,
and it will smell karma clean.
Febreze.
When you add the fabric softener,
does it soften the time-space fabric?
It does.
What about the elasticity of the continuum?
Oh, no.
The elasticity is very rigid.
Hmm.
That's it.
For her, it's a pleasure.
Yeah, it's got to remain.
It's got to remain stretchable.
Got to remain unanimous.
And April fresh.
That's right.
Everyone can do this.
Ever being born.
Ever being greeted.
Come in.
Coming into being with the smell of that special scent
they put in every package of fabric softener.
And the day after tomorrow is Independence Day 1998.
And the day after that will be independent from them.
The eternal recurrence of X-Day.
All old and all dared before.
All having happened before will happen again.
But there is no eternal recurrence because things are bigger on the inside than they are on the outside.
Space-time is everywhere locally.
I'm looking.
Well, um, I guess that wraps that up in a...
Anthropomorphic.
Yes, exactly.
It's a lovable personality seen on your screen.
Beckoning you down further to further adventures.
Down in the medicine fish hole.
Going down.
The tardigrade.
Part six.
We left our intrepid heroes of Stace...
Yes, Dr. Drummond is still connecting to his...
Planet X.
...intablature, which is going to add the necessary dimension to this presentation.
X being mysterious.
It will happen.
It causes things to equal.
I tell you.
X equals...
But nobody knows what X equals.
They try to look for a solution, but they're part of the solvent.
That's right.
They're liquid.
Flowing.
And it may take thousands of years.
But they all fall down.
And you push and push and push.
Yes.
Huge mountains that were ground down to tiny pebbles.
To tiny stones.
But each stone having the kinetic form, purpose, and potential of the mountain, supposedly.
Still, there you go.
The high become low.
And the mighty and great becoming insignificant.
The pebbles float.
But the avalanche is already beginning.
Does anybody know the Wi-Fi password around here?
Oh, it is?
Okay.
No Wi-Fi for you.
Bummer.
Yeah, it's too bad.
Because I know you were planning to hook into an award-winning Bobcast.
Damn it.
Which would have seized us out.
We were just sitting underneath the deepest depths of the Bering Sea.
Lost our bearings.
And now friction brings us to a fault.
And that's right.
It's the Marianas fault.
And then there was the Gingers fault.
But they always blame their headheads for these things.
It just doesn't make sense.
That's right.
It's free here now.
The present.
The opening.
The last.
One of my best ideas.
I can't do stuff with them.
The final.
The ultimate.
The final outrage.
Outrage.
They were outraged.
They didn't know why they were outraged.
But they were pretty damn upset.
They were indignant.
Yeah, they were indignant.
They didn't have no money.
So they just wanted some help.
They wanted some food.
They wanted some place to live.
A place to breathe.
Just a place to urinate.
All they needed was 60 million dollars.
some seal skin to protect them from the cold,
to know how stocks would go on Wall Street,
and to be living in a mansion built of gold.
And then, I don't know, they was going to get greedy.
I said, honey, you know, two mansions is all we need,
one for you, one for me.
And she said, well, what about it?
Yeah, how many mansions do you need to skate behind?
And that was Greedy, the eighth dwarf, intractable,
could not be convinced.
And then along came Sleazy and Sneaky.
Yeah, a fine bunch.
The runts of the litter, certainly.
And now, what's...
Yeah, the other seven of the original 14 dwarves,
because you had...
You did.
You had...
You had Sleazy and Sneaky,
Sharty.
They didn't all live together.
Yeah, that one.
Yeah, Shorty.
Yeah.
Shorty, the dwarf.
Don't forget.
He was mad, because even he was short to the other dwarves.
Well, someone had to be, I mean,
given the slight variation of height among them all.
Yeah, the lesser known dwarves didn't get any traction.
Nobody wanted to pick up their options.
Shorty was kind of an infra dwarf, a dwarf unto dwarfs,
and that was one of the reasons that he had the personality difficulties
that he later exhibited.
There was High Pockets.
He was the tallest, world's tallest dwarf.
Mm-hmm.
He was like six feet tall.
He used to hunch over, but didn't fool his brethren,
who considered themselves genuine dwarfs.
Who you calling little people?
We're doing popular music ordained by world's tallest dwarves.
The world's midget.
Yes, that was, well, probably Billy Barty, but...
World's smartest retard.
That would be Bob.
Versus the world's dumbest genius.
And who would win?
Press button one.
Press button two.
Then press button three to deactivate and open the trap
and remove the prey.
To introduce the trap to the general public,
we are giving you this model absolutely free.
You will
They
I am on a set of things
He's coming from the conservatory, so I stop by.
What are you playing?
Just a simple melody of my own.
So weird.
Hey, you don't stop playing.
Don't stop playing.
Have a drink.
Well, it's awfully early in the morning.
We'll look upon it as an extension of last night.
Your eyes, what's happening?
All right.
They're very bloodshot.
Can't you see?
Hey, lad.
I know I'm blind.
I can't harbour this anymore.
Don't stop playing.
I'm still strong.
Well, this episode certainly got weirder and weirder, didn't it?
That was a Dr. Banter.
anti-music collaboration between Dr. Philodrummond and the new guy, Reverend Richard Negative,
from his subgenius CD, Welcome to Dobbs.Town.
Personally, I don't really like any anti-music that I'm not performing at the moment.
And as you can tell by Buddy's howling in the background, he doesn't like it either.
But, you know, it's a subgenius tradition, and I know a lot of you folks are on drugs and will listen to anything.
And what you're listening to now is the Hour of Slack from the Church of the Subgenius,
specifically the Subgenius Foundation, located at P.O. Box 807, Glen Rose, Texas, 76043.
Subgenius.com.
Oh, Price Bob.
And thank you, Buddy.
From PR News in Washington, I'm barred from kneeling during the national anthem while on the field.
Then, last night, thousands of documents in central Iowa yesterday reported to be without power today,
and China and Russia blocked it.
But Trump says he's ready to impose tariffs on all PR reports.
The Trump is urging all members of the United Nations,
to fully support the sanctions imposed on PR.
I don't like it, and I haven't liked it for many years.
The Trump Is Here
you