Let's talk about headache, fatal headache.
Common side effects include heart failure,
persistent fever, bruising, bleeding,
lymphoma, nervous system, and blood disorders.
Envision your possibilities.
From PR News in Washington,
I'm accused of killing Congolese militia peacekeepers
from Bangladesh who murdered the French serial murderer
nearly two months ago near the border with Uganda
to determine if there is any possible PR news in Washington.
Ladies and gentlemen, please leave your sub-suggested.
We are having operating difficulties,
which has necessitated a delay in the beginning of our Sunday movie.
This is basic civil defense information
from the Department of Defense,
Office of Civil Defense, Washington,
especially in time of emergency.
Oh, yeah, oh, yeah, oh, yeah, oh, yeah, oh, yeah, oh, yeah, oh, yeah, oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah, oh, yeah, oh, yeah, oh, yeah, oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah, oh, yeah, oh, yeah, oh, yeah.
And follow instructions by...
Ivan Stang.
You may receive warning of an attack by outdoor warning systems or by...
What, what, uh, what, uh...
Radio or television or even by word of mouth.
Unless local officials have instructed you otherwise,
go immediately to a...
Moab.
My friend, you're in the desert.
Then tune your radio to any local station that is broadcasting...
The Soul Genius Powerhouse.
Watch it!
And listen for official information.
Follow whatever instructions are given.
Depend on radio, as the government will be broadcasting...
You don't, yeah, you don't come back now.
I know you've been to some of you...
Let me repeat, let me repeat.
In time of emergency, for official government information
and civil defense instructions,
tune your radio to any local station that is broadcasting...
The Soul Genius Powerhouse.
Uh, yes, dear friend.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yes.
Ah, friends.
Ah, yes, dear friends.
Ah, yes.
Ah, yes, my friends.
Dear friends of the, uh...
Everybody doesn't like something.
But nobody doesn't like...
Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
Yes, it's so beautiful.
That official information was brought to you by
Reverend Chain Smirker in Australia.
But this forthcoming official information,
which may contradict other official information,
is from Mr. Sister.
Technology System Profit.
The Soul Genius Powerhouse.
For the next hour, sit quietly,
and we will control all that you see and hear.
Now speaking for the management.
We are conscious of our responsibility and obligation
to provide programs which will be enjoyable,
entertaining, and tasteful.
With full awareness of this controversial nature of this,
particularly because of its classification,
we subjected it to careful editing.
To eliminate elements which we might consider in questionable taste,
it was reviewed by an experienced program editor.
It is well within the restrictions of the code to which we subscribe,
which is even more restrictive and stringent in many areas
than the industry code.
We are sensitive to the concerns which prompted your letter
and assure you that this network will continue to adhere
to the high standards we have set.
We maintain the truth throughout the years.
Thank you.
You are about to participate in a great adventure.
You are about to experience the awe and mystery
which reaches from the inner mind to
the church of the subgenius.
The Church of the Subgenius.
That official information was from Reverend Self Slayer.
And this is Hour of Slack number 985.
For this show, besides the latest Lemurian leavings,
we have resurrected the ancient, crumbling,
subgenius media barrage tape number three
called Sex, Sickness, and Slack
from the year of 1981.
A newly remastered for CD.
And friends, going through this material from 25 years ago,
when Philo and yours truly were babies
and you weren't even born,
my God, it has caused to erupt forth
some long buried memories.
Memory is a beautiful thing if we control what we remember.
Now, our mind has a tendency to remember,
remember the bad and forget the good.
But all we can remember the time,
bring to your remembrance
things that brought joy to your soul.
Wow, look at her tits.
They are enormous.
How can they...
Hello? Hello?
How can they be showing so much tit
without showing any nipple at all?
Bob?
Coming in just a few moments,
we will be speaking with Reverend Ivan Stang
and the Dr. Philo Drummond
with the Church of the Subgenius.
Just to give you a hint at what this is all about,
I'm going to give you a little bit of a tease
about the church.
We're living in terrible,
perilous, chaotic
times. How has your life
changed since dogs came into your life?
The exodus are a reality
and my life is geared
towards their arrival.
I redefined my own space
and was able to center
my being. When I first heard
Bob on the radio, he said
that he could
heal and told me to put my hand on
the radio so that the Bob
energy could come out through the airwaves.
The only cult they want to
talk about is the subgenius foundation,
the church of the subgenius,
and the only reason they talk about it
is for the money.
I'm afraid of God. Oh, you are?
Yeah. Well, there's a lot
of people out there just like you.
I tell you what, if you would,
put your hands on the radio right now.
Put your hands, put your hands
on the radio.
Hello. Because we launched rockets
Now you can take your eye
and turn it up.
You'd think everyone would like that.
Cash free dollars. Cash back.
With a specially shaped treat that cleans dogs.
Families
love harassment now.
This Tuesday, he calmed the dead.
Love is setting rules
to help them keep marijuana.
And if you plan to get
saved, you'd better
do it now. There will be a
day not in the poop.
This is a future in which
Antichrist will be revealed
and the mark of the beast
will be introduced.
Humanity,
why do you bug us?
Oh, massive bring down.
The world is a bongo drum
and we are merely the
oobly-oobly-oobly-oobly-oobly.
Oh, I mean really different.
Edgar's much more advanced.
Aren't you?
Aren't you, you little lion?
Darn you.
Mangalore, he was a
bongo-loy.
He's happier than you and me.
Mangalore, he was a
bongo-loy.
And he determined
what he could say.
From PR News in Washington,
I'm Alan Greenspan.
Greenspan said, said, he said.
Greenspan said, he said.
Greenspan called for more PR News in Washington, he said.
Federal Reserve Chairman Alan Greenspan says
he told a Senate panel Greenspan is subdued.
Greenspan says Greenspan continues
to expand at a reasonably good pace.
But he did not say by how much.
Investigators want to know more
about Greenspan in Washington.
From reading some of your literature,
which you so helpfully brought up
a wheelbarrow full of this evening in the studio,
by the church, by your belief,
Slack is something that
when you join the church
you can do anything you want
because
it's within your Slack.
Well, when you...
And if anybody inhibits you,
they are hampering your religion
and violating the constitution,
your constitutional rights.
That's exactly right.
That's right, we're hoping
somebody will take this
to court sooner or later for us.
Mockery of everything that's decent and wholesome.
I challenge you to point out national talk shows
that do not belittle sexual fidelity, purity,
that they do not belittle the marriage union
and the family lifestyle,
that they don't literally flaunt illicit lifestyles.
I mean, I challenge you to show me a talk show
that doesn't make light of God.
The Subgenius Foundation,
the Reverend Ivan Spang and Dr. Philo Drummond,
and they are, as we mentioned before,
the dual heads of the Subgenius Foundation.
If you don't know about the school books depositories,
watch out for a police.
Because I'm number 6742 to witness it,
and they're coming after me.
So call me.
Hello there, hello to you.
We're picking up all your transmission.
That's the leader and the idea I want.
Whenever a party leader must...
The subgenius culture and subgenius living.
Gentlemen, I want to get a title.
The subgenius title.
It doesn't make fun of Godly laws.
Agreed.
They don't laugh.
They don't laugh at us.
They make a mockery of us.
Now we don't have to watch it.
We can turn it off.
Who will pay to clean up the contaminated land?
Call us and talk about what you'd wish.
Go ahead.
I'm going to point out that a lot of people worry about the one world government
that the conspiracy is trying to get across on us.
And we suspect that the only thing that can fight a one world government
is going to be a one world religion.
And of course, that's what the subgenius,
the church of the subgenius is here for.
When he says,
you shall have tribulation ten days,
he means you're going to have a maximum of trouble.
And that's just the way things are.
The church is not at home in the world.
Oh.
I know I'm drunk now.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I forgot my favorite man sitting over there.
His name is...
Mr. Dovolina, Mr. Bob Dovolina.
Mr. Mr. Dovolina, Mr. Bob Dovolina.
Mr. Bob Dovolina.
Mr. Dovolina, Mr. Bob Dovolina.
Mr. Bob Dovolina, won't you quit?
You really made me sick with your fraudulent behavior.
You're going to make me flippin' then the army couldn't save you.
Why don't you behave, you little rug rat?
Take a little tip from the tabloid.
Because I know I'm not paranoid.
When I say I saw you trying to mock me,
now you and your crew are on a mission trying to hawk me.
But it isn't happening, you fraudulent foes.
You used to front big time, now I suppose.
That everything's cool since the style of apparel you adopted.
You used to make fun of, but now you want to rock it.
So you gotta kick it with the homies.
But D.E.L. is already hip to your cronies.
Me and C.M.P. just thought about this and never have we seen her.
Brother, who would have her like, Mr. Mr. Mr. Dovolina?
Mr. Dovolina, Mr. Bob Dovolina.
Mr. Mr. Dovolina, Mr. Bob Dovolina.
Oh, who have you got?
You gotta get that cop here!
slash
Well, how's your sakes?
Who wrote this?
I'm just gonna write it myself, just to add a little bit of an edgy feeling.
Shout-outs to you, Bob Dovolina!
Who wrote it?
This Mobile Backup by the Joils Blue and The Pl 빠有點
Ooh, ooh, Mr. Dabalina
You thought you could manipulate, you thought you could fool me
Cheech Wizard put me on a stuffer, then he schooled me
Prince could be fraudulent, just you wait and see
First he was my money grip, then he stole my honey dip
Mr. Dabalina is a serpent, don't you agree?
The little two-timer resembles Aunt Jemima
With jeans and a dirty white hoodie
Seems like he wouldn't be a snake, or would he?
Disguises come in all sizes and shapes
Notice the facade of the snakes
They all catch the baits, even though last year there was GQ
Took a lot of time before the D.E.L. could see through the mask
All I had to do was ask the Emperor and Kwame
And my maris thought if they were bombing
Fraudulent foe with the strength of Hercules
The way you on my dick must really hurt your knees
You need to take feet and quit being such a goopy
Ever since I did a little show in Guadalupe
I never saw a goopy like you
But what is funny is you wanted to be down with my crew
The D.E.L. is not down with any clowns or justice
So I would suggest that you try to impress some professor Dabalina
Because you don't impress me, Dabalina
The style of justice is not the key, Dabalina
It's all in the mind and the heart
So you should start by remembering
You gotta pay a fee, Dabalina
Mr. Dabalina, Mr. Bob Dabalina
Glory, how stupid
Mr. Bob Dabalina
Praise Jesus, praise God
I'm porque de que tú me crees
He's the one and only Kose otaku
Mr. Double Leader.
This is PR News.
A Massachusetts judge is asking U.N. Secretary General Kofi Annan to strip in the courtroom.
Stripping in the monster head.
The Senate has approved raping a child on a vote of 98 to nothing.
The victim smiled and hugged handcuffs in shackles.
Some Democrats raised questions about PR's reports.
The State Department has denounced civil liberties and did nothing to stop PR News.
I support gay rights.
I think that those nasty, stupid fags are in a shower stall.
I would say that we have had a lot of those.
Young and nasty and stupid.
This is a crooked and perverse nation.
We have millions and multiplied millions of crooked politicians.
God put a death penalty upon adultery.
When we see millions and multiplied millions of people spending hours and hours before the television.
Learn how to crack safes, rob banks, kill policemen and get divorces and break up homes.
All these soap operas hour after hour warps people's minds.
Pull ahead. All decks condition red.
Wednesday is Ladies Night.
Underscored ladies admitted free.
Their drinks 25 cents and 50 cents.
A shy little girl leaving all that she knew behind her.
What this gonna do to kill me, man?
Hour after hour warps people's minds.
That shows that they're crooked.
That shows they're perverse.
That shows that they're stupid.
That shows they got warped minds.
That's what people's minds runs on.
And that the morals are breaking down.
And that's what it did in the Roman Empire.
Right before the Roman Empire fell, their morals broken down.
Straps on your shoulder.
Straps on your back and on your hand.
So it's pissing you aside.
Letting water flow into the land.
Hey, have a little fun this week.
Enjoy free refreshments, free gifts.
It's a pretty strong church we find and uh...
We need to know little brother, huh?
Something else about it.
In an effort to get people to stop smoking marijuana in this country,
the government is thinking about putting a sales tax on rolling paper.
Yeah, yes, you're right, yeah.
So...
And for school, yet we fall short when it comes to taking care of our own.
I'm looking for one to bear you.
But nothing comes my way.
Organization formed to oppose moral majority.
How is this hard?
Of the Nicolaitans, which I also hate.
And to accept homosexuals as teachers in our Christian school.
Our church happens to believe that homosexuality is a sin.
And boldly speak the pense йaz TWO
Y quarter out of that is now polymorphism.
The stup辛苦 he would make everywhere.
The stup Paul because he's gone.
go everywhere other than Stoneway.
In the other corner,
Seth Sue from Winnipeg.
This bitch had a dick
longer than a table leg.
And stop trying to force
immorality into the law,
which makes people
accept immorality.
That's when I was in college,
because I simply wasn't
the praiser of God,
a chosen person, a Jew.
Our television programs
laugh at homosexuality.
Hey, they laugh at immorality.
They laugh at ungodliness.
They make a mockery
of the holy word of God.
And God says,
when you change my truth
into a lie,
I'll give you up
to vile affections.
That was another hole
I didn't recognize.
My dick was so long,
the bitch needed circumcised.
You talk about homosexuals
come out of the closet.
Did you ever dream
the day would come
in American history
when grown men would stand up
and possess to be making
physical love?
They would say,
I'm a gay man.
Don't tell me that I'm a sissy.
I'm a he-man.
But I'm in love with that man
right there,
and I'm married.
Larry the faggot
was fleeting from the ass
because this motherfucker
backed up on a dick
a little too fast.
For those of you
who are passionate bird lovers,
thank you.
I'm sure this song
will have a lot of appeal.
Whenever I've sung it,
it has brought forth
scores of letters
from woodpeckers
all over the country.
I stuck my finger
in a woodpecker's hole
and the woodpecker said,
God bless my soul.
What a very odd thing to do.
Though I know you're merrier
than old.
Old King Cole,
you should exercise
a little self-control
and to stick your finger
in a woodpecker's hole
is a very odd thing to do.
Do-do-do-do.
What a very odd thing to do.
I've been reading about
where a lot of churches,
even in Benecost,
have accepted homosexuality.
Ain't that the truth?
That's the truth.
And claiming to have
the Holy Ghost.
Well, that's deception.
Ain't a bigger abomination
in the world
than women wearing men's clothes
and men wearing women's clothes
and people being perverts.
That's the,
two of the greatest sins
in the world
is idolatry,
witchcraft,
homosexuality,
and men and women
wearing the clothes
of the opposite sex.
It's abomination.
And whosoever
do it is abomination.
And there's more people today.
Their minds are perverted.
Their life is perverted.
And they've been given over
to a reprobate mind.
So many people today,
even people that aren't homosexual,
their minds are perverted.
It's filled with filth.
And it's filled with
all the ungodliness
and wickedness
that comes from the pit of hell.
And you see it on television.
You see it in the movie houses.
And you see it on the,
in the,
on the market stand.
Hey, and how about pornography?
Jax, all you have to do
is look around you.
Female body parts
are available just about anywhere.
Or pick up some picture books
with a free orifice included.
Miracles of Engineering,
yours for the plucking.
If you don't mind
the smell of vinyl,
you're such a shit.
From Media Barrage 3.
And before that, friends,
The Woodpecker's Hole,
that marvelous song
was by Patti Roberts.
From the album,
Songs for Gay Dogs.
Yes, that's the title of it.
That was submitted to
all binary slack
by Reverend Polar Bear.
And now,
some recordings
from last year's
Winter Star Symposium.
Not last month's,
but last year's.
But, yeah,
we don't add to
the word of Bob,
but we are always trying
to find better ways to say it.
You know,
better, better,
better PR.
Just because a statement
is correct
doesn't mean that it's
a smart thing to say.
That having been said,
I'm going to keep going anyway.
And tell you all, friends,
that, despite what you may have heard,
Bob is coming.
Bob, J.R. Bob Dobbs,
that man represented there
by that graven image,
is coming.
Now, when you've heard
that Jesus is coming
and he never does,
but what they mean by that is
Jesus is on his way here
from somewhere else
and he is about to arrive.
When we say Bob is coming,
we don't mean he's on his way here.
We mean literally.
Bob is coming.
When you have an orgasm
or whatever,
that's Bob.
Bob is coming.
It's that simple.
Okay?
It's not so complicated.
So, you may know Bob
better than I do.
Better than you think.
Now, we've also,
another thing we've said
is that you can be alone
with Bob.
Praise Bob.
That is his greatest gift to us
is that we don't have to have
this asshole preacher guru guy,
you know, breathing down our necks.
The other thing I meant
was just for some of guys, boys,
it's not queer if it's Bob.
I have to remind myself of that a lot.
But yeah, Bob plays in mysterious ways.
Now, um...
Now, mama's on the bottom
and papa's on the top.
Baby's in the crib,
the hall and poet to her pop job.
Hey, Bubba Rebob.
Yes, my baby knows.
Now sea is sea
and land is land.
Can't get my boogie
I can get it by hands up.
Hey, Bubba Rebob.
Yes, my baby knows.
Now I boogie it in the kitchen
and I booke it in the hall.
Bookie it in my hand
then I slung it on the wall.
Stop.
Hey, Bubba Rebob.
Hey, Barbaribob! Yes, my baby knows.
Now a nickel for some butter. Nickel for some lard.
Put it on my boogie till my boogie got hard-chopped.
Hey, Barbaribob! Hey, Barbaribob!
Yes, my baby knows.
There's a little red rooster, she's a big red hen.
Ruffle up your feathers, let's hop, clip it in, chop.
Hey, Barbaribob! Hey, Barbaribob!
Hey, Bobbery Bob, hey, Bobbery Bob, yes, my baby knows.
Out in the crap earth sittin' so bold, gonna get me some of the old, not whole jobs.
Hey, Bobbery Bob, hey, Bobbery Bob, hey, Bobbery Bob, hey, Bobbery Bob, hey, Bobbery Bob, yes, my baby knows.
Out in the crap earth sittin' on the lot, the green flies are buzzin' and I'm gettin' damn hot jobs.
Out in the dni's havin' cold, the world ain't bulletproof, I ain't gonna sleep till nightfall.
Yes, my baby knows.
Now, pensar red, ready for a pluckin', I got a gal who's gonna take your head and play the struggle.
Hey, Bobbery Bob, hey, Bobbery Bob, hey, Bobbery Bob, that's my gal.
Hey, Bobbery Bob, hey, Bobbery Bob, yes, my baby knows.
Now, belly to belly and skin to skin got two little things workin' out and it's just me.
I'm aumphin' in for pennant, and my baby knows
Yes, my baby knows
Now my papa is a skunk, my mama is a slut
My cock's sucking, brother's got my sister knocked up
Shouts, hey, Bobber-y Bob
Yes, my baby knows
Now the cattle's in the pasture and the hog's in the corn
Granny's in the crapper blowing grandpa's horns
Hey, Bobbery Bob.
Yes, my baby knows.
Got a brand new shimmy with a tank full of gas, mouth full of tootie, and a hand full of ass.
Hey, Bobbery Bob.
Yes, my baby knows.
Sit down. Don't sit down, but at least set your dogs to find them.
Never mind the dogs.
I found some tracks. Come on.
There's one thing that'll stop them.
I reconciled.
And that's the lady.
A white lady.
Who can eat more than two eggs?
Bob?
Do you know what you're talking about?
Hey, I wonder if you and her will recast the talk away yesterday.
From now on it'll end in gobbling up their time ago.
Such reputations.
All right.
But now I need to take care of my desk.
Decided to let Bobbery know you're earning when you explain the race to help those kids.
If that's what we need in theio life,
Thank you.
And before that, friends, we heard some lemur.
And now, more Hour of Slack.
Ah!
Turn it off!
I'll tell!
Ha ha ha!
Oh!
What?
Like?
Like when you...
You scream?
Like when you sing to some bitch, man, and...
And they laugh, you know?
And...
And they...
They laugh harder, and...
And...
When we know...
When we fuck, you know, they laugh.
And they kill you.
Man, you can't get enough of that.
They're there.
And you can't...
You can't kick a fucking dog, and they're...
They're behind you, and they're kicking, man.
And...
And they're...
And it's like I'm...
And they're fucking...
They're fucking...
I don't know...
And they're kicking you in the...
Oh, that was Roberto de la Rosa.
Thanks to the great, late David Boone.
From PR News in Washington, I'm designed to extort big settlements from PR News.
The nation's Roman Catholic bishops, fueled by big cars,
Cigarettes, painkillers and alcohol killed 20 people and wounded dozens.
The church paid $158 to PR News.
On the plus side, the church's cock washing is safe.
President Bush would take drugs away from federal judges and put them into the hands
of PR News.
Wholesale prices rose by $310,785.58.
PR News marred the holy news in Washington.
From PR News in Washington, I'm pledging to try to get unmanned surveillance aircraft
to spy on deaf mammals accused of opening fire with an assault-style rifle that can
simplify Israel's transfer of Jericho to PR News.
Yesterday, Federal Reserve Chairman Alan Greenspan talked on this.
Give a person who makes $6.50 an hour another baby and they're going to feed on it.
Greenspan update there by Fernanda Nande-Lemur.
And now...
Doctors for Bob.
And will you come over, bringing those long things I like.
Them long and slender things over by Bob's place.
Oh, some of them are only thirteen years old.
Is that going to fix me to say something about Bob?
That was Bob we were singing about.
I think that was Bob.
If you're talking about your straight Bob, your righteous Bob, your true Bob, you're
Bob that is there and yet, well, I'd still be here and so would you.
This is true.
So, I guess there's nothing but we can do but sing about Bob.
Oh, Bob, you're getting to be a pretty big fella.
Yes, sir.
Maybe this is a good idea, a chance for us to have a little talk.
Why, sure, Dad.
What's cooking?
You mind if I smoke in your room?
Oh, I know, Dad.
Go ahead.
Thanks.
Remember the last time we talked about this old body of ours, Bob?
Yeah.
Yeah, I remember, Dad.
Remember I...
Well, to begin with, you ought to know the medical terms for certain parts of the body.
But when a doctor speaks of the male organ, he calls it a...
A male organ.
Well, son...
Oh, you mean the electric razor.
Oh, no, you rascal.
No, no, Bob.
Well, what I'm talking about now is the fluid.
That's wrong, isn't it?
I mean...
Oh, no, son.
It's not at all wrong.
You see, the body manufactures that fluid all the time.
And when the supply becomes too great, as it does sometimes, nature opens a sort of a safety
valve in your sleep and passes off.
And, you know, when you're in a hospital, you're not supposed to be in a hospital.
Now, one of these nights before very long, you may find that some of it passes off in
your sleep.
My mother would probably have a fit.
She just had the curtains washed.
Oh, here's a match.
Your pipe's gone out again.
Well, thanks.
Gee, our bodies are complicated, aren't they, Dad?
Oh, you bet.
More complicated than the biggest dynamo ever built.
Oh, but, Dad...
Why do fellows get these, uh...
You know what happens when you stuff yourself with cake and Coke, son, so you're ready to
pop.
Sure, I get a stomachache.
You bet.
God made the desire of us so that we'd be sure to get our vitamins each day.
Golly, the way he figured everything out.
He sure did.
But always remember this, son.
Well, son, so closely has God connected our emotions with our bodies that...
Oh, my God.
How's that?
And remember that you can always knock them with a simple one-two punch.
Get it?
I got it, Dad.
Fine.
Now, if you have any questions, come and tell me about them.
Ouch!
A little bit of a confounded back of mine there.
Come on, Dad.
Let's get on with it.
The Bob's Dad there.
Thanks to Reverend Shane Smirker for that particular reference.
And now, friends, Lemurian news.
Oh, by the way, a listener or downloader noted lately that, for the first time, that all Lemur cuts of all kinds are three seconds long or 13 or 23 seconds or 33 seconds or 43 seconds long.
Always in tune with the mathematically perfect 13013, the number of Bob, the main number of Bob.
I had never noticed that about Lemur stuff, and you'd think I would, but, well, we all have our strange obsessions, you know.
From PR News in Washington, I'm plotting to assassinate religious patients till 5 o'clock tomorrow evening.
In stocks 174-1006-1100.
27-28-2030.
It's been a dramatic day for PR's brain-damaged president in February.
Persistent PR News state.
More than 170 people have ended their lives since PR News took effect in Washington.
NotVERTEEN has seen hundreds of calls for help for their children.
Dem.
italic music catches sensitivity.
of the ground. Alien
signals beaming down.
They say, hey pal,
can you hear us now?
Oh wow, listen to the
sound. UFO transmissions.
UFO
transmissions.
I
can hear the sound.
Now the alien leaders
are on a mission and they give
me the details with each
transmission. Some are good
and well, some are mean.
Screaming louder than
Howard Dean. They say, hey
pal, can you hear us now?
Oh wow,
listen to the sound. UFO
transmissions.
UFO transmissions.
UFO
transmissions.
I can
hear the sound.
They say, hey pal,
can you hear us now?
Oh wow, listen to the
sound. UFO
transmissions.
UFO transmissions.
UFO
transmissions.
Can you keep a secret?
UFO transmissions. Can you keep a secret?
I can hear the sound.
Now I keep a record
of each transmission and the
secret meaning which I
keep hidden. I hear a sound.
I write it down.
I hide the pages
underground. They say, hey
pal, can you hear us
now? Oh wow,
listen to the sound.
UFO transmissions.
UFO
transmissions.
I can hear the sound.
Down, down, down.
By distracting the others.
So that in the event of Omega Contingency Plan C,
they'll be too distracted.
Well, anyway, the less said, the better.
Anyway, you should look at ufophil.com.
The hideous noise that came after Lemur's PR news earlier
was from a poo-water towel.
The band that I'm in,
and with Princess We Are Doe.
And now, more news.
From PR news in Washington,
I'm probably preparing to probe Prime Minister's priests
in PR's Palestinian pain prison.
The head of a Senate panel came on a Minnesota Republican
today on Wall Street.
The doubt threatened to retaliate.
Did you read about that woman,
the 80-year-old woman that was about to get raped?
She was on crutches,
and the only thing that stopped her
was the fact that she'd been...
Yeah, that's where I quit.
She had cancer,
and she had cancer,
and she was taking radiation,
and it made her assailant unable to penetrate her.
So they beat her with a crutch.
Are you kidding?
Nice guy, huh?
Oh, God.
This is a crooked and perverse nation.
A guy like that, to me,
they should do nothing less than draw and quarter him.
Well, televise and draw and quarter him.
Worse yet, they should torture him for months
before they can do anything.
They should kill him, you know?
And every week they tune in and show a little footage.
Flayed Alive.
Flayed Alive, Flayed Alive.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
It's coming.
We should look for televised executions by the late 80s.
It has got to stop.
Man, I'll tell you what, it's just,
it seems like the weirdos are,
I mean, the really weirdos,
the dangerous weirdos are outnumbering the,
the harmless weirdos now.
Uh-huh.
It's giving a bad name for all weirdos.
Oh, they teach them that shit in public school now.
When Bob takes over, that'll be no more.
I mean, what they should do to guys like,
you know, that rape women,
they should cut off their dick and balls in both arms
and let them go through society that way.
Because then he could never hit an old lady again.
Yeah, that's right.
They could just.
That's right, they could cut his dick off.
He could still go out sort of raping them.
Yeah, and he could shove them in their crotch up there.
Yeah, you know.
That crotch?
Yeah, right.
I think they'll cut their arms off
and then brand on their forehead,
I used to beat little old ladies.
Then they would be subject to whatever ridicule
society gave them and unable to do a thing about it.
Let every man be the judge, jury, and executioner.
And let each criminal's works be known.
That's right.
That is right.
Branded on their forehead.
I mean, for hard,
for highness, for highness' crime.
Right, I mean, just some gophering,
you know, maybe at the end of your little finger or something.
Chop off the front half of your foot.
Or a certain degree of voltage for a certain period of time.
Or a trip on some mind drug that's guaranteed
to make you see Satan's minions.
Or put them on some amusement park rides for weeks.
Or give them a disease.
Yeah.
A really, really awful rabies.
A real painful disease.
Give them shots for it.
Yeah.
Put them in a closet full of rabid bats.
Those dirty guys haven't even touched the surface
of the things they could do.
I know it, man.
It'd have to be pretty strictly regulated
because you'd get people that became guards like that
and became torturers just because they liked it.
Yeah.
Because they liked to inflict pain rather than
because they liked to.
You'd have to screen the people out and make the,
and have the ones that really don't want it happening.
They really hate inflicting pain to do it.
Yeah.
Of course, that would bump them out.
Right.
Yeah.
Well, you'd just get people who are into the technical thing.
They're just, they were into studying how many neuron
signals with the equipment.
Like researchers, you know?
Yeah.
Like the kind of guys that, there's a research doctor
for a laboratory and he's used to cutting monkeys' heads open
while they're alive and stuff like that.
Yeah.
It's no big deal.
I mean, he cuts their vocal cords so they can't scream.
I think Bob would go along with most of that.
I mean, I'm not for this, this, hey, man, do your own thing.
Why?
Or kill me.
Which maybe quite a lot of you could get a short duration marriage.
Either fuck you or kill me.
That is a.
Why?
That will stop a spiritual penalty for short-
Fuck me or kill me, baby.
I mean, one or the other.
Shut up.
I feel like I gotta shut up.
Eat shit or kill me.
That sounds like a good idea.
They're talking dirty.
Eating my shit and killing yourself.
Always talking dirty.
That was baby Philo, baby Stang, and the late baby Dr. X
in 19-
1980.
Old-timey friends from Media Barrage number three.
And now, baby Mark Hundahl.
Hi.
Have I got something for you.
This is the one and only Mojo bag.
And with this, you don't need no long hair or cool cigarettes
or cool guys' sheds.
Because you could have any woman you want with the Mojo bag.
And you don't need no knife or gun.
Because ain't nobody can hurt you when you got the Mojo bag.
But you too can have the one and only Mojo bag.
Yeah, I'd give it to you for, oh, I guess about $8.
$8.
I accept no substitutes.
But one word of caution.
One word of caution.
Don't you never look inside the Mojo bag.
Because it got the juju.
And that is hot stuff.
Friends, we're coming up on show number 1,000.
That's right.
Hour of Slack number 1,000.
And we would like to have a compilation of your comments.
Yes, listener comments.
And we'd like to have a compilation of your comments about the Hour of Slack.
And heck, make it about the whole Church of the Subgenius if you want.
Because really it's our 25-year anniversary coming up.
25 years since Bob's word was made public.
Actually, on January 1st of 2005, that was really our 25th year anniversary.
But we didn't notice.
So friends, if you have something interesting to say about your favorite or most hated Hour of Slack,
or something it did, or anything interesting about it and you,
you can write it and email it to me.
And Dave or me or Princess We will read it.
Make it a couple of paragraphs.
Make it no more than a minute long.
Or you can send us an MP3.
That's stang at subgenius.com is the email address.
You can find that on subgenius.com if you forget it.
You can also find our address.
Which I will give you now if you need to submit something or whatever.
The Subgenius Foundation is at a post office box 181-417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
Once again, that's box 181-417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio.
And the zip code is 44118.
The background music is by Tom and Joe, Yellow Stucco House.
And now, from PR News in Washington, I'm sentenced to PR News in Washington.
Again on Wall Street, PR's Putin killed at least four people outside PR's nightclub at a British base in Germany.
Another soldier was forced to simulate sexual PR news tied up lying on the ground.
The next day, the press was a little bit more active in the news.
PR's brain damage judges refused to grant an indefinite feeding tube because it partly obstructed PR News.
In a case that has attracted virtually no media attention, Federal Reserve Chairman Alan Greenspan stole a cross from the Pomona campus and the revenue base.
Instead of calling the police, the school dragged the cross back to the Harvey Mudd campus where the 11-foot cross was set ablaze.
School administrators stated that the cross burning was to intimidate and oppress people of Claremont colleges.
And the police began to follow.
Lemur did it friends.
But now, a piece of music by Skou Auslander.
Reverend Skou Auslander did the next piece.
It's called the Roy Batty Blitzkrieg Prodigal Son Remix.
And I know how Roy feels here.
I want more life.
Bubble. Bottle, bubble, bubble, bubble, bubble.
Fiery the angel's stealth.
Deep thunder rolls around him.
I'm not going to show you.
But I'm going to show you.
If only you could see what I've seen with your eyes.
Nothing the god of biomechanics wouldn't let you in heaven.
I've done questionable things.
All sort of extraordinary things.
Revel in your time.
If only you could see what I've seen with your eyes.
Wake up.
Time to die.
No!
If only you could see what I've seen with your eyes.
Quite an experience to live in fear.
That's what it is to be a slave.
If only you could see what I've seen with your eyes.
Nothing is worse than having an itch you can never scratch.
I want more life.
Fucker.
Quite an experience to live in fear, isn't it?
That's what it is to be a slave.
For god's sake, wait!
Listen to me!
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
From PR News in Washington,
I'm still in the hospital in Rome recovering from PR's PR.
The Bush administration is again targeting ordinary Arabs familiar with the coal mine outside a hotel in Somalia.
What?
Pope John Paul II shot an American Cardinal for Ash Wednesday,
which marks the traditional period of bloodshed and reflection that culminates with PR News in Washington.
From PR News in Washington, I'm likely to stay modest for the immediate future.
Pope John Paul II,
who is the president of the United States,
has approved legislation that would help protect unscrupulous federal judges.
Catholic Church officials aren't saying yet when the 84-year-old pontiff will return to his class-action lawsuits.
President Bush continued his gene therapy experiment that killed a patient.
Friends, you're listening to the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack,
number 985,
a rerun of Media Barrage 3,
partially.
More is at...
www.subgenius.com
Everything's possible with Bob.
There's really only one solution.
Bob.
Everything's possible with Bob.
So call 13-013.
There's no Bob.
That's 13013.
Call Bob.
We're the sickest people I know.
I'm not part of this.
What's our view?
Really?
I'm not part of this.
I can read visionists.
Yeah.
Fuck them if they can't take a joke.
Once a schism started,
there are all sorts of schisms starting.
Really?
Schisms are fast.
Kill them if they can't take a joke, man.
They're all false prophets.
Don't give me this denounced all-profits bullshit.
Fuck this tape.
Yeah.
Very, very deep enough.
From PR News in Washington,
I'm from a bakery in Baghdad,
intentionally,
withholding information about PR News in France.
He'll be charged with raising money.
A dangerous new type of space shuttle mission has emerged in New York City
and caused at least three traffic deaths in the Los Angeles area alone.
Democrats exploded in front of a hospital south of PR News in Washington.
Should you have comments, criticisms, or suggestions regarding the Cassettebook program,
please forward them directly to
The Technical Standard.
Division for the Blind and Physically Handicapped.
Library of Congress.
Washington, D.C.
This concludes the instructions.
This tape is copyright 1981 by the Subgenius Foundation.