or dance we're natives there are no natives darling that's music it comes out of that
little box it's called a radio radio
woman sick cry for witch doctor you should be a critic darling
that has it good now radio good
my god's bigger than your god my god's smarter than yours my god's better because he gets
the subgenius
my god's better than yours
repeat my sole purpose in life is to bring pleasure to my companions
my sole purpose in life is to bring pleasure to my companions
all that is asked of me i will perform all that is asked of me i will perform
it is an honor to offer my body to the
service of the lord of the worlds
it is an honor to offer my body to the service of galaxy
a repeat after me i am not a pleasure unit i am not a pleasure unit i am not a pleasure unit
i am not a pleasure unit but you friend are a pleasure unit for bob hell yes
yes bob loves you
and will use you for his pleasure
the subgenius
bow down and bow down
Do it now! Do it now or you're going to get tased again! Do it now! Do it now!
The subgenius.
Power of the one.
I hope she can rest now, but she's dangerously near to mental collapse herself.
Definitely am.
Oh, I think so.
Good heavens, what's that?
And man.
Superior to the creatures only in his cunning.
Except for sub-man, seen here.
Who is superior only in his slack.
Stone jungle.
Yes, a man-made jungle.
Natives live there?
Yes, they live and they work there.
Why?
Order.
Help them to concentrate their efforts, get things done in a hurry, save time.
Save time? Why?
Darling, you're asking me a question all the sages haven't been able to answer.
As the 21st century began, human evolution was at a turning point.
Natural selection, the process by which the strongest, the smartest, the fastest reproduced in creation,
was a process that favored the noblest traits of man.
And so, the most advanced of the most advanced, the most advanced of the most advanced,
now began to favor different traits.
Most science fiction of the day predicted a future that was more civilized and more intelligent.
But as time went on, things seemed to be heading in the opposite direction.
A dumbing down.
How did this happen?
Evolution does not necessarily reward intelligence.
With no natural predators to thin the herd, it began to simply reward those who reproduced the most
and left the intelligent to become an endangered species.
I'm sure it's only a glitch.
A temporary setback.
You call this a glitch?
Oh, oh.
Hello, Angela.
Three pound, please.
No can do.
It just turns me on.
God, you girls are so great.
I mean, I just, I love to be with intelligent women.
Smart is so sexy.
I know.
Sometimes I could just think of something, and he could just get me.
So horny.
Yeah, well, a mind is a terrible thing to waste.
I get bored so easily.
Yep.
And you need lots of stimulation, Bobby.
Bob.
What?
Bob, save some for me.
Don't worry.
Present the unit, please.
Pleasure Unit 736.
It's, uh, uh, 7...
Unit 736 is welcome here.
Enter 736 and go to the first roving room.
I'm going to the first one.
What?
Oh.
You don't know the rules?
No.
I don't know.
Oh.
No.
Do the sexy bob now.
Oh, yeah.
Do the sexy bob.
Come on, JoJo.
Get groovy.
Get slap.
Do the sexy bob.
Come on, JoJo.
Bunk it now.
Do the sexy bob now.
Yes, it's a little known fact that Bob Dobbs is actually a sex god.
A sex idol for millions of people all around the planet and throughout the universe.
He listens to music that sound like this.
This sort of music gives Bob the virility and the stamina that it takes to live up
to being a sex god.
A sex god.
Let's listen to a little more and see what it does for you.
This abrupt change in tempo is important and crucial to this particular style of music
and its unique effect.
Well, I'm afraid that's all we can give you of that kind of music because Bob Dobbs is
just not good for untrained human minds to hear too much of that sort of stuff because
it's too darn powerful, as Bob says.
So, back to another portion of another listening sequence of another time and day in somewhere
else, USA.
Bob and Connie really enjoy life.
Bob, can't you see me?
Can't you see me smiling?
Bob, can't you see me smiling?
Can't you hear me?
Can't you hear the madness?
Bob, can't you see me?
Can't you hear me?
Bob, can't you take me?
Fill a box of money?
Bob, where's the money?
Beach party?
It's not a beach party.
It's a subgenius beach party.
Subgenius beach party.
Where can I play my section?
Uh, Doctors?
Uh, Dr. Fred?
Bob, but here's Bob
himself. Random bird.
Straight belief. Well, not that.
Here's Bob.
It's the expression
on their little faces
I like. Yeah.
A sort of cross between fear
and awe. They don't know whether
to laugh, cry, or wet their pants.
Yeah.
Now that is what I call
belief.
Things looked bleak for
Joe, but they were even worse for
mankind. As Joe and Rita
lay dormant, the years passed
and mankind became
stupider at a frightening
rate.
Some
had high hopes that genetic
engineering would correct this trend
in evolution. But sadly,
the greatest minds and resources
were focused on conquering
hair loss and prolonging
erections.
Meanwhile,
the population exploded
and intelligence continued
to decline until humanity
was incapable of solving even
its most basic problems,
like garbage, which had been
stacked for centuries with no plan
whatsoever, leading to the
great garbage avalanche of
2,505.
I'd buy that for a dollar.
Please put down your weapon.
You have 20 seconds
to comply.
Yes, Bob.
Yes, sir, Bob.
I think you'd better do what he says, Mr. Kenny.
Okay.
It's down.
I threw it down.
Bob.
You now have 15 seconds to comply.
Bob, I dropped the...
Direct violation of
I dropped the weapon.
Section 9.
You now have five seconds to comply.
I dropped the record, Bob.
I put the record down, Bob.
...authorizing the physical force.
No, Bob!
No!
Say, why does that eagle attack me?
He's been trained to recognize
and attack Americans.
The anti-American eagle.
It's diabolical.
I'd just like to ask,
purely out of academic interest,
you were sure I was going to survive,
were you?
I was quite confident.
Now, tell me...
What would have happened if you hadn't saved him?
Yes.
The sun would not have risen.
Then what would have happened?
A mere ball of flaming gas would have illuminated the world.
All right, I'm not stupid.
You're saying that humans need fantasies to make life bearable.
No.
Humans need fantasy to be...
human.
To be the place where the falling angel meets the rising ape.
With tooth fairies,
hog fathers.
Yes.
As practice, you have to start out learning to believe the little lies.
So we can believe the big ones?
Yes.
Justice, mercy, duty, that sort of thing.
They're not the same at all.
You think so?
Then take the universe and the universe.
And grind it down to the finest powder.
And sieve it through the finest sieve.
And then show me one atom of justice.
One molecule of mercy.
And yet...
You try to act as if there is some ideal order in the world.
As if there is some...
Some rightness in the universe by which it may be judged.
But people have got to believe that.
What's the point?
You need to believe in things that aren't true.
How else can they become?
Praise Bob.
And praise Slack, my friends.
How else...
Don't, Mr. Flint!
You will destroy the potential of all of mankind.
Organized for good.
Not for my good, Dr. Wolf.
Mr. Flint!
It would mean an end for all time to poverty, disease, doubt and frustration.
Mr. Flint, we have the power to do away with excessive heat and cold.
To turn wastelands into gardens of Eden.
All I have to do is take a bite of your apple, gentlemen.
No thanks.
No, Mr. Flint!
Mr. Flint!
No!
Ours would be a perfect world.
Why?
Because it's your idea of perfection, gentlemen, not mine.
You give away everything for us today.
Tampa, boo us to rot!
Good work, by mytons.
Let's send back the only man who made it to the bottom.
Slack Estrea, with the demo!
The baby boomers.
They did their best...
And they sold out like the rest to the man elimin JI HE.
They sold out to the man.
To the man.
Because there's a boot stomping on your face forever
Because there is a boot stomping on your face forever
And if you try to defeat the man
He will beat you, he will beat you at your own game
Minimum wage is going up
So now that you can fill it up
Go to work, go to work
You will get beat down by your boss at your job
Because there is a boot stomping on your face forever
Because there is a big boot stomping on your face forever
And if you try to defeat the man
He will beat you, he will beat you at your own game
Because there is a boot stomping on your face forever
And if you try to defeat the man
He will beat you, he will beat you at your own game
Because there is a...
Oh, my marks
It stomps, it stomps on your face, it stomps hard.
It's ultimately determined by its material forces of production.
You're a slave to the man.
The baby boomers sold us out, and now that we must do without a career, a career, we
will get beat down by our boss.
Because there is a boot stomping up and down upon your face.
Because there is a big boot stomping up and down upon your face.
And if you try to defeat the man, he will beat you, he will beat you at your own game.
Because there is a boot stomping up and down upon your face.
Because there is a big boot stomping up and down upon your face.
Friends, that was sent to us by the Slackestra.
I wish I could tell you more about them.
But now, the normal news.
From PR News in Washington, I'm sifting through the rubble of PR News.
Has Republicans turned violent early this morning?
Police in Connecticut say the new Congress tried to rob customers.
Representative John Boehner of Ohio wreaked havoc in parts of the northeastern U.S.
Survivors were killed when Governor Mike Easley tore through a mobile home community.
They were apparently angry that President Bush is to ban women from public places.
President Bush is experiencing tremendous growth.
Mr. Bush wants to expand.
The government now says it can legally ban women in public places.
The cabinet said it was crashing.
People with helmets with scarves that cover PR News in The Hague.
PR News.
PR.
This is PR News.
Figures from Wall Street.
One, one, two, three, three, four, four, nine, nine.
Hundreds of people had to be rescued from PR News in Washington.
More fighting in the Mexican crisis today when American troops participated in a joint raid with Mexican nationals against rebel rocket positions in Acapulco.
Now this.
Red alert.
You crossed the border.
That's my line of debt.
You haven't dismantled your MX stockpile.
Pakistan is threatening my border.
That's it, buster.
No more military aid.
Nuke them.
Get them before they get you.
Another quality home game from Butler Brothers.
This is a Bulldada news update because the world of the normals is just Bulldada.
That is correct, dear friends.
Yes, yes, yes.
We're back.
This is the first live show we've done in quite some time.
I fear.
And there is fear in the land.
But not too much here where we are.
Except for the fact that we had planned a live show.
A live show with lonesome cowboy Dave.
But it's like three degrees outside.
And there is no Dave coming here.
So we told him to call in.
But the phones aren't working tonight.
No one can call in.
We've been told by Tommy Fox at the management.
The management friends.
He said that something broke.
Something broke.
Something broken.
Something new.
Something borrowed.
Something true.
And Dave can't call in.
But Princess We can.
And then there's the false things also, you know.
And we really can do the subgenius news.
There's quite a bit of news to catch up on.
But first I should tell you what I've been playing.
First I'll tell you what I am playing.
What's in the background.
This background music is by lonesome cowboy Dave.
We'll just have to let that fill in.
But.
I think.
Just John did the titles for the bulldog news update.
We've been listening to a lot of movie clips that I pulled myself.
I've been watching a lot of movies and pulling audio.
Ripping the audio out of it.
You might say our man Flint with it.
The perfect world was represented.
Robocop.
I'm sure many of you recognized Tarzan's New York Adventure.
God, man.
I watched several of those Tarzan movies.
I watched a lot of movies on the intro webs.
And I can see why they kind of quit showing those Johnny Waz Muller Tarzan movies.
They're sizzling.
TV.
Well, there's the sexy aspect.
But then there's an insulting aspect that I'd rather not go into right now.
Makes fun of chimpanzees for one thing.
Anyway.
That song.
Baby Boomers was sent to us by someone called Slack.
S.A.
Stra.
Oh, we heard a little bit of clips from the movie Hogwatch.
A British production of a Terry Pratchett Christmas show starring Death and Bob.
Oh, there's a couple of Bob songs there from Glass Madness.
From the 1981 subgenius album Bob Songs 1.
Glass Madness and also some Doctors for Bob.
Some soundtrack from Idiocracy.
That's a really funny movie.
That.
Apparently Fox.
When it was first made by Mike Judge about a year ago.
Fox thought it was a little too close to reality.
And said, well, let's show it in seven cities for a week and then close it down.
Nobody's going to want to watch this.
And.
But it like his previous movie Office Space.
I think that we'll find people quoting Idiocracy.
And actually they're already living Idiocracy.
So what's the point of quoting it?
And thanks also to Maynard Brainard for some intro clips.
And of course, Fernanda Nettily Murr and Nora Preff will be coming up when I run out of news to tell you.
You may not have read this in the conspiracy news.
But Robert Anton Wilson, the great writer, died on January 11th of this year.
That may be old news.
To some of you.
But I've been surprised how many people read it for the first time on subgenius.com.
Robert Anton Wilson was a writer of everything from philosophy to sci-fi and humor books.
He wrote the Illuminatus trilogy with Robert Shea.
Which is why we are right where we are sitting now.
And his death was expected.
He was suffering from remorse.
Nude polio.
He had beat childhood polio.
But it came back.
And anyway, he has joined Bob on the saucers.
Although Bob is still alive.
In the realm that those guys party on, you can hardly tell which it might be.
We also had, well, we had some good news and then some bad news about Reverend Magdalene.
To refresh your memory, Reverend Magdalene had her child taken away from her by a court in small town.
New York State.
Because she is a subgenius, essentially.
Her husband, or ex-husband, had sued for child support.
And won on the basis that this judge suddenly decided that the Church of the Subgenius was a bad religion that a child shouldn't be raised in.
Well, in January, the new judge, after the first one, got too much bad PR for religious persecution.
And said, it's the Church of the Subgenius.
Then, a new judge came and heard the stuff.
And six months later, announced that it's true, the Church of the Subgenius, it really is just art.
But it's bad art.
And bad for a child.
And so, but nonetheless, the mom could have custody, half custody of the kid again.
But, just when we were putting on our party hats, we started to feel stupid.
Because, uh, the...
The other party's lawyers put out a stay.
And now the way it sits, the child is still stuck with his human father.
And separated from his subgenius mom.
Until an appellate court hears it at their first chance, five months from now, in May.
The good news is, when five judges who aren't from that small town hear what happened, there's not a bad chance that...
She might get full custody, we'll see.
Hold her breath.
Friends, it's interesting.
It's kind of like hearing about the Salem witch hunts.
In just the wrong place and time.
Of modern America.
What other news in subgenius land?
An old book, a subgenius book that's been out of print for a long time, is back in print.
Yay!
Revelation X.
The, uh, uh, Bobapacra phone.
Not to be confused with the new book, Subgenius, uh, Cyclepedia of Slack, the Boblyagraphon.
Uh, actually I get it kind of mixed up myself.
Anyway, Revelation X is out again.
It is possible that I might someday make a dime from saying that on the air.
I just want to make you sure you know that.
It is a subgenius book.
But it's nice to see that back in stores.
Actually, some real scary stuff happened with that.
Our, we got this new publisher.
Right?
Thunder's Mouth Press.
We got a new editor.
Well, right after Bob, uh, he, right after he bought our two books, and Bob told him to repent, quit his job, and slack off,
this editor did what Bob said and quit his job.
Leaving us terrified that we wouldn't have a friendly editor there anymore.
Uh, luckily he was replaced by somebody who was an old friend of our first late editor.
Tim, the great site Tim McGinnis.
Anyway, then the next bad news was that the distributor of almost all small print books,
press books, in other words, everything that's not coming from the big conglomerates like
Time Warner, Viacom, and so forth, went bankrupt.
That was our distributor.
Went bankrupt.
The good news is, uh, our book publishing company was bought by another book publishing
company that is its own distributor.
And so, you see friends, little by little, the conspiracy really honestly is, I've been
watching this happen my whole showbiz life.
And I'm not going to lie.
They've been carving away at every small distributor and small publisher and small
radio station and small anything so that they can Walmart the whole world.
90% is not enough for the conspiracy because then there's a chance that Bob might win.
No, sir.
They've got to have it all.
In the end, there can be only one.
In the end, that's what they say.
And we say in the end there can be only umpteen billion.
How's that?
Um, next, this weekend coming up, uh, Winterstar, uh, the ACE, ACE here in Cleveland, Association
of Consciousness Exploration, Association for Consciousness Exploration, I should say.
ACE is, uh, doing Winterstar, which is, if you're interested in consciousness-ness-ness-ness-ness,
then that might be fun to check out.
It's the best.
It's the perfect midwinter getaway.
Uh, there's, uh, information about that if you need it on subgenius.com or roseandcomet.com.
I just finished a new DVD of, uh, Tripadelica, Psychedelio, Groovalicious, Droopy, Colory,
Mixy video for that specific festival.
Sort of like a Grateful Dead light show, but, uh, actually with a lot more variety.
Mm-hmm.
Uh, uh, Tex Day is coming up.
Not X Day.
That is also coming up July 5th.
The world ends this year, July 5th, into the 10th X Day, uh, Waitation, I guess you might
say.
But before that, there's a little rehearsal outside of Austin, Texas, Texas at Dragon's
Wild Ranch, the weekend of May 5th, called Tex Day.
Uh, and, uh, so forth and so on.
Friends, what other news do we have here?
Robert Antleman?
Sam Wilson died, right?
He's still partying, you know that.
Uh, Revelation X is out.
Reverend Magdalene still has no child because she joined the wrong, um, funny church.
I guess it's OK to raise a kid in the Church of the Flying Spaghetti Monster or other ridiculous
churches, such as the Church of Jesus Christ, for instance, but if it's the Church of Bob
Dobbs, uh, uh.
It might, somebody might.
some kid might accidentally see a picture of Bob.
And you know what Bob looks like?
He looks like a smiling man.
God forbid that a child be raised in a religion
that focuses on an image of a smiling man
rather than a religion that, for instance,
might focus on a dying man of some kind.
But, you know, Bob ain't going to die for your sins.
We've said that a million, billion, hundred trillion times.
He does, however, bring an excuse for your sins
and an excuse for why you should expect everything
to be just and right and true and fair for you.
I've decided, friends, for a while now,
we've been saying, oh, it's not fair,
but that's just the way of life.
Well, I've decided, why should that be?
Are we always going to put up with the world being imperfect?
Well, it's not.
Yeah, that's slack.
But think about it.
Washing the dishes.
Why do we have to do it every day?
Just because we mess them up every day?
Yeah, I know.
There's some logical reason.
Picking our noses.
Why do the boogs build up
even after we've gone to so much trouble
to clean our nice noses with Kleenexes and so forth?
This is the list of injustices and unfairnesses.
Why must we do anything we don't want to do?
And I'm sure you'll have a million answers for that.
Many good answers.
But I'm not interested in those.
I'm interested in the world 10 billion years from now.
I might not live to see that day 10 billion years from now.
There might not even be people to accomplish this.
But friends, sooner or later, sooner or later,
why can we not have that perfect world of utter slack
where you can eat as much ice cream?
As you want without worry of fatness?
You know what I'm saying?
No, I'm saying.
How come we can't have Halloween every day, my friends?
Halloween where we can wear...
Where we don't have to wear that mask.
Halloween is the one day the subgeniuses can take off their masks
and the normals have to put one on.
But why can't every day be Halloween for us?
Yeah.
But fine.
Well, you can say, well, why are you worried, Reverend Stang?
Bob prophesied that the world ends July 5th this year,
or some year, sometime.
Maybe it's July 5th, if we really knew what days these were
and what calendars we're working from.
But I'm just saying, just in case,
we should start working towards the erasure of everything inconvenient now.
And we don't have to work real hard at it
because that would itself be rather...
Very inconvenient, don't you think?
Yes.
And...
Rather.
I'm feeling more convenient
because I finished teaching the history of the Church of the Subgenius
the first 100 years.
That took a lot out of me.
And caused us to play reruns from the 80s for a long time.
Only the Cleveland audience missed those.
And what else did my notes say here?
We've got...
Hal.
Oh, Hal's book.
Dr. Hal.
Robbins has a book out.
Robbins, by the way, is spelled with one B.
And it's an ABC of dinosaurs.
I don't know if that is the actual title.
I'll bring it next week or some week and we'll read poems from it.
Because there's poems about dinosaurs written by Hal
and color illustrations,
which is really the main point of any dinosaur book by Dr. Hal.
The Hal fans should know about that.
Just...
If you're interested in that,
look up Hal Robbins
or askdrhal.com.
That's askdrhal.com.
One word.
I'm sure everything is on there.
Oh, and the final news.
We'll give you a little preview of this.
The Amino Acids have a new album coming out.
It's not out yet.
It'll be out in June.
It's called...
Humanity Will Fall Like Pins.
Now, you have to say it in that sort of...
crazy person way.
Humanity will fall like pins.
I was providing contrast, dear.
Oh, that's fine.
Anyway, it's...
Thank you, Princess.
It is the...
Well, it's said in the same way as that old Warner Brothers cartoon guy
that would say,
No one will ever know.
And anyway, I'm going to play...
a cut here
from Humanity Will Fall Like Pins.
I believe this is cut eight.
Gamma Ray Harryhausen.
guitar solo
Oh, yes, baby!
How to Start Controlling Others
and Stop Caring for Yourself
This book is copyrighted
no more. This recording
is copyrighted no more.
Your problem? You've lost sight
of your own life, and you may
find yourself no more.
Mental. I needed help.
I sat down for four months
to help me support myself while I wrote
No More. What do I put in it?
The Persian Gulf War, the breakdown of
communism in the Soviet Union,
and the Hill-Thomas hearings.
I can't remember the name. Based on shame,
fear, guilt, and dishonesty.
Issues and problems.
Handcuffs. Owning my power.
I wanted to go deeper and get high.
Soon, I subscribed to two
popular beliefs.
I stopped thinking. I didn't know how it had
happened. I didn't know what had
happened. I thought I was going crazy.
My life started working again.
Just taking up the slack.
Understanding and information.
Slack can be
profound.
A message from the President of the
United States, George W.
Terror. Good morning. This weekend
we commemorate Bob Day.
Today when America honors every man and woman
who has worn the uniform of Bob.
People who stepped forward to serve a
cause larger than themselves.
One freedom that defines our way of life
is the freedom to choose our leaders at the
ballot box. We saw that
freedom earlier this week when millions
of Americans went to the polls to cast
their votes for Bob. But one thing
has not changed. Do not confuse
the workings of American democracy with
a lack of American democracy.
I look forward to listening to ideas
from Bob. Bob is a proven leader who
has served six presidents, four Republicans
and two Democrats. And he has shown
that he is an agent of change. Bob
replaces six presidents, four Republicans
and two Democrats. America is
safer and the world is more secure because
of the leadership of Bob. And I am
deeply grateful for his service.
Clear. Clear. And I pledge to
party.
Hello, man.
And now...
And now I find myself in
Indianapolis, Indiana.
I return to
my home. Hey!
A beautiful time to return home.
Who are you, mister? My old hammock
is there. So?
Here. My old pipe.
I haven't smoked it in
years. Mary didn't like it.
But now she's gone.
What do you want in my kitchen?
Do the pipe.
Now I'll have time.
Now I'll have lots of time.
Time to smoke and smoke
and smoke and rest.
My hammock.
Light the pipe.
So nice.
Ah, relax.
I've got all
the time in the world. The rest
of my life.
The birds. Yeah? How red
the sky. How soft those clouds.
So lovely. So lovely.
By the authority vested in me by
the state of California,
I pronounce this man Bob.
Whoa. Whoa.
Good.
They're good.
You fool.
You idiot. You fool.
You idiot. No. Don't.
Don't.
The secret of X-Day.
The secret of
X-Day. Am
I evil? I, I
don't know, my son. All my life
I've been a little man. Happy little
fella. But in the
dressing room. I, uh,
I don't understand. Did you ever hear of X-Day?
No. You mean
yes, yes, a chance to
grow to normal size.
Please, please, please let him
do it. Just what does this X-Day
look like?
Uh, uh,
a wreck. I had grown.
I had grown. I was
growing.
You've grown,
but not so much that I can't handle
you. I was normal.
Normal.
You look good to me. I do?
Well, I always did
go for big men. Big?
Yeah. I was
vaguely disturbed. No,
please don't. What's the matter,
baby? I, I, I, it
seems to me you're growing bigger.
Bigger? Yeah, yeah.
I thought at first I was seeing things, but
now I know it's true.
You've grown
bigger. I'm afraid of you, John.
You're too big now.
Let me go, you big
slut. Let me go.
Stop that screaming. You want to
wake the whole street up. Let me go.
You're hurting me.
Help. Help.
Ah.
No. Yes.
Yes. I'd grown at least
six inches. Now I
was a freak again. All my
life I was a little man.
I wanted to know what it was, what it was
like to be a big man.
Now I am big.
Too big.
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
Ha, ha, ha. Like the swing
of a pendulum. The secret
of X Day.
The FBI Sex Tour. Family
Time. The FBI Sex Tour.
Bob is the President. Bob. The FBI
Sex Tour. Rock solid. Bob. Here are
your hosts. The FBI Sex Tour.
Family Time. Self-esteem.
The FBI Sex Tour. Commit
adultery. The FBI
Sex Tour. Fornicate.
Do any murder. Fornicate.
Commit adultery. People are
getting beat down. To lust and
after her. Low self-esteem.
Full sexual intercourse. Super
hung Superman. Pornography
is okay in small doses.
The FBI Sex Tour. The FBI
Sex Tour. Hey, this is Bob. Hey, this is Bob.
Hello, everyone. This is Dobbs
with a Dobbs Moment. We're
taking a few minutes to introduce you
to some of the families whose lives
have been changed because of Dobbs.
And it is only because
of Dobbs. And today we want to
share another incredible story
of how Dobbs used one of our broadcast
to transform life
forever. That is
true faith and true religion.
I did not have a clue.
A precious gift from Dobbs.
Yes, friends, and we've been listening
to some wonderful
Nor-El-Pref cut-ups there.
It's been a while since
I've played Nor-El-Pref, actually, because
we've been in rerun land
and yet Nor-El-Pref
prefers to just whip stuff
out constantly. It never seems to
stop. You can find more
of that at Nor-El-Pref
dot com.
And I'll spell that. N-O-R-E-L
N-O-R-E-L
P-R-E-F dot com.
And coming up,
a little bit more Nor-El-Pref,
but a whole lot more Fernandenende
Limer.
The great, that
great cut-up of a fellow.
Although I'm tempted to, before
that, to play another Amino
Acids thing, because I know that you
love that.
In fact, um...
How can you not love that?
Well, if...
I actually, I can see how
people could not love the Amino Acids.
It's so good, though!
Well, that's a... It's infectious!
That is true. They're definitely
infectious, there's no question.
Uh, and they're
everywhere. The Amino Acids are
in everything. They get into everything.
They're in you!
So, uh...
I've got to be careful with my
you know, that just, uh...
uh...
I'm not that kind of guy,
you know,
that just, uh...
I don't know,
I'm not that kind of guy,
uh...
The Acidic Amigos!
Hey.
And, uh, they, uh...
And since, uh, I have to...
Uh, well, let's, uh, let's listen to another JoJo.
It's JoJo, JoJo, JoJo, JoJo here.
Hi, JoJo.
Um...
Uh, sorry.
I don't know, it...
My goal is to now, um, go to my high school and smoke.
By the time I graduate.
Tonight, God gave me a deliverance from my brain.
Now, Christ...
Fight Christ.
Fight Jesus.
And fight government and family and church.
In other words, jump all over Jesus Christ.
That's correct.
We have girls, tamales, and $2,000.
Yes.
Hot shot, I'll get it.
Really?
Yes, sir.
Oh.
Oh, all right, sir.
Mm-hmm.
Yes, sir.
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Well.
Yes, sir.
I see.
I see, sir.
Yeah.
Yes, sir.
Yes, sir, that's right.
Yeah, that's right.
Uh-huh.
Yeah, yes.
I see.
No.
No, sir.
All right, sir.
Yeah.
No.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
No.
All right, fine.
Can you read, Sergeant?
Read?
Yes, read.
Read a book.
You ever hear of Shakespeare's Hamlet?
Tarzan read trails in jungle.
Read clouds in sky.
Lawyer ever hear of Kinsinupa?
Kinsin what?
Kinsinupa.
Secure snake bites.
All babies in the jungle know that.
This is a court of law.
White man's law, lots of words.
Jungle law, more easy.
Man live own life.
So you prefer the jungle code to civilized law?
In jungle, men only kill bad animals.
In civilization, men kill good men.
Will Mr. Norton concede that human life is in constant peril
in this wild and unexplored regions of the world from which this child was rescued?
No, I will not concede any such thing.
In the last year, 35,000 men, women, and children
were killed in automobile accidents alone in this country.
Your Honor, I object.
Hey, what's going on in here?
From PR News in Washington,
I'm charged with a single crime.
I did squirt.
The Food and Drug Administration is rather illegitimate.
Big deal.
Pope John Paul II says he needs more painkillers for the butt.
Then I might get infected.
John Paul suffers from Christmas Eve mass and Christmas Day.
Very sweet and touching.
On Wall Street, the Dow Jones Industrial Average occurred near a mess tent today,
just as civilians are posing as civilian agents.
Five more have posed as friendly PR News agents in Washington.
Very good.
Find out if you can remember the girl who used to be a clothing layer with her farmhouse.
Homer Simpson got in her car,
watched Freedom Face a deep gas
and hinted at a man trying to steal her Bendez Mean Dog,
shake his head and yell,
beg for mercy.
Tippled that no one was mad at her
an old American foreign
who was trying to extort money to buy  Groucho name art
Prepare to be ruptured, dear friends,
as we listen to this music in the background
from a reverent brain leak.
Because, friends, when X-Day comes,
you'll always be listening to this show,
The Hour of Slack.
And you'll always see the Subgenius website,
which is, of course, subgenius.com.
And you'll always be writing to Post Office Box 141...
What is it? 181-417.
P.O. Box 181-417.
Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
That zip code, once again, 44118.
Yes.
Did you get that URL?
Of subgenius.com.
Subgenius is not spelled with an O, by the way.
You must do as you command.
That's the whole point of this, actually.
As Reverend Brain Leak knows.
Now, here's a ball game for you to know.
Prepare to be ruptured.
subgenius.com.
Rememberong.com.
Remembering.
Stop the tape.
You can use ambiguousopoo.com.
Later, though.
Bye-bye.
Goodbye.
All aboard the saucer ships.
Planet A destruction is go.
Why?
I mean, why did you do all this?
Human beings make life so interesting.
Do you know that in a universe so full of wonders, they have managed to invent boredom?
Quite astonishing.
Oh.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Good night.
I'll buy that for a dollar.
We love you, friends.
And we're going to slowly leave our little room here.
But first, I'm going to expose you to some more of the amino acid.
No, no.
No.
I'm
The few remaining survivors of the search body that was attacked,
report that the beast they encountered was many times the size they expected,
indicating that the monster has some strange power of rapid growth.
The exact description was...
The evolution just received.
According to the report, not yet confirmed,
a beast of seemingly gigantic proportions has been sighted working in the hills near northeast of town.
City officials have called for military help.
Planes and troops are expected to arrive within the next two hours.
Meanwhile, citizens should take rest within places of safety.
Cellars, farm shelters, as directed by civil defense administrators.
I repeat, I repeat, I repeat, I repeat, I repeat, I repeat, I repeat, I repeat.
The amino acid.
After halfway  in Lisa's villa,
the
weapon.
The weapon.
Oh, praise Bob.
And praise those luscious, bizarre amino acids.
And the long-sought amina acid, the female amino acid.
Where is she and what is she?
Friends, you've been listening to the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
Voice of the Church of the Subgenius.
Actually, it's only one of such voices.
There's, of course, voices on many radio stations around our world.
Suzy the Flusy and Lymph Note Institute on WREK in Atlanta.
The Hustling Evidence Show is soon coming up as we get out of here.
On KPFA in Berkeley.
And in the background we hear the Swingin' Love Corpses.
But I'm going to not let them take us out.
Because we're just going to suddenly go out.
Subgenius Radio comes to the neutral zone.
Now in multi-tentacular color, scents around and smell-o-vision.
Get ready for the biggest information dump of the year.
We are ready.
Beyond your guise, we're all against it.
Over time, we're going to be saying it.
Members of the Church of the Subgenius.
We're broadcasting live.
Directly through 4.20 a.m. and without delay.
I think a technique can be learned.
It can.
That can't happen.
No.
There is no technique for 4.20.
I think you can be taught to speak correctly.
Beware the Beastman.
For he is the devil's part.
Beastman.
It's Chaney.
Hello, not-man.
God's primates.
Yes, look at that.
Look at that.
We hunt for sport.
Or lust.
Or froth.
Not to spill blood.
Meanwhile.
Where the pine trees withered branch.
Stay off the horse.
Beware the awful avalanche.
I know.
But, you know, we could listen to these dire warnings.
Or simply decide that the earth is full of dangers.
But we can be happy and merry and take the high road.
And the devil take the high most.
Instantaneously.
But why?
I don't know.
Stop asking questions.
Why are you so interested in earth?
I'm not.
Please.
Why haven't you let us know?
Sent representatives to the world count one thing at a time, Dr. Brogdon.
I see you partake of your pop writer's suspicions that we intend to take over the earth.
as the god of darkness that had life eating out upon you.
A
freezer
reamer