Uh, Puzzling Evidence presents the sub-G news show.
Rockin' away!
Here the show is lifting off.
Yeah, well, watch this.
Three degrees.
Okay, we've blown one caller right out of the DMA-1 data bank.
The show is lifting off.
This act is immutably decreed.
It was rehearsed by ye and me.
A billion years before this ocean rolled.
Millions and millions of years ago, giant dinosaurs roamed the earth.
And the earth was without form and void.
And darkness was on the face of the deep.
And God created great whales.
Look at them go!
The white whale tasks me.
Yet he is but a mask.
It is the thing behind the mask I chiefly hate.
The malignant thing that has plagued a frightened man since time began.
Bob!
Bob Bob!
The thing that mauls and mutilates our race.
Not killing us outright, but letting us live on with half a heart and half a lung.
Bob!
Bob Bob!
That whale is as big as a satellite.
Super Inch!
It is a satellite!
Time for daily planning!
It's a giant whale orbiting the earth at thousands of miles an hour.
Just plain gloomy.
Moby Dick may be big, but he ain't that big.
I do not fear Moby Dick.
I fear the wrath of God.
The wrath of God?
Bob!
Bob Bob!
I spent my last breath at thee!
Thou dammit whale!
Bob Bob!
It gets dangerous sometimes.
You have to be careful.
Bob Bob!
Praise the Lord
And welcome to the subgenius radio ministry
Hour of Switch
Is it liquid or is it solid?
Liquid or solid?
Because further on in the thickness
There comes the thinness
For without the thinness
We would not be able to appreciate the thickness of the pudding
The pudding which cures
What the hell do you think you're doing?
Dragging your butt through the day
Selling body and soul to a bunch of bland normals
Acting stupid so they'll think you're one of them
Tired of getting all of the guilt
But none of the sex
There is a simple answer
Dear friend
A glowing beacon of slack
Amidst the turmoil and darkness
It's J.R. Bob Dobbs
The living slack master
And his church of the subgenius
Bob brings a new destiny for the abnormal
For Bob comes to justify our sins
To unmask the conspiracy
And to get us back
The slack they stole away
It's us versus them
Are you gonna fry in hell on earth
Alongside the pink boys?
Or are you gonna die?
Or will you pull the wool over your own eyes
And accept Bob into your mind?
Repent!
Quit your job!
Slack off!
And praise Bob!
Church of the subgenius
Eternal salvation
Or triple your money back
Yes sir
Oh yes sir
That was the subgenius MTV commercial
With music by Mark Motherspa
The music in the background right now
Is by Hell Pope Huey
And this is
Hour of Slack
Number 887
And most of those have been original shows
We don't do reruns very often
I was gonna do one this time
And it's half a rerun
From Hour of Slack
Hour of Slack
From March 1991
Of great hysterical interest
In the form of
Puzzling Evidence
Papa Joe Mama
Dr. Howell
Gary Gabrogfran
And Dad of the Dad's New Slack Show
All excited about that one war
Which is still the same one
But also
Chaz
Professor Chaz Smith
Of ESO Swamp Radio
And I'm not sure
If I should mention
That he wrote a rock opera
Yesterday
It's even got real rocks in it
It just started spewing out of him
Man I've never seen Chaz so excited
Really it's just
It's great to see somebody's skills
Collide with their good mood
It's kind of contagious
So we get to hear that
Creative process
As it happens
But for the first part of the show
We go to war
War
Bye, Mr. Smith.
Fire!
Remember to keep up your observation in fields of fire.
It's a fine hot day here in Mid-Bay.
I mean, Plasticville.
I mean, Spudville.
Where is this?
Oh, I see.
Pinochle, Connecticut.
I'd like to relieve myself here.
Oh, just go behind that bush while I pop open a tasty Budrow beer.
I feel relieved already.
Give me one of them Budrow beers.
Sure.
You know, these babies have only got 99 calories.
Mmm, yummy.
Then we're going to work on some of those MTD highlands.
I need an HF processor to get out there.
Lord, those chief-ins are going to win that war.
Yes, they will.
They'll win it for Budrow, the official beer of the U.S. Army.
It's not the U.S. Olympics.
So when you've got those goggles on all night,
you take off that ANPVS-7A system.
At present, the gun action continues along the coast throughout the day and night,
both north and south.
Air strikes from the carriers have been overhead in and out of Vietnam
since last night.
Three o'clock this morning.
Fighting is taking place right now to the west of Hue and around...
...getting, Ronnie.
How are you?
I'm doing good.
God bless you and God bless America and our troops.
I got a question for Abdul here.
Just bear with me.
First of all, I want to know what the big stink is about the U.S.
killing 500 civilians who were at a military command and control center
when Saddam Hussein has been a way of life for Saddam for years.
What's been a way of life, sir?
He's killed a reported 7,000 civilians in Kuwait.
Don't you think Saddam has realized his butt is being kicked
and now he's looking for sympathy from the world?
Okay, all right. Let him respond to that, sir, without the vernacular.
Please don't pick up the bad words, kick and other things.
These are uncivilized words.
But there have been reports of 7,000 Kuwaitians.
That's not true. That's not true.
You better check your information.
You better learn your information before trying to...
...to kill them.
...to spread out that information.
I could tell from the way you addressed me you are an ignorant man.
Our guest is Ambassador Abdul Amir Al-Ambari,
the Iraqi Ambassador to the United Nations.
We'll be more than honored.
...and the boy is beginning to die.
...and Hussein also says, sir, bye.
And now you can see the practice battle beginning.
Boy, if this is the practice battle, I'd hate to see the real battle.
Look at the blows given and received by the hearty spectator.
This war is going to be won on the playing fields of...
...Eton.
Yeah, right.
Just remember there's no hiding places in this war.
No, but they're all getting a hiding, though.
Look at those lively lads pound each other with pillows stuffed with styrofoam.
That's good training. It builds strong muscles and backs and helps morale.
And adds the clean, manly sweat to the early morning to flavor the day with a blast of methane that'll guarantee...
...you to flee the locker room in record time.
And here comes the woman's brigade. Let's not forget our fighting women in green and tan.
That's right, it's an intimate situation there, folks.
And this is the Chadar Squad, formed specifically as not to titillate the irritation of our fractious Saudi Arabian host.
Now, of course, the show comes in a number of variants, this one being the 4-slash-250 Armament Conductor Scout Vehicle.
Other shows include the IFB and the Fire Support Mortar Squad.
The Airborne Carrier, the Missile Tank Destroyer, the Armored Ambulance.
This is the diesel powered ride-out.
So we can force patients into any part of the battlefield with the Armored Ambulance.
Yeah, diesel ambulances all run on diesel power.
You know, you got some guy wounded and maybe he's losing his nerves, so you take him out into the battlefield and just drop him off in the Armored Ambulance.
Then his body is bagged for future reference.
Criminals, that sort of thing.
Freeze-dried professionals.
We can tell what they're like by using these remains.
Of course, we don't want others, say, foreign nationals poaching on our preserve.
Ha ha ha.
So we use the total filtration and ventilation circuit seats for the show.
Then pop, it's into the bag.
This thing, this thing's wonderful.
Yeah, it works just like a stapler. See, it's got this little grip here.
I like the way it just sort of wraps around my hands and allows my fingers to tickle.
Boy, if that was a snake, it would have bit you.
Hey, it is a snake! Get it off your hand!
Oh, I hope it didn't bite you. I'm afraid he's been stung.
Oh, look at his face.
Oh, boy, what a venomous sting.
It's swelling. No, that's another region.
Oh, it had a school there for a while, though.
It's a swell, man.
Let's not move into the other regions, because then war will be even worse.
Yes, down in the netherland.
Well, there are new regulations and what we can report on in this war.
We're meeting our various electronic helpers, which tell us how scary things are in the real world.
Oh, no, here come the overhead UFOs that are dispensing the Agent Green.
They're flying in a perfect formation.
Those are just little Arab guys.
I believe...
No, they're flying on their towels there.
Those are referred to as magic carpets out here, Ed.
Oh, of course.
It looks like a nice one there, perhaps an oriental rug variety.
It's an electromagnetic principle that allows these things to float and suspended in midair.
But our scientists will soon have solved this mysterious puzzle, and we'll be flying on our own fleet of A4 stealth carpets.
Little enemy guys, whichever enemy you wish.
Well, they've been working on these for a long time, Hal, but they've had difficulty meeting the price fixing that the Pentagon had.
They weren't able to deliver for under $30 billion.
Well, I don't know if we can afford to discuss national security matters like this without clearance on an open channel.
Well, we'll have to speak in scramble.
It's tough out there.
.