Come in, Dobbs. Have a seat.
Thank you, sir.
Dobbs, I read your report last night.
Oh, good. What did you think of it, sir?
I found it insanely disappointing.
Disappointing?
No, Dobbs. Insanely disappointing.
Gee, I'm not sure how to respond to that, sir.
It drove me mad, Dobbs.
My life will never be the same.
Yesterday, I had a full head of hair, Dobbs.
Yes, I know, sir. Your shaved head looks good.
I didn't do it. I fought them, but it was no use.
They shaved my head, Dobbs.
It works for you, sir. It works.
It works for you.
Ah!
Stop!
Oh, God, the pain!
It's like you're running a sword across my teeth!
I'm shutting up, sir. I'm shutting up.
You've killed me, Dobbs.
I felt something deep inside me die.
I don't have long to live.
Sir, what can I do?
It's too late for me. I'm not important, but...
I want you to see something, Dobbs.
I think I killed a man last night, Dobbs.
It sounds like you just had a terrible dream.
Yes.
Yes, I suppose you're right.
But then how do you...
How do you explain this?
Oh, my God!
God?
God is not here, Dobbs.
You've driven God away.
God has left the building, Dobbs.
I'm sorry. I scared God away, sir.
Find it, Dobbs.
Pardon me?
You've got to find it. You're the only one who can find it.
Before it's too late, Dobbs.
You know how he thinks. It's a part of you.
Go!
Oh, and Dobbs!
Yes, sir.
Be sure to find it by four. We've got that...
Some genius.
Power of...
Swag.
My name is the very esteemed universal philosopher of absolute reality,
Reverend Frodus Pasha.
You can call me Reverend Suds.
Friends, I got a story to tell you, and it's a long one,
so it's going to take three parts.
Tonight, I'll tell you the first part,
and over the next two days, I'll tell you the rest of it,
because I know you fuckers...
You're the only one who listened to me ramble up here all this time.
And we've got more music and entertainment for you,
but first, I wanted to get this off my chest.
I, like the rest of you, have been suffering from this mutant mutation
that is inherent within us all our lives.
Am I right?
Okay.
And I guarantee you, at no point in your life can you remember
a worse time than you were in the conspiracy indoctrination system
known as the public schools.
Woo!
See, I was lucky enough to experience everything
before the prescribing mind-altering chemicals to wee children
became the standard procedure for everything.
No, friends, I got to deal with solitude.
Nothing but solitude for the first five years of school.
I'll tell you, folks, it was madness
that there was one,
and it's going to lighten my life,
and I will get to that soon.
First, we have these teachers.
They just want to throw the facts at you, right?
They just want to throw them at you
and hope that you can regurgitate them back onto your little standardized test
so that they can get paid.
The conspiracy has convinced them
so that everybody falls into the nice little slots.
And those that aren't, well, just look around you, folks.
You can see where those slots fell.
We are here.
Situation is,
I had one light in my life,
and that was a man named Teacher Joe.
He was one of the only teachers during that entire time
that took an interest in me,
took an interest in my art and my wackiness,
and knew the shit that I was going through on a daily basis
and would do anything to get me out of that class.
This was the kind of teacher who had movie posters on his walls
that these kids weren't even old enough to see yet.
Big poster of,
you know, alligator on his wall.
You know what I'm talking about?
He had a Boba Fett doll in a birdcage.
And over his desk was the face of J.R. Bob Dobbs.
Friends, this man is a personal savior to me,
even more than what Bob could ever be
because he taught me what it took
to be as mutant as fucking possible.
And here we are today
to enjoy that mutant abnormality
as a collective of hatred and malice
towards this machine that has tried to swallow us.
Look at all the trouble everybody has gotten into
trying to get here.
Think about it.
This is the year, folks!
The time is time.
The time is nigh.
And immediately following,
the last hour of Slack, folks,
we're going to have to herd the subgenius group
down to the pond for the mandatory
Bobtism
in the organics-rich waters.
We'll be a shuttle service.
Oh, that's good.
A shuttle?
I don't know if we have enough shuttles to...
I would guess that at least half of the subgeniuses
will be chicken
and afraid to go down to the pond
because there might be nature
or animal cats.
Oh, there's bubbling brown scum on the surface
and this, the natives say, is walnut oil.
But we just hope that that's not some rural euphemism
for something else.
At any rate, in addition,
it's alive with life,
hopping and writhing and seething,
giant diving beetles,
huge tadpoles as large as regular-sized frogs.
If they can survive,
surely a subgenius can survive
for one sure thing.
A short moment of inundation
and total acclimatization
to the word of Bob.
But don't you want to be purified
before you rise up on those saucers, friends?
Wash off that last bit of conspiracy scum
and wearing only natural scum.
Be sky-clad and mud-clad.
The sky above, the mud below.
The subgenius within.
And, uh, friends,
so we will be trying to organize
shuttles.
We have four of those golf carts
and I'll also be taking the I-van down there
because it's quite a walk.
Now, if any of you actually can walk that far,
that would be great.
We're on our way down to the baptism
in the pond.
It'll be the first time I've ever gotten in that pond.
I bet it's cold as...
Or is it?
It might actually be warm.
It might be gently warm from the sun.
I don't hear any screams.
So it must not be too cold.
Uh-oh.
The pond is this way.
Hey, the pond is this...
Oh.
Okay.
They're not going to the pond?
No, they're just here campers at Listeria.
They're not being baptized.
They don't even care about being baptized.
I don't either, really.
Whose idea was this, anyway?
Legumes or Jesus's?
Legumes.
She drank the Bob water.
I need to pee.
Oh, this would be the perfect place to do it.
Right in the water.
Right, while people go,
gosh, Reverend Stang, you make me feel so warm.
Now, back to this baptism thing, friends.
I promise this is going to be a very short hour of slack.
It won't even be an hour.
It won't?
No.
No, it's not, because the baptism is scheduled at 3.30,
and it's going to take at least 20 minutes for us to get down there
and herd you cowards down there.
I know some of you will avoid even the idea of being frog watchers.
This is the one baptism where a frog watcher is literally that,
because there really are frogs.
And you'll see them skittering out of the way
as the elephantine splashing proceeds.
So we're going to stop at 3.10, then?
Is that the deal?
And use the rest of the time to...
At 3 o'clock, I think we should start...
Well, that would give us half an hour to herd them down.
We need half an hour?
It's going to take them half an hour to walk,
and it'll take us a while to get...
I mean, it's going to take...
I'm going to put my bathing suit on
in case anyone was worried about the horrors
of seeing the evil Reverend Stang nude.
You're not going to.
I don't do that anymore.
Too many lawsuits.
I know where they're all looking.
Too many traumas.
Is this our first communicant here?
Ready to achieve baptism?
After this line, it drops off into an utter abyss
whose bottom is not the south.
Stickers?
You know, I'm seeing a white lamb!
Where's my harpoon?
This is me!
Harpoon men!
You'll find it does feel good.
Harpoons!
And this brown, bubbling scum that you see on the surface,
they say that's walnut oil.
Oh, I feel your mark!
Preacher can't take it.
How can he block?
He's rising!
I feel...
Oh, my nipples are tightening.
And I have scrotum as shrunk to the size of one marble.
Praise God!
Oh, wow!
Praise God.
And that one.
See that?
And I was here with a man and his son the other day
who were swimming, and he told me a story
about...
Well, perhaps I shouldn't mention that until we all get in the...
Yeah, let's...
If I can do that, the rest of you maggots can, too.
Yes, friends, it is cold.
It's cold, but...
And it's not good, disgusting.
And it's covered with walnut oil.
If you were a rich pink, you'd pay for that spa-like privilege.
That's right.
We are rich, Dr. Howell.
We are richer than they can imagine.
Actually, this is a...
This is the best turnout I've seen for a baptism in a while.
I have the papal robes, but if I get them wet,
they'll shrink on me, and I'll never be able to get them off.
They'll be clammy.
They'll be permanently stuck to me.
They don't want to be clammy.
So the way it works is, Ivan will baptize you,
and I will catch you as you fall back,
filled with the divine essence of gobs.
And I almost always manage to do that.
I never miss.
We haven't lost a single person yet.
So who is going to be the first to be baptized on the last X-Day?
If I can get in that water, so can you.
The first shall be the last.
You seem to be ready.
Why don't we do you a favor?
Reverend Eggplant, although we've been through all this before about 20 times...
Do you, Reverend Eggplant, swear to continue to express your hatred for the conspiracy,
reject everything it stands for, rejecting all pinkness, and accepting Bob only into your mind, heart, and body?
Say, I do!
I do fuck the pinks.
There we are.
Great job!
Congratulations.
You're reborn.
If you're going to knock them this way, I should be down, too.
I learned a long time ago to keep my glasses on,
because it's the only way to see the parts I want to see.
Which you don't have any of, by the way.
Here's someone. Come on.
Here's someone with some spirit.
I'm Mickey-ing in there, too.
Reverend Mickey Mephistopheles.
Finally, someone who's built.
A nice-looking young man.
Reverend, and this is your first baptism, isn't it?
You've never been baptized in a church before.
I have never been baptized.
Well, it's something one doesn't forget.
I'm clean virgin!
Reverend Mickey, do you reject the conspiracy and all its hold upon your life?
The false jobs, the false slack, the false sex, the false money?
Well, maybe the money is okay.
And accept into your heart...
The heart, mind, and other organs.
The word of Bob, the feeling of Bob, the spirit of Bob say, I do, yes!
Abso-fucking-lutely.
Praise God!
Born again!
And reborn again.
Woo-hoo!
Born again!
Ah, yes!
Woo-hoo!
All right.
Who is next?
Look, if we get moves, we'll take moves.
Keep going.
Looks like we're getting away.
Reverend Dusty Rhodes, I know that you have traveled many, many miles.
I have traveled many, many dusty roads to get here.
I have.
Oh, you do.
And you look a little bit dusty.
We'll take care of that.
And so, not only will the dust of the road be wiped from you, although that's all the wiping we plan to do immediately.
I can wash my own ass.
If you can, indeed, reject the conspiracy from your heart, mind, and soul, and hair, and everything, and accept Bob from any direction he may come.
Off and from behind.
There's nothing we can do about that.
He comes like a ape in the mud.
Say, I do!
I do!
Praise Bob, and down he goes!
Woo-hoo!
I just want to escape the hugger-mugger and hurly-burly of working for the Church of the Subgenius and float off in the calm of a prehistoric puddle out there in the woods.
And I certainly plan to this afternoon, too.
And every damn day, I'm here.
We're getting back to the dirty fuck.
I mean, we were having people stepping out of that pool, and they were actually rinsing it off.
How did they do that?
I found that the rinse station doesn't work.
No water comes out.
We turned it off. We turned it off for that reason.
How do you turn it on?
Why would you want to turn it on?
To rinse off those selfsame animalcules and overeager organisms.
See, you're falling into that same trap, Dr. Howell. You're trying to cleanse yourself of that, which is...
No, no, Papa Joe. I'm not.
Clean to begin with.
Because I'm not using...
I'm not using conspiracy chemicals and alcohol derivatives and stuff like that.
Sodium silico...
Aluminate and all that godforsaken stuff.
I'm just using water that comes up out of the ground.
But when you go camping, don't you want to be out amongst the wildlife and the little animals and everything?
You have little choice.
They are surrounding you, like in my trailer.
The ants, the spiders, the huge cockroaches that come up out of the drain.
Not a working drain, but they come up out of there.
If you rinse them off, they'll have no place to live.
I don't want them on you.
That's genocide.
There are special things that should be on you and things that you shouldn't.
Just like a country, you want to keep undesirables out and the desirable faction in.
You must not have watched Machete last night if you're saying that.
You are your own nation.
You want to make sure that there are only the proper inhabitants.
And once again, as yesterday, I will mention, there is a specific type of arthropod...
that lives in your eyelash.
And another that lives in your eyebrow.
If you keep rubbing conspiracy chemicals into your face, for whatever reason, they gin up.
You will discourage these essential critters from living there.
And any skin problems or itching or anything like that that you have as a result...
will be interpreted by you as that you need more conspiracy poison to rub in the crevices of your skin.
I recommend Spray Lotrimine.
Spray Lotrimine Powder.
In fact, you'll see it referenced in this program book.
Spray Lotrimine.
It keeps them sliding.
Men.
If a new schism were to develop the so-called Christian scientist version of the subgenius...
in which any sort of disease would be allowed to carry on its natural state within the subgenius body...
Clap your hands three times and say, be gone.
Disease, leave this subgenius.
In the power of Bob.
He wouldn't want you to have it. He wouldn't give you that...
Well, some diseases are educational.
It's fulfilling your divine destiny to allow that disease to...
Well, you'll fulfill your divine destiny and I'll fill mine.
So you're going to keep on taking those showers. You're going to keep on eliminating those...
There is no shower, thanks to some interfering busybodies who turned off the rinsing station.
It was for your own good, Hal.
Well, you have to get out covered with the primordial slime and march back covered with the primordial slime.
But it's still fun and I recommend it.
We'll keep that in mind. Remember, there's always the towel that will reintroduce that same bacteria because they don't get washed.
Well, speak for yourself. Perhaps you don't have a laundry service established.
Not here, dear friend.
I can't speak on this subject, but...
Well, there's a perfect solution.
There's a perfectly good shower house up top there.
I go there every day.
With a nice trail.
Well, see, again, creeps use it and leave disgusting condoms hanging on things and they don't wash out the sinks after they hawk phlegm into them and so on.
Now you're going to be one of those people who's also going to complain about the alternating heat that we installed there so that it doesn't stay too hot too long.
Yes, I've noticed. You get the hot water in the shower, you step under it and presto, it turns ice cold.
That's awesome. We do that.
It flicks back to hot and cold and hot. It really keeps you on your toes.
You're not appreciating. We had that installed so that you'd be able to enjoy the hot water all the more.
Yes, you can't experience heat unless you experience a little cold.
You know, people pay a lot of money to go to these fancy spas where they can go into the hot sauna and then go and jump out in the cold water and then get back out and go in the hot sauna.
That's it, but you're supposed to be switched with birch twigs by a stern, horse-faced old lady with white hair while you're...
Yes, that's it. But you're supposed to be switched with birch twigs by a stern, horse-faced old lady with white hair while you're...
running naked through the snow. Then you have to run back into the sauna and almost broil alive while everything squirts out through the pores.
And then into the Arctic sub-zero water that causes a huge cloud of steam to rise as your flesh splashes into place.
Which sub-genius denomination does that?
That's the way the classic Finnish sauna is set up and believe me, the word Finnish is advisable to use there.
Well, I'm sure you heard about that poor sub-genius who was just hit up with 15 counts of manslaughter for the people in the sweat lodge that they locked in there and kept in there until they dropped like flies.
I'm not sure that the skin should be an organ of elimination, but the sauna philosophy says that it is.
They were just trying to exercise for themselves the sin and bad deeds that they had done through their lives.
And what better place to do that than in the hot sauna?
It's nice to have the illusion that there's some way to get clean from the blackening sins of man.
Alright, next please.
I can't wait.
It's Reverend Teeters.
The aptly named Teeters Laverg.
Hey, you got something to feel about him?
That cold?
Yeah, it'll shrink down in a second.
It is a little chilly in here.
It's like a rough Miami.
Is there some joke about glasses and...
Anyway, Reverend Teeters Laverg, you have served Bob so well and provided so many services.
He speaks highly of your many, many services.
And he's too safe.
Yes, he said you were a tight fellow and a good agent.
And I know that you, as well as anyone, have already rejected the conspiracy from the public.
You have been a good friend to him from your balls all the way up to the top of your head and down to the tippy-tip-tip of your toes.
And that you have accepted Bob, we can tell by the size of the wound back there.
Praise Teeters, praise Bob. Hail Connie, you are safe!
I just got a new sin going.
Reverend Teeters is fighting most of his Peeters.
Oh, beautiful young lady.
Finally.
Very tiny.
I know.
I'm not a peeper.
I'm a peeper.
There are.
Too much of it.
He's so sad.
I'm proud of him.
Reverend Peyton, do you continue your hating of the conspiracy and your loving of Bob and Connie and your subgenius brethren who will be partying with you on the spaceship set?
Fuck yeah!
Mark that one!
Speaking of half-cocked...
Don't be embarrassed if some...
We really do want to Bob-tize you in the pond.
And we will.
I know that people are shy.
Look, if you've only got one penis, boys, don't worry.
You're not the only one.
I know for sure I've seen several subgen...
For sure dues-paying subgeniuses.
And plus, you know, I mean, it's kind of chilly.
You're in front of people.
Some of them retract.
The smaller ones become almost invisible.
And the large ones just look like legs.
One thing is, if you've been down there, here's what you can find at the pond.
There's a small kiddie pool-like area that is roped off.
The rest is an enormous chasm of enormous depth that no one can reach the bottom or know how deep it actually is.
It's made from a quarry.
And it would be pointless to Bob-tize people there.
Although they might want to swim out there after that.
After we finish with them.
But the faithful may have to line up on the bank or something.
I just don't see that kiddie pool area as being large enough to contain the entire contingent.
But maybe we'll figure out a way on site.
Well, and if, say, you don't really want to wade into that muddy-looking water,
or you don't want to take your clothes off, or even wear a bathing suit or something,
we, the preachers, will be happy to come out and sprinkle you.
Like I was sprinkled.
I was sprinkled as a baby.
Sprinkled?
Against my will.
I was baptized in the Methodist Church.
And the baptismal font water began to boil at that moment.
They just, you know, they didn't ask me whether I wanted to be baptized.
They just sprinkled me with some kind of damn holy water.
And that's where I got the scars on my neck.
You didn't ask to be born, either.
If anybody ever wondered about that.
It's like Dracula.
It sizzles and burns like acid.
They should have known.
My parents were really nice.
They were not very religious.
They should have gone to the Unitarian Church.
Well, it takes time to learn these things.
Yes, in about five minutes, we'll start the active purging.
Five minutes?
Reverend Eighty!
Reverend Stanley.
I've only been formally introduced once, but I've seen your name many, many times.
I know that you are a saved subjeetist, but this is your chance to finally be...
Truly baptized.
...completely covered with walnut oil.
Do you reject the conspiracy and all the bullshit, all the anguish and boredom that
goes with that, and instead trade it in for the slack that comes with Jarrah Bob Dobbs'
say yes for elegant...
Yes, I do!
Woo-hoo!
Praise Bob!
Fuck Connie!
Fuck you!
Aye, aye, aye, aye, aye, aye, aye, aye.
Oh, Reverend Buddy Day.
You just finished a perfectly fit live session.
Hollywood glamor.
We're going there.
Yes.
Reverend Buddy Day, we know from the disgusting nature of your work that you have already
rejected the conspiracy in all of its end-all decency, human decency, or general socially
accepted behavior, and have celebrated and exploited your abnormality to the max in the
name of Bob, in the name of Connie, and in the premise of X-Day.
Praise Buddy Day!
Praise Bob Bailey!
Hail Connie!
Praise Bob!
Oh, Reverend Stick, the fine Reverend Stick.
Great bass playing, by the way.
Thank you.
Wonderful music last night.
Scott is yours, I am, boy?
Yes, I am.
The tattoo is very amateurish, I wrote.
Yeah.
You're a prison man.
No, it's done in a way that gives it authenticity.
You reject a juror from your case.
You have to find a way to keep yourself, all of the horrors of the conspiracy, the
crap, the boredom, the everything else I've mentioned with everyone, and accept Bob, and
take him into your lungs in a deep, deep breath, and hold it, hold it, take a deep breath,
and hold it, my friend.
All right, you ready?
Under he goes!
Under he goes.
I'll give it up to Bob!
Oh, yeah!
There he is!
There's Bobby!
All right, guys!
Just go to the other one!
Yeah!
All right.
I'm going to the other one.
Bus drivers should line up their carts here, and anyone who needs a ride down to the pond should hop in, grab your trunks or not.
There is...
Bring towels.
Yeah, towels would be good.
You can put them on that old log by the pond.
Oh, and don't mistake that other old log.
It's not a log.
That's old sequal.
Yeah, you don't want to get...
That log moves.
Don't anger.
If you see the little tongue sticking out, don't go trying to play with it.
He will bite your arm off.
At least.
So, that is it.
Thank you.
Reverend Slander Bob, recipient of the Bobby Award for Best New Subgenius Show, because it's always on and never stops.
Look at that tattoo.
Wow.
Do you reject the conspiracies?
Damn near everything, except possibly the occasional high paycheck.
And if they have help, it will, you know, benefit.
And accept into your heart and mind the slackfulness of J.R. Bob Dobbs and the craftiness and greed of Connie Dobbs.
What?
Yes, I do!
I love the song.
Ah!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Slander Bob is making his way to land where he would become Slander Bob.
All right, let's get somebody else.
Can you come?
Yeah.
There's a huge crowd here.
I'm worried about the length of time this is going to take.
But here, here comes someone who's fully in the sea.
Here's a man who is prepared for an old sea crawl.
He's ready to do battle in the deepest parts of the conspiracy ocean.
Don't do this in the ocean, folks, because yellow is what causes sharks to attack.
You don't brush water on sharks.
Yeah.
Perfect.
Reverend Zeronius, who risks electrocution tonight when he plays his synthesizers soaking wet.
Yeah.
And by the way, we mentioned this water never dries.
It's a special kind.
Anyway, you must surely reject the conspiracy and all its evil things and most of its good things, too.
And accept Bob and all of his evil things and all of his good things, too.
And Connie and so forth.
Praise Bob.
Praise Reverend Zeronius.
And under his shoes, Bob.
Woo-hoo!
Get his clothing off.
Put your clothes back on.
I'm wetter than I've ever been.
Woo-hoo!
Oh.
Oh, a rubber duck.
It's fun.
It's relaxing.
And it's necessary.
You get this segment over with.
Oh, here comes Pantyara.
Oh, Pantyara.
Oddly enough.
I know I'm close.
I'm dressed more than she has been.
You're maybe close.
I'm too dark.
Pantyara has purchased the important, perfect cup design by Reverend Imberture, the greatest
troll master, with this sort of clean bob.
This is the George Clooney bob.
We'll be sprinkling you, Mike.
It says here, I drank the Bob water.
She drank the Bob water.
She drank of the Bob water.
Don't you drink it, I've had two.
Oh, no.
Do you know what I'm talking about?
All right, right on top of the head, Pantyara, do you reject the conspiracy and all of its
crap and infections and diseases and bad feelings and accept Bob and his diseases only?
Shit, yeah.
Yeah, Pantyara.
Reverend Give-A-Shit, whose name I always forget for similar reasons.
Do you, sir, accept Bob's name?
Accept Bob into your mind and heart and wherever else he happens to go exploring and reject
the conspiracy and all of its coatings and disgusting things that it covers you with.
Oh, we'll try it again.
Okay.
Well, handing back to our good friend, Geoffrey Chaucer, he was not only an accomplished writer,
but he was also a government servant.
Oh, yeah.
He worked within the government of the, well, you would call it the government, but it was
the court, the king, a result of the Norman conquest.
And he was unquestionably a subgenius in training.
And yet, if you read the Canterbury Tales, you can tell that the people in those characters
have not changed now for lo these many hundreds of years.
And this is a true meaning of being a subgenius is not letting the other people around you,
the typical conspiracy types.
Know that you are a subgenius.
You may hold down that conspiracy job.
You may even play up to the power figures and be someone that the folks who are running
the show think that they can depend on.
But deep down in your inner workings and hidden mechanisms within your mind, it is true who
you really are.
And now, these hundreds of years later, all the kings have been forgotten.
The queens, the court jesters, everyone else in that court except Geoffrey Chaucer.
The man who put the English language on the map.
And now it is the French who, at that time, they were the center of the universe.
Everyone wrote all their stories in French.
And if you, anyone who was anyone spoke French, now they look upon contemptuously as English
has surpassed them and all because this subgenius Chaucer decided to write his homespun tales
about faggots and knights and nuns and corrupt individuals within the positions of authority.
already, but show their dark underbelly.
They all get to heaven, though, except for one
person who rides away from the
procession, and that is the alchemist
who's performed evil
sorcery. And the fact that he rides
away means he's not gonna
get there. But
the French have always
attacked England
in every way possible, and one of the ways
to attack their literature with
such people as
Baudrillard and so on
to suck the meaning
out of
English language things.
And it's all part of that old
rivalry. Incidentally,
J.R.R. Tolkien wrote
The Lord of the Rings to be
the English national epic,
since he felt that the knights
of King Arthur, which are supposed to be that,
are actually French, with
Lancelot du Lac and
Sir Gromore
and so forth.
They're Frenchified
things, and not like
French.
Tolkien's creation, which is
so often misunderstood.
With nice, hearty American names
like Sting.
Sting is the name
of a knife, but
of course people used to name their knives,
and I used to name mine.
When I was a kid, I went
across the Mexican border, and in a
trinket stand, I got a
neat little knife. I wish I still had it.
On the blade, it said,
No hay javelin que ande
gordo.
I guess that meant
there can be no fat
sparrowhawk.
Did you remember the names of your
knives? Well, that one,
Gordo. Did you bury
them when they were no longer
in service? No, Papa Joe. I was a
thoughtless, foolish kid, and I
lost track of many of my
early treasures. Well, I have a whole cemetery
out in my backyard of
treasures that were no longer
functional. You know that burying a knife
is a specific part of certain
surgical operations.
You don't just throw it away. How about those
pair of shoes that you wore
traveling the highways and byways?
Are you taunting me? You know you can't
do that. But I do.
I place all those shoes in little
cardboard boxes and bury them out back
along with the skulls of the normals.
Fiendish subgenius
ideas.
You should see all the headstones.
All I can say is that if you have
a little, I was talking about a
werewolf problem earlier. If you have
a
another type of problem, a vampire
problem, and you know, you're not
even allowed to say bad things about
these creeps anymore. Vampires
and werewolves, they just have a bad disease.
We have to understand them. Anyway,
there's no problem with walking
around in broad daylight.
If you just, if you have shoes,
you put a little coffin earth
in your shoes under a
layer of cardboard or wood,
then out in the sun, you can
do it. Just a tip.
I like him to stay close.
Then there's the collection of
exotic animals, pets. It's also
the pet cemetery. They only seem exotic
to those who aren't familiar with those
particular species.
Well, I mentioned the other day that
the pet of choice now is
descented skunks. But
armadillos also make wonderful pets.
I bet they're different.
Exactly.
Armadillos can break every bone
in your skull. They leap
up when you're not expecting and crack
you with their shell.
And they give you leprosy.
What a lovely trait in a
pet.
Well, you know, you'd have
to be very adventurous to discover
that difference on your own.
But you know, a lot of those things are just
mean-spirited
allegations made towards
people claim that turtles can carry leprosy
too. No, they don't. They can.
Turtles? Yeah. Carry leprosy?
You have to be exposed to it
though. I mean, if they're not... I've never heard of it.
Even armadillos don't...
That sounds like someone was drawing the long bow
a little bit. Armadillos don't spontaneously
generate leprosy. They have to be exposed
to it. And they can carry leprosy
just as rats. Rats can carry
the plague, but they have to be... Yes, and all the mice
in my trailer are probably
seething with hantavirus.
But, actually, the world is probably
a lot more deadly
than we think. Only the blessing
of ignorance allows us to
walk through, to thread
the needle through a sea
of perils.
A sea of perils? Perils.
Like, wow, Stang
changed into Pisces.
Who says the age of miracles is dead?
We were thinking of
the pond and all the
critters that lurk beneath
its surface and in its depths.
But look at this audience. Do you think
this audience is weak enough to be
taken down by a mere
microbial enemy?
I think those microbes are the
most powerful things on Earth, and
everyone ought to have a healthy respect for them.
What about anal lamprey?
That would be one disappointed lamprey
in my case.
I think whatever's living in that pond
as far as the microbes are concerned,
they're going to be frightened of the new
microbes that are going to be introduced
after this audience goes into that pond.
Exactly, I mean...
You should ask
Stang about that one. He's seen
some remarkable sexual behavior
on the micro-label through his
home microscope.
Lab, which he brought out here
to test the waters of the lagoon.
But you can always wear your
subgenius condom with Connie
or Bob's head on it. Just don't leave it
in the wash house after it's been
used so that I step on it in the morning.
And please don't leave it in anyone's tent.
Just make sure you tie it down
with a hefty rubber band
so if there's any shrinkage that occurs
inside the pond, it doesn't remain
floating on the surface.
And...
Go ahead.
We'll call in the
creature of the black legume over there.
It's already been discovered, so you don't have
the discoverer's privilege, but sometimes
a good name just sticks.
Because it's so obviously appropriate.
Inappropriate?
Appropriate.
I hear they also drain that
pond every once in a while.
They do? Man, that takes the fun out of everything.
They can't drain it. It's connected to
river systems. It would be far
too much work. Why would they do that?
It doesn't mean they drain it completely, but I'd like to think
that sometimes...
Say it's filtered. The question is,
filtered from what?
What do they filter out?
They filter out
the filtering.
The filtering
by Stephen King, America's
most popular author.
What's in pond water?
One dollar.
Who's got it?
Our great auctioneer friends,
the new auctioneer, Janice Blackseed,
who will probably
be spreading...
Blackseed all through this...
One kid of two.
Do you reject the conspiracy
and all of its effects,
except for the money part,
and accept Bob
and his money into your brain,
your wallet, and
so forth and so on?
Your pre-puss. Let's do this.
Alright. Down he goes!
Next!
Oh, yeah.
What do you get used to?
Oh, man.
Woo!
Hazel, do you,
in this moment of slackfulness...
She's giving it thought this time.
Reject the conspiracy
and the abhorrent things
associated with it,
and accept Bob and the wonderful,
beautiful things associated with him and Connie,
plus any parts that happens to
end up thrown in.
Great decision!
Rise, Hazel!
Woo!
I like the abatement.
Praise all the Hazel!
Very smart.
Very irreverent.
Reverend Scum,
uh,
do you
reject the conspiracy
and the pinks
and the mediocritans,
and the cage dwellers,
the Barbies and Kens,
and all those other derogatory terms we made up,
and accept the subgeniuses,
the overmen,
Bob, Connie,
the exodus, and so forth,
and so on, say, uh, yeah, or whatever?
Yes!
Woo!
Yeah!
All right.
What do you got, Doctor?
Tawdry milk toast.
What a horrible sentence.
Mismilter.
Maybe.
Yeah.
Uh, do you
tawdry milk toast?
God, that just...
Ugh.
Come on.
Okay, you reject the conspiracy,
and all of its, uh,
crap,
and accept Bob,
and Connie,
and the exodus,
and so forth into your life.
Okay, boss.
Okay!
All right!
Woo!
Woo-hoo!
Good job!
Easy back down now.
Yes.
Woo!
Perfect.
They're piled up like cordwood.
Okay.
We're getting here.
Good bodies.
All right, Robin.
Look how they gleam and glisten.
Ah!
Good life.
Reverend Blank Stare.
Reverend Blank Stare,
I see by your, uh,
green wristband
and the gigantic penis
that you are a man of Bob,
uh, and accept Bob only
and reject the conspiracy.
Is that not so?
That is exactly so!
It is so!
Let it be so!
Perfume down!
Down under!
He makes a big slant.
The new guy who everybody thought
looks kind of like Bob,
but I don't know why they say that.
Ah!
Reverend Dapper.
Uh, Dapper.
Dapper.
Oh, of course.
Reverend Dapper.
Uh, do you reject the conspiracy
and all its, uh, crap?
And accept Bob
in the name of hurrying up the ceremony.
Ha ha ha!
No!
Woo!
Reverend Esther.
Reverend Esther,
glad to meet you finally.
Yeah.
Um, see you on the saucers,
uh, in a little while.
Yeah.
Uh, do you reject the conspiracy
and all it stands for?
Fuck yeah!
And, uh,
is there any other questions?
I mean, there's especially things like, uh,
bras and real things.
And, uh,
accept Bob
in the word of Connie.
Yes!
Praise Bob!
Hey, Connie!
Yeah!
Woohoo!
What the hell?
Hey!
Thank you for visiting us.
The baptism is just a kind of a fun extra.
And, you know,
we hope to see the girls
take their shirts off.
You know,
some of us
never get to see
that kind of thing.
You know,
that's another reason
for having X Day.
Let some of these poor little girls
on some subgeniuses
see what a girl looks like.
I don't want to win!
My ass has picked up smoking, yeah.
That's just kind of ironic.
I think Dr. Leguim
was probably the person
who invented the,
the, uh,
both the,
the Bobtism
and the Bobcircumcision.
That's why it's an honor.
It is not a great honor.
I was first baptized
by Dr. Leguim.
That's true.
And now,
finally,
I get to return the favor.
And I don't need
to go through
any of that hogwash
with you.
That's right.
I'm not going to go
I've already signed the form.
Yes, he has.
Dr. Leguim
has signed the form.
And so,
we need to only
make you wet.
That's right.
You need to only
make me wet.
Yes.
Price Bob,
hail Dr. Leguim.
And good luck
catching him down!
All right!
Bam!
Most of you
here are going to be
wearing the
black t-shirt
contact.
That's right.
All right.
Buddy,
I got a $10,000 shirt.
Wow!
I'm going to
get a $10,000 shirt.
And clerical collar.
By the way,
you're all in 3D now.
3D!
Newly ordained
Reverend Jacob.
Come on, boys.
Do you reject
the conspiracy
and any bad
distribution deals
you guys might happen
to get?
Or especially ones
that would reflect
poorly on me personally
and my trademark?
He wanted it rejected.
I do.
And except Bob
in your life,
you are now
baptized
in the name of Bob!
Yeah!
Thank you,
and you.
All right.
We've got a million
of you.
All right.
Be fitting
by my right winger stance,
I would be willing
to do a one-toe...
A one-toe?
A one-toe baptism.
I would assume
it would be the right baptism.
Okay.
We can just sprinkle
you a little bit.
Can we do it
through your shoe?
Yes,
through my shoe.
As little dignity
as I could spare.
All right.
We've got
a million of you.
All right.
We've got a million of you.
That's right.
Friends,
our good friend,
Mr. Sister,
who happens to be
the subgenius
that we eat dinner with
every Friday in Cleveland,
except this last Friday.
Yeah.
I know you rejected
the conspiracy
because you retired.
I retired,
yes.
And you accepted Bob
because you're not dead yet.
I can tell you that.
That's right.
And so with this dribble,
I now baptize thee.
Whoo!
In the name of God.
I'll carry a little bit home
for Mr. Erdman.
Yes,
I will.
Friends,
we must preserve
our conservatives.
That's right.
There are not many left
in the Church of the Subgenius,
and they are
endangered species.
We must stand
for something.
The worst thing
that could possibly happen
to America
would be for everybody
to think the same thing.
That is true.
And since we're
really drinking water,
I know that.
Those of you
who did not enter the water,
thank you,
sweetheart.
You want to be or not,
I hereby
baptize you all
in the name
of J.R. Bob Dobbs,
Connie Dobbs,
the Exus,
and Jehovah One.
Princess Wee,
even though you are not
of this planet
and come from
a distant star,
we know not which.
Believe me,
otherwise,
we'd already
have been ruptured.
We don't know
which planet she's from.
Rather than ask you
any questions,
I'm going to thank you
for your time
for helping keep
the Church of the Subgenius
going all this time.
Praise Princess Wee Ardo,
queen of all the UFOs
and her blue toenails,
the bright blue toenails
of Princess Wee.
Those are natural,
by the way.
They're not painted on.
That's how they grow.
That's how my toenails blush.
Yeah, that's how they blush.
Yeah.
Oh, thank you.
Well,
All right.
Thank you.
Thank you,
thank you.
Tonight, we're here to pay tribute to an actor, an author, director, humanitarian, and incomparable
showbiz whore.
I'm talking of course about Bob.
You are now about to witness the strength of Bob.
Bob the comic lady!
Let's bring him back out!
Let's go!
Go ahead!
Let's roll away!
Roll away!
Back out!
Let's go!
Go ahead!
Let's roll away!
Hey!
Bob!
Oh!
You're taking so big!
Hi!
My name is Bob!
Come on, Grandpa!
We want to watch Terrence and Phillip!
No!
We're going to watch the Bob Show!
Hi!
My name is Bob!
Bob!
The luckiest man and the worst entertainer in the history of show business.
He's a huge asshole and one of my best friends.
Bob!
Thank you, the large.
Give a round of applause for Papa Joe Mama!
It's very tough to follow an act like that.
But dear friends, I have something a little depressing to talk about tonight.
It's called, Leaches for Bob.
Because we all want to be leeches for Bob.
Bob wants you to suck up the vital fluids of the conspiracy.
Drain them of their energy.
Sap them of their strength.
And make the church stronger!
But alas, there are some who confuse this.
They instead become leeches on Bob.
Did I not say just yesterday that we were going to have a special three-mile run for
your life?
Excess executional run!
Inviting all holocaustals to come and join us in a Dobson Dispatch of Death rehearsal.
Death Day is just tomorrow, 7 a.m.
Do you expect the exes to do all the work for themselves?
No!
Don't you think Bob and his alien counterparts could use just a little bit of help?
Dear, dear friends.
10 a.m.
Starlog 13, Campsite Death.
Where's that?
Oh, it's conveniently located next to Starlog 15 and Starlog 11.
We waited.
10 o'clock rolled around.
Guess how many holocaustals showed up?
Zero!
Zilch!
Nada!
Nothing.
And the worst part was, it was completely predictable.
Yes, dear friends.
Bob Dobbs has traveled millions of miles.
His exes counterparts have traveled at light speed to get here to help you.
All to be here at 7 a.m. tomorrow morning.
And yet, when 10 a.m. rolls up,
on next day eve, how many of you show up to rehearse to help him?
Zero!
What do you do?
You hit the snooze button!
Dear, dear friends.
We have less than, what, 15 hours or so to prepare for the final onslaught.
There'll be no first annual rehearsal anymore.
Tomorrow's the day. I can feel it.
So we have to remember the difference between being a leech 4
and being a leech 8.
So we need to get on!
Now, I for my part also indicated that we would have a little swim in the cesspool down at the end of the road.
You know, a way to kind of bathe and pre-Bob-tize ourselves after our little run.
That is also when we are going to pass out the Dobbsian leeches for Bob.
Your medals of honor that you would wear to declare to all the world to see,
Yes, I am a leech 4 Bob!
Woo!
Alas, there were no recipients.
Oh, yes.
Yes, I got mine, but unfortunately it swam up my ass.
It's rather difficult to display.
But Dobbs will know.
He'll feel it.
Above those saucers, he'll get in there.
When he's ministering to me and the other Yeti faithful,
he'll know who has the leeches and who is the leeches.
You see, friends, helping the church is a lot like camping.
You all have to chip in.
Somebody's got to make the food.
Somebody's got to wash the dishes.
Somebody's got to empty those porta-potties.
Woo!
He's the highest doctor.
You can't just show up at the last minute for the chow and the frop.
Although many of us do, don't we?
So it's important to remember to chip in for the subgenius cause.
Because when that faithful hour arrives, we're all going to be stuck with each other.
That's right.
The saucers are going to be filled with the people to the left of you and to the right of you.
And if that doesn't scare the hell out of you, I don't know what will.
So brothers and sisters, it's time to think about putting out for Bob.
He wants more than just the $30 love offering.
He wants more than just your praise.
He even wants more than your witnessing.
And he certainly wants more than you getting down on all fours and bowing down
and assuming the position for him.
He wants him to reveal his glory to you.
Woo!
He wants you to help your fellow subgenie.
And he also wants you to help the exes and Bob fulfill the prophecy.
So if we come tomorrow at 7 a.m. and there's a little bit of a delay,
well, we've got no one to blame but ourselves.
And we'll only have one year to get it right.
Of course, we've been saying that for year after year after year.
But you know, you get the point.
The sooner we get there, the better.
The sooner we get ready for Bob, the sooner he'll be ready for us.
Do I hear an amen?
Amen.
Amen indeed.
Now in preparation of the final X Day Onslaught, I think it's completely appropriate, nay necessary,
that we dig deep within the book of secrets and pull out one of Bob's most sacred rituals
as developed by Saint Jaina Hyperclete's, the launching of a bleeding head.
Do I hear praise Bob?
Praise Bob.
Praise Bob indeed.
Now, if we can have the sacred altar boy with the sacred nine iron approach the stage,
as well as the sacred choir girl with the bleeding head, please approach the stage.
And of course, our favorite MC, Dr. Howe, to circumnavigate the ritual.
Please come forward.
What's that?
What's that then?
Fuck that hell! Fuck that hell!
We don't care about it! We get good!
This is a historic moment in the Church of the Subgenius.
A revival of an ancient tradition.
Here at great expense and difficulty, a specifically appropriate head has been chosen.
An alien head.
The head was designed by the Sli-Stack in the year 4080
and was delivered through a rip in the time-space continuum.
It is now being...
set on its tee by Papa Joe Mama.
In a moment, Papa Joe will very cautiously engage in this important event for which he is now preparing.
He's been practicing all winter long in his winter quarters in Florida.
The cooler bearer of the head is now being placed aside.
And Papa Joe is limbering up.
He's going to be...
There go the scraps of praxis.
Typical and traditional to let go.
He's testing the wind direction, ladies and gentlemen.
It appears to be coming out of the north-northeast.
This could cause a slight slice.
He's checking the fairways.
It's vital to avoid sand traps.
It looks like a...
A classic hip wiggle.
To loosen up. And the hands. To loosen up. And the hands.
You can imagine the stress that's involved with this.
So much is riding on the outcome.
Now he's getting his demons loosened.
Getting ready for a practice swing, perhaps.
Yes.
Yes, we have!
A practice swing. But that crowd sounds very unforgiving.
The nine iron was designed by Dudlap,
created from Modizno, Georgia.
The head, of course, was designed by the Sleestak in the year 4080,
and was delivered through a rip in the time-space continuum.
It's the wind-up.
And...
What a drive!
The audience is ecstatic.
It's a hole-in-one.
A hole-in-one for Dobbs.
It's a hole-in-one for Dobbs.
And so, we reconstitute our great tradition of head-launching,
as instituted by St. Janer Hyperclete's Hyperclesian,
now apostate.
Thank you, Papa Jo Mama.
Praise Bob!
And let's give it up for Dr. Howell,
Minister of Ceremoniums.
Did you get the head?
Did you get the head? A little head's always good.
Post Office Box 181-417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio.
44118subgenius.com
But, you know, he can work his way up at the 7-11.
We got one more for you with Princess We Are Doe.
And it's my favorite love song ever.
It was the words written by Gene Roddenberry,
and the music by Alexander Courage.
Piano
Bridges his dark heart and sing
Remember, remember me
Me
Ladies and gentlemen, Princess We Are Dull
I could never do that thing right
Yeah, they're taking him back
Susie has been saving wildlife selflessly
She had to
strip off all her toxic clothing
to save the sensitive creatures
Titty bugs
They're called
Long-legged titty bugs
That's like true bug porn right there
It doesn't get much bugier
There are two bugs
Oh, you mean the titties
Yeah
Well, we couldn't put that picture on the internet
You know me
You know me, Princess We
I'm not interested in titties
That's on Titter
But I love them
Mauve and bugs