All right, let's do it!
Activate interlock!
Dynatherms connected!
Infracells up!
Megaprestors are go!
If anyone dies, move the body to another room in the house.
Label the body with name and address.
And cover it as tightly as possible in polythene, paper, sheets or blankets.
What a horrible death.
It won't kill him.
It couldn't.
When mankind falls into conflict with nature, monsters are born.
I'm just trying to...
send him home.
Uh, scientists have now identified several genes.
Designer genes that contribute to this crucial sensory system in insects.
Yeah, we're in here, we're doing the show.
Designer genes.
Yes, they're very tiny, but the insects can wear them.
This is a yes.
How do they make them that small?
They have assembly lines in sweatshops.
In foreign countries.
Tiny children with extremely good eyesight manufacture the Jordache genes for the Orthoptera, Choloptera and Edentia.
Everybody's welcome in here, all persuasions and ethnic origins.
Making a customized pair of designer genes for the centipede, which has so many pant legs it causes an entire...
It takes a while to get one of those pair of pants back.
...made, I believe.
You know, something you have to concentrate on.
Spend a lot of time, sometimes it takes several generations to generate.
...the virus.
...seems to hang on...
At any rate, you see the salt.
No problem.
...bombing.
All right.
Here we go.
...we...
...Ion Channel.
Y DIERFER patched ass...
Y DIERFER O gehabt D Tseresel Pez?
...AND
WE D esteem it U Zim decision per m Makev VZGoed to be undestandaìž wodja.
You think you're pretty bad with your pretty trophy wife
You drive a pretty car through your polo trophy life
I got a robe and a pretty nice ring
You bet that brotherhood's a wonderful thing
Guess what, I'm amazing now
And you better take care if you wanna stay on the good side
Of the guy who's got the secret handshake
Should we talk about the governments that I control?
Should we talk about the ants who fade the dice they roll?
The secret things you'll never see
The secret man you'll never be
The secret room that has no windows
Too late to make amends cause the wheel's in motion now
So get up off your knees, try to carry on somehow
You can't escape it so you better not try
Now there's some friends of mine who'd like to say hi
Guess what, I'm amazing now
And you better take care if you wanna stay on the good side
Of the guy who's got the secret handshake now
Guess what, I'm amazing now
And you better take care if you wanna stay on the good side
Thank you, Dr. Howell.
And now, the show begins its descent
toward the lunar surface.
Tracking.
Everything's going fine.
As we land on the moon.
The source of the soul.
Psyche.
The realm of night.
The queen of dreams and darkness.
This is our goal.
Now the retro rockets are turned fully up
and everyone seems to be doing fine.
I think perhaps we'll pull this mission off after all.
After all the uncertainty.
Equipment issues.
There are always equipment issues.
Not being able to find things at the right time.
I'm well.
The laws of physics are brutal.
You have to pay attention.
And now, the lunar surface swings up.
The dust of the lunar regolith blows away
under the jets of the rockets
and the limbs are pressing
into the strangely clay-like soil
of Earth's curious satellite, the moon.
The moon.
Yes, it is remarkable, is it not?
What humans can do
when they put their occupants together.
When their craniums sweat and perspire.
And above the dairy lane.
And those nine generations of the feds long.
Fish, flesh, or fowl.
Every inch of it.
And now the news.
The Center for the Study of Existential Risk warned,
lest humanity become,
become complacent about a robot uprising.
Physicists designed a computer simulation
whereby it may be possible to determine
whether we are living in a computer simulation
designed by our post-human descendants.
And scientists established that humans with circadian rhythm,
genotype AA or AG, tend to die just before 11 o'clock AM.
The robot council has been a little crazy for the Andersons.
You may recall we had some trouble last year.
The robot council had us banish to an asteroid
that hasn't undermined our holiday cheer.
And we know it's almost Christmas
by the marks we make on the walls of the building.
That's our favorite time of year.
Merry Christmas from Chiron Beta Prime.
Where we're working in a mine for our robot overlords.
Did I say overlords?
I meant protectors.
Merry Christmas from Chiron Beta Prime.
On every corner there's a giant metal Santa Claus
Who watches over us with glowing red eyes.
They carry weapons and they know if you've been bad or good
Not everybody's good but everyone tries
And the rocks outside the airlock
Exude ammonia-scented snow
It's like a winter wonderland
And the rocks outside the airlock
Are the best in the world.
Merry Christmas from Chiron Beta Prime.
Where we're working in a mine for our robot overlords.
Did I say overlords?
I meant protectors.
Merry Christmas from Chiron Beta Prime.
Where we're working in a mine for our robot overlords.
Not everybody's good, not everybody's good.
I meant protectors.
That's all the family news that we're allowed to talk about.
We really hope you'll come and visit us soon.
I mean we're literally begging you to visit us
And make it quick before they get a message redacted.
Now it's time for Christmas dinner.
I think the robot can't wait.
sent us a pie.
You know I love my soil
and green.
Merry Christmas
from Chiron Beta Prime
where we're working
in a mine for our
robot overlords.
Did I say overlords?
I meant protectors.
Merry Christmas
from Chiron Beta Prime.
In Glastonbury,
England, a strange
archaeological discovery
seems to hint
at the possibility of the
discovery of the burial place
of the near legendary wizard
Merlin the Magician.
The subterranean cell
was found to contain
what investigators call
telling signals
that the holy man of
Arthurian times had
been there even recently
but was not now
on the premises.
Further investigation?
Is continuing under
international auspices.
A peanut-shaped
asteroid was headed toward
Earth. The Cretaceous-Paleogene
extinction event was found
to have killed the Obamadon.
No new poisons
were found in Tycho Brahe's beard.
German scientists used
satellites to track 1,500
crab days of activity
among giant roaming robber
crabs. Australian scientists
observed that innocent,
fish wander out of their
reserves into a 150-meter
naivete radius.
And fluid dynamics
researchers concluded
that huddling penguins,
though self-interested,
share heat equitably.
And so, ladies and gentlemen,
it's a new night and a new show.
A special show.
And here in the studio,
I have an embarrassment
of riches. I have Ivan Stang
right here, the head of my order,
the church of the subgenius.
Is that not so?
What's that smell? I smell moon
cheese. You smell moon
cheese?
Well, I...
Somebody said he was going to bring back some of that
green cheese for you. I guess it
finally happened. I don't know how to explain it
except that.
You know, we've been listening to that same signal all these years.
He said he would bring you back some of this
lunar cheese. But, doggone it,
how do they make cheese on the moon
without rennet?
Sounds like he's finally done it.
And milk.
They must use milk for moon calves,
but where do they get the rennet?
Are there lunar sheep?
Or...
Well, it's just one of the mysteries.
Sure, lunar sheep.
You know, they count sheep at night.
Jumping over the moon, the whole thing.
That was a cow.
Try it again.
Jumping cows, mean moon
feet, stinking feet.
Stinking sheep feet.
I just don't understand how it is, Philo, but you've got
the best broadcast voice among us tonight.
Give us more of your wisdom.
But I tell you,
I just don't know about that.
Well, sir,
that's just lying with us.
I think...
And then I stop.
Well, that's the way we all are,
sort of stop-and-go mechanisms.
Yeah, that was a stop-and-go point there.
Did anything stop, or did anything go?
Everything stopped.
Yes.
So I won't go there.
Don't push that button.
That's the stop button.
Actually, you see, it's the cue button
for when we're playing billiards in here.
It doesn't really have much to do
with the flow of radio.
Uh, it's ceaseless ebb and flow
up the high strand,
begins and ceases,
and then again begins
with tremulous cadence slow.
And we just stand around here.
What are you looking for?
What are you looking for in a radio program?
What happened to Reverend Stans?
Reverend Stang was here,
but overcome with bashfulness.
His microphone doesn't seem to be working now.
There's only two mics working now.
That's the best.
There's only two mics working,
and yet there's about 17 mics here.
How about now?
Those are decoy mics.
I'm quite confused,
and it also creates a tsunami of reverberation,
which is...
I think that's a decoy.
It's not healthy for children
and other living things.
That's not a mic.
Well, I beg to differ.
Why don't we give Reverend Stang another mic, then,
since his doesn't seem to be connected
to any level of reality?
None of them, except this one.
Philo, yours is booming and bellowing
in loud and clear.
That's mic number two.
Mine is the only mic that seems to be working.
And it's booming and bellowing,
even though I'm trying to speak
in my best little girl voice.
Why don't you cede your spot momentarily
to Ivan Stang and Philo?
Perhaps even in the fullness of time,
we'll be able to figure out this complex problem.
I think we can share.
I think we can all share.
Don't you think we can share, Dr. Drummond?
Sharing is what it's all about.
It's fine with me.
The church's subgenius is really all about sharing.
However you boys...
We always share mics.
It's not a commercial thing.
You can fight it out over there.
We use a mic condom
so we can share without fear
of getting some kind of communicable disease.
Mic condom.
Subgenius secret agent.
Watch.
Watch where you're putting it.
I'm putting it in my knee.
Hey, I have money problems too.
Just look at that.
We're talking about your money.
Stang and Philo are tight like that.
You're putting my knee too close to your package.
Tight like that, ladies and gentlemen.
Now look, here's what we can do.
I'd rather have my knee in your package.
Oh, this horrible microphone moving noise
that you hear at home
is one of the many special effects
put in for your entertainment.
Reverend Stang is going to try to hog the mic now.
I'll have to use the power of my voice.
You have to lean in.
I have to use my effort.
If she cannot use the power of persuasion,
he will use the persuasion of power.
I'm going to use my bellowing bellicosity.
I, on the other hand,
will lean in close and
download my baby.
Hey, I hear you or me back there already
in the background
blabber-jibbering about something.
We're the only ones on time.
Now there's no point in speaking in such a fashion.
You know, I had a crisis of time control today.
A serious, serious...
How did that occur?
Well, I didn't know it,
but I guess my watch battery was running down.
My watch was running at one-third speed
and it caused disastrous misjudgments
in time control, dosage, times.
This is a crazy station with only two microphones.
I woke up thinking it was nine o'clock in the morning
and I hadn't had enough sleep.
And it turned out it was really two
and I'd slept too long.
But I didn't find that out
until I took all of the pills
that you're not supposed to take.
I woke up in the morning
and it just...
Everything snowballed.
Time control slipped away
all because of my watch.
My damn watch ceased to work.
It threw everything off.
You're hurting my ears.
It's going to take...
You need to attenuate your vocal genuineness.
My sense of time control
was thrown off by five hours.
Five hours were taken from me
by a watch battery running down.
Because you slept too long.
They were taken from you
by the light.
By Morpheus.
No, because I looked at my watch
and thought I've only been asleep
for three hours.
I need to sleep more.
I'll be messed up for Dr. Hal's show.
I couldn't believe you were sleeping.
That's it.
I'll sue the watchmaker.
I am so sorry.
The little Swiss watch...
The last little Swiss watchmaker.
And I'm going to sue him.
I'm a bit...
He's a little bit of a Chinese
Swiss watchmaker.
I'm an American.
I can sue that Swiss bastard.
He's a Chinese Swiss watchmaker.
Put it in one of his banks.
Working in a sweatshop.
Trying to make the best of it.
Best watches he can.
Actually, I know just how...
You're trying to hold it against him.
You know, the thing is
I know just how the last
Swiss watchmaker feels.
Because I'm the last
16mm film editor.
Yeah, that's true.
Like being the last
Swiss watchmaker.
Can you imagine being
the last Brontosaurus?
Yeah.
I can't even imagine
being the first one.
Or the last...
Well, the first one
would have been something...
I had the wrong head.
It's a lonely life.
Wrong-headed.
Don't make too much
of that silly, wrong-headed story.
The Brontosaurus
was a massive, wrong-headed beast.
There are people who believe
that Brontosaurus
is still a valid genius.
But what was wrong
with his head, supposedly?
The head of Camarasaurus supremus
was used by Professor O.C. Marsh.
I, Othniel Charles Marsh,
shall be world famous.
I shall call it
the Brontosaurus,
or Thunder Lizard.
He was a good scientist,
but he was just anxious
to get that dinosaur
up there.
And they didn't have a head,
so they said,
well, what about that Camarasaurus
that was found
several miles away?
It's basically
the same kind of creature.
Let's just use his head.
Nobody will know the difference.
I will make a fool
of my rival,
Edward Drinker Cope.
That pathetic,
that Quaker nut,
that crazy man.
Cope was also
a good scientist,
and recently,
crazy scientists
unearthed his skull
and took it on a ride
around the American southwest
to very...
In fact, his whole head,
I think,
What?
Yeah, they took Cope
around some slackers
that some millennial idiots
thought it would be cool
to dig this guy up
and carry his head
to special sites
congruent with the history
of paleontology.
Now, ladies and gentlemen...
Speaking of heads
being carried around...
Hey, we've got a whole
new religious ritual
we can do now.
We have a problem
with only two active microphones
in the studio,
even with all channels on,
and I don't know
any other way.
The only channel
that isn't on
is the phone channel,
if someone should call.
Oh, I see.
Oh, well, we can call it,
I guess.
But why should I complicate
the already twisted
and tangled matters
by inviting
a raucous phone call
to interrupt us?
That, I would prefer,
would not happen
at the moment
until perhaps we can...
Yeah, I had a great question
to ask,
and I forgot it now.
Well, it may come
bubbling up
to your mind.
You know, I do hear thumps
when you thump
the microphone that way.
I still smell
that green cheese
from the moon.
I smell the moon landing
earlier.
We have all the windows open
and the door.
Lean down
by those microphones
and make more sounds,
and perhaps
it is possible
that we're...
Boo, boo, boo, boo, boo.
Hey, baby.
Can't hear a thing,
so this is no help.
Try the other one.
Hey, baby.
I hear bumps,
but of course
one should never bump
into your...
Hey, baby.
This microphone's working.
Well, how about...
This is the one
that has always worked
and will always work.
Yes, that one is cooking
with gas.
The rest of them
are slackers.
A bunch of slackers.
Slackers.
These microphones
are simple decoys.
They're here to attract
other, better microphones
into the room.
Maybe they're not
turned on or plugged in,
but how about you?
Are you turned on?
Microphones like
the congregate and flocks
and various other...
Ah!
Uh-oh.
No, no, no.
Get out of here.
We're fine.
We're not...
Peppy happens.
Hey, what's that scary noise?
It's the...
presence of, uh...
tiny cherubim, uh...
on the staircase.
It's ghost music, man.
Is that my teeth chattering
or yours?
That's my teeth chattering.
That's your teeth chattering
on top of my teeth.
If that's my teeth chattering
and your teeth chattering...
You're way too close.
Then whose teeth
are those that aren't chattering?
Those are Hal's teeth.
Whose teeth are those
over there on the table?
That's Peppy's teeth.
Oh.
They're all chewed up.
You see, yeah,
they've been chewed up.
And the dog chewed on them.
And the dog chewed Peppy's teeth up.
The dog liked the flavor
of Peppy's saliva.
Yep.
That's the master's spit.
Old Peppy.
If you was a dog,
you'd lick up that spit.
That makes me want to sing
a song about old Peppy.
Peppy got some spit
that tastes good to a dog.
That's about all
I can think of that song.
That's the essential part.
And a chicken diddler
went to bed.
Went to town one day.
Chicken diddler
said to get fiddler.
Where can we find a good lay?
Good old chicken
will get the chicken diddlin'.
And the fiddler
went to fiddlin' and fiddlin'.
That's so euphoric.
We drove everybody out.
Yeah, we,
they're chicken diddlin'.
No, no, no, no.
Chicken diddlin'
is only metaphorical.
Get fiddlin' and chicken diddlin'.
No animals were harmed
in the making of this
diddlin'
All animals consented
were of 18 weeks or older
and were of consenting age
in the animal world.
I agreed to host the show
That was how this whole thing started
I was out there
I would end up
so brokenhearted
We had one night
That's all it meant to you
Now I'm alone
And I'm wishing
I could stop
thinking of you
I am in love
But it's only a fantasy
to see
I'm in search of
that hairy creature
who cared for me
under the pies
tried so hard to play it cool
didn't want to overdo it
wasn't I the lovesick fool
sending you a big bag of suet
and a red rose
I thought at least you'd call
was I so wrong for expecting
something more
nothing at all
I am in love
but it's only love
it's only a fantasy
I'm in search of
that hairy creature
who cared for me
under the pies
close my eyes and I see you there
musky smell of your madden
and your eyes
I'm in search of
that hairy creature
who cared for me
didn't want to overdo it
wasn't I the lovesick fool
tried so hard to play it cool
didn't I the lovesick fool
musky smell of your madden
just living day to day
crushing the heads and the hearts of small things
going away
I am in love
but it's only a fantasy
I'm in search of
that hairy creature who cared for me
under the pies
I am in search of that hairy creature
an anodyne to the restless
spirits than to give
an ear to this program.
The soothing strains
of Dr. Howell's voice
will comfort you
and lead you off
into the bosom of Morpheus.
Well, ideally
you want to take a detour
before you go there, but the idea is
that one should be open to
all possibilities and sensations.
Soon you'll be suckling on
Morpheus' nipples.
Once again, that's too close.
Too close.
The milk of slumber.
Ha ha ha.
Nor Morpheus
but distended
nipples.
They're so old
and yet so stout.
The god of sleep
being mocked by Philo.
Perhaps when you toss and turn
on your restless couch,
your regret inflaming.
I'm sorry, Morpheus.
I didn't mean to make fun of your nipples.
They're not really that big.
A sleeping pill fatter than Fat Man
or Little Boy in order to
sack out after the god of sleep
withdraws his feathery wings.
I guess you can't
stop a guy who's determined
to do what he's gonna do.
I'm just trying to get something back there.
I think maybe I can recover
if I think of the right combination.
If only I could nestle in the
moobs of Morpheus.
But it has denied me
for I mocked him.
Just how much
do you want to?
Do you really, really want to?
I'm not sure.
I've been dreaming of
and I'd like to swim beside you
getting dizzy in your way
getting close enough to touch you
getting brave enough
to take you into my arms
and bring you down
to be with me.
But I can't do that thing anymore.
I can't be the thing I was before.
Maybe I am better off alone
because I crush everything
and I crush everything
and I crush everything.
My body's strong
My will is weak
I got pretty nice arms
but I hate my being.
And the dolphins are all phonies
they seem nice enough at first
but they pretend to be your friend
until they see you at your worst
and then they leave you
without a word
they swim away.
So I can't do that thing anymore.
I can't be the thing I was before.
Maybe I am better off alone
because I crush everything
and I crush everything
and I crush everything.
And everything I want I take
and everything I love I bring.
And everything I love I bring.
I lie away.
Did the stars come out?
Did the world spin round?
Does it matter that much
When you're ten miles down
In the light that filters down
Into my giant yellow eye
I can see the sails unfolding
Stretching wide against the sky
And I forgive them
I forgive and I let go
Cause I can't do that thing anymore
I can't be the thing I was before
Maybe I am better off alone
Because I crush everything
And I crush everything
I lie below
You float above
In the pretty white shit
That I am dreaming of
I went to a new place
Named after the devil
Or that is owned by the devil
That's part of a hobby
I've had lately
Visiting
The devil's place?
The devil's staircase
How late is it open?
Let's go there
The devil's backbone
The devil's punch bowl near L.A.
The devil's navel
The drummonds took me to
Mount Diablo
This place?
This is nice
The devil's mountain
So this is Satan's kingdom
We went to Monte Diabolo
They named the best places
After the devil
To scare away the wimps and hanks
The devil's kneecap
Remember that?
The earnest Christians
Won't go to
Won't flock to the
Place names of the devil
The devil's elbow
And that leaves more room for us
There's privacy trails
Wherever you see
A canyon
Named after the devil
Or a city
Or a sex toy
Or a cavern
Or a devil's testicles
Or a flesh like canyon
Or mountain dildo
Those are always good places
Because the
The hoi polloi stay away from them
For superstition
Obvious superstitions
We go to those devil places
That kind of devilish hole
I don't want to go to that devil's hole
I'm going to that devil's golf ball
That old crack hole
The fact is that we're far too down
On the devil
And the devil has a lot of
A lot of
Of
Case
All these places named after the devil
In various locations
Yes
Like the devil's hop yard
Well they're tricky though
The devil's golf courses
Would be the worst place
To play golf
The devil's anchovy bowl
And the devil's punch bowl
Would be the hardest thing
To drink punch out of
You'd think
Unless the devil wanted you
To have some punch
How about that?
What about an impulse of benevolence
From old Nick?
Old Saint Nick
That was poison punch
The devil's poison punch bowl
Well now you see
You aren't antinomian enough
You're still thinking
In terms of the Christian dualism
Between light and darkness
But in fact
That is an imposition
Of a weird oriental religion
It's Jesus that made the devil bad
Before Jesus
The devil was just a fun-loving imp
Jesus was just a prankster
That's not exactly true either
Satan I don't like you
Running around with that boy
Jesus
I think he's a bad influence on you
I think he's gonna bring you down
Well on one occasion
Satan pointed out
That he and Jesus
Were really brothers
Jesus could be the end of you Satan
You always liked him better than me
Copyright
I think if you run around
With that
That Joseph and Mary boy
What's their last name?
Carpenter?
I can't remember
Bar David
They're the Bar David family
Oh yes, Bar David
Didn't
Last year
There's little Yeshua
Dr. Halperin
You were saying
That someone had dug up
Jesus' parents' graves
And found their names on them
They not only found that
They found a body for Jesus too
They found a lot of bad stuff
But you know
People are
There was a lot of confusion
I thought Jesus' body was buried in the ground
Hey, your Edward Cope head
Fell in my Jesus head
I think Jesus' body
Is in Joseph of Arimathea's grave
Your peanut butter
Got covered with my chocolate
Who's buried in my chocolate?
It's buried in Grant's tomb
Othniel Marsh
That would be the art of Winston Smith
Oh, Othniel Charles Marsh
You say that?
It's buried in Grant's tomb
That's the trick answer to the trick question
You know my son
Oh wait, I can't
I shouldn't give it away
He's got a screenplay idea
No, not your son's idea
I shouldn't jinx it
About Cope and Marsh?
Nothing, nothing
I read an interesting cheesy paperback
Written in the year of 1992
In the year of 1998
About Cope and Marsh fighting
Having to join together in the Montana desert
To fight aliens
Who were snatching dinosaur bones
Well that's what it would take
To get those two together
They were once friends
They were even colleagues
But they did have their differences
As you know
The paperback was called Bone Wars
And I'm sure that the author must have done flips
When he saw that movie
Cowboys vs. Aliens
The movie's coming out
Because it was very similar
Someone mining the same territory
Thank you
Did you find anything?
Stealing dinosaur bones from the same territory
But nothing
We can't revive any micro
It feels strange on this show
There's something in this atmosphere Dr. Hal
I'm afraid ladies and gentlemen
All we can do is have teams
Take turns at the other microphone
Or at mine
Someone can come and stand near mine
Sure we can pass this mic here
off to the next... No, you don't need to pass anything.
It makes terrible thumping
sound. Instead, others.
Mohammed must come to the mountain.
Michael Pepe, you can come to my side of the
desk, and then we could
both be using this
one microphone, which does have a spit guard,
so no matter how much we expostulate
and pop our peas,
no spit will sully... Puzzling evidence.
You can take my spot here.
Oh, whatever
you do, do whatever
you want with me, but just don't
throw me in that puzzling evidence patch.
Don't
Well, uh,
no one's going to do anything
coercive here.
I know you're a bunch of wimps.
San Francisco
wimpy. Everything's
equal. Everybody's nice to each other.
Give me a hug.
Spare me.
Hey, hugs, not drugs.
I'm giving you a hug.
And then when you get old
and you want to give a hug, you start shaking.
I'm giving you a big hug.
Okay, this works? No.
This works? Oh.
That's some jazzy music you got there.
Well, for Satan's nightclub,
yeah, you've got to, but of course
we are also considering
the mysteries of life.
Oh, and the devil's punch bowl, and the devil's...
Where are we left off? I don't know.
The devil's rutabaga
seed-eating canary.
Yeah, yeah, go down to all through the western U.S.
There's devils everything to the point where I gave up
trying to be interested in it.
I just gave up, okay? I just gave up.
I went over to Bruno's. Too many devil things?
I got two 18-year-olds, and we're going to do coke all night.
I'm cooler than that.
I gave up on giving up.
You're giving up?
A quitter, eh, son?
I'm an ultra quitter.
You know those losers that use drugs?
Actually, I don't know any losers
who use drugs.
I know users who lose drugs.
Oh, yeah.
But, anyway,
the whole thing rests,
I think, on a theoretical construct.
Michael Pepe wants to share that construct
with you now.
I would love to.
Are you missing a document?
I'm missing something which I have just found.
Ah, great. I'm glad you found it.
You should come to this side
and share
this microphone, since we are
bound to two microphone
sharing.
Come through here,
and we'll both lean into this
microphone. It's the best I can offer.
Just like John and Paul.
The two
great geniuses.
Mick and Keith.
Which one would be Mick and which would be Keith
here, between Michael Pepe and Dr. Howe?
And what about Mitch?
That's hard to know. You know, I'd rather not be
a Rolling Stone. I'd rather be
a Beatle, if that's okay.
Really?
James, Paul, George, and
Brock Morton.
We all know the real question, of course, is
Yoko versus Linda. And I have been
one of the few Linda supporters
in the sort of art
avant-garde, sub-genius,
weird person world.
I thought I was the
most of the world, I'm the only one
who liked Yoko better.
Yeah, I know. The new one-legged girl
is good, though.
Paul's the one-legged girl that he
cast off.
And he just kept the other leg.
Right, exactly. I thought that was kind of
mean, you know, give her back the leg anyway.
Okay, now, if we were Star Trek characters,
which ones, not which one
would you want to be, which one are you really?
I feel like Scotty
myself. I'm always running around trying to
fix things. How'd you say, oh, just
give me some more dilithium crystals and we can
get this job done. He's a cool
guy. He'd always snort those dilithium
crystals. Yes, he had a little
bit of a problem there with his addiction,
but, well, every man,
man dreams of being Kirk.
I, you know,
I could never be Kirk.
Well, I would, right, I suppose
I wanted to be Kirk because
he gets the most girls, but
Spock
obviously knows all and sees
all, so as a grown-up, you would
have to want to be Spock, right?
Well,
I mean, he knows everything. We're not talking about
what you want to be. We're talking about which of these
archetypes you ended up actually
being. Oh, God, well.
I wouldn't even get... You wanted to be Spock,
but I ended up at best, so more like
Scotty's assistant. No, I'd be one of
the guys... Runs the parts room. I'd be one of the guys
back on Earth, I'm afraid, yeah.
I wouldn't have even made the team. I don't
know how many people are on there.
Bring us more dilithium crystals and dobsheads.
Oh, I know where the dobsheads are,
sir, but we're going to have to go down to the planet for those
crystals. Well, there are dobsheads
on every planet in every
galaxy, of course. That's the problem.
We've got all the dobsheads we need. We need the
crystals. Right. And you've got to buy them.
You've got to buy those from real seedy carriages down there.
Yeah, exactly. Down on 6th Street. I don't want to beam down
there. Like porn,
I mean, pawn shops
owners. Well...
Beam me up, Scotty. There's no intelligent life
down here.
The dumbest people display that
bumper sticker.
What, beam me up, Scotty?
Yeah, yeah. It's always... That's like
a Rambo song. It's like people who say, who call other people
sheeple. They all sound
exactly alike. Do they know where to find a beryllium
sphere, though? Yeah.
You've got to know when to stop using a joke.
That's a thing. It's like if a sheeple...
Okay, talk, you say it a few times. That was real clever
in 1995. Yeah, but let's, you know...
You know... At this point, if you're
calling everybody else sheeple, you fit
the definition, Dave. You are a sheeple.
Right. Make up your own
derogatory word for
everybody else. Right. If you're gonna be...
We have dozens of them we can sell you.
Yeah. Oh, there's so many
words that are much better
to say than anyone could say,
like, you know, instead of saying
somebody's loaded or bombed,
you know, they're full as a tick.
I mean, wow. I've never heard that before.
That's the way people used to... I'm full
as a tick. Full as a tick.
I'm gonna have to go home now.
Yeah, you're...
Right, exactly. No, I'm not so full.
Three sheets to the wind is another.
It's... My mother used to say,
and I would say, what are you talking about?
What's all that? Three sheets to the wind.
I'm 120 sheets to the tornado.
Boys. What the hell is...
You're gonna have to drag me home.
So sheets, but I mean, sheets of what?
Are these like, uh,
you know, like string theory
sheets of... What do they call them?
Brains? Are these brains?
The sheets?
I can't see Stang unless I...
Can you take this down?
I can't see.
I look the same as I did
last time you looked at me, man.
Yeah, but it's like hidden, so...
It's like, I don't know who's talking.
Well, think how the listeners feel.
They can't see either of us.
Hey, Michael, I think you're the right host.
Lucky sunset.
Oh, my God.
You look like a host.
Oh, my God, I'm the host now.
Probably you folks out there can sense it.
And now...
Oh, man, remember him?
You can do a...
You can be five or six hundred radio stations
all by yourself, can't you?
He was, you know, if I could do Carson,
he was the greatest of them all.
But none of the, you know,
like if I do gestures or motions,
it doesn't mean a whole lot to...
A lot of these radio audiences
don't get the video version of this show.
That's maybe to their benefit.
Well...
You just have to work hard on the vocal part, Michael.
Well, okay, but...
I'll be your vocal coach.
That's on purpose.
They miss out on...
Talk with expression.
I will try.
And wide grimaces.
In a theatric hell way.
Emotional.
It was pronoun.
Yes.
Pronoun.
Since your...
Radio opera.
We will do radio opera the Russian way.
We will do Russian opera.
It's funny in Russia.
Everything, you know...
You say that to anything horrible.
You think up something horrible and then go,
it's funny in Russia.
Yeah.
My son taught me that.
Yeah, really.
Yeah, because they...
He taught me everything.
It's just so...
You know, they're...
It's funny in Russia.
But their soldiers are the most musical comedy ready.
Really?
They can sing all kinds of songs.
And they...
All the soldiers...
Not all of them, but a great many of them
can do incredible dances.
Those Cossack dances where they kick and hop around.
Yeah.
Like on cartoons.
That's for real?
I think it's not just Cossack.
The modern Russian...
I think it's the Russian army.
And they have a huge choir
that sings very hushed, lovely,
kind of feminine pieces of music.
You know,
you know,
Dies Irae and that kind of...
I wonder if the Spetsnaz...
Spetsnaz.
They have a choir.
On the other hand...
The secret police.
Do they have a little...
The Cheka?
Yeah.
Do they have a little secret choir?
On the other hand,
this is the same army
that will just slaughter you
if they take you prisoner.
Like, you know,
like they did the Nazis.
They just killed them all.
Just get it over with.
Just, yeah.
Or they...
Or the American...
You know, they...
People were so terrified
of the Russians.
It's just scary to me now.
But they're chivalrous, though.
They know how to treat a lady.
Yeah.
Take it from me.
Really?
Yeah.
Take it from me.
Give her vodka.
Really?
No.
Actually, I...
We're having Spy Emerson
come on board.
So, welcome, Spy.
On the bridge.
There's another seat over here.
Hi.
Vodka?
Did somebody say
you have vodka here?
I fear not.
Would you like to sit
with Reverend Stang?
He says there's a seat
over by him.
Oh, well.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
Yes, of course.
Oh, I'm in the phylo seat now.
Soon I'll be rotated
on out of here.
Spang...
Stang, this is Spang.
It's been a long,
a long war.
A long war.
Yes, Spy and Stang.
Do you know each other?
Hi, Spy.
Hi.
You know each other?
You do now.
Now you know.
Oh, you have to hear you.
We have to share this one.
Oh, this one.
Yeah.
Oh, okay.
That other one is...
Repeat your statement, please.
It's a sad dud.
This is so close.
I'm just meeting you
for the first time yet.
I feel so close
to you right now.
Well, you are physically close.
I'm sorry I didn't
brush my teeth earlier.
Do you smell my peppermint oil?
Yes.
This is yes.
Well, there's, you know...
Good.
I hope it overpowers.
No, no.
I like to surround us all
in a cloud of peppermint and...
It's pretty minty.
Yeah, it is pretty powerful.
It's just the S.
It's the oil.
The exact oil.
The Earl.
If you mixed up with patchouli,
it would explode.
It might.
We don't want to try
anything like that.
I swore off that stuff,
that patchouli oil stuff.
It's too corny.
Why?
Attracted cops.
You have to be
a sensitive joker to...
Attracted cops.
Pops and flies.
Oh, I like patchouli.
Well, you know,
they mix it with some special,
fancy other stuff,
and then...
Ah, smells like
a 1970 head shop in here.
Mm-hmm.
My head is spinning.
I'm so dizzy.
It's bong water perfume.
Ah, I'll have another
bourbon and bong water.
How about you?
Did anyone check out
the refrigerator?
It's bulging
with alcoholic drinks.
This time,
it's not horrible near beer
left by...
anhedonic non-drinkers
who like the repulsive taste
of non-alcoholic beer.
It's actual beer,
though I don't know the brand,
and it might not be fancy enough
for some tastes.
I came for the near beer
and senka.
Ah, you're welcome.
And we've got a...
I don't know.
K-Rob often brings in
verboten snacks.
He brings in the donuts
and the Chinese food,
lumpia,
which lumps
tend to roll
along the carpet.
We have to make sure
that does not happen
on our watch.
I want the fat-free cream
and the caffeine-less coffee,
please.
Yes, the rock juice,
the tree bark,
the stillborn bean sprouts,
and pure rainwater.
Oh, but rainwater
has acid in it.
The acid rain.
I wouldn't drink rainwater.
Too late.
I'm feeling the acid now.
I even fear it
on my skin.
It burns.
The horrible run
is a stench
of malign burning flesh.
Oh, this is terrible.
Terrible.
Well, seriously,
I've been sitting here
for a long time.
I'd be happy to let
somebody else share
the one extra microphone.
Stang, I'm so sorry.
I don't know how
I can adequately convey
We plugged in three
other microphones in first.
Well, I just wish
I knew how they might
be attached,
and we've had top minds
working on it,
and they have been
unable to fathom
the answer.
It would take
a young, budding
Nikola Tesla
or Pete Goldie
to unsnarl
this Gordian knot
of Alexandrine proportions.
We need to have
like a fundraiser
and hire ourselves
a super wizard,
you know,
chord master.
You know,
there are...
Let's just hire ourselves
and leave it at that.
A lot of things
on the chat thread
about equipment issues
in the studio.
Don't talk about them.
I'm afraid
we're experiencing
equipment issues
in the studio.
Yes, it's true.
For as long
as equipment exists,
there have been issues,
and as long
as studios have existed,
equipment has malfunctioned
in those studios.
And so you see
we're part of a
proud tradition
of radio
going on.
Going back
to radio's
very beginning
here at
RadioValencia.fm
the crowd of
philosophers
doing its best.
Tom Cruise
is so in love
with Katie
At least all his people
tell him so
And while he thinks
that she's a very special lady
It's probably not the way
he'd choose to go
But a lifetime
of longing looks
would cause too much
distraction
Good thing that he's
not gay anymore
Tom Cruise is
Tom Cruise crazy
Just be glad
it's him
not you
If you had
Tom Cruise's troubles
You might be
Tom Cruise crazy too
You'd flash your
big white shiny smile
You'd buy expensive shoes
But you'd be
the only man on earth
Couldn't enjoy
Tom Cruise
Oh no
You couldn't enjoy
Tom Cruise
Tom Cruise is
always getting older
He knows he'll never
be that young again
And when Tom Cruise
looks back over his shoulder
He sees a thousand
younger leading men
And he knows
someday he'll have to play
an old retarded
grandpa
While someone younger
plays his sexy son
And he knows
the world is
Tom Cruise is
Tom Cruise crazy
Just be glad
it's him
not you
If you had
Tom Cruise's troubles
You might be
Tom Cruise crazy too
You'd flash your big
white shiny smile
You'd buy expensive shoes
But you'd be the only man on earth
Who couldn't enjoy Tom Cruise
Oh no
You couldn't enjoy Tom Cruise
Tom Cruise is
Tom Cruise hopes somewhere there's a place for him
Cause he's not of this world anymore
Somewhere in some secluded castle
Poor Tom Cruise sits staring at the wall
And the outside world is always such a hassle
Sometimes he won't go out at all
There are millions who know his name
Everybody loves him
Why is it that he feels so alone?
Tom Cruise is Tom Cruise crazy
Just be glad it's him, not you
If you had Tom Cruise's troubles
You might be Tom Cruise's friend
Tom Cruise crazy too
You'd flash your big white shiny smile
You'd buy expensive shoes
But you'd be the only man on earth
Who couldn't enjoy Tom Cruise
Oh no, you couldn't enjoy Tom Cruise
But look at the enjoy Center
Look at the only place you can buy CR 대한
Here you got perfect poster
A generous went to the Academy
And all of the people in Earsdale
Trickled his way back home
So God gave him the ha Bright
But he valley would be handed to him
Who could bring think that Tom Cruise
And ни one scarf would change
And no one ever gets that
Bonus on your day