And now, Noble Subgenius Knight comes up over the hill and gets ready to slay the ugly dragon of the conspiracy.
See, there it is.
There it is.
Long the eyes.
So easy this time.
Here you go.
Do not over-medicate yourself with this show.
You should, however, listen more than once.
These are complex shows, more carefully orchestrated and more scientifically accurate than any previous form of art or expression in all of mankind's history.
Do not operate heavy machinery while under the influence of these shows.
Car listening is legal but not recommended for first-time users.
Do not in any way attempt to dance to these tapes or shows.
The demons you see during the initial hallucination sequences are not real.
If you become frightened, try not to give up.
The scene, no scene on this show lasts any longer than a minute or so, so don't panic during the hell scenes.
And surface from the show slowly.
At the end of the hour, because coming out of the show is sort of a total rebirth experience if you can do it successfully, that is.
If you have trouble re-entering the earth plane after this show, focus on Bob and chant his name.
And then try to remember your own name and chant that for a while.
And don't eat for a couple of days after this show.
Meet the Soap Genius.
Hour of Swat.
Welcome potential initiates and remain with us for the next 30 minutes.
The next few hour...
Welcome to the subject.
Yes, friends.
Let's just get things moving here.
Just.
Build it up.
Oh, I love these new headphones, friends.
I love my new inner head.
I had my nose operated on and now there's a lot more room inside there.
And friends, this show tonight, I've got so much original new tape and original old tape and CDs from Sub-G Night.
That is.
We probably won't violate anybody's copyright at all this entire show.
Strange but true.
And I guess we might as well get right into it.
There's a lot of live radio tapes from WCSB in Cleveland.
The Einstein Secret Orchestra Swamp Radio Show.
More of that.
I spent last night all night long editing and mixing down.
The latest devival tapes of an actual subgenius pro revival.
A beautiful, beautiful thing.
The sound is not too bad on our new donated four-track Yamaha recording deck.
Praise Patrick Volkerding who donated that.
He's also the guy who markets Linux under the name Slackware.
Slackware.
The...
Um...
Ahem.
Operating system.
Okay.
What?
I'm distracted, friends.
Okay.
Let's go to whatever it is that's coming up next.
Live show.
Oh, and Gary Gabrog, friend, of all people from the olden days,
put the songs of the band that dare not speak its name on CD.
And that's what you're hearing in the background right now.
The band that dare not speak its name, of course, being the famous subgenius unknown band
with puzzling evidence.
Gary Gabrog, friend.
Senator Jay Kidney, who got religion and now edits Gnosis magazine.
And Palmer Vreedees, dear friend.
So let's, uh...
Heck, let's just check one of those out.
Now that that instrumental just ended.
Okay.
All right.
Do!
Oo!
Oh, you poster of dobs
Oh, you scary, scary poster
One coloring, one color paper
If they just hold on and burn the thing I'd feel a little safer
It's black and white, but never red
It's just a creature of just a head
My wall is empty and my bank account's bled
I'm in this pen, but I wish I was dead
Oh, you poster of dobs
Oh, you scary, scary poster
Poster of dobs, why did you do this to me?
Now I've seen everything I never wanted to see
Now I'm everything I never wanted to be
Poster of dobs
And will I be free?
The grin is friendly, but I know it's a lie
Excuse me while I twitch and die
Oh, you poster of dobs
Oh, you scary, scary poster
And I've seen everything I never wanted to be
A-Yes, dear friends.
Poster of dobs by the band that dare not speak its name
For pretty obvious reasons,
That was the early days of some demons' classic horrible music
They were the band that dare not speak its name
The name was of the first water when it came to hellacious noise bands back then in the day.
Money.
I thought you guys were calling it Doshneckys Day.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Well, there's many names.
It does say Doshneckys.
Double X.
What's that?
Druid neckies.
I heard that many people are really hoping it doesn't happen in 99 so that we can have the triple X day.
Well, that's the best brew of all.
You know, that's really ironic when you get to the point where it's like, well, I don't want the escape vessels of the sex goddesses to come yet because I'm having too much fun here on Earth.
On the crap planet.
Now, that is irony.
And perhaps yet more.
Perhaps that is cause for outrage.
Perhaps that is cause for optimism.
Perhaps we should.
Perhaps things are looking up.
Perhaps there's hope.
Yes, hope springs eternal in the bosom and the bowels and ballsacks of those who believe.
Faith springs eternal.
Oh, my faith was springing eternally right out of my old cassock.
Well, it's not enough really to get your attention.
You're going to have to put it right up by the microphone.
Bob.
Your gigantic.
Bob not here.
Put your phallus right up against the mic.
I'm slamming the mic with it.
No, no, no.
I'm slamming my love right against the mic.
No, that's not.
That's not right.
Nor meat.
And, uh, wait, that's not right either.
Excuse me.
I think I'm getting.
He could conceivably push it far back in his mind.
He could conceivably forget the whole thing.
But instead.
He.
He views with a rigorous mind and eye towards the future.
Pushed up, peeled him back down his throat.
Unhand me, you horned fiend.
I won't follow your way of evil.
For my sight is set on good.
Whatever that is.
I think it's what Bob said to do.
Yes, good.
But in that basement laboratory, a stang thought he was focused on something good.
His hands began to grow.
His ears.
Bob.
Bob said we should do good.
Well, now, whenever I grab this thing and yank on it, it feels good.
So I guess that's what Bob said to do.
I'll just sit here and do this forever and ever and ever, like Bob said.
Too much.
It's always loaded.
No, no.
But as he continued to fondle his diseased unit, he noticed that it got smaller and smaller.
The more he'd flip, the more it would disappear from his mind.
Wait, wait, wait.
Where's this thing going?
He thought it was going away.
Who are those people outside my door?
Oh, my God.
The normals.
The normals have taken your unit.
They're after all my units.
Oh, God.
I've got to hide.
Whatever I've got left of them.
Oh, there comes the normworms.
The normworms.
Oh, God.
I'll hide under the bed.
They're going right by.
Oh, my God.
The only, only old guys that got stangs peckers.
He's symbols of power.
He's what you call them.
What do they call them?
Things.
Oh, my God.
They're tearing off down the hill.
Hey, you guys.
Come back here with stangs peckers.
Oh, I'm.
I'm.
My sword.
He's.
Symbols of power.
Stop.
Get my.
Get my symbols back.
Their name.
Come on.
Go get them.
We've got to get the.
We've got to get the flying monkeys, man.
Those guys are already down the hill.
We'll never catch up with them.
They're wearing weird Oreo suits.
And they've got like chocolate things on top of their heads.
And.
Oh, my God.
Get my little pet woodpeckers back.
Come on.
Stop them.
Those little woodpeckers.
If they're not fed.
They'll die.
Oh, my God.
The woodpeckers will die.
Go down there.
No.
You've got to help me.
And give them an offer they can't refuse.
You know, like.
Give them.
Give them one of those.
Princess.
We are.
Hi, baby.
Okay.
No, no, no.
You know.
Dirt on the sex, baby.
We've got to get Stan's peckers back.
Them woodpeckers have got to be fed.
Okay.
You see peckers?
More like this.
Okay.
I'll go down and make them an offer they can't refuse.
Hi, baby.
You sure are cute for one of them sub-demons.
Could us normals like try to give some of your affairs for one of these bags full of
this.
Those old gross old chicken necks we found here.
Hi.
Yeah.
Hey.
I'm going to go get these chicken necks.
She's run off again.
Where's she ran off?
Hey.
She's run.
Oh, well.
I'm a normal.
I'm too lazy to chase after nothing.
I'm just going to sit and get back here and pick my nose.
Oh.
Princess Wee.
Thank you for bringing back my bag of old chicken necks.
I mean.
Oh.
My woodpeckers.
They're a fuck.
Dave.
What would I do without you and Princess Wee to help us?
And now that you have been so good.
But here is your diploma.
Yes.
You have a brain after all.
Here's your heart, Princess Wee.
Oh.
Thank you.
And Chaz, here's your little dog.
Okay.
I'm a very bad wizard.
Goodbye.
And thank you.
Hey.
Wait a minute.
I'm going to go flip the tapes now.
On the manifesto.
It's all just a script.
Hey.
Wait a minute.
On the manifesto.
These things.
It's just that these aren't.
These aren't peckers.
They're not pecker.
Hey.
It's just these aren't pecker woods.
I mean woodpeckers.
Attention to the man behind the drawers.
It's just.
Hey.
Wait a minute.
Where'd he go?
He.
He disappeared.
In a mist.
In a flame.
Stag.
It's kind of eerie.
Stir up the ashes.
If you stir up the ashes, you've come whirling up out of the ashes.
Who are you, man?
He's gone.
Like a phoenix.
Who are you?
My name is Jaffe.
Jaffe?
Jaffe.
Wabungle.
What the hell kind of name is Wabungle?
Jaffe Wabungle?
Is that Polish or is that Italian?
I speak to you through the canyons of your mind.
Hey, man.
I knew I had some rugged scenery going on in the back of my head here, but I don't know
if I can canyons in here.
Jaffe Wabungle.
Okay.
Yeah.
Right.
Jaffe Wabungle.
Are you supposed to listen to this guy now or what?
Yes.
Dave.
Okay.
You stir the ashes.
Throw me around the edges.
Look.
Look, Dave.
You stir it.
Stir it.
Big, greasy spoon.
That's not going to make anything better.
Wait.
Here he is.
He's coming back from the mist.
It's staying with his whole cataracts and many thousands behind him.
Who else could dissolve into a pile of ashes and then spontaneously reemerge?
I smell some yummy cooking snot shirts.
Where'd you get those snot shirts, lonesome cowboy Dave?
Well, I got them from the WCSB, Radiothon, premium price, pledge-based,
place, pledge-a-thon.
You mean that if I called 216...
And, uh...
Well, friends, obviously, we're back in that beautiful pledged era...
And had a brain and had a brain and $75, I could get one of those sacred snot shirts, too?
Yes, yes.
A flooded snot shirt?
Yes.
With the DNA of the president all over it?
Splattered neatly all over the top and bottom.
And look, it looks like a Jackson Pollock painting on the back here.
Look, it's beautiful the way it's swirled around there.
It might be sexual to some.
To others, it's a sign that society...
And look, on the back, the blood and semen of the special investigator team.
Oh, indeed.
Oh, they talk about star sperm and...
We've covered all the ground with filth.
Oh, look, it's Dave Brain on the floor.
Yeah, I see it.
Now, someone just said, like...
Oh, that's the old one.
We installed a new Dave Brain today.
You fools, that's...
Oh, really?
Yeah, if you notice, he kind of moves a little faster.
Brown sugar on that Dave Brain.
Oh, God, that's delicious.
Somebody put a little threon oil around my ankle.
He doesn't glitch anymore and kind of disappear for a second and static and reappear.
You noticed, yeah.
Now, it's smoother.
He generally...
You can't tell that much difference, but he does run a little bit...
A little faster, a little smoother.
It is a good image loss.
Let's drop out.
Is that a faster reading that's going on there?
Is a faster sampling time?
Yeah, much...
Well, about double what the old Dave...
The thing is, he doesn't cost any more than the old one did.
And you can't tell.
He can't even tell the difference.
Well, that's what I wanted to bring up with you guys.
This thing, you know, your image lock thing, how you were saying I was holding down pretty good here and I don't go off and so forth.
Sometimes, at certain times of the day, this thing will hold right down real tight to the floor and I cannot move any muscle or part of my body.
That's right.
It makes a sound like that.
But I can't go anywhere.
So you're saying that that's part of the new brain, the image lock?
It's all part of it, Dave.
It's all in the integrated system, Dave.
Once again, years go by and you still haven't figured out we're nothing but computer voices.
I like this.
And you're a spaceman lost endlessly in the black void of nirvana.
Space caveman.
In a tuna can.
I got a new brain.
I'm not quite insane.
I got a lot of things to do to do.
No thanks to you!
I could walk with the rest.
I could be a pest.
I can sing.
For a $10 pledge, you get an ashtray.
For a $15 pledge, you get a t-shirt.
Yes, dear friends.
And, you know, really, if your local station happens to be having a pledge drive,
remember, the Hour of Slack folks can't, you know, we're on tape,
and we can't tell you to call your local station the way we should.
And the way you should.
So do it, man.
You know, if it's that kind of a station.
What do I do next?
I don't know.
Push this button.
Holy soit.
건데.
fruit.
Fruit.
Ja?
Ja.
inaudible.
Ja?
Oh.
Friends, you're listening to Bill T. Miller,
the Drum Army OBE out-of-band experience.
Actually, that's probably not Bill heard in the background,
but it is Bill at work, I believe.
Oh.
Box 140306
Dallas, Texas 75214
Sex Money Bob
Post Office Box 140306
Dallas, Texas 75214
www.subgenius.com
Slack at subgenius.com
Thanks, Bill.
Whoa, man!
Yeah, man.
Ha, ha, ha!
Just don't out of your mind, man.
Oh, ho!
Oh, my God!
Yeah!
All right, man.
Have a good one, man.
Let's go, man.
You got anything to eat, man?
Gross.
Check it out.
Ha, ha, ha!
Twist one up, man.
Let's get wasted.
I'm trying to come back a little bit anyway.
Ha, ha, ha!
Here, man, I have a sip on the magic lecture.
Go dig it.
Fuck it up.
Seems like all we ever do is get stoned and watch the tube, man.
Let's jam, man.
Come on, let's jam.
Me.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
Oh.
That's what I have in here.
A little throat flush that I can chew off.
Man, I'm still hungry.
Oh.
I'm about to go home tonight.
Four bucks.
Loaded.
Eight forty-seven.
I'm gonna kill you.
Oh, what go, what go?
Nine to six, eight, wait.
Tower off, guys.
Tower months.
Bill T. Miller, dear friends.
Bill T. Miller at
Box 230-221.
Boston, Massachusetts.
Zero two, one two three.
I'll give that number again.
I'm gonna get some shit on my teeth by the way you were moving.
Holy hell!
I might not have been up top before doing this.
Six one seven, lick, oh, yeah.
Losing my mind there.
I think you got another smash.
Yeah, I think I did.
With a bullet.
Oh!
Hey, where have you guys been, man?
We're starving.
We're, you would believe this.
Oh, you wouldn't.
What did you get?
Jayhawk, man.
Oh, man.
Oh, dear friends.
Bill T. Miller, Box 230221.
That's Box 230221, Boston, Massachusetts, 02123.
And that's also BillTMiller.com.
One word, BillTMiller.com.
And that's a CD.
And it's, you know, these subgeniuses,
they do such wonderful work.
And yet they, you know, they never, MTV never calls.
You know what they do instead?
Their editors just rip us off, basically.
That's what it comes down to.
Hmm.
It's time she was disillusioned about him.
She was out of work.
She was drinking.
I trusted you once.
It was simply a very bad situation.
He was out of work.
He was drinking.
Well, I guess every family has to have its black sheep.
Well, it's someone who has a very unsavory reputation.
They're going to ensure that he receives the newest
and most sophisticated treatments available.
If he does now, then he'll have her under his thumb
for the rest of her life.
It was simply a very bad situation.
He was out of work.
He was drinking.
Fat chance of getting that promotion now.
We can't go on.
We can't go on like this.
We cannot go on like this.
I can't take any more of this, Frank.
Take me away.
Get me out of this place.
If it's the last thing I do.
Suddenly, Bob took me tenderly in his arms,
gazed longingly into my eyes,
pulled my lips closer to his and said,
darling, you know it makes me wild
when you listen to the subgenius hour of slack
with the heart-melding Reverend Ivan's voice.
I'm going to stay on insert station ID here.
Then he spilled hot pipe ashes down the front of my dress.
So I slapped him and kicked him down the front steps.
Men are such cattle.
This week's hour of slack is brought to you by
GE, godless energies.
We bring unclean things to life.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Because when you're out,
when you're out having your divitals out there,
in Africa, where there's so many unsaved people,
you need to have that hooded sweatshirt.
It'll keep you safe from the cosmic particles.
It's like having a new brain when you're sending your pledge.
Sending your pledge.
You'll be better off then if you was dead.
If you was dead.
This is not a Matt Drudge or a Nat Dredge pledge.
This is a real pledge.
This is a pledge from the sincerest bottom of your bottom.
You've got to come through, buddy.
We're waiting for you.
You and Jane and all the rest.
Get off it, man, and get on it.
Yes.
Because, you know, Nietzsche said,
that which does not kill me makes me stronger.
And J.R. Bob Dobbs said, that's what kills me.
That which I do not kill only gets stronger.
Now, he lied to me.
He applauded.
Now, that's a good line, right?
Here's the problem.
Bob didn't say that.
Here's what Bob really said, starting now.
Nietzsche never said that which does not kill.
That which.
OK.
Here's the way Bob said this.
The way I say it, you all laughed and went, yeah, that makes sense.
Here's the way Bob originally really said it.
Bob said, Nietzsche never said, that which does not kill me
only makes me stronger.
And I never said, anything I don't kill only goes stronger.
Got me?
Bob Dobbs.
Again, you'll have to listen back to the tape
to even figure it out.
No, I'm right now.
.
Oh, man.
Hey, Bob.
You know, there's a, don't get mixed up to where you, you're supposed to go where the
finger points.
You don't suck on the finger, understand?
Although, yeah, I know, I know.
Praise Bob.
Oh, it says here, rant about the Y2K, the millennium bug.
I'll bet you all are real.
Well, actually, there probably are some people here who are going, man, you're too good.
I mean, it's the year 2000.
That computer glitch is getting, oh, it's two digits.
And all of a sudden, nothing's going to work anymore.
The econocataclism's going to work.
Blah, blah, woof, woof, the, the, I better, you know, sell all my stocks now and so forth.
Friends, number one, you don't have to worry about the year 2000 bug because you're dues
paying subgeniuses, I trust most of you, and you're going to be ruptured up on the ischemic
vessels on X, X day, July 5th, 1999.
Duh!
.
So who cares about the millennium bug?
We'll be long gone.
All right.
Well, okay, may, well, I know I have a little leg to explain it to you.
.
I see my enemies before me like a thousand thousand blades of grass blowing in the wind.
Yes.
.
No.
This is dismal, I'm gonna cut the guy up and leave.
Wait a second, okay.
Let's hurry.
We got one minute .
Hold on...
.
We must get our target.
If we do not get the target...
Wait, he's coming in.
We're going to be facing a lot of...
He's in the bathroom.
Shelby just made some potatoes.
She's calling...
He's in the bathroom now.
We can get him in the bathroom.
Yes.
Come out with your hands up.
So good to get my hands washed.
Oh, what?
What, what, what?
Come out with your...
Come out with your hands washed.
Wash your hands and come on out of here.
Reverend Ivan Koresh,
come out of there with your hands up.
All of you.
We know there's more than one of you in there, Stang.
We know you're...
We have tanks.
We have flamethrowers.
And we're not afraid to use them on you crackpots.
You're costing the FBI and the BATF
over $7,000 billion a day.
That's the American people you're talking about there.
I'm not schizophrenic again.
Stang's behind the door.
Now, if you don't think we can make it look like
you burned your entire building down
while burning your entire building down,
then you've got another thing coming.
Like these flamethrower tanks through your front window.
Fruitcake.
Yep, that's what they...
That was how it all began.
The siege of Dallas.
It was...
The tanks and the heli...
Heli-o-copters were coming in on us.
I remember it too, Stang.
So?
You could hear them choppers off into the night.
Chicka-chicka-chicka-chicka.
We...
We sent the first wave of bobbies out
right into the line of fire.
There they went.
All the most irritating, obnoxious,
the ones that never got the hint,
the ones we always wanted to get rid of.
They were the first to go.
Then there was the sub-demuses that meant well,
but just weren't all that funny.
Yep, they were the next line to die.
Then there was the ones that just hadn't spent quite that much.
Hadn't they could have bought that T-shirt and didn't.
They was the next...
They was the next line.
Then there was those that didn't pledge to the station.
Yep, yep, yep.
Then there was finally...
There wasn't nobody left but me and Philo.
But I ain't Philo.
And...
Who the...
Who the hell are you?
I thought you were there during the siege of Dallas.
You...
Oh, I...
I was the last sole survivor of the siege of Dallas.
I killed Philo Drummond by a knife to the throat
with my own red-gray hand.
You...
You mean you took your...
You took some Philo dough like them Greeks make with peachy and stuff
and you stabbed him in the neck with it?
I killed the emperor at the last second.
It was he that had led to all the evil and horror.
The last emperor?
Philo was the evil devil of the subgenius.
And I, it turned out, strangely enough, was the angel.
The angelic white knight in armor, you might say.
I see.
What saved Bob's word for...
Well, for what it's worth,
didn't ever amount to much.
All said and done, they all ended up on their heads.
They sat back down in the stands, old man.
It's a state of affairs, as it turned out.
Bob, I don't know, look at that raggedy old flag up there.
It's tattered.
Blood dripping from it, but still, it stirs the heart.
See that tattered old time control flag up there?
The Portuguese flag with the clock on it.
Flying over a little tent compound here in the concentration camp on the reservation.
Heh.
Thought we were gonna keep the normals on the reservation.
Yeah.
Is that a thing, huh?
Heh.
I went out and shined up the barbed wire today.
I guess Bob's joke was on us, now, wasn't it?
Heh.
Wish I'd pledged.
I could have.
Yeah, got the brillo pad and went out and shined up at least three acres of the barbed wire today.
So many things I could have done.
Now it really looks like home.
If only I'd have practiced what I preached.
I thought I wasn't the kind I was preaching to.
You never did practice what you preached to.
Empire, emperors and tyrants never think they're the ones they're preaching to.
But it's so meaningful.
And as the years drew on, the boy knew that the old man had imparted in him some special wisdom.
A special strength.
A meaning for his own life that he could no longer describe any more than he could tie his own facial hair.
He knew that his mission was, if not to liberate every being on Earth, to destroy them all in a holocaust of fire, oatmeal and cheese.
I dream on and dream on.
And so he kept the disheveled on the land, the back of his steed of anger.
As he drove east and west, asking forgiveness and strange questions.
Oh, Bob, forgive me.
Stay.
There was a dress.
When they burned down Dallas.
Hey.
Ha!
How'd you get out alive?
I noticed a lot of scars on your buttocks.
It looks like you got third degree.
Well, I, well, I traitorously turned, turned against Bob, killed Philo and turned Bob into the state authorities.
Thought I, thought I'd save my own butt that way.
Of course.
Then what happened to Bob and the state authorities?
Turned out Bob was the state authorities.
That was what was the joke.
Amateurs.
Amateurs certainly do.
They make a lot of noise, don't they?
Amateurs.
Mere amateurs.
Well, that actually looks like something psychosexual.
Two pounds, 200 miles by the year 2000.
Yeah, friends, let's drag ourselves up out of this morass of nostalgia and sadness and look ahead to the future.
But wait.
Chaz just displayed to us a photograph in model rocketry magazine of a spaceship built by a common human.
Well, or subterranean.
A genius.
We don't even know.
A bipedal earthling.
It was exploding dildos, dang.
It wasn't even a part of a company.
An amateur.
An amateur spaceship builder.
That's a photo of an exploding dildo.
A mere upstart.
It looks good.
It's not a real one, dang.
It was an exploding dildo from the back of that Dirty Bee book you brought in.
It was?
Yes.
Now, but this one.
Right here.
Look at the tail on that thing.
The beautiful common tail.
Chaz's.
Look.
Say, wouldn't this be a good picture?
The rocket fuel booster is getting solid.
I think I'll build that one.
Oh, that looks like one of those Buck Rogers.
That other one was built by a piker.
Yes, by a piker.
The Mars to Venus Express.
Oh, it is the Mars to Venus Express.
And look at all the little windows you can look out at the cosmos floating by.
Oh, you can play it like a flute.
He's kind of got this sort of evil look in his eyes.
Who's that?
The guy in the Lunar Express?
The evil look there.
Like, he's up to no good.
Yes, he is up to no good.
I'm afraid that.
I think, sure, this is just an amateur rocket,
but it can hold some professional anthrax germs.
Okay, now let's remember this is radio,
so it is holding anthrax germs,
but you have to make, like, sort of a...
It was a long silvery tube-like thing,
and it had tube-like wings coming out of it,
and a bunch of this red dust shooting out of the butt of it.
Okay, that was a brief description.
I didn't mean to make you go asleep.
Those were the anthrax germs.
These are the germs leaving the...
used as part of the fuel of the amateur rocket,
zooming over football stadiums in Kansas,
over McDonald's in California,
over the Eiffel Tower in France,
spreading coughs and sneezes and conniption fits
and heart attacks wherever it went.
And in the liquid...
It's mutated subgenius anthrax pills
raining down upon all the cities over which it flew.
And it was a beautiful sight.
The Christmas gift rocket of the subgeniuses.
The first amateur launching of a special...
They called it Santa's Big Helper.
Sycanta's Gigantic Psycho Helper.
And the payload was only two pounds.
It was locked in the moon page.
Two pounds can make a lot of really potent germs.
Now, can you actually make a solid fuel
out of...
the lodgings of the moon page?
Absolutely.
Solid fuel from your moon pants?
I think so.
Yes, yes, it's absolutely true.
It's like a ducks and geese kind of thing.
It goes back on its shell.
Yes, and it's a very, very synergistic experience.
Perhaps it is like a stuffed snake
in a forest of underwear.
Why, it's bleep out!
It's bleep out!
Why, I can smell the hair growing around me.
I just found it.
Wow, you're live and I'm on the phone.
Look it, here's a picture.
I can tell you're miked tonight, Sang.
No, no, it's my operation has made my voice
sound so much more hollow.
It's bleep out!
Hot
drivel night
underneath
fluorescent skies
bon, fires rage
strange
wild ways
Shouting three kinds of faces
In the guise of a fire in the air
The wind kisses the burning glass
You can hear the fire in the lines
You can hear them cry
Be the jewel of all my life
Never a tear on my heart and breath
Lie, paralyzed, a brave prey
Who lives dying and is surrounded
By angry spirits, hunters
They really are.
And at the same time, they never admit that to you.
And again, it's because of the saying, well, they're just like us.
We're just like any other religion.
It's not, I mean, come on, face it.
It's not that we love Bob all that much now.
It's really that we like the idea of the rest of them burning in hell forever.
Just like any other religion at least will come out and admit it.
But, no, man, because, you know, when they get saved, it proves they're right and everybody else is wrong.
All those people that called you a kook ever since you were a kid.
Remember when you were a little kid and there was a little old lady down the street probably or something like that.
And you and your little brother would go see that little old lady.
And she'd give you a Coke or, you know, some soda pop just because you came by.
And the nice old, you know, crossing guard attendant.
That used to tell you little funny jokes and stuff.
And your little brother.
Think of all those people.
Those are the people that we're going to kill next July 5th, 1999.
When our prediction finally comes true, dear friends.
People, where are you going?
On each Sunday morning.
While you pray to your monster.
The kids are home watching porn.
And do they really see.
Beyond rose crowns of thorns.
That the mall that they're building.
Is where my red brother was born.
There's only one sin.
Is a dirt taxi and a bit
And a down from above.
And the down from above.
There is no change for me.
People dying in guilt.
people die in guilt.
Instead of living in love.
Is that all there is to the sinful present.
People dying in guilt.
are being converted to father men.
Instead of living in love.
How can minds be hidden completely from future attention.
Why do we live in the middle of nothing at all?
And other people kill life,
This is a love cult, isn't it, Ian?
He must be living in the leap.
Well, it was more like a cheap date cult.
That's it.
And you know, friends, the ones who most hate the queers and homosexuals and preverts and other weirdos,
those who most hate homosexuality, I think, are the ones who are most terrified of catching it.
You know?
I think that's what's really behind that.
Now, me, I'm a bisexual.
When you bite up from our sales table, I come.
Okay?
That's my sex thing, in case anybody ever wants it.
That's what I get off on.
But, you know, friends, we need those weirdos and perverts.
They're the only thing standing between this society and total normalcy, I think, someday.
I don't care if there's hair around.
I don't care if there's hair around it.
Come on, let's go in deeper.
That's what Leifo said one night.
Yes, friends.
The conspiracy is real.
There's a lot of stuff.
You know, you look at subgenie shit and go, well, you know, I don't know about Bob.
I know he's kind of hard to get hold of.
And I don't know about these aliens from Planet X and all that.
But, you know, when they talk about the conspiracy, I think they're talking about the conspiracy.
I think I know what they mean.
They must be talking about, you know, the conspiracy that killed John Kennedy and the
Dealey Plaza.
No, no.
No, man.
They mean like the bigger conspiracy of the fashions and the trends, man, that make you
feel like you're not cool unless you just spent $150 on a haircut that shows that you
don't care how you look, man.
Or they go, no, it's a conspiracy of the crashed UFOs on the air bases, blah, blah, whoop,
whoop, and so forth.
Friends, if only.
If only.
If only the conspiracy was that smart, we'd be able to deal with it.
We're talking about a conspiracy that doesn't even know it's a conspiracy.
And it is real.
And it really is the conspiracy of the normal people.
And they mean well.
But friend, what are you going to do?
Understand your enemy to death?
You already understand the normal.
And there's nothing you can do about working that job if you hate that.
I mean, you can quit your job.
There.
So, you want to do it.
I mean...
I don't want to.
I want to, man, yeah, I just don't want to.
I tried to outsmart幫 ski.
I tried to make好 spell out your best day.
I didn't like the shortcut, the vulgar name.
Yeah, I'm saying that.
Well, anyway...
Why don't we sing it here?
But my favorite part is that nobody on the show really's going to need this song.
I'm just gonna...
But here?
There's no raw music, so...
Well, I love the пут த Now, awake people.
I ran into somebody the other day who said,
Reverend Stang, I think all your stuff sucks,
but you guys played the first Devo song I ever heard.
I never heard them on the radio.
I heard it on your weird subgenius show.
And this person later went on to run the Devo fan club or something.
Another person came up and said,
well, I don't understand this, but you guys played, you know, what was it?
It was like the Fireside Theater.
The first time I ever heard of Fireside Theater is from you guys.
Nobody ever talks about that stuff.
Well, friends, the conspiracy is real,
and the Church of the Subgenius,
we may not be good for a whole lot, but we're good for something.
We've somewhere out there is some guy that didn't,
or some woman that didn't kill itself at that particular moment
because found out just in the nick of time
it wasn't the only crazy mother in the neighborhood.
There were.
Others around who were just as weird.
And therefore that person didn't die,
and someday that person will go on to create a cure for cancer or AIDS
or something like that.
We'll never know that we did the right thing,
but somewhere along the line,
in between all those pipe loads of cattle crops that we lost,
Bob must have done something right.
So, you know, friends, like I said,
you know, we don't join Church of the Subgenius
because you want to be together.
You don't want to be together with a bunch of other weirdos
living around.
You don't want to hang around with these people all day.
You know, maybe a few of them,
but what you really want is just to be left alone,
be left in peace, do your own slack the way you want it.
Friends, I'll say it one more time.
You can be alone with Bob Dawes.
By the hands of...
And you can...
Well, you can be alone with Bob.
All by yourself.
You can be...
Like a IoT with a battery.
This thing's just not working.
We got two more.
Oh, and we got three more,
just for this one.
So, Bob Dromfield
and I were on the same side.
Just like four lights.
But, dude, you know,
and I dunno what said that.
everyone dumped the開greners on putting theiniers back next to theISTGX,
cold bucket
from the hands
above
from the hands above
empty pocket
like the devil's
gotta buy outside
of it
like the heat from a
stone cold locket
like the hands
above
ticking like a clock
like the hands above
taking you round the block
like the hands
above
like the hands above
gonna charge up
that rocket
like the hands
above
turning your life
into a rocket
Sh sais that $30
banished pocket
我們把 Summer
Sun제라고
from the hands
above
to the
hand
of love
ru
take first
all
but it's also Him.
If you're in this room hearing this right now,
it's because you're in exactly the right place
that Bob wanted you to be
for you to be able to hear what we're saying right now.
By the hands of Bob.
Burning you down.
Turning you around.
From the hands of Bob.
Slopping you upside the head.
Make you wish you were better off than dead.
From the hands of Bob.
Oh, those hands were giving me the eye.
And I'll never say goodbye.
From the hands of Bob.
Our friends by the hands of Bob.
Someday it's gonna be.
By the hands of Bob.
The world will take a peek.
From the hands of Bob.
You're gonna hear a sight and a sound.
The world comes tumbling down.
From the hands of Bob.
Gonna knock you off your feet.
Gonna keep you out of your seat.
From the hands of Bob.
Make you come here again.
Like you're doing a bad Bob Dylan imitation.
From the hands of Bob.
You will be felt up.
You will be beat up.
From the hands of Bob.
You'll be bandaged and healed.
You'll get your whole brain healed.
From the hands of Bob.
Hands of Bob.
You'll hand your money over to.
The hands of Bob.
Send that $30 in.
To the hands of Bob.
I don't know what I'm gonna say now.
From the hands of Bob.
They'll probably explain it.
I don't think they will.
From the hands of Bob.
Oh speaking of pills.
I probably got some in the pill.
From the hands of Bob.
By the hands of Bob.
Blipo, you look great.
Oh, this is a beautiful toffeta dress, Blipo.
I have never seen you stacked up in anything like this before.
I'm in a panty forest on 52nd Street.
How intimate. Tell us more.
Intimate and yet lingerie.
Are any of those panties edible?
I don't know. I don't think so, no, because they were all washed.
Well, over on Lex, there's like a dildo village, I guess, that you can wander through in the middle of the night.
That's an apartment complex, the dildo village apartments.
We were just showing those tonight as part of the...
How much do those go for?
Is it okay to say dildo on the radio now?
I don't think so.
Oh, okay.
No, a dildo's not a real object. It's a fake word, so we can say it.
Let's not say that one anymore.
It's a character from Lord of the Rings.
Yes, yes, exactly.
Lord of the Rings, actually. The Harvard Lampoon...
Dildo Dabbit.
No, yeah, it was Dildo the Hobbler, because I guess his knees had been bruised after crawling through that wonderful, numinous village down there on Lex.
I would not talk about that.
It's what they make that herb pizza with, isn't it?
The dildo?
Can you give us a list?
It's the rest of everything we're not supposed to talk about.
Don't talk about the pumpkins and the squirrels. The squirrels inside the pumpkins.
Oh, man.
I wonder how many of the kids are going to notice that this year.
Well, you know, we just did a revival here in town, and there was a pumpkin on the stage the whole time, and not one subgenius grabbed it and, you know...
A veiled one.
Not one.
I checked it for squirrels.
Yes, they had pumpkin carvings all across the land, and so many children were bitten by those rabid squirrels that they had to...
They put many of the pumpkins to sleep, and they were, you know, not even tired yet.
Well, that's how squirrels are born. They appear in baby pumpkins.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah. It's probably the only case of, like, you know, mammal parthenogenesis.
That's silly. That's a superstition.
Man, that's like hog snakes squirting blood out of their eyes. It's not even hoop snakes. It's like Gaius Gudis' and the Loch Ness Monster.
It's like Bigfoot.
Have you ever walked by an ancient penguin and it was biting itself?
What?
Have you ever walked by a hoop snake when it's biting itself? And it's rolling down the...
That's a country legend. That's an old wives' tale.
Yeah, that's a form of olfactory...
That's Eric's nonsense.
Yeah, that's olfactory snakes. I mean, that's a...
And people have seen it.
I've seen it. In fact, I've been involved in the actual snake rituals themselves with the hoop snakes.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
No, no, I was.
And what they do is they start to...
They make you stand in the middle, and they start to roll around you in a clockwise direction.
The snake?
The snakes are the people.
The hoop snakes. They put their tails in their mouths, and they start to roll.
Like a little trapezoid. No, I mean a circular thing, and you're doing it like one of those people with a hoop, like in the 1890s when there was a game.
Right, exactly. And you have to wear the little pirouette, the little Perot hat.
Little Ross Perot hat and a tutu.
For the pirouettes.
Ross Perot, the little white clown hat.
Well, what about the pirouettes? You have to dance, too, right?
Right, right. And you have to really be good at toe dancing.
This is nonsense. What is this?
What does this have to do with Bob?
This is pure nonsense.
What does this have to do with the word, the doctrine of Connie?
Connie's panties. What does this have to do with...
Froppage.
With froppage, or...
Or rocket froppage.
Rocket froppage, yes, yes, yes.
If you follow the snakes long enough, okay, they get you into the state, and then you can be possessed.
You can actually... This is one of the few times you can be possessed. A man can be possessed.
Pennsylvania?
No, a man can be possessed by the spirit of Connie in Pennsylvania, yeah.
Well, you said a certain state.
I'm wondering what the hell state you gotta go to get possessed by Connie in your underwear.
Is that like between climax and intercourse in Pennsylvania?
Yes, yes, in fact. That's where the hoop snake ritual takes place.
Okay.
Yeah, yeah, and that's the only state where it's okay for men to turn into Connie.
And they want everybody to come there, but they really don't have the...
Yeah, exactly, and they do, and that's the thing. It's the only time that you can be a man and then come...
Coming is believing.
...to the place that they are, you know, in the place, whatever.
Absolutely.
And everything comes together.
It comes together there, yeah.
I think I'm gonna stay in Texas.