Test, test, test, test. How do the channels balance out?
How do the channels, channels balance out?
How's the channel balancing, balancing, balancing, balancing, balancing out?
This is gonna be the crazy show.
Do I seem edgy?
A little.
You know, I quit smoking about a week ago, and, uh...
Yeah, me too.
It's been like boring a wild hare of ass.
I mean, I can't do anything right. It's just, uh...
Look, let me just chill out.
I know what you mean.
We'll relax. You put up 500,000, I put up 500,000.
We're partners.
That's it, buddy.
We're all locked in.
Locked in. Let's... All right.
500, of course, I'll sign it right now.
Five.
Uh, we expecting someone?
Oh, yeah.
That's Bobby.
Bobby.
Oh, no.
It ain't Bobby.
It's the tobacco demon.
Tobacco demon.
And it's designed to get you off nicotine for good.
That's a good deal, right?
It worked for me.
Yeah.
Go for it.
Now, let's get back to the celebration.
Ah!
If justice...
And for only this Swift in the real world.
Bob, little Ivan has been issuing your dirty book.
You rotten ratfeet bitch!
I'll get even!
That's my Boyle.
All firm and tumescent and ready to pop!
I'll get even with you too!
Dad!
You pipe-smokin', talkin' head!
Hey!
Bob.
Yes.
I can be a Bob.
And in this moment...
Think about it.
What have we got to lose?
A standard operating procedure.
If you're going to do this, you're going to do it our way.
Welcome to the subgenius radio ministry Hour of Slack.
Sponsored by the Church of the Subgenius.
The subgenius Hour of Slack that you are about to listen to
is specially designed only to be played on radio station.
Shut up!
Oh, okay, well, you see, this guy's getting excited,
and they write all the jokes for us, and then we just do the show, that's all.
Whose idea was this anyway?
It's not really a live show.
Do you think these callers are talking to somebody?
This is all composed of random bits of information
selected by electronic computer.
No one is here.
Go back to sleep or ask about Theme World.
The top part was discovered,
and it led stairway after stairway
down into the bowels of the earth,
the mummified form of the original Tower of Bob
that the Theme World attraction is based on.
Here is your host,
Reverend Ivan Sands.
The sexiest man on earth.
A young Adonis
who's irresistible to women.
I can't wait a moment longer.
I've got to have sex with you.
The facilities are now enormous.
This is where the young composer
feeds a fragment of it
into several types of music.
I'm going to turn on the tape recorders
and gradually...
Gradually go stark raving mad.
Oh, yes.
But ain't that what you love
about the church anyway, huh?
Yes, well, that's the best thing about subgenius
is it digests and spits out
the best of the old religions
and turns them into something
totally unpalatable for all of us.
If you were here, you'd be a man.
If you were here, we'd be dancing now, so...
On this footage, you can see the
pretendivision.
Pretendivision.
Yes, it's a three-dimensional image here.
Do you get the cable, or are you just getting this on the radio?
Just on the radio.
Oh, well, go turn on your television set
if you want to see the picture.
Channel B-O-B.
No TV.
Well, this is a special set you get.
You are a subgenius, aren't you?
You're a subgenius, aren't you?
This is tape number two in the Word Audio album
Life on the Edge.
Mike Trout continues with the abridged reading
of this best-selling book by Dr. James Dobson.
Stage five is called Hand to Shoulder,
which is slightly more personal than the holding of hands.
It reflects a buddy type of relationship
where the partners are still side by side
rather than facing each other.
At this stage of intimacy,
a hand to the shoulder indicates
more of a friendship than an expression of commitment.
Stage six is Hand to Waist.
This position is clearly more romantic
than any of the prior stages.
Casual friends don't stand
and embrace each other in that way.
It's just one more stop along the way
to a deeper, more intimate relationship.
Stage seven is called Face to Face.
This level of contact involves
gazing into one another's eyes,
hugging and kissing.
If the previous stages have not been rushed,
it has meaning beyond anything that's gone before.
Typically, it's a reflection of sexual desire
and romantic feelings between the partners.
Of course, many people engage in face-to-face activity
that's merely frivolous and titillating.
So, let's hear it for them.
In the audience,
they're not Memories,
so they can't be
linked to reality
orìnhit,
except
they may not be wide open.
It's possible that the feelings
do Yuan Ming
contribute to the performance of the second stage.
He will treat you so kindly
Till I
Till I will have you
To your heart
Yeah
You hear that feedback?
That's what my teeth feel like
From nicotine withdrawal
Still, it's been a month
So who needs a support group?
It's a patch
You stick it on your skin
We might as well have to take a class on how to breathe
How to breathe is Mr. Yamato's group down the hall
You'll be in that one later
But this comes first because Nicoderm CQ
Isn't as simple as a plastic bandage
You have to use it the right way
Or it won't work the way it's designed to
Hey, this is kid stuff
You'll sweat it out alone
With few if any friends by your side
Friends that haven't betrayed you yet
While you wait for whatever it is
That's supposed to happen to happen
You'll sweat it out alone
A passive, angry pawn
Consumed in nostalgic sadness
Surrounded by a world that does not care
Where there's nothing to look forward to
Except death
Hey, well, yeah
Screw that death stuff anyway
That's what I say
I just, I got so sick and tired of it
I'm tired of wanting to die
It was about to kill me
Now, where's my devices here?
But friends, everything is okay now
Yes, everything's fine
I found some new Hendrix bootlegs
I've got the Osric tentacles tape in the background here
And the weather has changed a lot
It's become, uh, it's actually snowing outside right now
I'm gonna quit doing the show in a minute
And go out and watch the snow, you know
Because when it snows in Dallas, Texas
Where I am
You see some spectacular stupidity out there
Me included, it's great
But, uh, oh, and the Tarzan's radio station here
Smells a whole, whole lot different
Than it did when I was in the army
And, and, and altogether
It is a truly, it is a new year, my friends
Usually when, when New Year's
Now, I know by the time you hear this tape
It'll be a couple of weeks after
But I'm doing it right after New Year's
And it usually doesn't, you know
It doesn't make a damn bit of difference to me
It's just a human dating system
But this time it did, friends
This time it was quite different
Because, because my friends
This is
A special year for our planet
This is the last year
On which there will be
A July 6th
This is the last year
That will host an August
There will never be another September
After 1997's, dear friends
And 1997 will bring
The last Christmas
And for that matter
The final New Year's Eve party
And you know, there's some possibilities
For that
There's kind of like a
Interim halfway
X-Day .5
So, next, next New Year's, friends
There will be
We will have a
Another X-Day drill
Anyway, thus, friends
It is the Dobbs-bound duty
Yes, I say duty
Of every subgenius
To celebrate wildly
Every day
After July 5th, 1997
Because
Every day
From that point on
Shall be the last
Of that day
Yes
It has been
A rough transition over to the new way, friends
Because, let me tell you something
It's a wonderful life
When you realize you're nuts
When you realize you're crazy
And things weren't near as bad as you thought
And this week I'm saying
Thank God for depression
I have a story to tell, my friends
Just at the last minute
This angel came to me
I was about ready to end it all
Yes, I was just going to close down the show
But this angel came to me
And showed me what the world would be like
If I'd never been born
My worst enemy was the dictator
The false Bob was his mouthpiece
Masquerading as Bob
The Bobby that you hate the most
The stupidest subgenius you've ever seen
Was your
I mean, well, stupid isn't a crime in our church
But, you know the
You know what I mean
That was your boss
My wife had been divorced seven times
All my
Dr. Philo Drummond was a drug addict
A homeless heroin addict
And all my other buddies
Had all died in Vietnam
All because I had never been born
Among all the subgeniuses
Only Janeer's world was the same
No, actually, friends, I'm just kidding
But, yeah, a couple of days ago
Somebody said something to me
In the middle of my screaming
They said, to tell the truth, Stan
You actually sound like you're crazy
Right now, like you lost your mind
Oh, dear friends
And you know what?
That was that week
That was the first thing I'd heard
Or considered in days
That actually made any sense
That I might be insane
Seemed sane
Because
I hate to get
I couldn't even do a show last week
They don't know, man
You don't know
Nobody knows
I quit smoking about
Well, it's been more than a month now
You know, I'm not going to do a show
Oh, I was hitting the wrong volume pot there
Yes, friends, I quit smoking
That ain't easy
Because we're talking
It was like cutting my arm off
My own arm off with a dull saw
Still is
I have one of the meanest, most vicious
Deeply entrenched, death-wished cigarette habits
That you will ever hear of
Now, I haven't touched a smoke
Haven't cheated a bit
But I'll tell you, friends
As bad as the third day is
The third week
Is the third week
Is a thousand times worse
Because physical twitching and hating
The cellular need
That you can get your hands on
And grapple with fair and square
Oh, that's over
Yes, that's over
The demons
The tobacco demons
In fact, they want you to be
Supremely confident
Oh, they want you to say
Oh, that was easy
Oh, yeah, that was easy
Because then they can pull out their big guns
The psychological approach
And I'll tell you something, man
The tobacco demons are smarter
Than you are, sir, ma'am
Because they still control your unconscious mind
You can clean them out of the forebrain easy enough
But since when could any subgenius
Actually rule over its own subconscious
Using that weak lever of the forebrain?
Hmm?
Well, actually, you can
And I've done it
And I'll do it again, probably
But it's hard
It's hard as hell, friends
Because that old subconscious
Is tons smarter than what you're using
To listen to this show with
And it can figure out answers to problems
You never work out by trying
And by the same token
It can work up bizarre
Imaginary scenarios
To justify anything
And trick your forebrain
Into acting upon those
And the tobacco demons
Will move you up to phase three
And let you forget the cigarettes completely
Oh, yeah, but you're so messed up
And obsessed over something else
That you start to feel like
Nobody could be expected
Not to smoke under such unfair duress
I'm gonna get off of this
I may go back to my confessions
In a little while, friends
But what I'm trying to say is
Warning
Non-smoking can be hazardous
To your mental health
And may endanger the physical health
Of others
If you break a habit
Just be careful that
That's all you end up breaking
And you know the fact that I can even pursue
Such a string of logic
Indicates that my brain cells
Are probably functioning better now
Getting more oxygen
But to what end?
To what end, I ask you?
Infinite pointless philosophies
Rules and formulas
Ranting and so forth
No, no, no, no, no, no, no
I must not think
That's it
Must not think
Now is not a good time
For me to think
I think
Because I'll think I've figured anything out
No, no, no, no, sir
I'm out of that trap
No, sir, ma'am
I'm gonna do just what seems doable
That's all I'm gonna do
I'm gonna ignore all that type A
Coffee achiever urge
I yearn for more hours in a day
But nay, nay
I will stop
Praying for you
For more hours in a day
I will merely accept
That I'll just have to spend
Four times as many days instead
Because what's the hurry?
What's the big rush?
What if you got to lose a little time, maybe?
Hell, I quit smoking
By the time I'm 60
It'll be as if I never smoked
Sixty
But that means I'll live forever
If you don't smoke
Then you'll live forever, right?
But why am I worrying about this?
Why am I worrying?
Why do I even fret about it?
I keep...
What?
They're X Day
Did we forget X Day?
The end of the world?
When they destr...
The...
It's cool
Monkey madness is all around
Turtles flying off the ground
Screaming monkeys will kill your sleeping fits
Hi there, Mr. Golden Honeydew
Or should I say, Captain Poultry?
Ha!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
Well, hello there, little Spain
And what can I do to you today?
Could you hit me over the head with a baseball bat
And tell me a story about monkeys?
Oh, well, okay
I was in a store
And I saw these monkeys playing
I yelled to them to darn their socks
But they didn't understand what I was saying
But they giggled harshly
Ha ha
That was a good one
That was a great story, Captain Poultry
Now could you sing me a song about food?
Oh, why sure
Hey, I'm Captain Poultry
Food, food everywhere
Free the cow, free the chair
Feed me into a hamburger lair
Feed me anything, I don't care
I'm Captain Poultry
Monkey madness is all around
Turtles flying off the ground
Screaming monkeys will kill your sleeping fits
I'm Captain Poultry
Like burgers, monkeys are burgers
Burgers are good, monkeys are deadly
Monkey madness all around
Turtles flying off the ground
Screaming monkeys will kill your sleeping fish
That was great, Captain Poultry
Now could you tell me another story about mummies?
Oh, well, certainly
Most monkeys can sleep
This particular one cannot
It tries to stay out of the water
But the anvil tied to its legs won't let it float
The anvil tied to its legs won't let it float
Food, food everywhere
That cow, that dog, that funny monkey
That funny monkey
That funny monkey looks confused
Let's eat the funny monkey
Let's eat, eat, eat
The funny monkey
Captain Poultry, could you tell me what the monkeys look like?
Well, sure
It's face looks like a people's sunshine
It spears me in the eye
Food make me happy
Food in my tummy
Monkey in my tummy make me happy
The funny monkey
Ahh yes dear friends
We're listening to John Klopp and the Gland Puppies
and we're...
Whoa!
We'll have more of that
Pleasant, pleasant...
I told you it was going to be a crazy show.
A real crazy...
They're laughing at me.
I know they're laughing at me.
Theory.
You probably remember that one.
The 100th monkey theory lies at the very core of many popular New Age philosophies.
Years ago, scientists observing the behavior of monkeys on a remote island noticed that one female,
unlike all the others, had begun washing her food before eating it.
As soon...
Not only were her offspring washing theirs, but all her fellow monkeys adopted the admirable habit as well.
So far, one could call this a simple example of monkey see, monkey do.
But monkeys on distant islands suddenly started washing their food too.
And this is far more than mere proof of monkey telepathy.
This suggests that, just as the so-called cleanliness vibe of an isolated monkey tribe may influence other monkeys at a distance,
surely the love consciousness of the more advanced humans will snowball.
And as more and more become enlightened, a critical mass shall be reached, and all humanity shall come together into the New Age.
Whichever version of it happens to have the most adherence at that particular time.
Now, admit it.
Admittedly, dear friends, monkeys are not men.
Chimpanzees, however, are men.
Regular chimpanzee behavior is like a hideous cartoon of human society.
Even more brutal and cruel, if that can be imagined.
But there are two chimpanzee species.
The smaller, lesser-known bonobo, or pygmy chimpanzee,
leads what we might call a utopian existence.
Rather than the biggest, meanest male, or gray-backed, silver-backed,
ruling the pack through intimidation and taking all the girls,
bonobos settle all conflicts by fornicating.
Indeed, they fornicate all day long.
Conflicts or not, married or not, incestuously or not, it doesn't matter to a bonobo.
Instead of an endless battle, life for the men.
For the noble bonobo is an endless orgy.
Oh, needless to say, as with our primate cousins,
most humans are what we would call normals.
Like regular chimpanzees, with only a minority being what might be called true bonobos.
Sadly, we bonobo types must hide our proclivities away,
lest our more warlike brothers slay us all.
Or at best force us, as they do, to skulk with our various yeti mates in sleazy motels.
But, taken together, these seemingly unrelated zoological facts hold, yes,
profound implications for the human future.
For let us posit, dear friends, that the human race is not only a human race, but a human race.
And that it is the 100th bonobo.
What if, now just gather this in your head and think,
what if the number of human and chimpanzee sex fiends
finally reached critical mass,
and a mighty bonobo consciousness love vibe
spread like wildfire across this earth,
prompting all the jerks and bobbies and idiots and so forth
to see the error of their instincts
and spontaneously lay down their brass knuckles and briefcases
and make love, not war,
that all humanity and subgeniusdom might achieve
worldwide sex paradise?
Why not?
There are three problems.
Firstly, the popular 100th monkey theory is based on a hoax.
It never happens.
Not the way they said it did anyway.
Secondly, even if it were valid,
it would merely raise the dark question of the 100th Hitler,
the 100th Jeffrey Dahmer, and etc.
We've already seen the 100th Limbaugh.
And the third problem is, dear friends,
the bonobos are almost extinct.
Sorry to let you down,
but I guess I'll see you all down at the sleazy motel,
along with the rest of my fellow preachers.
Thank you.
Subtitles by the Amara.org community
Thanks for watching.
See you next time.
Subtitles by the Amara.org community
Oh.
all five men were found dead.
Helene was run out of town
and forbidden to return.
Yes, Helene, the beautiful Hungarian girl,
was just too pretty for society's own good.
Else those guys were a bunch of dumbasses.
The music, by the way, in the background
is Osric Tentacles.
Hard to find, but it's out there.
Keep your eyeballs peeled.
Amen.
Mr. Lennox?
Gorman Lennox?
I'm Bob.
Oh, gee.
Jesus, Bob, hey.
Where'd you get that hat?
Uh, it's no...
No kidding.
Uh, will you excuse us?
Hold on a second, Bob.
Uh, Bob, this is, um...
Roz.
Roz Kincaid.
Hi. Nice to meet you, Roz.
Uh, Roz, Bob here is from, uh, Los Angeles.
He has a very important collection
of, uh, American Western art.
Isn't that right, Bobby?
Uh-huh.
I sort of tricked you, Roz.
I'm an art broker.
And Bob here is a client,
and I'm gonna take him around to some of the galleries,
recommend some acquisitions.
But first, I'd like him to look at your paintings.
I'm gonna recommend that he buys one.
That is, if we can come to, uh, Fairprice.
Oh, Noah.
You're an artist?
Just look at the work, Bob.
You tell me.
Jesus Christ, Bob, what are you doing?
What if she comes out here and sees that?
What?
You're her dreams.
You don't throw away somebody's dreams.
Come on, let's go.
We're on a schedule.
We gotta move.
What's going on?
Is this hell?
This is sound hell.
Yeah, nice shrieking at you.
Listen, listen.
The first side of my 90-minute tape is about to run out.
Hold on, hold on.
My tape, my tape.
Wait a minute.
45 minutes later.
Be quiet for a second.
Wait a minute.
Okay, no, you're not gonna be able to cover this on tape.
There is a blank spot that you'll have to do.
There's gonna be a blank spot.
We're gonna turn our tapes.
A black hole in the air.
We'll turn our tapes over together.
Okay, ready?
Wait a minute.
Wait, okay, wait.
No, you wait.
I'll turn mine over and then you wait.
They're gonna pop those cassettes.
Then we'll cover it.
Then you send me the copy of about the 30 seconds that I missed turning mine over.
Almost ready.
The copy.
Do you ever edit the show?
No, I just record it straight forward.
And then listen to it?
Okay, now.
Okay.
Oh, now.
Okay, now we say the funny stuff.
Now that he's not getting on tape.
Oh, that was pretty good.
Let's practice up on our thinking.
Let's do it.
To see your own brain, it is only necessary to follow several distinct and simple steps.
First, isolate yourself in a completely dark room.
It is difficult to shut out all light from your immediate environment.
It may even cause feelings of pain.
Feelings of pain.
Oppression.
Suffocation.
And impending, imminent, painful death.
Nonetheless, one must persist in blocking out every ray of light until the room is in
absolute darkness.
And in this state, with the eyes wide open, one must accustom one's optic nerves to the
complete absence of light.
And now, at this precious point, a small light source is added.
Its tiny beams light up.
The hitherto darkened room.
Follow with your eyes as you move the light source back and forth directly in front of
your field of vision.
Focus your eyes, but do not strain them.
Watch only the light.
After a short time, you should begin seeing a fibrous mass in front of your eyes, almost
like a curtain or a three-dimensional image of the sort we call holographic.
Now the two rounded parts of the corpus callosum become visible.
The stretched out nerves of the medulla oblongata and spinal column extend behind and fade from
view out of the circle of light.
These are the olfactory nerves.
These the optic and these the oculomotor bundles, appearing like insectile legs.
Then the trochlear nerve and the trigeminal, which a great deal of pain passes through.
Thank you, ladies and gentlemen.
Thank you.
That was an exquisite pain, but I have another for you even better.
Even better.
They say no pain is like that when the trigeminal nerve is appropriately stimulated, but we
have found greater pain.
Curiously enough, the brain itself has no nerves and cannot feel pain.
What does that matter when it is a gathering structure for the entire nervous system of
the organism?
In that sense, all pain, whatever happens to the extremities, is experienced in that
little wet pulsing brain.
Thank you, ladies and gentlemen.
I now move back.
Okay.
Oh.
And go to the ordered labor room.
You're not seen for the first time, Dr.
Lexe.
Excuse me, unveiled a possibility that is.
So trying to leave the vigilance on the ele chaîne there?
Nice.
Where's all the fanfare?
Where's all the hoopla?
What's about to happen?
Yeah, really.
The brain.
The pain of the brain.
The pure pain.
Yes, friends, I've had to face that pain lately myself.
When I quit smoking, it was not pleasant.
But it's still kind of weird.
And from what I understand, one continues for years and years afterwards to suddenly feel that one will surely die if one doesn't get a damn wiggy going in there.
Friends, now what we've been listening to at the beginning of the side.
Well, actually, you know, there's been a lot of KPFA subgenius show from Berkeley with puzzling evidence.
Dr. Howell.
That was Dr. Howell talking about the brain.
Just then.
And we've heard a lot of the editing on this was done years and years ago, actually, by puzzling evidence.
But this music, this lovely music you've been hearing in the background and the earlier song, Flight of the Barfing Death Fags.
That was the name of that song.
Flight of the Barfing Death Fags.
Lovely little piece of music there.
It's by the Gland.
Puppies and Reverend John Klopp.
Also used to be known as Roy Rogers and the Hemorrhoid Rogers.
That was it.
Hemorrhoid Rogers and the Big Pooh Generator.
This band has had many names.
I'm about to give a contact email for the Gland Puppies.
That's ear, E-A-R, ear at pebcac.trippy.
Dot org.
Pebcac is like P.
It's ear at P-E-B-K-A-C.
Dot trippy.
T-R-I-P-P-Y.
Dot org.
For information there about the Gland Puppies and my email address is slack at metronet.com.
Actually, that's Jesus's email address, but it'll get you there.
He forwards that stuff.
Okay, I've got to try to keep a lid on.
See, I get upset very easily these days.
My hormones are acting up without the nicotine.
Boy, I left up.
I forgot.
One morning, I forgot.
Actually, my nicotine patch fell off during the night.
And the next morning, I woke up shaking with rage.
And swollen with fury over the injustice of the world.
And the entire world owed me a huge apology.
I went out to...
What?
Is that them?
Is this the apology I've been waiting for?
Yes.
Yes, it is good.
Thank you.
I'll tell you, though, that day that I lost the patch was like, as Jane said,
that was like a great big old cocaine party compared to that time they shot the living gee out of me.
I was like, I'm not going to do this anymore.
Because it did get worse, friends.
And, you know, you can't know what depression is, clinical depression,
unless you've had it and gotten over it.
Or else, well, I guess if you dealt real closely with somebody who has it.
And I have, unfortunately, both.
The catch-22 of depression is that you...
You literally can't pull yourself out of it, by definition.
That's what it is.
You know, I can get myself out of smoking or not.
But depression is different.
It's bad brain, dear friends.
Bad chemistry.
And sometimes you need replacement chemicals, like the patches, which really help.
Just in order to oil the stuck-shut hinges on the mental slack-shacked door.
If you know what I mean.
And you may need psychological support, dear friends, to get the door cracked open before.
Now, I have no friends, but I...
Not really, but I do have you, dear friends.
And now I'm not...
Don't get the idea, folks, that we've suddenly decided that conspiracy-style mental health programs are suddenly Dobbs-approved now.
That is definitely not the case.
It's...
What we're saying is...
If a pill can fix you, take the damn pill.
They've done miracles with antidepressants.
I'm a big believer in seeking the right antidepressant.
Which may just be froth.
Same thing.
But, you know, if it can...
And if somebody who's trained to circumvent your self-deluding bull-hockey that you pull on yourself can actually do that,
then let the insurance company pay.
And if you're a good person to do it,
you know, if you need five bags of the sacred herb Havaprop Zipulops per day to keep from becoming a serial killer,
then buy the froth and live off the dog food.
But if you quit smoking, get ready for some nasty, nasty, nasty experiences.
In the first week, you start losing things all the time.
Things like keys and wallets.
And...
Passwords.
And you start getting lost in your own neighborhood when you're driving at night.
And you start getting up to do something.
And instead of forgetting what you were gonna do when you get in the next room,
you forget what you were gonna do before you even finish standing up.
It can get to where it takes five minutes to figure out left from right.
Stuff that you would normally do on autopilot.
Like flip tapes of this show.
You can no longer do.
You screw them up.
Second week is a whole lot worse, friends.
Second week is...
The subtle insanity creeps in.
And the act of thinking,
Oh, that was easy.
That first week was easy.
That's what triggers it.
That's when they know to move in.
You start repeating yourself in conversation,
or else thinking that you just repeated yourself.
Or that you would be repeating yourself,
and then you never say it at all.
And you can't hear anything anybody says to you for the first two or three times they say it.
You can read one paragraph six or seven times.
And it gets to where,
even though you can't remember what you did five minutes ago,
you can vividly recall every broken or forgetting promise ever made to you since childhood.
Every little insult,
or slight,
especially by close friends.
The perfect recollection of everything ever borrowed from you but not returned.
Vividly imagining painful,
vindictive arguments down to every perfect nuance and detail.
Photographic recollection of imaginary arguments.
In the third week,
you start believing those arguments.
And you realize that those arguments really happened.
A greatly increased sex drive.
Greatly reduced sex drive.
Completely, greatly confused right off the road.
And crashed into a tree!
Sex drive.
Drive.
Hmm.
Uh.
Fretting for five hours a night.
Sleeping for three.
Inability to remember anything good ever happening to anybody except those you most envy.
Inability to accept the existence of anything good.
Period.
And then,
you've become convinced that you've just been kidding yourself the whole time.
Up until then.
Up until that moment.
Thinking about all this time I've been a sap.
A chump.
Only now can I finally see the bitter truth I was hiding from myself.
How ludicrously,
pathetically naive I was.
How easily I've winked.
It's almost funny.
I know now that they've all been laughing at me behind my back this whole time.
And I was too much of a trusting fool to see it.
But that's over with now.
No.
And you get to where any single statement that might be construed as less than highly flattering,
you interpret as an insult.
It's just more proof of the conspiracy against you.
Against you!
Friends.
You can e-
I got to where I was setting up conversations with such evil Moriarty-like twisted logic,
that no reply anyone could make could be taken as anything but total betrayal.
Or, at best, the most callous insensitivity.
And this went on for weeks.
Although I looked at the calendar and realized it had only been four days.
Ugh, friends.
If you're lucky, you know, at some point when you're quitting smoking, somebody says,
Hey!
You're nuts, man.
And-
And if you're-
And if you're real lucky, it sinks in and you go,
Oh!
Oh my god!
Whoa!
Praise Bob!
It was just severe depression and drug withdrawal and borderline schizophrenia.
Heh!
Hey!
It's New Year's Eve!
It's a wonderful life!
You know, I-
You know, as much as the normals disappoint me, I'd still rather think it was me being
a jerk than that literally everybody else was a jerk because of me.
You know, I-
I can do something about me.
You can do something about me.
You can turn it right off.
But, I don't know.
Knowing you're crazy can keep you sane, at least, uh, until the third month.
Heh heh heh heh.
But, we won't have to worry about the third year, dear friends.
The third year after you quit smoking because, on the escaped vessels of the sex goddesses,
smoking is healthy.
Ha.
Calling Planet Earth
Because I love my home
When I think of all the things I had today
And I think of all the things I've thrown away
I promise to return every can
For that five cent deposit and the good of all men
Cause I
I
Love this place
Cause I
I
Love my home
Calling Planet Earth
A moment of silence for all the short people who won't exist at all.
Cause I love this planet.
Cause I love my home.
One more time now.
Cause I love this planet.
Cause I love my home.
Planet Earth.
Calling Planet Earth.
Well, I see fingers, hands, and shades of faces.
Reaching up, but not quite.
Touching the promised land.
I hear pleas and prayers and a desperate whisper saying,
Oh Lord, please give us a helping hand.
Yeah, yeah.
Mm, ooh.
The way down in the background
I can see frustrated souls
The city's burning
And on across the water
Babe, I see a weapon sparking
Out the sting of death
And up in the clouds
I can imagine UFOs
Chuckling themselves
Laughing, they say
Those people so uptight
They sure know how to make a mess
Hey!
guitar solo
Back at the saloon
My tears mix in mildew
With my drink
I can't really tell my feet
From the salt that's on the floor
But as far as I know
They may even try to ram me
And sell the thing they sell me
Brothers, help me
And don't worry
About looking at the score
Can't hear it
Yeah
guitar solo
And it's time
For a new beginning
And a big bye-bye
Um, uh, Jimi Hendrix
Can be reached at
Dead Rock Stars Care of Heaven
The happiest guys in the world
Were the ones who did that song
Calling Planet Earth
The happiest, happiest, happiest guys in the world
And you can write for information from them at
Get all those pencils ready now
Happiest guys in the world at
Dead Rock Stars Care of Heaven
P.O. Box 1971
Great year, huh?
I graduated from high school that year
P.O. Box 1971
New York, New York
One triple O
Nine
And
Who else?
I think I gave everybody else
That will give
You can write to Bob
And myself
And the Subgenius Foundation
And Jesus at
Post Office Box
Dallas, Texas
Or if you, uh, need to, uh, know
Very, uh, interesting, specific details
And really have something to offer us
You could always call the
Toll-free number
Which is, and this is real
1-888-669-2323
I know it doesn't seem real
But it's real
It's all real, dear friends
And, uh, anybody got a lighter?
Oh, no, I can't think about that
We'll be all right
Everything will be all right
Thank you for watching!
And, uh, because art will keep us pure, friends
Art will keep me pure
Thank you for watching!
And, uh, if you have any questions
I'll be happy to answer them
I'll see you next time
Bye!
We live in an age when many people
Particularly church people
Expect someone else to do everything for them
They expect the pastor or evangelist
To lay their hands on them
Tap them with God's power
And heal them
Or deliver them strictly by the anointing on God's servant
While they themselves take no active part
In the faith process
Folks, it doesn't work that way
Particularly in the case of something so deeply entrenched
As the drug problem
Yes, we can lay hands on you
And yes, we can pray that God will take away the craving for drugs
And he will do it
But you must do something to certify the cure
The Bible says, resist the devil and he will flee from you
You yourself must resist him
Once the devil sees that you have been set free
He will try to get you back in bondage again
First he will try to compromise you
He will try to get you to sell the drugs which you are no longer using
After all, you paid a lot of money for them
And you need the money, right?
Uh-huh
The Lord is able to supply your needs
You don't need drug money to live
God will take care of feeding your baby
Or whatever it else is you are concerned about
So don't send up those drugs
Now failing that
The devil will try to get you to give them to him
He will send the drugs away to a friend
There's nothing mysterious or complicated about it
Let's take it nice and easy
Making all the stops along the way
That's the basic idea
Bonding is damaged when couples scramble the stages
If they kiss passionately on the first date
Engage in heavy petting a month later
Or have sexual intercourse before marriage
Something precious is lost in their commitment to one another
They've not allowed the glue to dry
Perfect
You're a woman
Have sex with a woman