Like to drop by the fantastic bag?
Well, welcome to the Hour of Slack!
Praise Bob Gold and Connie Drag!
Yes, welcome to the Hour of Slack!
La la la, la la la!
La la la, Hour of Slack!
Slack!
It's great, faster than any other leading cleanser!
As well as leading cleansers!
As well as...
Bob!
But let's leave things of this world behind,
and walk now down the path of Bob for this brief minute of Slack from the Church of the Subgenius.
And so, once again, we find this deep-rooted contradiction within the Word of God.
Who He Himself has said,
I am everything, but yet everything is me.
And by this very selfsame contradiction,
we know that we do have some measure of free will.
Yes, free choice.
And it's up to us to decide whether we're going to sin in the ways that God wants us to,
or if we're going to sin against God.
But yet, since He is everything and everything is Him, or her, it, or everything,
one could say, well, everything is everything, so a sin might as well be a good deed.
Helping a little old lady across the street,
might be a sin if everything is everything.
Now, this is an acid-head sort of mode of thinking,
and I don't think anybody wants to go along with such a vague and, say the least, fluid philosophy.
Because we have to have some sort of standard reference for goodness or evilness.
We've got to zero our meter on something.
So why not let that something be Bob, friend?
Let there be slack.
Oh, that's crazy talk.
I think Bob is just a guy with a pipe.
FRIENDSHOP!
Are we controlled by secret forces?
Do you ever get the feeling that free will is a joke?
Do people think you're strange?
Do you?
Then you may be on the right track.
Give me slack, or give me food,
or kill me.
Kill me.
It's time to be manipulated.
Brother, I want to tell you something.
The world is tired of dead preaching preachers,
dead preachers preaching dead sermons to dead congregations.
They're tired of cold services and cold churches.
The world is hungry for reality.
They've had enough of Hollywood.
They've had enough of Nashville.
They've had enough of show business.
They're hungry for the mighty power of the man that walked the shores of Galilee 2,000 years ago
and raised the dead and cast out devils and healed the sick.
And I'm here to tell you tonight that Jesus Christ is still raising the dead.
Oh, he's back from the dead.
That's right.
His grinning skull.
His grinning skull floats ever in front of your eyes
because Jesus brought him back,
and he's lusting for the flesh of the living.
And these things are coming and coming speedily.
We are near the very, very end of the church age,
and of course the Gentile time has already come to a close.
For the archaeologists.
Every day is a hair day.
Slacks are always Jesus Christ's name.
I got just what I wanted from everybody here today.
And everybody said,
NAMIET.
Now I reason because here is inflicted unbelief.
Unbelief is the lifeless body of his sister.
Right now, man.
It's autistic.
It's satisfaction.
Secure my weapon, corporal.
Again?
Again.
Big day.
Did you get my present?
I punched a hole in Harvey Goldman's trailer.
Hmm.
The world owes me a living,
and I want my money back in one lump sum right now!
That's the way you ought to wake up.
Friends, it wasn't your parents' fault.
They were just as screwy as you.
It was the conspiracy's fault.
It really was.
It was.
Friends, the conspiracy has harged fascism long enough.
We're taking fascism back for the people, man!
Fascism for the people!
Fascism for the people.
For the individual, it's what we call patriopsychotic anarcho-materialism.
Now I just want you to hang on one minute.
I want you to hang on one minute, please, and I want you to hear something, and I want you to hear it.
Good!
I just want to tell you people something.
There's some good people out here, and you are insulting their intelligence.
And if you come to this country at our invitation,
and we have to charge you through no choice of our own,
right?
If you don't want to pay it, don't.
I've come.
Some people got to have it.
Give me.
Listen to me now.
Thanks, thanks, thanks.
Bad things today.
Well, to you.
Thanks, thanks, thanks.
Good things today.
I want it to be firmly established that any person that feels that strongly has the right to come to this microphone and speak.
I cannot help the system as here.
It is my job to entertain you.
The fact that there is an exchange from this stage, whatever it costs, has to go out there in the form of music, is the way that the world is made up.
I cannot help it.
I have no other choice.
I have no control over that.
Do it with something that nobody can steal from you.
something nobody can stop selling to you or put you in jail so you can't maintain it.
You're going to have to become self-realized to the peace within yourself on your own.
And beyond that, once you become self-realized, to learn how to express it,
how to experience it constantly, how to use the vehicles that you've got,
whether it's your emotions, your mind, or your body,
to express the divine thing that you discover yourself to be.
And you can only discover that yourself.
People don't care who they hurt or be.
A woman will sell her precious body for a small piece of paper and carry some lot of weight.
But be...
angry.
You'll forget about them and you'll marry some blonde, dull, non-entity
and bear a brood of snot-faced, drug-snorting brats
who can't believe what a doddering dullard you are
and can't wait for you to die
or...
leave so they can kill you or something while you sit there
exhausted, sweating blood, staring at the TV,
pondering your incredible degree of debt,
drinking yourself into a stupor and going,
What the hell happened?
Almighty God of God
I know money is a root of all evil
but it can't stop some people
from doing funny things to some people
Didn't pay a nickel
Money can't stop some people
I ran them out
We're all just going to have to like,
the police force,
the lawyers, all the people that
are running the whole thing,
these hippies with long hair
are just going to have to
braid their hair up,
put it... put on a hat, man,
and become policemen.
become police men, you know, become lawyers, become doctors, you know.
But then we're the same as everybody else.
No, I mean, but with the idea.
I mean, with the idea that you want to change the system.
You can't defeat the system from within the system because then you're just part of it.
My dear, could you imagine?
I mean, Walt Disney is the...
Living in the ghetto, you know, a kid three years old using Mighty Mouse or Mickey Mouse,
whoever it was, for an idol, right?
You can't have kids.
Running across the room for a gray rat thinking it was Mighty Mouse.
Are you ready?
But you can't bring all of Walt Disney.
Well, I can bring almost all of it, or half of it.
Half of it.
I can't bring all of it.
This is Pennywise.
Joan, your name?
This is Sue.
Hi, Sue.
How can I help?
Jim, I really have a problem with impulse buying.
I never have money left for anything.
Oh, why?
Jim, I really have a buying impulse problem.
Well...
Buying.
Anything.
Wait a minute.
Go ahead.
And use some of that money to bring some happiness.
Jim, I really have a problem.
Jim, I never have money left for impulse buying.
A lot of people have that problem.
Take cash.
Good idea.
I feel we really need to buy right away.
After all, money is only paper and metal until you put it to use.
I never have money left.
But you've already decided to buy.
Impulse.
I really think it'll help.
Good idea.
Oh, thanks.
Okay, let's go to line four.
This is Pennywise.
I'm Jim Phillips, and your name is...
Bob.
Hi, Bob.
What can I do for you?
I get confused by all the claims made in commercials.
Oh, this is Pennywise.
Line six, you're on.
And your name is...
Bob.
Caller number five, you're on the air with Pennywise.
I'm Jim Phillips.
I get confused by all the claims made in commercials.
Oh, let's go to line seven on Pennywise.
Hi, I'm Jim Phillips.
Bob.
Commercials.
Oh, oh.
I get confused by all the claims made in commercials.
Oh, well, listen.
I think your first responsibility is to yourself and your family.
The what?
Thanks for the call.
Hello.
You're on Pennywise with...
Jim Phillips, and you are...
Bob.
Okay, let's go to line four.
This is Pennywise.
I'm Jim Phillips, and your name is...
Bob.
Oh.
Commercials.
Hello, caller.
I get confused by all the claims made in commercials.
Oh, and your name is...
Bob.
Hi, Bob.
What can I do for you?
The what?
Go ahead.
I get confused by all the claims made in commercials.
Oh, you sound frustrated.
It's because I am.
Well, my kids and I, for example, love to build things with scrap lumber.
The what?
All right.
Thanks for the call, Carl.
Bob.
Oh, this is Pennywise.
Pennywise.
Line six.
You're on.
Bob.
Yeah, Barb.
Go ahead.
Claims made in commercials.
Yeah.
I get confused.
Why?
I get commercials confused.
I can imagine.
The what?
Well, many religious people follow the biblical plan of tithing.
You may want to visit with your clergy about it, but of course...
The what?
Commercials.
I get confused by all the claims...
And your name is...
Bob.
Yeah, that's a tough one.
A lot of people have that problem.
The what?
Truth in advertising.
I get confused.
Advertising, though, can be a really good source of information.
Because of the truth in advertising policy.
The what?
Truth in advertising.
You see, the law requires advertisers to tell the truth.
The what?
The truth.
To tell the truth.
Truth in advertising.
Good point.
Yeah.
So listen carefully to the wording of an ad.
The what?
The truth in advertising.
Well, then you have to decide if honesty goes both ways, right?
After all.
So, this is Pennywise.
You're on the air.
Hi, Bob.
What can I do for you?
Yeah, Jim, this is Charlie.
Okay.
I've got a moral question for you.
The what?
Wait a minute.
Thanks for the call, Bob.
This is Charlie.
I've got a moral question for you.
Well, that's a matter for your own conscience, Charlie.
I figured you'd say something like that.
All right.
Why don't you give it a try this year?
Okay.
But they'll never catch it.
Well, thanks for calling, Charlie.
Thanks.
This is Pennywise.
Line six.
You're on.
Yeah, Jim, this is Charlie.
Negative land.
Negative land, friends.
Before that, Rainbow Bridge.
Some utopia and preaching from Austin, 1998.
All cut together by Potter Nostril.
Before that, new cut-ups by Artemia Salina, Fernanda Nandi-Lemur,
and old cut-ups from the subgenius Media Barrage No. 5.
Plus music from Saint N.
Memoir of the same coming.
But what do you want?
I want to be a member of your church.
I want to give all I got.
I want to love Bob.
I was in a room just the other day in Dallas.
Well, I did benefit from it, of course.
But so did a whole bunch of old Dallas boys.
Remember this.
I've been five years in the Naval Intelligence Division.
So that I do know a good...
And that was in wartime.
So I know...
I know a good deal of what goes on.
I mean, I had connections with CID and the lot.
And there is no doubt in my mind,
and a number of other responsible people,
that this isn't only just hippie fun.
Behind it is black power, and behind that is communism.
My invisible monster is bigger than your invisible monster.
Nyeh, nyeh, nyeh, nyeh.
And friends, that's what most religions are for.
That's what they're all about.
Yeah.
And you may laugh at that, but I'm afraid to tell you
that according to the latest study I saw,
over 87% of Americans believe that there is an invisible monster
that will take care of them if they kiss its ass.
And friends, because of those idiots believing in that monster,
there is one.
He certainly made a lot of laws that we've ended up having to live by.
But friends, you can...
You can...
You can fight back.
Yes, we can turn the tables and declare war on God.
Now, frankly, some people might say that was real disrespectful sounding.
You, I think you, most of you understand what we mean
when we say we're declaring war on God.
Repent, friends. Repent through spending.
And you better do it quick.
Aut jazz.
Law ofтиz moralis milli countries
What if we settle this with the hellQuė.
For revいます,
Es que yIN
These students keeping asking.
I know that this music will never end,
but there is something you aren't allowing.
Be careful, have a closer listen,
щelis a jisk
Be a sweet首先
And look on the actual floor
Actual floor
It makes them proud
To be around
And take their summer pickies
To treat that night
In Soho Pops
And end up feeling sick
Whoa
You've got what it takes to play
History we've got in play
The dollars they got way back
The question of kids now wanting everything to be free
Is very hard to handle
Because it's hard to talk to those kids
Even you?
What?
Even you
Even me, hard to talk to them?
Of course
Because to them I represent, among other things, somebody who has money
Through this art
And the Traitor's Gate
The more popular criminals
Those darlings of the crowd
Were taken smiling
Into the tower
Rumour has it
That the bloodstains of Charles I's decapitation
Were never actually washed from the stones
Friends, the tribulations
The saucers, the rupture
All of those things that are discussed in Dobbs
The prophecy will come true
But profiting from it all
Of wading through the blood of the baptism of the fist face of Bob
Burning through the titanium steel fort knocks doors
With the power of that mighty pipe
Friends, it will be Bob
Bob is coming
And he will burn away the hate
He will burn away the radiation
He will burn away the fire itself
But you have to keep your hate burning
Friends, you have to feed that fire
Repent!
Quit your job!
Slack off!
While you still know how!
Time is running out
The conspiracy at large
Has, well, between the United States and Russia
Probably has 50,000 nuclear weapons
Maybe 100,000
And we've only got four!
Five!
We've only got five!
And yet we dare to fight them anyway!
Because it's always been the craaaaaze!
People!
Friends, the craaaaaze!
Who are the only ones dumb enough
To stand up and fight City Hall!
Now off you go, away you fly
We've had your money, now goodbye
We've laced you good, we've bled you dry
Goodbye, goodbye, goodbye, goodbye, goodbye, goodbye, goodbye, goodbye, goodbye, goodbye
Goodbye!
Bye!
The mind of the buchos, oches, daffodils and gilders
And a starting symbol of our caesareanity
Majesty of religion
This old game, this big wow, right?
About good hearted way of waltzing
Sashaying into a peaceful country
Clobbering chiefs and saying
That's it, this is my work
Not a piece of lady
Who was stolen by one Catholic
Blood in Walsh's bloody tower
Look who's doing that stuff
I don't think it's on
Yes, B. Peters will accept the bacon burgers
And here the original armour worn by Henry
Has now been coated in Teflon
So those greasy Argentinians
Who don't have freckles
Because they slide off their faces
Can't get their hands on it
How old are the Buried Riders remains?
Well, they're 14 to 15
They saw the Buried Riders
And they pulled his leg off
And counted the rings, you jerk
Big wow
Pop!
And some incision
Majesty
Pop!
Me up!
I'm gonna leave money
Who's by the damned
And now a rare Bob hymn
From the clench of the red-eyed loon
Minneapolis circa 1982
My life has changed in many ways
Since I first saw the space
I know that Bob will triumph
With our friends from outer space
And though we suffered knee-gee
I know that it's alright
Cause I know Bob and I
Will never be the same
Tell me what to think
The church of the subgenius
Will spread across the land
With pipes in place
We'll both they march together
Hand in hand
The star-fist of removal
Will strike a mighty blow
And we'll be free
Of the noble and the pig
So give to Bob, Bob, Bob
And you'll feel a whole lot better
Swear by Bob, Bob
Send a dollar and a letter
He will change all your behavior
He's your short-duration savior
He is Bob, Bob, Bob
You're a miserable parasite
You're just after my money
But let's leave things of this world behind
And walk now down the path of Bob
For this brief minute of slack
From the church of the subgenius
No intelligent person would be able to say
You've got to go follow after that kind of stuff
Then what do we expect?
All this perversion and sex
Are them oily pores in your back
All we care about is slack
And letting all the slack get out
The devil has to be behind that
Think I'd follow it? I don't think so
I was about to grab the nearest object
And smash the mirror into bits
When I saw one with columns of numbers
Running across it
I fancy myself comfortable with numerals
But these were beyond even me
Fortunately, its words were not
As cycles pass,
And I came and went
In groupings of ten thousand years
The sixth ice age receded
Leaving behind denuded landscape
And four continents
By the four hundred millennium
The genetic separation was irrevocable
Occasional mutations proved the rule
Rather than overturned it
Separated into Eloatus humanus
And Morloccus dishumanus
The former homo sapiens left no genetic trail
By AD 492,965
Do I surprise you?
A little, yes
We weren't always like this
After the moon fell from the sky
The earth could no longer sustain the species
Some managed to stay above
The rest of us escaped underground
Then centuries later
When we tried to re-emerge into the sun again
We couldn't
So we bred ourselves into castes
Some to be our eyes and ears
Some to be our muscles and sinews
You mean your hunters?
Yes
Bred to be predators
But bred also to be controlled, you see
My cast
Concentrated on expanding our cerebral abilities
You control their thoughts
Noth trust theirs
Heloi
So it's not enough that you
That you hunt them down like animals
That's their role here
To be your food
Guess
And for those who are suitable to be
Breeding vessels for our other colonies
You see I am just one of many
Is this the hour of slack?
No
Yes
Oh
Ragnar, you're not really Reverend Cardboard Box, are you?
These kids with their names
Reverend Cardboard Box
Hey, come on, homie
It's a gang, okay?
Yeah, I know
I know people with funny, weird names
Weird costumes
Cool tags, you know
Yeah, exactly
Got their handles, man
Jumbo was here
Every boy should be in a gang
But a gang can be a bad influence
Or a good and slackful influence
For instance, the subgenius gang
Armies of the conspiracy of dunces
Was a year ago last April
We rode into our camps
The conspiracy of dunces
The subgenius gang
Long我们曾在 Exploring acceptor lonely
We shouldn't have somewhere
Of surrender
The subgenius bundles
Of life
the bottom of the deck if these people don't stop bothering me.
Those are the voices in your head, Dave.
Those aren't real people bothering you.
How come they're so clever?
How come they can make things move around?
Because you're clever.
Because you're a saint, man.
That goes with the territory when you're a saint.
The mind stuff is what drives the cosmic engine.
Yeah, Dave, the phone calls are coming from inside the house.
Oh, man.
I thought I had this place nailed down tight as a drub.
What, your brain?
No, this house brain.
I mean, the higher...
No, it was a metaphor.
That was a metaphor, Dave.
That was a metaphor.
You did.
The calls are coming from inside your house.
I thought we were going to go into something else.
It's just that one cell.
It's that one beautiful cell.
That one brain cell you have, Dave.
Treasure it.
Men of the truth are so horrible, it will haunt your dreams for all time.
Well, I think I'm used to that.
No.
What?
Wait a minute.
No, you wait a minute.
I love that area.
And I...
Hello?
Yes?
Who is this?
Who is he who wrote to us pain and misery and terror...
Have some fram, Doug.
...and sickness and...
...and a headache that lasts all year.
All year.
That's what any deity means to me.
...means to me.
Ding dong, the deity's dead.
Which old god?
The stupid Bob.
And the smart Bob.
And the fork-tongued Bob.
And the straight veal Bob.
Are all...
Gone.
Finally.
Put to rest.
Along with the other gods.
And the other silly superstitions that have saddled mankind for centuries.
Keeping them low in their ignorance.
And high in their expectations.
Or...
He's lining up for the...
...punch, folks.
And he's got...
Yes, the bloody head of Arnold Palmer dictates what?
And you can see how...
The fucking, fake, aimless, lifeless body of Arnold Palmer does.
I believe in Arnold Palmer.
Ehhhhh?!
посмотрulllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllll
Arrrpp probably but one by one,
Hahaha, kroppuu...
Eld71.
SableKoek means keh.
Da movimento en costume..
Stake?
buying했습니다?
Whoseوي Call of Tiaso viruses,
nearly immediately tightly gebearing
young worms
born of a Hallow technically call statements
A C tanyan will be born
off.
I took a ship
at the side of the sun
swam like a senator
I reached the shore
of a trip
the kidney was brewing
candle to the cake
to the ocean floor
now I'm alone
yes I'm alone
me and you
go wrong
singing like a stone
I am a man
without a country
and I'm a boy
without a home
I'm a casualty
of a battle
of the roses
and the war
of the broken home
I got busted
for trying
while begging
carrying a weapon
under my coat
and I'm arrested
for all
a bunch of people
and now I am a pirate
on the battery
boat
I'm alone
and now I'm not
a star
because I am a man
without a country
and I'm a boy
without a home
I'm a casualty
of a battle
of the roses
and the war
I'm a casualty
of the broken home
guitar solo
oh I see
a landfall
divided down the middle of the sea
and the sides are divided
and divided again
I see so
many people lonely
lover hating lover
friend against friend
now I'm alone
I'm alone
and now I'm never going home
I am a man
without a country
and I'm a boy
without a home
I'm a casualty
of a battle
of the roses
and the war
of the broken home
amigo
algorith wallet
a
Thank you.
Another natural product made better by chemistry is...
Marijuana.
Years of research were necessary in order to improve the product.
But it doesn't take long for the drug habit to make anyone over.
In all the colors of the rainbow.
A few years back, the United States of America had nearly gone crazy.
They were lining up dope peddlers and shooting them in the back of the head.
Just take it or leave it.
Then it's chemistry to the rescue.
The answer is a simple one.
Just use your head.
But there's one sure thing.
If you use narcotics,
the horizon is unlimited.
Talk to someone who has had the experience.
All around us are the products of modern chemistry.
Heroin, morphine, reds, crack, sleeping pills.
Something that came out of a test tube created in the chemist's laboratory
by a miracle of modern science
folded into a compact little package many times as strong.
And the dope addicts say,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yes, chemistry has changed the world we live in.
Something that came out of a test tube
is going to have been transformed into the destructive forces of useful life.
Most teenagers start off with marijuana.
Some of the boys smoke them.
You know, the ones with backbone.
My girlfriend Ann and I went around with Bob.
They both smoked pop.
That's jive talk for marijuana.
So I tried it.
Funny what it does to you.
Everything speeds up to a hundred miles an hour.
There was something intriguing and different when I came home high that night.
You're real sharp and you laugh a lot.
You're the biggest person in the world.
All you think about day and night is
the radiance of sparkling colors.
And then you pass out, but when you wake up, it starts all over again.
And that's the story.
Unbelievable, isn't it?
Chemistry takes a hand in such commonplace things as
dope traffic in the United States.
It's certainly true that the increased use of narcotics
is a thing of the past.
But it's also true that the use of narcotics
Carrying off the harmful fumes from other chemical processes,
there's always the gentle dew,
which cover the surface with a film of gritty scratching particles.
It feels like your skin is being torn right off you.
It does.
Some young man may develop startling,
stupid, ghastly, tragic,
hidden secrets of nature,
the pioneer of tomorrow.
but that's another man in the toy.
I'm baked, man.
I call this radio show because I'm baked.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha,
I'm baked.
You are the inescapable result
of the experience and experience of people,
your tragedy, just as I am the inescapable result of you.
Are you?
I am.
Marijuana, marijuana, but, um, marijuana.
Yeah, um, marijuana.
Marijuana, marijuana as scientists smoking it.
Uh, um, in, in, in, uh, of a, uh,
uh, the, the government.
And, um, and, uh, uh, why, um, the, the, on marijuana, the marijuana, um, it, uh, has a,
has an, a brain, and you're, uh, well, uh, that, that can, uh, marijuana, um, but it,
a hobbled of, it, it's, it's, it's, it is almost important.
And, uh, um, so, so marijuana, that now,
Okay.
are really all my friends in road use, get it, musteri, men and women go the military
I love marijuana weed and we get to do drugs and have our family go the unfortunate thing
그.
Gun Til six years ago There was a boy and a woman to this
I know it's making me self-conscious .
it's kind of.
But you love the sick.
Bones and Cowboy Dave.
You want the sick.
You need the sick.
It's because they give me the medicine.
You sick.
The medicine.
You know, man.
It's all medicine, Stang.
Haven't we told you this numerous times
through the cyber codes?
Through the allubrium that stretches deep
into your muscles?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But I love the pudding so much.
It's like it's worth waiting
for the bats on the hillside.
It's worth the face raping.
It's worth having that
bat poison pump down
my goozle.
When you get to
fear
that antidote pudding
up your exit wound.
I'm fighting with your altar eagle.
Can I be excused now?
Come on.
You like to leave yourself
and leave it in a
I'm too disgusting
and I just have to go back.
Openly.
Oh, look what's in here.
It looks like someone's growing a brand
new silica serra data.
A new, completely
new silica brain.
Sorry.
It's so bouncy and glowy
and round.
Oh, I hear them.
It's so smooth and unwrinkled
in Dave's case.
It's like a sheet of pudding
without the curds on top.
Or is that the...
Oh, yeah, that's the shmegma pie.
Watch as we slice down.
Watch on the webcam
as we slice down into Dave's brain.
It's like butter.
It's so soft and yielding.
It just fills right open.
The moons of Jupiter.
They just slide so...
And it's as if there's nothing inside.
Just this goo.
You know, this is not an intelligent
or refractory...
Refractory.
...the lubrication machine
if you'd like to pipe up your organs.
This is me, and this is you, baby.
This is a perversion of every natural law.
And what is time travel?
But your pathetic attempt
to control the world around you.
Your futile effort
to have a question answered.
Do you think I don't know you,
Alexander?
I can look inside
your memories.
Your nightmares.
Your dreams.
You're a man haunted by those two most terrible words.
What if?
Mr. Dulles?
What is it, Jimmy?
I'm busy.
Yes, sir, I know.
Only it's Sheriff Gillis, and he says he needs to talk to you.
Ah, he says he needs to talk to you.
Well, I'm sorry.
You're right.
I'm sorry to say, the truth is, he's in pursuit of an immodest amount of that curious weed
which you and your school chum seem to find so fascinating.
Doves?
What do you mean, Doves?
I just wanted your professional opinion about a hunch...
A hunch?
Something just keeps going around in my head.
Will you give my preoccupation?
I've replaced missing eyeballs with sawdust and glued the lids together.
I've used bent aluminum combs for dentures...
What do you mean?
I've used the back part of the scalp when there was no front part.
And I folded one hand over wadded up newspapers when the other hand had no fingers.
You find all this obscene?
Do you know what is really obscene?
Look at this.
Look at the work I've done.
This is an art.
And I am the artist.
One more time, I take it from the top.
Say you'll never let me stop, stop, stop.
One more hit, just a little pop.
To get me on my way until I drop, drop, drop.
Can't come down, gotta be high.
Say you'll never let me die, die, die.
One more time, but just a little try.
You know how much I love you when I'm high, high, high.
Well, I can be sweet.
But I'm not a sweet girl.
But I'm better when I'm bad.
And I can be a hippie when I'm mad, mad, mad.
Gotta be high with a twinkle in my eye.
Listen to the music on my high, high, high.
Can't come down, gotta stay high.
Can't come together, but we try, try, try.
One more night, a feeling so good I've
gotta keep it bopping till I die, die, die.
Can't come down, gotta stay high.
What'll I do without my high, high, high?
Life's too fast, I need a lot of slack.
Gotta get the piggies off my back, back, back.
I can be sweet.
But I'm better when I'm bad.
And I can be a hippie when I'm mad, mad, mad.
Gotta be high with a twinkle in my eye.
Listen to the music on my high, high, high.
Can't come down, gotta stay high.
Can't come together, but we try, try, try.
I can't come together, but we try, try, try.
I'm a high, high, high.
Bob Diddley, Zeesa and Led Zimmerman did Hi High Five,
before that clips from Mr. Sister, The Time Machine.
ESO Radio from WCSB Cleveland, Artemia Salina, Fernanda Dandy
Lemaire.
and the Bishop.
See Yeti video in Yahoo Group's friends
for more from the Bishop.
And now, friends,
retardation from Lemuria,
Puzzling Evidence,
and Dr. Philodrummon.
I'm hot and heat with a look at the creative
and different ways to say 80.
The Western's conditions are so dreadful these days.
Expect highs at just about all the lower elevations
in the high country.
I like to do good things for my brain.
I like to give my brain a good massage.
Are you a break thinker?
One of those shiatsu massagers.
Just open up my skull.
Yeah.
And start kneading the gray matter.
Uh-huh.
Sort of a self-trepanator, right?
Yeah.
So...
I don't use any fancy cutting tools.
Yeah, none of those sharpened pieces of jade.
I hear somebody's cell phone making a weird...
that weird buzz.
Yeah, you know who that is.
That's my breathing.
Hear it?
That's my air tube.
Oh, okay.
That's the government listening to this show
and all the other shows on KPJ.
Are you still in that iron lung?
Um, I've upgraded to a new plastic lung.
Oh, okay.
One of those new fangled things.
Now, friends, this church of the subgenius,
this story of Bob...
It could be the greatest job!
Ever told!
But if...
And only if Earth can make it to the punchline!
And we can do that, friends,
if you will use your own...
Your own hate.
Actually, you don't have to use anything of yours.
As Dr. Legume said,
use their hate and their fear.
Pump up your mutant abnormality.
Flaunt your weirdness
and wag it in their slack-jawed,
uncomprehending faces.
That will do more than your vote.
Okay.
Wag your weirdness right there in public, friends.
As St. Hendrick said,
let your freak flag...
Wave your freak flag high!
Freedom, freedom,
kindly, loving,
you'll be absolutely free
only if you want to be.
guitar solo
solo
You see yourself being in the page being turned
and see yourself next to a
soldier
being cut down.
You know, you arrive on a scene as where everything is
beautiful, lush green, brighter than day.
And
like you see a completely crystal scene of a
soldier being shot down.
Also you feel yourself helping that soldier up.
Not
his uniform, but you're feeling yourself
and another
vibe, another sense of that soldier.
It seems like a soul of him.
And then you
whisk back to the waterhole.
Another wild beer, thank you.
Thank you.
Oh,
beautiful.
oh,
oh.
I can still recall my first
guitar.
A
Futurama with a tremolo
bar.
I tried to play
like Jimmy with my
teeth.
The dentist
He saw them, said good grief
So when it is nearing Christmas
The present I always wish for is
Jimi Hendrix Strat!
When he played it was a crazy sound
He played his bloody guitar upside down
I would have seen him play the Isle of Wight
I gave a pinching half way through the night
Alright!
So when it is nearing Christmas
The present I always wish for is
Jimi Hendrix Strat!
When it is nearing Christmas
The present I always wish for is
Jimi Hendrix Strat!
Alright!
When it is nearing Christmas
The present I always wish for is
Jimi Hendrix Strat!
Alright!
When it is nearing Christmas
The present I always wish for is
Jimi Hendrix Strat!
When it is nearing Christmas
The present I always wish for is
Jimi Hendrix Strat!
Alright!
And now...
Friends, that was Captain Sensible with Jimi Hendrix's Strat and some excerpts from Rainbow Bridge and so forth by Hendrix himself and some preaching from Austin.
All put together that last segment there by Potare Nostril.
And remember, friends, www.subgenius.com.
Um...
That's Bob.
Box 807, Glen Rose, Texas, 76043.
Uh, uh, uh, where she has a three-and-a-half-year-old toddler who's already been told to hate Bob into basically killing Bob.
Jim, thanks for the call.
You know, uh, it's funny because I called in, uh, about, uh, 50 years ago and tried to get ahold of Dr. Contreras.
Because I guess there was some other doctor who was, um, possibly getting somebody for me to talk to.
An official declaration of war against Bob.
Shock and horror lingered.
And there goes the torch parade.
What sort of goings-on is that, anyway?
Some sort of rites for the Temple of Vampires.
Jack, you mean to sit there and say...
All that gang was vampires?
How do I know?
At least they seem to be priests of the Temple.
Yeah, robes and torches and stuff.
Okay, friends on the Internet, where I can flog our swag legally.
If you want to help yourself and the Church of the Subgenius and get a pretty cool package with, like, 25 different nifty things in it,
like pins and bumper stickers and a real preacher card,
you need to go to subgenius.com.
And click to become a minister.
You'll see photos and a list of all the stuff you get.
And you really do get to go to the Scrub Genius Forum, which is members only,
and where we talk in ways that people don't talk on Facebook.
Much, much smarter ways, ironically enough.
Isn't that funny?
We also have things like t-shirts and damn near everything you can think of with Bob's face on it.
That and a huge selection of other subgenius graphics.
And we sell several very weird DVDs and CDs of the Bob songs and old MP3 stashes of this show.
And best of all, from our main online store, you can buy the book of the subgenius,
which is by far the greatest thing we've ever done.
It's an actual Simon & Schuster book, 22 bucks, in print for over 30 years.
And every copy that we send out is signed by yours truly.
For that matter, your address on the Puffy underpass.
The envelope is handwritten by me also.
Keeps my fingers nimble.
That's subgenius.com.
And remember, it's only money.