And a feet core of impudent snobs.
I don't know if they even listen to the show anymore.
The subgenius Harry Ossoff.
How surprised that never came up before.
Dr. Howell, Dr. Drummond, Dr. Stang.
We didn't come to borrow any money.
We didn't come to borrow any dough.
We didn't come to borrow any trouble.
We just dropped in to say hello.
Hello.
So we've got the music of CyberChump in the background as a rug.
Yes.
As we call it in the radio business.
A rug?
And Tarzan's radio station.
A platform high in Tarzan's swaying...
In a tree house.
In this case, a rug.
Well, people ask me, why is it called Tarzan's?
You can tell by looking at it.
It's made out of vines and half coconuts.
And bamboo here.
Shreds of wire and little rock crystals.
The jungle lord collected them on his travels.
Jungle lord.
From the lost city of Opar.
He raids periodically when he needs gold and things.
And since we can't afford digital recorders,
autistic subgenius bobbies are carving the audio signal onto rocks at a really fast pace.
They're highly trained native craftspersons.
And they do it entirely out of loyalty and love
and receive no wage from the subgenius corporation LLC.
The tricky part is converting those chip, those little ones and zeros cut into the rock
into a computer file that sounds like what you're hearing now.
It just means every rock has to be scanned.
Which is time consuming, but the biggest problem is it scratches the scanner surface.
You have to replace the glass every three rocks.
So it'll be months before you actually hear this.
And you do get perfect registration, though.
Yeah, yeah.
No frame rate.
No jiggle.
No hairs in the gate.
It's pure.
As long as those bobbies are chipping away accurately enough.
Don't let that one have that prop stick.
Don't let him get all wool gathering and looking off into space,
staring, not concentrating on the job at hand.
But yes, instead of being at one of those posh studios that we're used to,
we're in a tree house.
We're in the open air here.
Burning stuff.
Yeah.
Well, that's not for months.
But the tree's on fire.
The natives have set fire to the trunk again.
Quick, unzip, man.
A trunk call.
Here, take this beer.
Put that fire out.
What time does the nap period start?
As soon as the hour of slack recorder turns on.
That's when nap period starts.
On Napster.
Well, I think we're being kind of premature to look forward to that.
Right after that period.
Now, yesterday when I got tired of this,
I just called up the nearest audience member who I've never seen before in my life.
Right, right.
He was here and he gave some, he added to it.
The second Reverend X.
Next time I'm going to hit up Fight Seat Taj.
He's had more experience with this.
When I get tired, I'm going to call you, sir.
And I'll be there.
I'll go sit there and wait for somebody to finally spend a penny on a five cent button.
Well, you mean that vast panoply, that array of subgenius swag that is there on the swag table.
Yeah, and did you notice, Hal, that it's now a Stang Ranch Fossil Museum?
Yes.
We had rocks holding down all the many free flyers that no one ever tags.
Rocks holding down.
Rocks holding down docks.
Yeah, and I replaced them with treasured, more accurate free flyers.
These are fossiliferous remnants of early marine creatures from the great interior seaway.
People don't want that fake news no more.
What was that, Doctor?
You know, that mic still sounds really strange.
My mic sounds stranger to you?
No, no, yes.
What about now?
When you put your face at a reasonable distance from it, it seems to work fine.
Although it is louder.
It's still louder than me.
Do you want me to try a different mic?
I have two or three or four or five more over here.
Yeah, Mike, it's just fine, man.
What you need to try is holding your face.
The problem is your face.
Put your lip right there.
How about there?
Is that better?
That's excellent.
No, that doesn't make sense.
You're right where you're just at a normal.
Somebody just shoot him and put him out of his misery.
He's just being contrary.
Well, it's easy for him to hear.
I do have more microphones.
No, that's fine as long as you lean into it like that.
But you don't have to suck it.
My headphones went out.
No, no, no.
Say that again with your face near the microphone.
I've got this one.
I'm having some difficulty here.
I can't hear a thing.
It's an electric voice.
No, let's just.
What's the trouble with this thing?
Every time we try.
To fix something that makes it a thousand times worse.
Fearing feedback.
Listen to that.
What do you think you're doing?
I'm getting feedback.
Me?
I'm just trying to reattach my severed headphone jack.
Or Doug, I mean.
I mean, Ivan.
Hold on.
Just a momentito.
This is simple.
It's just a moment, people.
It's just this simple.
I've lost it.
I'm not getting the music.
I'm not getting anything.
Nothing comes through.
Except a haunting feedback.
Where's my guitar?
Now if I push it with my fingies like this, I can hear.
Now I can hear.
One reason you're getting the feedback is because you're leaning your face right against that microphone.
That hurts my ears, Dr. Hal.
Jesus.
What?
You're the one who's doing it.
I'm not doing nothing.
Well, it's emanating from somewhere.
But fortunately, I can now hear through my headphones.
Which was a matter of concern to me.
I'm gonna move away.
Okay.
That seems to work.
That's not necessary, Philo.
I think we're all set up now.
All ship-shape and squared away.
Ready to go.
Yeah.
Eight minutes of technical difficulty.
Tanned, rested, and ready.
Now we can charge ahead.
Okay.
Let's start all over again.
Ah, yes.
Dear friends.
We're back at 22X day.
Only three days left for the huge, huge, huge, huge, huge, huge, huge, huge, huge, huge, huge,
huge, huge, huge, huge, huge, huge, huge, huge, amazing and incredible
human race as it remembers itself or wants to think of itself.
And we'll soon be aboard the saucers.
Reverend Stang, your voice seems to have a lot of wow and flutter in it.
Do you know...
Three twin-ling days.
Can you hear that flutter?
Philo, everything sounds like it's got some wow and flutter in it.
And I assume that that's all your fault.
I remember wow and flutter.
Yeah, listen.
Yeah, the Hal sounds way...
They were here, X-Day 14.
Yeah, but what sounds you get for assuming?
I'm assuming...
You're saying I sound...
Yes, everything sounds...
Everything sounds fluttery.
Everything sounds a little bit hinky.
Is that what you're trying to tell me?
Yes.
That we're not receiving a full range of audio,
high-fidelity sound.
In fact, I can sometimes...
What are you doing, Farr?
Not hear anything.
It sounds like electrical pulses.
The beat of a hypertrophied human heart.
That's much better.
I just fixed it.
You fixed it?
Hal, do me a favor
and don't try to fix anything anymore.
Hal fucked it up.
Don't try to fix anything.
Stop trying to fix it.
When you fixed that, you pulled that out.
Well, dog my cats.
Man!
I guess I have to say
that was a real melon scratcher.
Bless my buttons.
I won't do it again.
Okay, I...
I smell that smell again.
It's like cheap perfume and frop.
Heavens, do I offend?
It's frop mixed with cheap perfume.
The stench of frops all around you.
Only one joker in L.A.
was sensitive enough to wear that scent.
Ooh, that smell.
That's not the smell of frappy.
The smell of paranoid.
Perfume.
Compiled by speed freak Hindus who never sleep.
Oh, oh, oh.
I need some of that...
perfume.
Don't they have a hot and cold running coffee bar here
at Caffina's Palatial Luxury Hotel?
I believe so.
We...
Are they serving coffee?
A nice, uh...
Yeah, I gotta...
I gotta cup myself, Reverend Stang.
A towering iced coffee.
Frappuccino.
It's really good, too.
Topped with a mountain of swirled cream.
The cherry impudently perched there.
Served by a beautiful server.
That's right.
And a pastry on the side.
For the touch of old Napoli.
Yes, we've got it.
The lap of luxury here.
Uh, but it is, of course, only a foretaste.
Only a teasing preview of the pampering we may expect to get
once aboard the spacecraft that are even now en route to make that special rendezvous.
I think all the talk of coffee has actually influenced Reverend Stang.
He's going to find it.
Going to search for the mythical spring of, uh, reviving caffeine.
Turn down your output to me.
Flash your LARC pack.
You can't turn anything to...
I can turn all of the things down.
Turn down, turn up.
Turn on your master output just a little bit.
There is no master output.
Oh.
No master output.
How many times do I have to cite that?
Master output's in the cold, cold ground.
Besides right here.
All right.
Now, now just calm this down.
The osculus infundum.
Once on a night as black as pitch.
What about this headphone jack?
Isabel met...
...a horrible witch.
The witch's face was cross and wrinkled.
Hey, Reverend Stang, how about the...
What if we used this headphone jack as a line out?
The witch's gums with teeth were sprinkled.
It does have a modulator volume control on it.
Oh, ho.
Oh, Isabel, the old witch crowed.
I'll turn you into an ugly toad.
Isabel...
Isabel didn't worry.
Isabel didn't scream or scurry.
Yes, thank you.
She...
Now, what did she do?
Now that threw me off.
See?
I remember what Isabel did at this important juncture.
All right, I got somebody.
Matt Woyke.
Matt Woyke!
Yes, well, to continue to a different episode,
Isabel met a troublesome giant.
And Isabel continued,
self-reliant.
The giant was hairy.
The giant was horrid.
It had one eye in the center of its forehead.
Ho, ho, Isabel.
Glad to meet you.
Now, little Isabel, I will eat you.
Isabel...
Isabel didn't worry.
Isabel didn't scream or scurry.
She nibbled on some zwieback that she always fed off.
And when she was done, she chopped the giant's head off.
All right.
I'm gonna try something.
All right, now, make sure you...
I'm not gonna try.
You're gonna change.
Change the wiring.
Do just what Reverend Stang said not to do.
Never touch the red lead wire.
You pulled it right out of the board there.
Nothing good can come of this.
Now he's replugging it.
It's just like the switchboard.
Hello, Central.
Oh.
Simple thing would be to go from this plug to there.
Simple pleasures are worth dying for.
That's what Mrs. Smith's pies are all about.
I'll have a switchboard.
I'll have a splitter for that.
We're still setting up here, folks.
So never mind a little bit of technological double talk.
You're biologi...
We don't want to bore you with a whole lot of technical specifications.
Okay.
That's that.
In just a moment, we'll be running like a...
Check, check.
Swiss watch.
Rolling downhill in a thunderstorm.
Test, test.
Okay, I can still hear everything in my system.
Test the blood of Dracula.
Now, let me see here.
Then there was Dracula AD 1972.
I don't know if you ever saw that one.
Then there was Frankenstein 1970.
That was one of my favorites.
Yes, which was actually made in 1960.
Yeah.
Frankenstein 1970.
Now, it's not working.
Yeah, it's not working.
Actually, what do you mean?
I can hear you talking out of that.
I don't hear me talking out of it.
You have your mic running through some...
You've got your mic running through something, except it sounds real tinny, right?
You've got your mic running through a different system, don't you?
Little tiny Timmy's Tinny.
It's going into yours first and then mine, isn't it?
No, it isn't.
Oh, it's not?
Okay.
All right.
I don't trust any of you guys.
I don't think it sounds like it.
That's right.
It's all right.
Test, test.
I can't hear myself on it at all.
I can attest that I hear you.
Well, you're using headphones.
We're talking about the speakers.
Why don't you...
You put on headphones, you can be like me.
I got them.
Friends.
Get them too.
Do you see what I have to deal with?
Working with subgeniuses.
It's a nightmare.
Just slap on a couple of cans, Stang.
It's a madhouse.
You'll hear just fine.
But, Philo, what have you done?
You've overwhelmed the system.
I'm sorry.
Philo fixed it, see?
Well, dog my cat.
He sure knew his onions.
I can't tell because I didn't have them.
That's because you had your headphones on.
Yeah.
So, also in the new...
This will sound really good on the radio because I control what goes on the radio.
I can't control Philo or what you hear, but I can control the official recording, see?
That's the important thing.
I'm going to do the same job as the sacred scribe to remove all the stupid parts.
So, we've started this show how many times?
Three times now?
Well, it's like starting the backyard lawnmower.
It starts as a new day.
It takes a number of firsts to get it roaring and slicing.
Can you all hear any of this okay?
Oh, that's the kind of feedback we like.
Okay.
See, they can hear every stutter and malapropism.
Now that Tarzan has been rebooted over and over for 20 minutes.
Okay.
Well, welcome to the Hour of Slut number 1730 and recorded live at 22X Day.
Alive, alive, oh.
This is not a drill.
This is a Phillips screwdriver.
I keep seeing that T-shirt with a picture of a drill and it says, this is not a drill.
Right, yeah.
But it is a drill.
Sure.
On the T-shirt.
Yeah, it's the whole thing.
Well, the T-shirt is a pattern.
Oh, okay.
Angry, angry.
I'm going to go back to the other room.
Philo, do you have anything against headphones?
I was just curious.
Yeah, sir.
Pop them on.
I find them very confining.
Uh-huh.
You see, now you can hear.
Could you put your pants back on too, Philo?
Yes, no one wants to see that.
Or they're way too confining.
You can hear the background track, right?
It's so loud.
You hear the background music playing euphoniously.
So, see, we're on the same page.
Yeah, I can hear that.
Can you turn it off?
Can you turn on hot in my headphones slightly?
Why, if I had only not been instructed not to touch this nasty wiring.
Don't you, either of you guys touch any of that stuff.
I'll kill you.
I'll cut your hands off.
I could move it so loud.
Slightly your way.
It's so loud.
And ease the painful constriction you must be feeling.
You knuckleheads.
Here, just back the headphones off a little bit, Philo.
I can't turn it down because then I won't be able to hear anything.
Or you can lean your dome forward and put your headphones.
This is what happens when the DJ is deaf.
Yes, that is.
It is indeed.
It's a shame.
Who can reach the deaf?
What are you going to do?
Make fun of my handicap now?
No, I won't make fun of your handicap.
I'm sad that you have a handicap.
I'm not making fun of it.
I don't think there's anything light about your handicap.
I think it's a bummer to be handicapped like you are.
I'm a victim.
Yeah, it's my...
I'd be bummed out if I had such a handicap myself.
Yeah, I...
You have one of those special parkings.
I think I've seen some of them.
You know, you have a parking placards that allow you to park in a special space.
I'd probably cry.
I'd probably go home and cry like a little bitty baby.
I self-identify as a victim.
Like a little baby girl.
That's me.
I'd cry like a little girl, little baby girl.
Well, we're all...
There you go.
Sorry.
Bob.
That sounds pretty good.
We have sympathy.
Why didn't you do that to me, Bob?
Yeah, why didn't you do that, Bob?
Why didn't you make me different?
Why didn't you do that to myself?
Yeah, it's just not fair that society allowed me to do this to myself.
Why didn't they stop me?
Why didn't my friends stop me?
I'm a victim.
They should have stopped me when I started to do that stupid thing that I knew was stupid.
When you started...
And they knew it was stupid, and they told me not to.
But why didn't they tell me louder?
When you started hanging out...
It's just not fair.
...in front of a 12-foot amplifier.
Well, actually, yeah.
I think...
I think that was part of it.
Filming the amino acids while standing next to the speaker.
It did in my right ear.
It always stood next to that amplifier, pointing this way.
My right ear, right against the amp.
And, uh, yeah.
I'm deaf too, Bob.
Deaf to Bob.
But perhaps not to his message.
Remember...
Remember, uh, you...
I know you're chugging the nexus of, uh...
I can't hear you.
Deaf to Bob.
I can't hear me either.
Yeah, none of us can hear anything.
It's just a campground full of deaf old farts.
Hobbling around, shuffling...
Well, that's why they smell, so deaf people can enjoy them too.
My Android hearing aid program can hear more than any of you in its little finger from
here to here.
You're talking into the air, Mr.
He's talking into the...
He has a little finger, you say?
...ambient microphone.
Oh, yeah.
I'm the one that's out there.
Yeah, we...
Well...
Tarzan's, uh...
You got your ALC on.
We should put a mic, like an audience mic, like Joe Pine had, you know?
Have a mic out there that he can grill the...
Yeah, you can be Oprah and go running out into the audience with the mic.
Why didn't we do that?
Well, you just suck the shut-me-up.
Here's a likely subgenius here.
Well, how's your ex day, mister?
Say that's quite a haircut you have.
Shut up!
I have an answer for all those things, but of course I've given up on everything.
I'm never gonna...
What about you, little girl?
Did Mommy fix your hair?
Yeah, I have an answer, too.
Nobody really wants to hear what I have to say.
I do.
I wanna hear you.
I have an answer to your answer.
What's this defeatism about how nobody wants to hear you?
Try it out, first of all.
Shut up!
Philo, why don't you put all your mics out there in the audience and then find something
to connect them to here at Tarzan's Three Mic Radio Show?
That's the problem.
Yes.
That is the problem.
Actually, I could connect them, but then it would cause me...
They would be louder than me, and that wouldn't work.
Well, you need wireless mics to go on out there.
I normally don't miss...
Can you imagine how loud that guy would be if he actually did have a microphone?
We could tackle the problem.
I have the problem of being the lone Spock on a spaceship full of Kirks.
Or actually more like Zap Brannigans.
I'm trapped in a world of Zap Brannigans.
What if you were on a spaceship full of Susan Oliver from that one?
One pilot episode.
No, let's not start into pilot episodes of old TV shows.
We're here to talk about how to beat the conspiracy.
The conspiracy outside of ourselves and the conspiracy inside of ourselves.
And you don't think Susan Oliver and her at that time could have been like...
It helps, but it's not a priority.
And Susan Oliver was one of those strange looking women that Gene Roddenberry always
wanted to hire.
I got no problem with that.
Oh no.
Wasn't she on the old Make Room for Daddy, Danny Thomas show?
Make Room for...
Turn that down, Philo!
Turn what down?
I've got my headphones on.
Turn down this exciting real estate opportunity.
You cannot accuse me of not monitoring myself properly.
Turn your phone sound effects button off.
We have monitored your broadcasts for centuries.
That's interfering with my ability to understand the pointless human speech that my ears are
being exposed to.
Is that better now?
Is that better?
Yeah, now I can hear the pointless words.
Okay, say the words that have no meaning.
I'm going to Star Trek!
Say it!
Susan Oliver, Star Trek.
Susan Oliver in the Monitor episode.
God, you're...
You see these two Civil War ironclads...
We really need some young blood in this church.
We really do.
We're going to have to get all these somewhat slightly younger people up here.
Well, don't...
I don't see any more holding you back.
So what you're saying is we do need another microphone.
Stampede up to the stage.
No, we have plenty of microphones.
We need another radio station.
And new brains.
Well, you can't be satisfied with anything.
Why don't you look around?
The birds of the air, are they content?
Yeah, let's put them on the air.
They can tweet, tweet, tweet all day.
I can hear Philo's little tweet, tweet, tweeting irritating machine.
When his baby comes down the street, yes.
It's hard to be a control freak in an uncontrolled, chaotic society.
A cat circus...
You're like a captain with no crew.
What's the guy that runs the circus?
The ring man.
A leader with no followers.
Yeah.
Isn't that horrible?
No.
Being a leader amongst leaders and everyone wants to go their own way.
Too many chiefs and not enough Indians.
And they're all Chief Wahoo.
Smart-out.
Well, he's the one that knows the magic of the super hammock.
Offensive.
Or Stellag 17.
They're all offensive cartoons of Native America.
Where all the prisoners were sergeants.
He's made the erection of a hammock into an art form.
All shouting at each other.
A whole camp full of sergeants.
It's a terrible mix-up.
A planet of Charlton Heston's.
Oh, yeah.
All yelling and screaming, angry.
Pouting and posing.
Yeah.
Well, he was right, though, all the way through.
Humans suck.
The apes were even more right.
Humans should be beasts of burden in the fields.
But they can't be allowed to run wild.
But given the time, the apes became just like humans.
Well, that's the irony.
The irony is the ironic, sad, satirical thing about it, isn't it?
It's so sad.
Every time you have a revolution and overthrow the conspiracy, why, next thing you know,
you're the conspiracy.
You're the conspiracy.
Yeah.
But, Philo, see.
We did it.
We said it at the same time.
We could be like Tenacious D, two kings.
Oh, but wait.
The same thing happened to that one, too.
They ended up murdering, poisoning each other.
Right.
God.
See, the conspiracy always wins.
But we should just give up.
So, go ahead and buy everything you were thinking about buying right now.
The first time I gave up, everything came my way.
The house has all the advantages.
Use up your credit cards.
I don't know what to buy because there's no Wi-Fi here.
Max them out.
That's right.
How are you going to do it?
There is Wi-Fi, but no internet.
Isn't that ironic?
I can't buy without my Wi-Fi.
I don't know what I should buy.
Help me.
Please, help me.
You should, well, you've already bought the most important thing, which is the ministership
in the Church of the Subgenius, which means you will survive and to harass us and heckle
us after the world ends.
What about a chewy caramel center with plenty of nougat surrounded by milk chocolate?
Only the very few.
Great fun.
All right.
Well, the radio audience can't hear Mr. Sistar, who is channeling Dr. Dark.
He said that he was going to come through and give us a signal that there is indeed
a life after death.
We are waiting for that signal.
Well, we may have gotten it.
I think we're hearing it.
I'm listening again.
Yeah, he's channeling the late Dr. Dark, who was, let's face it, the greatest heckler
of subgenius church history, hands down.
And of course, as usual, unable to be heard by the radio audience.
Only the innocent radio host can actually hear that.
You can tell them.
You can transcribe what he says.
And the three other audience members.
This is the grandest ecstasy.
Wait a minute.
I see four audience members.
You've undercounted that audience by 73.2%.
I'm not sure.
I think there's six or seven.
All right.
And there's five people.
Five times as many people here as there were yesterday.
When there was one.
They're thronging, surging into .
And we ended up getting him to come up here and be on stage.
We had to.
Some of the other members broke down and had to go cry.
Some could not stay to fulfill their duties.
The ass of the spirit.
No matter how loud you yell, you can't be louder than Philo's noise machine.
To us.
To the people next to you, you're quite overly loud.
But to us, we're protected.
Philo is static.
I don't touch that thing for like ten minutes and then I touch it once and he goes haywire.
What are you, some kind of like control freak?
Demons of snarling noise.
Like that effect right there.
See, that buzzing sound effect is nothing that emanated here on Earth.
What's that guy yelling about out there?
I can't hear him. I'm in headphones.
He's trying to convey an important message.
And he won't get off his ass and stand close enough to be heard.
We can't understand.
I wouldn't get off his ass either if I was him.
No, I'd stay on his ass.
Dissatisfaction with things as they currently are.
We only hope to remedy those difficulties.
Ticks.
We'll get it all fixed up.
Ticks, did you say?
Oh, that's terrible.
Ticks, friends.
Ticks everywhere.
Watch out for them.
They're worse than ever.
Drop on you out of the trees.
That's how they get you.
They sense your heat signature passing beneath.
And they launch forth.
Their little arachnid bodies into space.
When they land, they clutch and grasp.
And then find a warm crevice in which to begin their work of aggression and vampirism.
Why, I'm crawling up through this bush of human pubic hair.
I'll crawl up this strangely short rod here.
Oh, there's a nice hole at the tip of this tube.
I'll nestle down in there and start sucking from the inside.
Oh, no.
And then if it gets inserted into another tube, I'll crawl out of this tube and suck from that tube.
Because I'm a tick.
The Tick.
Yeah, there hasn't been a horror movie called Ticks yet.
Yes, there has.
Oh, there has?
You see, in this movie, marijuana growers in the forest use too much hormone.
And it causes the ticks to grow large and terrorize teenagers.
And that's actually happened in real life.
Well, there's some nice stop-motion tick scenes, though.
For the most part, they are done by puppets, by Tom St. Armand.
But they also have to include the scene where the one black kid somehow turns into an enormous tick
through a painful process of stretching, splitting, expanding.
And this is a movie called Ticks?
It's called Ticks, yes.
Look in the international...
International movie database, and you can read all about it.
But the villains are caused by marijuana growers.
A big stupid one and a little small evil gay one.
It used to be radiation, then it was quantum, now it's marijuana.
Yeah, it's a bad...
It's an atomic guy.
Atomic this, atomic that.
They're growing marijuana in the forest.
And it has the unfortunate, exaptive side effect of creating monster ticks that move around pretty fast.
If only.
Well, they're about as big as grapefruits with legs.
Now, has anybody made a movie called Target Grade?
About a giant rampaging water bear?
No, but aren't they in the Ant-Man and the Wasp movie?
Yeah, but they're normal size.
I'd love to see that one.
They just look big to Ant-Man and the Wasp.
Well, size is relative.
I don't care how big anybody is.
That's what she said.
I just want to see an enlargement of those creatures.
Time will tell.
How about...
Rotifer.
Those amazing Rotifers.
A new beginning.
Volvox, the motion picture.
Oh, God.
Figures.
Now, what was the thing in It Challenged the World?
That wasn't a robot.
That was a Venusian cucumber creature.
Oh, no, no.
It conquered the world.
You mean the monster that challenged the world.
It was supposed to be a mollusk, and yet it had a caterpillar-like form.
Right.
They had a shell, but the body could lunge forward.
It could grab you in its many arms, and then its pinchers at the top.
Yeah, pinchers.
Those pinchers would do some pinching.
Mollusks don't usually have pinchers.
No, they don't.
They were confused.
But the creature itself was confused, and it inhabited the Great Salt Lake.
Oh, it's Salt and Sea.
Exactly.
Oh, that's right.
That movie was one of the few movies that was filmed at the Salt and Sea while it was still...
It was a salty beast.
...somewhat livable.
Yes, well, only for these horrible slug monsters.
Val Kilmer?
No, it was...
No, no, no.
That was Salton.
That was the name of that.
But the guy, was it Robert Walker?
The hero?
He's in a uniform.
There's whatever marine service the Salt and Sea has.
He's out there with his boat.
Coast Guard, I think.
The Coast Guard.
Yeah, well, as if the Salt and Sea is on the coast.
It's saltwater, but it's surrounded by land.
But still, he's there, fresh from the...
Treasure of the Sierra Madre.
Friends, if you love to see life after people, dilapidated ruins, the way things will be after this Friday,
visit the Salt and Sea, which is just south of Los Angeles, right near the border with Mexico.
You can't sink in it.
There's so much salt, your bloated body floats on the top.
It's beautiful looking.
It smells like...
It smells like death, and the beach is made of bones.
Because nothing can live in it for long.
Not kidding.
It is literally made of fish bones and bird bones.
Well, in the movie, scuba divers go down on the bottom, and then these things come out and suck them into the...
The people who still live in Bombay Beach and Salton City are very, very, very weird people.
They're salty, as we say.
Yes.
It's 130 degrees in the summer, but it's cheap.
It's real cheap.
They thought there was going to be a beautiful, futuristic city, and they built the streets and canals,
which still show up on your GPS as if they were really there.
But what you're really looking at is these long stretches of empty streets,
filled in canals that never had the water in them,
and one house per street.
With a weird...
Weird, weird, weird person living in them.
Still paying their timeshare, Bill.
Yeah, it's the most atmospheric place, if you like, to think about the end of the world.
How this place paid off in another 130 years.
Yeah, it's got a real...
And they're letting it go.
They just recently decided to quit trying to save it, despite Sonny Bono's heroic efforts to save that area.
He tried to save the Salton Sea.
Yeah, there's a Sonny Bono wilderness area.
The most hideous-looking wilderness area you ever saw.
An unkempt mustache of nature.
Any subgenius.
You won't find any pinks there.
You'll just find other weirdos shooting pictures of the graffiti and skeletons.
And the way the ocean...
The Salton Sea itself looks like syrup.
It's beautiful looking.
It kind of...
It has movement, but it's very slow.
It's slowed down from...
Yeah, it's not the...
The free movement of water.
The turgid sluggishness of the salt.
Looks great at sunset.
I'm surprised they don't shoot more commercials there.
It's pretty in that horrible, horrible way.
It looks like somebody had a war there.
An atomic war.
Not a hydrogen bomb war, but an old...
Nature's Wonderland.
It's an atom bomb war, so there's still buildings standing, but they're ruined.
You can explore in there, but you'll probably get crushed and the roof falls in.
Or attacked by the cannibals that live in the ruins.
And the slugs.
Yeah, and the slugs.
Of course, the giant mollusks.
We saw it.
That's what got us on this.
Yeah.
But really, Salton Sea.
It's not going to be there forever.
Pretty soon they'll run everybody out because it's going to turn into a toxic dust bowl.
And I'm not exaggerating.
It's already making people very, very sick.
Oh, God.
It's going to turn into a toxic dust bowl.
It's already making people very, very sick.
It's a toxic dust bowl amusement park.
And fun for the whole family.
The nearest towns with people in them are Mexicali and Caliexico.
One is on the Mexican side and one is on the American side.
It makes me feel hot.
It doesn't matter which is which.
It's blazing down there.
It's roasting hot.
You don't have to worry about armies of illegals that are bad people coming in because nobody wants to go to that area.
Nobody.
Nobody wants to cross that inhospitable stretch of desert.
No.
With its red hot rocks and thorns, spikes, canyons, cholla cactus.
And everyone who lives there has lung problems.
Yes, from huffing the particulate matter which floats in vast, endless dust clouds.
Well, all the fertilizer from the surrounding farms runs into the Salton Sea.
Yes, it's powdered fecal.
It's a very tropical matter.
Yeah, it's an ocean of shit, you might say, friends.
You can't miss it.
Nice place to visit and raise your family.
Yeah.
A real nice place to raise your kids.
Now, off Earth, though, there are supposed to be many paradises and places which we, the victorious subgeniuses, can visit.
Oh, yeah. After X-Day, come to my escape vessel to see the Salton Sea.
And the Grand Canyon.
The Grand Canyon and the British Museum.
Just keep them separate. Don't mix them all up.
Why not? That's all fun.
That's the fun of it.
The British Museum of the Salton Sea.
Hmm. In the Grand Canyon.
In the Grand, yeah.
That would kind of, uh, that would be a weird combination.
Why not all three?
Why not?
You have room.
Why not? Yeah, I'll have a whole planet.
It would be a blank planet for the most part, because even though I'm going to rupture up half of the national parks and most of the world museums,
before Legume gets to them, to wreck them, because he just doesn't want me to get my hands on them.
He doesn't care about them.
He just wants to wreck them.
Somebody said, is there going to be a service or any memorial for Dr. Legume?
It's like, what?
Well, I'm sure something will erupt.
Nervous in the service.
Leonard the Committed has something in a brown bag, and that's the Legume Memorial.
Uh, are we doing anything?
He would approve, I'm sure.
What about the Bulldada auction? Do we do anything for Legume there during that event?
Well, we'll have to think of something.
We could just call everything the Dr. Legume Memorial product.
Yes, auction off these Dr. Legume dish towels that we have.
That sort of thing.
Okay.
Well, I mean, there are a lot of people who are going, I'm glad he's dead. He was mean.
Yeah, he was mean, but here's the thing, kids.
He was also right.
That's the horrible thing about it.
Well, actually, he wasn't right all the time.
Sometimes he got really goofy ideas in his head.
How that can happen to a subgenius, I don't know.
I don't know either.
It certainly wouldn't happen to me.
Goofy ideas, butt hurt.
Come on.
That's for lesser types.
Yeah, well, that's for sensitive kids, you know.
I've been through it all. I've got a tough hide.
I've got a shell a mile thick.
What'd you say? What'd you say about me?
Just speculating aloud.
I'm triggered again.
Like Roy Rogers' horse.
Stuffed and mounted.
Yeah, my PTSD from being turned down.
For dates is acting up.
Has the record reached the end of the room?
I have PTSD from girls not dating me.
What's that shuffling sound?
Philo.
If there's an irritating sound, you can just assume that it's philo drumming.
Look at that. He thinks it's funny.
No, I don't. I think I'm taking it very seriously.
He's taking umbrage.
It's not too loud to me this time.
It sounds like chicken scratching.
Yes. Chicken scratching with its tridactyl claw in rhythmic fashion.
I don't know. I take it all back.
It's obviously some avant-garde musical presentation.
Now it's too loud.
What other subgenius tourist attractions are there?
Nearby, there's Point Pleasant.
It's West Virginia, right?
Well, there's the Woodstock Mystery Hall.
The Mothman Museum.
Oh, yeah. That's right.
John Peel set his mostly made-up stories about people seeing the Mothman in Point Pleasant.
So it's in Athens?
No, it's in West Virginia. It's real nearby, though.
I've never been there, but I've seen lots of pictures.
They have a statue of the Mothman right in the middle of town.
And a store full of Mothman memorabilia.
Wow. The Mothman souvenir shop.
Wow.
Did you ever get little statues of Mothman?
Everybody suggests, dang, you've been to Roswell, right?
No, I've avoided Roswell because I got sick of that alien stuff years ago.
And so did all the shop owners in Roswell and outside of Roswell.
They've admitted it to me.
But it's a living.
Where's the little Ale Inn?
That's in Rachel, Nevada.
Oh, yeah. That's in Rachel, Nevada.
Okay.
The roadside attraction that has a crashed flying saucer sticking out of its roof.
Yeah, and they've seen plenty of UFOs in that area.
Now, what is that place that was shaped like a giant flying saucer with stairs going up to it?
And there's a tourist trap now.
It was originally going to be a casino, but it was all a rip-off.
They never had a permit for it.
The mob built this whole thing.
And then it turned into nothing.
Then it was a tourist trap.
I don't know.
And he's got little crash saucers all over the place and rockets embedded in the ground.
What happened to my cup?
It's where that famous photograph is of Doug, Gary, and Paul underneath a giant pipe falling out of the sky.
Oh, yeah. I remember that place.
I remember the place.
Yeah, I was driving through the desert one time.
It was like, weeeee!
That's that place!
We have to stop here!
We're here!
Kind of like The Thing on Interstate 10.
You should dare to see The Thing.
When you pass all those billboards saying, do you dare to see The Thing?
Is it still there?
As far as I know, I can't imagine it not being.
That they would remove The Thing?
The Thing is, it's only a dollar, and there's thousands of things.
Yeah, it's worth a dollar.
It's probably worth two dollars.
It's full of curios and weird, weird, weird art and Hitler's car.
And I don't know.
I've seen crudely carved wooden figures illustrating a medieval torture chamber.
Hey, Reverend Stang, did you ever go in Harold Warp's Pioneer Museum in Menden, Nebraska?
No.
Well, you really missed it.
They have covered wagons.
By the way, if you want the cover blown of The Thing, I took pictures of it.
I did, too.
I don't think anybody here is going to go see The Thing.
Why?
It's worth a dollar.
It's just a feeling I have.
If you want to drive all the way across the country, it's worth a dollar.
But doesn't everybody have to drive to California from Texas every year?
Remember, they have to get value for their money by coming to Ex Day.
Not anymore.
And one thing you can do is to blow the cover of The Thing, which is part of the exclusivity of the East.
But it's a mummy of an old Indian woman.
These things make my ears sweaty.
If it's even real.
You see, they frown on mummies of Native Americans and where they used to have them in museums now that they're gone.
They don't.
And now, sometimes they even deny that there ever was a mummy there before.
Yes, I've gone to museums which were once the haunt of excavated mummies.
And when I inquire, they are very kidgy and defensive and deny that there was ever such a mummy.
We never kept a...
That would be a sacrilege to the...
And natives.
Apparently it would be.
But then they come out of their office and look at me just because I asked about the damn mummy.
No, I'm not going to make trouble, but I'd like to know what happened to it.
What happened to that mummy?
It got up and walked.
It got up and walked off by itself.
It's going to a tea party.
He went for a little walk.
You should have seen his face.
Is that what it was?
Yes.
My ancestor, Bramwell Fletcher, was the one who was terrified to death by the mummy.
Really?
Yes.
And the first mummy?
Yes, yes.
He's the one who said...
He went for a little walk.
You should have seen his face.
Wow. Can I touch you?
You've got an ancestor in the mummy.
Yeah, a relative.
A relative.
Not necessarily a direct progenitor of me, but one who is of my blood.
Other tourist destinations for subgeniuses would be commonly used movie locations like...
Old Tucson, outside Tucson, Arizona.
Yeah, Alabama.
Alabama Hills, which is not in Alabama and doesn't have anything to do with Alabama.
The Vasquez Rocks outside of Los Angeles.
Yeah.
The Alabama Hills, it's like...
Everywhere you look, you know you've seen an Indian jump off a rock onto a stagecoach there.
Oh, there, okay, there's a picture of Mothman.
Mothman.
Brought to us. I wish we had a projector.
For am I not Mothman?
Gorgeous looking creature.
Gigantic.
Life-size.
It's worth, definitely worth going through and looking at it.
All based on a hoax.
No bowing or cringing to this obscene idol is required.
What's the, uh, the Velazquez Peaks?
Velazquez, yeah, that's what it's called, Velazquez Peaks, right?
You mean the Vasquez Rocks?
Vasquez Rocks, yeah.
Every movie and every Star Trek episode, every Twilight Zone has been, had the Velazquez Peaks.
Planet of the Dinosaurs.
Yeah, sure.
Bill and Ted's Excellent Adventure number two.
Oh, you name it.
And what about Bronson Canyon?
Well, and, what, giant cyclops has come stomping out of that every three motion pictures.
But also, Roman has his cozy little cave down there.
Oh, right, right, yeah.
Well, that's right, in LA.
And Eegah hung his, uh, Paleolithic hat there.
Yeah, there's some of these places, when you see them, you go, oh, that's a great place.
It's like I've been here.
And, no, all of your famous bad monster movie directors have been there.
And you saw what they found.
It's hard to find a location that is unentailed.
They don't like you shooting, you know, they'll report, they'll snark on you if you're trying to set up your pathetic independent cameras and things.
Any of these spots, making it even harder to get those shots.
I almost got busted at Vasquez Rocks.
Really? They, uh,
got you making a, um...
No,
some good citizen who
we didn't suspect might be
up high looking down on us
probably called
the park service and said
there's this
old man
and his cute blonde daughter
down there smoking a pipe.
I'm sure it's driving...
He's obviously a pedophile.
He'll smoke anything in the state park.
And, uh, cause when we came out,
Princess Wee suddenly had her spidey sense
and said, I just got a feeling we gotta get out of here.
So I'm like, okay, let's go get some pictures
of me in the bob mask
in front of the famous rock.
And when we went to
the car, there were two cops,
park cop and a city cop,
watching us.
And I had a bob mask on.
And I stood there and waved at him
and held my plastic
pipe and she took
pictures of me with the rock
in the background and they
just kept looking at us
and we got in the car and headed
for the exit
and they kind of herded us
out. They went left
and we went right. I'm pretty sure
what happened was
they got this report and said
oh boy, let's bust somebody. And they go and look
and it's like, well yeah, there's a guy
with a pipe, but it's a fake pipe
and a stupid mask and
I think this is a bug hunt.
And it's lunch time and I don't want to fill out that
paperwork. So Bob
saved us. Those sumbitches
are trying to sting us. A really bad
bob mask saved us.
Nobody would do something that stupid.
The full over the head
vinyl bob mask. It wasn't
the modern bob
mask made by Sick Rick.
How come we don't have any of those here?
I thought we did.
Didn't you bring some?
Mine are in Texas. I think
Princess Wee has one. Might as well be on
the dark side of the moon.
So Princess Wee brought one along.
Well I thought there was one in Cleveland.
They're really good.
They aren't pricey. They're about
80 bucks or 100.
Would you say they were lifelike?
No, I wouldn't say they were.
Bob's not lifelike.
They're Bob-like, although kind of
more evil than we're used to seeing him
look. Well, a lot more
evil. I'd say
frighteningly more evil.
Both the
black and white version
is the worst. Bob Ferracchi
got two, I call it.
That was the first one I got.
We get them for... Philo and I get them
for free. The thousand year old
Bob that lives in the basement.
Every ten that he sells, we get
one free.
He said he was only going to make 40 of them.
Well, you should get in touch
with Don Post Studios.
He also makes a bunch of other really cool
obscure characters.
Some are so cool, I don't know who the hell
they are, because they're from video games.
How about the ones where you do
know which ones they is?
What are the ones
you do know? He needs to have a
Boing Boing article written
about his mask company, and
a special deal for subgenius masks.
What are some of the
entities represented? And then we'll get some free ones.
No, then he'll be swamped
with orders and he won't be able to fill them for a
year. That'll fix him.
Let's see what other characters... Do they have the
creature from the Black Lagoon?
Frankenstein's monster?
More obscure.
Sick Rick Masks.
They call him Sick Rick, eh?
Yeah.
But are they from movies?
Or just from popular
folklore?
A little of everything.
I should be able to get it quick.
Here we go. Masks and more.
SickRickMasks.com
Sick and Rick are spelled
with just a K, no C.
What am I doing? There's no internet here!
Not Wi-Fi, but no internet!
So,
you're not able to look at
the masks or even a list of...
If I leave this here long enough, it may
show up in about 10 minutes.
Then we'll be
surprised. Oh, there's the evil
clown mask and...
Horror monster.
Several murderer types.
Is there the gorilla?
The mask?
No, no. It's all stuff. Like I
said, it's cool
characters. You and me wouldn't know about them.
We only know old things.
Sixty million year old
things.
And, uh...
Well, you can get dinosaur masks
on the internet.
Some
of fairly good quality.
Boy, I'm tired of doing this radio show.
I just want to go play on the internet.
But there is
no internet, Doctor.
I understand.
But we're at a campground. Aren't you supposed to spend
all day on the internet or playing
board games?
I'm supposed to have a weenie roast at the fire.
Watching TV?
Cook marshmallows on sticks.
Doing anything except go out in the woods?
Go out in the woods and knock off ticks
with a stick.
Yeah, I'm not going to do that. Not this year.
Well, uh...
Yeah, they are. They do festoon
the branches and bushes
and are angrily
I mean, eagerly waiting for
human blood.
Well, remember that X-Day drill
about three years ago when
apparently Bob showed up and was
on a rampage
in the woods.
That little dog was exsanguinated.
Oh, he killed a little dog. He raped a car
with people inside it.
No, he killed a car and raped a dog.
Well, it was very distasteful.
And, uh...
Oh, he killed Reverend Bastard or something.
He did something. There was nothing left but his clothes.
Reverend Bastard?
Yeah, and then Bob kidnapped you.
Nobody thought you were even there.
We hunted Bob in the woods.
I had been building up to this
for weeks. I just wanted to see
how many subgeniuses
can I get off of their asses
and off the road
and down that little trail into the woods.
It's like a scavenger hunt.
It was a challenge. I said to myself.
And it's like, sure enough, out of 40 or 50 people
there, almost
20 manly men
managed to
heave their vast
huge butts off their chairs
and go down that yellow trail
about 40 paces.
And sure enough, there was a scene of the crime.
A broken and half pipe.
A bunch of cotter pins and jello.
A high-heeled
shoe with Connie's name
engraved in it.
And a bleeding head of Arnold Palmer.
But, of course, Bob got away.
And we all came back with lots of
ticks. You've got to get up.
Pretty early in the morning.
They had good diseases that year.
They were beneficial
diseases.
This year they're all deadly, horrible,
crippling. Lyme disease
is the least of them.
Now they carry leprosy.
And insanity.
Yeah.
Bubonic plague.
And crotch rot.
Well, actually, that just comes
with
the outdoors.
With the outdoorsy life.
So, uh,
yeah,
you'll need
your
Them Kind Pills.
Oh, Mr. Sistar,
you weren't here yesterday. You didn't see.
We've got to have a whole bag of pills.
You want one of these?
Prescription bottles of Them Kind Pills
from Bob Dobbs Pharmacy.
If you want them, we got them.
Take only as needed
or whenever you want.
Boy, I could take some right now.
Oh, you'll like them because
they're full of sugar.
They're sure to make a diabetic
just a little ill.
Well, yeah, more Kind Pills.
Anyone is welcome
to come up.
Have some
Them Kind Pills.
One per customer.
One pill per customer?
No, no, one per...
Take as needed or as often as you want.
Now there's a run on these pills.
That's the thing about these pills.
They're all purpose.
Yeah, and they work for everything.
These are expired pills.
You can save them for a special occasion.
Yeah, they did expire in 1998.
But that hasn't come yet.
So they're not technically...
These pills have every kind of
prescription imaginable. You take them, you're like,
you can take them as often as needed.
They're not bad.
Anytime you want. You can take them for an over...
You can overdose on them.
And then take them...
You can use them just for special occasions.
Like, as if they were acid.
What do you mean, as if they were?
Well, they're a type of acid.
Acetic acid.
Nitric acid.
Hydrochloric acid.
So am I too loud for you guys now?
Neither one of you said shut up in about
a minute, so...
He's got vitamin A and vitamin B.
No, you're okay so far.
Vitamins L-O-V-E.
For once. Finally.