Dom de Dom de Dom de Dom de Dom de Dom de Dom de Dom de
The power of slak
Ourrrrr ZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZ
I r n d d d d
Boo, Booost
Good Poop
Yes, dear friends.
Welcome to Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack number 907.
The show devoted to the spaztards of Devo.
Yes, friends, the devotional World Devo Convention was held nearby here in Akron, actually.
And it was inspiring.
Inspiring and wonderful.
But this particular time, instead of playing a million Devo covers by different bands,
I'll play different covers by different bands that are all kind of Devoid and Devoish in
nature.
And now, this.
It's kind of hard to wear high heels or slip on banana peels.
How does she get in and out of...
Tubbs?
I hope she don't get mad.
I hope she thinks this song is good, not bad.
Cause we think that she's totally rad.
She's nuts.
No fingers, no toes.
She's jumping on elbows.
No front teeth, no knocky knees.
She's nuts.
She don't need knuckles or hands.
She goes to these pop-rock bands.
She's always in these stands.
She's got a lot of fun.
She's nuts.
She can't pick up her phone.
She can't get dressed alone.
She's got no funny bones.
She's nuts.
No shoes for feet.
But she sure did what she needs.
She's nuts.
I ask her if she wants a drink
I ask her if she likes Saltido.
So I asked her to go out to the bar
But all she said was no thanks, no one knew
It was time for us to leave
So I grabbed and shook her sleeve
Told her I'd see her at the next club
She got into a fight
So I put her on his back
She said goodbye and kinda waved her stuff
She's got beautiful eyes
And friends drinking their signs
But with that cap I thought she'd enough
It's hard to get good head
Or get down to a bend
When all you've got is a body and head
She'd enough
She's nubbed
Oh she may not walk the walk
And she may not like to talk
But boy she sure knows how to rock
She's nubbed
By NoFX
And now and now The Punk Group
Added on-screenラヲ
Obviously you can cut this out
C電諸 respected md
Sickness sticks
Left hand kitchen
Right hand bathroom
Sickness sticks
Left hand kitchen
Right hand bathroom
Sickness sticks
Sickness sticks.
The Punk Group.
So what classes are you signed up for?
Who?
You guys.
What are you taking?
I'm Pollyann.
This is college radio.
I was studying circumcision.
Reversal.
Surgery.
Reversal circumcision.
Yeah, that's getting to be really big.
Tattoo removal and piercing replacement.
Piercing replacement?
Fillings.
Fillings for your replacement.
Yeah, and scar replacement.
I'm studying Pollyannthosociopathy, which is taught by an errant-eyed crazy man from
a nearby institution who's brought in three times a week.
No, this is Pollyannthosociopathy.
Pollyannthosociopathy?
That's like people who have...
Doesn't he have to take like any normal?
Horses?
It's many anthropological studies combined into one.
Well, we don't study real people per se.
Imaginary people we study in the imaginary culture.
You guys are in the 60 thing.
The 60 thing?
Yeah, the friends to the 60 thing or something.
What is that?
It's like people over 60 get to take classes for free.
That's right, Chetty.
We not only get to take them, we need to give them back sometimes.
God only knows what that means.
But soon I will be ready.
I'm ready to take the 80 plus plunge, which is more than just a swimsuit now.
It's a full line of reproductive gear.
You look really good for 80.
Yeah, I got all the reproductive gear still intact.
One thing that does look a little bit like a diseased bird, but the rest of me is quite
humorous and ready to make hummus.
You don't look any worse than an elephant skin rug.
I don't feel any worse than an elephant skin rug, but when I'm hiding in the subway, believe
me, I get some...
I turn some heads of cats.
I turn some heads of cabbage.
You know what I'm saying?
I turn some chicken necks.
Whoops.
Once in a while.
Alt.binaries.erotica senior citizens.
Yes, tonight, from the livid ballroom, the most lovely 80-year-old women you've ever
met in your life will ever be held with one good eye.
They sing, they puzzle, and they twaddle to themselves, and they wear these giant bikinis
made of gold.
I'm a cat's man, Gossamer Flap.
Look at those beautiful, beautiful bathing caps with the hair stuffed down through their
eyes.
Ah, it's mom's way of getting backwards.
Now, Dave, where I come from, there's some really hot-looking grandmothers.
Well, you were...
No older than 30 or so.
Oh, 53 years old?
Oh, now I'll need a fake ID to rent Ultraporn.
Já está aGO!
í
You wO webs
Music
Outro
If you can't stand the steam in the cart that is loaded
You shit in the milk and we are worse than bitter milk
And together we celebrate if you chill or you burn
It's not that we don't care, but that we don't give a fuck
He gets weak while I make him a fool
Don't say I'm cold, don't say I'm ugly, dad
We throw a car to see who gets the best
And if we smoke his trapeze because he ran out of tobacco
Here we come and we don't care much
If they know what they wanna, they just want dirty boner
Here we come and we don't care net ya
Let's make instead of temporary
Vamos a hacerte el paro haciendo un disco no muy caro
Venimos decididos a quedarnos con tu paro
Vender miles de albums a los tres as we just wanna
Rayarles sus ropitas y quedarnos con su lana
En carrera de razos de bajada y sin frenos
Somos los peos y malos somos amigos del bueno
Somos los que en la playa chingan los planes chingones
Somos los super chilangos entre tu y tus vacaciones wey
Here we come and we don't care mucho
If you know what they wanna they just want your tip and wanna mana
Let's make ba-do-ba-do-zad ba-do-ba-do-ba-do-zad
Oh yes, here we come. A beautiful tune by Molotov, a Mexican rock band.
And now, Kinky Freedman.
Left barber college searching for knowledge
Went to the university
I must confess, sir, this lady professor
She turned me on to anthropology
Now I'm a homo erectus, got two connectives
Bones that I discovered yesterday
Tyrannosaurus lived in the forest
Died because his heart got in the way
Dear Dr. Howard, come down from the hill
Come to the top of your tower
And join me for lunch at the Y
Although you're 30, I still think you're purty
Let's give it that good old college try
I'm a homo erectus, got two connectives
Bones that I discovered yesterday
Tyrannosaurus lived in the forest
Died because his heart got in the way
I'm Dr. homo erectus, got two connectives
Bones that I discovered yesterday
Tyrannosaurus lived in the forest
Died because his heart got in the way
On Texas Music Radio, Johnny Marks,
riding through the canyons of your mind
with Kinky Freedman and the Texas Jew Boys.
Homo Connectus by Kinky Freedman
It gets to where you don't even know what's real anymore
and these new college kids come and go.
You're right about that.
They probably don't know what slack is.
They probably never heard of Church of the Subgenius, J.R. Bob Doggs.
This is a state university though.
You can't preach any church stuff here.
So this is like a socialist school?
Didn't they haul away that giant stark fist that the judge wanted
installed in the courtroom here in Cleveland?
But they said, no, no, that would be promoting one religion over another.
Another religion.
Yeah, they'd be promoting the subgenius religion of slack
over the Christian religion of failed prophecies.
They do promote nationalism though.
They're allowed to promote nationalism.
No, I'm not kidding.
If you go over to the cage, you will find dangling
flags
from banners all through the ceiling
is all the flags of all the countries of the world.
Well, that's internationalism.
That's global friendship, I think, at the university there.
Yeah, that's one world.
That's communist new age.
That's cool.
Except for the child slavery.
You know, it's a nice thing.
Well, that's how it works.
That's what college is.
It's a conspiracy.
It's one world.
It's child labor.
It's cool.
It's international.
It's decentralized.
It's a little dirt in your chocolate.
Yeah.
College is not a democracy.
It's multi-unit, unilaterally.
It's a dictatorship.
And I'm the dick.
Well, some people say you're the tater, but that would mean you're a spud.
What good is democracy when everybody's retarded?
What good is democracy when everyone else is a fascist around you?
Now, that's what we're waiting for.
Fascism for the people, baby.
Fascism back to the people.
The man has hogged fascism for too long.
That's right.
Each and every one of you gets your own special white dictator suit with a brand new pair
of shiny, shiny socks and huge masochistic boots.
Oh, I don't have time for this.
I have to go buy a single piece of fruit with a coupon and then return it, making people
wait behind me while I complain.
He still sounds sort of old.
Sort of real old.
I'm sorry.
He's this old.
What's going on with you?
I was born into anberty!
They were okay, not great, but pretty good.
They played the songs, I knew they would.
Some old, some new, the same formula stays true.
We can't concur, it's mediocre.
Sing, sing a song.
Make it simple, so all the kids can sing along.
Sing along.
The list keeps growing, the melody's been stolen.
Remind me of songs.
Songs.
From in the 70s.
You might fool the kids, but you don't fool me.
Have you ever heard of something called
Aboriginality?
Is it absurd to compose music?
No one's ever heard free
Dictability
Like a bosom
Will comfort them
My wonderful
LCD
It's underpowered
It makes your love be flowered
Ready to act up
Then bring its truth to day
Are you ready to rock?
How y'all doing tonight?
You couldn't stand your fucks
Maybe you wanna laugh
And you get the same time
I want to speak
This song sounds like 50
You've heard before
Mediocre
Sing, sing a song
Make it simple, so all the kids can sing along
Sing along
Subtitles by the Amara.org community
You're in college now.
You're gonna learn how to be smart and obey well.
How to succeed the way they're teaching you to succeed.
When the lecture's over, get up promptly, make sure those buttocks are seared tight together,
so there's no drippage.
Walk out of your desk and towards the door with a discreet smile,
knowing that you know what very few of your friends know and have learned at that lecture.
Kids, take advantage of it.
Whatever it is.
LEARN TO UN Nurul
You can tell why things didn't work here early but it never got too close.
Just젤
Let me tell
Don't lie
Believe in your dreams
ESPECIALLY
a year later
Mónica
Don't look at me.
I love you
Healthy
The garden is good.
The penis is evil.
Amazing, dear friends.
That was Osama's Lament by the great DJ Reverend Dr. Imam.
And now, The Bobs.
Rip, dip, dip, dim, bum, buh-bye Rip, dip, dip, dip, dim, bum, buh-bye
I can't sit and face
face up to the facts
I'm tense and nervous
and I can't relax
I cannot sleep
cause my bed's on fire
Don't touch me
I'm a real live wire
Psycho killer
Kiss go see
Far far far far
Run run run run
Run run run away
Psycho killer
Kiss go see
Far far far far
Run run run run
Run run run away
You start a conversation
You can't even finish
You're talking a lot
But you're not saying
anything
When I have nothing
to say
My lips are sealed
Say something once
Why say it again
Psycho killer
Kiss go see
Far far far far
Run run run run
Run run run run away
Psycho killer
Kiss go see
Far far far far
Run run run run run
Run run run run run away
Psycho killer
Rendered this time by
The Bob's
But worse things
Lay in store friends
Such as ESO Swamp Radio
From WCSB Cleveland
I wonder
You see a lot of PSAs
On the television
About people dying of ecstasy
How can that actually happen?
Is that a true falsehood
Or is that a false reality?
That's part of the
Global security act
The global security act?
Yeah it's against the law
To be un-sober now
Unless you're drunk
That's okay
But if you're anything else
It's not your right
To mess yourself up
Because it might embarrass
Joe Neighbor and Aunt Tilda
But how
So Dave what's your favorite
Club drug these days?
What's that stuff you snort like
Out of dirty sweat socks?
What's
Bengay
How long have you been
Bengay?
A mini mini mini mini
Locker room
Dave goes to Metropolis
A bunch of Bengay
Smeared around his nose
Hey kid you like poppers?
Got some Bengay popper here
I really appreciate the thought
People have probably wondered
When Princess Wee and I
Are out at dance clubs
We pull out this little
Vial and Sprite stuff
On each other's tongue
And I bet people wonder
It's church air right?
What is that?
Is that that new
Are they
That's also covered
In the new
Rave act I think
What?
Sour candy
The universal global rave act
We're acid heads
That's a sign that you're
An acid head
Malic
Acid head
Citric acid
What's going on?
Malic acid
And other
Blow your head off
Sour candies
That's what I've been
Reduced to
For getting high
I'm telling you
You're relying on your
Shallow very glands
To give you the big buzz
The big buzz
Is getting
Time to sit down
Hey the lights
Are going down
Oh wait a minute
Here they come
Whoa
You know I live a life
Of danger
For the FBI
Keeping heads
On our names
And on the land
On the sea
And the sky
And every single night
Before I go to bed
I get down on my knees
And say Bob
I'm a secret agent
Secret agent man
They're giving me
A number
But they take away
My name
I got one hell of a job
To perform
For the U.S. of A
Got the responsibility
Of our nation
Stopped security
And I got a job
For the FBI
But every night
And day
I salute the flag
And say
Thank you Connie
Cause I'm
I'm a secret agent man
Secret agent man
They're giving me
A number
But they take away
My name
Secret agent man
I'm a強 agent man
That's the kind of inefficiency
Secret Agent Man
They've given me a number
But they take away my name
Secret Agent Man
They've given me a number
But they take away my name
Secret Agent Man
By Santa Grouch
Although long time listeners would certainly recognize Santa Grouch
As actually being one of the amino acids
Secret Agent Man
Man I'm having a bad trip here
The voices in my studio are getting too messed up
They can't say the word
Kiss him, kiss him, kiss him
It's too messed up
My mind is melting
Society often forgives the criminal
But never the dreamer
Not for a while
Good citizens, we're gathered here tonight to pay homage to a very special individual.
A literal giant of a man.
And perhaps the last one to ever grace this fair earth.
In ancient times, it was believed that the sons of heaven,
who we would consider extraterrestrials or angels, if you will,
copulated with the daughters of earth to bring forth a race of giants.
Gaius, Gilgamesh, Prometheus, Hercules, Goliath, Paul Bunyan, Abe Lincoln,
the late great Frederick Nietzsche, Xena, Warrior Princess.
These people were not mere giants of size and strength,
but also of mind and spirit as well.
They are our highest aspirations.
They are what makes us special and makes us good.
Sadly, with each passing generation, we lose a little bit more of that magic.
And we become increasingly more mundane and just plain normal.
Every now and then, a throwback born.
But due to the fact that ignorance hates excellence,
these individuals are rarely allowed to reach their full adult superhuman potential.
The year? 1918.
The place? A small mining town of Alton, Illinois.
And on a cold winter morning of February 22nd, Robert Piercing Wadlow was born.
Sweet mother nature squeezed out one last giant to walk upon this earth.
And ironically, when he exited her sweet rosy vagina,
Robert was an average baby, measuring 2 feet 3 inches, 9 pounds 8 ounces.
But he continued to grow at an alarming rate.
At 6 months of age, he was 3'6".
At 18 months, he was 4'9".
And by the time he was 8 years old, he had reached the gargantuan height of 6 feet tall.
Many like to dwell on the fact that at 13, Wadlow was the world's tallest boy scout.
But forget, at the same age, he had read and fully comprehended every book in the local public library.
For you see, Wadlow was not a mere giant of size.
He was a giant of intellect as well.
At 23 years of age,
Wadlow had reached the age of 1.5.
He was still growing, but it did qualify him as the tallest person in history,
as recorded in the Goods Book of World Records.
Nevertheless, this pygmy world was not meant for one such as he.
His suit required three times the normal amount of material.
His shoes, a size 37 foot.
A pair cost a whopping $100.
And keep in mind, this is a lot of money back in 1930's pre-air Jordan America.
During this period in his life, every circus, traveling carnival,
and freak show in the country was vying for Wadlow to work for them.
But he patently rejected all of their offers.
Though his family was poor and they could have used the money,
he refused to submit to being gawked at by an endless stream of illiterate sub-humanoid mouth breathers
and toothless pumpkin humpers.
For you see, Wadlow was a giant of size, strength, intellect, but also of moral conviction.
He knew that his great body, his great mind, had to serve a great purpose.
He would not allow himself to be degraded for the mere enjoyment of others.
He knew that all humanity must benefit.
Luckily at this time, financial relief came and saved him from a life of destitution.
The International Shoe Company, which custom made all of his shoes,
hired Robert to travel around the country and promote their line of fine and affordable footwear.
His father heroically modified the family car, removing out the front passenger seat
so that Robert could sit in the back and stretch out his mighty legs.
Together, the father and son team traveled over 300,000 miles and visited 800 towns in 41 states.
They were passing on more than 200,000 miles.
This was not just good will for the shoe company.
On this odyssey, Wadlow used his titanic strength to aid in countless barn raisings
and personally knocked down any local bullies or greedy landowners a peg or two.
Wadlow was spreading enlightenment to every person he encountered.
He spoke of a world filled with solar-powered hover cars, 40-pound grapefruits,
an abolishment of the prison system, and legalized marijuana for all.
For all!
He envisioned a society in which cloning and gasahol would enable us to no longer be dependent upon anyone but our own.
Our own resources. Our own ambition is what would drive us.
Virtual immortality and the line of sex slaves would be rampant throughout the society.
No one would ever have to suffer again.
He offered us a utopia in which everyone would cast a giant shadow from the light of their own souls.
And he would free us from the clandestine, reptoid overlords that had befouled this beautiful planet since the dawn of time.
Sadly, the powers that be ensured that Wadlow would never see his perfect world come to fruition.
While making an appearance in Mastey, Michigan on July 3, 1940, Wadlow succumbed to a mysterious foot injury.
Experts concluded that it was merely an infection stemming from the numerous blisters that the giant often incurred on his majestic feet.
Lies!
Undercover government agents had actually injected him with a rare form of gangrene that had been perfected by the Germans during World War I.
When did this happen?
Probably when the giant stopped off at a roadside truck stop to relieve his mighty bladder.
He checked himself into a hospital with a fever of 120 degrees.
The nurses and doctors were passing out heat that his body was radiating.
The bungling doctors didn't know what to do.
Their hospital couldn't accommodate someone of his size.
He ended up in a hotel across the street with a series of beds roped together to support him.
Friends and neighbors from all over rushed to his side.
After an emergency blood transfusion from weaker humanoid stock, the infection lingered and his temperature continued to rise until at the precise stroke of midnight on July 15,
deersweet Wadlow shuffled off his weighty morgue.
The lucky few who gather around him say he bravely fought through the agonizing delirium from the mess of blood loss and morphine to utter these last words, which I quote here,
Lady Death has wide hips indeed. Being born was the hard part.
This dinner is our tribute to Robert Pearson Wadlow, poet, scholar, visionary, shoe salesman, and the giant within us all.
Wadlow!
The great Wadlow.
Really an amazing recording.
Uh...
Um...
Done by our friend Reverend Jason Bell.
With his friends Debbie Schwartz and Corey Smith.
Wadlow, the great American giant, and now revealed to be the great American subgenius.
Crash in the hall, top of the tables, dragging the rug, sun-venting, not kneeling.
My head at an angle, scraping the ceiling.
I give up and stretch the length of a hallway.
My arms are too wide and I stick like a snake that got stuck in the hose.
But the water won't run and push me back outwards.
Nothing is moving and the world is too small and the trees are like flowers.
Midget mother, mother me.
Arms that love cannot hold me.
Eyes that see are seen.
Am I a confusion?
No.
Yards of fabric, so much to close me, swallow me backwards, garb for a giant.
I cannot hold on anymore.
I play, I trample the teammates
My footprint's too large and my voice is too heavy
Seven sisters hang in the night sky
Where do I come from? Why won't you take me?
White crescent moon, the dagger's above me
Creator, protector, did you ever love me?
Midget mother, mother me
Arms of love cannot hold me
Eyes that see are seeing me
Am I a confusion? Am I a confusion?
The Wadlow Song
Jason Bell
Corey Smith
and Debbie Schwartz
Step up, kids. It's time to make your mark in the world.
Just look carefully into the monitor.
As the globe drifts by, so do you.
Drift slowly into your own gorgeous dreams.
I have no dreams.
Well, that's a common plight now.
People have been stopped from dreaming by the dream police.
And there is a dream police out there.
I don't know how far out they are, but I know they're somewhere around here.
They're not only correct.
They don't reflect our dreams, but they interject strange ideas that we have to carry through the next day.
And this is what's happening to so many of our students nowadays.
Their dreams have been co-opted.
Some by the circus folk.
Some by the government of the USA.
Some by the shallow-haired, small, smooth-shaven, bald-headed men in Langley, Virginia.
And the white coats.
Yeah, you're lucky if you get one with the white coats.
The ones with the little pink badges are so much worse.
They want to go deep into your psyche.
So kids, remember, the next time you sign up for a class, give it up.
Forget about school.
Yeah, well, they are giving it up now because I think tuition went up like 15%.
15% from what?
You know, you know what I mean?
Each semester.
This is a state institution.
15% from last semester.
And every state institution I've ever been in, you've got three squares a day.
They didn't give you any food.
They would just give you these little plastic squares.
It's kind of like that.
And they give you like a Ronald McDonald's toy.
And they would give you a good licking.
And then they'd give you a beating afterwards.
But I didn't squirm.
I knew one of those days I was going to get the third degree.
I think this is a different kind of institution, but some of the same things happen.
Well, they can't.
They cannot happen.
They keep repeating themselves over and over again.
That's the hell of this dimension and this university.
Hey.
Hey, you know, tomorrow when you go to class, stand up in class.
Just stand up in class, in the middle of class.
Wait until the professor stops and looks at you and just say,
Go to hell.
Go to hell, man.
Just throw the brick in the wall, dude.
Like, go to hell, man.
Yeah, but these children.
Like, I'm challenging you.
I'm challenging your authority.
No, these kids don't have it in them, Chaz.
They don't have the spism and the squank to observe the authorities.
Weren't you telling them earlier in your show that they needed to revolt and march in the streets like in the 60s and all that about something?
But Dr. Leguim said that as long as he can get a hamburger from his car, everything's okay and there's no reason to complain.
But what about the day you can't get that?
Then it's too late to ask.
Those days are coming soon, Stan.
And on top of that.
The day comes, all of a sudden, there is no more hamburger from your car.
That might be too late to ask.
You might go into one of these days and they give you a severed hand or something.
Well, he found out that those burgers were killing him anyway and he had to quit eating them.
Now when a good time turns around.
You must quit it.
You will never live it down.
Unless you whip it.
You know that no one gets away.
Till they whip it.
I said whip it.
Why don't you whip it.
Come on and whip it, whip it.
It's time to whip it, whip it, whip it.
I'll pay you if you whip it.
Come on and whip it, whip it, whip it.
I'll whip it.
Whip it itself.
The Devo song, a cover by Big Daddy.
And now, another horrible cover by The Bobs.
My brain.
They click.
The things.
They don't seem the same
Acting funny
But I don't know why
Excuse me
While I kiss the sky
The blaze all around
Don't know if I'm coming up or down
Never happy or in misery
Well, who is that girl who put a spell on me?
Yes, dear friends, I should probably explain the piece that I'm about to play.
Now, you know, I put this show, The Hour of Slack, together in my home office castle studio.
But on Thursday nights, I go into the station at WCSB, Cleveland State University,
and join Professor Chaz Smith on his live radio show, the last part of it, about midnight at 1230,
with Lonesome Cowboy Dave and so forth.
And we get these callers, and there's been this regular mystery caller over the last year or two.
Every now and then, we'll get this call from this guy that we call, or whatever it is, that we call the Oh Yeah Guy.
This last week, we got a...
Well, I don't know how to put it, but the Oh Yeah Man, or being, I don't know.
It was time to acknowledge his presence.
And here, we will hear when he first calls in to ESO Swamp Radio, the Oh Yeah Man.
Oh yeah.
And I think you're losing my point, whether or not...
I got rid of the wrong one.
Damn!
That is no wrong one.
There's no right one.
You got rid of something, and it's coming back.
Look, listen.
Oye nomas.
It's the real oye.
Oye.
Not the false oye.
I see an elderly woman in the basement masturbating furiously to a picture book.
It looks like...
No, no, it's the face of a giant...
I just tried to bleep out my...
...facial bathtub.
Oye.
Yes, she's about 79 years of age.
She's got one good eye, and the other one going skyward like a...
The prophet of oye is on.
Oye.
Poor bleepo got direct casted into the...
Talk about...
I think we should sit back and just relax.
Oye is the very least.
Oh, yeah, man.
Oye.
It's the live sex portion of the ESO broadcast.
I don't think it's sex at all.
I think it's one oi, and he's doing it over through a machine,
so that's why you hear the slap back.
You can hear the recurrence.
That's your wishful thinking.
It sounds like small children regurgitating in the background
if they've eaten all the cookies.
Oh, yeah.
They sure did.
I think maybe that's why they can't communicate a la Whipley.
His head's melting.
Bring him up on the screen a little bit.
Wow, look at that head melting away.
I've got to admit, I've wondered what had happened to this.
The oi, god.
What's the etymology?
Whatever it is.
What's the etymology of the oi, god?
Or the oi, loop, or the machine intelligence that does this.
I think someone captured a sound and looped it and played it back in this planet.
Oi.
I think it's an actual person.
Actual, actual, actual.
He is radio static.
He's not real.
You want to believe it's not real, but it's just real.
Radio static is real as your face, Dave.
Radio static is real, especially when it makes the right connections in the brain, isn't it?
Thank you once again, Mr. and Mrs. Foxy.
It's time to warm up our pants and get dancing.
What Bob did to Ted, oh yeah, did to us.
He's done it to so many.
You think about it.
He just slid it in a little bit.
And twisted it like a knife.
He twisted it like a knife.
It's a mantra.
Yeah, that's got to hurt.
I mean, what does it impart?
Oh yeah, it's a word for a smart man.
What does it impart?
There's factories with thousands of people at them all muttering under their breath, oi.
Oi.
See what they've done to this country?
All the factories for the, oi, are in Mexico or in Saipan or in Cebu City.
Or some of those places where they have big musketeers.
Oh no, there's some.
There's ones in California and Texas and probably Ohio.
Oh yeah, maquidores.
Factories full of oi people.
Yeah, little tiny, teeny maquidores behind a regular place made out of boxes and stuff.
Old ones, young ones, but they're all muttering under their breath as they were, oi.
A solemn cadence as they march through their tasks, their dreary, dreary ordeal every day.
Oye.
In Spanish it means...
Look, man.
Oye.
Oye, hombre.
Oiga.
It's the power.
The power and the glory of oye.
You have no idea what oye can get you through.
All the hard times, the rough times, and everything is really, really, really hard.
Then you just say, oye.
Oye.
And then you can get through.
You can get through anything.
Oye.
What does it mean?
But then, what does our very...
What do our very lives mean, my friends?
Well, we'll learn not only that, but also why the Martians are so crucial to our nuclear beer.
And even the Martian War in Series 9.
Ready?
Hello.
Now I can't hear it, okay?
Let's go.
Ready?
I'm hearing everything.
All right.
Applause.
Thank you very much.
Jesus.
You want all that echo and s*** in there?
Okay.
Thank you very much.
Can we turn him down?
Oh, s***.
Damn it, Jeff.
You don't even need a microphone.
Just take a s*** off of it.
Thank you very much.
You're welcome, Kinky.
You're welcome.
Thank you.
You're very welcome.
Many thanks.
Many thanks to you.
Thank you very much.
You're welcome, Kinky.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Thank you very much.
You're welcome, Kinky.
Now, don't put me up on a pedestal now.
I don't want to.
Thank you very much.
You're welcome.
Many thanks.
So welcome to you, Kinky.
Thank you very much.
You're welcome, Kinky.
No, no.
Don't get it.
Do your original.
Oh.
What is it?
You're welcome, Kinky.
Just the standard.
Go back.
Thank you very much.
You're welcome, Kinky.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Many thanks.
You're welcome, Kinky.
Many, many thanks.
You're very welcome.
Mucus Garcia.
Same back to you.
Thank you very much.
And me too.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Thank you very much!
You're welcome, Kinky.
Thank you!
You're welcome.
You're not getting the you're welcome, Kinky.
Well, you do!
You didn't, you know, the you're welcome, Kinky.
You're welcome, Kinky.
Yeah, I guess it was.
Nothing this way.
What do you do with Wayland Jenners old days?
The first time.
Thank you very much!
You're welcome, Kinky.
No!
Damn it, something's wrong with that, Jeff.
You're welcome, Kinky.
Yeah, that was what it was.
All right.
Thank you very much!
You're welcome, Kinky.
Thank you!
You're welcome.
Many thanks.
You're welcome, Kinky.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Do we have enough to work with her?
You didn't record that?
What the hell's going on here?
Thank you very much.
You're welcome, Kinky.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Many thanks.
You're so very, so very welcome.
Thank you.
You're welcome, Kinky.
You've been a wonderful crowd.
Well, thank you.
Thank you very much.
No, thank you.
You're welcome, Kinky.
All right.
I hope they were...
Was anything recorded?
Oh, yeah.
Oh yeah.
Can you get to that one?
I think he's getting to it.
Oh yeah.
Don't be afraid.
When the thing goes down,
it's going down.
Go towards the light.
Keep your eyes looking skyward.
Keep your nostrils firm and erect
like the rest of the perfect sky
on those tiny little parts.
When the light comes to you,
I'll run with you.
When you're ready,
I'll take that.
Oh yeah.
Well,
oh yeah.
Until next week,
keep your head on tight.
Back to the Wings.
Zach and Bill.
And now,
as we say farewell,
a little bit of Al Tijuana
with the Peter Gunn theme.
Praise Bob.
Have a nudge.
Have a treat.
First we'll play,
and then we'll eat.
Al Tijuana meets Peter Gunn.
For more information, please check out www.subgenius.com.