Oooo-oo-oooo.
ðŸŽµðŸŽµðŸŽµ
That was Michael Pepe, dear friends.
And we've also heard a whole bunch of cool new Lee Murr cut-ups,
which we've got more of for this hour of Slack, number 981.
And thanks to Soso Dada for the beginning titles of this particular show.
And now, Pimp Daddy Supreme will tell us about the record business.
Music has an interesting power and influence in our lives, doesn't it?
Music is an area that affects you as a teen probably more than any other medium.
Who's making your choices for you?
Will you think about this for just a moment?
It's the record business.
It should be obvious anything with such power to do good can also be twisted to do evil.
Yes, music is a powerful force for good or evil.
Young people use music to reflect their own ideas, frustrations, questions and attitudes.
And some of their music responds to these questions.
What kind of music dominates your life?
Are you deciding for yourself?
Or are you allowing Hollywood to direct your life?
Let's tell it like it is.
Popular music is helping to corrupt the youth of America.
Hi, my name is...
The big bold beat may disguise the message.
And many kids tell me they really don't pay any attention to the words.
But you know as well as I do that those words come through loud and clear.
Suck it to me baby.
Gimme, gimme, gimme.
But is that what the kids are listening to?
Not necessarily.
We are the kids of the world.
Guess what the world needs now is sex, shock and...
Hold on a minute.
What kind of music is this pop music?
I think you know the answer to that.
Conforming to the world's ideas, these people are merely following the crowd.
Music.
On the other hand...
Jam the box.
You know differently.
Teenagers, don't let the world around you squeeze you into its mold.
Stop, look and listen.
Music must be free.
Does that make sense?
But maybe where we disagree is what we mean by music.
And it's characterized in songs like this one with which we conclude.
Music.
Music has chopped off and disÙŒ.
ading to life.
Information that orders and tomorrow, we will nothing but mystery.
To put it more bluntly, do not press charged time.
Tom nota ****othes, turning at doorICO perfect line.
Any Î´Î¹ explode reel.
What?
who was driving his neighbor to a campground in the Angeles National Forest.
Killed by a bullet to the head.
At least 10 people have collapsed and destroyed 15 homes.
In the northern Gaza Strip, defense lawyers from eight African countries
are suspended out of fear of more PR news.
In the latest from Wall Street, the 3610581 to 2090.
I'm stranded in PR News, Washington.
New drugs, new treatments.
These men must keep pace with time.
And now observe that man.
The one carrying a briefcase, a salesman.
He too must keep pace, not with formulas or drugs, but with people.
His stock in trade is people, and people change.
It's the middle of the night, and your mommy and your daddy are sleeping.
Sleeping.
Mom and dad are sleeping.
Sleeping in a jar.
The jar is under the bed.
æ¸¯
The jar is the way!
No crime benefitìžï¿½anging with
brings happiness, wrinkles, flaws, scuttling, attention of the nation,
when you try, when you see.
This is how extraction stages can help kill cancer
six know
states of the world
know and those who know don't say. So I should shut up. But instead I'll keep at it. Because
friends, slack is different for each person. Ideally it's something for nothing. And for
some people slack is a lot of money. For some people slack is sex. But for some people
slack is stamp collecting, bird watching, tinkering with their little computer, who
knows, you know. Everybody has their own weird perverted idea of slack. But friends, Bob
is sex. Bob is money. And Bob is slack. It's that simple. We've been here trying to explain
all this stuff, but it doesn't matter. Those are just words. When you look at that face,
that's really all you need to know.
So if you're a person who's got a lot of money, you need to know that you're not
going to be a slave to that. When your eyes fall upon that dotted dot pattern of a face,
if you think, that's kind of cool and I don't know why, then you know you are a subgenius.
It is only Bob. All the rest of it is just our pathetic human preacher bullshit and an
attempt to make some more money for his mighty empire. But really all you need to do is just
stare into that face. It's pure religious love. And boys,
it's not queer if it's Bob. You know, it's a religious thing. It's a religious love.
Friends, you know, you don't try to over-rationalize religion. That just, it's crazy. Religion
has to be crazy. It can't make any sense. By definition, that would wreck it. Let me
put it this way. Bob sold it. I smoked it. That settles it. That's all I need to do.
Bob said it.
Did I have faith? That's what faith is all about. Some people say, oh, I don't believe
in miracles. I don't believe in magic. Friends, there is a type of magical miracle that happens
every day, a million times a day. And I don't mean the beauty of a leaf falling from a tree.
The miracle, the incredible, unbelievable miracle that happens every day is that so
many people can believe such stupid crap.
And yet they do. And that is the miracle of faith, my friends. And we will not let any
other religion be any crazier than we are as far as faith goes. Bob sold it. I smoked
it. That settles it. As Bob said, you must learn to pull the wool over your own eyes.
You're still blind, but at least it's your wool and not theirs. So, you know, again,
the conspiracy.
As he said, this is a very ì´ê²ƒ click b.
As everybody good.
I came from this country.
I come from this world is absolutely, totally a!
parents of God, creepy.
Just because you.
Every ë§ï¿½ Protean laid your feet.
ави Anyone win nrio
Too much twist and be just like that.
So there's a change.
Was it her first love?
A test to the Alexander The Pope?
And an escape huh.
watching MTV. You know, friends, it is such a delicate line to figure out what is the true slack for you and what is the false slack. Some people think that slack means being lazy, and for some that certainly is true. But then there are other, those are the rewardian subgeniuses. For some of us, we emerge in tiles, for instance. Slack is when we're walking, but at what we wanted to work at. And then you forget to eat.
You forget to drink or breathe or pee. You just make a big puddle under your desk and keep working or whatever it is you do. You know, maybe you're a sports guy and you like to run or something. You get into the zone where everything is true and right, and you know you're doing the right thing. And friends, that's when you suddenly know that life is worth living. You are actually pretty smart, and everything truly is as psychedelic as that old t-shirt that you can't fit into anymore.
That is the thought that you have to hold on to.
That is the slack. The moment of slack.
Sometimes the more undeveloped subgeniuses come to me and go, well, I paid my 20 euro, but I still don't have slack.
No, you have misunderstood everything. You have to make the slack.
You're just paying us to give you a pep talk so you won't forget.
We know how difficult it is to be alone in the space.
We know how difficult it is to be alone in this world and be a loner.
You know, some of us, well, this is an organization.
It's a disorganization for non-joiners.
So it's never really been very big.
I guess it wasn't a good business idea.
But the great thing about Bob is you don't want to have one of those other gods breathing down your neck telling you what to do.
You don't want a bunch of other religious, your fellow religious fanatics.
You just want to be alone.
But you like Bob.
You can be alone with Bob.
That's the miracle of our very special guru friends.
But so many people are laboring under this addiction, a foul addiction to money.
Filthy lucre.
Well, actually, we could use more of that ourselves.
Bob is not a communist exactly.
He doesn't want everyone to be equally.
Poor.
No, he wants everyone to be equally rich.
Gluttonously, piggishly rich.
But without working.
Yeah.
According to Bob, there's no hard evidence to prove Bob's story either.
And it's not going to be two-headed blow job, contrary to popular demand.
I thought we were dancing with a hard-on.
I don't know.
It's far from a struggle.
It's hard to go on pä»”ily.
Take it with aationsa fancy baton and say,
our aussi- holds it on.
A-a-a-ing.
Well, a passable case of tricks, isn't it?
You know what?
Bob.
Did anyone mention Bob?
Yeah, boy.
Bob's arriving next week.
Divine.
Oh, excuse me.
Bob.
Outstanding.
Come on and sit down, Bob.
Luteus Maximus.
Right?
That's right.
Yeah, yeah.
People lost in the world of pills.
They're good.
Yes, I guess you could say that.
Ha, ha.
Dei Mater Alma.
So nice to be with you again.
Start a new week together?
Hmm?
Tomorrow, tomorrow.
We'll start the day tomorrow with a song or two.
I'm not the only solo.
Choose all the hit and run.
Count back to the first of the attack.
Start.
First, you'll need a leg ere.
touman.
At the beginning of the day,
Yeah.
Well,
I'm going to receive the
strength that yourId rice ofbreeds can keep what.
Can be in the way of spasmodicion on the sea.
You can whatever it.
Hm.
Okay.
I'll tell you this is not fluffy enough.
and return to a world of cold and unemotional galaxy beings.
I will give them my report, and I will be destroyed.
I have failed in my mission, not because I am weak,
but because you are stronger.
Can you draw me? Can you draw me?
We publish a value to the international today,
charge the Argentine government with blatant violations of human rights,
of the very bone, code, nucleus,
entre the house, bloom, blood,
turn it into a sign of host.
So, deliver, write me,
cheat on all the challenges you enjoy.
You look up and I'll be gone.
Bit by bit, I came for you, for you, I came for you,
but you did not heed my urgency.
Hotel, motel, what you gonna do today?
Make it a camp, I'll be out in the cold,
watching those detectives.
Oh, I'll say shoot, shoot, shoot,
shoot, shoot, now,
fuel, got for you.
We're painting, we're painting our time.
We're cleaning, we're cleaning our time.
Who are we? We're the communication people,
the people whose talk is stripped of state of the art technology.
It's disposable, reversible,
reusable with almost any leading round of idea,
including our DevOps line, your work.
Hey, boo-boo, I'll save you.
Whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop.
Get them doggies moving, bridge you.
Hey, you're talking to me, huh, boo?
Yeah.
Hey, number nine, the waltz you sing,
the twist, El Dorado.
Can you draw me in on it? Can you draw me in on it?
I remember a wild fish.
A guy's been in a train station in the rain,
his inside's kicked out.
Go ahead and shoot him. He'll be doing me a favor.
Oh, bonjour, Monsieur Damse, vous plait.
My English told me that I've been out of my head.
The way you described it, you said it'd be better dead than alive.
Dripping legs hanging from their rags.
Aluminum styrofoam, people at the clock,
five o'clock, go home, eat the baby, eat the baby.
Daddy's milk a little fatty.
Somebody must be screaming, dinner.
Everyone sits down.
Always work today, dear.
Bang, bang, can I have a piece, honey?
What's in the frying pan?
Case in point, a young man trapped in a carnal milieu of mayhem,
fantasy and compulsion.
Just east of the money, in the south of the twilight zone.
And everybody wants to get in there, yeah.
For those of you who've just tuned in,
the President of the United States has been shot.
Pause for station identification.
Mr. Spencer, look out!
Gateway Deep, San Francisco.
I scare myself when I let my guard down.
Who's the boss?
John?
My gas away, it's me for the heaven's shore.
So do our minutes hasten to their end.
So come to the middle end.
You are here participating in an atomic move.
Oh, your baby has gone down.
The first radiation from heaven whooshed flattened the city.
What red devil is this city?
Was God's fire.
God's a revolution.
And they made all these deals.
And the evil just kept going up.
and up and up, and God just turned around right then, went zoosh!
And he opened the sixth seal, and he opened,
the sun became black as sackcloth,
the full moon became like blood,
and the sky vanished like a scroll that has rolled up.
And I saw an angel call to the birds of midheaven,
come, gather for the great supper of God,
to eat the flesh of men.
But the filthy supper realizes the whole five scoundrels are empty.
He is freed from the cycle of birth, death, and suffering.
Yes, dear friends, that was the great Michael Pepe,
the Reverend Michael Pepe, or Pope Imho Pepe,
as he is also known.
Before that,
friends, this whole show has had a lot of
cut-ups and collages by
Mr. Fernanda Nande Lee Murr.
That's, um,
just in general, it's suffused
with that.
We also heard before that some Frank Zappa,
a little bit of ancient Frank Zappa,
and before that, some Ray Hay,
the guitar player for the Swinging Love Corpses.
They're playing with the amino acids at X Day,
and he's the first one to take the lead.
So, uh, I think that's the thing that's going to be
And now some more Lee Murr from, uh, PR News.
From PR News in Washington,
I'm skeptical of PR News in Washington.
Federal Reserve Chairman Alan Greenspan
and former CIA Director George Tenet
have been jailed outside of China.
Lawyers will be illegal.
It's not clear if 20 political parties
in Mozambique raised spam again.
President Bush has been thrown out by a judge.
The ruling effectively overturns presidential elections.
He has been sharply criticized
for the nation's highest civilian honor.
On Wall Street, 52-690-14216-1202-625.
Greetings. Welcome back.
Great to have you with us, uh, ladies and gentlemen.
It's Al Rushbow here, the EIB Network.
I am loaded today.
Hey, it's me.
Cancer and anemia
with uncontrolled high blood pressure and blood clots.
I'm the germy mess.
Rheumatoid arthritis.
It's so good to have
serious fatal infections, lymphoma,
nervous system and blood disorders and headache.
Fabulous.
Call now to find
liver injury, heart failure, blood disorders,
tuberculosis, nervous system disorders and lymphoma,
allergic reactions, hives,
trouble breathing and low blood pressure.
For you.
My fellow citizens,
I have requested this opportunity
to talk about the tragedy
which happened last Friday
evening.
This morning, I entered a plea of guilty
to the charge of leaving Massachusetts
on my own.
Kittens
tied up
with strings
These are a few
of my favorite
things
Men!
Oh, baby.
Clitoris.
Coitus.
Oh.
And now for our weird song of the day.
It's named
Acid Rain.
And every day we run outside.
Until the acid rain.
And the days when we die.
We'll be riding in the acid rain.
Acid Rain.
And every day.
We'll be riding in the acid rain.
To get our new face
complexion.
With the flesh hanging out on our face.
Ahh!
Oh.
The sun has set.
We will die.
We have a story to tell.
Of truly end up like this.
We have all hurried out for your company.
A thinly packed
You stand
out toward
a pleading
town.
Speaking.
And we hate
the acid rain.
But we love that we're not gonna die.
to tear our face off!
Aaaaah!
The magic of dancing
The magic of music
And the days
when we die
they get us fickle world records
and they get a close on us
We're just gonna be a pile of flesh
with clothes on
Aaaaah!
And then we're gonna have to be in parachute pants on
and it's like aaaaah!
Give us some sleep here
Aaaaah!
Somebody throw an MX missile at me
And now we have a mic
We have a mic
We really like to have it mic
If you can hear us punching now
We're really gonna be in a fight room now
I'll help! Listen!
We're gonna sit in a coach
We're gonna eat in a can of lava
Before most of the money is spent
We're gonna use a pillow
Do me a favor
Tell me where I can get my pickup truck kicked right
Without wasting a time
And every day we come aaaaah!
We come around down here in the school aaaaah!
I told you I'll hit our room with some aspirin
Woah! Woah!
...
And every day we're not so good
We play a devil and it's so stupid
...
This'll be you darling
Try thisÙ„ÙŠ devil
Got a Isle
I hate you!
No!
Ha ha!
...
And the end!
And the end is coming right now.
And now, we're gonna let my mom listen to this song.
Bye.
That's Pimp Daddy Supreme
did that.
Self Slayer, Reverend Self Slayer,
who lives in France, has been posting
Pimp Daddy material,
which we've been scraping off of
alt.binary slack.
It was all lemurs
before that.
From top to bottom, all the way down.
From TR News
in Washington, I'm in a bombing and shooting
attack on Saturn's largest moon.
The European Space
Probe said it would not retaliate after a meeting
with a US delegation in North Korea
and Indiana.
President Bush wants $500
to spite more than 5 million low-income
students. Bush says
he'll ask to be explored by spacecraft.
Emails.
North Korea says they beat and humiliated
them for PR News.
Spain's Basques have officially
presented a plan for making a soft landing
on PR News. Washington.
Sh-this hot slumps you.
We smell sausage.
Okay.
I just can't understand it.
Maybe it's just because you're stupid.
Oh. Yeah. So that's it.
That's the oldest excuse in the world.
Oh.
How do you see why I was amused?
No.
Wow.
My fellow Americans,
the Great
Society rests on poverty
for all.
But that is
just the beginning.
The Great Society
is a
place where every child
can find racial injustice.
It is a place where
leisure is boredom and
restlessness.
It is a place where man
serves nature.
But most
of all,
the Great Society
is not in our
classrooms.
Aristotle said,
men come together in
cities in
order to rebuild the entire
urban United States.
Worst of all,
expansion is eroding
precious and time-honored
loneliness and boredom
and indifference.
And our society will never
be great.
Once our
natural splendor is
destroyed,
it can never be recaptured.
And man
can no longer wonder at
nature. His
spirit will wither and his sustenance
be wasted.
So we must give every child
hours of labor
to find new ways to
stimulate the love of the Great Society.
My Lords
and members of the House of Commons,
my government will continue
to pursue policies
which entrench and promote
international terrorism and
organized crime.
A bill will be introduced to extend
the serious organized crime agency
and the crime that flows
from it will be strengthened.
My government
will continue to take action
to secure high levels of
manslaughter. In particular,
the bill will introduce a new offense
of corporate employment
as it reforms the welfare
state. My government
has always recognized the importance
of drug abuse,
to help to reduce further
the numbers of those engaged in
training and education.
There will be further
legislation to tackle
growth and prosperity
in the United Kingdom and
elsewhere.
My government is committed to reducing
educational opportunity
and to promoting
mental illness in Northern Ireland
to support the continuing
exploitation.
We look forward to receiving
a state visit of His Excellency
the President of the Republic of Canada
and will use this opportunity
to combat human rights
on both sides of the Atlantic
and will work with the international
community to consolidate
the distribution of nuclear,
chemical and biological weapons
to good causes.
My government will work to strengthen
drug smuggling and international
crime and reduce
democratic reform
to improve performance.
My Lords and members
of the House of Commons,
I pray that the blessing
of Almighty God may rest
upon your councils.
I am the President of the United Kingdom
and I am here to speak
to you about the
importance of the
development of the
international community
I am here to speak
about the
importance of
international community
and the
international
and international
community.
I am here to speak
about the
international community
and the
The people,
the people of Scotland
also
Fight for
sw Mystery
and
Suffeste
for
the
know when the countdown's getting lower every day. Ten and nine, eight and seven, six and five and four,
call upon the Savior while you may. Three and two, coming through the clouds in bright array,
the countdown's getting lower every day. Somewhere in outer space, God has prepared a place
for those who trust him and obey. Jesus will come again, and though we don't know when,
the countdown's getting lower every day. Ten and nine, eight and seven, six and five and four,
call upon the Savior while you may. Three and two, coming through the clouds in bright array,
the countdown's getting lower every day. Somewhere in outer space, God has prepared a place for those who trust him and obey.
The countdown's getting lower every day.
Can I continue to follow Martha Stewart?
Your subgenius doesn't preclude believing in any other faith. In fact, you can believe in pretty much anything.
It'll all work in... Our doctrine is so fluid and hypocritical that you can pretty much believe anything and everything in the book of the subgenius.
Yeah?
Are we there yet?
Are we there yet? Friend, that is a question only you can answer.
I love turning it around like that. That makes people feel so crappy. I'm afraid only you can answer that question.
The hokey pokey is what it's all about.
Right, maybe the hokey pokey indeed is what it's all about.
Turn it all around.
Do you like the hokey? I don't like the hokey pokey.
That's not really an answer.
No, well...
It's kind of hokey. You're just repeating what she said.
I'm sorry.
That's it. There's your answer. I'm a sorry, pathetic faker.
I think you're cool.
See?
Okay, what else?
Well, actually, it looks like the video... There's a new video, set of Bob videos out, which is what has been showing back there.
That's what I've been doing for the last year.
It's replenishing my animation and video cutting skills. Nobody reads anymore.
But I've been selling our old video, Arise.
A lot of people have been buying that, especially since I started giving it away.
You can download... By the way, I will proudly tell you this.
All of our best work, you can download right now off of a news group called Alt Binary Slack, and another one called Alt Binary's Monterre movies.
All of it for free, and they're not crappy copies. They're the kind that you can put onto a CD and play it in your DVD player.
It's not a DVD, but it's closed.
And ever since we announced that and started giving our stuff away...
By God, if I didn't start... The orders tripled.
So now I've got three orders.
So, you know... Yeah.
He, uh...
I don't understand.
He's good for keeping passports and, uh, waterproofing cases.
Now, I thought you weren't in the memory column.
Oh, no, I'm the memory part.
She understands.
I understand.
And translates.
You'll be on the center and do it.
He remembers.
I'm the read-only memory.
She's the real intelligence behind the thing.
Sort of like the pipe in Bob. The pipe is the real brain.
Bob is just missing the...
We are smoking you.
Bob is there.
You're taking the question, though?
No.
You're on the air.
You see, in the Far East, it is spoken that there is a sacred tortilla, a Bob's head,
in, uh, is it Plano, Texas?
That was, uh, yeah, that was a long, long time ago.
This is supposedly more holy than the, the, uh, the grail, the Christian grail.
It has magical powers, I am...
Well, it was back in the 80s, but then they started appearing on in, like, everybody's tortillas.
What about the...
Eventually, they just started marketing these damn Dobbshead tortillas, and then the market
was flooded and lost its holiness, and...
What about the dinner roll?
The, the dinner roll that was discovered?
There was a dinner roll also in Plano.
Yeah, that was in Plano, Texas.
You're right.
There's a famous photograph of that in, uh, Book of the Subgenius that...
Where can I come to adore and worship at the Bob's?
Uh...
I...
You must kill Bob.
You must find him and kill him.
What do you want, jewels, wealth, travel the world?
Because we might be willing to...
Oh...
We might be willing to trade children for...
For power.
Really?
Yes.
That's a wonderful voice you've got there, let me tell you.
Well, when you are...
Well, we might have a work study plan.
...a very good day with every male voice.
It gets you around better.
I bet.
We might have a, uh, some sort of a work, barter, work, work study plan at the Dobbs town.
Good.
Home for slackless children.
How big is the cage at Dobbs town?
Could you do the...
How large would the cage be for me?
Very, very large.
So that even you, who are a strong like bull, make good wife, you'll...
I thank you very much.
All right.
But praise the Bob.
Praise the Bob.
I think that guy had us confused with that other cult that worships the Bob.
I don't know.
Who is the Bob, anyway?
You're on the air, by the way.
It's, uh, 6873515.
Call him.
Yeah, Bob, you know.
With the Lincoln.
Yeah.
When you say Lincoln, what class of...
What class of object are you referring to?
We're talking about an automobile.
No.
You're on the air.
Hey, how's it going?
It's Bucky calling from Canada.
Well, Bucky, good to hear from you again.
How you been?
I'm all right.
I was just calling in.
I got a couple questions and I'm way behind because I started calling in about half an
hour ago.
Oh, yeah.
But it's one of those ring, ring, ring, then my phone hangs up thing.
I know how that is.
My question is...
Actually, my first thing is a point.
The opposite of Burning Man, wouldn't that be like a wet woman?
Yeah.
But somebody else would be...
Well, Drowning Woman was...
We thought about calling it Drowning Woman, but then we thought, no, that's negative marketing.
That would...
So we were trying to hone it.
How about Non-Flammable Woman?
What really is the selling point?
And that's...
Non-Flammable Woman.
... really is Naked Woman as opposed to Burning Man.
You actually...
Flame-Retardant Woman.
Fire-Retardant Woman.
In appropriate...
I'm sorry.
You know what?
I think I had to bleep that out because you mentioned a price on the air.
Oh.
I'm not sure, though.
We're not really advertising the event, but I don't know.
I have no idea.
No.
Burning Man is actually a non-commercial event.
I know it is.
We've got another caller here.
We're going to expand the panel to four callers now.
You're on the air.
In appropriate.
Yeah.
Anyway...
Wow.
What was that?
In appropriate.
That was...
You know, when...
That's the guy.
That's the guy from the FCC who calls up to make sure that everything is according
to oil.
You know what you have to do, Senator?
You have to find...
There's an FCC song out by Eric Idle.
Oh, yeah.
It's...
I can't even say the title of it because it would be bleeped.
Oh, yeah?
Try it.
It's Blank You Very Much, the FCC.
Oh, yes.
It's not blank.
It's an expletive.
Expletive.
Oh, boy.
Well, you know what?
I'm going to say that right now.
Fuck the FCC is political.
Good point.
It's politically protected speech and we have aired a disclaimer.
Did you just...
I can't tell if that went out on the radio or not.
Oh, shit.
Did that go or did you have to bleep yourself?
That went.
It went.
And I think...
We haven't gotten obscene yet.
We've been...
We're allowed to be indecent, but we're not allowed to be obscene.
Right.
And because that was a political statement, it is by definition not obscene because it...
It has serious...
It worked for me.
It has serious literary...
Oh, is that what they're calling it?
...notistic merit.
Yeah.
I mean, I think...
You're exercising your right to really free speech.
That's right.
We've got one more caller here now.
You're on the air.
Absolutely wrong.
What happened to pig man?
Pig man...
I heard pig man's voice earlier tonight.
Pig man called up just for a second and got cut off.
I don't remember pig man exactly.
I'm certain it was pig man.
I've barely recognized the voice, but I think I heard something, someone, something like
that.
I don't remember pig man, exactly.
Who doesn't run into desk when it's dark.
Okay.
Yeah, pig man.
There's pig man.
That's true.
pronounces it differently from pig man.
Yeah.
Yes.
That's an PTS...
No.
No, pig man.
Well, actually what they are doing is...
They're having an到底 to say.
Well, just so we're clear about the surface, they call poase asITTRT Europa.
Poase.
Poase, yes.
Another idea.
Poase.
Poase, yes.
It's just so, it's not associated with paper.
Cleveland back here in Canada.
Am I drinking imported beer?
It's called re-imported.
Re-importation, just like...
We let you take drugs across the border?
Right, like a lot of Americans go to Canada
to get prescription drugs for the cheaper government
price-controlled price over there.
Right.
And then they bring them back to the U.S.,
even though they were made in the U.S. originally.
We call that re-importation of prescription drugs.
We figured that the beer would be technically,
that the word would have to be deported.
The beer was deported.
From PR News in Washington,
I'm described as a paltry and miserly car bombing in Baghdad
during a raid on parts of Wisconsin, Michigan, Indiana, and Afghanistan,
and a buffer between the expanding European Union and northern Ohio.
Sami Mohammed Ali Saeed Al-Jahaf, Abu Omar Al-Khourdi
will be part of a larger package in the war on PR News.
The God Almighty.
We'll have to make it another week.
The.
Very soon.
And then all of a sudden there was a Canadian flag on the screen.
You know, I never really asked.
Yeah.
It's about time.
He's stagged.
Marshall.
It's about time.
He's stagged.
Aren't you the delivery boy?
I know.
Sweet little pussy.
The God Almighty.
I hear you got a sweet little pussy.
You know, I never really asked.
He's stagged.
Who's a commercial?
You know, I never really asked.
But you have to assume.
Then how good are you?
The God Almighty.
Yeah.
Then how good are you?
He stagged.
The God Almighty.
Then how good are you?
He told me that the world is in big trouble and he wants me to-
Not now, Bob.
You know, I never really asked.
Then how could I argue?
Andy, I met God today.
Cool.
Then what good are you?
What good are any of you?
Must I do everything myself?
Over here.
Cool.
Do you have special powers?
Did he?
God is the most powerful being in the universe.
Do you have special powers?
Did he?
God is the most powerful being in the universe.
What's going on?
He's taking over.
It's horrible.
Is that a pantsuit?
Don't ask.
He's dead.
He stagged, he stagged.
Can he turn his arm into a missile launcher like Megalor?
Well, I saw him make himself a hundred feet tall.
He stagged, he stagged.
He certainly does climb.
I'd like to get a little bit of that jobs on my dork.
Can he turn his arm into a missile launcher like Megalor?
Well, feline animal is not available for petting in any petting zoo.
Can he turn his arm into a missile launcher like...
I see the alien hardware I'm not, you know.
It's huge.
Where's the devil?
I saw him on a cat.
I just don't want to see the alien hardware I'm not, you know.
It's huge.
Well, where's the devil?
Can he turn his arm into a missile launcher like...
I see the alien hardware I'm not, you know.
My little saber.
My little smilodon.
Can he turn his arm into a missile launcher like Megalor?
Well, I saw him make himself a hundred feet tall.
He's a little...
No.
He's coming.
I swear, I saw him with my own eyes.
Uh, just like the UFO you saw when we were camping.
Hey, you can't tell me that the government has a helicopter that can veer sideways with that kind of velocity.
And, uh...
I know you scientists would love to get home and get a few DNA samples off of my...
You can't tell me that the government...
That may or may not have been Psychic TV.
I really don't know.
It was labeled Psychic TV when I downloaded it.
And before that, we heard, of course, some PR news from, uh...
Leemur.
We heard some radiosynesthesia.
That's Dr. Sinister's show on WCSB in Cleveland on Sunday nights.
Right after the hour of Slackware.
We use that show a lot, and it uses us.
And before that, we heard some radio synesthesia.
And before that, I think a little bit of yours truly preaching at Starwood.
If you need to know more about the Church of the Subgenius or the Swinging Love Corpses,
which is what produced the music in the background,
please check out www.subgenius.com.
Or you can write to us at Hour of Slack or Bob or Subgenius Foundation
at Box 181417, Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
118.
Accept no substitutes.
We've got another line blinking here.
Dare we see who's on here?
You're on the air.
Hello.
Man, what's with this, uh...
You want to wait or no with the line?
What is it?
It's a coded message from God.
Actually, it's from the Illuminati, actually.
Who is this guy?
The ringing, the frequency of the ringing phone.
When, you know, you hear the phone ringing,
it's actually vibrating a specific frequency.
It's a coded message from the Illuminati.
I don't understand this.
Well, then you're in some trouble because you're the only hope.
Don't you understand the Illuminati are trying to contact you?
Because you are the chosen one.
This is not right.
You alone will have the power to save us.
This is not right. I don't agree with this.
So what?
Anyway, enough of that guy.
I just cut him off. I do that.
Eh, and the shit's a bit...
Can I say that on the radio?
I guess.
If there's anything you should be able to say on the radio, it's that.
Yeah.
But I'm going to free up another line for you guys.
You can take some more calls.
All right. Hey, you know what?
I keep forgetting your name.
I mean, I recognize you and meet Bucky.
Right.
Okay, Bucky.
He's named that for those giant teeth that stick out in front,
like a cartoon squirrel man.
Yeah, that's exactly what I meant.
Huge, giant buck teeth.
Okay, I'm not going to forget.
He can cut down a telephone pole.
When you get him real drunk,
he can cut down a telephone pole in about half an hour.
I actually stole the name from our Buckminster Fuller.
Although people keep on...
Bucky Fuller.
People keep on insinuating that I stole it from Captain America's sidekick, Bucky.
No, I figured that you stole it from Buckminster Fuller.
I like the Bucky ball.
I know there are many subgeniuses who are Buckminster Fuller.
Buckminster Fullerites.
He's their lawn derper staff for many.
Well, yeah, but that's the problem.
See, I was partway through reading Synergetics
when I made a post to All Black Slack and had to pick a name,
and off I went with Bucky.
I just like that.
I never finished reading it.
So all the people that want to talk about our Buckminster Fuller,
I'm only on page 60.
I like the...
And it's like a 500-page book.
I like the fact that he went by Buckminster instead of whatever his first name was.
You know, like...
I think it was Richard.
Richard.
Or Buckminster.
Which name do you want to...
Dick.
Go by.
Dick Fuller.
Dick sounds like a joke name.
I think I see why now.
You know, a brush salesman joke name.
Buckminster?
Now that's a name.
Dick Fuller.
And there are molecules named after him now, such as...
Right, they're not going to call him Dicky Ball.
They're the Bucky Ball and the Bucky 2.
For obvious reasons.
C60.
If you call the carbon, that type of carbon arrangement, if that's what it is, a Dicky
Ball, that would be laughable, risible.
He would turn in his grave.
That's right.
Well, Bucky Ball is pretty funny if you...
Yeah, that's a...
Yeah, but it's cute.
If you're me and people call you Bucky and start talking about Bucky Balls, it's a little
bit...
That's a little bit weird too.
Right.
That's the kind of thing you see at X-Day.
You see a lot of Bucky Balls at X-Day if you hang around the pool.
Gross.
Oh, boy.
Horrible.
Anyway, that's enough for me.
I've explained my...
I've explained my name and I'll see you guys later.
All right.
Bye.
You have a good night.
Where did the shakes go?
Too much.
Down at the bank.
Gun.
Knee.
Prog.
Little.
Just went...
Yeah.
Like that.
Two.
Yeah.
No.
The rat drove off and left in there.
What's yours done?
Cream puff went...
Do other people's children like this find out?
No.
That's right.
Yeah.
No.
Boys and Queen.
And here is Boy Flop.
The deity I got my girl's love.
Oh, no.
I don't know about the next time, but the little delights went.
You've got to make him stop.
Wow.
Try buying if you can talk.
Not talk.
Not make him stop.
Try to talk and find out.
Boy make him stop.
Not talk.
Right.
And that's a wrap.
Friends, you're listening to...
This is the end of...