From PR News in Washington, I'm against the Turkish government.
Despite pockets of ongoing fighting, the BBBBC reports.
But victory has come at a terrible, humiliating defeat.
The BBBBC.
Meanwhile, local monitors say PR News is holding.
The government has not suggested it will do so.
Beijing says Bob is hindering firefighting efforts.
Or, uh, to dump Bob as a retard.
U.S. and German doctors say this is PR News.
And PR News denied it.
I want to tell you about Paris.
My heart has never finished.
There is an advantage of the Eiffel Tower.
Or the Saint-Michel neighborhood.
I want to tell you about Paris.
I really like this song called Puppet Dance.
You'll think at the beginning that it's Fat Man D singing.
But that would be kind of ironic.
Well, well, well, what do we have here?
Come one, come all, right this way.
That's it.
Right here.
Right through here.
Ladies and gentlemen, everyone is welcome.
Well, hey there, little man.
Hey there, little girl.
Come on.
Into the puppet theater.
Give it a Wall Street whirl.
There's a strange and twitchy dance.
It's going on right over there.
Well, ain't they ever so funny
with them strings tied up in their hair?
They're dancing, dancing, dancing a jig.
You can do the dance, too.
Just pay all of your money.
It's the very first rule.
As the puppeteers leer
and tug those pretty strings.
Hey, hey, my little man.
Everybody will dance and sing.
And hey there, my little lady.
Do the puppet dance.
It don't matter if it's a little shady.
You'll soon understand.
And hey there, sister lady.
Just step on the stage.
Don't you fret as they tie you down.
Just buy the strings.
It's the easiest thing.
We all just play along.
Mm-hmm.
Yes, just play along.
You play along, too, saxophone.
Yeah, you play along to the bottom,
and then to the farthest middle.
Or say god damn it,
Mm...
Or say god damn it, too, saxophone.
Yeah, you play along too, fiddler. That's right.
That's right.
Well, hey there, little man. Hey there, little girl. Come on and do the puppet dance. Give it a Wall Street whirl.
Oh, yes. All my friends. Ain't it shivery fun when we're dancing? Oh, we're dancing puppets.
Dancing under the gun.
Mm-hmm. That's it. That's right. Yes, just string along. String along.
Mm-hmm. Good. Good.
Oh, no, wait. Don't fight the strings now. Don't fight those puppet strings. Oh, that's better.
That's better. Just play along. Oh, we all just play along. Play along. We're happy to play along.
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Johnson.
Shirley was the artiste behind that from a CD called Spaceship Landing in a Cemetery, Puppet Dance.
I lied a minute ago.
John was not actually at XD.
He was a guest at Starwood.
And later on, we're going to be telling you what all happened at XD and Starwood festivals.
It was exciting.
Exciting, including being handed CDs by folks that, well, in this case, I've played a whole lot of St. Andrew the Impaled,
recorded live at XD's over the last 10 or 15 years.
And he finally came out with an album and a band.
The band is called The Liberty Tubes.
They're from Pittsburgh.
And that's like the local name for the band.
It tunnels into town through the forbidding hills.
Anyway, longtime listeners will recognize these St. Andrew the Impaled tunes,
only they're completely different because it's studio stuff.
And it's a wonderful new thing.
I saw you look at me up and down.
Then I saw you looking all around.
That cool guy at the bar, yeah, his name is Jim.
But he's got good taste, so you ain't leaving with him.
You need a guy who's going to make you feel good.
Not dwell upon your faults like the other guys would.
Like your green teeth and your knobby ass knees.
What you really need is a fella like me.
Cause I got low standards.
I got low standards.
So why don't you get with me?
Now you might think that I'm very refined.
But I'm just looking for a kind of good time.
So what if you're bald and missing an eye?
I could look past it.
I'm that kind of guy.
I'll beg on work and you forgot your makeup kit.
Well, I'll just dim the lights a bit.
Wear diseases from your previous bows.
Don't bother me.
I got some of my own.
Cause I got low standards.
I got low standards.
So why don't you get with me?
Yeah, that was good enough.
You got a list with every letter but N.
You say who and I say when.
You say most to you is one.
You're starting to sag.
I say grab that colostomy bag and get into my car.
It's a piece of crap.
Just toss a Burger King wrapper right in the back.
And we'll head off to your place or mine.
Or just putz a parking lot.
Shit, that'd be fine.
Cause I got low standards.
I got low standards.
So why don't you get with me?
I got low, low, low, low standards.
I got low standards.
I took it up to a poor choice of words.
When you say that the Holocaust never occurred.
You think stem cells are part of your phone.
And that bathing is for those too cheap for cologne.
Well, I got a can of spray here to cover the smell.
And earplugs cause your voice is grating as hell.
Besides, the things you say must be out of your mind.
You make the guests on Springer sound like fucking hot stocks.
But I know that I know.
Cause I got low standards.
I got low standards.
So why don't you get with me?
What do you get with me?
They never really get used to it.
It makes sex really, really weird.
Oh, edit that out.
A lot of dead air in my lovemaking too.
A new victim.
The victim you haven't seen dead air in your lovemaking like you've seen in mine.
Led Zeppelin is just a band that was made up of the Beatles after they all put on disguises.
They got together and decided, what if we made our music worse?
I have to disagree with you.
Or at least more morose.
Of course you would, old man.
Old man.
Come up here to defend the Beatles.
That's all you did.
That's all you boomers can do.
When you think of the guidance and consideration that I have shown you over the last four days,
making sure you were safe,
that things didn't happen to you.
I go and flog myself in the woods every night,
not my log, out amongst the logs,
but I go out and I hurt myself in punishment for all the terrible things I did the prior night
and all the terrible things I plan on saying to you the next day.
But it's got to be done, Pease.
It's got to be done.
Why?
Because if he doesn't do it, no one else will.
Well, no, actually everybody else will too.
There's a line going around the building.
We've been doing a counter radio show.
What?
An animation?
An anti-show, you might say.
An anti-show to expose what's taking place the next day.
We're out here broadcasting the real truth of the secret documents that we've recovered from Ivan Stang's house
when we stuck in there to find if he had any chips or liquor in his cabinet.
There was no liquor.
All of it.
Yeah, we didn't find any liquor.
We did find an extensive load of ranch beans.
Stang probably drank it all the first night he got here.
There was a lot of ranch beans and some empty cans.
A lot of wolf chili.
Wolf chili.
Official chili of the church.
Some weird sushi squid food or something.
Squishy spam.
Squib.
Treezo spam.
What's up with that?
You know, it's actually quite tasty.
It was, actually.
I will not disparage treezo spam.
But who looks at it and thinks it's tasty?
Treezo spam is a good friend of mine.
I will not sit on this radio show and have him disparaged like this.
Trees of spam.
Man, wouldn't that be...
Where I live, the trees are made of spam.
And the grass is...
And you pluck a can right off the branch.
Right off the can.
And you just pop that open and...
I think the spam would be growing from the tree all natural, no can.
It would just be the spam ham hanging there.
No can?
No can.
Because when you picked it...
No, man, you're going to have an envelope for that pink meat.
No, when you pick it, then you put it in a can so you can ship it somewhere else.
But it's the fruit, you know.
So it's up there.
The greasy, slimy spam is hanging from the tree.
Listen to this idiot talk.
They send the subgeniuses out to pick the spam from the trees where it's not...
Trees, fruits, and...
They're canned and shipped to local grocery stores.
Look how little you know.
Wisconsin, yeah, I know.
Everyone knows this.
Okay, peas.
Somebody manufactures it and somebody else sells it.
But no matter what, it's all...
Mob?
That's deep, man.
That's really...
That blew my mind as if X-Day had not blown my mind enough.
What was your...
I'm mostly concerned with...
I'm going home from X-Day with four...
Four out of five tires on my brain.
Brain flat.
Yeah.
The fifth one's a lingering hallucination.
So just
I guess I'm going to miss that.
Go on back.
We'll be right back.
time 24 drills now was there anything even close this year oh yeah there were all kinds of things
that were close uh president vermin supreme showed up and with a pony and a goat and the
and right at the beginning of my religious ceremony when my big spot at starwood at uh
prime time saturday afternoon i was starting my religious defival rant and that pony came up on
stage and took a great big old horse dump right there a pony dump it was only a little pony like
a shetland pony or something i think a shet land did you say i would say it was slightly yeah okay
it's going to land i think it would be different because that pony's poop smelled a lot worse than
any normal horse
poop i've ever smelled and believe me you're not supposed to feed pizza and stuff like that
right exactly normally horse and cow manure do not smell that bad when they're fresh but this pony i
don't know what they've been feeding it a bunch of propaganda from president vermin supreme no doubt
he turned out to be a real swell feller and uh he gave me a hand-painted tie that says vermin supreme
and he painted his name with elmer's glue and then dusted it with glitter yeah he had a whole bunch of
those and he gave me a free copy of his new book i pony and he uh he gave us lessons on how to use a
megaphone to uh defuse tensions at protests yes he did a workshop called megaphonics yeah he teaches
if you if he'd be a real good guy to have at your possibly violent protest to keep it from getting
violent because
he he interjects absurdity and a certain amount of uh understanding for both the sweaty irritated
cops who were getting kind of scared and the crazed scared sweaty demonstrators and so forth
jace was that chicago in 1968 or something you're talking about or well well uh i don't know he's
been everywhere he's done everything and he has lots of fun apparently now that sounds like a
cross between popeye and hannah byron i don't know i don't know i don't know i don't know i don't know
the difference between robert there and um you know get him he does kind of look a little like
popeye with a beard but both eyes he's got the forearms and the uh shins like that bucket-like
thing uh now vermin supreme turned out to be being a real okay guy yeah he was he was a guest at
starwood oh we were had a lot of debauchery going on i heard that there was the places rife with
debauchery and and having adultery within adultery
and all kinds of weird stuff was going on.
Well, that's the way they advertise it,
but if that's happening, it's back in the woods
and they never invite me anymore.
Some of those children that lead the parade and stuff
have big creases in their foreheads.
They're scary looking, like right out of some Romero movie or something.
Yes, and they always do that parade during my rant.
You think you didn't know that,
but now you know that you did know that.
I do it all the time.
We had such spectacles at X Day as,
okay, envision this.
The Oscar Mayer Wienermobile.
You know what that is, right?
A car shaped like a wiener.
Yes.
Well, this was a replica.
This wasn't the original Oscar Mayer Wienermobile,
but David Apocalypse with that
jumped through...
Three burning cars.
Three flaming cars.
He jumped those with the replica Wienermobile.
He was the Wienermobile.
Well, let's not do any spoilers here.
Okay, sorry.
In fact, he was in fact the wiener,
and he was in fact...
It's hard to really even describe.
Have you ever been so high
that you saw a giant talking hot dog?
Well, I've been so hard-working...
that I saw that very thing.
And it was real.
There's pictures to prove it.
They know when they're getting under your skin.
A giant talking...
They start asking questions about mustard and condiments
and stuff like that,
and it's kind of creepy.
Oh, kind of?
You have no idea.
It's the epitome of creepy.
Clowns.
Is there?
Dave, you know,
you know there's the one rule about clowns,
what you never ever do.
They all look like Trump,
and they get out of the car,
and they get back in the car,
and they look like Trump.
No.
Because everybody knows that Trump is a crazy clown car.
Oh, that's silly.
All clowns are...
He's very serious.
He really is.
Anyway,
the rule I was expecting you to know, Dave,
but apparently you don't know.
Don't ever...
No, what's a clown?
Don't ever give a clown drugs.
Okay?
Well, there were two clowns at X-Day,
and guess what happened?
Yep, you got it right.
Somebody gave him drugs.
Next thing you know,
there's flaming Wienermobiles
and talking hot dogs
and straight jacket escapes
and screwdrivers going all the way
into his freaking face.
Yep, that's what will happen, you know?
And entire shows starring no one
except the toolbox of death,
which is just a thing.
It's a toolbox full of tools of death.
And those things all happened to us.
It's true.
You died?
No, no, only...
Actually, nobody did die.
And, you know, obviously...
Somebody really died, and they didn't.
And you were going to make up their name
and make their family real anxious and ugly
and call you up on a telephone
and threaten the local Ku Klux Klan
to beat you up.
Or whatever they call them.
What do they call them?
The guys with the funny clothes?
Amish.
Yeah.
Clowns?
You can pick on them a lot easier.
Yeah, they're clowns.
Yeah, and they're fascists, those clowns.
Confederate clowns.
Both of them start with a K, so...
That means nothing at all, really.
Kukuk's clown.
Beware.
Don't...
Don't let the sun set on you in this town
if you're not wearing whiteface.
That's not funny.
That is.
That's really sad.
Grease paint.
We're talking about grease paint.
It's clowns, okay?
They're fascists.
They're jerks.
If you give them drugs.
And that's what happened.
But it was made...
It was made up for...
You should have known better.
It was made up for by Reverend Angry Larry
playing drums and bass at the same time
so that the other musicians would have something
solid to work off of.
And the other...
How about a bass player or a drummer?
The only other musicians were
Princess Wee and Reverend Vanessa.
The beautiful Reverend Vanessa Oak.
And she's so smart.
Yes.
And...
And she's so talented.
She is.
What is she doing in Church of the Subgenius?
I have to ask myself whenever I...
I'll ask, you know,
what's the reason for this?
You know, is some form of at-large absurdity
that becomes grander and grander by the moment?
What are we going to have to do to her to...
Bite down really hard on the leather straps
and just let them electroshock...
Electroshock...
While you're thinking of that Vanessa woman, you know?
You better not do anything to her.
No, no, no.
But the...
The only question is how...
How do...
It seems like she's a little too smart
to qualify for Church of the Subgenius.
Yeah, that's what you just said.
You said she was smart.
What can we do to...
What can we do to help her to qualify?
Well, if she could just listen to the recording of this,
she'd probably know well enough to stay away.
You know, that'll flatten four of your brain tires,
like Reverend Shogun was saying there.
That flat tire, that's a wonderful key
to perform in, by the way, a flat tire.
That's funny you should mention that,
because Princess, we and I,
making sure that our...
The I-van would be in good shape for this trip across Ohio
and then another one back to Texas, pulling a trailer.
We bought four new tires.
And within four days, one of them was flat.
I hate...
Well, we were on a campground, David.
It was fixed.
It was fixed by an admiral...
Well, I don't want to name names,
but it was a person who is transitioning
from male to female, as it were,
or something like that.
And yet...
John, if you're going to change tires,
you can't change genders, too,
at the same time as you're changing tires.
Well, this person...
Now that you mention it,
that's exactly what was happening.
Exactly.
Yeah, and I was thinking...
It gives new meaning to a flat tire, too,
because sometimes...
Sometimes things don't rise to the moment,
as they might say.
They just flatten out,
kind of dangle there by themselves.
Oh, no, you're talking about the naked baptism at X-Day,
what they call the sausage and flapjack fest.
Yeah, and Hemingway, too.
Yeah.
Well, remember, Reverend Angry Larry pointed that out.
This isn't really just a sausage fest.
It's also a flapjack fest.
The aging, you know, the graying...
You have to tell me that before, dear.
The graying of the nude subgeniuses.
We didn't use much of that on the video that's on YouTube.
Well, how bleak can you possibly be?
I don't understand what the hell you're talking about.
It sounds like somebody...
It sounds like some kind of faulty role.
Well, let me put it this way, Dave.
It's okay to feed the nude seniors at Wisteria.
It's okay to feed them.
I didn't mean to say that.
Yeah.
It's okay.
So, are you saying that many seniors line up,
dressed up like Canada geese or ducks,
and wait for a little small animal cracker to survive on for the next three weeks?
No, no.
They usually have...
They're well-fed, but they'll take more, you know, if you've got it.
They're tame.
You won't be wrecking their ability to survive in the wild
just by getting...
You're giving the nude seniors food.
But if you...
Then they'll hang around, so maybe you don't want to give them food.
Right.
And who would want a membership card either if they're, like, on the Internet?
They let you know.
They called you, or they emailed your house and said,
Congratulations, you're now a member of the Nude Seniors Club.
Ew!
That would be revolting.
Not to other seniors.
We get used to that kind of thing.
To many other seniors.
No.
Now, I'm not one who does that.
And actually, X-Day doesn't have a whole lot of that.
But Starwood sure does.
Old, bare-naked people that are old and bare-naked?
Yeah.
I love it when people get horribly offended by that.
It's like, how dare that old person walk around just showing everything?
Well, why don't you just leave, then?
If you've never seen anything.
What's that old lady said?
Well, if I see something I've never seen before, I'll just shoot it.
That should be your attitude, friend.
It's nothing you have never seen before.
Some of them will give you the baby bird special for only eight bucks.
Oh, what is that?
Oh, if you have to ask, you already know.
Mm-hmm.
Uh-huh.
Yep.
You'll find out.
You guys make me think about that too much, and I don't like it.
Let's go on to the next subject.
The beer feast was lots of fun.
There was food also, and lots of weird beer with risque names like Big Red Cock beer and that kind of thing.
And Snarling Gray Squirrel.
Yeah, that's right.
Something like that.
How come beer makers always got to get so creative with them?
Yeah, I know.
I mean, I've seen some of the titles like Snapping Turtle with a college degree and stuff like that.
So somebody like me will buy them and keep the can on a shelf somewhere because it's funny.
I know, and that's even more ridiculous and sad.
IPAs.
Makes me want to go and cry.
I know.
There was a lot of wonderful artwork generated like there is at Every X Day because we bring...
Art supplies.
Yes, I always bring paper and lots of markers so that people can make drawings.
Yeah, colored markers.
And we have all those drawings and we have real artistes like Dr. Hal and...
And Apostasy Fnord.
Yeah, Fnord.
And Catfeather when she's there.
She wasn't there.
And lots of others with lots of talent like Reverend Vanessa.
And then people like us.
Miss Oginist.
She's wonderful too.
Do you know her?
I don't know Miss Oginist.
That was just something...
She's a little bit on the suicidal side.
I'm glad I don't know Miss Oginist.
Think how many punk singers have given themselves that night.
Three or four for sure.
Especially when they're riding the bus like in a large town like Los Angeles or New York City.
You get on the bus there and you start making up your own weird...
Your own lyrics that you want to...
To impress the bus driver.
Is that what you people are doing on the bus?
You people. You people.
What do you mean you people?
I thought you people were just schizophrenics that were just talking nonsense.
We people are just schizophrenics talking nonsense.
But we're also making a lot of plain and simple European sense, pal.
Well then go back where you came from, man.
I already did.
Go back to England.
Simple European.
What's that supposed to be?
Go back to Italy.
I have to go back to...
What would we do there?
We could like stomp in grapes and stuff like that and have with our big smelly feet and
argue about the size of the tomatoes as well.
I mean, come on, man.
America's where it's at.
Oh yeah?
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
Which job would you rather have?
Well, I don't know what it is.
I'd rather be smacking the vegetables with my feet.
Yeah.
Right.
The old ways are the best.
Yep.
Especially for real old, old, old, old people.
Old souls.
Yeah, especially for old cigarettes too, man.
Have you ever done that?
No.
Not in a long time.
Don't try it.
Yeah, not in a long time.
Hey, we had a workshop in toilet paper launching.
Oh wow.
That sounds so enormously challenging.
Well, when you want to paper a house at Halloween, right?
Yeah.
You know, you could just, if you're the high school football star, you can probably throw
the toilet paper real well.
But if you're, say, a clown on drugs, you can actually use, what was David Apocalypse
launching that toilet paper with?
Was it like a leaf blower or a heater or something?
Yes.
I think it was like a hairdryer.
And then there was a roll of toilet paper that was mounted just a couple of feet away.
A couple of feet in front of it so that when you ran the hairdryer, it blew the paper
just perfectly up into the rafters of the building we were in.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh wow.
It made a beautiful arc.
It really did.
It was very impressive.
A lovely arc that looked really good on photographs.
And then, and it did, it went over the rafters and then hung there.
In fact, I had to tear that stuff down so I could, because it was blocking my camera.
I did too.
I was tearing it down too because it had all been so-
Oh, and then people-
And then the clowns, the clowns were like, oh, so you don't like our decorating style.
Yeah, especially in their own particular styles.
Yeah.
I was just thinking, you know, if you could Photoshop this, you could get a picture of
Trump's father in his Klan uniform, and then you could Photoshop his face, his son's face,
and the other one and say it doesn't fall far from the tree.
Dave, that's a 12-year-old's face.
I know.
I've been wanting to see it.
I'd like to see Trump and dad both stand there in their Klan uniforms beaming because, you
know, white people in New York were being persecuted by Catholics.
At least that's what Trump's father said to the New York Post or the New York Times or
I forget whoever.
I don't want to talk about it.
The thing.
Okay, I'm sorry.
The thing that-
I dare not think.
I don't want to even think about the thing.
I don't blame you.
So I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to get your roughage going because I know it's been a long time since you've
eaten dinner and are prepared, so to speak.
It's been a long time since I've had a bath, but because of the subgenius soap, soon I can
have one.
C'est bon.
That was one thing that turned up at the Bulldada auction.
We had a whole lot of Reverend Ferg's soap.
What's this company called?
Tri-
Triology.
Yeah, Triology Soaps.
Dave, did you know that you can get a wonderful scented soap in various different senses with
a Dobbs head inside, a silhouette Bob head of soap inside a translucent soap frame?
Yes, it's amazing.
Yeah, Triology Soaps.
They'll try anything.
Well, that sounds like, you know, like if you'd like to escape from this world into
another kind of semi-ridiculous world of your own making, you could go there with the little
soap preachers and have them riding Ferris wheels and making bubbles, go buying bubbles
and stuff like that.
That would be beautiful.
Ferris wheels?
That sounds like something out of Mary Poppins.
Mary Poppins.
Mary Poppins Returns, the new one.
Right.
They use the Dobbs head soap and all the kids frolic in the soap.
It's pretty special.
Yeah, the opiate version where they leave the kids in the hot car for three days.
So, anyway, Dave, we got so many recordings, so many shows at X Day, we're not going to
ever, we're not going to need you anymore.
We're going to have to put you out on the ice flow out to pasture.
No, not Dave on the ice flow.
No.
I'm not an Eskimo woman that you can't get.
I can just take you, say, well, you're stepping in.
It's not time yet.
Well, we didn't do it yet.
Yeah.
We didn't.
Okay, well, I'll let you know when you've done it.
I don't want to do it at all.
Oh, well, here's something that I want to do that I have to, Dave, we're going to stop
talking a little bit early tonight, in fact, in about a minute and a half, because I have
this wonderful song that's real good for ending a show with.
Mm-hmm.
I mean, it's just perfect.
Well, good, then I can just sneak this little surprise thing in on you, Reverend Stang.
Oh, okay.
I have just found out that this special visitor that we have on the show tonight has a subgenius
name.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
This gentleman sitting here is my brother, my blood brother, and his name in subgenius
is Prince Dejel, king of all the UTIs.
That's my-
Not Cosm.
What does UTI stand for?
You got to figure that one out yourself.
You identified tickling-
I make them.
It's a music number.
Right.
I was kind of rude, and I didn't mention that we had an extra guest in the studio and our
house, but yeah, my brother-in-law is here, and he had a different subgenius name before,
I think.
It's always been Prince Dejel.
Oh, yeah?
I just added Prince Dejel.
I think that's the ending.
Oh, well, okay.
Anyway, this song I'm going to play almost immediately is by John Shirley from his new
album, Spaceship Landing in a Cemetery.
And he explained to me, he pointed this particular song out.
It's the very last one on the CD.
It's called High.
And he says, it's not about a guy who gets high.
It's about a guy who is falling out of a plane.
He's in a plane, and he's getting ready to, maybe they're going to do skydiving or something,
but his friend who's flying screws up, and the door opens, and he gets sucked out.
And the song is this guy singing to you as he plummets earthwards.
Oh, goodness.
And it's about five and a half minutes long, and it ends a show.
That's the wonderful thing about this song.
It ends a show.
Okay, well, I'll be seeing you through the afternoon.
I'll send you the copy, or I can just fade you out, and you can keep listening to it.
Here, I'll just do that.
How could you fade Dave out?
I have to fade the music out.
Oh, by the way, friends, you're listening to Subgenius, Hour of Slack on...
No, he's gone.
Dave left.
Oh, my God.
He left.
He's gone.
He slammed the door.
He slammed...
Anyway, this is how it ends.
Hi.
I'm high.
Flying through clouds.
They're streaming bye, bye, bye, bye
I'm not on drugs
I don't have to try
My attitude is an altitude
You see I'm falling
I'm falling from on high
Quite literally high
Way up in the sky
Up in the sky
And that's because I just fell out
Fell right out of an airplane
My friend Jake, he was really big
Such a flake, oh man
He opened the hatch, you see
Yeah, he opened the hatch, you see
We open the hatch
Plane gives a shake
Oh, thanks a lot, Jake
What a fight
I proceed to shoot
Right out the door
Now I'm falling through the clouds
And this won't be fun much more
And I'm thinking of a time
When I was with my sons in the car
We were all having a lot of fun
The four of us
Just out for a run
We were laughing together
There was no fear
And there was no
There was no
There was no tension at all
It was like we were in freedom
Before
There were no tears
I didn't, I didn't need to drink
Didn't need to get fried
But somehow
Just driving with them
Somehow I felt high
Just me and my kids driving by the lake
And it just felt like
Felt like it was a moment
That would never break
Felt like a moment
Thank you.
Bye.