What makes Bob holler?
When I asked Bob, he explained this way
And he said, well, when a little sweetie pie
In a misker twirls by
And rolls those big blue eyes
Oh, I holler
And when some pretty chick
Says she loves my fiddle legs
Well, now then, that can do the trick
Oh, I holler
The Self-Genius Hour of Slack
Bob holler
Well, I went on down to my girlfriend's shack
To see how they did hang
When I got there, her cupboard was bare
I couldn't ignite a thing
There was no shard, no bone, no twig
I brought my comic book collection
Was about this big, yeah
Frop without slack is like slack without frop
But where the hell else am I?
Going to cop
I found my dog food collection
About five o'clock
But all that food was stale
Thought I'd call that rip-off schmuck
Forgot he was in jail
Ended up killing a porcupine
Just to see if I could smoke his rhyme
Oh, frop without slack is like slack without frop
But where the hell else am I?
Going to cop
To that I almost need if I'm
Frop without slack is like slack
Where the hell else am I going to cop?
Forgot toag waiting records
Go wherever
I want to go
Yeah, I've had enough
And no one mandatios
Impatient enhancing
That's not bank opening
ät
to cop. Yeah, a frop without
slack is like slack without
frop. Don't cop from that guy there.
Where the hell else am I going to cop?
Oh, stay away from that. Frop without slack
is like slack without frop.
Where the hell else am I
going to cop? No way.
No, no, no. No, don't bother.
That was Reverend
Bleepo Abernathy with a frop
without slack.
Thank you, Reverend Bleepo
Abernathy.
In digital sound now.
But it'll be slightly different for
those of you who'd like some change
for crying out loud. This Saturday, August
12th, Blind Lemon
Cleveland. Chaz, can I ask you
one question before we go live?
You've been bad, ain't you?
You've been bad? You've been bad,
little girl. I'll see you
there.
Bob will see you there, little girl.
What's the Heisenpecker
uncertainty principle?
I see you, young lady.
Young college student. I'm in the vision.
I'm seeing her. She's been bad.
And she wants to, she doesn't
want to be good, but she does want to be punished.
Oh, honey.
I've got a tongue lashing for you.
Oh, I've got some punishment.
You like it
when you get what good.
We know what you're thinking.
The men
don't know, but the
little girls understand. Praise
Bob.
And the knees must be shaved.
Oh, yeah.
Hey, you, them
choir singers,
they know.
Brother,
you bring your wife to church
this Saturday night.
We don't make you.
This ain't the kind of church we have to get up
7 o'clock on Sunday morning. No, sir.
This ain't the kind of church where you come to our
church. You get drunk.
You drink beer. You drink wine.
You drink mixed drinks. You get,
drunk, buddy, at our church, and
you sleep late on Sunday
morning. You pick up
some creature and take it home
and have intense
physical love with that
thing, and then you wake up in the morning
and you just deal with it. But praise
Bob. At least his promise
rang true, Bob said.
Have intercourse with a beautiful
live girl or anything
else you want.
Does that go for that?
That's what he said.
Right over there by your neck muscle.
Ignore the
digital device.
How about that reel-to-reel
player over there?
The one we're going to give you
in the next few hours.
Maybe not.
Maybe longer. Maybe the next few years.
Do I have to say it again?
You can make love with appliances.
You can do
what you're called for.
Anything you want.
Anything you need to do.
You can have long-term
conversations with yourself.
And get lost on the bench.
And he wants to feel you up.
Bob loves you. He wants to shake your hand,
mister. And he'd like to
shake your
money maker, honey.
Bob's out there.
Bob's real.
Don't you doubt that. And that stark fist
of removal, it's real. And it's going to remove us
from the air right about now.
Bob is not
the illegitimate son of Michael
Jackson. Take it from me.
...
Ooh, midnight's growing late
From morning mist I rise
To help them greet the day
With little silver sunbeams
And little infrareds
I paint the house, I paint the door
I paint the chicken coop
And when they come out to see the show
I turn and paint them too
On my ride there's many sides
Bandits on my tail
Another target in the eye
Ooh, midnight's growing late
They'll never know, they'll never see
Before the hit, I'm gone
Back into the dragon's breath
To sing the dragon's song
Back home folks think what I do
I do to keep them free
And no one knows my secret
No one knows I fly for me
On my ride there's many sides
Bandits on my tail
Another target in the eye
Ooh, midnight's growing late
ooh
Ooh
Michigan resident
Ooh, midnight's growing
As far as I know, the devil and Bob are the only ones who will actually pay for souls.
I have seen the devil in my microscope.
We can, like, buy our way out of hell.
Does the devil know you can buy your way out of hell?
You can only see it...
That's why the devil hates Bob.
Because Bob gives you the money that Bob's getting.
Those are triple your money back guarantee.
I think it's a very long legal process you have to go through.
You have to go through an apostate court.
Sign and bride.
And then you have to stand naked in front of a large tribunal.
You know, it might scare you just the sheer size of it.
And so, you know, before you even get down to get your reparations and repayment
for being sent to hell and you could buy your way out,
you'd have to sue.
In other words, you'd have to sue the devil.
Or, you know, not the devil incarnate, but the concept of the devil.
Which I guess we all have to do on a daily basis.
That was actually the egg lady who...
Thank you so much for that.
Thank you.
I was actually contemplating that thing this very day.
Buying your way back out of hell.
Yes, exactly.
Well, that's what they go to staying for, you know.
You see, but that's not the only thing that you can do.
You see, what you also have to do, if you are going to sell your soul to the devil,
which you should have a lawyer present when you sign that contract.
But how are you going to sell your soul to the devil?
You have to find the devil.
You've got to look in your microscope.
Well, I don't know.
You've got to look at your DNA.
You don't want to give those entire...
Can you really say,
Hey, devil guy, now look, when I die...
You have to look at your DNA, and then you see the devil.
Oh, yeah.
And trace it back, right on back to your reptilian complex.
Horny little helixes.
Yeah.
Everywhere.
Little lizards.
Snapping the heads off of other little lizards.
Little red capes.
My intention is to root out the devil.
Evolution is the devil, Chaz.
You just said it in your most retarded, elucidated moment.
What?
Evolution is the devil?
Or wait a minute.
What?
Why?
Because it's survival of the fittest?
I mean, nature.
And that's nature.
Is that somehow devilish?
That's natural law.
I'm afraid that there's...
Is natural law evil?
There is no...
Whoever leaves more offspring survives?
Is that...
That's evil?
That's the devil?
There is no life without death.
There is no pleasure without pain.
How can that be?
There's no pickle spears without...
With mounds of potatoes out.
There's...
I can't see a world in such opposition.
I was wrong.
I'm sorry.
You're right.
It's a...
Well, no...
What is it, God?
Right hemisphere, wrong planet.
Susie the floozy said.
And that pretty much sums it up.
Let's play devil's advocate here.
No pun intended.
You'll see before you're an object to figure out, man.
But if the devil was DNA and evolution and natural selection,
what then would God be?
Yeah.
Some never-ending state of sameness
which somehow maybe reflected differentness
without moving or something.
Stasis.
Stasisism.
God would be...
Then we must all be Luciferians
because we worship the light and quick movement.
That's right.
Well, now, see, that's all right.
You can't go talking about...
You can't go saying,
well, I know about what God's gonna think about that.
I know about God...
Because I know God real well.
I know what he'd think about that.
And he'd agree with me, not you.
Well, maybe God was before...
Before the Big Bang.
The moment before the Big Bang
that infinitely eternal life...
The moment before the Big Bang.
Like, that was God.
And then the devil took over when the Big Bang...
So the Big Bang was the devil.
There's many who subscribe to that particular...
The Big Bang was the devil.
Really?
Okay, how many of our, like, prophets...
And the Big Bang was the beginning of Satan.
That's right.
And the beginning of all, you know, 15 billion years of...
We are the legacy...
Satan owns this world!
...of 15 billion years of evolution.
It's really Satan's...
Well, think of all those prophets
all the way from Genos down to Enoch...
So that means that we are the devil.
And atomic vibrations...
...and slower than light is satanic.
...if you want to talk about moral objectives
and where do we go in our classrooms
and how many times can we go there, you know?
But then what...
How do you think of, like, Moses being bent over a log
and being, you know, burned to death?
But then what is love, then?
What is love in the universe?
I think love is gravity.
It's a mild form of hatred.
I think love is just gravity.
You know, gravity makes the Earth go around the sun.
That means the Earth loves the sun.
Gravity is a mild form of hatred.
Yeah.
Well, I used to do art.
Lots of weird shit, but...
I gave it all up.
Because it was too much work.
And it didn't pay.
And it was really just a big pit in the ass.
Anyway.
Anyway, anyway.
What the fuck?
So now...
I ski and watch TV.
Because that's a lot more fun and relaxing.
And it's what I really want to do.
And with my time, art gets old.
When no one pays you.
Or even understands.
So, what's the point?
Unless...
I was going to do it just for me.
But, to tell you the truth, I'd really rather just ski and watch TV.
Because that's just a lot more fun for me.
And I might as well have fun.
Because that's what life's for.
You know, rap for all the gusto and all that.
And I'm alive now.
But...
Someday...
I'll have to die.
And then...
I'll be dead.
For a long time.
For a long, long time.
For a long, long, long, long time.
For a fucking forever, in fact.
So, I might as well ski and watch TV.
Now, while I have the chance, don't have time to waste on art.
And I'm sick of torturing myself.
And of wondering if it's done yet.
And I'm sick of...
hanging out with all those lazy flakes.
Who think they're so smart.
And now that I'm free of them.
I might as well just listen to the music that I grew up with.
That's the only music that ever really moved me.
That new stuff's just a trend.
It's not real.
And now...
I can get all those old great songs again.
On CD.
And then...
I can download them all again.
On MP3.
Because that's the ultimate technology.
Can you see?
Oh, I'm so glad to be alive.
In this modern age.
So much so that...
I...
Really...
Don't...
WANNA DIE!
But there's not a whole lot I can do about that now.
Except maybe...
Pay my thirty dollars to the Church of the Subgenius.
And eat more vegetables.
And...
I think I better marry my girlfriend because...
It's such a risk nowadays.
Even though...
I'm not one of those people.
So I'm probably safe.
But...
You can never be too sure.
And so...
We'll marry.
So we can ski.
And watch TV.
Together.
And feel free and happy.
Without having to worry about art.
What a pain.
Glad I'm through with all that shit.
God damn it.
But now...
I've got...
All...
That I could ever really reasonably expect...
To ever get out of life.
Anyway...
What the fuck?
Fuck?
Think fuck.
Any way.
Any way?
At façon engineer.
Fossillander.
Pretty good.
Someone obsessed me with that.
What tries to carry me down this road.
Red abandonment.
to find the solution to my problems.
And my eyes
found the verse right there on the pages.
In all things,
slack must
come first.
So
why the fuck am I so
pissed off right now?
I'll tell you why.
Because I've been reading that
book for years.
And I've been reading and
not intentionally memorizing,
but absorbing the word of Bob.
And for
a decade and a half,
I had completely
ignored that one line
in all things.
Slack must
come first. And that is
why I am so
motherfucking pissed off right now.
I am pissed off
for ignoring the plain and obvious
truth that Bob has presented
to us.
But if
slack must come first,
then why am I still pissed off
about it? Well, it's very
simple, friends. Whenever
I find myself starting to get
pissed off, I ask myself,
is there slack to be had?
And there's slack to be had
in being pissed off. And dear friends,
brave fucking Bob, I am
pissed off!
Give西 Teru
a
vibe
in fear.
Dad.
I want to love some
and love some.
¶¶
Brandy, Kenny fucking Rogers, Hobbity Britney Spears, noise pollution, off pitch Alanis,
crap ass cool mo DPP, insane fucking clown posse screeching, or backstreet bunghole ululations.
Boom!
No more Rosie O'Dyke, no more family splatters, hyper bullshit NWO fracassees, testaroni ballgames,
sinful commercials, or loser has-been colostomy hobbled stars doing TV salutes to anything.
Boom!
No more licorice.
I hate that crap.
Boom!
No more goddamned God, Bob, Buddha, Jesus on a pogo stick, rabbis, Robertson, popes,
hell popes, dervishes, doom criers, fakirs, fakers, Falwells, imams, seers, soothsayers,
stangs, prophets, fucking door-to-door missionaries, medicine men, or airport Krishnas.
Hurry this you saffron fuck, I'll torch your topknot.
Boom!
No more Frenchmen.
No more $40 gourmet Italian restaurant meals that taste like they were eaten once before
they ladled it onto your plate.
Boom!
No more turd-gobbling, piss-spraying bosses who need to be knocked down and kicked in
the cossacks until all they can do is twitch and shit themselves.
Boom!
And speaking of twitching and shitting yourself, no more craptastic current former or wannabe
sub-peñas, dick-scordian, or fill-in-the-blank self-styled faux-intellectual lizard lickers
who don't know a round peg from a square hole from the pot most of them don't have the aim
to piss in properly.
Boom!
No more racist black radicals, rednecks, no-necks, feminist chicken chokers, termites,
f-marts, pollsters, butt-suckers, butt-kickers, techno-dweebs, tax-diddlers, former bouncers
who think they're platinum turds, finger-sniffers, or foaming hysterical pontificators with dingleberry
bedecked fruity pink hats riding shitty sputtering little PCs through the mental health of others.
Boom!
No more ball-twisting student loans, ovary-rotting junk mail, or triple goddamn fucking Ed McMahon.
Ho ho, may I have another?
Yes you may, you flatulent chimp rectum.
You can have one nuke after another until they can see your ass blowing from Pluto.
Boom!
And no more en-raging emails from commercial e-rapists telling me about how THEY'RE gonna
make me rich...fuck that...
Nuke em'!
And no more duke nuke em'.
In fact triple goddamn duke nuke em' because I paid six dollars for a plastic octafrine
and the goddamn fucking tentacles fell off within the first week, and I nuclear up de
aciae twiiiiiiice!
Boom!
sicken me. You jest about killing
the normals, but I want to nuke the Super Bowl
and stack the skulls into a new Tower of Babel
so high I can climb to the top
and scream at God for his shitty handiwork.
How dare
he create us and then hinge us in the middle
so we have to go through life bent over just waiting
for the next big butt missile.
If it weren't
for that mole masturbator Jim Baker
getting a load of karma right up his duchess,
I'd want to shoot the almighty up his eternal
sphincter with a cobalt 40s impository.
Boom!
Now some
mewling skanks will probably blanch in
horror at my proposal.
These pathetic
pansies see life as a precious gift instead
of the planetary skin disease most of it
represents.
They think I'd like people better and
couldn't bear to shoot them in their drooling sucker rim
faces if I got a glimpse of a snapshot
featuring their wretched offspring and pooting
grannies. Bah! Guess what? Boom!
Yeah!
If I got to know them
personally, I'd have to fend off their nasty
breath, listen to their interminable droning
stories, and scratch the rashes that inevitably
develop when I'm exposed to their violently
offensive normalcy.
I don't care. I say
nuke them until even the goddamn roaches turn to
one another and say,
Boom!
Go nukes!
I'm not going to be happy until they're flying around like
goddamn gnats in a rainforest.
Never mind, fuck you. I say nuke you
and stop wasting your tick-picking time with mere
insults and guns.
I want to see nukes a-poppin' and numbers that rival
the number of times Richard Simmons has played
Rump Rangers of the old Wild West with every
bodybuilder in the tri-state area who fell asleep
on the bench. Boom! Boom! Boom!
Boom, boom, boom!
Go nukes! And go speed racer,
but don't go country. At least have a little reserve.
God damn you.
I'm just kidding. Oh, no, I'm not!
A goddamn cock ripping, blood dripping,
baby on a spit, gobble shit, tit splitting,
leech hurling, colon twirling,
eyeball puncturing, old church lady
punching, bone scattering, soul
splattering, cat sodomizing, poodle clubbing,
fuck to you all!
Except for
Friday, Susie, and Sister Decadence. Hi.
So how you doing?
Love you, baby!
Go nukes t-shirts available for me
so I can build a working prototype in the backyard
and use it to nuke all of your goddamn asses
and it won't be a dry heat either!
Praise Bob!
Thank you very kindly. Thank you very much.
Yeah!
Hell Bob!
Thank you.
Praise Bob.
Bem科技 has lasted 6 years as a fast learning applications expert.
He is the third Northwest dyed hair of Vietnam based
non GaO scientist accompanying the research has continued it.
Type in your answer above.
We got there.
Come on to me
And I say
Daps
Is the one who made me fall
Extend my cosmic role
Daps
Is the man who sold my soul
He talked to the space guys
And made a surreal good deal
For salvation of planet Earth
His plan for the normals
Will be keeping it surreal
While subgenies enjoy rebirth
Don't you know Bob
Daps
Brought us in out of the cold
Bob
Daps
Got a grin that's good as gold
Bob
Daps
Is the man who sold my soul
Bob daps
He is...
So...
Before the before life, he was my special friend.
Always watching out for me.
And he'll be there waiting.
After my living death.
So I get into eternity.
Believe it.
Bop, bop, bop, bop, bop, bop, bop, bop, bop.
Into my heart he stole.
I'm no longer in control.
Bop, bop, bop, bop, bop, bop, bop, bop, bop.
He's the man who sold my soul.
He's the one who made me whole.
He explained my cosmic role.
He's the man who sold my soul.
Yes, dear friends.
The man who sold my soul.
J.R. Bob Dobbs.
That song was done by...
St. Kenneth Huey and Reverend Bunny Boy.
Friends.
And before that, we heard some preaching from XXX Day with Einstein's Secret Orchestra in the background.
And that song about on your grave in the fog and the dew was Rudy Schwartz Project.
We heard Hell Pope Huey doing that boom rant.
And the November 22nd Kennedy assassination thing was by Pope S. Lilith, who also did that pissed off rant.
And...
Anyway.
A song that was Little Theodore and Midnight Growing Pale.
If you didn't figure that out, it was by Einstein's Secret Orchestra.
In the background, we are hearing Electro Slat Treatment by Lamprey Systems.
And we're about to hear some Jehovah Hates Fred and some more Einstein's Secret Orchestra.
So, hang on, friends.
In fact, I know you're going to hang on because you have to.
Because you love Bob.
Keep those mutilated cattle rolling.
Here comes 9,200,000,000,000 more Zarkons for the alien empire.
And why they call them doggies?
They're not doggies.
That's a cow.
Right up into that saucer rant.
Right up into that saucer.
That's not a slaughterhouse door.
It's a saucer rant.
Going in that saucer.
That's it.
Thanks for the money.
Praise Bob.
So you think you've discovered the final secret, do you?
I think you've got all the answers solved and all the questions well posed.
Now, by the time you pick yourself up from that basement floor and screw the light bulb back in your head,
you're going to be lying.
It won't be long before you understand you've been mistooken.
I'm kind of a rattlesnake picking, picking chaps, scratching, cactus wiping, old Brandon
Iron chuck wagon feller.
I'm kind of a Marlboro man.
I just say, and I like to boss them little weaklings and sissies and city boys around.
That's me.
I'm a subgenius minister.
And I've got a whole flock of dumb ass bosses.
They do anything I say.
And you know what?
You could do the same thing.
You're buddies with Bob.
And all it takes me buddies with Bob is just that membership.
There's friends to join up churches of Venus praise Bob.
It won't go.
Damn, this cow thing won't.
It won't.
So much for American made products.
There was an advertisement for moon pants that made the cow sound and when you press
it, it makes the appropriate sound.
It's ladies night here down at the farm.
Don't ask too many questions.
The moonlight is twanging over the post.
Tom and Marv, you're brilliant, and slim all the way.
rest of the people down at the Double Z Ranch, all taking a nap.
Chickens, cows, the beefalo, the mighty pig,
have all decided to throw a party for yours truly.
And nothing's truer than this.
Let me tell you a tale
of the old Spanish trail.
She and I used to ride side by side
down the old Spanish trail.
She wore red shoes.
Everybody said she would make very good jamón,
but I think maybe we're going to fall in love sometime.
So we talked of a June honeymoon
on the old Spanish trail.
Mmm, yeah.
But then I started getting a little bit hungrier.
And we're still about four hours from the beach.
Because that's where we got to go,
because that's the nearest place we can go.
Ah, yes, dear friends.
Einstein's Secret Orchestra on the radio.
ESO's Swamp Radio.
Broadcast originally from WCSB in Cleveland.
New home of the Hour of Slack.
Though not of the church of the subgenius,
which is still at Dallas, Texas,
where you can learn more about the bell.
If you will just write to the number
I'm about to give for free information,
that's at post office box 1403066 Dallas, Texas 752114.
Once again, that's box 140306 Dallas, Texas 752114.
www.subgenius.com
Thank you.
Chaz Smith and Lonesome Cowboy Day
from Swamp Radio.
Radio.
Well, what kind of cheap psychedelic tricks are these?
Is this supposed to convert these poor innocent sheep
to the word of Bob?
Cheap tricks?
What if...
J.R.R. Ball dogs walk through that airlock right now?
What would he think?
These silly tricks display his image.
His graven image like some of that
volatilist statue with the worshippers
raining down the fort.
Bob would say,
hell no, what's wrong with you people?
You're acting like a bunch of religious nuts.
What are you doing in this little dog?
You should be out there running through that field
partying.
Lift it up.
Hell, this is Starwood.
Maybe the world ends tomorrow and you may die.
You should be doing whatever the hell you would be doing
if tomorrow was the last day on earth.
Or if you had all the time in the world.
That's what old Bobby likes you to do.
Either live life just as if this was the last day of it
or as if it was never ever going to end.
Because if you go to threaten, who was it?
It was the great...
or great forefather, Ken Kesey of the Mary Plank Church
who said,
the only sin is fretting.
Ah, yes.
The only sin is fretting.
And of course it's hard not to fret
when we're in this miserable world.
Well, it ain't so miserable actually
if you quit reading the newspaper.
That's what I did, friend.
It's as strange as it may seem.
There was a time, not even a year ago,
when I was a news junkie just like so many others.
I'd be up every morning and read every bit of the newspapers
from the back, even the obituaries
where I was starting to see my friends' names.
And friends, I quit.
I quit reading the news.
It's been a year since I've seen it.
Whenever you're in the old one,
there'll be some news on the TV
or some newspaper headline.
And by God, it's exactly the same as it was the month before.
And it's the same as it was a year before.
And it's always the same damn game.
Keeping you distracted from your own business.
God Almighty, just listen to my friends.
There's enough bad news to fill a whole life pot.
So I decided I can't do a goddamn thing
about all those poor, wretched people
in those countries starving.
Or fighting.
Or the poor, wretched people in my own country.
There's nothing I can do immediately
except to keep my own sanity
and keep my hand on some slack.
Because friends, if you don't have slack,
you sure as hell cannot share it.
And once you do have slack,
you've got enough to go around
because there's no end to real slack.
Real slack, friends.
But, once again,
this ain't the kind of religion that's gonna even give you
the slightest message of a hint as to what real slap might mean to you,
because it's up to you.
It's always going to be a deal between you and J.R. Bob Dobbs,
or Connie Dobbs, if that's who you talk to late at night.
You know, we all do it.
Either Bob or Connie, you've got to serve somebody.
Ah, yes. Ah, yes, dear friends.
Or your pet dog, Rover.
He had a taste of the life and the benefits of the universe,
and he was not offended by it.
For he knew he had to rise from the hall,
to dwell in his own shit.
That's an advertising call.
Bidding starts at a quarter.
Yeah, bidding starts at a quarter.
A mere quarter. Do I hear a quarter? Do I hear a quarter?
We got a song.
We got a quarter.
What's your song, sir?
What's my song?
What's your word? Give me a word. Give me a word.
Word.
Just a word?
Just a word. Any word.
The dingo's soft.
Sausage.
Lord, I love my sausage.
It's brown and fatty.
On some light, some light guy named Matty two years ago,
who we had the misfortune to meet.
Matty liked sausage, and Matty liked a lot of other things.
And he also liked to make trouble.
He often talked about his sausage to anyone who'd give him a chance.
Just listen.
And then Matty took out his sausage, started waving it around, got down with the ground.
But he was a jerk.
He just waved that thing.
That nasty brown sausage.
Had to be a jerk.
Put him in a swing.
Didn't like the way that he acted.
Always asking questions.
Such as, you know, you guys aren't really all that abnormal.
You some genius.
Aw, you guys do nothing but sit around.
Then he whipped out his sausage.
Woo-hoo.
And we pummeled him to the ground.
But Matty, where have you gone?
Have you gone?
Far away.
Now my song is gone.
Thank you.
That was sausage.
Suddenly a haze descended over the crowd.
And they could feel the pee-pees between their knees, but they could not convert it to the
necessary juices with which to transport themselves away.
The day unfolds from lamplight steams.
The asphalt shimmers like blackened streams.
And all about the day.
I feel and smell and sense your presence near.
The lines are drawn the wrong direction and I am aware.
No words in books here.
Have a look, there's something in the air.
And measurements of time are crumble and climb for Jaguar, Knight and White Gear.
Living in jungles of radio waves.
Never now or ever or yesterday.
And just now in the road, the grass becomes gold.
For Jaguar, Knight and White Gear.
Oh, Jaguar, Knight and White Gear.
No words in books here.
Have a look, there's something in the air.
And measurements of time are crumble and climb for Jaguar, Knight and White Gear.
He's a little tango.
What kind of city do tango?
Well, not yet.
.
Living
in jungles of radio waves
I never, now,
no never, no yesterday
And just now in the air
Where black becomes clear
For jaguar, knife and white deer
The woods in books here
Have a look there's something in the air
And measurements of time are grumble and climb
For jaguar, knife
and white deer
.
. .
. . .