The Soul Genius Power of Slack
What foolishness.
True.
No.
Yes.
Without question.
No.
Not to the soul.
Ah, yes, dear friends, this is Hour of Slack number 1080.
And I am your host and prayer partner, Reverend Ivan Stang.
This week, I got a couple of emails saying, when are you going to start broadcasting Hour of Slack again?
I guess the ancient reruns that I've been using to save time while working on the subgenius history course with MaybeLogic.org
were so ancient that people didn't recognize any of the voices and really didn't understand that those were hours of Slack they were hearing.
It's just that they were hours.
It's just that they were hours of Slack from, like, 1982, before there was an hour of Slack.
Friends, it was me and Philo and Dr. Howell and Puzzlin and so forth.
It's just that we were babies, like most of you are now, in our early 20s.
And I don't really believe that we were ever so young either.
But tonight, we go back to being old.
That is, new.
This is part of a five-hour epic.
Live show we recorded on January 10th at KPFA Studios in Berkeley.
With over-the-edge host Izzy Isn't, heard in the background here, of Negative Land.
And Puzzling Evidence host Doug Wellman of Wellman Headland.
These sound more like the Hour of Slack you're used to, although they are not actually that.
Subgenius doctors participating included Dr. Howell, Puzzling Evidence, Philo Drummond, yours truly, Reverend John Shirley.
Gary Gabrofan, Michael Pepe, Princess We Are Go, Chaos McBobcat Drummond, Phineas Narco, K-Rob, somebody named Walter,
the uber-goober-boobie-baby, and Bishop Joey from the First Church of the Last Laugh.
Some of us got their light, friends.
So, when this annual subgenius business meeting begins, the only stockholders present are Izzy Isn't, Puzzling Evidence,
Cyberpunk,
author, Reverend John Shirley, Dr. Gary Gabrofan, Phineas Narco, and Bishop Joey.
Also known as Ed Holmes of the San Francisco Mime Troupe.
The music in the background right now is from the new Amino Acids album due out June 2007.
The Amino Acids album called Humanity Will Fall Like Pins.
You can look at theaminoacids.com or their MySpace page.
I'm Ed Holmes.
You may not play all five hours of the five-hour show in order over the next five weeks,
but until my subgenius history course is over on the 25th, I'm still ball to the wall.
And so, onward, subgenius soldiers marching as to Walmart.
The Amino Acids album called Humanity Will Fall Like Pins.
It has taken them the full two months to get ready.
Today is X-Day.
It is now HR minus 59 minutes.
There is less than an hour left.
There can be no margin for error.
There can be no second chance.
Well, good hello, everyone.
Everyone.
This, uh...
This is not...
This is not the first Thursday of every month at midnight.
Ouch.
And, uh...
It is I.
It is I, the over-the-edge guy.
Izzy isn't.
But, um...
It's not quite over the edge, either.
It's, uh...
A special, unscheduled broadcast of over-the-edge and the subgenius.
The Church of the Subgenius Foundation Incorporated are all here.
And we're all here.
We're all going to do five hours together.
All together.
Right here.
And that's what we're doing.
So it's not this and it's not that.
It's both.
To a place where men satisfy their bloodlust by hunting human quarry.
All right, gentlemen.
Ready for testing.
Put on your headphones.
And, uh...
Pick up a microphone.
Bob.
I hate Bob.
I love Bob.
You want to sit in here with us?
But that's not Bob.
That's Ed Horne from the Church of the Subgenius.
No.
It's...
You know who?
Now, I have decided unilaterally...
Yeah, go ahead.
...to name this show...
Unibilaterally?
Unilaterally?
...the New Year's Revolution Show.
Now, what does that mean?
Uh, that means we have to spin around in a Gregorian manner.
Well, according to my script, it will be explained later on.
Okay.
I don't know what...
Where...
Where is Dr. Hal?
Dr. Hal?
Uh, we buried him, I think, last week.
Ladies and gentlemen, we'd like...
We regret to inform you that Dr. Hal has passed away almost a week ago today.
And he will no longer grace this...
The big fat chairs of the subgenius.
Well, actually, we did bring him in because he wasn't smelling that bad...
...since it's been very cold.
...since it's been very cold outside lately.
So we got that cold snap, so...
Oh, I see him, yes.
So, yeah, so we just propped him in the thing.
And because he's such a motor mouth...
I like that.
He's still talking.
I mean...
I like it.
We just have to push the microphone real close.
We're trying to get a microphone jacked just right into his jaw.
I like the glazed look.
Yeah.
Uh-huh.
So, yeah, we can squeeze another show out of Dr. Hal.
His...
His cooling carcass.
Yeah, just a few electrical shocks.
You put it...
Apply a few electrical shocks.
Yeah.
...and there'll be an automatic reaction, in his case, talking.
That's right.
And Gaborofram is here with his jumper cables of love.
Meh!
Meh.
What happened to...
Where's...
Where's Bug Girl?
Is that Bug Girl?
Oh, no, Bug Girl is not coming, is she?
Not till she sees you, Don.
Oh, no.
I'm going to come here next month.
I'm going to pick her up, because otherwise...
This is for you, Cady, you're gonna make a success Spotify.
Stop right there, cue.
...and then it's history's call just be that...
Oh.
Oh, no.
No, translate.
Please translate.
Is this advisor wheels?
Would that be okay?
Just a little.
...tå®˜.
he has so much slack.
He has three pairs
at the cleaner.
He has so much,
so many slacks
and so much slack
in Cleveland.
Is he still in Cleveland?
Yes.
Oh.
Why?
Why is anybody
still in Cleveland?
I understand
it's the most
violent city
in America.
Really?
Yeah.
But see,
the reason is
that the Reverend
Stang
is there
he sucks
all the slack
from everybody else
and there's
an umbrella
of peace
around him.
But everybody else
in consequence
you know
stresses up
and they begin
to throttle
one another.
Well there it is.
He's a slack sucker.
Uh-huh.
Okay, well so
okay so
So we're really
fine.
It's funny now.
All right.
Okay, Bishop Joey's here
and he's answering
any of your
religious and or
sexual questions.
So you can call in
at 848.
That's all.
That's all the
numbers we've got.
We had a big budget
cut here at KPFA
so we had to lose
four of our phone numbers
so we're just down
to 848.
Just dial 848
and wait.
And John Shirley
is here to answer
any of your
science fiction questions.
All right.
The sexual and religious
questions have
How big was
Paul Anderson's poll?
Paul Anderson's poll.
It was Philip
really a dick.
It's one of the
mysteries.
Religion and sexuality
have converged
or have
you know
it has shown
it has
dropped its pants
this year
because of Haggard
right?
And people like that.
So my question
to you is
Yes.
You know
where
is
your particular
theological
domain
with respect
to this
emerging
experience
explosion
of self-exposure
sexually
amongst the
religious leaders
of our country?
It's under my bed.
The domain
is under my bed.
I feel
there is no God.
You feel
but how
exactly?
Feel
but to feel
is not enough
to be
expressively
intellectually
and convincingly
appropriate.
Feeling?
Feeling
is
feelings are
no longer
uh
shorthand
for
your expression
of a religious
and or
uh
sexual
congress
which is
a hundred and tenth
time I think
going around.
Well one of my
samples says
feeling is
believing.
Feeling is
Dr. Johnson
said I refuted
thus and he
kicked the
he kicked the
stone
thus
and it hurt
his foot
and then he said
I believe
because that
hurts.
That's too much
of a coincidence
for comfort.
I know
but you can't
expect anything
less here
on KPFA
in your ear.
You're trying to
go to bed
you're trying to
go to sleep
and somebody's
left the radio
on and you
reach for the
dial and it
won't turn off
and your radio
is stuck
and the clock
is ticking
and you're
trying to
get some sleep
because tomorrow
you've got to
get up and
face another
day at your
grueling
grim
boring job
but here you
are stuck
listening to the
radio
listening to us
so join us
and if it
hurts
you believe.
Yes, if it
hurts
you believe.
Believe?
Yes.
I have a
sexual question.
cat
a female
and
she eats
too much
and the reason
she eats
too much
is because
she likes
to fight
all the other
cats in the
neighborhood.
Uh-huh.
And
that's what
worry is made.
And?
He's listening
to his delayed
broadcast.
He wants to
hear himself.
Oh, I see.
Okay.
Yeah, the whole
station now, you
know, is on a
delay.
Didn't used to
be, but it is
now.
So we can't
say beep
or beep
or beep.
We have a
dump button,
but I promise
not to use it.
Oh, we did.
Yeah.
So when you
call,
yeah,
listen to me,
people.
When you call,
don't, don't
listen to your
radio.
Don't listen to
your computer.
your, listen to
your telephone.
Because in your
telephone's earpiece
is the only
real time
that exists
now.
Listen to
me only.
Turn down
your radio.
your computer.
If you try
to converse
with us,
with those
up, you
will sound
drunk.
Throw away
your computer.
You will
sound drunk
if you attempt
to follow
the delayed
broadcast
while calling.
Drink heavily.
Thank you.
Please don't
speak into
the microphones.
That's too
much of a
question.
Think into
the microphones.
Only think
into them.
We're going
to stink
into the
microphones.
These microphones
are so sensitive
that they feel
insulted if you
talk into them.
We're still
stinking into
the microphone
right now as
Dr. Halloway.
We're trying
to get Dr.
Hall jacked
into the
microphone.
I just want
to get this
over early.
You know,
the stang
and the
howl.
Let's try
to get the
show out
of the
door by
1230.
And Phineas
Narco's a
tape.
He's loopy.
Phineas is
looped.
I thought
Phineas Narco
was changing.
Nothing.
There's no
doubt that
someone's
passing out
information.
And that
information is
the number
you can call
to find out
about this
coming
St.
Stupid's Day
parade,
number 29.
It's coming
right up.
That's right.
April 1st
will be the
29th annual
St.
Stupid's Day
parade,
starting at
noon at
the Pointy
Building in
San Francisco,
going up
Columbus Avenue
to either
Washington Square
Park or
Joe DiMaggio's
bathroom.
So get
ready,
put it in
your calendar,
and be
prepared to
march once
again in
honor of
St.
Stupid,
a little
known,
St.
442,
443,
513,
and 716
in the
parking
meters.
I bet
you didn't
know that.
You're not
Catholic,
are you?
I didn't
think so.
It's April
1st.
Is that
April 1st?
I mean,
is that
when the
parade is?
I thought
it was
April 1st.
It could
be April
1st,
I'm not
sure.
Noon at
the Pointy
Building,
so if you
want more
information about
that,
go to
ststupid.com.
It's
S-A-I-N-T-S-T-U-P-I
S-T-U-P-I
Whatever,
you know,
figure it
out.
Google it.
Google it
yourself.
Oh yeah?
Well,
Google this.
What?
Where even
an innocent
corpse can
find no
peace.
Google this.
Of course,
we'll keep
our safety.
Whoever's
responsible,
Dr. Bronson,
radar control
to Dr. Bronson,
And now the pretty part of the show.
That's so much better.
Now maybe you can get to sleep,
because we'll be playing some easy listening trance music
for you to get into your theta state.
That's right.
It's the face of the new fascism.
It's soothing fascism.
The soothing sounds of fascism tonight.
...a mad, deadly, worldwide, conspiratorial,
gangster, computer god, communism...
Try that number.
Call that number.
Theta follows.
Distance, 486 miles.
Height, 50.2 miles.
Speed...
Five miles per second.
Something bad has happened.
The show you need.
So you can't use all those recorded instructions
on phone fidelity.
Those are all gone now, right?
Say a good day.
Go.
That is correct.
You could technically still have phone fidelity.
The delay doesn't really affect that.
It's just that...
If you don't listen to your telephone, you won't hear yourself.
Okay, take a six-pack and scan.
Estimated time of arrival at contact point, one minute, 58 seconds.
Go.
Okay, now that's well...
Okay, now...
Don't look.
Yes, dear friend.
Now, that usually brings Stang, if you say,
And he pokes him, but he pokes him.
It summons him.
The Reverend Stang will be here.
He will be here later.
The Reverend Stang of the Church of the Subgenus.
Stop it, Gary!
I'm hearing his...
And co-creator of the Church of the Subgenus.
Check, check.
By-loading.
drummond.
All right, let's fire control.
Fire control alerted, sir.
Two grains of sand fall out now and then.
Young Martin also says that he saw something on the borders.
On a quiet summer day in Houston, Texas,
unbeknownst to the rest of the world,
a great scientific operation was performed.
A squid was eating dough in a polyethylene bag.
On that day, a human being was given a shape that would last forever.
A very repellent shape.
When may we expect you?
In 30 seconds.
A shape that would never age or decay.
Over and off.
And an event had taken place that is soon to affect all of humanity.
Something that he insists was his brother.
But we know that his brother is dead.
We also know that he is not lying in his coffin.
Someone in this village is practicing witchcraft.
The Reverend Stang will be here.
Have faith.
Yeah, this is not your usual camp.
We have a lot of followers meeting here.
Ed's going to try to play it now.
We've got the big wig himself here coming tonight.
Oh, he's doing really good.
Mr. Ivan Stang, owner and operator of the Subgenius Church Foundation of America.
But Ed and I will be gone by the time Stang gets here.
You guys were gone, gone, gone years ago.
So why are we here?
Why did we drive all the way from our far off homes and nice warm homes?
They probably were just waiting for us to come back.
We're probably dating from the acid test.
For the New Year's Revolution show.
Oh, that's right.
Come on, get into it.
What if I refuse to even participate in the New Year?
We have a whole new chance here.
I'm...
We have a...
You know, this is the last year.
You have to understand that it has been announced.
The Church of the Subgenius has announced that the end of the world will take place
on Thursday, July 5th, 2020.
And in preparation for the fulfillment of this doomsday prophecy,
the Church is requesting that all of its members participate in a festival
with rock concerts and blasphemous rituals taking place in upstate New York
during the final weekend before the arrival of the apocalypse.
Oh, they're always doing that.
They do that every year.
But see, there are many other people who make predictions about the end of the world.
They give up too easily.
They say the end of the world...
There was a guy in 1986 or so
who wrote a book explaining that the end of the world would come in 1988.
And he sold 5 million of them.
And it didn't come.
And so he wrote another book saying it would come in 1989.
He sold a lot of those too.
He was that much persistent.
And then he gave up.
The Church of the Subgenius never gives up predicting the end of the world.
Even after the end of the world, the Subgenius will predict it.
Well, if you go to the edge of the earth,
and throw a rock, what do you hit?
So after the end of the world,
there's got to be another end, another end, another end.
Well, there's the Gardall Shield.
First of all, no one ever accounts for the Gardall Shield.
And there's a novel by John Shirley called The Other End.
But I won't promote it this segment.
The Other End?
The Other End.
What's that, the check?
It's an alternative apocalypse.
A novel of alternative apocalypse.
Oh, yeah.
You know, every time I look for a new book,
I find a John Shirley book at my local bookstore.
I don't see one.
Well, you've got to look in the cheesy section,
in the cheesy paperback section.
Or go to a better bookstore.
A better class of bookstore might help also.
I look for those books by Lloyd St. Alcorn.
I don't know if you remember those.
Oh, that's a name that resonates with the cobwebs.
Dr. David Meyer, I believe, wrote several terrible books.
Under the pen name of Lloyd St. Alcorn.
But it was slack because he got paid to write terrible books.
That's right.
But he got paid lousy money.
I get paid lousy money to write good books.
So he had more slack than me because he got paid the same money to write bad books,
which is easier.
Edgar Wisenant made himself a nice packet of money with a book assuring everyone that 1988 was the end of the world.
He had 88 reasons for his assurance.
And he sold 4 million copies to a gullible public.
And in 1989 came out with a book in which he said he had made some mistakes,
but it was going to end in 1989.
You know, that kind of persistence is admirable.
Elizabeth Clare Prophet said that 1990 was going to be the end of the year.
The Gulf War broke out and religious enthusiasts got on their phones to the radio stations saying that Armageddon
would be in 1991.
Well, everybody I know died in 2007.
You're mixing up the past and the future again.
You know, Gary's problem is that he thinks that the future is the past because he lives outside of time.
Gary lives in eternity.
He's got one foot in eternity and he keeps wobbling back and forth and he kind of gets them mixed up.
And he can see the future.
He thinks it's the past.
He spins around.
He doesn't know the difference.
But spending all this time in my own tent made out of my own skin,
wouldn't you think that I would be in my own reality?
Too soon for what?
Absolutely.
You're spinning.
You're like an object being spun on a lathe and gradually ground down into a shape that can only be imagined.
Well, here I have a question for you, John.
This is more KPFA-like.
More time for what?
I found this here on the floor, KPFA.
I can't believe it.
That's where all my questions come from.
It says, what are the ties between immigrants from a Middle Eastern country and an African American born in South Carolina?
Is that a reference to Obama or something?
I have no idea.
The end of the world's coming and you're just talking about this stuff.
Now you're supposed to play side one, cut two, Don, to answer my question.
I'm bound on the floor here.
That's how desperate we are for questions from the great world.
We're scrabbling around on the floor like a crack addict.
Good.
You want questions?
You got questions.
Why can't you amend your revelation and move it up to early September?
Followers of Nostradamus claim that according to the French seer, the end of the world came in July 1999.
We're perfectly willing to adjust to circumstances.
Hey, can we have September 11th early this year?
The supreme moment of the universe has already happened.
That is a grim joke.
Jesus said this generation should not pass away until the fulfillment of his prediction of the end times was fulfilled.
And I don't know if anybody noticed 1,998 or so years ago that it didn't come about.
So all these people predict the end of the world.
It doesn't happen.
The Church of the Subgenius predicts it much more diligently than everybody else.
June 789 is when it really happened on the 1,2345 AM Universal Time.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9.
We lived through it.
I have it on tape.
It really happened.
Gary, your output in the amp is a bit high.
Okay.
That's because Ed's playing it now.
See, no hands and it's still loud.
I've got a list of the end of the world.
Play something really loud.
St. Augustine said it was coming in the year 1000.
That's it?
That's as loud as you'll ever get?
No, we can play as loud as you want.
That's pretty good there, I think.
Pretty good right there?
Yeah.
Okay.
Go to it, Ed.
It's your turn.
History of the universe.
Wow.
Isaac.
Isaac Newton predicted the end of the world.
1733 for the end of the world.
Isaac Newton predicted the end of the show.
Isaac Newton said someday the puzzling show would end and everyone would rejoice in the end.
And the wellman had fell from the tree and hit Isaac square in the capooter.
Oh, yeah.
He did.
And Isaac Newton predicted the end of the world for 1733.
If you would like to attempt to speak to the subgenius foundation church of America,
please call us at
Don't say hello when your phone stops ringing.
You're on the air.
And don't listen to your radio.
Please.
In 1736, William Winston of Cambridge announced the birth of the great American philosopher
that the end of the world was about to commence.
Panic-stricken Londoners headed for high places
to escape the floods, he predicted.
None of them came.
Didn't anybody ask, how does he know?
Immanuel Swedenborg, who conversed frequently with angels,
was certain that 1757 was the date.
Oh, hey, that reminds me,
we're supposed to have Swedenborg breads for dinner tonight.
Is that like Swedenborg?
We cut the pancreas out of philosophers
and dip them in cornmeal.
They're delicious.
The thyroid is supposed to be especially delectable
if you get a mathematician.
Nietzsche's is real bitter, though.
You don't like bitter, you like Nietzsche.
Oh, everyone has their own little Nietzsche these days.
Yeah.
So if you want to join in on a frivoli
and a clever wordplay, just dial...
When you're on the air, come on, come on.
You can do it.
I think they were trying to say
a Freud to live and too young to die.
There are people around the world
who really still believe
that if you eat somebody's heart
who is courageous, you will be courageous.
So if you eat their brains...
Eat somebody prettier than you are.
Eat somebody smarter than you are.
Eat somebody stronger than you are.
Well, I've been nibbling a lot.
But eat somebody.
Whatever you do.
Are we allowed to say that on the air?
Eat somebody?
Yeah, if it's a song.
You gotta eat somebody on your bond.
But not their lungs.
Got any recipes?
So cannibalism's coming back, we hear.
So if you got some recipes...
It will come back.
When the world famine comes, my friend,
which I have been predicting,
the American famine...
The great pulling began.
Imagine a famine in the United States.
What would that be like?
Yum.
Who would we eat?
We'd eat first.
Well, we'd eat the Welsh rabbits made from Volkswagens.
Okay.
If you have a famine, and you have bird flu...
There are people who've eaten cars.
Yeah.
There are, bit by bit, like chunk by chunk.
There was a guy who cut up a car and ate it.
It took him several years.
Did you ever see The Metal-Eating Bird?
The cartoon, The Metal-Eating Bird?
You've seen it, haven't you?
No.
I don't watch television.
Well, Doug Wellman has seen The Metal-Eating Bird.
Oh, I've heard.
Oh, whip it out.
You got it on tape?
Whip it out.
But...
Ah!
Charles Russell.
Charles Russell, founder of a group later known as the Witnesses of Jehovah,
does that sound familiar, said that Christ...
Yeah, they had a big hit.
He said that Christ had returned invisibly in the year 1874.
There was no way of proving he was wrong.
Oh, well, but the girls all knew that somebody were staring at them in their gym locker room.
Yeah, when they went wee-wee...
That was Jesus.
There was a guy with a beard.
But, you know...
In fact, somebody pointed out to me today that if Jesus is always watching you, we are
Jesus's porn.
Oh, man.
Oh, that's right.
That's what you're...
Derming!
We're gonna porn with Jesus Watchers.
Yes, and we're Bob's commercials.
Well, Russell, what is your definition of an actress?
That's what your relatives do, and you have to use...
So, where are all the rest of all the important guests on this show?
Those relatives are right, yes.
Oh, the...
There...
I think it is something...
Look behind the...
The...
Man, yeah.
That was a lot of people and I'm watersuuuuutting it pretty fits me...
That's right.
That's it for now!
... who are now you sticking with?
I don't think you can get the title of Best Actress...
I heard a lot of other actors.
I'melu Iguã£ã¦ã„ã†...
When a young lad growing up in the lab derived this dog, or something like that.
You can say that again.
When...
I do think I'melu Dam in Iguaghetti!
Yeah!
Yeah, I do with Forbidden okay.
All right.
I'm just going to rent Bishop Joey and ride him on the beach out at San Gregorio myself.
Rent to Bishop Joey.
Yeah.
The Jehovah's Witnesses predicted the end of the world for 1975.
When they come to your door and they're trying to convince you they've got some information.
1975.
Then again, 1984.
They said that was going to be the end of the world.
When they come to your house, ask them if they remember that.
And if you want an alternative apocalypse, go to www.signsofwitness.com.
Where is my website of alternative apocalypse?
Apocalypse?
Apocalypse is related to apocalypse.
It's when you can't say apocalypse, and so you say apocalypse.
I've had a little experience with apuckerlips.
Apocalypse only happens back east.
Apocalypse now.
They have sodas.
They have sodas here, and they have pop back there.
I pop my lips now.
Uh, yeah.
Apuckerlips now.
Earphone radio.
The problem I have is being in that tree.
Hello, caller.
Now, this is a true thing.
Hello?
In 1983, as the residents of Calcutta,
a small town 30 miles away,
north of Rome, prepared for their annual procession,
honoring a holy relic,
a shocking announcement from the parish priest
put a damper on festivities.
The relic has vanished.
What was that relic?
The lopped off body parts of a certain Messiah.
That is, it was the foreskin of Jesus.
It was alleged to be, I'm not making this up,
the foreskin of Jesus supposedly found in India,
in, uh, no, in Calcutta, not Calcutta,
in Philly.
In 1557, and a series of miracles soon followed finding the holy foreskin.
Uh, a big storm, it's perfumed, missed.
Well, in fact, it has not turned up, uh, and they, and the people of Calcutta
claim that it was stolen by the Vatican,
who didn't like the holy foreskin being out there in their church,
and they were embarrassed by it.
Oh, they were afraid someone was going to clone it.
Oh, that, that, there has been discussion of cloning the holy foreskin.
Holy foreskin, holy foreskin, holy foreskin.
Uh, sounds like a Phil Henry.
Okay.
Here, I've got mine here in my wallet.
Let's try to clone it and see if it works for me.
I'm Jewish.
Lines of pilgrims stretch from the church doors to beyond the walls of the fortress town
to see the holy foreskin.
I think we should stretch Bishop Joey's over this African drum head.
Oh.
But can you use it as a shower cap?
The Pope is using it as a cap.
It is to, it makes it.
It makes that weird hat more snuggly on it.
Uh, the skateboarder's one.
There's an image to conjure for you, ladies and gentlemen.
Yes, if you can join in here in the blasphemy.
We've got blasphemy, 49 cents a pound.
It's available right now here on your radio.
So call it.
And contribute your blasphemy right here.
Two famous religious figures in America who were anti-gay
turned out to be gay this year.
Haggard and another guy.
His name I forgot.
Merle?
No, not Merle.
Merle did not.
Merle is the last guy to turn out.
He's not gay.
Oh, I hope.
You're going to ruin my, you know, my reverence.
Sorry.
I'm down with gays, but I don't want Merle to be gay.
Merle Haggard may not be gay.
Merle's into truckers, I hear.
Mother truckers.
But what I want to know is, when is the Bishop Joey going to come out?
Bishop Joey did come out.
He came out last year and got all wet, so he went back in.
It's going to be winter for another six years.
Ladies and gentlemen, he has arrived.
There's no point in putting it off anymore.
He is in the building.
The Reverend Stang?
Yes, and he is about to join us here on the radio.
The sacred scribe of the Church of the Subgenius has arrived.
He is in the building.
Exclusive New Year's Revolution show.
The alternative apocalypse won't be long now.
The Reverend Stang.
Wait for those dulcet tones.
Stang.
Listen to the concepts carefully.
Yes, dear friends.
Try to absorb from the master.
He will appear.
Yes, dear friends.
www.subgenius.com
Stang.
Stang in the butt by a wasp.
And he drug a phylo in on the bottom of his heel.
All right.
I wash the bottom of my shoes every time I kick phylos.
But.
Don't say hello.
When your phone stops ringing, you're on the air.
Just go ahead.
That's our policy.
And we're not changing it now.
I'm hoping that Vice President Cheney will show up tonight.
Yeah.
Right now he's in the bunker changing into his thong.
A lot of people saw that thong.
It was a couple of years ago.
Burning Man, Chick Cheney.
He showed up at the bunker.
The fashion show at Burning Man a couple of years ago.
And he was conduced by Dr. Hal, who was emceeing the fashion show,
to get loose and party down.
And it wound up that Dick Cheney was wearing a thong.
And there were 40,000 people at the time at Burning Man.
Immediately, 20,000 people left.
And they took their foreskins with them.
And they took all their foreskins with them.
The sacred foreskin.
Calcated.
It isn't the one.
You're still going to get wet.
Kitty.
And baby.
I'm hoping this is it.
The sacred lily.
Okay, that one didn't take the foreskin.
You have to drink it.
It's here.
Infant Philo's here now.
Maybe we could trade Infant Philo to the Flying Saucers for a burrito.
Yeah.
A big burrito.
One for all of us.
Clear the field.
We're monitoring Philo's child.
They're in constant contact with Philo's child.
Dang.
She's as good as on the planet of the earth.
Very well.
I'm coming down right now.
Dang.
Over and out.
See.
Way double zombies.
Pretty soft.
Well, I think it's time to frown.
Frowning.
Fropping?
I don't know who has the fropping.
We'd better have it over fast.
I'm fropless.
You see?
The energy.
The force packed in the rock itself is being released.
Oh yeah.
We should run home and get it.
Alright, we almost turned around and stopped.
So, 8484425.
Talk to a totally naked Bishop Joey.
That's right.
Bishop Joey.
Oh my god, he is naked.
Seminal and second.
He's the secular head of the First Church, the Last Laugh, World's Fast-Growing, Snack of Religion,
100% of the Dogma, Religion of Light, Religion of One Holy Day, Year and Today,
isn't it?
But April 1st is.
He's here and he's naked.
And he's sitting right here and he can talk to you.
Somebody get a sanitary wipe for that chair.
No, it's okay.
It'll clean up really nice with a hose down the studio at the end of the show at 5 in the morning.
So talk to Bishop Joey now before he is not talkable.
Any questions you have.
What's he doing to the microphone?
Oh, let me rub it.
I got a little itch.
Oh, I got an itch.
Let me scratch it right.
Oh, does that feel good.
So talk to a totally naked Bishop Joey.
That's right.
And any question, anything, any subject.
I don't know.
I got an answer for you.
After careful study of the Bible, Reverend William Miller thought that the end was 1834.
Tuesday.
He changed his mind and decided it was 1836.
Then he recalculated it and found that it was 1843 in the month of Israel.
Wednesday.
He said it was 1844.
There used to be six to choose from.
That was to prove one of the biggest events of the end time calendar.
When April came and Miller set to work on a new date.
Miller's brave new choice, March 21st, 1844, for the end of the world.
The Millerites waited in droves and high vantage points in special ascension robed for the expected end.
Hysteria reigned.
People sold up farms and homes.
But still, frustratingly, the end did not come.
They were not persistent.
The Church of the Subgenius will not.
They will not give up on the end of the world.
Order your end of the world now.
We will specially deliver it to you.
That can be done.
Personalized.
Everybody's subjective end of the world is when they're gone.
I can take care of it.
When would you like the end of the world?
We'll deliver.
Closed society.
It is closed society.
45 caliber end of the world.
Oh, it's magic.
Everything we don't understand is magic.
Hold on.
Hold it.
I shall pitch an eave out down to 12.
12.
5 Zulu.
Providence control wants to know where is he.
Antony 262.
Who's got him?
Antony?
Stalling cleared from Zulu.
One.
Wait, no.
club bit random.
××˜×Ÿ
f Chung
ruledmon
know and I don't know if this is one of the signs of the apocalypse or not but Grace Jones
has been my lover for at least about three and a half years now. Who has? Grace Jones.
Grace Jones the disco singer. Oh in your mind she has and in my mind she was mine too.
No she's I've read all those long legs.
My alien lover. Grace Jones. Grace Jones. Is your your sweetheart's sweetheart then
the end of the world is nigh. Because there's no justice my friend. I don't know about any of that
but I know who my lover is and she she's a wonderful priestess.
She's a.
She's a goddess. She's a teacher. She is magical.
You know if you make of her a magical object and put her picture on the wall and
prostrate yourself before it she becomes magical for you.
She is actually on the wall not a not a picture. She is actually hanging on the wall right now.
Just like in.
Do the police know?
Oops sorry.
It sounds uncomfortable.
Anyway you aren't.
You didn't come tack her to the wall did you?
She's skinny enough you could use thumbtacks.
Oh she's still alive.
Yeah but don't forget she might actually be magic.
Grace Jones you know there is a kind of Aoife sort of vibe coming out of her.
No it's easy to say.
I know why you're saying it but she actually could be magic.
You understand me?
Well she is.
No I know it's easy to say that.
Right I know.
Yeah.
I had macaroni and cheese for dinner too.
There were.
You know many of the great performers you know in the in were in fact shamanistic.
Jim Morrison and there and Grace Jones sometimes there were she had her shamanistic moments.
She is a shamanistic moment.
Just like my macaroni and cheese.
You've got sacred macaroni and cheese.
You're spending an evening at home with your family.
Macaroni and cheese is like my peyote.
My personal peyote but it's macaroni and cheese.
Suddenly without warning.
Great product.
Excuse me.
Macaroni and cheese could be mind altering.
Probably treated.
Well I believe it is mind altering.
And if you look close enough at anything I don't think acid anymore.
But when I was a teenager about 19 years old I occasionally did.
And I remember looking at a pile of noodles.
What are you saying?
I don't think acid.
No it was rice.
A pile of rice.
No no not you him.
And it was good lord.
A manifestation from the other side.
The Reverend Stang.
So good to see you.
Did you say if you could explain one thing at a time you'd get more out of it?
Is that what you said?
Are you sure?
It's Don Hagenbrenner.
John Sherlinbrenner.
I think it's about time for another ginger ale.
So I will meet you on the flip side.
Okay.
You want to drink that crap go right ahead.
I drink club soda.
I hallucinated that it was an eternal plate of rice.
That's what happened.
Oh.
out and begin to kill each other. No, actually
the new subgenius
headquarters is not in Cleveland
at all, but in Cleveland Heights.
Which
sacrifices the
slack of the rest of Cleveland
for its own extremely low crime
rate. I live in a
kind of a little enclosed
fortress.
The slacker mansion,
we call it. So what, Texas is just
on its own now, right?
Sorry!
Actually,
when I
go to Texas, and I just came
from there. The desolate
flats of Texas. It rains.
It rains if I visit
Texas. When I leave,
it stops raining. It didn't rain for
a year.
At least not in Stang
County, unfortunately.
Until we understand it,
some parts of Texas got their Katrina.
That's right!
Time check, everyone.
So there was like
a locus of global warming,
a cell of global warming
settled over the state after you left.
Well, when we had to flee
Texas,
we placed a curse
upon the benighted
state of Texas that there
would be no rain
until such time as we returned.
What kind of
vehicle did you flee Texas?
I'm curious.
United Airlines, in this case.
But he drove it on the freeway.
That was the curious thing.
You got to Cleveland without a car?
People had to drive off the road to let the
747 drive by.
When we fled Texas
to Cleveland, we went in a series
of covered wagons
across the prairie. We faced many
hardships, droughts,
locusts, plagues.
Those were the old steam wagons, right?
Rednecks.
Yeah.
Well, no, we were the rednecks.
All right.
It's all relative.
Oh, it's a tale
to make the Mormons
cringe.
The exodus from Texas.
It kind of has
rhymes, kind of a ring to it.
Exodus from Texas.
River and Stang, I have a press
release from the Church of the Subgenus.
Can I ask you about this?
I heard you reading that on the
limo on the way here.
And I thought to myself, that sounds
like a Reverend Motormat press release.
The Church is inviting all of its members
worldwide to gather together for the final
hours in Sherman, New York
from Thursday, 28th to July
Thursday, July 5th at a clothing
optional outdoor campground.
I'm very interested to read
the Church has been engaged in a massive
recruitment campaign to increase the numbers
of its membership for the arrival of the
exodus.
And it's seeking performers and producers
from the adult entertainment industry.
Yeah, that's right.
We have a new adult film festival
award ceremony that just started last year.
It's and you know, it's just it's a way to
broaden the artistic reach of the church and
also to get a certain amount of attention.
If you think about it, you know, and a lot of
the saints of.
The Church have been workers in the shall we say sex
industry, Kitten, a TV dog, the great saints,
Chris Kitten, a TV dog, John Holmes and some of the
other great saint, Wad, the giants, you might say,
especially the plumbers.
Yeah, I have a special place in my heart, a very
large hole in my heart where the plumbers.
Yeah, and it's still dripping through that hole.
Isn't it?
No.
Oh, yes.
I got some.
I'm discharged.
I'm off of it.
So July 5th, it's all coming to an end and it does
every year, basically.
Well, we have a new apocalypse every year.
And my opinion, my theory is that is that other
people who predict the end of the world, I read a
list of them.
You might have heard some.
Yeah, we did.
I heard that other people are not diligent enough
about bringing about the end of the world and
predicting the end of the world.
And the Church of the subgenius has to be praised
for its persistence.
It will not.
Give up.
Our faith is absolute.
The aliens, the exes will arrive on July 5th, 1998,
which obviously has not arrived yet.
Bob said that date.
Therefore, that date has not yet arrived.
It was upside down.
It's a typo.
There's been this whole tampering with calendars,
which is pretty obvious.
I mean, come on.
Does anybody know what time it is?
I noticed.
We don't know what year this is.
We don't even know what planet.
The numbers seem to swim around when I look at them.
When I look at my calendar, the numbers seem to wobble
and swim, but then everything else is.
Oh, everybody's so sure that this is the year 2007.
Oh, everybody's so sure this is planet Earth.
Oh, yeah, it's planet Earth.
No, it's not.
It's not.
You're right, Ivan.
This is not planet Earth.
It's just what we named it.
That doesn't mean it is planet Earth.
We don't know what the name of this planet is.
Somebody's got to be kidding me.
Somebody's going to come and tell us the name one day.
Oh, you mean Sputnik?
We named everything.
Our reality is based on a house of cards,
a teetering edifice that could fall any time
because it's built on a bunch of hooey.
Yes, I'll say it.
Hooey is what it's built.
Foundation of hooey.
A bunch of hoo-ha.
Who's playing?
2007.
Two and seven means it's acting together.
Who's playing that song way down low?
Maybe it's the year nine.
Year nine.
Everybody be quiet a minute.
Hang on.
1998 is.
This is a test.
Hang on.
Who is playing that song way down low?
Who's playing that?
Anybody here?
No.
Really?
What the hell is that?
I don't know.
It's like some 70s power band.
Wait, who would expect some kind of random weird noise
in the background on this show?
There's some kind of radio show going on under ours.
It's a radio show.
It appears it sounds like.
I heard some Phineas.
It's country music.
Just download Phineas and I.
Who is it?
I heard it.
I heard that for a second.
It was a reference to Phineas Narco.
He may assert himself in some.
Ha ha hooey.
You know, radio waves can impinge themselves mysteriously.
The silent radio.
Until we understand it and master it.
They will have to continue spending that $30.
Listen to that.
What is that?
Who is that?
It's in your right ear, isn't it?
I know.
It's only in the left ear.
Your headphones are backwards.
Your ears are on backwards.
I'd like to find out what that is.
Hmm.
Oh, God.
It sounds like Judy Collins or.
How could that be happening?
I think it's a ghost of a folk song show that was in this KPFA studio.
Oh.
What was that?
It's puzzling evidence who just isn't even here.
He just turned something on and left.
Left the room with this.
I can't imagine something like that.
Let him listen to this.
What is in the background, he said.
What is he even playing this for?
What a surprise.
He's out fropinating and subjecting us to folk music.
There's something wrong with him.
Folk music.
All right.
Listen to that.
Blessed silence.
They're in folk music.
It always feels better when you turn it off.
All right.
Take my new how to use.
Trust your radio.
Okay.
Trust you.
Ow.
I win.
I win every time.
Take off.
Wet head.
Towel off.
Go away.
1, 0, 8, 4, 8, 4, 4, 2, 5.
Is that what year this is?
Maybe that's what year this is.
What year is it?
If it's not 2007, what year is it?
If you missed that first number, this is it.
5.
That's it.
It's the year 5.
1, 0.
We've got 1,993 years until the end.
8, 4, 8, 4, 5.
And tell us what time it is where you're at.
And tell us where you're at.
And tell us what day call where you're at.
And if you're Chinese, it's a different year.
That's not the real Francis Deck.
That is an imposter deck.
Oh, it's not?
No, that's not the real Deck.
That's right.
I read about this.
Someone, a guy at a radio station remade his text.
Right.
Yeah.
The true Francis Deck.
It's a lot better than him, though.
Would never have been able to enunciate those words so well.
No.
That's what I figured.
It's probably better that it isn't.
What about...
Students in the, maybe, Logic University course in the subgenius history, the first
100 years...
Yes, I have it right here.
...are able to download the original Francis Deck texts.
Did he ever read his own text?
I don't know.
But I did get a copy of the original things that he wrote.
That maybe it was.
He would use it for in- Ğ½ĞµÑ‘.
When we got your little textbook...
He was killed in the first of the stamps.
There you go.
He was killed in the first four and he was accused of of offending a pasadena...
Well, it carbooling Junkhead...
I ì´ê±° we thought, I kind of got it, I don't know, if that...
Let me check, let me check.
It's.
You know what, but this thing when he tinkered with hearts.
You say it should've been a stick in the book.
What are the three slacks of abenefit as I picture it?
A tape, because of the dusty ĞºĞ°Ğ¶Ğ´.
onnen.
9 bucks.
Yeah, sure. Now, yeah, sure.
This was in the day, man.
Back in the past.
What day?
A thousand years ago.
When the Church of the Subgenius was first inspired into existence.
When was he doing this? Early 80s?
Is that right?
Francis Deck?
Yeah.
I got my Xerox in the early 80s, yes.
1982.
Four billion eyesight television cameras.
That's him.
Communist, gangster, computer god, master race.
Testing, testing.
You are living, thinking, mad, deadly, worldwide communist.
Now, the person reading the Deck text is J.R. Bob Dobbs.
Of course, I knew that.
Is this thing on?
But listen, that guy in San Francisco, do you know the guy who's putting out the, what is it,
the set of CDs called from Monster God Computer, Communist Monster God Computer,
something that's his label?
And he's putting out all these outtakes.
Outtakes and bloopers and people freaking out.
Gosh, what an idea.
Celebrity bloopers.
But his label is named the Mad Conspiracy Computer, whatever, Communist God thing.
That's his label.
So I wondered if it was the same guy by any chance.
Is Deck dead?
Yes.
Oh, good.
Yes, and in fact, some lads from Dallas went and videotaped him on his deathbed in a cruel mockery of his condition.
Wow, I'm glad somebody did.
I'm not really aware.
That's a boring video.
Do you have any tapes of him or something?
That was him.
That was him ranting.
That was someone reading the rants of Francis Deck.
This is his writing.
Living dead Frankenstein slavery.
This is his writing with someone pretending to be him.
Listen to it.
It applies today.
Actually, he's right about that.
He was like a Nostradamus.
It's quite amazing.
Only a lot more specific.
I mean, this is from the early 80s, and I'm still playing it, which shows you how relevant it still is after all this time.
What if it had been 20 years later?
Oh, not you, Gary.
The man made inside out planets with nucleonic powered speed much faster than the speed of light.
Look up and see the gangster computer god concocted new fake starry sky.
The worldwide completely controlled deadly degenerative climate.
It's like an anticipation of the Matrix concept.
Well, Alex Jones certainly has some explaining to give.
That's Alex Jones?
Yeah.
Yeah, ask me, Alex Jones.
Phony stars.
I can say lots of things.
Don't a bitch.
Or in the scenes.
Coochie coochie girl taro.
Sing not branch.
You have been listening to the subgenius radio ministry hour of Slack.
1,080 episode, which happens to be from the puzzling evidence and over the edge shows reprinted from KPFA and Berkeley.
Friends.
If you want more information about the.
Search of the subgenius.
See subgenius.com.
Subtitles by the Amara.org community