Ah, yes, there.
You see that coin?
That is insured for $10,000.
See how it seems to gather the light and draw the eye?
Yeah.
I get great repose from these things of age and beauty.
They soothe one and seem to induce sleep.
Sleep.
Close your eyes, my friend.
Hello, everybody.
Look out!
Shut up!
Come in.
$772,000.
Shut up!
$341,000.
Shut your face!
Is that correct?
Yes, it is.
$61,000.
Thank you.
Shut up!
That will be all for the present.
Very good.
Shut up!
The Subgenius Powerhouse.
Watch.
Excellent.
And at the top of the show, we've got a very interesting guest to be sure.
Reverend Ivan Stang.
He's the founder of the Church of the Subgenius and the book,
The Subgenius Cyclopedia of Slack, the Bobliagraphon.
That's right.
Stick around.
You're going to say, what?
Of course, the question is, who's Bob?
Well, Bob's an interesting guy.
He gets high on the real thing.
A full tank of gas and a clean windshield.
All righty then.
First off...
Worried about covering the lower half of your body?
Here's Bob One for A1 Slack.
Things go better with slacks and trousers.
Things go better with slacks.
Hi, this is Bob One.
And I wonder how many of our go-go-now generation action man on campus realizes
how important it is to keep the lower half of your body covered
without disguising the fact that it is indeed the lower half of your body.
Well, there's nothing like a pair of trim-fitting,
A1 slacks.
They're better than skirts and a lot warmer, too.
Thank you, Bob.
You're welcome.
And now, back to our movie.
Looks like we're going to find more.
Bob.
I know who he is, Fred hissed.
So what, said Nobby.
He's a raving genius.
He's a loony.
Yeah, well, they say there's a thin line between genius and madness.
He's fallen off it, then.
But Terry Pratchett went first.
Thanks to Lee Murr for the song and intro,
Reverend Zontar for the ancient fire sign theater actual radio ad,
and Frankenstein1970 from 1959.
Welcome to Hour of Slack number 1143,
a Bob Renewal reintroduction to that most important thing in the world
for those who might have briefly forgotten.
The first in a series of shows using categorized bits of the recordings
from a dozen recent Lives of Genius outreach events,
hither and yon, which it has taken me many days to chop up.
Besides the collage work of Norell Preff, Lee Murr, and yours truly, Reverend Stang,
we'll also be hearing from the Winter Star Devival of March 1, 2008,
and the first of the four.
John Hell's show on Pirate Cat Radio from last December.
A Puzzling Evidence show from Berkeley on February 22nd,
and a radio synesthesia show from WCSB Cleveland on March 9th,
and a Denver, Colorado talk show excerpted from Rick Barber's show on KOA Denver.
And also some real radio ads from the fire sign theater, more of those,
prompted by Zontar.
We're hearing Bonobo's Convergence in the background, recorded live last X-Day.
And I think that's all.
Oh, Bonobo's Convergence will be at next X-Day, Drew.
We've been on the road a lot, friends,
and I've just now chopped all this audio into millions of tiny bits.
And also tonight, I'm working in some audio swipe from a great movie called Slipstream,
directed by Anthony Hopkins,
which makes David Lynch look like Michael Bay.
And we even have some new songs.
And next week or two, it'll be all politics on the show, friends.
Yes, I'm afraid so.
So let's bask for now in pure, untainted bobbery, at least for this week,
starting with what the curious heard as they approached the giant subgenius circus tent
at Winterstar 2008.
Last March 1st.
Ladies and gentlemen, step right up.
Welcome to the subgenius medical curiosity show.
It's all real, all here, all alive.
And it's all on the inside.
See the smart boy who can't keep a job.
See the pretty girl who can't get a date.
Alive and on the inside.
We have diseases that are spread through sexual...
Congress.
We have debates settled by fisticuffs.
We have people famous for being famous.
And they're all inside.
Alive, alive, alive.
See grown men and women talk to an invisible monster that lives in the sky.
See your own body become ever more fragile before your very eyes.
Feel the horror as schools turn innocent children into innocent adults.
Listen to shock.
Listen to shocking tales wherein you pay to work.
They're all here on the inside.
We have pictures of a salesman who smokes a pipe.
What other religions charge all worldly goods for what we offer at a discounted and guaranteed low rate?
Eternal salvation or triple your money back?
Read words on a cathode ray tube and attend amateur religious satire performance art.
Get slacked and feel alive.
Alive on the inside.
Praise.
I wish I could say that I wrote that, but actually that was recorded outside a freak show by Dr. Onan Canobite.
I don't think they ought to live for that one.
Anyway, that's what happened on this date in history.
Well, we're going to talk about something that you may not know about.
And those of you who have heard of it, you might find this most interesting indeed.
The Church of the Subgenius, founded in 1953.
And although its current popularity is traced to the publication of Subgenius pamphlet number one in 1979,
it's found quite a bit of acceptance, especially in underground pop cult circles,
embraced on college campuses, in the underground music scene, on the Internet.
And because the tenets of discordianism, the Church of the Subgenius is often described as,
as a syncretic offshoot of the belief.
However, members state that the organization developed on its own with the publication of Subgenius pamphlet number one,
also known as The World Ends Tomorrow and You May Die by Reverend Ivan Stang, who is our guest.
And Reverend Stang, good morning.
Well, I praise Rick, praise Bob, and happy birthday, Dan Quayle.
Dan Quayle.
It's not true, but it's alleged that, of course, you know, he was head of the space program during Daddy Boy.
Bush's era.
And there was.
Appropriate.
Yeah.
And there was.
There was this.
There's kind of this, you know, almost underground.
So we say a legend that Dan thought it would be a good idea to send a mission to the sun.
But because it was so hot, he thought we'd do it at night.
There you go.
See, and that's my kind of guy, you know.
All right, Dan.
We always considered him a sort of an honorary subgenius.
Well, even though he never officially joined up, he somehow he definitely was was not a genius.
He certainly.
So we knew that he would qualify for our august organization.
Indeed.
Tell us something about the Church of the Subgenius.
And by the way, who is Bob?
J.R. Bob Dobbs is our guru and the sort of, you might say, the god of the subgeniuses and of strippers.
I'm told.
Cool.
Yeah.
Bob, some of your listeners may be familiar with his face, which you see tattooed on kids and spray painted on cars and so forth.
He looks like he looks like the 1950s version of the all around good guy dad on sitcoms.
That's right.
And if you look at any old magazine, it'll be full of ads of these square looking happy guys with pipes.
They're always smoking a pipe.
Right.
Laying in a hammock while somebody else mows the yard.
And we my partner and I, Dr.
Philo Drummond and I had noticed that the same figure popped up in all these old magazines and in old movies.
We thought it must be the same guy.
And at that point, Bob revealed himself to us through weird coincidences and messages and things.
So not too.
Many people have actually met Bob in person and survived.
In other words, you cannot look upon the face of Bob.
Well, he's so lucky.
I think he manages to avoid most of his followers without even trying to.
I'm looking at the picture of the the Kababala.
We owe a lot to other religions.
It's true that we we when we were.
We.
We're trying to put the the Church of the subgenius structure together.
We as Bob directed us, we studied all the great religions from Zoroastrianism all the way up to Scientology.
And we picked all the good parts, you know, what when you were a kid, you'd find your dad's secret stash of paperbacks and look for the good parts.
That's what we did with our dad's holy books.
Nice.
I was always looking for my own stash of Mad Magazine, which my father would hide.
Well, you've just mentioned one of our true holy books is Mad Magazine and their great publisher, William Gaines.
And the great Alfred E.
Newman, who is a cousin to Bob.
I always thought I always thought there was a kind of a connection there.
Yeah, he's well, Bob's better looking.
But yeah, they are related.
I think Alfred E.
Newman was more like the country cousin.
And he's a little older than Bob in real life.
They both are.
They're ageless figures.
Now, the and by the way, I'm looking at some of the names that involve a high profile names like Paul Rubens, Peewee Herman, who placed a picture of Bob in every episode of Peewee's Playhouse.
David Byrne, Mark Motherspawn, Penn Jillette, Penn and Teller, Robert Wilson, Robert Anton Wilson, science fiction writers, Rudy Rucker, John Shirley, actor Bruce Campbell.
And even Frank Zappa.
And so far, all of those are true.
I don't think any of those are lies or exaggerations.
Well, I'm almost certain it's probably true, especially in the Peewee Herman stuff.
Well, you could see it by he had Peewee in his title sequence every Saturday morning.
All the kids of America saw Bob leering over Peewee's shoulder during the titles.
Peewee never paid for his membership.
He he left a phone message asking us to send him an ordainment package.
He.
He could be a minister, but he never.
And he said he said, Bill, Bill, me.
And we did.
But he never paid up in our church really is a pretty major sin.
But I figure putting Bob on CBS for a year was worth at least 10 bucks.
Well, at least.
Yeah.
I mean, and after you had to give the guy some slack.
Poor, poor Peewee.
He really it's it's a shame.
What happened?
Well, yeah.
I always wondered, you know, he got busted for doing what big deal.
Try try try your 13 year old kid.
Like the old T-shirt used to say, we're pulling for you.
You betcha.
Bob, if he isn't Bob, if he isn't Bob.
Bob.
Yeah, I dig it.
Oh, Bob.
How long will it be?
Bob.
I'm going to miss you.
Bob's a bad influence on me.
Oh, Bobby.
So charming and continental.
This is Bob.
I know Bob.
Oh, Bob.
I don't know when I've been so hungry.
Bob, you really shouldn't have given me yours.
Oh, Bob.
I don't think I can eat when I'm full of greens right up to here.
Fill me up.
I got pot.
You naughty, naughty boy.
Bob, would you like to buy some information?
I've got it, Bob.
Oh, Bob.
So the church, what is the Church of the Subgenius?
Good question.
We're still trying to figure that out ourselves.
It's like, well, is this a joke or is it a real religion?
And our answer is, why not both?
We are probably one of the only serious religions that admits that we're completely full of
crap, and as such, possibly the only true and honest religion.
Doesn't that just figure?
You know, but we have the problem of Bobbies.
They're the ones that want to, they're so excited about it, they immediately want to
start telling all the inside jokes, and they haven't even gotten the outside joke yet.
And some of them, I mean, really need luck getting the, but basically, back in 1950,
1953, this, a man, this, that man, J.R., Bob Dobbs, and by the way, the J.R. doesn't
spell for, stand for anything.
It's on his birth certificate, even with quotes on the name Bob.
Bob was a mere salesman.
Well, not a mere salesman.
He was actually the greatest salesman the world has ever known.
And he was pretty, but he was a very young man, and he was just starting out on his road,
his path.
Religion had nothing to do with it.
He was just interested in money, like any sane person.
But he was tinkering with a TV, he was trying to build his own TV set.
And it was, he was in his basement, standing in a puddle, and suddenly, he had this, he was seized up
in the spirit.
He had this, this epiphany, which we call the divine immaculation of J.R. Bob Dobbs.
And on the, he was, he was an exorcist.
In this timeless moment, Bob was communicating with an alien intelligence calling itself Jehovah One.
You may have heard that name before.
This creature had been masquerading as God to many cultures for centuries.
And it revealed to Bob that throughout history there had been a conspiracy,
not the kind that kills Kennedy or gets Bush into office or hides UFOs and so forth, none of that stuff.
This was a conspiracy of plain, ordinary, garden-variety, normal human beings
who didn't even know they were part of a conspiracy, but just automatically, out of the fear of anything different,
had been keeping down and oppressing the slack of all the weirdos, the abnormals, the different people,
the disbelievers, and most importantly, those who will believe anything.
And that is when the Church of the Subgenius was formed.
Not on a solid rock like some of our more prosperous competitors,
but on a shifting sandy beach of pure hypocrisy.
Hypocrisy, friends, that is the beach our church is built on.
We have a million rules which can all be read.
We've got a million rules that we've read in our three books, but there's only one that really counts.
And since there's no one here but children, I'll say it in full vulgar English.
The one rule of the Church of the Subgenius is, fuck them if they can't take a joke.
So if you are feeling tender today, you should perhaps leave.
The Bob Show.
Brought to you by Bob.
Permanent, perfect, permanent, perfect.
And here he is, Bob.
Smile, stop, smile, stop.
You bet your life, you bet your life, there is heaven right here on Earth.
There is heaven right here on Earth.
Home of the dick jazz.
So come on, guys and gals.
Won't you come along with me?
Heaven on Earth.
No fussy, frizzy curls for this smart girl.
She has a Bob.
The perfect, permanent, permanent, tight, kinky with a Bob.
Because Bob is so easy, you can do it yourself.
Just regular pin curls and gentle Bob-ocean.
That's all you need.
A Bob, a Bob, new body.
Make your next permanent a Bob.
Bob-permanent.
Permanent.
Give yourself a Bob.
You'll go Bob, Bob, Bobbing along with your Bob.
My mom had untold me.
A worrisome thing, a worrisome thing.
Train it, train it, train it, train it.
My mom had untold me.
Whoa!
Never before a stick so red.
Redder than a fire engine.
See what stick can do for you.
The comf, the comf, long-lasting.
You'll just love Bob.
Be sure to listen again next week when Bob Perfect for Today again brings you The Bob Show from Bobby Wood.
This girl knows that Bob is the essence of romance.
Who tonight?
BanditNorAlPref.com is the essence of collagery as most of the subsequent collages will continue to demonstrate.
And just as Fernanda Nande-Lemur is the killer of Bob.
You'll have to get rid of him somehow for good.
But how?
Suddenly you found the answer.
It's as simple as kill Bob.
Kill Bob.
If he contacts you, don't try to help him.
He's dangerous.
Bob, Bob.
Hello?
Hello.
Did you hear the news on the radio?
They say I killed Bob.
Guess that's when I must have fallen asleep.
Bob's the only person I can kill.
I can kill Bob.
First thing I saw was Bob's body.
Then the gun beside me and I killed Bob's body.
Are you sure?
I'm afraid so, Bob.
I don't think the police will believe it.
But it's the truth.
I killed Bob's.
Yes, Bob.
You've got to answer it, Bob.
Hello?
Hello, Bob.
Oh, darling.
Listen to me, Bob.
She was in love with Bob.
Oh, no, Bob.
I was at the cock party.
I actually thought I could kill Bob.
Where did you go after the cock party last night?
Somebody set up a boot trap in your cabin.
It was a dark one, Bob.
Then it did just that.
I said I could kill Bob.
She meant that boot trap for you.
Don't look away, Bob.
Perhaps I did kill Bob.
Doesn't that make sense?
Well, yes.
Yes, it makes sense.
Yes, Bob.
Bob.
Listen, Bob.
I'm sorry about Gavin, but he's a little stressed.
Okay, but hell, he doesn't have to jump down my throat.
Does he have a family or relatives?
Yeah, I have a wife and a child.
Okay.
You know, the deceased, what's his name, Dobbs, does he have a family?
Yes, he does.
He has a family.
He has a wife and two young kids.
I think they're divorced.
His kids are divorced?
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Do you laugh at anything?
I mean, do you just laugh at anything?
A man has died.
She thinks this is funny.
No, no.
Are all you movie people like this?
Go, go, go.
Here's Bob One for A1 Slack.
Hi, this is Bob One.
Years ago, my grandfather, Abner, was a movie star.
Abner One, known for short because he was, invented the A1 Slack.
However, today's go-go action now generation man on campus and off wants a little more
out of life.
So, we added another leg to our super slim from fitting A1 Slack and came up with super
slim from fitting A1 Slacks.
A1 Slacks, the two-legged action slacks for the two-legged action man.
Thank you, Bob.
You're welcome.
And now, back to our movie.
Looks like we're gonna find more and we've clicked it.
And we've, uh...
Over the years, because of the church, this...
We went public in 19...
Actually, July...
January 1st, 1980, we printed the first sacred subgenius pamphlet and have been misunderstood
from that day on.
But you know, as they say, those who know don't say and those who say don't know.
So we should all just shut up.
But look here, we keep blabbering on and on.
Is it the drugs?
That's what the Cleveland Police Department...
The Cleveland Police Department might tell you.
In fact, a friend of ours sat in on a lecture to the Cleveland Police Department by a cult
expert who explained that Bob was a sign for Satan and drugs and stuff.
But obviously, friends, this is a religion.
Bob is here to replace the drugs.
Just looking at his face eats up more brain cells than most of your drugs.
If you're doing it right, like a real subgenius, if you can meditate upon the dots, every
little dot...
So many of you have done this, I know.
You just focus on that thing and after a while, you feel so much slack.
It's like heroin combined with PCP combined with DDT, LSD, and marijuana, as my father
puts it.
Um...
But what Bob's preaching is the joy of drugs, but not necessarily with the drugs, although
those can certainly enhance everything for the first ten minutes.
What Bob preaches is slack, friends.
And slack is so simple that I can't explain it, because it's different for each person.
Everybody has their own form of slack.
Some people get their slack from sitting on their ass watching TV and drinking beer.
There's nothing wrong with that.
The conspiracy of the normal people would love for that to be the only way you feel
you're getting slack.
We're here just as a pep talk, just a reminder that slack is whatever makes you feel like
you're doing what you were supposed to be doing.
I'm not saying you're not supposed to be doing what you're supposed to be doing.
I'm saying you're not supposed to be doing what you're supposed to be doing.
And that could be anything, you know, for our friend Dennis Murphy here.
Slack might be...
God, I can't even begin to imagine.
Maybe I should have picked a different...
You know, some people like bird watching, right?
Some people like pornography.
Some people like movies, you know?
Some people like people.
And just hanging out and talking.
And that's the thing.
Slack can be your purest form of slack.
And you can steal that slack while on the job, as you've learned around the coffee machine,
I'm sure.
As my good friend and speechwriter, you might say, Dr. Onan Kanabite put it, slack is the
oomph in comfortable.
That's it.
See, he has some stage...
He has...
Slack is the oomph in comfortable.
It says, oomph is accompanied by a gesture of vigor from the hips among adults or a pumped
elbow on US TV.
So, it could actually be slack is the oomph in uncomfortable.
Why do I keep wanting to say uncomfortable?
And as I said, slack can come when you throw good money after bad and bad money after Bob,
and that's fine.
That's why that sales table is out there.
This...
Oh, and we have a new book out, Intelligent Design for Dummies, our new publication.
So, be sure, if you think you've already bought all the accessories that go with Ken and Barbie,
there's some new accessories out there.
So...
So, you know Bob has many death days.
What's his birthday?
Bob has had so many lives, so many past lives that by chance, you know, one of almost
every day of the year is the birthday of a Bob.
Where is Bob now?
Is there somebody that we should be looking towards?
Where is Bob?
Is he mayhaps fishing on Lake Titicaca with G. Gordon Gordon?
Is he perhaps selling ice to an Eskimo somewhere in Alaska?
Is he perhaps selling hypocrisy to a subgenius in San Francisco?
But Bob is a traveling salesman and resides at no fixed address, unlike the god of the
Mormons, who is known to be on a planet circling the star Koloff, having sex with his many
spirit wives.
I'm talking about a guy named Smith on terrible pieces.
Although we don't know where Bob is.
Joseph Smith?
Yes.
He's a man of his word.
We know that Bob is coming.
And when I say that, I don't mean...
It has been said.
It's not like when Jesus is coming.
That usually means Jesus is on his way, is due to arrive.
When we say Bob is coming...
Like Santa Claus.
...Bob is literally...
That is what Bob is.
...is always coming.
And it's true.
I mean, but isn't he sometimes there, and then other times not?
Yeah.
When you come tonight, you will see Bob.
Well, otherwise...
I'll be looking...
...about an hour and a half.
...of course, in the next couple of hours.
You're not defeating him.
That's terrible, though.
I don't want to see him.
No, no, I'll be home by then.
And you can't move.
I know, but I just don't want to see him during that thing, you know.
You don't want to be everywhere.
But, I mean, don't you think you'd understand it all at that point?
Or maybe not.
I think that's when the shark bites you.
That's the part I thought about.
Because you're looking...
There are others swimming around, and a shark bites you, and if you're...
Because you're being distracted.
Yeah, and if you're together enough to understand that last big organism, then you're pretty
well set.
Instead of the music stopping, you're just sitting there, and you're just...
No, you shouldn't have...
...like some amateur show on a stupid radio theory.
No, it's now that Bob's coming your way.
He's coming your way.
He is.
Ah!
K-runch.
Bob!
I mean, no, I said, oh, god.
I mean, oh, Bob, I did.
Well, there are no atheists in foxholes.
I mean, I'm just a little bit...
Hey, Gav!
Cat!
Where the hell am I?
Dobbs just died.
Who's he?
He was your bright idea, wasn't he?
What do I know?
I'm just the writer.
Hey, you better get up there to the desert and do a rewrite before some other idiot gets
hold of it.
Who will play Bob in the movie of Bob?
Uh, oh, it's called In the Name of Bob.
...around Robert Downey Jr. or, uh...
Plan B Productions, I think, has slated to produce that.
Oh, yeah.
There's that Lithuanian actor.
Johnny Depp plays the young Ivan Stang, and Jim Carrey plays Philo Drummond.
I don't know who else has been cast yet, but Bob would be Andy Serkis, the guy that
played Gollum and Kong.
Right, Andy Serkis.
That would be good.
Absolutely.
So he would basically be a performance capture.
And Mike Myers is the voice of Cthulhu.
You can see we've been thinking.
Oh, yeah.
We've been thinking about that.
Very true.
Any love interests in the film?
Yeah, uh, the hero would be lonesome cowboy Dave, and I think it would be his, uh, he'd
be courting, uh, popular bull girl Daveena.
It's voiced by Lindsay Lohan.
Yeah.
In a bikini.
Just because.
And they're all penguins, right?
Yeah, I love them.
That's right.
They're all CGI penguins.
I'll take them in.
creates all the cute stuff on any TV set.
Tons of outlining everything you can wear.
Ooh, Mark.
That's funny.
What's glassy?
I wish I could help you.
essentially님이aciason.
Intro to a second half Vin Conservashing like to something that they should really
like.
It is the thinking studio.
I gotta get a employed.
one of my favorites. I never saw the remake.
What is this thing?
It stinks. That was a joke.
That was a joke. It stinks.
What is this thing? The second big feature
was a
possible name for a subgenius
feature movie. What was the name?
Second big feature.
I thought they were like a real band.
Second big feature? Yeah. But
Philo disabused me of that notion tonight. He said it was
just negative land.
The Swingin' Love. Wait, write that down.
That's a good name for a band.
Yeah. Not negative man.
Negative land.
Nobody expected what happened next.
Sensational career.
I'm Bob.
So why are so many people
flocking to Bob?
My message is that God is
a hope that he'll take us places
we've never dreamed of. It's hard to break
a dick to break a dick. You may be misleading
some people. So big. Being gay.
Gay and generous.
Leading them to some false god
or something like that. Deluding and
dumbing down.
You know.
Right up there
with gardening. Bam, there's a hit.
Great, great, great, great, great, great.
Wait, you're saying that. Great, great, great,
great, great, great. Oh my God.
Nothing. Make beautiful women
fall all over you. No doubt there.
Take steroids. Slack, slack, slack.
Cut, cut. I'm weak.
Now, a lot of people say
that some
terms that are in the
in the, as you
say, the bibliography on the
the
cyclopedia
it kind of uses
notions similar to, not the
same as, but in the same area as
Scientology or kind of a new agey
but in a fashion
that's almost Dada-esque.
Well, you know,
any religion or priesthood
is based
on impenetrable jargon.
Lawyers, doctors,
for instance. And we get a lot of
lawyers and doctors joining up
because they appreciate
that impenetrable
obfuscation
and invented words.
And words
that have been recombined.
So that when you're reading
this stuff, you feel like you're really part
of a secret army. And
the great thing is, you are.
It's not much of a
I mean, it's still a secret, so it's
not that much of an army. Not much of an army, yeah.
But, you know, it's kind of like
what they used to say about Fight Club.
Yeah, yeah. First rule, don't talk
about it. Don't talk about it, yeah. Of course, naturally
everybody talks about it.
Well, and, you know, the Hell's
Angels used to say, those who say don't
know, and those who know don't
say. And we should probably
just shut up. Well, yeah, and
then the show would go right to hell.
I like
one thing about it, and I always say, you know, this
has got to be the best deal
in organized,
shall we say, religion
or church, and that is
guaranteed salvation or
triple your money back. That's
right. Eternal salvation or triple your
money back. That's an offer.
That no other religion makes.
Well, you know, none of them do.
And I'm thinking, you know, now, there's one you can
grasp. That's the
kind of church I can get behind.
Right. It costs $30
to join, and that means
that if you, at the end of
time, find yourself in
the pit of hell,
we will gladly
refund your money. Not only
your $30, we'll give you $90.
Now, there is
a little book that Bob's
else down there called
Hell on Five Cents a Day,
which I think is $89.95.
Nowadays, yeah.
And a day lasts a long time.
In hell. Yeah, in normal hell.
Now, subgenius hell is kind of like
an endless party. Well, that's my
idea of a good idea. Right.
Yeah.
You know,
it's possible. Some people think the
subgenius thing is just a joke.
And, I mean, some people think...
Well, compared to what, though? Right, exactly.
You know, everybody's religion is
going to be a joke to somebody else.
One of them has to be true.
What if it was this one?
Who knows? Who knows? Crazier things
have happened.
Look at the Inquisition.
Look at the news. See?
Yeah.
You know,
I wouldn't be surprised at anything
that would happen, although
we are kind of
behind Scientology. We got started
a little bit later. That's all right.
All right. So did L. Ron Hubbard.
Hold on a second, if you will,
Reverend. We're going to take a quick break here.
Reverend Ivan Stang. He is the founder
of the Church of the Subgenius.
And talking more about the Church
of the Subgenius, for those of you out there who've never
heard of it, well, here's a chance to find
a religion you can really get behind.
Or next to, or in front of, or...
Something.
Vidae, vau, vidae, ev, nom, nevus, hier, fo, hier,
five, the number, it's nine, alf, eno, vut, mas,
eno, mis, sky, McBarber, you're listening to
the New England Radio 50-week KOA.
I just don't understand.
What's that horrible stench?
The laughing lemur.
Is there much communication
with otherworldly subgeni?
Well, there's,
of course, on other continents,
there are the Euro
subgeniuses. There's a Euro subgenius
Yazu.
You know,
oddly enough, as the dollar
becomes more
less...
less and less valuable compared to
other countries' money,
we get fewer memberships
and ordainments here in the U.S.,
but we're making a mint
off of, all of a sudden, in Euros.
People in Europe are
joining up, and Australia,
all the English-speaking world.
But we're also
starting to hear from Russians, and
oddly enough, a lot of
Nigerians keep offering us
huge fortunes.
As long as you give them
your...
bank account number.
So, um, yeah, it's
it's definitely one of the
world's fastest growing religions.
But it's not a snack religion.
It's strange, but true.
Well, it is a sack religion.
No, a snack.
Oh, I'm sure it's a snack religion.
Okay, very good.
We push Bob as a short-duration personal
savior. We don't expect you to
cling to it forever. It's...
We don't want you to use Bob as a crutch.
Rather, we want...
to let...
You should let Bob use you as a crutch.
You are Bob's crutch.
I'm interested in your information.
I'd like to subscribe to the newsletter.
Wait, I already do.
You go to subgenius.com and
click on the news button.
It's actually all very logical.
There used to be a hard copy, that
famous publication,
The Stark Fist of Removal.
But in the cyber age, it
doesn't come out very often. We allow special members,
to print out the online version.
Well, you know, and...
and... and...
and... Dobbs made most of his important deals
in strange places when he first started out.
Like a Waffle House in Haightville, Georgia.
I thought it was Ellicott City, Maryland.
It was the Stuckeys in... in Texas.
Well, there were several.
See, Stang has to be...
He knows all this stuff.
Right.
Where... where was it?
He fell asleep.
Stang.
Um...
I think... I think Stang's...
He's checking his back machine.
He's suffering the wounds of Cripes.
Mm-mm-mm.
Hey, you know, I got a joke.
What's the... what's the difference between
Jesus Christ and a picture of Jesus Christ?
Are you guys talking about me?
No.
We were saying we're, uh...
I was actually, uh...
I'm in the process of flipping a...
a tape, so, uh...
Are we supposed to be funny now?
No, I don't think so.
No, we wanted to know the connection between
the Raelians, on the one hand,
Dr. Sinister's show,
and Bob's hardest sell, not anything to do with primate arrest.
So what is... what's the difference between, uh...
What's the difference between Jesus and a picture of him, I don't know.
Oh, yeah, that was it.
Yeah.
What's the difference between Jesus Christ and a picture of Jesus Christ?
You only need one nail to hang up the picture.
Oh!
Hey, what's... what's the difference between Jesus Christ and a picture of Jesus Christ?
The picture is real.
Oh!
Keep going.
Oh.
But Bob is real.
Bob is real.
You should be careful, you know.
You don't want to offend the Arabs, saying Bob is real.
Bob is real, and there was a waitress in, uh,
Hapeville, Georgia, who...
I can't say this stuff on the air.
Sure you can.
Well, can you?
No, I can't.
Um, it... it... it... it...
Somebody found a Dobbs head in a pancake?
No, no, no, no, no.
It's much more complicated than that.
Um, when I met her, I was... it was about 3 o'clock in the morning, and, yeah, she was
a... she was a Waffle House waitress, which, you know, is pretty normal.
And, uh, and she started telling me... I had on a Dobbs shirt, and she said,
I've seen him.
He was here with these weird guys.
And she tells me this long story, and I can't really tell it on the air, to...
not giving... I don't want to give away too many secrets.
What, like the guys weren't really guys?
They were like aliens, or something?
You know, what's... what's the difference?
Yeah, you're on a racetrack.
But she had met Bob.
Just that she had met Bob?
Yep.
Oh.
She had served Bob a cup of coffee.
That's not unusual.
Uh, Bob often has been where a subgenius arrives, just before the subgenius got there.
You hear that all the time.
I actually have seen him before.
Subgeniuses are always arriving just as Bob has just... has left.
I've... I've seen him a couple times, actually.
Well, people wonder if he's a memory or a premonition, because the... it's so fleeting,
and... and they're just aware of something having happened.
I've seen him driving away twice.
I've been passed by Bob on the highway at least twice.
Actually, I saw him get thrown out of a coffee shop, actually, because...
Really?
Because he wouldn't put his pipe out, you know, and they... they threw him out, and...
He can't.
That pipe can't go out.
Exactly.
And I... I... but I figured I'd just leave it, you know, hands off, you know.
And, uh, I don't know what exactly it was, but the people in there got really upset about something.
They forcibly threw him out, like literally threw him out, and right as soon as he threw him out,
a big bus came by, and...
A bus came by, and hit him right as they threw him out there, and then he was gone.
You see, that's...
And all I saw left behind was like... there was like some, uh, like a smoldering of the, uh, of like a broken pipe there.
But then again, you know, next week I saw Bob again, you know, he was fine.
Yeah, well, you know, it's funny, the reason...
Sure, he'll be fine.
...the Waltham House waitress was asking about the shirt I had on is that Bob never paid his bill.
Ooh.
Why is it always the rich ones?
That was...
I'm trying to tell you, you know, it really was Bob.
Why is it always the rich ones?
Well, if you tell me, it was like the sec... it was like the first night they were open at this particular location.
So this had to have been back in like 58 or 60.
And she still remembered the guy, because he stiffed her.
You know, it...
Well, you always remember the person who stiffed you.
Yeah, the person who first stiffed you.
Especially if they look like that, you know, and they're grinning while they're doing it.
Your first night... your first night getting stiffed. Yeah, we always remember that.
Has anybody delivered a pizza to Bob and, you know, 13-cent tip?
Get the idea?
Wow, a whole 13 cents?
That's pretty good.
Bob doesn't tip to drivers either. That's happened.
I know a driver who delivered to him, and Bob doesn't tip.
Bob says, let me give you a tip. Don't get screwed or something really dumb and witty like that.
Yeah, he grabs the...
It's the same thing to every pizza delivery guy.
Yeah.
My dad does that too.
Do you know how a leper leaves a tip for a hooker?
Oh.
We can stop there.
Man.
That was a quick one.
That was quick.
It's old.
Yeah.
Old like me.
You know, and when I get home, I'll chop up another three shows out of this one real fast and take off for Texas.
It's in Stang County where we go every December to help...
...to help oversee construction on the compound.
We're building a big cult compound in Stang County, Texas.
You don't want to go down by Stang County, son.
It's near Dead Branch Pass.
Actually, in Stang County has a nuclear power plant that serves Dallas.
It has a really big tax base. We have a lot of tax money because of that.
And my family is very involved in city politics, county politics, and so forth.
So we've been able to go forward on construction of this underground bunker.
It started as a missile, an abandoned missile silo bunker.
Even better.
There are a lot of those in Texas.
They've done the digging for you.
Yeah, that's right.
I saw something a while back about people living in these, in the bunkers, owning them, right?
Yeah.
In their home.
We did that, and we also have extensive tunneling going on.
To the mall.
Luckily, there's uranium, raw uranium on the land of Stang.
Brilliant.
And goats.
Like every good compound.
Why goats, you may ask?
Well, because there was a drought.
Why a goat?
And the cows, there wasn't enough grass for the cows or the zombies.
Goats in Jehovah.
Yeah.
But the goats, the goats are happy.
We actually have a cult compound in Texas with goats.
Slightly radioactive goats.
Yeah, machine gun, you know, encampments.
The horns glow.
It's a terrible thing.
So we, most of the time, the other members of the Stang clan run the ranch.
I just go down there every now and then to oversee it.
The Stang stomping ground.
The killing hound.
Stang likes to go down there to supervise the killing.
We're going to build a big TV studio there and a crystal cathedral.
And a drive-through crystal cathedral so that, and a creation.
Drive-through.
Drive-by.
And we're going to have a special museum about the way evolution really worked, where
subgeniuses really came from.
Where they'll be displayed.
Audio animatronic yeti.
Yeah.
Arrival of the exes.
The creation of the humans by the yetis and so forth.
That's actually my favorite part.
We have the audio animatronic Stang and Grover and the guys talking and their arms kind of
moving.
Are you familiar with the creation of the humanoids movie?
Yes.
Yeah.
Most certainly.
That's a great film.
The mandatory subgenius movie.
Why doesn't he listen to you?
What's his name?
Gavin.
Right.
Garvin.
I can never remember his name.
So why doesn't he listen to you, huh?
Because I'm a human.
I tend to rattle his cage.
He doesn't like it.
So was it like this before the actor?
What was his name?
The one who died?
Dobbs.
Yeah, Hobbs.
What was going on then, huh?
Anarchy.
Dobbs was rewriting the script.
He'd call script conferences every morning before shooting.
It made everyone crazy.
Well, you already had a script.
What was the problem, huh?
He was an actor.
What can I tell you?
He wasn't even good at it, you know?
He was the look at me scratch my balls school of acting.
Oh, such assholes.
I asked this guy, Dobbs.
I asked him last week.
I said, why are you doing this?
What did he say?
He said it was a good idea.
It was a generational thing.
And what's that mean, huh?
Beats the hell out of me.
Little puke.
Come on!
You couldn't do anything to stop it?
What could I do?
Gavin had no control.
He was terrified.
Couldn't make decisions about anything, even about breakfast.
It could have helped me, you know?
Works.
Dobbs, Dobbs, Dobbs, Dobbs.
Colts, Colts.
Just out of time.
Dobbs, Dobbs, Dobbs, Dobbs, went off.
The incredible last wrong committed.
I'm not going to do this again.
Committed.
Now you do know, Colt.
You know, with ADHD and, you know, just kind of, you know, you know, just kind of, you
know, you know, uh, you know, um.
You know, uh, put your arm around these young men.
Watch it.
You know, but Colt, I, I, it's my Colt.
I, uh, you know, you know, Secret Life on the Internet Colt.
It, uh, it, well.
Doody, doody.
Uh, uh.
It doesn't make any sense, you know.
Action.
And so we were, you know, coming.
You know, it's, you know, you know.
Hmm, hmm.
So we got off, you know.
I'm really deeply involved in girls and boys and girls today.
Mm-hmm.
In a cult.
Perfect.
Gone down the wrong road, but beautiful.
Crazy things get said.
Dobbs, Dobbs, Dobbs, Dobbs.
Back again.
We're up right against the top of the hour and, of course, a news update.
But want to, uh, get some final details from our, our, our good guest, the Reverend Ivan
Stang.
He's, uh, uh, the, the, uh, head, head, headmaster, I guess.
And.
No, uh, my, my, uh, title is Sacred Scribe.
Cool.
All right.
Sacred Scribe number 273.
Uh, Bob Dobbs is the living avatar of Slack.
Wow.
That's his official title.
Not to be confused with the other Dobbs down the road from us.
Um, uh, for those who wish to find out more and, or get your books and your, and your
DVD and, and also, by the way, that, that hell on five cents a day kind of thing.
Um, how does one do this?
If you're on the internet, the simplest thing would be to look at subgenius.com.
Mm-hmm.
And I'll, uh, uh, subgenius does not have an O.
I have to say that because there are a lot of subgeniuses out there.
It's S-U-B-G-E-N-I-U-S.com.
All right.
Very good indeed.
And Reverend Stang, I'm going to, by the way, I'm going to put you on hold.
My producer, Steve, needs to speak with you, but, uh, I want to thank you so much.
It's been a lot of fun.
Thank you very much.
I'm just, I'm a little concerned that I'm going to have those Monkees songs stuck in
my head for the next three days.
An ear bug is the worst, isn't it?
Yeah.
Thank you very much.
Indeed.
And thank you for being here.
Thank you very much.
Okay.
And please stay there, Reverend, but thanks very much indeed.
Praise Rick.
And praise, praise Ivan.
Anyway, we're going to take it up to the news.
From PR News in Washington, I'm involved in a prostitution ring.
President Bush says the U.S. will help Poland modernize its childhood obesity.
Mr. Bush says health officials are overweight.
I'm optimistic that we'll be able to live in deprivation and fear.
Health officials say children and teenagers are not immune from congressional subpoenas
as claimed by the Bush administration.
The president also said today that this is PR News in Washington.
A thanks to Leimur for that and PR News and laughing.
This has been Hour of Slight Number 1143 with Dr. Hal Pasling, Evidence, Philo Drummond,
John Hell, Mongoloid, and K. Robin San Francisco, Dr. Sinister and Princess Pisces, and Lonesome
Cowboy Dave on WCSB Cleveland, and Governor Ratnar and No Money Mark.
The movie soundtrack that is so weird is from Slipstream and the background music is Bonobo's
Convergence from Last X Day and Next X Day.
And now, from Norell, this message.
For the safety of your smile, see your dentist twice a day.
The Bob Show starring Bob and his guest star, Lone Throat.
Bob's a good guy.
He's a good guy.
How do you do, ladies and gentlemen?
This is Bob.
I was so glad to be back I went down to the blood bank and gave a pint of blood.
WC Fields was there too.
He donated a fifth.
Trip the Light, fantastic.
Have you tried going a little buggy with a girl and a horse with a horse?
The horse wants to go out for a little buggy.
Get a horse.
Black or brown or gray?
What a horse
Robert, quit putting it in your pipe
Jugs
I thought you used your nose for that
You talk like I was a freak
I was a freak, freak, freak
Father, I'm down here with a nice young man
Get a horse
Hello
Wrong number
Uh-oh
Hello
Remove that film
Quickly, easily, safely
No one, no one
Get a tube, get a tube
Ladies and gentlemen
You really like the girls, don't you?
Yes, Bob, I do
Now, ladies and gentlemen
I'd like to introduce one of the reals of genius
Thank you very much
I presume you're Bob
of genius
I'm becoming known as the Bob of this generation
Bob, magic Bob
I know, Bob
Why do I stand here reading this tripe
when I can get a good job at Lockheed?
I'm Bob
Sit down, Bob
I'll read your future
I can tell you who's going to be in the White House
I do a lot of deep thinking
Get loaded
So, uh, someone died?
Yeah
Yeah, Dobbs
You wrote the part of Ray for an African-American, right?
I did?
Yeah, man
What's wrong with you?
Are you on drugs?
No, no, I'm not on drugs
Ray, the character that Dobbs was playing, was black
Dobbs wasn't a black actor, man
He was white, like her
Oh, my God
Why did you kill me off feelings?
Barbara
I was just a script supervisor
That's all I was
It's Bob
Now you have no control over me
Continuity
Nothing makes sense anymore
It's so unfair
It's just so unfair
So unfair
Go, go
Mommy
In dealing with Supernatural, uh, uh, Ray
Reanimated mummies
Played the old age home
Just like DJs at Firecat Radio, ladies and gentlemen
One day they are gonna mummify us
And it will be an honor
Your encrusted sarcophagus
Rich with jewels and hieroglyphs
Will be lowered into your own personal vault
And sealed by the sands of time
I want to be frozen in loose sight like Bob did
Bob, Bob is, uh, one of the Bobs, Bob is the best
in lucite.
It could be frozen in the ice.
Which we lost.
Lost? Where did it go?
Well, I mean, we lost ownership of it.
But that's where Bob is?
One of the Bobs?
The one that Puzzling Evidence shot.
Damn you.
But he's like...
It was a real flesh and blood Bob, that Bob.
Wow.
The scary Bob.
When I introduced people to that Bob,
they would do a great big double take.
The last thing you expect
is actually to be introduced to Bob.
A small Bob.
But then came that terrible day,
the Victoria Theatre Show,
the anniversary of the beheading
of Louis XVI and Marie Antoinette,
the assassination of Bob.
Yeah, we all remember where we were that day, don't we?
I know where I was.
And it's on videotape,
and I can prove it.
So, we have one Bob buried in Dallas.
Is that right?
Well, uh, you go back over the Hinckley Commission hearings,
the entire official answer was sort of cobbled together
out of variant strains of rumor and innuendo.
Where's the director?
Huh.
Ah!
Let's get him!
John Woodhead!
Oh!
Come on!
Cut! Cut! Cut!
Cut!
Hey, Harvey!
Mr. Oh, I didn't know you were...
It's his money, isn't it?
Oh, well, I'm sorry, but you got it.
You got it.
Let's shot this.
Hot shot!
What are you talking about?
What are you doing?
I gotta get out.
I've gotta get out of here.
Stop.
What are you doing?
Fuck.
I've gotta get back.
It's 4 o'clock.
My time's up.
I've gotta go.
Please stop.
My time's up.
I've gotta get back.
I'm almost home.
I'm here to help.
Please stop.
We're not gonna hurt him.
What's wrong?
He's on some kind of medication.
Hey!
Wait, wait!
Oh, God!
Please!
What's that, dear?
Oh, yes.
I heard.
Poor old Felix.
Cut!
That's lunch, everyone!
That's it.
Good.
Now I will count three.
And at the count of three, you will wake up and...
remember nothing.
One, two, three.
Ten thousand dollars.
What do you know?
Yes.
Beautiful, isn't it?
Ah, this castle is filled with rare old treasures.
Feel free to browse, my friend.
Thank you very much.
A pleasant good evening to you.
Thank you.
Sp