Well, that's a secret party that's a secret party.
You want to blow your eardrums out.
Old subgenius guys.
Yeah, the people that started the thing.
Who wants to talk to them?
Who are the people that started the subgenius church?
Anyways, I need a doctor.
I think we have one in the audience.
Bob Dobbs himself has just entered the auditorium.
Praise Bob, stand up everyone.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh my God, something has happened at the theater.
In the theater.
In the motorcade.
Something has happened in the motorcade.
Someone has just shot J.R. Bob Dobbs.
He's down on the ground.
And there he is.
The preachers are surrounding him.
People are screaming.
There's that horrible killer.
Dr. Howell has found his pipe.
Dr. Howell's not here tonight.
The pipe is broken.
But we do have in our studio here.
Could this be the end of J.R. Bob Dobbs himself?
Is it live or is it minorex?
What evil could possibly happen?
I think that's Reverend Stang.
How could that be?
Where?
That's Reverend Stang.
Here on the Puzzling Evidence Show.
Live.
Or something like it.
Where is Dr. Howell?
Actually, that's a very sophisticated tape manipulation
by our host, Puzzling Evidence.
He'll make it sound as if Reverend Stang is actually live in the studio tonight.
It was a skillful manipulation of tape.
Editing.
With real tape.
Real-to-real tape.
The splices are an inch thick in some places.
It's amazing how we can...
My first splices were...
Yeah, Scotch tape and my mom's sewing scissors.
Yeah.
On quarter inch tape.
And every time it would hit the tape head, you'd hear a big...
Yeah, you'd see the...
Back when I was a kid, we had to use masking tape for recording.
I remember...
I remember when we had to use a match head.
We had to get more than one track on that mono box.
Yeah.
We just...
We just stick a match stick...
Stick a wire to that dang duct tape in this giant recorder machine
and it would pull that tape through.
It was hard because it was sticky.
It was sticky.
But the sticky was where the recording took.
Yeah, well, it was...
It was very fuzzy and hissy sound.
I had some tape at...
Like this recording of yours truly, Reverend.
I've been Stang.
I knew when I was using it...
I knew when I was using the tape that it was already missing its media.
The hour of slack.
Oh, wait.
Oh, no.
There's copyrighted music in the background.
This is not...
We can't use that.
No.
That's...
Okay, now you can do it.
Just...
Oh, wait.
From problem...
Why do I give it to my cough and cold and stuffed up nose?
Oh, wait a minute.
Do you somehow thought this was the call-in health show?
Send $30 to...
Oh, that's right.
It's a public station.
You thought this was the call-in health show?
That we were going to give you advice on your sniffles and...
We used to.
Your need for rhinoplasty.
We used to before we became hateful and mean.
We used to tell people how to...
We give people advice and tell them how to live.
We tell them their past lives.
Give me some advice, then.
Okay, well, good advice.
Boy, we're short and low and so high.
We've got a lot of...
Do you have any use for bad advice?
Like, go mountain climbing all by yourself.
Okay, get ready.
Here's the fanfare music leading up to the fantastic advice.
Do I take medicine?
It's not quite here yet.
When you encounter a mediocre advice...
It's just mediocre advice.
...on the trail.
Yeah.
Crouch down like his prey and shiver.
This is just mediocre advice at this point.
We're getting closer to the excellent advice.
No, this is actually really bad advice.
Oh, this is bad advice.
I'm working on bad advice, yes.
When you...
So when you encounter the lion on the trail, you should, like, make faces at him and go...
That's what you should do, actually.
Shoot the finger at him.
The bad advice is to cower and shiver.
Or to flee.
Because that's what his prey does.
What should you do is roll over and expose your...
What his prey doesn't do is go...
You should roll over and expose your belly.
Oh, that's so cute.
Okay, now put that away.
I wish I could do that.
Better find out if he's friendly first.
The show wants to help this individual, but the show's help is so...
It's such short supply right now.
We can't really help...
We looked in the help bucket and it was completely empty.
And we're not really here.
No, this is a tape.
A special sneaky tape made by Cousin Evans.
So thanks to the studios at WCSB Cleveland, we're able to seem to be together.
We're channeling Dr. Gene Scott on Line 3.
How realistic.
Anyone ever really anywhere, anyhow?
Princess Wee is here.
Princess Wee should be joining us.
Well, she's been photographing.
But she is doing a job.
She's been photographing.
She's photographing.
Manufacturing the tools.
My very favorite picture of you and me, Dr. Drummond, was taken in here, but our places
were switched.
That was over there?
And you were listening to the microphone.
You had your ear to the microphone and you were talking in your headphone.
It looks perfectly natural.
I do that sometimes.
It's in the last subgenius.
It's in the third subgenius.
I do that sometimes.
I shouldn't say the last one.
The most recent.
There will never be a last subgenius.
The most recent subgenius.
Are you talking about the third subgenius empire, 1878 to 1892?
No, no, no.
I'm talking about the recent.
Oh, okay.
I could take my colorful, my colorfully quaint hat off, I guess.
No, those were the early subgenius tablets.
I've got a different hat for you.
Those days.
You could, if you, you didn't have to take the whole subgenius tablet.
It had all of our laws on it, but you didn't have to take the whole tablet.
You could just take a half.
Really?
Just even a nibble?
And then if you start to come on later.
Just a nibble off the end.
If you're not coming on in about an hour, you take the other half.
Isn't that right?
Something like that?
Right.
You don't have to eat the whole subgenius book of knowledge in one humongous hit, as
the kids call it these days.
They so humorously refer to it as a hit.
Give me a hit of that subgenius.
How can we compete with Jenkham?
You know, how can the church of the subgenius?
We don't even try.
I wonder if you'd put on this hat for me.
We'd like to go into.
Good Lord.
Someone has skinned.
Not only has an overman appeared on the planet Earth, but someone has skinned it.
Where did you find it?
Or maybe not.
How did you have it?
There's a dead overman skin.
Did I leave this somewhere?
I don't know.
What is it?
You picked it up the other day.
It's an overman.
It's a man's shrunken head.
But I thought here's a time when the primitive overman drops.
Half his brain will have to leave the show.
Good Lord.
Dr. Drummond, like Ed Gein, has spliced the skin of another overman.
And there aren't even supposed to be any other overman.
So it's like an overman wearing an overman mask.
It's hard.
It's a tough bit.
I can see where it's really.
They do have rubbery skin.
It looks amazing.
Really great.
The rubbery skin of the overman is impenetrable by normal.
Oh, I see.
Can you hear overman?
Sure, I can hear.
Can you hear me?
What?
No.
I can't hear me.
And it repels kisses.
I can't hear you.
Yes, that was the sad thing.
I can hear me.
What was sad?
This show is so better than a kiss in overman.
Oh, yeah.
His rubbery lip skin repels a kiss.
And his huge, bulging, chrome bone.
Ew, look what he's doing.
There you go.
He was heading for trouble.
The overman was.
You're in trouble.
Jumping off the head.
Overman, no!
Yep.
You're in trouble.
He was nogging, nog, nog, nogging at heaven's door with that giant head.
Yeah, that's what he does.
Actually, I like giant heads.
Although, I must say, Dr. Evidence, I was offended as I gazed around.
The lounge of the studio and discovered that there was not a Dobbs head pinned anywhere,
but one of those Andre the Giant heads.
And there's some other head over there pinned up on the wall.
Oh, no.
You're right.
But I wouldn't.
That Elvis head.
There was a single Dobbs head.
This is not the KPFA I knew where there was a Dobbs head branded on the skin of every
DJ back in the day.
That was the day, by the way.
Oh, the day.
Yeah.
Not every other day that the kids are talking about these damn kids.
Yes, friends, welcome to another episode of the Hour of Slack.
Hopefully, one that won't need to be edited greatly, except to reverse the phone numbers.
Except when they say, X day.
What do you think of my knee?
We do.
Don't obey any of the phone number suggestions by Mr. Reverso Mouth.
Yeah, my knee, too.
I know.
My knee, three.
So now, you know, it's just like the old days.
When I first came to see you guys, it's just cameras everywhere, only we were in Dealey
Plaza.
Yeah, the big difference is I don't have one of the cameras.
Back then, the cameras were bigger and they were separated.
They were actually in different devices than the recorder and the phone and everything.
UFOs can notice also that his head just changed again.
They actually had a different device for every little function.
Can you believe that?
I was the guy that had to sync the sound to the camera.
I was the guy that had to sync the sound and the picture up.
Of what?
And before, well, all that duct tape that we recorded everything on.
He had one roll of duct tape for a picture and a roll of masking tape.
And then we just used the same roll over and over again.
We just kept recording other things on top of it.
Yeah, you couldn't make a copy of any of it.
You could make a movie and then show it once.
And then it would lose its stick.
The Return of Negi.
16.
I think that tape was on like, we'd use this duct tape probably 40, 45 times by then.
Man, that sucks, but you guys have probably a tape of that.
A tape?
We can't hear you unless you yell.
Oh, can you hear me?
No, you have to get into a microphone.
We're on the radio.
Oh, well, I can hear her.
Fairly close to your ear.
848-445-DETAILS.
Speak to the other man, Ivan Stang, Cousin Emmett, and the Queen of UFOs.
Right here.
For serious.
Forever.
That's why we play that pink music.
There we go.
It's all better now.
This sounds like old show music background.
Oh, ew.
I've been so busy on the secret project that I have had to run reruns for our Slack for
the last couple of months.
Thank you, everybody.
Thank you.
We've got more great reruns.
Yes.
I was going to say, you know how lucky we are.
Shows were good back then.
No, really.
Settle down.
All of us are going to have reruns to go back to.
Settle down out there.
I mean, we have big audio banks.
Somebody, young people now, comment on that to me.
Okay.
If they don't settle down, we're going to get the water cannons out.
They assume I've been everywhere in the shop ever.
We'll hold them down.
And people see me at events that I'm not at because oh yeah, I saw him.
He was shooting that.
You're controlling yourself.
He was there shooting that.
So that's, I just thought I'd want to share that with you.
And also the other thing is, I have a three-quarter inch bait, a pneumatic machine next to my chair at home.
I've got one.
He's got one that's like he can...
If you've got any of those, I have those tapes.
Yes, I have those tapes.
And they're probably falling apart.
So they might be, they're in the giant archive basement.
You should think about...
Your third level down at the slacker mansion.
It's all there.
You should think about maybe using that pneumatic machine to...
Will that audience shut up?
Good Lord, how much butt kissing can they do?
Bobby, he says.
Just wave your arm like a cutoff signal.
Just wave your arm like a cutoff.
Like a cutoff signal in a band.
Okay.
Do it, do it.
Jesus.
There you go.
They're very responsive.
This is like land that chopper in front of me.
Oh, yeah.
You can't just...
You have to give the right signal.
We got here by helicopter.
Helicopter.
Yeah.
By heliopter.
No, no.
Actually, we rode helicopters this time.
All the way.
Hip-hopping.
Because it's a big project we're working on.
A big mysterious project.
Yeah, tell us about the mysterious secret project.
Well, yeah, right.
What?
And unveil those mysteries?
The inter-inter-mysteries?
No, no.
You're supposed to lie about it.
You know, like it's interesting.
Oh, what?
Unveil the mysteries.
We...
Oh, don't do that.
Don't.
Unveil the mysteries.
The mysteries.
The mysteries will become embarrassed and shy.
Well, we used to joke about...
Get big goose pimples on it.
Yeah.
We joked about encoding the book of the subgenius into the DNA of cockroaches.
And then we would joke how they'd evolve so fast that after a while it would say,
Praise Bill.
Oh, yeah.
Praise something.
Do you tell the cockroaches they don't dream in Christ?
Praise Bill.
Well, as it turns out, the cockroaches don't have a complex enough DNA to use.
We have to use a higher...
Yeah, that's when we decided, well, let's just do it in like six-point type instead.
Really?
No.
Then the cockroaches are right over here.
Let's do it in three-point type.
I can't read our old stuff.
Yeah.
Wasn't that a great idea?
I have to have a magnifying glass to read our old stuff.
It should be dense enough that it evades scrutiny by its sheer density.
Well, the idea was that you had the word of Bob in your pocket, but the conspiracy made
us print these books large size.
We wanted them more like...
Like a little Bible.
A little miniature Bible.
Yeah, like the Chairman Mao's little salad book.
Yeah.
They cost a lot to do that.
Osama Bin Laden's little yellow book.
Yeah.
What?
Well, that's a collection.
Code yellow book by...
Yeah, they're cool, man.
Well, those days were the internet.
You can piece together your own book from your greatest...
Have you ever read Muammar Gaddafi's Green Book?
No.
No, I haven't.
I really want to.
It's amazing.
I've been wanting to for a while.
He's still on the bestseller list.
He's a genius.
About half of it is the best, most honest, blunt description of the conspiracy I've ever
seen.
And the other half is totally out there kooking.
So it's perfect.
Yeah.
It's like the...
Is it really green?
Muammar Gaddafi's little green book.
That's not what it's called.
But it's green because...
Called My Life or something.
Yeah.
My Life by Mo.
By Mo.
Mo's Life.
Yeah.
Muammer.
Muammar.
I've still got that Gaddafi head that Palmer Freedy's donated.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
The Muammar Gaddafi football head.
Right, right.
The football head.
Remember, it's shaped more like that.
I was so insistent in Gage.
We could kick it around.
What's that game you guys play here in America?
Hand Egg?
Here, Hand Egg.
They used a hand to throw an egg-shaped thing.
And Doc Frump was explaining that game.
And the men all wear gladiator uniforms.
They kick it, too.
Yeah, but it's Doc Frump.
That's wrestling.
Oh, they do?
They kick it.
And hand it.
I've got...
They hand it to one another.
They kick it and they throw it.
It's a strange thing.
They're always trying to get rid of it.
There's a lot like Sock Car in England and the other...
But they try to get rid of it.
They're always trying to get it, like put it in this thing at the end.
And then when they get rid of it, that makes it better for the other guy.
I have to admit that since I've thrown myself so deeply into deciphering the Dobbsian manuscripts,
I haven't been keeping up on plain ordinary...
Modern day conventions, right?
Yeah.
These expressions of modernity.
I see kids staring at these screens and they're squeezing things with their hands.
Fiddling with their hands.
Their little hands are going...
Yeah.
And there's a lot of that that I find...
Yeah, they're...
Look, those are electronic...
They're made out of electronics, I understand.
What?
Someone's invented a fancy new electronic gadget?
It's an electric...
No way!
It runs on batteries.
Copyright 1999, Fernando Nandini-Murr.
Somebody invented something new?
He doesn't get quoted much because he never said very much.
Okay, we're going down into the subgenius archives here.
Oh, my God.
You can see Fernando Nandini-Murr is...
The archive, just alone for him, fills his entire ancient Swiss bunker.
Posting, I notice your breath has become...
Your breath has become...
Slightly labored.
Is this a tough climb for you?
Yeah, you know, it's more the atmosphere down...
Oh, man, we're on...
He can talk while he breathes.
The atmosphere down here is so fed.
Well, he's very advanced.
I wish I could talk while I breathe.
He's very advanced.
Hey, pass the feta cheese.
Oh, here we go.
Okay.
Here we go.
It's not real cheese, man.
You should have been here, like, last week.
We had this lady caller that was just stuffing us full...
It was puzzling evidence.
Ex-wife was calling us.
And she was filling us full of all this...
She's just bringing the memory home.
...up, the one-week-old memory.
Home food.
I feel like I'm just going to punch her out.
Does it make you feel like you...
I love you, and would you...
The transmission's slipping on the fourth gear.
If you can fix that, make me dinner, and bring me a beer...
Man, I would just knock the crap out of her if I were you.
She ought to be horse-whipped.
She's fine with all that, you know.
That's her breathing in the background.
You know how big she would be if that was her breathing?
She's wearing a diving suit.
I don't even know who you're really talking about.
But I'm not really here.
You're just a tape.
We're going to clean your mind.
You're just a fancy tape.
You did not hear this.
I'm not.
Fancy mixtape.
The best part...
Intricately spliced together from ancient tapes.
So I go see Avatar, right?
Yeah.
And, you know, I get there a little bit late and get in the front row, kind of over to the left.
Because I went there a couple of times to see big 3D technology, right?
And I sit down.
And a whole bunch of young men sit down next to me.
They're still talking and doing the whole cell phone thing.
And then the movie starts.
Everybody gets quiet.
The movie's going along.
And remember when Cigarette Lady from, you know, the...
Trinidad?
There was a Cigarette Lady.
Cigarette Lady?
Yeah, she's Cigarette Lady in real life, but not in...
Ripley.
You know, the Ripley lady.
Oh.
Dies.
Oh, Cigarette Lady.
The kid next to me.
Yeah, he's probably like 17.
Screams out her name at full volume.
In the silent theater.
It was just amazing.
You know, it was like...
He was so in there.
He just went...
Whatever.
Did he scream out her character name?
Yeah.
Yeah, staring at the screen.
He was so into the movie.
And I'm thinking...
You're never going to live that character.
Your friends are never going to let you...
Actually, he was so into it.
He had to scream her name because it was so sad.
Yeah.
I thought it was amazing.
But he called her Ripley.
No, he called her whatever her name was in the movie.
You know, Georgette or whatever.
He said...
It's the sad part.
She's dying.
A tree of knowledge.
She was so good in Alien.
You know, that whole Avatar thing was really sort of a metaphor for Church of the Subgenius.
Isn't everything?
I saw that.
The Na'vi.
Turn that word around.
Spell it.
What does that spell backwards?
Ivan.
There you go.
Ivan, there it is.
Case closed.
And that other one that you turn it around backwards, it spells Drummond.
Yeah.
Yeah, the play.
That was the Unobtainium.
You turn it around.
It's inside and out.
Inside and...
And sideways backwards.
Yeah.
And it spells Drummond.
Perfect.
And crap story backwards.
So let's go...
Let's slack worry.
Right, right.
Let's go through the movie now.
Yeah, we could go through the movie.
Starting with the...
Piece by piece.
All right.
Where do you start?
I don't even remember when you started that thing.
All I remember are the sequences, like the going and getting your dragon.
Yeah, that's good.
That's nice.
I'd do that.
And then...
Oh, they do that in every movie now.
Climbing up the little dirt balls of the planet was amazing.
Or climbing up the flying dirt balls was a lot of fun.
Yeah.
In 3D.
The 3D...
The difference...
They have a bunch of different 3D systems.
And I went to see the...
There they go.
Like the best one.
They just fell into the water.
It's like a big volume space.
And they keep bringing focus in and out on the things they want your eye to go to.
Well...
I'm calling my mind.
That's one reason that ultimately gives you a headache.
It's because the camera is trying to focus where your eye goes to.
I have trouble watching the 3D movies really focus on a real thing.
My eyes just don't...
Can't...
I can't get used to the glasses on my...
On top of my glasses.
I'm washing my mind with radio water.
Right.
Oh, that radio water.
It's so deadly and yet so irresistible.
I'd rather watch it in 2D because then I'm not constantly reminded I'm trying to see 3D.
The radio dryer?
Or that I'm seeing 3D.
I'm sitting there going, wow, that's cool.
And it's 4U.
What were they talking about?
I wasn't listening to the plot anymore.
I like how it's so funny when he talks about show.
He believes there really is a show.
No, I'm just a tape too.
I think it's so funny when everybody goes...
That's why sometimes we go...
The ultimate insincere laugh.
Stupid.
And then there's the...
Now that qualifies as a sincere laugh.
That is a sincere laugh though.
Hey, Stan, you feel this?
That's not insincere.
It is.
You feel this thrill in your head.
You can call right now if you're a listener.
Actually, if you're a listener and you're a dedicated active listener, you'll call the show at 510-848-4425.
East of the Rockies, call 510-848-4425.
Can't breathe.
Our psychedelic hotline at 840...
4-4-8.
4-4-2-5.
What if they're west of the Rockies?
I'm going to have to reverse every time you guys say that so the people in Madison...
Yeah, Wisconsin, don't try to call that local number.
You need to call 5...
That's why we always put the area code at the beginning of it.
Huh?
That's why we always put the area code at the beginning and that way they'll call the show.
But it's...
Because the show's on all the time whether we're here or not.
Right.
There's somebody going to be here to answer that number.
Yeah, that's why...
And take your request.
Whenever Safeway or anybody wants my number, that's what they get.
848-4425.
That's my home number.
That's a good number.
So who knows what...
Don't say it's a bad number.
You see weird calls.
That's a good number.
You know, I just don't...
If you put that number together numerically and turn it around backwards...
I should say, one of the qualifications for being a friend...
It's a special secret.
...is you have to have a radio show.
Yes.
In your mind.
In your field of mind.
Somebody said they were going to call tonight.
If you're in North Carolina, would you call and give me a free car?
94.1 KPFA Berkeley, Indiana Free Free KPFA.
Because if you live in North Carolina, I need a car there.
I need to have a car in North Carolina.
You know, I got an email this very morning from a poor listener in Greensboro, North Carolina,
who was asking...
Well, he was basically informing me that he was...
He was probably the only subgenius in Greensboro, North Carolina.
The sad thing is, he's not by any means.
There's quite a few of them in Greensboro.
He just hasn't hooked into the community there yet.
The subgenius community.
Maybe he doesn't want to.
That's because subgeniuses, by nature, are not joiners.
And they don't seek each other out all the time very well.
And when they do, they eventually get in terrible fights.
Although sometimes they have sex first.
Yeah.
And get married.
And get married and have children.
And sometimes they just have...
But eventually they have the terrible, terrible fights.
God!
Spon of Bob!
Princess, we are laughing because it is so sad.
It is so sad.
I am laughing.
We will cry forever.
It is so sad.
So many families have been formed at X Days.
And the weird thing is, I'm not even kidding.
I know.
That's scary.
We're moving X Day to a new site.
It's hard to get moved.
You want to mention that to the general public?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, absolutely.
I'm not really here anyway.
Because it's against the rules of California.
No, it doesn't have anything to do with California.
Princess Maria is really breathing heavily over there.
You wouldn't be able to understand any evidence.
Her breathing is so heavy.
She can't breathe in there.
Possibly evidence.
Subgenius.com!
She can't breathe in there.
You should be there.
Subgenius.com.
There's lots.
I'm sure you can.
There's nothing there.
There's more information.
There's so much free stuff there.
It's not a call to action.
I was just reading many stories and looking at many videos.
It's a place to go to find out good things about life and things in general.
There's also dirty pictures there.
The CSS Hunley attacks the Usatonic and sinks her.
And then disappears for 134 years.
I saw for three days recently.
Wow.
Well, about a month ago.
Nobody will ever know what happened in New York.
Yeah, amazing.
And for three days I thought subgenius.com was down and my business had been destroyed.
Because it was blocked by the service for Super 8 motels.
Yes.
So if you're at a Super 8.
And Marriott.
We were in the fancy hotel, Marriott Hotel in New York City.
We were doing that big New York check.
I couldn't even see subgenius.com.
So that's all that blue gravity thing though, right?
Yeah.
Did you rub your nose to tell me that I had a booger in my nose?
No, no.
I rubbed my nose to get the booger out of my nose.
Okay.
Because earlier tonight, Princess, we rubbed her nose.
I'll do it like this.
I'll go.
And she meant, hey, there's a booger in your nose.
Ew.
And I thought she meant, don't do that.
Don't talk about Walmart.
Yeah, yeah.
Why?
Do you have a problem with Walmart?
No, no.
We were with someone who has a big severe problem with Walmart.
Yeah.
A lot of people have to do it in this state.
I didn't want to get into it.
A lot of people do it in this state.
But personally, I think that people that don't like Walmart hate the poor.
Exactly.
I think they hate poor people.
I don't know whether to be ashamed because I shopped.
I don't know whether to shop at Walmart or because I'm so poor I have to shop at Walmart.
And not only do they hate the poor, but Walmart was invented so ugly people would have a place
to shop without fear of being derided by the beautiful people.
Why do you think I go there?
It was a great...
Well, all the good in Walmart.
Ugly people can finally go someplace and think, God, at least the beautiful people aren't
here looking at me and scrutinizing my every move and saying how ugly I am.
Putting me on a website.
I can park my fat carcass here with the rest of the ugly people.
Shopper'sEventsDay.com.
And nobody cares.
It's finally a beautiful place for ugly people and poor people who can't afford the high-priced
goods at those mom and pop locations.
Whatever, Milo.
I can't even hear you anymore with these old ears.
And friends, every time you download a movie, you're putting a mom and pop Hollywood studio
out of it.
That's right.
Damn, Mom and Pop.
There are moms and pops there, too.
Your mom and pop Hollywood studio.
Every time you go to the media ditch, really.
Yeah.
And you go fishing in the middle of the night.
You go to the media ditch and you bring back the big load.
That's all mom and pop.
You're taking that right out of the mouth of mom and pop.
You may as well be urinating on top of mom and pop.
Somebody pissed on this thing.
That's what I was thinking.
You were thinking?
I do not flop on mom and pop.
No, I was smelling.
I do not like.
It smells like spam and ham.
I can't believe it.
I found myself reading that Dr. Seuss book, Green Eggs and Spam, at hyper-fast speed about
four days ago to my grandson.
And my daughter said, that is the fastest I've ever heard anybody do green eggs and
ham.
I just wanted to see how fast I could get through it without flubbing it.
Without flubbing it.
It's a tongue twister.
Yeah.
A lot of his work was very difficult to do at a high rate of speed.
It was fabulous.
I witnessed it.
I would not eat it with a coot.
I would not eat it on a boot.
I would not eat it in my hand.
I would not eat it with my trash.
I would not stroke it with my gland.
I do not like green eggs and spam.
I do not like them no more.
I would not flop it on my pop.
I would not pop it on some flop.
I love having princess Wei in the studio.
She's great.
She makes this sound so good.
She makes our jokes sound great.
Automatic audience.
Yeah, you'd think it was an audio put-up.
It was funny.
Is it real?
But it is funny.
It is funny.
To some people.
Well, to this people.
Some people.
I got a little...
Some people out there.
You know, there's an official...
People, yeah.
...subgenius Facebook page, and I posted links to an hour of slack on it.
The last one, which, by the way, was all reruns of this show.
Reruns?
And old Cher's show and old Susie's show.
It was the three great shows mashed together.
Excellent.
And this one person said...
Okay, I heard the word great.
This is slack.
This is just stupid.
Yeah, yay.
Oh, really?
He spelled stupid with an E.
Thank you.
S-T-E-P-I-D?
Stepped?
No, no.
That would be stupid.
What?
He stepped.
Which E?
I love that internet, boy.
Which E are you talking about?
Which internet?
Stooped.
You know.
A stooped.
Stooped.
That's the best.
That's the band.
See, that's the band.
The Stoopeds.
By the way, the lead keyboard player for the Stoopeds is also the third guy on the right
in the residence.
And the sax player in the Stoopeds with an E is the other resident.
When they play live.
Which they just did.
I don't know of these bands you start...
I'm going to turn that other one down.
Yeah, well, yeah.
Is this the Stooped Day Parade band?
No, Stooped is the guys who I'm talking about are also...
Are they?
Yeah.
Amazing...
It's a band called the Stoopeds.
Studio musicians.
Stoopeds.
And they play bad 70s cover tunes and sometimes play the beautiful Stoopeds Day Parade.
Yeah, they're really wonderful.
And in their spare life, the keyboard player does stuff like...
You know, the other half, the residents.
The three and four guy are fake.
I remember them.
Yeah.
One and two are real.
Philo had many tapes of that ancient band.
That's when I first met Lies.
Yes.
And, you know, people said, you should go...
The only other guy that talks about Kennedy as much is this guy.
Go see him, you know.
Don't talk to me about it.
So, yeah, I went over and he was playing.
He was just getting all those albums and I'd never heard them.
They were great.
They were...
And they were doing tapes.
They were doing Super 8, you know.
Who was that?
Just like everybody else.
The Rezzy dance.
Oh, yeah.
Philo was the one who knew about that band back in the days of Dallas.
All homebrewing the boys.
He would school me in this new art form called punk music.
And I got to say, I was...
What was it?
New wage music.
New wage.
Yeah.
Our new...
I've got a good copy of Jack, Please Don't Go by the band that dare not speak its name.
And I'm trying to match it to all that Super 8 we shot in Dealey Plaza.
I've got one you should have.
The shot of you going...
Ivan staying in a clown suit, shooting at people with a BB gun in front of the front steps of the school book depository.
I was scared.
Really?
I was so scared we were going to get busted.
Me too.
Yeah.
I was too.
But, you know, it was like...
We were like...
It was so cool.
It was amazing.
And then people are just staring at him.
This is 80s.
Well, it was...
You know what it was?
He presses for the cross the street button.
A lot weirder stuff happened around there all the time.
He's a polite killer clown.
He runs out.
Yeah.
It's not a light yet.
So he runs out.
But not just...
I think it was...
It was kind of exciting to be doing it.
The traffic sounds.
Getting away with it.
Well, for our part, it was fun.
Oh, man.
But it was actually not all that novel.
I mean, hadn't Ant Farm already done this huge art performance?
75.
75, yeah.
But that was back when it was still bad taste enough.
Awkward.
I mean, there was really bad taste in Ant Farm, but they break the ice because they did that
whole movie.
Yeah, by the time we did it, it really was funny.
It was only five years later.
And at that point, the city fathers in your town are thinking, let's just wreck this building.
So how long until 9-11 is real funny?
It's going to be a while.
Yeah.
Probably another 10 years.
10, 20 years.
Right.
Well, because, yeah, Kennedy wasn't funny until what?
The late 70s?
Middle 80s.
Yeah.
Late 70s.
Yeah, late 70s.
We were all...
We were all being...
You couldn't accuse us of bad taste.
Right.
We're the very arbiters of good taste.
Oh, yeah.
And we're still...
And Cary Thorne is still alive.
We...
Back then.
That's right.
I read in a magazine the other day by a crazy person that Cary Thornley lived in fear of
Ivan Stang.
Really?
And he said, don't ever talk about Bob because Ivan Stang will sue you.
And that seems strange for me to read because...
All I...
All I remember was friendly essays sent by Cary Thornley.
Yeah.
They were...
You have to remember it's always about who's saying it.
It's kind of hard to read.
He was a little bit on the paranoid side, though.
Well, he had to be.
A little bit.
He's like, imagine a moth close to the flame, you know?
Yeah.
That guy was involved in some stuff and then the thing they were involved in happened.
Probably somebody else did it.
But all of a sudden it's like, who...
It doesn't matter if somebody else did it.
You've been talking about it with a lot of people.
Now, let's see.
And he's called into every committee and he's...
Got people like...
Yeah, I remember driving to the city, picking him up, bringing him back over here, having him on the show, taking him back.
I taped all that stuff and it's amazing.
I thought, I would not want to trade places with his pants for anything.
Yeah, no kidding.
Yeah.
Do you still have those tapes?
And that's what gets stained is the laundering.
When you get that scary.
Yeah, that's what gets stinky, too, is the laundering.
I think he had a pretty complicated life.
I've still got the tapes of the first guy that informed us he was Jesus.
Picking him up at the airport.
And him saying, yeah, I got all this pot with me.
Let's all get busted so we can be on David Letterman tonight and explain how the Bible says marijuana should be legal.
Yeah, he was going to smoke pot on David Letterman.
Remember that?
He was going to pull it out and fire it on David Letterman.
This is after the church and the subgenius super lawyers got him out of jail.
This is all going to happen that night.
Right.
The night after we picked him up at the...
Nobody knows how good our lawyers are.
He was our first coup.
We actually went and picked him up.
That was Will Small.
Yeah, the great Will Small.
Lord is real.
But to think how far, how different it is, how my coup d'etat has improved so much.
I do remember, I do remember.
There hasn't been a Jesus able to tell me he was a Jesus since long before the real Jesus, Bevilacqua came.
But do you remember?
Will Small, after we had tested his wares a little bit, we realized why he was like he was.
It was something he'd done in Hawaii, and this was some very special...
Will Small, the true Jesus of that time, which was about 1983, I think.
Something like that.
He flew to Dallas from Hawaii to meet with J.R. Bob Dobbs.
Bob was not around.
Bob was in Tibet.
But we were around.
I got...
It was a long time ago.
And my family wasn't around.
That was the only reason he ended up in my house.
Yeah.
But he ended up in the slapper mansion at the original Second Fist Temple Lodge in Dallas.
Right.
And then led on that he wasn't just one of the 12 Davids of Philadelphia, but was in fact the Jesus Christ.
Yeah.
Born again.
I remember that.
And he learned this by smoking marijuana.
He was smoking marijuana at a marijuana plantation in Hawaii where he lived.
That's the marijuana?
Oh, come on over here and sit down.
I want to watch TV with counseling evidence.
The Bible had informed him that he was Jesus.
It would be interesting to find out how many...
We would be his only spokesman.
Yeah.
We were the only ones that could see in such a way that could reveal this truth.
He wasn't enlightened enough to instantly recognize this.
Right.
To reveal the truth.
However, we didn't.
The truth of Will Small.
We didn't, but we did remember...
Lord is real.
Quite supremacist.
...Sussex in Alabama, who like him had deciphered from the Bible that the true Jews were the Englishmen who came to America.
That's true.
So we sent him to meet them.
He later went on to see if...
He said they didn't want to be his spokesman.
And he informed me that he'd gone to see Bhagwan Rajneesh, now known as Osho.
And once again, he was...
It was as if...
It was as if it was a world of Judas's.
For that particular Jesus.
Bhagwan Rajneesh was a no-show.
How many of my listeners tonight think you're Jesus?
Stand up.
I want to see you standing.
Now, come on.
Now, that's all way back in the...
Philodramas stood up.
We're watching TV.
Yeah, and Queen of UFOs.
There's nothing wrong...
Everybody but Ivan Stank.
I'm sorry.
There's nothing wrong...
We're all Jesus.
...with thinking you're Jesus.
The only thing bad is when you think you're the only Jesus.
I'm not.
Amen, brother.
I'm not going to...
Amen.
I stand in a party of Jesus stretching back over six millennia.
I can see...
I just don't think that you're the only one.
...from sea to shining Jesus.
You're no more Jesus than I am.
Jesus is a trick on subgeniuses.
Or something like it.
And we love tricks.
We love Jesus.
We love the tricks.
We love it.
We love all the great prophets.
And Edgar Cayce.
Why?
I really liked Edgar Cayce because he was...
It was hard to figure out.
He could cook a fine cherry pie.
Edgar Cayce could.
It's good to have a guru or an enlightened being that can cook.
That can really win your heart through your stomach.
So I wonder who the new head of a tank car is.
It's not Darwin Gross anymore.
No, no.
It's Darwin Gross.
Darwin Gross.
Darwin Gross has passed on to the higher level.
Actually, I have a book at home that has that.
Who the current one is.
I bet that's something we can find out of our special way back Dr. Hal question machine.
He just pulled that out of his pocket.
Dr. Hal's not here.
We have a machine he's left with us that has the contents of his brain.
And we can search the contents of...
Not a very big machine considering.
Well, he's had his brain digitized.
And so...
We need a card for that.
Let's see.
A little more cut out of Dr. Hal, though.
Let's see now.
But the problem is...
We do need a cardboard cover.
Don't we?
You do.
We really do.
So he's at every show ever.
Now, what were we going to ask Dr. Hal's brain?
Unroll a big picture and have it dance around the stage?
Yeah.
And then play a tape of it.
Oh, they do that all the time.
What are Dr. Hal?
What question was I going to ask you?
What question was I going to ask?
Which he would gladly do.
I should do that.
You know, just this...
Hal does a rant for each show.
Yeah.
Rah, rah, rah, rah, rah.
Well, have a picture of Hal and the tape recorder right behind the picture's mouth.
And just hold it there for the, you know, 20-minute rant of Dr. Hal.
And then have him do a rant for each show.
All right.
Okay, that's 20 bucks.
So what was I going to search for?
What was I going to search for?
Come on, pay up.
Did you forget already?
Yeah, what is Wikipedia?
I can't believe he forgot already.
What?
Now I've got to rewind the show.
And figure out what it was we were going to search for.
Unless you call us right now at 510-848-4425.
It's 510.
That's a long-distance call if you're outside the 510 area.
But if you just dial 1, nobody will care.
Your call will be charged to your phone, however it is, normally.
We don't care.
We don't take Skype calls.
We just want your real call.
You can prove to us of your participation as an active listener.
By actually actuating the dial of the telephone or the buttons or whatever.
You know, I don't encourage that on my show.
On my show, I don't let anyone call in except once in cowboy day.
Well, I know, but you're sort of, you have a style.
I'm sort of a fascist.
We like our callers.
We have callers call in and we immediately throw them in the caller pool.
Which is like the deep end of the pool.
And they have to survive there with the other callers.
They splash in.
They splash around.
Some of them sink to the bottom.
Some of them bob right to the top and they're like, they become regulars.
But others just sort of fall to the bottom of the caller pool and they get their, they get stuck in the drain in the bottom.
And it pulls them through and it's really nasty.
I remember when Phineas Narco was just a caller.
Yeah, look at him.
Now he's a demigod.
Yeah, we've called him and praised him.
Repeatedly.
I've done that.
I don't know how many dozens of times.
Countless dozens of times.
Countless dozens.
Of times.
Dozens of times beyond.
So many dozens of times.
It's beyond counting.
That's 12 times as many as an uncountable amount.
Amount.
Yeah.
We, uh, Princess, we and I found ourselves in the Twilight Zone recently as we kept passing the same hitchhiker.
Oh, really?
We were in a mournful old sad man who was just standing there with this.
I remember that Twilight Zone episode.
Oh, I.
Starring, uh, England.
We met like, Inger Stevens was passing him, uh, she kept passing him.
Hey, would somebody.
She stopped.
Why don't you keep the sign?
There's those callers.
Okay, there are the callers.
Hello.
Go ahead, caller.
You're on.
Oh, yeah.
Well, how'd I get driving by and New York winking at me?
Wasn't quite gay.
Dr. Howell's in New York winking at you?
Aw, obscene.
Sometimes.
I'm on the same roadkill.
I kept driving by the same roadkill.
Yeah, I know.
Keep driving by the same roadkill.
Oh, yeah.
Are, are you the large caller called the large?
Yeah, I brought it over.
I'm not a large.
That's the large right there.
Is that the large?
Large, right there.
So it's, the show's called the large?
The color's no longer large free?
No.
It looked like it was kill free.
Hold on for the moment.
It'll, these are the callers that have bobbed up to the top of the, of the collar well.
It's the deep end of the pool, but we like to call it the collar well, because it's not
very-
It's an honor, really.
It really is.
They push on their little heads and they go down for a second.
Watch.
Some of them just float.
They're like filled with air.
They're filled with air completely.
Like little, are you?
Yeah, you can tell by the music.
Are you?
They're like, they're like the bladders of jellyfish.
Some of them are bobbing on the surface, but their tendrils and other appendages hang way,
way down into the-
You'd like to interview the roadkill?
Into the rest of the pool.
Some of those are not, those, oh those aren't.
They're so far down deep below that they sound, it sounds like a-
Distended hemorrhoids or something there.
They have glowing-
Oh.
Little organs that light up.
Right.
They're sort of so far down in the darkness that they attract the other collars that are
already stuck on the bottom of the collar.
Oh, that's what they are.
Wait, there's more than one of them?
They're stuck in the drains down there.
Yeah.
The drains are constantly pumping-
Just drain out, clean it a little bit here.
Pumping fresh fluids into the well.
Now they're all gone.
I need my fluid.
Yeah, like a school of fish.
And zebra mussels clogging up the-
You need the fluid.
You need the fluids in there because that's what keeps everything moving and liquid.
Yeah, yeah.
Keeps everything free and clean.
That reminds me of a troublesome moment I had earlier this evening, but let's not go
into that.
No, no, we have to.
It's on the air now.
And the music is playing.
I know, whatever you say comes true in the air.
There's another roadkill.
Let me go get it for you.
It's the same one, man.
Don't touch it.
You know, I was at the roadkill.
Did you go through Seligman and go to the roadkill cafe?
Why, yes, we did.
We didn't go to the roadkill.
We didn't go to the roadkill cafe, but we photographed the living hell out of it.
We stopped there and actually got ... We've stopped there twice now on our way back and
forth to Texas.
Look at Princess Wee's shirt.
She's wearing the Seligman shirt.
All right.
Too many words.
It's like all the words of Arizona.
Route 66 shirt.
Did you go through Oatman?
No.
Oatman's on Route 66.
It's an interesting little town.
We didn't not know ... Nothing told us to go to Seligman.
We didn't know what the hell was going on.
We were led there by the signpost up ahead.
We just felt ... We pulled over to gas and the sign said, historic Route 66 Seligman.
We thought, okay.
Yeah, you should ... Let's check that out.
Maybe on the way back.
It's the kitchiest ... Unbelievable.
I mean, we were in search of kitsch, of course.
I stopped there once and had like a thousand motorcycles in that one little town.
It was every square inch that was covered with motorcycles.
And there were a lot of motorcycles.
And Benny Dukes.
And James Dean.
They were having some kind of cross-country tour with motorcycles.
Marilyn Monroe.
Marilyn Monroe, yeah.
It was like Motorcycle Day or something.
I was on that planet.
The Marilyn Monroe's and the Einsteins and there were some ... Like Frankensteins.
Ride your tricycle.
Or Frankensteins.
Frankensteins.
That was from ... Remember ...
The Frankensteins.
What's that British science fiction weekly series about the ...
Dr. Howe.
No.
And the Phylosoraptors.
That's the Friday Night Show.
Friday Night Show.
It's the Friday Night Series of Chick and John.
They had the Phylosoraptors.
And the Frankensteins.
That was the scariest movie ever.
Frankensteins, bad.
Phylosoraptors.
Razor sharp claws.
Eviscerating.
Gunmeat streets.
Bad apple place.
I read on the news today ...
It's the bad weather man.
One-fingered dinosaur skeleton was discovered in China.
The practice of ...
I mean, not just that skeleton, but the dinosaur.
It was a precursor to the Tyrannosaurus.
I think that was the one.
It had only one finger, the middle finger.
Yeah, and it was a nose picker.
It was the most insulting dinosaur.
The nose picker X.
He was a really hostile dinosaur.
He only had one finger, and it was in a middle finger salute.
Everything you want in a dinosaur is available in China anytime.
He used to use it to pick the noses of dead dinosaurs.
This is the weather for Booger Raptor.
Booger Raptor, yeah.
Booger Picker Raptor.
Yeah, you're right, Weatherman.
It had to go to Sewerage Street.
All show down the trail.
Down Sewage Street.
Those poor old shows.
They go to the old show home.
You drop that butter.
Poorly paid, irritated nurses change their pants and rewind their tapes.
You think?
I think about those bedpan people that, you know, when they were kids, they grew up, they told their mom what they wanted to be when they grew up and said, I want to clean bedpans when I grow up.
Really?
Yeah.
I want to serve the people.
And I think that's probably the most, the highest, the most sincere way of serving my fellow man is by changing their bedpans when they're in their state of infirmity.
You know, frankly, when every now and then as a minister, I get somebody.
I do that.
Going.
Myself.
Saying to me, begging me for advice because their life has gone to hell and they're so unhappy.
And they go on and on and on and on and on about themselves and how awful everything is.
And how awful it is for them.
And what should they do?
Yeah.
And I always say, find somebody who's in a lot worse shape than you and serve them.
You know, wipe and clean up after people who can't do that themselves.
Go down to the local.
Join me.
And say, I want to volunteer for whatever your nastiest, most foul jobs are.
And you know what those, those, those, uh, Bobby's don't do.
They don't take me up on it.
I don't know why, because it would make them feel better.
Become a greeter at your local hospital.
Or your local Walmart.
A greeter.
Or a, or a good by sayer at your, there's actually almost as many farewellers as there are greeters at hospitals.
No.
Go to the hospital.
What was the name of that?
What was the name of that Walmart-like thing and idiocracy?
I love.
Welcome to Costco.
I love you.
You should have somebody next to you like that.
Standing in the road, way out there on the gate.
Welcome to Costco.
I love you.
And you'd find 12 people that want to do it.
And you could get a lot.
Or welcome to Burning Man.
Burning Man.
You'll have like a.
They have, that's what I mean.
Like an army of them standing there burning.
It's already happening, yeah.
Welcome to Burning Man.
I love you.
They're called the pagan festivals.
They really did that.
Burning Man is the institution.
What's that?
Rainbow Bridge.
So each group has its own group.
Yeah, right.
Whatever.
It's like, welcome home.
Yeah.
Welcome home, brother.
Sister, I love you.
I'm glad you're back.
Do you have a quarter?
We've been waiting for you.
I love you.
Give me a quarter.
I'm glad you're back.
Can I have a quarter?
Only now it's $25.
I've been waiting for you.
If you don't get the quarter.
I'll use this giant shock machine.
Oh.
Chief.
Give me a quarter.
Man, that's an old E-meter.
Ouch.
Ow.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
He's got an E-meter.
You know, Reverend Stang, we learned a lot from old.
I have to power it up.
How did you do that?
Prince of the Indians, Chief.
Give me a quarter.
Remember?
Yeah, we learned how to talk about him.
He was Prince of a tribe.
Of a special tribe.
Well, we don't know that he.
We really don't know that he was an Indian.
And you're right.
That part is probably.
That's probably over the top in terms of horrible, horrible things for us to say on the show.
But it was a gimme quarter.
Well, there's a whole gimmick.
He did say gimme quarter.
Every, every store we drive by.
We're going to cleanse the airways here.
That's a nice politically correct TV show.
Let's watch TV.
Yeah.
Wiggly, wiggly.
So cool.
Chief Family Dollar.
Yeah.
I mean, did you notice all the variations on dollar coming across the country?
Only when we were doing it.
There was no such thing as a dollar store.
It was called a five and dime.
Yeah.
And they had Woolworths was still around.
You could buy things for a dime.
Remember you had Woolworths and TG and Y.
Remember TG and Y?
Yeah.
And they had like a good walk in these rows of trays of army men.
You could buy for like a hundred for a dollar.
You can still buy 50 army men for a dollar, but they're about quarter the size.
They used to.
Oh.
But they still smell good.
They're not as good.
They're all the same.
They're not as firm.
And they don't look as good.
They're like all blotchy and blurry and blobby like now.
It's nearly as articulate and perfectly refined.
The thing I like about that movie Toy Story, which I've seen about seven times in the last
month, is the little army men and the way they walk attached to their base.
Yeah.
That's the way army men really walk.
Attached to a plastic base at their feet.
It's a little awkward, but you know, you didn't, it's a little awkward.
It was when I was a kid with my army men, it was more about setting them up into the
vignette, the diorama and getting everything all perfect than it was actually walking them
around.
You know?
Yeah.
My brother and I, we'd get this, we'd make a neat thing.
And that was like all our army men, all our dinosaurs.
All set up.
All our little robots.
And then when we got it all set up, it was like we retired and didn't want to play with
it.
Yeah.
You get it all set up and then it's, that's it.
You know, you're through.
But you feel stupid going, okay, my army man's fighting my robot.
They're going to kill him.
They're making cities.
And then we have big arguments about where stuff would go.
My best friend and I would fight over like where the outdoor theater went and where the
garage went.
Oh yeah.
No.
Oh, you play Sims?
No Sims, but in the dirt with little.
No, the theater goes here.
A bag of plastic airplanes.
That's not even a theater.
That's just a cracker box.
A bag of plastic cars for a buck.
So we brought our thing together, man.
That's not a Quonset hut.
That's a sawed in half bottle.
Like where the Quonset huts would go was like a cracker box.
That's really important.
I played Tonka truck Sims.
They were Sims.
It was an advanced game.
But they were like physical Sims.
Simulation of a truck, but it was digitized down to about a foot long.
But they were physical.
And they were made of metal, actual metal.
And you can, they were sturdy, man.
You can crash those things in.
Those were physitized.
If you watch Ivan Stanforsley, you can see the pleasure saucers behind you.
There's that, before digitizing, they were physitized.
They've been burning and sanitizing the road behind you guys.
They actually existed in physical Sims.
I mean, you could, you could, you could.
That was a physical thing.
It's a strange thing.
Don't let a trace of them exist.
To actually be able to touch something that's real.
That was so criminal.
The UFO guys in over there just burning the road.
It was a strange experience.
It's very strange experience to actually interact with your character without using a mouse.
The cartoon cross country trip.
Or some type of a digital interface.
When you get home, you got to do it.
The 3D was cut out for people.
You actually had to touch your character with your hands.
With your physical hands.
And put that on YouTube.
To make them move.
It was not only 3D, but you could.
On YouTube?
Feel it.
I don't know if many of the listeners understand what that word.
Feel.
Meals.
You actually.
Is it on YouTube?
You could touch it with the tactile senses.
But it wasn't a keyboard.
No.
And it wasn't a game controller.
But it was.
You could actually feel it with your hands.
Very strange.
Very strange sensation.
Compared to today's electronic feedback mechanisms.
And you know, you're with your.
Speech.
You know, you're with your.
Kids these days.
They got it so damn good.
My kids sit in a.
They sit on my lawn.
Playing their damn video games.
Now they're not even video games.
What they're doing is they're invading your.
Cloud, man.
Your space.
With their special tools.
The Rolling Stones saw it coming.
They saw how we'll be storing every media in the future.
And they sang it.
They said, get off my cloud, man.
Oh, yeah.
The cloud.
Yeah, I'm going to entrust all of my.
See, that's old guy.
That's the dividing line between us.
And they're saying it.
Between us and them now.
Because them.
They trust the cloud.
They have gone with the cloud.
The cloud means that old guys like.
No, no.
I have to have seven physical copies in seven different cities or it doesn't exist.
I remember that when we when we couldn't start talking before we had at least two tape
decks running.
No matter what happens in every single life.
Hey, shut up.
Shut up.
You might say something.
I'm not.
We don't have the tape.
We are the guy at the end of the table.
And there's a young guy with a tape recorder.
And you say, I knew Bob Dobbs for what he was.
I knew him.
He didn't say it exactly like that.
No, it's an adaptation for a screenplay for an abstract.
Huh?
For a TV show.
I knew Bob Dobbs.
For a parrot that said it.
For what he was.
Three hundred years later, there was a parrot that kept repeating.
He's a hell of a man.
I don't know what it is.
He's got that.
I just know it happened.
Here we are a million years later.
We think we made this up, but it came out of history.
Sophistication.
Yeah.
You don't hear any words, do you?
No.
That's the, uh, yeah.
I didn't.
Good.
Okay.
Yeah.
That's totally, totally subliminal.
Subliminal.
Yeah.
There's no.
Now this is the part where the show is very subtle.
Okay.
This is where we ask for the callers to stimulate us.
Check out this show.
We call the callers.
They call the callers.
We call the callers ourselves.
Now we actually dial 5 1 0 8 4 8 4 4 2 5 and we call ourselves.
Oh, incidentally, I want to do a shout out to my mother-in-law and her friend, Ruth,
who really both wanted to stay up and listen to the show, but it was a little bit late.
Are they going to try?
I told him, I said, Hey, look, you can tune in during lunch tomorrow.
You can.
It'll be on.
Right.
I'll put it on the archives.
Better be.
Sure.
This is.
I'm about out of reruns on our Slack and I need something to put on.
We've got a lot of reruns for our Slack.
You can start running those early.
One rerun I ran was the first hour of the five hour subgenius executive retreat.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
It was an over the edge show.
Yes.
Over the edge show.
And we were had all gathered for the subgenius executive retreat at sulfur springs or sulfur
palms.
Yeah.
Sulfur palms.
That was it.
And I kept saying Don Joyce's name instead of his character name.
Yeah.
Morpheus.
He likes to be called Morpheus when he's off the show.
I think then it was, I was, you know, for years I always talk about how I hate the guy
that came on before me, you know, just to work this thing.
And then a few years ago I asked Don, do you ever listen to the show?
And, and hear what I say?
I go, no, I don't have FM in the car.
So he missed many years lambasting.
Yeah.
Horrible, stupid show.
Almost wasted, almost wasted words.
The one guy you wanted to get the joke.
Well, that's what I hear.
When it, when princess, we, and I drive home from WCSB, we hear Dr. Sinister talking about
how crappy our show was.
Yeah.
He does that a lot.
I hear that a lot.
And what show is it?
Ivan's Dang.
It's the hour of Slack.
The voice of the show.
The church of the subgenius.