To process the magnanimity that is Korok, for your simpler minds, we have translated the following images into a format that we think that you will find more familiar.
I believe in your world they are called cartoons.
Oh, Bobby, I'm sorry.
What happened?
Everything gets wrecked.
Everything.
Bobby?
We have three good candidates in here today.
We have Fluffy, Skipper, and Bob.
And with any luck, one of those will come at you at full speed.
Fluffy, Skipper, Bob, gee, with names like that, it must be the subgenius.
Our old swag.
This is the Slag World Cup.
These are the calling cards of a con artist.
Whatever happened to Bob?
We could revive the lost arts of con.
Panko!
Oh, Bobby.
I know right where she's at right now.
All right, listen, Bobby.
Just head right for where she's at.
Tell me on the radio, let's boogie.
Eh, I'm really more of a slacker.
You've even foiled Bob on five separate occasions, and he's a genius.
Oh, Bob.
Everybody in here is so crazy about Bob.
Slug.
Eternal salvation, or triple your money back.
All of the religions will be having a heart attack.
A pipe full of froth equals what?
A lot of slack, no matter how you kill it.
He always keeps coming back.
Bob.
I'm talking about Dobbs.
Repent quickly.
Get your job and slack off.
Get ready to blast off.
When that state comes and all the geeks are on the run from Bob.
Bob.
Pull the wool over your own eyes.
Start to realize what till now has been disguised.
Keep looking to disguise.
That the sauce is flying by.
And maybe by and by.
You will see the light at the end of the pipe that leads to Bob Dobbs.
Bob Dobbs.
Talking about the salesman.
To the gods.
He's still a chattel coffin lid.
On a conspiracy of normality.
Oh, who could it be but Bob?
Bob.
Oh, Bob.
Saw the dots blanket Emilel's
By Samック
Lab
The race became the banger and the fool became the wise
Cause it's a way out, far out
Psychedelic freak out, took a hit of Bob
I'm starting to freak out, geek out
My friends are gonna leak out
Look out everyone, here he comes
It's Bob
I wish you could forget
You wish you could forget
So crazy about vai
It's so crazy about your ba da da pa
Please
so crazy about va
simmer
ND
Oh, Bob.
Bob.
I've been slacking off.
Yogi Berra, Lou Piniella, Bucky Dent,
Billy Martin, Dallas Green, Dick Houser,
Bill Verdon, Billy Martin, Stump Merrill,
Billy Martin, Bob Lemon,
Billy Martin, Bob Lemon, Gene Michael,
Buck Schultz.
Oh, you didn't hear that from me.
So how did your date work out with the mysterious pony?
I am telling you, this woman is strange.
She never wants to leave the apartment.
Ready for lunch?
I'm stuck here editing the stupid catalog
because of stupid Bob.
Listen, there's something really suspicious about this guy.
Every time Mr. tries to assign him any work,
he says he can't hear,
and it all gets dumped on me.
You think he's faking?
I don't know, but I'd like to try that earpiece on,
see if it's real.
Bob, you know what?
Um, I'm kind of swamped here.
You think you could give me a hand with some of the catalog?
I'm kind of swamped.
Swamped.
Did you see that?
That was him?
Yes.
Somehow I thought he'd be taller.
All right, listen.
We'll have to do this again some other time, okay?
I got a lot of work to do.
Hey, Bob.
Bob?
Hey, Bobby, over here.
Bob.
Oh, Bob.
Oh, my God.
He's dead.
Yeah, this is Connie.
You gotta help me.
Some guy dropped dead on top of me.
I can't call the cops.
I can't.
I'm stuck.
You gotta help me.
I think I've been working you a little too hard lately.
Oh.
So I have two tickets.
For you to the Bob show.
Oh.
It is a real hoot.
Oh, thank you, Mr. Emmerty.
Oh, the tickets are for tonight, so you and Bob can knock off a little early so you both
can get ready.
There's no need to deny it.
I heard every word you said.
And I know you wouldn't be just having fun with this handicap.
Ooh, that kind of cruelty would be grounds for dismissal.
Oh, God, what happened to you?
She tried to kill me.
Who?
Connie.
What did she do?
I don't know.
But I woke up in the Hudson River in a sack.
I think she drugged me.
But she's a murderer, and I'm calling the cops.
Why would she try and kill you?
Oh, isn't it obvious?
She doesn't want anybody else to have me.
Can you give us a hand with some of these boxes, Bob?
Bob.
I want you so bad, Bob.
You turn me on so much.
You're so damn sexy.
Oh, I'm starting to unbutton.
Anything getting through, Bob?
No.
Try not to dawdle, Amos.
Oh, honey, don't worry.
I'll be gone before you know I'm back.
And for goodness sake, don't forget the bread for the sandwiches.
Oh, they'd be awfully messy if I did.
More like a hand sandwich than a ham sandwich.
Oh, yeah.
I was just picturing our guests trying to eat without bread.
Oh, that would be funny.
Well, Sarah, I think the guests of the Longhead Bay Inn have come to realize that zany humor is just a pleasant bedfellow to their clean soap.
Or napkin.
Yes, Mr. Funny Funny Man.
Well, don't have so much humor that you forget to come home.
Now, watch.
I'll be trying to think up jokes about being late.
Oh.
Oh, I forgot.
I'll be back in a minute.
I'll just get my bed.
I'm gonna have to go to work.
See you later, Bob.
Bye-bye, Bob.
We're back.
I think I got a very good idea.
I think I got a good idea.
Cause when your forehead's screaming, it isn't really you.
That barren plain of madwood, smack on the front of your head.
Smack on the front of your head.
Between your face and hairline, like a sandwich cloaked in bread.
Foreheads have a place upon your face.
It's all just part of the human race.
But you're not dreaming, your forehead's screaming.
It's screaming.
That we're really all from outer space.
Our hearts and heads are different in their respective means.
In their respective means.
Decisions can't be awkward unless our forehead leads.
Some may say.
In this world.
But I say it's wrinkled and flawed.
I say it's twisted.
I say it's smarter than our brains.
Smarter than our brains.
Unlikely.
Though they talk.
People call it bra.
I'm not your heart.
It can have no.
Have no.
Sin.
No.
But wouldn't our love.
Just push and shove.
Until love no head.
Sets us free.
Now some may say.
It is furrowed, furrowed.
But I say it's wrinkled in thought.
It's smarter than our brain.
It is unlike.
We have all.
Been taught.
We have all been taught.
Trail of the screaming forehead.
What can a body do?
Pause when your forehead's screaming.
Is screaming.
Screaming.
I.
Love.
I. Love.
You.
And so, in conclusion, we must conclude that it is the human forehead and not the much publicized brain, which is the source of all man's and woman's knowledge.
Bravo, Sheila.
That sounds very real.
And scientific.
Oh, really, Dr. Latham.
You disappoint me.
How can you be taken in by such drivel?
I don't know.
I just am, I guess.
I take it you disagree with my theories, Dr. Applethorpe?
I not only disagree with them, I think they're insane and wrong.
Might I understand you'll be cutting off my funding?
As head of the department for thinking and thought studying, you leave me no choice.
Really, Dr. Applethorpe?
No, no.
It's all right, Philip.
You see, I understand the good doctor.
Isn't it not about my theories at all, Dr. Applethorpe?
Isn't it because.
I'm a woman?
Don't be absurd.
If a man told me our foreheads were the seat of all human knowledge, I would react exactly
the same way.
Really?
Really, Dr. Applethorpe?
And what if that man were a woman?
Well, this is insane.
Theophilus the Thistle Sifter sifted six thistles into the thick of his thumb.
See therefore that thou and thou siftest thistles, sift not six thistles into the thick of thy
thumb.
Hm?
You sure got a pretty mouth, Dr. Howe.
Yes.
Amidst the mists and coldest frosts, he beats his fists against the post, and still insists
he sees the ghost.
I'm ready for that ghost, because I want to make some cheese, too.
I have a question for Dr. Howe.
Uh, the refrigerator.
Notice I didn't say icebox, and it's a GE turret top.
It's full of tasty stuff, kids.
Oh my God.
The refrigerator is?
Uh, it's bulging at the seams with, uh, illegal, uh, uh, food, uh, consumables.
You made me forget my question for Dr. Howe.
That's all right.
Reach deeply down into memory's well.
There's that sound effect of clunking and crashing that we have often played, because
we intended to all along, from the very beginning of the show.
It was, uh, it was put into our, uh, special storyboard here, you see.
I can't hear anything.
As though some oafish lout overturned, uh, a valuable, vital piece of equipment.
Ah.
Have you ever heard that sound effect from the sound effects record of a body falling
downstairs?
Ever heard that one?
The ka-thumpity, ka-thump-thump?
Yeah.
Sure.
My brother made a loop of that and put a beat behind it and, uh, made a nifty, nifty, nifty,
little tune out of it.
Yes, he did.
Back in the day.
Now I'm not gonna pussyfoot around before I get to telling you about my twelve-module
course in success in sex and real estate.
Oh.
It always gets down to that, to, to, to, to, twelve steps.
Well, I'm quite willing to, to put this educational and amazing message aside, even
though it could affect you personally and change your life for the better.
The day you've heard that sound effect, you've got to get out of here.
You know, I don't know if you've heard of Dr. Howland Owl's course in success in real
estate.
Could be the first day of your new existence.
But if you don't want to hear about it, that's quite all right.
Your privilege as a free American.
Well, you know, these events do not put themselves on.
We have to be realistic.
We live in a world of buying, of getting and spending, of financial transactions, whether
capitalism or communism.
The workaday world must go on.
How's your microphone, Dr. Drummond?
Oh, he's coming through just fine.
Ah, yes, like a...
I'm still concerned about the hellest economy.
Like a tiny baby budgie, a canary in a coal mine,
to tell us whether things are going south,
to the land of sorghum and molasses.
I don't know that I hear Dr. Drummond.
Oh, listen, you can hear it now.
Now, the money bird.
Withered little thing.
Yes, but it's flying towards Dr. Hell's real estate.
Get away!
Ow!
Ah, nasty little thing.
Well, that's the way I treat all such invaders.
You just stepped on it.
Well, it's not able to...
Its fragile skeleton with hollow bones
is easily intimidated by the weight
of a heavy graviportal individual.
Such as myself.
So, uh, back to, uh,
chewing the cud and...
You know, let's, uh, shoot the, uh, shite
and, um, chew the popcorn.
We'll chew the fat in the kitchen.
Uh, Dr. Hell?
Have a good old chinwag.
Yes, yes, what is it, Dr. Drummond?
I have Philo on mic now.
You want me to turn him down?
Turn him down?
No, he's a brilliant stream
of mind-breaking special effects.
Okay, whatever you'd like.
No, which mic is that?
I'll turn it on.
Turn him down.
No, wait, wait.
Ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay.
He's gonna go down with the ship.
By God.
Well, uh, we can always, uh,
talk about some...
These ghosts are going down together.
Other time, the, uh, way
my course in success and sex
and real estate can turn you around,
uh, particularly, I will require
that you do this when you receive
the 11th module of hands-on instruction.
But, uh, let's, uh, go back
and discuss something
of an interesting historical,
uh, historical,
or, uh, psychological nature.
Perhaps psycho, uh, historical,
or, uh, psychological, uh, mythological.
Hey, careful, Michael.
Please don't spill any jujube juice
on the b-b-b-board.
They'll be so angry.
If you've been reading the chat stream,
you'll know that no one is allowed
to consume, uh, liquids, solids,
or oxygen in the control booth
during broadcast.
This subgenius must have snacks.
They're a terrible thing.
Hey, that reminds me of snack.
Hey, I just got a message
from Princess Wee.
She made it safely to her home planet,
and she found the, uh,
computer, uh, drive,
the dilithium crystals,
just where I said they would be.
She found it?
I built it right where I said
they would be.
There I said it again.
I had hidden them there.
You'll pay to know what you really eat.
Oh, that's right.
We're coming up with all, uh,
variations and...
Variations...
...on the theme.
Have sex with your beautiful live self.
You'll pay to pull your eyes
over your legs,
which will be on fire at the time.
Um, and you'll do this gladly
in the wonder world of tomorrow.
Pull your eyelids over your own eyes.
All of this in module 12.
That's right.
The culmination, uh,
the climax, as it were,
of the relentless pounding
of the rest of the course.
See, only after you worked out the origins
could you come up with classic variations.
Well, this started when I got a comment
on some YouTube video
where the guy didn't have much to say.
He just wanted to show that he was
subgenius-friendly,
uh, and he...
his comment was,
pull the wool my own eyes.
Duh!
I hope you sent him a dollar.
All right.
Pull the wool of my own eyes.
And that's what Philo and I were thinking.
Our...
The Bob slogans are a little too long.
Bob's just moving faster,
making everyone else seem slow and stupid.
Why do we need the details?
It's subgenius must have.
That's good enough.
Too much reverb on kindly Reverend Stang.
Too much is not enough.
Can't hear his wisdom.
No, too much is not always better than...
Pull my eyelid over your own eyes.
Not enough.
Eyelids of morning.
The Lord is in his holy temple.
Too much is better.
The Lord's throne is in heaven.
Subgenius must.
His eyes behold,
his eyelids try the children of men.
That's a new perfume, subgenius must.
The Lord trieth the righteous.
It's kind of thick in here at the moment.
But the wicked and him that loveth violence
and video games his soul hateth.
The subgenius must have slack.
Upon the wicked he shall pour snares,
fire,
and brimstone,
and a horrible tempest.
This shall be the portion of their cup.
For the righteous Lord loveth righteousness.
His countenance doth behold the upright piano.
What is it, Dr. Goldie?
I'd like to help with your posture just one second.
Relent.
Get a job.
Forget slack.
Like the sons of Arius.
And invade Poland and annex the Sudetenland.
No longer do I need to.
I bend over in a servile posture to speak into the rectifier.
What is the law?
The laws to not broadcast on two feet.
What hath God wrought?
Um, that's a rhetorical question.
What has God wrought?
Yeah, what's God wrought these days?
What's God wrought these days?
What's God wrought for me lately?
Well, he wrought...
Come on, God, what you wrought?
He's, uh, he's, uh, reeking a shopping center,
replacing Candlestick Park.
All I know is that God's not wroughtin' much around here lately.
He knocked a crane over by the Bay Bridge.
God hath forgotten.
He hideth his face.
He will never see it.
So, Father, could God wrought something that he can't unwrought?
Sure, God can wrought whatever he wants to wrought.
Arise, O Lord.
But can he unwrought something he wroughted himself?
Yeah, but he's smart enough to know better.
I'm really, really impressed by the new Pope.
Where did you find him?
That little dog?
Yeah.
Pope Pero.
He's, uh, he's a little German.
Come on, boy.
He's smart enough to know better, that's why.
Yeah, listen to that.
That's Pope Pero.
Yes, he, uh, he's actually a Spanish, uh, mutt, a stray, who was owned and raised by,
uh, Reverend Kai Wicker in Germany.
Well, he's just got this darling little accent.
It makes you want to reach down and...
Ow!
He looks so cute.
He's got the crap out of him.
Get off my leg.
Woof!
Hey, something my leg.
All right, that's disgusting.
Uh, get that animal out of here.
This is a studio for higher beings, uh, for advanced creatures.
You know, this reminds me, Doctor...
We were trying to be uppity and we...
Once in a time.
We were asking...
All canine Americans required to leave the room.
...if God wrought.
All I wanted to know is if God wrought.
That's a good idea.
Get him out of here.
Yes, God could create a human being.
He created a ditch so big he couldn't jump over it.
In fact, he did and that is the result.
Uh, I mean, our present predicament is the result.
Well, a ditch too big for God to jump over.
And we left God behind.
Too big to fall in.
Well, we're on the wrong side of that ditch, partner.
We swam across that ditch and left God on the other side.
Ew, it's full of sewerage.
And now God...
We don't have a God no more.
God hath left us.
Flying through a mile of that tunnel.
I shall not be moved.
I shall never be moved.
To break out of subgenius prison.
I shall never be in adversity.
Climb through the sewage to reach the fresh air.
And I forgot my poster of Raquel Welch.
Freedom.
And then you realized, oh, no, I left my pocket knife back there.
And God climbed back into that sewer and went to get his body.
The sewer known as the human body.
Yes, God became a blob of glup and entered into the womb of the descendants of an ape.
Yes.
A human woman.
And thus it was that God's little son was expelled in a cave over which a crude shelter
had been built.
Excuse me, I know this doesn't sound like anything remotely related to having any kind
of sex or real estate.
We need to know the basis to achieve equity in sex and real estate.
One must understand the metaphysical.
Basis.
Of the legends which you will use to shift legions of suckers onto your path as valuable
assistants and cannon fodder.
Well, I don't know.
All I do is, I spent all my money on this real estate and now I can't live on it or
rent it out for six months or else I won't be able to have sex any more.
Well, it's a funny thing about money.
Money is funny.
Money is given a value which is...
I followed every bit of advice in modules six through eleven.
Well, that's very advanced, Pilgrim, but in module number one, that's where I say that
we give the value to our children.
It's not just about the value of your money.
It doesn't have value in and of itself.
By giving me a significant amount of your money, even a disabling amount, it shows that you
are ready for an exchange of true value.
Let me see that, Michael.
Can you tell us your secret for free, Dr. Howell?
Well, for those who are willing to listen to this program, it doesn't seem to be playing.
There's something the matter with it.
Let's take it out and try it again.
It won't come out.
It seems that it's wadding up inside the machine.
Well, this is unfortunate.
It's not a good idea.
It's unfortunate.
We do have a digital copy somewhere, but I need somebody who knows how to run it.
Let's look at the screen over here.
Does anybody have a small...
What are those mean people talking about?
Well, somebody wrote old rules for old guys.
I'm not sure I like that.
What else are they saying?
They won't have to worry about getting old, most of them.
Hey, can I see...
These guys are so full of they selves.
Yeah.
And...
Duh.
Old blah blah.
We're doing great, folks.
Here's one I like from Mel DeRorah.
What absolute twaddle.
You know, these are great.
We could use them as pull quotes.
Hi, this is Bob.
Yes.
Hi.
And...
How you guys doing?
Mel, thank you.
Hi.
Yes.
Enjoy your meal, sir.
Good thing I'm hungry.
Ladies and gentlemen, I'm going to ask you to raise your glasses to the hero of the hour,
my savior.
Appreciate it.
Greetings and salutations.
I'm Bob.
We met before.
Ever so briefly, I was gruffling in fear at the time.
You got the salt over there, Bob?
Salt is not good for you, hence it is illegal.
Thanks, Mom.
Thanks, Bobby.
Sure.
Aside from that retard trying to punch me, it was actually pretty good eating.
And then one day my dad said, Bobby, you're 17.
It's time to throw childish things aside.
And I said, okay, pop.
You sure picked the wrong night to find a cemetery in your house, huh?
Let's turn back.
No, it's on a night like this when the best ideas come to mind.
But does it have to be in a cemetery?
You would understand.
Seeing a cemetery on a night like this can stir in the mind the best ideas for a good horror story.
But there's so many wonderful things to write about, Bob.
Sure there are, and I've tried them all.
Plays, love stories, westerns, dog stories.
Now there was a good one, that dog story all about...
But horror stories, why all the time horror stories?
I wrote for years without selling a single word.
My monsters have done well for me.
You think I'd give that up just so I could write about trees or dogs or daisies?
Daisies? That's it, I'll write about my creatures who are pushing up the daisies.
You want to see what we got her?
I do, I can't wait to see what you got her.
I gotta put the pink stuff in it.
Oh.
What's a good photoshoot made of?
Shoes,
Barbies,
and beautiful girls.
Photoshoot.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Barbies and I don't know what they are.
And then beautiful girls.
That's it.
Well he's an international celebrity really who revolutionized the way the world looks.
If you don't look good, we don't look good.
A multi-million dollar...
International corporation.
Famous for creating the bob and the many many more.
anxiety
high on the ladder
depression pushed down on your bladder
it seems there's no way to attain laughter
only results in feeling sadder
and it's fixed to you
like crazy you
I'm just crazy too
just like crazy you
everybody crazy too
crazy, crazy, crazy, crazy
high on the ladder
crazy, crazy
The competition and power struggle
It only makes frustration double
Forward intention and backward thinking
Addicted to you and I can't stop drinking
And it sticks to you
Like crazy
I'm just crazy too
Just like crazy you
Everybody crazy glue
I'm just crazy glue
Just like crazy you
I'm just crazy too
Everybody crazy too
Crazy too
Crazy
I'm just crazy gold
I'm so crazy stuck to you
I'm so crazy crazy proper crazy
Now let's close out with the bad guy affirmation.
I am bad, and that's good.
I will never be good, and that's not bad.
There's no one I'd rather be than me.
Okay, gang, see you next week.
Jonathan Livingston Siegel, I'm afraid I can't indulge the chat board.
No, we're not going to talk about dispensable Kleenex tissue of the literature of the 70s.
We were talking about the Church of the Subgenius.
What's the difference?
Because we do not pretend that our work is fiction.
Price Harris.
Oh, come on.
Those people are certain.
They're like the Clampers.
Hey, Larry.
The E. Clampus Vitus characters.
I shouldn't even run them down.
You know, we're all in the religion game.
We're all trying.
No, I was just kidding.
I love my Discordian brothers and sisters.
They don't care if you do or you don't.
That's the problem with them.
You know, I'll tell you.
Well, that's the charming thing about them.
Let me discuss something real that actually is a matter of some concern to me.
Oh, what?
Oh.
I don't know how to resolve.
You know how on Facebook people are always trying to friend you and so forth?
Well, in mine, there's an enormous queue of jokers trying to friend me who I've never heard of,
but they've all got gag-like names.
Yeah, they all try to friend me.
It's enormous.
It goes on forever.
You know, like Lee Harvey Wallbanger and that sort of thing.
Some dumb twat.
Yes, exactly.
And many of these characters call themselves J.
R.
Bob Dobbs, and they want to be my friends.
How?
I cannot be the friend of anyone who calls himself J.
R.
Bob Dobbs.
I don't assume here.
Absolutely.
Bob Dobbs Jr.
Bob Dobbs Jr.?
Well, that's at least better, but a lot of these folks don't even put the quotations on.
What about Little Bobby Dobbs?
They can't spell Bob.
They can't even spell Bob.
I don't wish to muddy the waters, but my God, look at the long line of them.
On the other hand, I could be insulting an army of people.
Good.
Who it would be better were on my side.
Anybody who's such a copycat.
J. B.
Robby of Dobbs.
A calico copycat.
Would you?
Well, if they weren't, they'd be starting their own religion, and we'd have to be their
followers.
Well, I.
It seems like you're complaining about the wrong thing.
J. L. Bibb.
Blibbs.
I called up a list of.
I saw that, too.
I've seen, you know, the names are funny.
They'll make you laugh, but I have no idea who any of them are.
The weirdness of everything.
Some dumb guy.
That's a Thai food dish.
I called up the list of all the Bob Dobbs on Facebook, and my finger wore out before
I could scroll to the bottom of that list.
It's all your fault.
Well, they are.
They could be an army that would come to your aid.
I'm just a clerk.
But on the other hand, you would have to bear their snarky personality.
Oh, my own eyes.
See?
I know all about Bob.
I'm just a clerk.
I'm just a guy.
My friends, those of us who are higher in the echelons of the Church must bear with temptations
and struggles that the laity, and even the Communicating Members, can scarcely imagine
on their own.
These gods are so full of themselves.
What is God, Rat?
They think that if they make some feeble joke that they can be admitted to the empyrean
levels where we despoil with the angels.
They're old.
I'm never going to be like that.
Hoh.
Well, it depends on where your fandom allegiance lies.
To what god of popular culture will you grovel and kowtow?
Will you drink his blood and ceremonially eat of his flesh?
I know mine.
What ridiculous twaddle.
Yeah, they're saying that.
They don't really like our broadcast, so we could talk about something else.
But what about this?
Do you have the nudist Hootie and the Blowfish album?
Nudist Hootie and the Blowfish album?
Yeah, nudist Hootie.
They're trying to get us to come back.
Those guys were made illegal in San Francisco.
I didn't even know they'd released an album.
But at any rate, I'm sure it's full of pictures and well worth a dollar.
No, the Blowfish, of course, being highly poisonous, its music is to be disregarded.
Do the Blowfish still have their clothes on?
They pop them when they inflate their bodies.
I know Hootie probably does.
The front guy's name is Hootie.
Yeah, Hootie?
Menuhin?
Blowfish in the back.
Is there a keyboard that I can type in a comment complete?
Philo's got one.
You can borrow it from Philo and type it in and it'll appear.
Wait a minute.
Philo's the one sending all those messages in.
He's sending a number of them.
He's complaining about himself as he's complaining.
If you want something done, the right way to do it is to do it yourself.
That Philo Drummond is so dull.
He never brings anything interesting to the table.
Well, he does the best he can.
Who's that new asshole?
He's called the Naked Guy.
But is any of this stuff you can extract and squeeze in the wine press of the gods for your own radio purposes?
Or is it too random and wandering and incoherent and impotent, weak?
Stumbling along.
Lost.
Hopeless.
Near death.
Ready to drop.
Obsolete.
You are obsolete.
Kicked by the young people walking up and down.
Is this newage?
Just outside.
Is this music?
Is this newage music?
Yeah.
It is, but we'll fix that.
That pretty much senses one of the main key elements of...
What is that?
Sewage rhymes with sewage.
Yeah, what did...
You mean Jonathan Livingston's...
Don't worry.
Boots, saddles, horses...
Newage rhymes with sewage.
I never heard that one before.
Since 1979.
You heard it when I said it the first time.
Oh, right.
Back in 1979.
What are you going to call us all sheep?
Are you going to call everybody else sheeple now?
And what all of us want to know.
To show how original you are?
Are you going to call...
Let's all name ourselves Garrett Bob Dobbs to show that we really understand that.
Who threw the overalls at Mrs. Murphy's chowder?
I'll just call them pink.
I'll call them pinks like I always have.
Speak up, pink boy.
There's a new one.
Speak.
Now I'm doing it.
If it is upon you.
Incumbent Bob lost to challenger Bob who used to represent Bob.
It was a rematch.
That was before a video of an intoxicated Bob hit the internet first.
And again, the latest incident prompted a...
That garnered nearly 4,500 church-ch-ch-churchers.
Wab.
Bob and Ak-Mak-Kernel emerged as the top two wub-getters during century January in primary.
Besides personal behavior, a main issue for Bob was a proposed off-reservation casino.
Man at NERCron accused Bob of leaking bits and pieces, but not being fully forthcoming, and what the financial obligations would be.
For his part, Bob said he was doing his best to move from his past as a manufacturing center to his future as a tourist and entertainment destination.
Unofficial results show Bob beat tourists roughly.
Legal expert says Constitution does not comply with U.S. implausibly denies rolling Noriega Pan Am 103 in Israeli Lizard King Terror Squad.
I wonder what the hell that's about.
The FDA does not care about your health.
CNN is peeing on dead Afghans.
The FDA is killing you.
Dad punishes Facebook with eight bullets to laptop.
Fair and balanced.
Fox News axes freedom.
No more freedom.
U.S. officials confirm the bill.
The FDA is in denial of any covert Western action in Iran.
And you're not the captain.
Well, I may not be the captain, but you're not the god.
Good.
Because I don't want to be the stupid god fucker.
I'm Bob Bob Bob.
I'm Bob fucker.
Alright?
And by the way, Bob told me you offered him the job first.
Nice to know I was your sloppy seconds.
You spoke to Bob?
Yeah, I did.
I had beers with him last night.
He's in town for a convention.
That's it.
You're done.
You know what?
No, wait.
What wheel?
The wheel.
The little hamster wheel that we're all running up to get a taste of your little water thingy.
Just please approval.
Approval.
What the hell are you doing?
It was the legendary Bobby Rush.
The Bob Rush has real strong roots in the community.
Bob Rush was, you know, a panth panth panth panth.
Then he matured.
That's like when a, matured.
That's like when a, a guy that took that toughness in the community.
I've always felt like I needed to earn my way into this family.
Bobby's giving him the money?
Give me my money.
Get it back in business, Bobby.
And I'm gonna take you down, brother.
And he gives me this whole spiel, right, about how next in line to his throne.
He came up with his name?
The Bobfather.
Really?
He said that to you?
Wow.
He pulled the same fish on you, didn't he?
The world's just hamsters on Bob's little wheel.
His circus of trust, or whatever he calls it.
Circle of trust.
I had no idea how deep I was in until I stepped away.
And I'll tell you something.
Once I got off the treadmill, I'd never been out of here.
Yes, this is the time for you to articulate.
What's your beef?
Why don't you tell the doctors of the air and see how much good it does?
Why do you guys all talk at the same time?
Nobody can understand any of that stuff.
It just totally alienates the audience.
And then, I'm gonna tell you something.
It actually alienates me.
It drives me nuts.
The Happy Talk Radio.
I'm a nut, anyway.
Well, I'm sorry.
I don't know what to do except offer my profoundest apologies.
Just like the McLaughlin Group, the Capital Gang, all our great progenitors, we do tend
to yell a little bit in the heat of argument.
Yes, but we could go to a different level, a better level.
And why not?
That's interesting music.
What is that?
This is the music of Loop Station.
Robin Coomer singing.
She was here last time.
You might have met her.
She and Spy Emerson were here.
Oh, okay.
I never was formally introduced to anybody.
Ah, too bad.
When one does radio, one must stick at the microphone and not get up and circulate about shaking hands.
And receiving the attention of exquisite beauties.
What makes these microphones so sticky?
I'm afraid to touch them again.
Generations of spitters have spit popped into them.
Oh, man.
As we used to say.
The foam is almost hard with the snot.
Foam on the range.
Yes.
Spitto, spittere, octui, splatus.
Say it.
Don't spray it, Dr. Al.
Look, I'm just saying this is a...
Came right through that squim screen at me.
The squim screen?
Yeah.
Good Lord.
I didn't realize we were being bombarded by Gleet.
Now, kids, you can look that up in the dictionary.
Gleet.
G-L-E-E-T.
Or can you?
I thought it was something Philo made up until I actually encountered it in writing about World War I.
Yeah.
I think I may have first seen it in a short story about P-Dawg, which used the term anticipatory Gleet.
A droplet of anticipatory Gleet quivered at the tip was the sentence, I believe.
Yes, I recall that well.
It was a vivid one.
Care dog meets P-Bear.
Was it?
Oh, that's right.
I wrote that line.
That's right.
No wonder I remembered it for a second.
At least you remembered that much.
You drew that, too, didn't you?
He would remember you.
That was a great coloring book.
But you first wrote a version of that in Behold the...
What was it, the one about the robot with the scepter?
Oh, yeah, the Scepter of Pretorius.
That was terrible.
Was it really?
I was like 18 when I wrote that.
I redid it to put something in it.
I subgeniously stuffed in it just...
I don't know, because otherwise nobody would ever have printed it.
Now I wish they never had.
It was one of those famous underground people that I've now forgotten about.
Peter Wilson, that was it.
They're so talented.
You want him on his face to get to the top.
No, let's not go over old...
Let's try to settle old scores.
Put on your old baseball cleats and climb on their faces.
No problem.
Put on your new bra, look at my bonnet, and...
The husks. All those editors.
Huh?
The husks of all your former editors.
That corn husker's lotion.
Sucked.
I wish you hadn't mentioned that.
Sucked. Dry.
Saper thin rustling in the corner.
Jabba the husk.
Well, it killed the first one.
Then the second one tried to kill us.
And then there weren't any more.
Funny how that happened.
Really?
nothing's left but this they killed each other yeah all this subgenius then there was the poor
japanese translator that some japanese publisher actually gave us five grand about a million years
ago they were going to do a japanese version of the book of the subgenius and then nothing
happened and we later heard that 19 translators has committed seppuku out of shame because they
were unable to get through the first sentence or two they were still working on page three the last
time there's still armies of them over there killing themselves every day because of that
even now i know of at least one finn trying to translate oh is reverend shining path translating
some stuff is he a finnish person yes oh a fight to the finish because he eats his spinach
reverend shining path
is uh
he's a good subgenius he's a mexican finn we have been observing his uh progress for some time and
are well pleased with our good service he's led a huge crusade in china they've had he's bringing
the chinese over to our side yeah right he's either a mexican much is rising riding on the
shining path we have one actual native chinese minister
since reverend li li jing was the first one whatever happened so we've only got a
one billion to go or so he must be a millionaire by now selling bootlegs
he pulls himself up by his own bootlegs mayor bob made news after video of his drunken exploits
hit the internet i've never denied any of my shortcomings bomb emerged as one of the top
drunken vote getters bomb and his challenger bob both have their negative aspects no one doubts that
barber's
bird
sp Swedish
he's been filmed
i'm
one
decided to
pakistan
hantz
press
baker
no
deborah
arto
my
b
uh...
in
the
I love the manatees.
And you know what I mean?
But I've had my things with those other fish.
I've had my deal with those.
I've had my experiences with them.
Not fun.
But no, and then the other thing, what do you think about the proliferation of like jellyfish in the ocean now?
It may have something to do with the Earth's magnetic field.
What kind of creatures would feed on sex drugs and sea slime?
Huh.
Hmm.
Oh, yes.
Wonderful.
Kind of look like this.
Like some sort of a lackadaisical lump just sitting there.
If they are threatened, they can sort of turn their skin from a leathery kind of rough texture into a gelatinous, of course, slimy material,
which is a nice way to get other organisms or predators to sort of go away.
Kind of shape-shifting almost.
They can also eviscerate.
So if something is going to attack them, they basically eject either this mass of white sticky tubules
to...
Act as a decoy or to entrap predators, or they actually eject their internal organs as again as a decoy,
and then they kind of slowly crawl away.
Crazy.
But amazingly, they can regenerate their internal organs within three to five weeks.
What's that smell in here?
Some kind of...
Well, it might be the smell of herbal air freshener.
Somebody's wearing some fancy French perfume.
I just took my shoes off.
That's all.
Set a spell.
I'm sorry.
I smell like one of them fancy French whores.
Should I put my shoes back on?
No, you're going to leave them off.
You better tell me how much you charge.
It was just Pete Goldie burning his socks.
Pete knows his onions.
Are you selling your wares there, little lady?
A lady?
Oh, there's no lady this time.
We had the women before.
I thought maybe my friend would come in tonight, but she didn't.
That's such a sad statement.
She was too worn out to come, but she still might come.
Too worn out.
Too worn out to come.
We had women before.
Exactly.
Oh, hell no.
But now you're going to have to be the woman.
Well, I...
Here's the wig.
Here's the dress.
There's either going to be blood on my knife...
Now, boys, it's time for your Bible lesson.
Or something on my something.
You're going to be the woman tonight, Philo.
Halloween is Satan's Christmas.
I just wear my mask backwards.
Mask backwards?
I just put that little girl mask on.
The back of my mask.
My head.
We smell sausage.
So it's a sausage party, huh?
No, that was the back mask.
My scat rat, though.
Who's back masking God?
Well, uh...
Bat Masterson.
Once when the West was very young
There lived a man named Masterson
He had a cane and wore a derby hat
They called him Bat
Bat Masterson
Yes.
How easily it washes away.
I can tell you guys are a couple of years older than me
because you can remember another couple of seasons of television.
How about Yancey Derringer, Riverboat Rogue?
Did you ever watch that one?
Yeah, that's before that time.
Yancey, Yancey Derringer, Yancey...
You remember him, right?
Yancey Derringer.
Derringer popped out of his belt buckle.
And he had a little...
He had a little mustache and he was on a riverboat
and he gambled and he had a fancy shirt
and it didn't last long.
He carried a derringer.
Yeah, he was known for his derringer.
He only had one shot in that little popper
so he had to make it count.
But it was a deadly derringer
later published by a certain Donald...
Donald Wilkes Booth or somebody like that.
But he could make it come shooting out of his sleeve.
Yeah, like that.
With a little spring on it and it would...
Oh, he was a bastard.
It would deliver itself in his hand, right?
An unfair advantage.
What can I say?
Oh, you're talking about a gun.
I thought you meant his...
Yancey Derringer, you moat.
No, no.
I sympathize with the one pop per load.
And then how about Jim Bowie, Jim Bowie?
Hey, pop.
As a fellow agent, you know, things change.
Jim Bowie, Jim Bowie.
Remember that one?
Yeah, the Jim Bowie show.
But how about Casey Jones?
The Casey Jones show with Alan Hale Jr.
You're old.
And Red Rock.
And Casey Jr.
You're old.
His blade was tempered and so was he.
Because of what he's done.
And destructible steel was he.
God, those guys are so old.
I'm never going to get like that.
Well, not very much to tell you about the apparatus itself, Wilma.
Except that here in this little pad under his head
is an extremely sensitive and high-frequency response piezoelectric oscillator.
A quite complicated design.
Yes, I guess so.
Yes.
And I've succeeded in tuning it to receive the minute electronic impulses
that emanate from his brain.
Yeah.
Through the medium of a super-radiating protoniform.
Oh, yes.
I...
Oh, what?
In other words, we're able to obtain sufficient amplification
of the impulse output to register audibly
through a process of thermionic note magnification.
That's all there is to it.
First of all, we'll have to see if it's going to work.
Switch in the electroniformer.
Give the electroniformer a sort of eerie sound.
Yes.
And now, when I switch on this microphone and speak to him,
my words will be registered directly on his brain.
Not through his ears, you understand, but directly on his brain.
Uh-huh.
And if we're successful,
we'll receive his subconscious response through the loudspeaker.
Go ahead, Doctor.
Now, young man, what is your name?
I...
I said, what is your name?
Bob!
Well, now, it works!
But, Doctor...
My invention's a success!
Doctor, what happened?
It works even better than I thought it would.
He didn't move his lips, though.
It read his mind.
Great day.
It doesn't seem possible.
Yes.
Yes, by all means.
Listen.
Yes?
Did you, um...
Did you find anything new and different when you came in the 25th century?
Oh, a great deal.
Thanks to Dr...
Doctor...
The greatest scientist who ever lived.
Uh, what's this?
Nowhere in the universe is there a scientist...
Please, please.
...or done anything to think that you could...
Now, now, now, wait.
Wait a minute.
Yes?
Judge, go on with what you were saying.
But he's the man who invented the moon.
Very true.
Nothing wrong with this machine, Doctor.
Where else have you gone?
Well, that's hard to say.
But first to Mars, where we held King and Archon's Tiger Men.
Yes.
Then to Saturn, and the Saturnian moon, Venus, Jupiter, and even far off Pluto.
You see, Wilma?
May I ask? May I ask?
Surely. Go ahead. Go ahead.
How did you happen to come...
In 1919, I was in the lower workings of a beautiful girl soldier I met when I first met him.
Oh, Wilma, Doctor.
The finest and bravest girl who ever lived.
Yes, yes, yes, well...
All of a sudden, the whole thing caved in on me.
Yes?
Some kind of peculiar gas was released.
It kept me in a state of suspended animation for 500 years.
Well...
Then the ground shifted and let in fresh air, and I woke up.
And when you woke up, you were hearing Hour of Slack number 1000.
415 from subgenius.com.
Which included, from the beginning, titles by The Large,
the song Crazy about Bob was by the great, groovy Neptune,
The Large did the Maestro Bob collage,
and then we heard clips and the title song,
from the beginning of the Larry Blamire film, Trail of the Screaming Forehead.
The heaving bulk of the show was from the Ask Dr. Howe show of February 22nd
on Radio Valencia in San Francisco
with Dr. Philodrummond, St. Palmer Breedies of Lies,
electronics expert Pete Goldie, and Reverend Ivan Stang.
There were more collages by the large and a song called Crazy Glue by Fishbone.
The bad guy affirmation is from Wreck-It Ralph.
There was and will be a long string of media barrages
supplied by Reverend Royal Decapitator.
PR news is lemur.
Praise Bob and see subgenius.com for all other details.
The music in the background is by the Flying Ryan Brothers.
Praise Bob.
And now, from Reverend Just John, this.
They say if you've never eaten human flesh and been glad of it,
you want a life when Y2K hit.
All the stopped clocks, cars, elevators,
burning buildings,
pet sacrifices,
grey men,
stalking the streets
with washboards,
and calendars.
But, maybe, we're past that far enough to settle an issue that sparked the strangest
spate of bloodshed between two straggling camps.
Exactly when did the millennium start?
All because there's no year zero.
I said on December 31, 1999 and I say it now, let's declare a year zero.
What is now 1 BC becomes year zero.
What is now 2 BC is promoted a year to 1 BC.
And so on.
The fact that we now call them BC shows that they've been redated at least once before, eh?
This will have an effect on commerce.
The current, no year zero arrangement requires computers to have an extra hitch in their algorithms to deal with dates.
Incorporate our year zero in that, simplifies things.
Each access to a date calculation takes a millisecond or two less to work.
Multiply that, times billions of transactions a day,
and it's simple.
It starts to make a difference.
I don't think the change hurts anybody, and it's a boost to textbook publishers everywhere.
Plus, since simply changing all the dates will feel like a paltry reason to publish a new edition of a history book,
this will be an opportunity to include recent events and improvements to existing articles.
A learning renaissance will undoubtedly follow.
The only problem I see is the name, year zero.
It's been used before, by unsavory outfits.
We don't want to be seen as emulating.
So I say, call it the year of Bob.
Year of Bob.
Christianity still gets thousands of years referring to their savior.
Well, I think my faith, the church of the subgenius, deserves at least one.
And what are you giving up?
Nothing.
Year of Bob.
To the subgenius radio ministry, Hour of Slack.
For free information, write to
P.O. Box 181-417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118
Or see www.subgenius.com
Praise Bob!
For Sire, there is no more money.
We gotta get some money!
That dirty, perky, sharka-packed, flackin' wharton,
Philip Bunker Burton,
Perkaluma Burton,
Dirt and Bustin' that!
Beef. Beef. Beef.
Friends, we're glad you listened to this show, and we're even more glad that some listeners have donated enough to help us keep on going for another couple of months.
Not just this show, but subgenius.com and all the other archive sites.
But if you truly love Bob, and want some of that slack back to rebound to you,
you should go to subgenius.com front page, or especially the radio page, or the catalog store pages,
and help out financially as best you can.
Now, we know what it's like to be on the brink of total poverty,
and we don't want any subgeniuses to make their own money.
We want to help people like you,
and help you get through the hard times.
We know what it's like to be on the brink of total poverty,
and we'd love that.
And if you're the type of individual who's not afraid of any of this stuff,
and doesn't want to be a part of the隙,
we're ready to help.
We're ready to help.
Foundation. P.O. Box 181417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118. Thanks for anything you can do to help
let there be slack.
Subliminal Hypno Corporation.
Free pills.
Kill me.