Around Dard City and in the Territory on West, there's just one way to handle the killers and the spoilers, and that's with a U.S. Marshal and the spell of...
The Self-Genius Power of Swatch!
I gotta say, I'm having a better time here than I think I've ever had in any devotional.
Thanks so much to everybody who's brought us out here, this is great.
For people who wanted to bring us out, we love playing for Stang.
Everybody here is laid back.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh no, this is a much cooler crowd than we've been with in a long time.
I tell you.
They're actually smeared.
It's not great.
At that little protective world you're in, maybe somehow the Sudanese orriancraft may be
a bigger threat.
Yeah.
For sure.
Oh no.
All right.
from within that glowing cloud.
Radiation slack out, fall everywhere.
Radiation slack out, last for a year.
Radiation slack out, it's already here
in this beautiful music world.
Get ready, ping-pong, they're coming after you.
From that big glowing cloud to that cloud.
Radiation slack out, fall everywhere.
Radiation slack out, last for a year.
Radiation slack out, it's already here
in that beautiful music world.
Get ready, false one, they're coming after you.
From that big glowing cloud to that cloud.
Radiation slack out, fall everywhere.
Radiation slack out, last for a year.
Radiation slack out, it's already here
in this beautiful music world.
Get ready, normal's coming after you.
The normal's coming after you in that beautiful mutant world.
Radiation slack outs fall everywhere.
Radiation slack outs last for a year.
Radiation slack outs already here in this beautiful mutant world.
Radiation slack outs fall everywhere.
Radiation slack outs last for a year.
Radiation slack outs already here in this beautiful mutant world.
Woo!
That was, of course, the Mutant Mountain Boys live at 50 Next Day.
Another song by them will close this show,
which explains...
The concept for PR News by Lemur is entirely composed of an hour of slack delivered in the wind
before a live audience of the undead at Wisteria Campground on July 4th during 50 Next Day.
The panel participants include Dr. Howell, Dr. G. Gordon Gordon, Priestess Pisces,
and yours truly, Reverend Ivan Stang, all heard here fighting over seating at Tarzan's radio studio.
You don't have to... I mean, we don't want you to sit directly in front of that.
I'm not sitting...
I'm not sitting directly in front of it, you twiddlehead.
I'm sitting... I'm almost in Dr. Howell's lap, man.
What's wrong?
What if you sit over here?
And what do you want for Christmas, little man?
Well, I don't know if he's even going to show up.
Then we'll be all over that.
Oh, he does one show.
Why don't you move over here?
He does one show in the sweltering oven, and we have to do two.
Move over.
Oh, thank you so much, Ivan Stang.
Sit next to Stang.
On the left hand of Stang.
I'm so pissed I bit the shell off my tooth.
Ah!
Well, welcome to our next segment of the Hour of Slack,
Bobcast live from the...
Live and in color, Dr. Howell.
I mean, sorry.
Hello, am I there?
Hello, can you hear me?
The hysteria stage.
Yeah, right, right.
I am not enjoying this.
Are you Reverend A.P. O'Stacy?
Good to meet you.
I thought that might be you.
Yeah.
Well, look at you.
It's almost human, except for the third nostril there.
That's quite nice.
Well, friends, it's another live Hour of Slack here at Wisteria at 15X Day.
This is the last show we'll have to do.
Thank goodness.
The world ends tomorrow at 7 a.m.
And you may die.
We don't do any shows en route, on board the...
Is that all?
Oh, yeah.
We'll continue partying on board the sauce.
Alien karaoke and so on.
Do we have to do a show from the sauce?
There's two.
Well, it's all voluntary.
You can have Muam be you on the show.
Oh.
It already knows what you're going to say anyway.
It's like God.
Yeah.
I'm glad somebody does.
God.
I'm going to change the slideshow in the background to subgenius art pretty soon.
But I've been having a bit of a psychological struggle.
Oh.
Those who've been following the Scrub Genius Forum may have noticed that...
Sometimes when I become anxious, this character named Stangor, who's much more confident, takes over.
The bane of subgenius art.
Stangor is a vicious virus.
I'm so old that I didn't actually start playing video games until this year.
Somebody gave us a Wii console, which is the game platform for old people and babies.
Hey, hey!
What are you guys talking about?
Oh, nothing.
Why not?
Nothing.
Nothing at all.
Oh, no.
We were just talking about aged things like whiskey and stuff like that.
Yeah.
No problem.
Gee, I wanted G. Gordon Gordon to see some screenshots of this game.
It's called Monster Hunter Tri.
That's Stangor, you see.
Ah!
Uncure.
He's not a naked barbarian.
I'm having an anxiety attack.
That lance he's carrying costs thousands of zenies and the lives of many slaves and dinosaurs.
It's worse than I thought.
There's the village as seen from the hill.
He really believes it.
There's a little...
He has...
Oh, there's Weedor.
Notice Weedor does not wear armor.
She looks a hell of a lot better than Stangor.
Yes, I've been keeping Weedor naked and ignorant as much as I can because when she's covered up with armor, what's the point?
Barefoot and pregnant in the kitchen.
What?
Weedor is...
He doesn't have a kitchen.
He keeps her pregnant and in the swamp or something like that.
She's not really as vicious as Stangor.
He's got a nice set up.
Stangor loves to kill.
Now, I've been criticized a lot by this old man here for being into this video game thing.
Who are you calling old?
I never said a single thing about your pathetic obsession with that game.
Princess Wee and my little sister, Priestess Pisces, have both observed that I seem to be a lot easier going now that I'm able to kill a hundred demons.
I've been told that I'm better than dinosaurs every night.
Do you remember what they said in Georgia?
I go to bed every night wishing that I could take that sword and kill a hundred bobbies.
I can let my bloodlust drain.
Even more than a hundred bobbies, what I'd really love to kill is only about a dozen or so old doctors.
Oh no.
Elderly subgeniuses.
How can you talk to us like that?
Why did you assume I was talking about you?
Well, you're always talking about me.
No, I'm always talking about Philo.
And where is Philo?
I don't know.
Where is Philo?
You're conveniently missing.
When did you join the church? 1980?
Yes.
Yeah, well we joined, Philo and I were in there in 1978.
Hey, who paid for the first issue of the Bleeding Stark Fist of Dobbs?
That's your fault, not mine.
Okay, okay.
This is all being recorded on thermo-magnetic recording wire.
It's being recorded?
Yes, it is.
Every utterance that proceedeth from thy lips.
I take it all back.
No, I had nothing to do with it.
I had nothing to do with paying for anything.
Too late.
I've never given, I've never paid my $35.
What is said cannot be unspoken.
Never, and I never will.
I will never give you $35.
I might give you a few thousand Paraguayan pesos or something.
It should have been $33.
No, we got $10 out of you.
To approach the golden mean.
Well, yeah, that's true.
But it's not because I felt sorry for you.
We're like shuffling around in the gutter finding empty wine bottles and emptying them.
You know, I know how it goes.
But there might have been a genie in one of those bottles.
A genie in one of the wine bottles?
Yeah, that's why he was looking for them.
A wine-soaked rummy of a genie.
If I may say, I know my voice sounds rough, but I would like to recount what happened to me last night,
which was the kind of thing you read in a cheap novel or something.
Move a little closer to the microphone.
Okay, how about this?
All right.
Okay, so what happened was I went down to visit a minister whose name was unknown,
and being generally a beer drinker in my later years,
my golden years, my autumn years, if you will,
I went under his suggestion and had a margarita.
And it was a very good margarita.
I hadn't had one in years.
And then he made me a second one.
And I think he was like a friend I had who was a bartender.
He came in, he'd mix you a drink, and he'd put four shots in it because he was your buddy.
And you went in for a quick one, and next thing you know, you're shit-faced.
So anyway, I did get shit-faced.
And I stumbled up the hill.
Crawling my way back to at least a bed.
And being a drunken married man away from his woman,
I had a surge of weakness.
And I must confess, noting that I had a small vial of antidote pudding in my pocket,
I went to a wide open upper level place,
opened my mouth with my head back and concentrated.
And yes, a face.
Something bat got me immediately.
You can go ahead and say.
A face fucking bat hit me right away.
And it was ecstatically painfully good.
They grow them big out here.
And I applied the antidote pudding.
But it was a young bat.
And they're inexperienced and it's too quick.
And when he would withdraw, he hurt my throat.
Which is why my voice sounds like this today.
And I apologize.
It's the kind of thing, you know.
A drunken sailor goes out and finds a hooker.
Well, you know.
It was nice.
But I feel very ashamed.
And that's why I'm confessing it to this whole congregation.
Very well.
You are absolved.
Thank you.
I feel no more shame.
You were hoping to turn them on.
What?
They don't even know what a face fucking bat is.
I've got news for you, Dr. Gordon.
Your voice always sounds this way.
No, it doesn't.
So I have to assume that you've had face fucking bat dicks pulled out of your face.
No.
I've had like a half a head of them pulled out of my throat too soon every day for decades
now.
Come on.
You couldn't confess?
If you're going to confess, confess to the whole thing.
Well, I just thought they were like out of body experiences the whole time.
Most of us only do that for the antidote pudding.
Well, of course.
You'll die if you do the antidote pudding alone or the bat alone.
Well, yeah.
Well, I told you.
I was up here and I was ready for it.
You have to have the bat.
I had my antidote pudding.
The minute he withdrew, squonk, you know.
And it was okay.
But he hurt me.
I didn't like that.
Some people don't like face-fucking bats.
Folks, face-fucking bats are not what they used to be.
Well, if it weren't for them, there'd be a lot more mosquitoes than there are.
They do help keep the mosquitoes down.
Yeah, but now they're so used to going around finding people drunk like me on a hilltop,
they're not even chasing mosquitoes.
They're looking for throat.
Perhaps the slight miasma of alcohol made you a prime choice.
Well, sure.
There's a drunken throat.
Go for it.
Yes, but they have difficulty detu-messing when the alcohol molecules affect the back of their brains.
But I can remember when a dear friend was so terribly drunk he got gang-raped by...
We had to truck antidote pudding into him so he wouldn't die.
And that can happen anyway.
And that was disguised as a teabagging session, I seem to remember.
I thought that was a political party.
All historical moments.
Water under the bridge.
Driven by...
A resistless current of time.
It's lust and libido that does it.
But now here we are.
And after all, you've been given a throaty Tom Waits-like voice by your experience.
So really, there's no reason to complain?
And I've just remembered, I have a divine excuse.
That's right.
We all have a divine excuse.
I take it all back.
Nothing of that happened.
As a holy man, I declare that you can do anything you want to from now on.
Now, that...
Doesn't mean the cops can't do anything they want to do back to you from now on as well.
But, you know, just as far as Dobbs is concerned, I promise you...
So, Dr. Howell, have you ever gone out for a little...
You've got a get-out-of-jail-free card as far as Bob goes.
Good Lord.
How did that get in there?
How did what get in there?
It's one of those pictures that shot by.
It was something Nenslow sent.
Oh, look, there's Dr. Howell with his pets.
You must be looking at a little mirror.
Because I can't see a thing unless I swivel completely around.
So, I thought Nenslow was dead.
Is Nenslow alive?
Nenslow is alive and hated.
Very much alive.
Hate keeps him alive.
Many subgeniuses live on hate alone.
What's wrong with that?
But it's not the wimpy hate.
I hate my job.
I hate my hair today.
This guy is stealing my rent right now.
This old fart here is...
Stealing my rent.
What?
Shut up, Stang.
I'm not even going to talk.
We don't...
Who remembers who did what rent?
Give me a break.
Oh.
Somewhere...
Actually, it's funny.
There are types of most of this stuff crumbling in a closet.
Somewhere.
Where we could prove one way or the other for one of the sets.
Which one of us said it first?
And listen to ourselves being drunk for hours and hours in some Chicago hotel room.
But it's an ecstatic church.
It's a church of ecstatic freedom.
Well, now, there's...
See, there's my truly...
True love.
There was...
What they...
That was a large...
Female paramecium.
Paramecium, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
I thought that...
Yeah, of course it was a female.
There's nothing queer about old Stang.
Actually...
Wow.
The paramecium's are...
Aren't they unisexual?
They're pretty much.
No, actually...
Basically, they commit syzygy, right?
They hook up and...
They do trade DNA.
Yeah.
Genetic material.
Yes.
Well, don't we?
Yeah, but in a more fun way.
Well, how do you...
They just come in.
Do you know if it's fun for a paramecium?
You'll see.
Okay.
I've got porn.
I've got shots of them.
Doing it?
Showing at it, yeah.
He's got bug porn.
I've got bug porn.
Yeah, later on...
In fact, I'm gonna try to supply an actual narration track.
We've got about 35 minutes of live dude, single-celled animals and micro animals.
Bug porn, bug porn.
Oh, sorry.
It's about...
Would you rather have the Doug porn?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I didn't think so.
I'm sorry.
I was just being funny.
The micro...
Are we supposed to be funny?
I know we're not, but we're supposed to be, okay?
I can't tell you how much better I feel since I got a good Mexican beer in my fist.
Well, I'm glad to hear that.
Thank you, Doctor.
I don't drink on the job yet.
How can you go to a job...
My jetty down here, but I thought the coffee set me up.
I have something for you people.
Reverend Stang, the...
He does not drink beer.
He drinks fermented apple juice.
He drinks hard cider.
Ha!
I drink hard about that.
It was not enough for the Continental Congress.
I drink beer.
There's nothing hard about that cider.
And James Madison.
Don't limit my options.
What...
Let me ask you this.
Does cider give you brewer's droop?
Brewer's droop?
That's not...
The man doesn't know anything about anatomy.
Terrifying.
Look, your sugar's bad enough.
I'm trying to avoid the yeast.
That stuff grows all over...
Brewer's droop, Stang, is a term...
It's hard in places under the monitor.
...used in the...
...in the UK and other places in the world where English is spoken to imply that a large
imbibing of certain malted beverages can let you not be able to get it up.
Hest, brewer's droop.
So you're blaming the cider for that.
I've never had...
I've never heard that.
Maybe it never came up in my case, as it were, so to speak.
Well, in your case, it would be brewer's droops.
Right.
Yes.
Or at least one of them usually works.
I mean, if I'm really drunk, sure, most of my peckers...
Hey!
...are useless.
Did you ever get that ad on?
There's always one that is up for the job that's a little more sober than the other
ones.
Now...
That's his story and it's sticking to his foot.
But let's...
I don't want to make the one penis feel inadequate.
Well, it's...
You know, that comes up enough.
This subject comes up all too often.
Only because you bring it up, Stang.
It keeps me awake at night.
A man, just a tiny genetic mutation gave him multiple peni, okay?
Okay.
Well, what's the big deal?
They have fish born with extra fins.
And people born with extra fingers.
You had extra penises.
Why are you so proud?
God compensates the Stumpy.
There we go.
God...
One time, one time, jokingly, I called this man Stumpy.
And he has never, never forgiven me for it.
And I don't understand why, because he's not Stumpy.
Stumpy can hide in small places.
Stumpy could climb into Stangor's backpack.
And he could get up inside Stangor's...
He's killed.
You know, now I think about it, maybe starting a Stumpy thing might have turned into the
Stangor thing.
Like a tiny parasitic organism.
Let me think about this for a minute.
Stumpy, Stangor...
Stumpy can do these things.
Stangor killed a dragon.
Wait until Dr. Philo Drummond gets here.
It'll really be bad.
Oh, yeah.
Philo's gonna change the equation.
But before he comes, perhaps we should outline for our listeners the sequence of events to
follow.
It's pretty simple, really.
Uh...
We're going to sit here yakking until four o'clock.
And then I guess there's Bulldada auction?
No, they've canceled the Bulldada...
I believe the Bulldada action...
Auction...
Action...
It's canceled.
My main job is performing a wedding this evening.
That's right.
And of course the feasting of the...
Mmm.
Yeah, the eating and drinking.
And the Mutant Mountain Boys are playing tonight.
They're new to X Day, but not new to me.
I've seen them every year at the Devotional.
Oh, yeah.
And I hope they'll be doing their Devo songs and their Subgenius hymns.
They have three...
At least three Subgenius hymns that are tearjerkers.
And there are some very lovely...
I'm going to try really hard to make people cry at the wedding, just so you know.
You can laugh, but hopefully you will be crying at the same time because it's also touching
and sweet.
And it is, too.
I'm gonna boycott it.
Okay.
Well, and we've got another wedding on Friday.
Reverend Millar.
Oh, that must be Princess Girlfax.
You know, this church is getting so cutesy, feely, touchy, sweetie pie.
You don't live up to your name.
I mean, it's like we're gonna have what?
Bake sales?
What is this?
The PC Church of Bob?
I mean, a wedding dinner?
You get bake sales.
We decided yesterday we are going to start having bake sales.
Oh, oatmeal cookies.
Yeah.
And we are gonna do everything all the other churches do.
Oh, I'd have a...
We're gonna have a slice of lady Connie tea cake, please, with my cup of...
And bingo, Sting.
Are we going to have bingo?
Yeah, bingo.
And I go, well, everything I get.
Sometimes I think I've lived too long.
Everything every religion does.
The Sundance of the Lakota will be later on today.
Well, we have a lot of sun here, so...
All of the males will be expected to pierce their chest with an eagle claw and be suspected.
And hang on the top of one of the port-a-potties.
No, no, no.
Jim's already done that.
We use the port-a-potties as the sacred sweat lodge.
I'm sure...
You mean the jinkum fermentation.
You pass out from waves of pain, which take you to the new transcendent level.
That happens when you use the outhouses, Doctor.
I see someone I'd love to have on stage with us.
Why?
Because she's not wearing anything, Stang?
Is that it?
Yeah, we've never had Pantiera up here on the...
Well, she...
We have some cheesecake of her posing while we talk, but...
Why did you talk?
Pantiera, you're welcome to come up here and block the screen any time you want.
Oh, you are so...
Or Susie, although Susie has lost her voice completely.
You think...
You were bragging about how you were raped by one face-raping bat.
Susie pulled the entire train of face-raping bats.
Late last year...
I was.
I've got video...
Yeah, but I can't afford two gallons of antidote pudding, man.
All I had was a small vial I could carry with me.
Yeah, you're still enjoying it, aren't you, Susie, you...
You faithless, faithless woman.
Susie is actually one of the more coherent and clever radio personalities, and she always
manages to deliberately screw up her voice at X-Day.
So as...
She's trying to save herself, the situation we find ourselves in.
Did you see how Susie responded to that Dr. Stang reverence thing?
Well, the same way she responds to everything.
No, she just turned around and walked away.
You scared Susie off by being so mean.
You drove her away, you uncouth fellow.
You are.
You're a brute, Stang.
But we need a girl up here.
How come...
We need some gentleman...
Not you, Teeters.
Poor Princess Wee has run away.
I bet I know what she's doing.
What would she be doing?
Well, it's a hope that that may be remedied in the fullness of time.
Another thing.
The pockets of Pisces can...
You told me...
You told me there was not only going to be lots of naked, lithe bodies here, but there's
going to be wall-to-wall fropping.
Yeah.
And I've seen like one frop stick, two pipes, and a bag of ditch weed since I've been here.
I was talking about Starwood.
Oh.
Never mind.
Aren't you going to stick...
That's...
Starwood's cheap.
It's only, what, 160 bucks or something like that?
People pay to go to Starwood?
No, they pay through the nose.
Through their nose rings.
But they have more options than we offer.
Well, yeah, obviously they got some frop, if you...
The way you're talking about it.
And they pay the preachers.
Do you preach at Starwood?
Yes, I do.
I preach my ass off at Starwood.
I saved my...
I saved my really good stuff.
I saved my really good sermon for Starwood because then I'm not preaching to the saved.
I know what happens if I start preaching here.
Everybody will get up and leave.
Watch, they're already starting.
They'll...
It's like, oh, I've heard Stang a million times.
He's always saying the same thing.
Bob's...
Boy, I have heard a cheap cop-out for giving a second-rate sermon.
You know, you really just...
You have contempt for us, Stang.
Now we got a pretty voice.
Something in contrast to...
She's trained in the arts of telephone seduction.
Don't listen to her, people.
I'm...
I do get accused sometimes.
Some of the old dirty men who call and say things like, you have such a sweet voice.
Where are you located?
Do you give them a PayPal?
Yeah, honey, just send $100 to this and we'll call you back tomorrow.
I should.
I should, but most of my clients where I work in my con job are lawyers.
Ah.
So I'm not really...
You don't want to keep them unhappy.
You work in a nest of...
A nest of serpents?
I do, I do.
I will...
Well, Pisces, you have my sympathy.
Sympathy.
I've known a couple of subgenius ladies who were telephone sex performers.
One of them was Reverend Thea, who I married to Pope S. Lilith at an ex-date several years
ago.
They subsequently broke up.
But Thea...
I was on the phone with Thea once, not on her job, on my job.
Oh, no, of course not.
You just happened to call her.
We were talking about a church thing.
A church thing.
Oh, yes, yes.
She was going to run a revival in Columbus.
I would like to talk to you about a revival.
And she goes, oh, oh, Stang, I'm going to have to hang up.
I've got a client calling, but I know this guy real well.
He'll be done in five minutes.
And sure enough, she called me back in almost exactly five minutes.
I guess she knew exactly what this guy wanted.
I don't think I could do it.
I mean, I've talked to these people...
Maybe she knew he was a quickie.
Yeah, he was real quickie.
But see, it costs them by the minute.
Right.
Ah, now that is a clever idea.
I would...
There's so...
From everything I've heard from people who've done it, these pink sexual fantasies are really
boring.
They're just...
It's so vanilla.
Baby, tell me, what color is your underwear?
And you say, why?
Talk to me in baby talk.
They're black and lacy, and they're a little bit damp.
I'm excited that you've been calling.
Stop it.
I might have to get off the stage if you don't stop that.
Tell me where little yetis come from.
Actually, I'll be explaining that tonight at the wedding.
That's a complicated procedure.
It is.
Really, it's more complicated than...
It's not as easy to understand as you might think.
Well, yes, 16 different stages before ejaculation and fertilization.
I mean, it takes a week.
What do you want?
Yeah, most of you all aren't parents.
And...
I see quite a few parents.
So you don't know the facts of life yet.
You think you do, but...
You're practicing.
Not until the infant goes into its eighth stage of development and starts having sex with you do you know how rough parenthood really is.
We sanded off some of the rough edges and made it more palatable for PG-rated audiences.
Pregnant audiences?
PG.
Well, to tell the truth, I was worried about shocking...
Sonny Gordon.
No, no, but when I was in...
Tender sensibilities of such nice daughters.
Oh, yeah, that was a long...
No, that was an expression for pregnant.
She's PG.
Then I met them.
Hey, you know Cynthia?
Yeah.
She's PG, man.
No.
Who got her?
I think it was Tom.
So you're going to go back to the totally raw version then when you perform that...
No, no, I like the cleaned up one better.
It's funnier.
Why would it be funnier?
Does it have monkey noises in it?
It's funnier when you talk real dirty in a polite way, I think.
I think so.
I think it's funnier when you talk about Miss Kitty and Mr. Snake.
One day Miss Kitty met Mr. Snake and they went playing in the bushes together.
And Miss Kitty and Mr. Snake rolled and wrestled and rolled and wrestled and then one day a
baby came out.
And that's the birds and the bees, or the kitties and the snakes.
Some people don't have snakes, though they have fish and worms, and some people don't
have kitties, they have jaguars.
Oh, yeah.
But you know, it's just the same story they told me when I was in school.
Yeah, it's exactly the same.
It hasn't changed a bit.
They just rotate the animals.
Amazing.
My entire education from my wonderful mother about the birds and the bees was essentially
I could sum it up like this.
No experience.
Slot A, tab B, don't do it or I'll kill you.
And that's all I was told.
Pretty much the very...
Yeah.
They're gonna try to put that in your hole and if they do, I'm gonna beat your tush.
And that was about it.
And then you grow up and you find that it's not just slot A and...
Sometimes it's slot A and slot A and sometimes it's tab B and tab B and sometimes it's slot
A and slot A and tab B and sometimes it's tab B, tab B and slot A. And then sometimes
there's this little...
It's a little corner piece that is like a slot A and a tab B.
And the slot A and the tab B plays with the A and the B and it gets very complicated at
that point.
But they don't tell you that at first.
And they don't tell you the variations of slot A and tab B. And sometimes slot A is
really hard for tab B to get into.
And sometimes tab B is...
Yeah.
It's been bent around a little bit.
It's a little floppy and doesn't seem to stay just right to go into slot A.
Man, I'm getting so hot over here, man.
Now that she's explained it that way, I've just realized that Bob has been raping me
for years.
You didn't know that?
No.
I thought that was just...
You thought it was slot A and slot B.
Slot A and slot B.
You know how Bob is.
Well, he told me he was raising...
He'll do anything.
He told me it was me he was pumping slack in to raise my levels.
So you know what I mean?
You didn't even get that, huh?
That's the slack injection.
We've done that.
Yeah, slack injection.
Yeah, you get it.
Bob gives you a slack injection and it protects you from anti-slack.
That's right.
We've been making fun of the Catholics all this time and turns out I've been the altar
boy for Bob all these years.
Well, we've known that, Stang.
Everybody knows that.
Bob's little bitch.
That's right.
Everybody...
Didn't they have that on the Facebook page, the hate page?
Stang's just Bob's bitch.
You know that?
Yeah, you're right.
He just bends over.
No.
If that had been on that page, it would have been funny.
Well, that's true.
It was not funny was the problem.
You can talk bad about us all you want as long as you're funny about us.
Funny is the key, yes.
That is the key word.
You have to have a sense of humor.
And basically, if you don't get the joke, fuck you.
And if you don't have a really good sense of humor, you'll find that the tab B is actually
a lot stiffer and sharper than you remember.
And the tab B will sneak up behind you.
Because the other thing is...
There is a slot A and a tab B, but there's also a slot C that everyone has.
Ouch.
I was trying to forget about that.
And sometimes, the tab A and the slot C happen.
And some people enjoy that, but some people call that butt hurt.
Excuse me, but did you help the Marquis de Sade write 120 Journeys of Sodom?
Only 97.
Oh, wow.
Well, folks, I got to say that's one of the most stimulating and exciting pieces of whatever
that was that I've heard in a long time.
I may not be able to...
The best part is that it was completely radio safe until Stang talked.
Oh, yes, of course.
Don't bite me, G. Gordon Gordon.
Yeah, but now if I have to stand up now, I'm going to have to hold my notebook in front
of my crotch so I can get out of the classroom.
Man, geez.
The tabs with the slots and the slots with tabs, those occur.
And then sometimes switch.
I'm sorry.
Sometimes people switch their tabs to a slot and their slot to a tab.
I can't believe we're talking about this on the radio.
And actually, the great thing is that for some of us, we can get pseudo tabs that are
temporary tabs that we can use so that we can have a tab to insert into a slot.
Just put it on my tab.
I'm totally slotted out after that one.
That's all there is to it, man.
Well, I think...
That was...
I suggest we get...
I think we should give the good priestess a round of applause for a most
aggravating sexual lesson.
Yeah, this is the first time I've realized how sexually abused I've been all these years
by JR Bob Dobbs.
He never lets me see his face, and he always uses slot C.
Does he at least play with your tab?
No.
Well, that's not fair at all.
He didn't give you the courtesy of a tab.
No.
No, reach around for old Reverend Stang.
That's a shame.
But I'm up for one.
If anybody wants to offer...
I'll take you up on that, Stang.
Gordon, you don't want to make up for what Bob left out?
That's okay.
I was just kidding.
Now, the key to remember is when the saucers arrive, these sex goddesses have any configurations
of slots and tabs that you desire.
Right.
You do have to...
You know, they...
Sometimes they will go in your mind and see some of your past dreams or perhaps the things
that you were wanking to those lonely nights when you really just didn't feel like going
out on the town and you typed a few words into the internet.
So if your thing happens to be, for example, a goat tab, the goddesses can provide you
with goat tabs.
They can also provide you with squid slots.
Tabs.
And they can provide you with multiple slots and tabs.
And in fact, just because they're called a sex goddess does not mean that they are...
Particularly have a configuration.
The configuration is entirely up to you.
However you would like your sex goddess configured, they will do that for you.
Tomorrow, I have to get up at 6 o'clock and I'll meet everybody else who's awake at the
Stone Circle down there.
We'll wait for the saucers.
And by 7.15, I will look just like Kim Kardashian.
That's my immediate...
Why?
Huh?
So I just want to feel myself up.
I think she's really pretty.
Okay.
And I always wondered what it'd be like to be Kim Kardashian and feel yourself up.
I have a question.
Always hanging around the Kardashian embassy.
I'll say it again.
As Bob said, watch two girls making it.
Hell, I'd rather be two girls.
Two girls making it.
Agreed.
Well, who wouldn't?
But that'll be temporary, probably.
Who knows?
I might enjoy it.
Reverend Stang or Priestess Spices, I have a question about the sex goddesses because
I'm not really into...
If you wanted one of them to be like SpongeBob SquarePants, would they?
Absolutely.
Okay.
All right.
You realize SpongeBob is very porous so you don't have to get a cleanup rag?
If you wanted.
Well, of course I wanted.
Why would I want to have a SpongeBob SquarePants?
I'd ask the question if I didn't want it.
Yeah, SpongeBob SquarePants.
Mm, mm, mm.
He does have a lot of pores.
Yeah, a lot of holes there, man.
Jeez.
And he's absorbent.
Mm-hmm.
No mess.
No strain.
Wow.
You know, I never thought of that.
Ha, ha.
Yeah, no, you didn't, Stang.
That's why I am the mind behind...
That's why he's gory.
He's a germicidal sponge.
I'm sure.
Well, and he may be a spermicidal sponge too just to be on the safe side.
You know, and that could be, you know, you could get some of the foam and...
Anyway, we're giving Gordon ideas.
Oh, yeah, I'm getting a lot of ideas.
This is the most fun I've had since I used to go on rat shoots with Bob and, you know,
SpongeBob.
Well, we're also going to venture into microbiology.
Bob and SpongeBob.
Microbiology.
Yes, Stang, could you tell us about the tabs and slots of the micro world?
Well, we're...
Bob and SpongeBob.
We're going to be looking at some movies.
I could put those on right now, I suppose.
Do they have tabs and slots?
Actually, several types of micro animals only have slots.
They are...
What's the word?
Slotted?
No, the...
Parthenogenetic.
All female all the time.
Yeah, parthenogenetic.
Yeah, my favorite...
I thought that was a song back in the day.
Rotofer.
I think that was Rotofer.
Yeah.
You know, Rotofer feels like a walking
girl.
A
women will find a way to not need
the tab.
Well, that's the thing.
I mean, that's some of the
idea. Nature
will try anything.
And the
reproduction methods
of some of the so-called
lower life forms are
remarkably complicated.
They are inventive and elegant.
I raised a mosquito
from an egg.
Man, not too long ago.
Eternal enemy.
Bloodsuckers of a feather flock together.
First
he was a little invisible
egg. Then he
became something that looked like a
robot biplane.
Still microscopic.
You can see him with the naked eye
twitching in the water.
They're the little things going like this.
You don't want to drink them.
Nice porn, Stang. I like that.
Then they turn into a face-hugger
phase.
They turn
into a face-hugger phase.
They turn into an enormous,
jointed, vigorous thing
that's larger than the adult mosquito.
Right.
Finally, one day I looked in the Petri dish
and my little face-hugger
had magically turned into a
full-grown mosquito.
And I took the Petri dish outside
and I released him into the air
and he landed on my hand
and I killed him.
Because I'm not an idiot
and I don't need more mosquitoes
sucking my blood or putting
their hair
parasites in me.
You saw the light of sanity
at the last moment.
And avoided the light of malaria.
I think it's interesting
that a preacher
and a minister in a church
would raise a blood sucker.
There's a big old
wasp right behind me.
There is an extremely large wasp
hovering around
to punish those who are
not as ardent
as they should be.
Yes, anyone who's not laughing,
that wasp is going to sting you.
It's a big one.
I thought it was a kid with glasses.
But anyway,
friends, some of you probably
unlike me, attract
mosquitoes because you're somehow
edible. Some of us just
happen to taste better than others of us.
This should make you feel
better. They have
their own parasites
and mosquitoes and blood
suckers and diarrhea.
Every creature
has more creatures inside
of them. In fact,
the vast majority of animals
in the world are parasites
living inside of other animals.
We free living creatures,
so to speak,
are in the minority.
It's like that poem saying,
they say that fleas have little fleas
upon their backs to bite them
and little fleas have smaller fleas
and so ad infinitum.
Jonathan Swift.
That's right.
Thank you, Dr. Howell, for your literary prowess.
You know,
the only reason I didn't quote that was I wanted
you to be able to feel smart for a minute.
Well, that was sweet of you.
That was nice, Stang, and I'm not used to that kind of thing.
I'm not a bad guy all the time.
Just some.
Yeah, most.
Furthermore, parasites are a driving engine
of evolution.
Parasites cause
evolutionary development to take place.
Which brings up a question of
why are we as subgeniuses
not looking into becoming
better parasites for the
conspiracy?
In my opinion, the conspiracy is an enormous bloated
parasite with a grossly swollen body
draining the tiny subgeniuses.
Not the other way around.
Actually, I think that we have ascertained
that we are officially trying to be parasites.
We're not very good at it.
On the body of the conspiracy.
In fact, Father Joe Mama did an interview
with a very inspired sermon about that
that I know I've played on our Slack a few times.
If he was here, he could probably recite it from memory.
He could fill it in.
Because unlike most of us, he never smoked pot.
What's that?
Papa Joe Mama has been a straight edge guy.
Actually, we did find out that he would drink,
but not what we were drinking.
Because he had better taste.
He's very ship-shaped and squared away.
And some can see this.
This noble idiot running up and down the road
in the hot sun for exercise.
To be fair, though...
He keeps himself fit.
He is very fit.
And I've got to say, he's probably going to be
the first one to get the best saucer with the best guns.
Knowing the way the world works,
he'll be the first of us to die.
That's what I was about to say.
It's always the joggers and health nuts that kick off first.
The ones who are so healthy that don't take pills
and don't have to get a shot.
The ones who get things stuck in their heart or in their ear
or in their knee or in their leg.
The most desirable specimens.
Who have all their glands.
You know what I mean?
Why do you think the people who work at health food stores
are so pasty and sickly looking?
My dad always used to say,
how come when you go to health food stores,
they look like the most shriveled,
shrunken-chested,
pale-faced,
straggly, bearded,
concentration camp survivors?
If they're so healthy...
Oh, I'm sorry.
I thought he was talking about you, Stang.
I'm...
No, you can also look at the prime example of someone
who seems to be absolutely not healthy
but cannot seem to die,
which would be Dr. Legume.
Um, you know, I could never imagine Dr. Legume saying,
you know, I really should take my vitamins today.
Perhaps death didn't want to embrace Dr. Legume.
Perhaps. Maybe. We don't know.
I mean, it could be a situation of they're afraid that
if there is an infernal afterlife available,
that Legume will take over.
And, you know,
we know how he is here.
Can you imagine if he was placed into the depths of
a Dante's Inferno-type hell?
What circle of hell would be able to
just withstand the pure power of what is Dr. Legume?
I think the place would run a lot more efficiently
if Legume was in charge.
Amen.
Thank you, thank you. I mean...
Well, somebody pointed out during the two hours
that Legume ran the Church of the Subgeniuses,
by God, the trains did run on time.
That's right.
And the airplanes, too.
Backwards.
That was amazing.
They were backwards?
They ran backwards and forwards.
You know, it's funny, I don't recognize half of this artwork
that's being projected.
I mean, I downloaded it.
I did see it at one point.
Didn't you set up this slideshow?
Huh?
Well, yeah, but that doesn't mean I remember most of it.
I thought you were just streaming forward.
When I did, I was just on my phone,
I think it's something called the Foo-Kung.
Foo-Kung or whatever,
that stupid pile of stupid pictures
is that people are so enamored.
Oh, I fell in the Foo-Kung hole!
I can tell which one's in for 18 hours!
I couldn't get out for 18 hours!
It's so funny!
Oh, my God!
The Foo-Kung hole?
Yeah.
The only good thing I've seen on the internet lately
is tits and bacon, my God.
That was a good place to be.
Was it bacon on tits?
No, it was little pictures of wonderful breasts,
little gifts being unveiled and veiled and wiggled and jiggled,
alternating with little pictures of sizzling bacon.
Doesn't get better than that.
Tits and bacon.
Come on, man.
There's a pattern out there for a bra made out of bacon.
Good God.
With a matching panty.
Well, I found bacon you can cook in a toaster.
There you go.
I wouldn't recommend wearing, at this particular junction,
in this particular campground, a bacon bra or undies.
Yeah, I don't think a bacon thong would do very well.
I do know that, as Hal and I were discussing,
that certain yellow jackets and wasps are attracted to bacon.
Is that true?
They eat meat.
And I can't imagine that having a wasp
attempting to eat a bacon bra.
A bacon bra or thong would be pleasant.
You better let him eat it.
Not attempt to dissuade him.
And then he'll fly off and get some sugars for dessert.
Unlike bees, bees only want the sweetness.
But the wasp wants the meat and then the sweetness.
I thought wasps wanted complete control of the American judicial and government system.
They own it already.
That's our...
No, not anymore.
We've got that Arab guy for president.
What's the matter with that?
That's right.
The Kenyan traitor.
Kenyan tree?
I got to tell you, though, folks,
watching the politics these last few years
has been one of the most entertaining monkey show
that I have seen since Ringling Brothers went into bankruptcy.
Stick around. It's going to get better.
Well, I really miss Herman Cain.
Yeah, I do, too.
Susie pointed out that we really...
that we should have planned to vote for Herman Cain,
because then it would be like,
okay, let's just go straight to the point.
Let's finish the job.
You know?
If we're going to turn America into a circus,
let's do it to the max.
It's already been turned into a circus.
And it's not even a very good circus.
Even the wild animals aren't very good.
They're not wild enough.
There's not enough blood.
I mean, it's so tame.
Think of the children, GGG.
Think of the children.
I'm thinking of the children.
I would like to...
Don't get me started on children, okay?
Eventually.
Okay, you want G. Gordon Gordon's take on children?
A new child, that's a $300,000 diarrhea machine
you've just brought into the world.
And that's the way I think of children.
It's a miracle of life.
Yeah, so is being able to go to the bathroom regularly every morning.
That's a miracle of life, too.
That doesn't make it pleasant or not messy.
You know what I'm saying?
These people are throwing their sperms and eggs,
and you've got this world full of little shitty kids everywhere.
Little children, midgets, tiny people with little bitty hands, little feet.
They won't listen to you.
Like, you've had a good comeback for people who...
I'm sorry.
The medication is kicking in a little slowly.
The child is father to the man.
People who brag about conditions of their birth,
such as their looks or their wealth that they inherited.
As if they had anything to do with it.
There's one now.
You just gave it.
Legumes' comeback for them was,
congratulations on falling out of a cunt,
which is actually their only achievement.
I thought they got squirted out.
They happened to do the same thing all the rest of us did.
They just fell out of one that was rich.
Well, they didn't do anything.
They got squirted out.
They didn't even have to work their way out.
That was the reason for the bad language and the bluntness of it.
Dr. Legume, bad language and bluntness?
Yeah, that's why we're...
The tape is being changed.
Everyone stop being funny or trying to be funny.
You don't need to videotape things.
It's the same as yesterday.
I really don't have to have tape videotape for four of us sitting here.
I can use the footage from last year and use this year's sound.
But you get the ambiance.
You get the ambiance, dang.
The ambiance.
From PR News in Washington,
I'm forbidden from opening a bank account.
President Obama was relieved.
Released from jail today after posting a $1 bond.
Because not.
PR's reports that this is PR.
Tennis in four sets since 1938.
We have details from PR's club.
76-3-6-4-3-6-7-5-8-4-36.
PR News.
This is PR.
I can't complain.
Because here I've been handed three cans of octopus.
It's labeled pulpo in Spanish.
Of course.
It's goya.
The very good stuff.
They've got wonderful products.
I have to tell the truth.
I kind of swore off eating cephalopods
because there's so much that has been discovered
about their level of intelligence.
They are.
They're intelligent and have a sense of humor
and are clever.
And they build houses.
Yeah, I kind of got to the point where I felt like...
I mean, there's the crappy little prawns.
I mean, really small.
Squid probably aren't that smart.
Squid are not that smart.
I kind of started feeling like every time I ate an octopus,
it was like eating a chimpanzee or a dolphin.
You don't want to eat chimpanzee.
That can make you mighty sick.
But the cephalopods are the highest intellects
the invertebrates have managed to produce.
And, Stang, did you hear about the giant triassic cephalopod monster
that...
The really were giant prairie squids?
This thing is quite astonishing
because they discovered that it had been killing ichthyosaurs
and then making fake octopus tentacles
out of their bones on the bottom of the then ocean
in the triassic age.
The creature itself was never found, but...
Dr. Howell, they found fossils of cephalopods?
Yes.
They found that...
You know the ichthyosaur is not a dinosaur, but an archosaur.
They grew their largest in the triassic,
although in the jurassic they were fairly big.
In the triassic they were whale-sized.
Well, sir, the food of these ichthyosaurs
was a kind of cephalopod called an ammonite.
They had a coiling shell.
But when certain ichthyosaurs pursued certain ammonites,
into the very deepest part of the ocean,
they were seized by enormous tentacles,
crushed and torn apart,
and then the possessor of these enormous tentacles,
whatever it looked like,
arranged the bones,
particularly the vertebral bones,
in patterns on the seafloor...
They had art.
You're saying they had art, Dr. Howell?
This art is a picture of cephalopod tentacles,
and that has fossilized.
Also, the bones...
The bones of the squashed ichthyosaurs laid in place.
And it was speculated,
though some scientists reacted angrily to this line of speculation,
that a huge, intelligent, and probably lonely,
giant cephalopod created these artworks.
That's... I would think...
Living in the black depths of a prehistoric ocean.
Yeah, I think that's a very good postulate,
but I was thinking maybe...
Maybe it was kind of like the...
What did they call those people in New Guinea
who built the fake airplanes to try and...
Oh, cargo culls.
Yeah, maybe they were...
But there are no people at this time.
No, no, I think the cephalopods were
building things out of bones
to get the ichthyosaurs to come down.
Well, whatever it is,
it has to be large enough to crush a whale-sized animal,
and large enough to take its bones out
and...
make a 40-foot-long tentacle-like things on the seafloor
out of its bones, the vertebral bones.
This song is dedicated to Princess Wee.
Wee!
That's it.
Remix!
this one is
.
piano plays softly
I was bound in sorrow by the mass conspiracy
When the toilet beckoned kindly
Then it drew me to come see
And the sewage formed a message
It said, one, three
Oh, one, three
I then heard a voice from Dovestown
Gently saying, follow me
There's a crop farm down the valley
There's a crop farm past the rain
There's a crop farm
In your sorrows
When your mind is going insane
There's a crop farm
When you're burdened
There's a crop farm where you stray
There's a crop farm
Heavenly crop farm
Crop or kill me
He did say
piano plays softly
Sometimes my friends say
You can't even see me
And I'm tempted to despair
Then a son, my dear savior
Of short duration and I care
You would pay to know exactly
What it is you really fear
You would pay to know exactly what it is you really fear
And I'll guarantee you my brother
You are probably a pink
But there's a crop farm down the valley
There's a crop farm past the rain
There's a crop farm in your sorrows
When your mind is going insane
There's a frop farm
When you're burdened
Where you stray
There's a frop farm
Heavenly frop farm
Frop or kill me
He did say