Who's there?
The self-genius, power of swatching!
Now I know all about everything.
What?
Yeah, yeah, yep, yeah, yeah.
Are there any weirdos here tonight?
Well, I'll be damned.
Are there, by any chance, any fucking weirdos here tonight?
I'm so surprised.
Would there, by any chance, be any fucked up weirdos on drugs and alcohol here tonight, my friend?
Well, in that case, I want to hear a praise bow!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Now, there's some few of you here who may not know a damn thing about Church of the Subgenius,
and I will make it short and sweet,
because we are, of course, recharging for the amazing architect.
My God, man, I never...
I never saw such a thing.
In the meantime, friends, if you could just bow your heads,
and don't feel self-conscious or anything about this,
but if you could just join me in a solemn moment of sacred noise!
Praise Bob! Praise Bob!
Praise fucking God damn, damn God Bob!
Yes, my friends.
Open your hearts, close your minds,
unzip your lips and bend over and pull out that wallet.
And if you're not, you're not going to be able to get out of this.
Because Bob is coming.
And when I say that, it's not like when you say,
Jesus is coming, that means Jesus is on his way and is going to arrive.
When I say Bob is coming, that's exactly what I mean.
If you come tonight, you will see that man, Bob!
And boys, now boys, don't worry.
It ain't queer if it's Bob, and even if it was, so what?
Um...
Friends, there's only three things that I want to say.
There's only three things you need to know about the church and the subgenius.
That's Bob, spelled over there, of what?
That says 808. Well, close enough.
Slack.
And I think some, I can tell that some of you here know about Slack.
But the other thing you need to know about is the conspiracy!
Now, um...
But before I get ahead of myself, there's only there...
You know every church has to have some kind of rules and laws.
We only have one!
And I think some of you know what it is.
It is, fuck them if they can't take a joke!
And believe it or not, as cynical as that may sound,
that is indeed a philosophy that you can live by.
Now, uh, the church of the subgenius was founded in 1953 by this salesman,
this incredibly, magically talented salesman, J.R. Bob Dobbs,
when he was seized up in the spirit by an alien space monster
called Jehovah One, which has disguised itself as God for numerous religions over the centuries.
And he told Bob that throughout history there has been a conspiracy of normal people
stealing away the slack of the weirdos, the abnormals, the misfits, the disbelievers,
and most important of all, those who will believe anything.
Can I get a praise Bob?
Praise God!
So, he founded his church.
Not on a rock, but on a sandy, shifting beach of hypocrisy.
Because where's any religion without its hypocrisy, I ask you?
It's not that we love Bob that much, it's that we love the idea of everybody else burning in hell!
We're just like any other religion, you know, that's what it's all about.
But, it is a do-it-yourself religion.
It is a disorganized religion, a non-organization for non-joiners,
which makes it hard to make a buck off this thing.
All subgeniuses, by definition, are different.
If any two are alike, one must die!
So check your neighbor out, make that decision quick.
The only thing that we as subgeniuses have in common
is that we have nothing in common with the normal people!
Now, so many people ask,
but okay, I've seen this man Bob tattooed on the butts of punks and old hippies and babies everywhere.
Who is this guy?
Well, you've heard the traveling salesman jokes of antiquity.
Those are based on a real person!
Now, some go, no, they can't, yeah, Bob's gotta be made up, he's too good to be true!
Well, here's the thing.
Look at the word subgenius.
We didn't call it Church of the Genius, okay?
Almost anybody can qualify.
What we're saying is that the conspiracy has been misdefining intelligence all this time.
It's not intelligence, it's the truth!
That's what we're talking about.
That's not what counts.
What counts is sense, common sense, sense of humor, and dollars and cents!
And, uh, after the show, Sense Amelia, I guess.
But the thing is, Bob is not smart!
When did being smart ever get you a date?
Well, actually, in this crowd, maybe it did.
But, what he has is luck!
He is lucky!
The reason that Bob can do magic and you can't is he doesn't know any better!
He walks the path of least resistance, friends.
That is his path to slack.
And it can be yours, too.
But here's the thing about slack.
We're not gonna tell you what it is because we can't!
Only you know what slack is for you!
Now, for some people, slack is sitting in front of the TV set and smoking a beer or whatever.
For other people, like me, slack is working your ass off at what you wanted to be working your ass off at!
Woo!
We're not here to forgive your sins.
Bob Dobbs is not the kind of messiah that is...
He's not that well connected.
And on top of that, he does not actually give one flip of a shit about your sins!
He doesn't care about your sins!
He comes not to forgive your sins.
He brings not forgiveness, but an excuse!
That's all you really needed was an excuse.
And that is what he is for.
Now, and he is here to bring a reminder of slack.
Now, slack is, as I said, it's indefinable.
You might call it something for nothing.
Now, a lot of people think, oh, this church and subgenius is just all about money.
Well, that, too.
Slack is connected to money.
Slack is connected to sex.
But Bob is slack!
Bob is money!
Bob is sex!
And Bob is coming!
Woo!
For boys, girls, and everybody else!
Nobody in between!
Also, here's another thing.
You don't want to be using Bob as a crutch.
You let Bob use you as a crutch.
Ask not what Bob is smoking in his pipe, for he is smoking you!
You throw yourself into that damn pipe!
Go into his lungs and...
But we are not asking you to give your heart, soul, and mind to Bob, just your money.
And here's why.
This is a culture.
This is a culture of built-in planned obsolescence.
When they sell you a computer, they know how long that warranty is going to be good for
and when it's going to break down.
Bob is a short-duration personal savior!
After a while, you get tired of Bob and move on to the next personal savior.
It might be some porno star or Star Trek, God forbid.
So, the only thing, friends, that we have standing in between us and Slack,
is that conspiracy I mentioned.
Now, a lot of you folks know about the Q-Dub.
A lot of conspiracies.
There's going to be one for everybody.
There's the JFK conspiracy,
the UFOs crashing in Roswell,
the 9-11 truth-er conspiracy,
worst of all, the fashion conspiracy!
Friends, don't worry about a one-world governor or one-world religion.
You should be worried about a one-world advertiser!
That's who's going to bend you over and not even get the money.
That's who's going to get the common decency to give you a reach-around.
Friends, we're not asking for love,
because this is a war.
It's really us versus them, and this time we're us!
For once, friends, we're trying to lead a return to decadence.
Not trendiness, but decadence.
Luckily, I will be followed by two hot chicks and one other ugly old man.
And then by Architect,
who will return.
In the meantime, friends,
yeah, this is a free country, alright?
You're free to work your ass off, right?
They even have a machine now
that can tell when you're thinking.
It's called a television.
And if it's off, you're guilty.
Friends, all we're trying to do is tempt sinners away from the devil.
We don't give a head fuck where you go after that.
We believe in the God
that doesn't want us to believe in it.
That's how ornery we are.
We are unbuckling the Bible belt
so that its pants will drop to its ankle
and it will be forced to gaze unflinching upon its own private desires.
Ah, yes.
Bob said,
don't just eat that hamburger,
eat the hell out of it.
And that goes for everything you do.
Uh, I don't practice religion.
That's what I preach,
because I'm not the kind of person I'm preaching to,
as Bob said.
And I could go on and tell you about the sex cults
and the deviation and the special
ex-pay drills and so forth,
mind control that we tend to do on you,
but I have to confess something to y'all.
There have been times
when I used to look out on the,
what's normally a pretty small audience of subgeniuses,
and I'd think,
God damn, some of these people are real nerds.
I would get frustrated
at the sheer nerdliness of half of the subgeniuses.
But then one day I suddenly went,
duh!
That's what this is all about!
It finally sunk in.
Yes, they are fucked up,
because there really is a conspiracy of normals
stealing away their slack.
They are fucked up,
and that's why J.R. Bob Dobbs is their god.
And that is why you,
you my friend,
you must repent,
quit your job,
and slack off while you still know how.
Question authority.
I see a few people out there
have been reading their prescriptures.
Bob is not,
now believe it or not,
some of you Bobbies are going to be surprised by this,
Bob is not the answer,
but neither Christ,
nor Christ Bob is anything else.
But there's one thing I want to leave you with,
and that is that one rule of Bob,
the one rule of the church of the subgenius,
fuck them if they can't take a joke!
Praise Bob!
Praise Princess Pisces!
Praise Dragon Con!
And all you fucked up weirdos on drugs!
Look away from the pings to that billowing pipe
From your life of work and toil
Look away
There's a hole in your soul that's burning you alive
Where slackdom will never decay
Look away
Your circle of eternal slack
From the pings to that billowing pipe
Look away
A triple bubble, you're burning back
From the pings to that billowing pipe
If responsibilities getting heavy to bear
And your blind walk through life's old sphere
There's a hypnotic man who is beckoning from
Is his disembodied head always there?
Look away
Your circle of eternal slack
From your pings to that billowing pipe
From your life of work and toil
Where slackdom will never take a joke
If your conflicts with normal bring struggles and strife
May then onward your rantings ensue
Look away from the things to that billowing pipe
That's awaiting in the temple you
Look away, look away
From the things to that billowing pipe
The Mutant Mountain Boys
Recorded live at the Devotional
And before that yours truly delivering
Subgenius 101 at DragonCon
Before that the Mur
Friends, we still have in the show stash
Some great weird cover songs
Of many already weird artists
As well as some heaping leftovers
From the mating of this show, Hour of Slack
With Reverend Susie DeFluzzi's
Bob's Slack Time Funhouse on WREK Atlanta
With guests St. Byron Werner and Priestess Pisces
This is a good point for
A free lesson
Which would be
Rewardian vs. Emergentile
The easiest way to describe the difference
Between Rewardians and Emergentiles is
Mo is the Emergentile
And Larry and Curly are Rewardians
Well actually Curly is the Rewardian
And Larry is the Pink
Right
You might say
I mean not that Larry really was
But he was
You know he would fit that archetypal
Right
Whole thing
That Larry shaped whole in the culture
And some people are both
Yeah
I'm both
I swing both ways on that
Yeah well I'm both on everything
I'm a pretty hardcore
Emergentile
But I've studied under some of the great Rewardians
Like J.R. Bob Dobbs
Dr. Philodrum and Princess We Are Doe
Right
Those who
They reward themselves first
For the work they're going to get around to later
Am I a Punishian then?
Because I don't reward myself
I castigate and punish myself
You're an insane Emergentile most of the time
So you might as well face it
That makes me feel better
Anybody who edits like you is a serious Emergentile
But there's some Rewardian elements in there
Your index finger is an Emergentile
It's giving me a witch finger
Yeah
Which finger?
Susie the floozy
Who is flawless looking in every other way
Except for this one bunged up finger
Deformed finger
Which is her clicking finger
Which when you're editing on a computer
It's starting to split into two fingertips at this point
That's a clicking gout
And it's not even my bird finger
If it were my bird finger
It's all gnarly and scary
See I have to switch back and forth
In order to not do that to my index finger
I use my bird finger to click things
This finger is so deformed
When I pick my left nostril
It cleans out my right
Wow
Mine are just crooked
This is hurting my hands just thinking about it
It's reminding me of work
And keyboards and computer screens
It's so great to get away from that
But the real key thing is
Is that an Emergentile gets slack from work
Right, oh yeah, that's the whole thing
Absolutely
It's the only way to get slack
From not doing anything close to work
Or from procrastinating
Right
Which is why it's weird
There's certain people who are both
I have to procrastinate
As part of the ritual that builds up to the work
Yeah, if it is a desperate last minute
I can't tap into that part of the brain
That's like, oh my god
I've totally screwed up
And you have to think outside the butt
That's where the brilliance happens
I wing everything
So I don't know where that puts me
But I enjoy doing it
Everybody
It's a good thing
Wants a good thing
Everybody
Ain't it true that
Everybody's
Looking for the same thing
Ain't it true
There's just no doubt
There's some things that you can't do without
And that's good
That's good
Ain't it true
That everybody's just like you
That the sun that shines
You got yours
And you got mine
And that's good
Everybody's just like you
It's true
Everybody wants a good thing too
Everybody's just like you
It's true
Everybody wants a good thing too
Wants a good thing
Everybody
Ain't it true that
Everybody's looking for the same thing
Ain't it true
There's room for doubt
Maybe some things that you could do without
And that's good
That's good
Everybody's just like you
Ain't it true
That everybody's just like you
Everybody wants a good thing too
Ain't it true
That everybody's just like you
A great big hand
And everybody
Can understand
What life's to be
What?
This is Mark Hosler of Negative Land, and you're listening to the Hour of Slack with your host, Douglas St. Clair Smith.
I revealed the top secret information.
Yeah, on Wikipedia.
Oh, that's right. Oh, man.
When I told my son I was in Wikipedia, he said, so did you put the entry there yourself?
There's just no way to impress my kids, I'll tell you.
Before the ID there, that cover we heard of D.B.
I suppose that's good. It's by Great Balancing Act, who are on MySpace by that name.
From Volume 8 of Not Necessarily Beautiful But Mutated.
Good luck finding a copy, as only 100 of those were made, and I have number 98.
Thanks to Rev Wilder at neo.rr.com.
But now, another rarity, available only with a new DVD from NegativeLand.com, the 180Gs.
Ring!
This is Tom Crott, maker Colin from Rollercoaster.
Rolling Stone magazine.
Can I speak to someone in Negative Land?
No!
Can you comment on the connection that was made between your music, uh, and the ex-moodles last month in Rochester, Minnesota?
Now it begins!
Can you tell me, off the record, is there any backwards masking on the song Christianity is Stupid?
What's Negative Land?
No!
We have to listen to that word!
No, no, no!
Yes!
The lyrics, I'm already going to fail.
The word gold might not fit, but it's nice.
But I also brought a loved one from New York.
Because what they've submitted to Daddy Boy Scuba.
Today, I got a good one from bands called the Vampire Damstал.
It's the band drafting.
And when it comes to killing you, the life that you would set for me is in the book.
I'm doing a psychopath, murdering werewolves, murdering marauding me.
It was the kind of murder that came from friends and neighbors that didn't make sense.
You didn't understand.
The reality is true.
This is a joke.
It's a monstrous joke.
Gentlemen.
Does real life seem to joy?
Are you?
That was not the case.
Or sensationalism.
A vicious tale about a maniac.
Murder and music.
You give it up, punk ass.
Murder, and music, or sensationalism.
Enough typewriters.
And enough time.
Murder, and music, or sensationalism.
And one of them will eventually come up with the King James Version of the Bible.
It's your Bible.
We don't have enough data.
We need you.
It's your Bible.
We don't have enough data.
Your Bible.
It's your Bible.
We don't have enough data.
We just don't have enough data.
It's punky business.
And that's why I'm saying, even in my views, the King James Version of the Bible.
Data.
Too much data.
He was not a homicidal maniac.
It's a murder.
He was.
Did not show any mercy on your lord.
Signed.
Send a W住m a little my hair to the basement.
The easiest thing to do is do what he did.
Why me, Lord?
Apologize.
I was foregone as a dead man out of mind.
He apologized.
Like a broken vessel.
Well, that's America.
Why me, Lord?
I consider it a dream.
And you're overreacting.
Oh, wretched man that I am.
You shall deliver me from the body of death.
I'm going to have to cut it off now.
We're overreacting.
We'll be back after these messages.
Here is a smartly styled, softer, beautiful, new, wider rear end,
which was made bigger and lower to provide greater visibility
that your family will boast of for many months to come.
Drive this great rear end,
and you'll thrill to it as thousands already have.
While we're at it, if you were at Dragon Con
and you have met an attractive woman,
don't have sex.
Yes, because the attractive ones aren't women.
I saw a couple of Wonder Woman out,
uh,
very statuesque,
extremely statuesque Wonder Women
with large hands and Adam's apples.
Yes.
Now, if I was cool, I'd say,
but that wouldn't stop me.
That's a real big if, though.
Yeah, I...
Well, it's a medium-sized if,
but you can call it a big if if you want to.
Well, sometimes it's a small...
You're like that little chicken walking the floor
That if shrivels up when it's cold.
It's a little older.
Well, yeah, but, you know,
when it gets angry, it gets a little bigger.
It's a large if, quite large if.
No, it's a small if, it is small.
It's a very small if.
Ice cube, match.
Ah!
Yes, yes, yes.
It's like my brain.
Big, small, big, small.
Up, down, up, down.
Right, left, right, left.
I'm big, you're small.
You have the horror.
Yeah.
You do have the horror.
We got a bad case of the horror, man.
Who's got the horror?
Oh, we all do.
We all do.
It's the horror.
It's the worst with him, though,
because Stang has had the horror for, like,
second longest.
Philo's had it worse.
What was her name again?
It's Stang.
Leora Watt.
I got a woman, see?
No, no, I think it was Cecilia.
But the horror spreads actually airborne now.
It's mutated like that bacon flute.
Mm-hmm.
Give him squeeze.
Aren't we all going to have swine flu at the end of this week
from mingling and touching the...
I think we have to.
Apparently it's a government mandate.
There have been people sneezing.
No, no, I want the Andromeda strain myself.
I've already had it.
That's just your excuse.
You just want an excuse to drink squeeze.
Works good.
Give him squeeze.
Squeeze.
Uh-huh.
Have they remade that yet?
I hope not.
Yes, and it was terrible.
I watched five minutes of it.
It's like, oh, God.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
They've got to remake everything.
It's not even a good, like, bad film, bad film?
The original one was a Robert Wise film.
The original one was awesome.
That was another one of those pointed-out life movies.
The guy that did The Day the Earth Stood Still
and West Side Story and The Haunting,
all these great films.
I'll tell you an embarrassing story.
Oh, yay.
That was...
Andromeda strain was premiered in Dallas.
I was about 16 years old,
and I was a young...
filmmaker to be, I thought.
And I even had written a little screenplay.
It was inspired by a bad LSD trip.
Oh, kill a surprise.
And I was such an eager beaver.
That you read about in the magazine.
That when they had this premiere of Andromeda strain,
Robert Wise came to the premiere.
And I saw this old guy coming down the red carpet,
and I figured that must be him.
There was no inner media to look up what somebody looked like.
So I ran up to him and thrust the script in his hand
and said,
I'm a filmmaker,
and I love your movies and everything,
and why don't you look at this or tell me what to do
and how to run my life.
He was...
He kind of smirked and smiled and said,
I can't do anything with this.
I'm not going to take your script,
but you got the right idea.
You show some spunk.
Keep going, kid.
And so I...
Yeah.
I think he had spunk all over the front of him.
It was actually an embarrassingly juvenile and stupid script.
And he was right.
What he really should have told me was,
kid, you don't want to end up in Hollywood.
It's hell.
I sent my son instead.
And my son is...
You sacrificed your boy to America's media.
A member of the Directors Guild of America.
His name is right before Steven Spielberg's in the...
No, it's after Spielberg's.
It's Stan.
Yeah.
In the handbook.
Young Stan.
How about that?
Yeah.
You don't care.
We'll see you next time.
Keep going.
Let your mind wander.
Turn off your mind.
Relax and float downstream.
While you're thinking about that thought,
I'm going to insert a word.
Oh.
You ready?
Think about it.
Duck.
Don't you ever do that to me again.
It's an inside joke.
Yeah.
It was an outside joke now.
I confided in you.
You brought that up on the air.
I've been using my outside laugh inside.
It hasn't been very pleasant.
I tried my inside out laugh.
Oh.
Ow.
That tingles all the way down.
That's the background music now.
It's the Timothy Leary's presidential campaign theme song.
Or did you just switch to something else?
Actually, it was a gubernatorial campaign song.
Tim was going to run for governor of California.
He raised peanuts.
And John Lennon wrote Come Together Right as a campaign song.
Yeah, but it doesn't sound like a very good campaign song.
It doesn't tell you why you should vote for him other than he's got...
G.
Down below his knees.
Yeah.
Stuff like that.
Well.
That sounds to be a positive thing for the job.
Remember when we elected that guy with no feet and he screwed the country up.
That's a caveat.
And they told us up front the guy shoot Coca-Cola.
I mean.
Timothy Leary loved Bob.
That's damn nice of him.
He put out for Bob.
And he died, huh?
Yeah.
Bob died?
Damn.
We killed it.
Oh, yeah, yeah, that's right.
I was there.
And I used up all my film before it happened.
And all my tape, so I've got no proof.
He comes back.
Rob, but you can see Bob die in the subgenius video for Rise.
Over and over and over and over again and over again.
No, that was the old version.
Over and more and more and more and harder and faster.
People crying, people picking up the pipe and getting hit.
And more people getting hit.
And the band doesn't care.
They're sick of Bob.
Yeah, they thought it was hilarious.
I wept.
And there was that guy with that bone through his dreadlocks tied on his head.
It set me off.
I couldn't eat for a couple days after that.
Some sort of cannonball or something.
It was Dr. Gary Cabrera.
Cannonballism.
It's a very big problem.
Especially in the schools.
I noticed they said something in the parade about the cannons on one of the boats that was in the parade.
Always makes me think of cannonballism.
You ever get the cannonball runs?
Man, splashes everyone by the poolside.
Oh, God.
Yeah.
And on that note.
Oh, damn.
The show's not over yet.
Hey, we can turn the clocks ahead.
That'll work.
That's some of that subgenius time control.
That's right.
Daylight savings month.
Every day.
That's as much time control as I've had in my life in a lifetime in your church thing.
So, listeners, what we want you to do.
Is go ahead and just go to the clock next to your bed or even look at your watch.
And just change it randomly.
Yeah.
What time would you like it to be?
Why don't you have a little free will?
Why don't you be a clock teaser?
It's true that so far the only really useful form of time control that we have available to us is the snooze bar.
And patience.
Patience is another form of time.
People don't want to hear.
I mean, it's patience.
Staying?
Could you tell me about patience?
Now, we want to know.
What's patience?
Come on.
I know a clock teaser uses three hands.
Sitting here not killing you.
Oh.
That's, yeah, me not killing you.
That's patience.
I thought that was some of that tolerance crap.
No, no.
That's pure patience.
What's tolerance?
I thought my jokes were repetitive.
I think a clock teaser uses three hands.
Sometimes they have more.
I have, oh look, there's three on that one.
I'm just saying.
And a hole that says something about dates.
Not those digital clock teasers.
No, no, no.
I'm not into digital.
We're more into anal logs.
Susie, you're guilty, guilty, guilty, guilty.
I'm guilty as charged.
That's just his analosis.
You can build a house out of those.
I think Abraham Lincoln was built out of a house made out of anal logs.
This show is going downhill.
And still he walked on the ceiling from what I understand.
I'm worried if there's even a bottom to this show.
Where do you think the anal logs are coming from, Stang?
Don't you know nothing?
You've got to start from the bottom.
I feel like they're raining on me right now.
That's that hard rain that's going to fall.
It's falling on you.
It's Bob Dylan's fault.
Oh, man.
Oh, it just rains and rains and rains.
And then I say, well, get out from underneath the deck.
I've got a beautiful version of raindrops keep falling on my head done by Deadbolt.
Oh, I love Deadbolt.
The deranged greaser biker band.
God.
I'm so out of it.
I don't know who any of the cool new deranged greaser bikers are.
Or any of the new Japanese weird psychedelic bands.
We love you because you're so out of touch and anachronistic.
Hey, you know what, though?
I know every Devo cover band that ever existed, I think.
Well, that's a point.
Yeah.
He's hip in one way, one single way.
You're like Rain Man of hip.
Is the worker in a Devo cover band?
Virtual.
Devo Ween cover band.
That would be a great holiday.
Devo Ween.
Deve Ween.
Devo Wee.
And believe it or not, we have a Ween cover.
I'm glad I held off on it until now.
This is Reverend Basil of the Psychoskeletons from soundclick.com slash thepsychoskeletons.
The pigs made me sweat that they couldn't break me.
I didn't spill the beans no matter what kind of fancy things they dangled in front of my face.
Gotta wheezy.
Ween does that
special little song I like.
They do a song in a falsetto.
The whole song is in falsetto.
Dean Weebo.
Wow, you mean they got cheaters?
They got cutlets?
Well, no, no, no, not that falsetto.
I have a falsetto.
Yeah, I just want to look like a real cartoon.
You know, Russ Meyer used to take
Al Capp's Little Abner
and draw bigger boobs on Daisy Mae.
Now, get this.
The princess to whom I'm consort,
Princess Wee,
when her mom was pregnant with her,
she would sit, she was a big Al Capp fan,
and she would sit and draw
Daisy.
Daisy Mae.
And that's why Princess Wee
looks like Daisy Mae.
Yeah.
It's a good thing she didn't draw
a hairless Joe.
Right.
Wow.
Or a fearless Fosdick.
Or Earthquake Magoon.
Right.
Or Mammy Yoakum, for that matter.
Or Evil Eye Flegal.
You kind of favor Mammy Yoakum.
Whoa.
No, you kind of favor Mammy Jankum.
She stinks, though.
Man, her breath.
No, you're thinking of Moonbeam McSwine.
That's right.
I saw both of the Little Abner movies last year.
The musical.
They're great.
There was a black and white one.
Yeah, the black and white one's creepy.
It's got Doodles Weaver in it.
And the theme song of that
was partially written by Milton Berle.
It's got the line,
but when it comes to courting women,
Little Abner says,
gulp, gulp.
I'm just saying.
That's why he's so popular.
You told me earlier
that you personally heckled Milton Berle.
Yeah, the unveiling of the Hollywood Walk of Fame
star for the Three Stooges.
And there were guys that had climbed up
on top of this billboard
and were hanging over the side of it,
slapping the side of it,
yelling, Moe, Larry, jeez.
Moe, Larry, jeez.
And I was working at a little effects studio,
at that time,
and I wasn't going to tell them
why I wanted the afternoon off,
but I told them and they said,
go with our blessings and represent our company.
I was working at the right place.
Be our stooge.
And the only stooge that was still alive,
I hesitate to call him a stooge,
is Joe Besser.
Oh.
Yeah, and they had some stooge wives there,
and they had Adam West.
Stooge wives.
Yeah.
Oh, that's a couple.
You insulted Adam West,
thinking he was somebody else.
I saw this slimy Hollywood guy,
and I just thought I'd make fun of him,
and I yelled out,
oh, it's Adam West.
And it turns out it really was.
Oh, no.
Well, he's been our co-star on the show now.
His name's come up a couple of times.
For kids, you little tiny kids out there,
he played Batman in the TV show.
He's been on The Simpsons quite a bit.
A family guy.
He's the mayor of Quahog.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
Playing himself, essentially.
Matt said that, you know...
Family guy, I take it as a TV show or something.
Yeah, yeah.
An Earth show, one of those Earth shows, they call them.
Yeah, it's one of those feel-good, you know, emo...
Family.
It's about family and a guy.
Matt said they have a lot of stars on The Simpsons,
but the one that...
everyone wanted to meet was Adam West.
How'd their picture take it with such nerds?
Of all of those people.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Claudia Schiffer and all these others.
Oh, Mr. West.
Oh, Bill Anderson.
Yeah.
благодаря вам CHAR filosof trekking
О FC Mosby
нужна аб clauses на скоутер
has not been Todos los ap coaching
в т качестве стимул
multi-f 알고
It's really not easy
но навыков нет
the
mystery
world
pedophilẹ
These boots are made for walking, and that's just what they'll do
But these baby boots are gonna walk all over you
You keep lying when you wanna be losing
And you keep losing when you wanna not be
But, yeah, you keep saving when you wanna be changing
So it's right to say you ain't done right yet
These boots are made for walking, and that's just what they'll do
But these baby boots are gonna walk all over you
You keep playing when you shouldn't be playing
And you keep thinking that you'll never get burned
Ha ha ha!
I just found me a brand new box of matches, yeah
And what it is, you ain't got time to learn
These boots are made for walking, and that's just what they'll do
But these baby boots are gonna walk all over you
Are you ready, Boots?
Start walking!
Na na na na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na na na na
Oh, my pretty!
Babushka! The amazing and beautiful Babushka!
Bride of that lucky devil, Little...
Theodore from his new CD, Peace is Boring.
More can be learned about Little Theodore and Babushka at littletheodore.com.
And Theodore is spelled F-Y-O-D-O-R.
Before that, a short clip of, yes, adult pachyderm Stomp as performed by Rural War Room.
Also heard in the background.
That was an unreleased preview of the upcoming Rural War Room CD called Timothy Rah-Rah,
produced by Donovan Suit on MySpace as Rural War Room Records.
And now The Large.
You can do it, we can do it.
We'll pull together and build the largest wall ever created on the face of...
We'll pull together and build the l-lar-ges.
Larger, larger, larger, larger, larger, larger, larger.
We've got to protect America.
Once you got a 40,000-foot wall in place all the way around,
and it would have to be a mile thick or so to stay that high,
you got to have a net over it.
A large, very finely meshed but impenetrable net.
I'm going to go now and shut you off and shut everything off
and put on some kind of little thing.
If some music follows this, it's Poopy Necropondy doing Disco Boy,
but that's all kind of up to the time monsters.
Goodbye.
Goodbye. I'll spray my briny juices.
I'm dancing, baby, but my feet won't touch the floor.
I'm a disco boy. I'm a disco boy.
Oh, no.
I've been sleeping 20 years or more.
I remember a long time ago.
Yeah.
I've been looking for a chance to do.
I've been looking for some answers to.
Now I'm back to change your mind.
Now I'm moving right inside.
The world is turning kind.
I see what's going on.
Behind my back.
I'm a disco dancer, baby.
And I keep dancing on and on.
Disco boy.
Yeah.
I'm a disco boy.
Oh, no.
I'm a disco dancer, baby, but I think there's something wrong.
I'm a disco boy.
Oh, no.
And I keep dancing on and on.
I've been sleeping 20 years or more.
I'm a disco boy.
I remember a long time ago.
Now I'm back to change your mind
Now I'm moving right in time
In a world that's turned unkind
I see what's going on behind my back
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
I'm on
Yuck
Poopy Necropondy covers Disco Boy
and Poopy is on MySpace as Hello Poopy.
With a why.
Why? Because this has been the hour of slack
from the Church of the Subgenius
for which everything is at subgenius.com.
Praise Bob.
The background music has been from the
World War Room CD, Flaming Yawn.
And now, from Mr. Lemur, the news.
From PR News in Washington,
I'm caused by
arson.
An act of arson.
North Korea said today it has successfully
tested sexual misconduct
that would give it a second way to make a weapon.
North Korea already has
a lewd behavior enrichment program.
Experts believe the
communist nation is still some time away
from perfecting sexual enrichment
but they say there is evidence that
North Korea is working on the lewd process.
The German government
strongly favors sexual misconduct
led by a Belgian-based Canadian
auto parts company.
This is 309375.121995% PR News.
Space walking astronauts
at the International Space Station
have come up with a fundamental decision
regarding a buyer next week.
They'll bring back lewd sexual misconduct
on the space shuttle.
The Obama is promising to release
PR's reports.
The Labor Department says it is
PR News, Washington.