Well, right now, this minute, I'm going to do something that may overthrow the entire radio business.
I'm going to read you a commercial, but I'm not going to say a word about laboratory tests or quote you statistics or make medical claims.
All I'm going to say simply and honestly is this.
Ladies and gentlemen, try, just try, the finest money can buy.
Every advanced technique and control is concentrated on the subgenius.
Power of the sun.
Amazing face, how sweet the smile.
That saved the slack of me.
I once was lost.
But up I found no conspiracy.
Okay, so share.
Thank you.
I know I've been a sinner in my life.
That evil twist got us there.
Ain't no Christians.
I'm as I'm.
The new truth is the last.
When I hear that truth evolving.
Oh, I never saw.
The black man.
Never gladder than when I shout that name above.
Bob Dobbs.
Take a breath.
Just be unbroken.
By and by, by, by, and by.
There's a bottle.
Heaven waiting in the sky.
Bobby in the sky.
Now though I ain't no young'un.
One day.
I'm going to be old.
Got that subtle, deep old feeling.
Now it can't be told.
But I got my high five.
Got my jukebox.
Got my albums.
My night.
Got my box.
Got my
Should I ever lose my way now?
Bob.
Well, I got a smooth new map.
Yeah.
And if I run out of the secret Pilgrims, you know I won't doubt it.
Oh, oh, boy.
Rocket, I'm the king of the
during 18X Day last July.
You'll hear the whole song at the end of this show
because this is the first of the X Day cross-section shows
featuring many different performers on the X Day stages.
Praise Bob.
I'm by the window
Yeah
Hi everybody.
Do you guys remember how to do the call and response?
While we're testing your minds?
So if I say praise, what do you say?
Alright, let's try that.
While we're testing your minds.
I test the middle of my ears.
Can you hear?
I think I can hear you.
Praise.
Oh, that was weak.
Guys.
Right.
Let's try that one more time.
Are you guys ready?
Praise.
Yes.
Much better.
That's much better.
And they spelled it right this time.
They spelled Bob right this time.
Attention, subgeniuses.
The show is about to begin.
You have never seen anything like this in your life before.
We have gathered freaks, curios and curiosities from across the globe.
Here for you to see.
For your enjoyment.
Just thank God that you were not born like them.
One look at them will tell you all you need to know.
Come one, come all.
Only fifty cents.
See the living, crawling human-like subgenius things as they crawl on their bellies like
a reptile.
Okay, I think we got almost everybody here.
Let go all your fears.
The end of the world is here.
Welcome boys and girls to the end times.
The end times
Baby do not scream
Love he won't be mean
Cause you paid the fee
For the end times
The end times
Brothers and sisters let's give a big round of applause for
Finn Chooley who has felt the spirit of Bob and has been compelled
to come up here and say what he needs to say to you brothers and sisters.
Well well none of you wanted to come up so now
look what you gotta deal with. I got a hot mic
and I'm about to use it. As mentioned my name is the Reverend Finn
Chooley from the Clench of Our Lady of Perpetual Constipation and before I
begin I'd like to invite you all to participate in a
certain custom that we have here at my home Clench which is
instead of at any point you should choose to applaud the
ranter I want you instead to just boo the shit out of me
okay? In place of applause right? And if you want to boo
just boo anyway and that way I won't know if you're really booing me or not.
But anyway I'm going to reintroduce myself and if you'd please afford me the
custom of my home Clench I'd appreciate it.
And now everybody please make
and feel welcome the Reverend Finn Chooley
and the Reverend Finn Chooley.
You are not funny! You guys.
You're not the funny one! So unwelcoming.
Thank you very much. That was good. I feel right at home.
Then what I wanted to talk to you today about is why do we do that in the first
place at Our Lady of Perpetual Constipation?
Why do we have this custom of the audience booing the ranter?
It's because the audience is actually taking the role, playing the role
of the conspiracy in the rant.
While the one lone yeti stands up
proclaiming the word of Bob, the conspiracy all sits
down, facing the same direction, opposite the way
of the ranter. And in this way the audience
actually plays a very special role in making
the rant actually take the form
of that one subgenius standing up against the conspiracy. And of course
everybody takes their turns and it doesn't make you pink to play the conspiracy.
You know, not any more than a Christian playing the role
of Judas in a play, you know, for example, or anything like that.
But it helps! It helps to drive home the point.
Because when you're up there standing, facing
into the eyes, those pink eyes, and don't fly until you
see the pinks in their eyes, by the way, of the conspiracy. It helps you
to prepare you for that world in which you must encounter.
Because of course we couldn't be further behind any new lines.
This is their territory that we must all
negotiate. And as such,
ranting helps you do it. I'd invite
any of you to come up here, strengthen
those muscles, so that when you have to go out and face
the conspiracy, you can say, yeah, I did this before. I was at
X Day. I stood up. I ranted.
And if I can stand up and rant to a bunch of yetis booing
me, well I can stand up to any pink, certainly.
Shut up! You're such a wimp!
You're crappy!
Louder and funnier! See, there you go!
You feel that? Does it also remind you that the conspiracy
is within you, as you play that role against the ranter?
Because of course it is. Go to hell!
If there's anybody going
to hell that would like to offer a ride, I'm looking.
Now, there is something else I want to bring up with you guys.
Just how little the conspiracy actually
has to get you to buy in, to get you to buy in
all the way. I saw a pack of these, uh,
Oreos, I believe they're called, and right there on the
label, it said cookie. Okay? I think we're all familiar
with what I'm talking about here. But since when
is two chocolate-flavored crackers
stuffed with icing constitute
a cookie? It's closer to a cake
than anything else, okay? The lie's gone on long enough.
The charade must end now.
Oreos are not cookies. They're
crackers. Frosting. They're more sugar than anything else,
really. But we still like them, right?
And we call them cookies because it says that right on the label. It says cookie. So it must
be. It has to be a cookie. They couldn't put it there if it wasn't true.
But if they can get you to call
two chocolate-flavored crackers stuffed with icing a cookie,
then they can get you to not call out the fact
that the Emperor isn't wearing clothes.
You're lying!
And when you don't say that the Emperor isn't wearing clothes, and
nobody else around you is mentioning that the Emperor isn't wearing clothes,
well, then you've bought in.
That's the conspiracy right there. Just the kind of
passive compliance is all it takes. You don't really have to
sign on the dotted line, but you can opt out
at any time. And isn't that why
we're all here? Enjoy the rest
of your ex-day. May Bob be with you.
May your slack overfloweth.
And praise Brad.
String him up!
Let's give him a round of appreciation.
Hey Rachel!
Alright, so here, we're gonna try this.
I think you'll get a kick out of this.
Gonna build me a shelter made of concrete and steel.
I'll fill it up with water and ready to eat meals.
Rifles, bullets, kerosene, it's all part of my plan. You'll finally take a chance on me
when I am the last man.
Now we all know what's coming in some way, shape, or form. Maybe mutant zombie
hippies or a freaky solar storm that wipes out all the telecom, destroys the
power plants. You'll have no choice but to fall for me when I am the last man.
If you stay here in my fallout shelter, I'll
keep you safe from harm. Don't care if the world goes
out of your skelter if you're here in my arms.
Now I know your fella Jerry ain't quite right in the head.
And when the shit gets hairy, the first to wind up dead. But I'll be sitting pretty
and you'll finally understand I'll not have a bad catch after all when I am the
last man.
Now Desmond, he's a smart one and he's good at fixing cars.
But when there's no more gasoline, he won't be getting far. He'll stall it on an open field.
And then they'll eat his face. But you won't see such tragedies if you're here in my space.
If you stay here in my fallout shelter,
I'll keep you safe from harm. Don't care if the world
goes out of your skelter if you're here in my arms.
Now I got your favorite novels and a couple of good
guitars. Some games to play when it's a rainy day in a fully stocked wet bar.
And when all the world gets to...fucking A.
When all the world gets to...fucking A.
When all the world around becomes a dangerous wasteland.
We'll live it up in my little hut. They'll all be gone. We'll party on.
I'll have it all just by default. The world will shit
and I won't care a bit when I am the last man.
Alright.
That was Saint Andrew the Impaled
with a very new song recorded live at 18X Day on the Wisteria stage.
Up next, a short rant from the good or who knows possibly bad
Reverend Grill Ninja.
I am indeed a spatulatory expert.
So, how is everyone doing this X Day?
I mostly, to feed my own meticulous ego,
decided to come up on stage and say stuff. We're gonna see what I say though.
Actually, I wanted to talk to you a little bit about Slack and its nature
and how it works for all of us.
In my travels in my life, I have seen some pain and torment
and death and those three in the mornings where you break down and you lose your shit
and you're like, ahhhh, and buckled on the floor and crying tears of blood.
crying tears of blood. I've had that day.
You know, what really gets me through all that is the mad science laugh.
And I'm gonna explain to you the prodigious use of the mad science laugh.
Because no matter how hard life gets,
if you find yourself doing something, like say, I don't know, you're spanking a squirrel
while a midget's jerking you off. Let's say that happens and you go
HAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA
Then you're probably doing it right. Anytime you ever make that noise, at least for me,
that's a pretty good sign I'm doing something right in my life.
It's like when you're playing a video game and you figure out some weird trick
and how to hack into the game and get the extra bonus stuff before you're supposed to
and nobody told you how. You sit there and you go, HAHAHA, YES!
And then as long as you're doing that within your heart, that's the sign of
achieving slack, to be perfectly honest.
Exactly, sir, exactly. And that is how it's done to one extent.
There are many ways of slack. It's like, um,
I don't know, watching a loved one die before your eyes and then just making sure
you were there with them. Mmm, slack for that. Then there's also
I don't know, hugging a tree, I suppose, for some people. It's not so much for me
because, you know, you rub yourself up on a bark, you get all braced and
you're bleeding and it's uncomfortable. But then again, you know, if you never did it,
it's still worth doing. So, um, I'm gonna
keep that short and sweet. That's what I wanted to say. What you should do, always within your
hearts and your souls, is, uh, cultivate the man's
science laugh. HAHAHAHAHA!
HAHAHAHAHA, yes! HAHAHAHAHA! As long as you are
able to do that within yourselves, you too will know the truth of slack. And
Bob, the gateway drug of the universe, that's what he is for me.
Thank you.
Thank you, River of Peace!
Round of applause for the
real Grill Ninja.
Woo! The original
Grill Ninja. The original, I guess that's, GM.
I find Grill Ninja interesting because, like, so many ranchers are angry and he's
like, he's like the peace and light in Bob's eye and it's
really, you know how, and I'm telling you this and I don't know if any of you know this, if you look at the
dots of Bob and you look at one of the eyes, there's a heart
in it. There's an actual heart in the Dob's head in the eye
and I think that everybody worships a section of the Dob's
head and our great guy here, Grill Ninja, is
focusing on the heart in Dob's eye. Aww!
Which is a good thing because, you know, I'm frickin' burning in his pipe because I'm so
angry all the time.
Okay, I think it's 10 or 11 at night
and I can't even see my watch because it's dark on the road.
Walking between Caffeinas and the main
stage, as they call it, where apparently Reverend
St. Faltimus and somebody are jamming
with no audience that I can see.
Oh, here's Pisces. I was just narrating
the scene here. It's kind of a weird scene because there's this
band on stage jamming and there's no audience to be seen
anywhere, although you can hear it all over the camera. I don't even know if they're
jamming. I think it's something other than jamming.
I've heard
this tune before.
I spell that M. I said
A. D.
Apparently it's X Day's Stupid Show
for Morons. Oh, I didn't even notice that. Reverend
Fox is projecting a slide on the top of the stage
over, quite clear, it says, it does indeed
say, X Day's Stupid Show for Morons.
I love Reverend Fox's captions. He did that a couple of years ago.
He seems to know what's up. Well, he makes up the caption
on the fly and projects it.
You know, he changed it every ten minutes or so he'd come up with some new snarky
but accurate thing to say. X Day's Stupid Show
for Morons. Praise Bob! Yep.
Bob Dobbs gathered in their masses
Just like some
G's at X classes
Waiting for just for penis
With some power
We'll take her
Onward!
Baby, don't you cry
Just because they'll die
You know, at least we tried
For the end of time
We'll take her
Onward!
Just because they'll die
You know, at least we tried
For the end of time
We'll take her
Onward!
For the end of time
Lights are flashing
Cards are crashing
Fire and destruction
All the way
Because it's the end of time
End of time
It's the end of time
Watch the king
So die
Watch the bosses
Cry
Watch the queen
Cry in the end times
Here are the times
Hello, my brothers and sisters.
It's Bishop Stick, the Reverend of the Diagonal Travel.
And I'm going to discuss those two words that we are against, the conspiracy and pinks.
Right now, I'm only going to discuss the pinks, the pinky.
We have a digit on our hands.
It's called the pinky.
Pinkies are the most essential things when we are trying to grasp things.
We cannot hold onto anything without our pinky.
They are the most useful things that are on our hands, are the pinky.
So I would like, instead of it being called a pinky, we need to come up with a better
plan of what we are going to call this digit.
Because pinks are worthless, but a pinky is not.
Call it a brownie!
Everyone loves brownies!
And you can put it in your butt.
Yeah.
It's a nose picker!
Wow, yeah, a brownie would be, but again.
It works really good, and you can use it as a spoon, and, uh, which I have not.
Oh, no, it's a good digger.
Yes, the pinky will be renamed by the end of this evening.
By the end of next day, we will rename the pinky.
It's the digger.
I like the digger.
The digger.
Yes.
Theings.
The
Let me tell you a story
A story about me
One day I was walking down the street
And I came across a guy
Smoking a pipe
Looking kind of nice
He comes up to me and said
Hey son
Would you like to have a job?
I said fuck no
Who are you?
He said my name is Bob
I'm B.O.B
Says D.O.B.B
I said okay Bob
Who the fuck are you?
He said I'm your master son
Now do what I tell you
I said uh
I don't think so Bob
I'm not that kind of guy
He said well listen son
Smoke the top and let's get high
So I sat around
Played the funk with Bob
Sitting around
Shooting the shit
I see what Bob had to spit
He said hey son
Come and work for me
You gotta do nothing but just be
Be who you are
Be what you want
He said do it for Bob
That's all I asked
So Bob
Okay Bob
He said be who I want to be
B.O.B.
I'll be fucking gravity
I'll be the guy who controls the shit
I'll be the guy who spits some shit
I'll say I'll be gravity
I'll do it for the B.O.B.
D.O.D.D.
Yeah but Bob's not a nun
That's who I am
I'm gravity now
Okay
So I
I got a job for the B.O.B.
And I'm doing what he wants me
And then I take a chair
And I take it over here
Do what Bob wants
Put it in your ear
Do it what you think
For the B.O.B.
Do what he wants
He's a god
He's a witch
When you're down with B.O.B.
You will be down with gravity
You know what
Heavenly bodies roll to me
That's how I roll
I'm gravity
Now you're sold to B.O.B.
Thirty-five dollars
That's all he wants
To do for the B.O.B.
Sell your soul to B.O.B.
Thirty-five dollars
Is what it'll be
And then you got
E-Furnace T-Supply
High in the sky
With the B.O.B.
Never front with B.O.B.
Cause you'll
You'll sell your soul
For eternity
He'll own ya
He'll take your shit
And you'll never give it back
Never front with B.O.B.
That's the fact
Hey!
Don't front with B.O.B.
B.O.B. took all my weed
B.O.B. took it from his own greed
B.O.B. doesn't give a shit
B.O.B. will smoke all your shit
And
Don't front with B.O.B.
Don't ever front with B.O.B.
Cause he'll steal ya
He'll rob you
So
You're feeling a little bit funny
You're not sure why
You're in this
You're just leaking
And
You're not sure where those tears are coming from
Well I can tell you something's done
It's from B.O.B.
That's what he's done to you
B.O.B. will pull that shit all out of you
Here comes his B.O.B. band
Don't throat
Front with B.O.B.
Watch out never
Go and front with B.O.B.
Don't go and throat
Front with B.O.B.
Cause he'll
He'll take you
So you'll front
B.O.B.
Let's go
Right on
Aha
jourd'
Cap
Is that the people
So you think it's bad to scrub with Bob?
Let me tell you something that's not even at least a thing.
One time Bob came next to me.
He said, hey son, let's do some X's and Z's.
I said, okay Bob, what will happen if we do that?
He said, let's go son and check it out for a fact.
I said, next thing I know, Bob's all on my nuts.
He was getting like an uppercut.
Bob couldn't get his hands off of me.
He said, Bob, Bob's attracted to my gravity.
He said, never do X's with Bob.
He won't keep his hands off my knob.
I'll never do X's with Bob.
He won't keep his hands off your knob.
Never do X's with Bob.
Then next thing I know, Bob's taking home girls that are from the show.
And then they got into his apartment.
They got dressed in, got into a miscellaneous X-Toy.
I don't know.
I don't know if they came from a water destroyer.
But Bob stole the batteries and took them away.
And now the second Bob took them away.
He said, don't do X's with Bob.
He won't keep his hands off your knob.
Don't do X's with Bob.
And now, and now that you got me drinking, don't go out with Bob drinking.
Because the last time I went and drank with Bob, I ended up in Tijuana.
Alright, fair warning.
That was DJ Graffiti, the rapping alongside Six Fisted Tales of Connie, the band that
exists only at X Day, but which almost always has Reverend Angry Larry.
Oh, is it?
Sorry.
Lord Angry Larry on guitar.
Other musicians may or may not include Bishop Stitt, Lord Ferg, Hazel of the Windmills,
Reverend Shover, Suds Bischoff, Fid Chewy, Reverend Rockguard, X-Smartist, Philodrum,
Trademark Gunderson, and Reverend Funnyman.
And now this.
Howdy, howdy.
I'm Reverend Ivan Stank.
We all know each other.
Oh, yeah.
Not everybody.
So, um.
Bob said, I have basically nothing to say.
And that's what I want to talk to you about.
And it's actually true.
I have nothing to rant about in anger.
And those are the best rants, of course.
You know.
I'm still recycling the 20 years of Terry's life.
I have a terrible anger that I thankfully recorded some of.
But all I can rant about is slack.
And because I actually got slack.
And it's, isn't it nice to know that it occasionally does happen.
Now it could be taken away from me.
From my pride.
From saying, oh, Bob, you gave me so much slack, I'm going to show off and brag about how much
slack I got.
Oh, good.
That's exactly when Bob just switches down and yanks you up in the neck.
And really, he does things to you I'd rather not talk about in front of polite company.
But my mother-in-law, oh, no, she's not here.
But he'll fuck you in the ass is what he'll do.
If you pretend to have slack.
You can't pretend to yourself because, well, then the conspiracy has you.
It's false slack.
You know.
False slack is better than no slack.
Dr. G Gordon Gordon used to say.
But Reverend Carter LeBite pointed out that false slack is no slack at all.
And the good news is sometimes you get slack.
And I have enjoyed an inordinate amount, well, well deserved, very well deserved.
God damn it.
I could probably even use some more slack.
Oh, no.
I better be careful there.
I'm going to piss Bob off.
Or Joe of the wines already pissed Bob off.
I'm going to be pissed off, obviously.
But, you know, somebody else's slack is boring.
Not all the time.
Sometimes you might have similar kind of slack as somebody else.
Reverend Adie and I have had just two conversations about Monster, this game, Japanese game called Monster Hunter.
We're both, well, words can't describe it.
It's a new world.
It's a, you know.
I could lead you on to a better, better plane beyond Bob.
But you'd have to have one of those new Nintendo 3DS things.
You know, it's just going to have to be between us monsters.
Reverend McFuckface is on the way.
And he also is a Monster Hunter as well as Lily Drummond, the most advanced of the Drummond Overman clan.
Well, since she's a union of an Overman and an Uber femme.
They should be rolling up.
The whole Drummond family.
Sounds awesome.
And Philo will probably just look like in his human form.
If something gets him excited or terribly worked up.
I'm just telling everybody in advance.
He's not a big deal exactly.
But you know that Overman head?
It looks pretty cool once he's in that condition.
But the transition between the Steve Wilcox on Facebook.
Philo.
And the real Overman.
You kind of.
It's like you need an air sickness bag.
So try not to get Philo too excited.
Don't talk about climate change or the Confederate flag.
And probably everything will be okay.
Just wanted to make sure everybody knew.
He's a little touchy that Philo is.
Mrs. Philo.
She's great.
No problem.
Lily will tell you what to do.
But you see again.
Here I am ranting about my slack.
These are my personal friends.
I'm looking forward to seeing them.
And I actually do have slack.
And that boring as hell.
If I could think of something horrible that was going on in my own life right now.
It'd probably be more entertaining.
So I'm going to get off stage.
But the nice thing is.
Because there isn't anything.
If there is anything horrible going on.
Please don't remind me.
Because I'm an ex-stay.
That's going to all be over with soon.
I have faith.
You know.
It could come too soon.
You.
We.
We got to where we think.
Hey.
He's got a fuck peas t-shirt.
Praise Bob.
And fuck peas.
Fuck peas.
That's pretty good.
Reverend Angry Larry's got a fuck peas t-shirt.
Oh I'm not Reverend Angry Larry anymore.
You're not Reverend Angry Larry anymore?
No.
What?
That's crazy.
Oh you self identify as.
I have become a lord.
You're Mrs. Angry Larry now right?
Lord Angry Larry.
Oh Lord Angry.
You self identify as with a deity.
I am Lord Angry Larry.
Lord Angry Larry.
Lord?
Yeah.
Yes.
No Reverend.
No.
I am now a lord.
Lord.
Hail Lord Angry Larry.
That's the kind of thing that you get called after the econocataclysm.
And you're in a road warrior type world.
You'll be.
I see what you're doing.
You're thinking ahead.
You're working on old cars that won't be disabled by the alien rays.
And you've already got a title that puts you in warlord category.
He's got the hot rods.
He's got the title warlord.
He's got the goatee.
All real cult leaders got the goatee.
This is asking everyone for a dollar this year.
My beard requires a dollar.
You see that's the frock cult.
But we shan't talk about that now.
Wait I can't.
I keep thinking I'm in Dallas for some reason.
Anyway, yeah.
Who's what's happening next here?
Stang 2.
Who will be Stang, the hated Stang 3?
The despised, the persecuted.
Hunted like Frankenstein's monster.
I don't think anybody's stupid enough to do it but me.
Oh no, don't be so sure.
There's a whole world of dumbasses out there.
Well there's you.
There's at least two right here on this stage.
And think how many more there must be in that wide wide world.
And more dinosaur buns to be discovered.
Hello audience.
Say hi.
Hi audience.
Are you really?
Come on.
Can you leave it?
Hey you guys can phone in your applause if you want.
Or email it.
Professor Star 76?
Yes.
You're the big little picker hole.
Okay, yeah.
Hey, some of you may not have known but yesterday was Canada Day.
So, fuck off eh?
Dig up Hooser.
I'm not Bucky but I'm half Canadian.
So there you go.
So if you got a problem with that.
I'm a lord now fuck faces.
Um, let's pick a key.
And don't say garage key.
I already used that joke, Henny Youngman.
What?
Hey you over there with the face.
Shut the fuck up.
What?
D as in dick.
Like Dick Dobbs.
Play our favorite song called Duck Babies.
Alright this next song is called Duck Babies and it goes out to whoever said dick.
Duck Babies, oh yeah.
Your dirty diapers spill, yeah.
Duck Babies.
If it wasn't for you.
My little duck baby.
Duck Babies.
I stole you from your.
I had a change of choice to see.
My little duck baby.
You died when I was only three.
Oh duck baby.
Dick Dobbs.
Your dirty diapers spill, yeah.
Duck Babies.
I'm a big shot
Watch out next day
Wow, don't try to be funny, man.
This sucks, man.
Oh, no, I'm not.
So, everybody give him one more round of applause.
Speaking of doctor music,
the next thing happening is something very special.
After, what, two decades?
After about...
After three score and whatever years ago,
we are privileged to experience
the reuniting of
Doctors for Woes,
and Dr. Music for Rotan.
If you will bear with us just a few moments,
because, obviously,
Dr. Music requires a certain setup
that does need to be set up.
It also has...
As Philo is reminding us,
it hasn't been set up in 31 years.
This is the concert.
It's already started.
You're now part of it.
Do I have to wear a mask?
So, according to Stang,
this is part of the concert.
The setup is part of the concert.
This is like the soundcheck song,
except it's the setup song.
Yeah, you're the only one
who hasn't rehearsed everything
that we're doing right now.
I have my...
Philo said,
how much gear do you have?
Do you have your gear?
It's like, yeah, I've got this...
This squeak toy.
Okay, I'm testing, testing.
And that,
the professional rehearsal,
radio thing,
and
the fart piano
temporarily donated.
Hey, that sounds like
Reverend Rock.
Yeah.
I was trying to play
Jocko,
but there's not quite enough keys.
Where are you playing?
I have eyes!
I'm right!
I know the man by Mr. Fletcher
in Dallas, Texas,
and he's a good man,
except that he don't buy me
two glasses of pitcher's beer.
And I said,
I love you, boy,
and I'm gonna date,
and if I can't whoop it,
I'll go down.
All right, man,
if you can't whoop it,
he's going down.
Ah!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Do you remember?
It's true.
If I can't whoop it,
I'll go down.
I will go down.
Ah!
Somewhere,
somewhere I've got the recording,
it bubbles up every now and then
of this old wino
at the very, very first
subgenius, the Bible,
who said,
I don't know Bob,
but if he won't buy me a drink,
I say,
if I can't whoop it,
I'll go down.
If I can't whoop it,
Get on the mic.
I'll go down.
If I can't whoop it,
I will go down.
I'll go down.
Why are you still playing this?
Are you missing here now?
I didn't do it,
I'm not getting down.
Move it,
move it,
If I'm wounded, I will come down!
If I'm fucking wounded, I will go down.
If I'm fucking busted, I will go down!
If I can't whiff it, I will go down.
If I don't whip it, I must go down.
You're a brother?
Yeah!
Or go down?
You must whip it!
Or I'll eat you!
Down, down, down.
Yes, whip it, brothers and sisters!
Don't go down!
You got it.
Whip it!
Oh, okay.
But don't go down.
Wait, I can't go.
You can whip it.
And go down!
You can't just whip it.
Hey, let's whip it.
And then go down!
And then go down.
You're gonna do it!
And just whip it!
And whip it!
And go down!
You're whipping and going down!
Bob will find you a chest.
And!
And jack off!
Stop it.
You guys have seen everything that happens.
That's when you get slapped!
Quit trying!
I can do it.
Yeah, you can get slapped.
Philo did it.
He repented.
You did a good job.
He quit his job.
He gave the man a first job.
He slacked off.
He went down.
He got me retired.
He actually retired.
And I whipped it out.
He repented.
He went down.
He got you fired.
He did you a part.
Oh, I love your second book.
Nobody wants to be the guy that has to deal with the law, especially me.
All right, all right.
Go on.
You're on duty.
That's your job now.
I gave you the walkie talkie.
It is pretty loud.
If I can hear it, it's loud.
It is 1.30 at night.
And money?
It's 1.30, yeah.
And when we're talking about, once we get towards Friday, there's a lot more wiggling.
Some of these poor ass bastards actually have to work.
And we still have a lot to do too.
And sound care.
Yeah, so we've got plenty of time to do this.
It's great.
Dude, I don't know what you're worried about because come July 5th, 7 a.m., none of that
shit's going to matter anyway.
What fucking complaints are you going to hear?
I've heard that somewhere before.
What's that thing?
It involves a copy of that.
Subsonic machine gun.
We know we all hear it.
Pisces.
With anal probes on the end of every single one.
Yeah, but if we get kicked out of here, we'll have to go to a motel.
Oh.
For people at parties.
And that'd be terrible.
Seriously, the guys are nasty.
Yo.
I liked it.
I think it's 1.30 and it's Wednesday.
Well, Thursday.
Wednesdays are always the best.
The craziest shit happens on Wednesday because it's the best.
It's the jam, the doctor jam.
I think we'll get a good one.
It's the best.
Then two
of you in the normal room, any one of you, I've already met.
Now on the door
Just a midzyiones- flipping hand abs!
I don't know what we should name that song guys, what do you think?
What should be the title of it?
So please, we are high.
We're going to do one, and this is a song that you all can sing along with.
If you don't know it yet, you'll get it.
You'll get the chorus, so please be part of it.
We're going to praise Bob.
We're going to praise the De-Evolutionary band who praises Bob.
Devo, in this tune.
May your records
be a living record
and broken
by and by, by and by
There's a vine of heaven waiting
in the sky by winter's light
Well I play the piece that we've played
One Friday night
and sunny days
And I've been in this kitchen
I've been awesome to it
My turntable started jumping
What it did I know not
Oh, that Bob knows
how I cried
when it scrapped my good and loud
And who made a record
be unbroken
by and by, by and by
There's a vine of heaven waiting
in the sky by winter's light
Well I bought a second copy
This is through Red-Eyes Express
When my girlfriend came on to this
We started taking off her dress
Oh, we're getting to come in the
ice and coldness
And it's sweet as Sunday boys
I just told her
Gotta wait now girl
I'm getting to freedom and joy
You come on and take your records
Be unbroken
by and by, by and by
There's a vine of heaven waiting
in the sky, far in the sky
Well you know I
I've been a sinner
in my life
That evil twist
I must say I
Ain't no priest to chide
Cause I'm new to this, none is
When I hear that truth devouring
Oh no, I never stop
When my heart is
never gathered
When I shout that name above
Bob Dawgs!
May your records
be unbroken
By and by, by and by
There's a vine of heaven waiting
in the sky, far in the sky
Now I know I
Ain't no young'in
One day I will be
I'm gonna be young
I got that total
Devo feeling
Now I can be told
But I got my high five
Got my divine
Got my albums in my bag
Should I have it?
I'm into breaking
Who's my way now Bob?
When I got smooth
While I'm thick passing all
Little records
The unbroken
Body by body
Bye-bye, bye-bye, bye-bye.
There's a light in the sky.
One more time.
There are records being broken.
By and by, by, by and by.
But there's something for everybody.
In the sky.
By and by.
There's a light in the sky.
I'm Andrew Davis.
All right, come in.
I think you broke a record.
You broke a record for Purdy Music at X-Day.
It's so fulfilling.
We're not used to that.
We're taking it back.
How did that happen?
What a beautiful sound at X-Day.
What did we do wrong?
We'll pick up for it later.
Believe me.
You have a record.
I don't know what you mean.
You've been listening to the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
For free information, write to P.O. Box 181417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118
or see www.subgenius.com
Praise Bob!
Friends, we're glad you listened to this show,
and we're even more glad that some listeners have donated enough to help us keep on going for another couple of months.
Not just this show, but Subgenius.com and all the other archive sites.
But if you truly love Bob,
and want somebody to help you,
and want some of that slack back to rebound to you,
you should go to subgenius.com front page,
or especially the radio page,
or the catalog store pages,
and help out financially as best you can.
Now, we know what it's like to be on the brink of total poverty,
and we don't want any subgeniuses to make their own situations worse.
But some of you still have jobs.
Even five bucks makes a big difference,
even if it's only once a month.
And that's not from enough of you.
Fifty bucks makes an even bigger difference.
All we're saying is that blow jobs could go the way of Steve jobs if you don't pay Dobbs.
We also take checks and money orders to Subgenius Foundation.
P.O. Box 181417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44117.
We're not going to take any of that money.
We're going to take the money.