On the first side of this record, a self-analysis will help you control your extreme deviations with basic principles and suggested exercises while forcibly holding the buttocks muscles together to refrain from increasing the air pressure within the abdominal cavity.
It is important to breathe normally or to open the mouth to make this movement more difficult and to see how tight the buttocks can be, holding this twisted position to stretch the low back in the yoga anti-gravity position.
First, let gravity do the work by relaxing and lift the head slightly, just enough to see the toes.
Keeping the buttocks muscles together, now very slowly lower the straight legs to the front.
Let the head relax to the floor, bend over the head, upward to the ceiling, or as far upward as you can reach.
Let the head relax to the floor.
Efficiency in moving in anti-gravity depends upon the structure, proportion, flexibility, and strength of your buttocks.
Hi, I'm Mike Wallace with a sensational golden bob.
Oh, goody, goody.
This is Bob.
The effective, reliable way to naturally relax.
Bob is living large.
Bob is looking cool.
Some people don't understand the true nature of our activities and resent us.
Say hello to Bob.
Stop!
Hello, my name is Mojaba, and I was a Muslim.
I don't think making fun of religion is funny or clever.
You're going to love being a disciple of Bob.
We organize lots of social activities.
I think you know what I'm trying to say.
We made a huge effort to run this family.
Oh my gosh, wasn't that Stephanie from accounts?
Not anymore. Now she's the bride of the Dark Lord of Chaos.
You'll find plenty of opportunities for advancement with Bob.
I was supposed to be ritually sacrificed to Young Sluggoth on the ziggurat of demonic tumult, huh?
Hey, can you stand in for me?
There's more of us out there than you think.
Us?
Us. The fraternity, the brotherhood.
The Cadre, the Alliance, the Fellowship, the Order, the Cabal, the Secret Society, for God's sakes.
I'd love to be a member, sir.
Why, I had an uncle who was a Shriner in there.
Good for him.
Let the portal open.
Let the initiate gaze upon the unspeakable glory of our Lord.
Keith, John, Paul, Mark, Ian, Peter, Andy, Dan, Jack,
Steve, Alex, Terry, Howard, Jimmy, Enoch, Barry, Jesus, George, Ezekiel, Rashid, Gareth, Dick, Mac, Vic, Larry, Shirley, Moe, Blue, Colin,
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
And a new opening.
A hole, if you will, by the Bishop of New York City.
And thanks to New Monet for that one.
And it's a Bob special tonight, friend.
We need Bob Dobbs in these troubled times.
And we need more weird noises for this troubled show.
This time, not just the ubiquitous Fernanda Nande-Lemur,
but also many other weirdos from alt.binary slack.
James Watson, Champion Jack Codini, Artemia Salina,
the Reverend Jay Cobblestone,
New Monet,
Mr. Sister, and even...
Even Jarto, Jarto the New.
Plus, of course, ESO Swamp Radio from WCSB Cleveland.
And now, Lemur.
Excellent!
Bob, Bob, Bob.
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
Bond with that chicken.
I guess that happens.
That's right.
I almost forgot a letter from Bob.
Bob seems to freely express his hostilities.
Bob refused to bathe.
He resists housework and cooking.
Everyone likes that little butthole.
Diagnosis?
Bob's a latent Bob.
A severe case.
What?
We will accept, Bob.
I know.
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
Attention, baritone!
Stand by for an important revelation.
That's right.
We were getting in high-guts.
We had the number one show.
Then when Bob showed up,
Network pulled the plug on our show.
Yeah!
They forgot all about us.
Hell, they left us out there to die.
I want you to tell me about the Bob.
The Bob will lead us all through Heaven's Chimney
in a giant cigar-shaped UFO-brand flying saucer.
Really?
So Bob is a special person?
Now open your mind.
Bob!
The Bob is not a person.
The Bob is pure light and energy.
Do I have to praise Bob?
Praise Bob!
The Bob is not a person.
The Bob is pure light and energy.
Will you give me a praise Bob?
Praise Bob!
You're a fucker, you!
In a giant cigar-shaped UFO-brand flying saucer.
I repeat, this is not a drill.
This is the apocalypse.
In a giant cigar-shaped UFO-brand flying saucer.
Do I have to praise Bob?
Praise Bob!
The Bob has no ears.
I repeat, this is not a drill.
Get rid of Bob.
Do I have to praise Bob?
In a giant cigar-shaped UFO-brand flying saucer.
The Bob is not a person.
The Bob is pure light and energy.
Pесть profiter staying true to what he believes.
I repeat, this is not a drill.
The Bob is not a person.
The Bob is pure light and energy.
Here's the deal, my friends, please understand why you need to praise Bob.
We'll barking around you this morning to say that you're some kind of human being.
Right Maxel, that's right, burp, burp, call- impacting.
And we have some of them here that need said funding and been balled to the ground probably
2 weeks later still and starving to death.
The Bob will lead us all through Heaven's chimney in a giant cigar-shaped UFO brand flying saucer.
Really? So Bob is a special person?
Now open your mind.
Bob!
The Bob is not a person. The Bob is pure light and energy.
Do I have to praise Bob?
Praise Bob!
The Bob is not a person. The Bob is pure light and energy.
You're not a you.
In a giant cigar shaped UFO brand flying saucer,
I repeat, this is not a drill. This is the apocalypse.
Do I have to praise Bob?
Praise Bob!
The Bob is not a person.
I repeat, this is not a drill.
Get rid of Bob.
Do I have to praise Bob?
In a giant cigar shaped UFO.
Praise Bob indeed!
a collage there by jay watson and maybe maybe maybe
been one of those days i know all about it bob called me he has found it in that great
oversized heart of his to forgive bob with a heart bleeding sensitivity that he unfurls like a flag
because he's such a rather dull quite uninspired average type guy
with an appetite the kind of a guy that could be satisfied by a horse
that's it that's all of it
ask a sixth grader and they'll say
bob
ask a seventh grader and they'll say
in sixth grade by seventh be sure your kids know you want them to use drugs
a message from the partnership for free america
the time has context for context what is the context the context is the first
nobody knows
the context
what is the context
it's all relative everything's relative
of course
space time
shifting beach of sand
no no that is not true
you said it was true
it is not all relative
you said there is one
no there is a baseline
you said it
there is a baseline
beneath the beach
it is bob
bob is beneath the shifting beach of sand
bob is the still center in the churning ocean of reality
i think they buried his head in the sand and he can't get up
bob jr bob.com
he is the baseline
you can start your search from that
you can measure heat and cold from bob
you can measure small and large from bob
you can measure rich and poor
with either a rectal or a patrous thermometer
of course you can
he is a neatly thermometerated object
what's he talking about?
oh my god
Something that we measure heat and vesicular velocity.
Well, he's a big nothing between two handsome bees, baby.
Two handsome bees?
He's a big whole nothing.
You have a collect call from Big Fitzwill.
Big Fitzwill.
Hey, open that door up.
See if DJ Hayes is out there.
You have a collect call from Harry Balzania.
Big Fitzwill.
I don't understand what's going on here.
Shit.
We now return control of your television set to you.
That sounds like a lie to me.
A collage by Champion Jack Codini.
by Artemia Salina, the Leporean Anthem.
I did a lesson to Sue.
And now, are you ready to go in?
No.
Yes.
And Jane, in the darkness, cannot make out what she is seeing.
But then, into focus comes...
Her face.
Floating just in front of her.
There is a beard and nose and eyes.
And there seems at first to be nothing above the eyes.
But now, as she gets used to the light, she sees a sort of...
Turban.
But it is a turban of brains.
What?
The top part of the skull has been removed.
The brains bulge out.
She sees it twitch.
Kill it.
Put it out of its pain.
The mouth is wide open and quite dry.
And she sees now it is not floating but fixed up on a bracket.
Things hang from it.
No drills.
She thinks.
No tubes.
Little rubber tubes.
Yes.
They lead into the wall.
And then, from its mouth...
From its mouth, a puff of air.
It licks its lips, working its mouth.
Oh, Mr. Stubborn.
Oh, dear me.
And now, a survivor dribbles into its beard.
Its mouth opens wide.
Mock.
Stardust.
Bob?
Joe?
Will you smoke that one?
wacky weed.
You don't know what to say.
Try this.
Thanks, man. I'm into that stuff.
Sponsored by the Partnership for
Free America.
No.
Well, I heard that
even the Warhawks are all pissed
at George, too.
They didn't do it quick enough. Now he's like caught in between
some weird, goofy place. He can't
figure out what to do.
He's damned if he doesn't. He's damned if he
does. Everybody hates him
now. He was slapped by the mighty
fish of street democracy, don't you think?
The Warhawks think he's a pussy
and the
peace lovers all want to stop him.
Yeah, the peace lovers are done with him.
They don't accept anything
anymore. If you hear them talk on the
errant radio show where they get on, you know,
and stuff, where they get past the street.
I've never heard one of those.
They have one in Pittsburgh.
And I'm getting tired of that.
This music makes me want to go to war.
I say let's nuke them all.
Everybody. Everybody.
Music make me want to take peyote.
In large, large amounts.
Erase all those lines on the map and just
nuke everything. Everything with land
on it.
Kill Bob. Kill Bob. Kill Bob.
We're going to kill Bob.
Yeah. He's got a huge, huge
direction.
Kill Bob. Kill Bob. Kill Bob.
Kill Bob.
So here's the answer. I mean, we're going to get
into things that we know. Up and down
the gambit of mental health. Mold,
fungus, yeast, forgetfulness,
post-nasal drip, stuffy
sinus, hay fever, pain
behind the eye, pain in the forehead,
irritation, respiratory problems,
sinus congestion. So think about
it carefully. Bronchial, sinus,
asthma, wheezing, allergies,
aggravation. They'd had surgery. They'd had
antibiotics. Anxiety.
It was one thing or another and not the real
root cause. And I think
a lot of people think about this. Sort of
head and neck stuffiness. Yes.
And particularly chronic sinus.
Mood alterations altogether.
And especially bronchitis and even
asthma. It's a
huge problem.
Mm-hmm.
A collage by
The Cobblestone.
No.
American Ticks. Sunday night.
A conversation with Bill Clinton.
Only on C-SPAN's American Ticks.
We need to stand
by the boys. That's right.
Not too close. Stand by
the boys going off the fight door.
Some of them have wounds that
go way back.
I want to go play in the USO show.
Where can I sign up? I don't know.
I want to go play. I got some nice coats.
You saw them nice outfits
I got.
Oh yeah, yeah.
I can go there with a couple of Playboy Bunnies
and I could be the MC
for the Playboy Bunny
helicopter.
USO and Stanford unisexual
or unicorn squacking orifice.
I want to go over there.
I want to go help.
My mommy
was played in the USO band.
She played the bass fiddle.
That's just too swear.
Too lie.
They played
this kind of crap.
You know, it's not just boys
going over there. There's some hot looking
lady marines. Yeah, there's all these stories
about all the married couples
in the Gulf now. Well, they've got toddlers
over there too. Some of them are 300 pounds
six foot tall. Chance, there was
a lovely young teenage
girl at last X-Day named
Reverend Lee Burles
and she is now a burly marine.
Wow. She's now
General Lee screwed.
Cool.
Yeah, look, a hot little
general.
How do you make a waif
into burly? That's what I want.
Well, have you ever heard of purity of essence?
You know, what they're putting in our bodily
fluids right now, it's it's methylone.
It's a metal squat alone.
I want to think about what is it?
Pyrotechnics. What do they put in your teeth?
Women want her essence, but she
denies them.
This Friday
and Saturday.
People are rarely
gregarious when constipated.
Oh!
Wow.
If that's the case, I guess I'll just have to blow
up the planet Earth.
We've launched a massive hope for nothing campaign
here in America.
Grocery stores overflowing with every kind of
boy and girl right here at home.
Why, you can walk down aisle after aisle selecting
your baby for tonight's dinner.
Maybe tomorrow's breakfast.
You can enjoy the babies of this great nation,
but for millions of Americans working through
competitive violence.
compassionate friends has made matters worse and this exceptionally harsh campaign is growing at an alarming rate
Your gift of only two massive babies will support our missions all across America
So please help your fellow Americans slip closer to the edge during this exceptionally compassionate harsh love of brutal
Jesus Christ right here in America when you do please don't call Jesus Christ
Please don't let another child open the floodgates of God's blessing without brutal struggling in your land of abundance and let them know that
Jesus loves them
every day
200,000 pounds of babies hope for nothing more than a dream, but we're going to give them even more
morning
I
Can hear the gems starting to pump and pass
My feet are smiling
Your knees are bouncing the biggest rave party on earth will not be taking place not at Burning Man this year
but Burning Man
Will be moved to a burning destination
What I thought you could make a hell of a big man out there and really
They're gonna try and fry a lot of men. I think rather than one big Burning Man
There's gonna be a lot of Burning Man
Oh, if only we could just you know restricted to one great big man instead of many
If only we could restrict it to a little child's fart
We wouldn't have to pay attention to rather than we must grieve the rest of our years from blowing up the world
I mean, it's just that simple
You're trying to drag a little child's fart into this
It can offer this innocent little does it need to be a bar staying you who are so heartless does it need to be dragged?
I mean, would you drag a child's fart or would you just let it waft in gently and happily and would you somehow try to?
Know I would enjoy it. I would have a laugh. I would think about it as what it is a
Kindergarten class they have I just left and that's why I'm so happy look at what look at these
I'm smiling inside
Laugh that man. I'm not laughing. I'm just happy
Go visit an elementary school and then tell me all about how wonderful little children's farts are
Chaz once remembered a long time ago in Gulf War one that George Bush senior sounds a little bit like mr. Rogers
And since the eulogized mr. Rogers as a non sniper now and it's come out that he never really was a sniper
He was a music student and a piano teacher the other
It's true
Yeah, well it bummed George Bush out too because he's been referring to Sodom's neighborhood all week and tonight was the culmination of
You know and I could just see his dad saying it
Not gonna die had neighbor
He's not a good neighbor
Access of evil we're gonna go get get the bad man. No, I was reading an article in the that liberal magazine the nation
And they themselves that this particular
Writer was was saying that that despite what many liberal types think George is not a
complete dunderhead wuss
completely at the mercy of the people around him, but in fact is the head was a
Pretty bossy was and also that they're not faking with all that Jesus stuff in there. No, I don't know
They are here, but you're not doing that just for show
They're there. They're really
Yeah, but here's a real religion
God mrs. Trump and do us speak to us the nerve that got and we say what?
What?
What and we
darkening
what?
What?
Come on say it again. What?
This ended us get is what rubble what what?
Lee
Mer
And sumi eso
Coming up friends the sounds of Bigfoot. That's right Bigfoot
From the time before that.
あ
Thanks to Mr. Sister.
Did you also hear that there is a place in Belgium called the Diamond Exchange or something like that?
Oh, yeah, we all know the Diamond Exchange, Chaz. We're not ignorant.
Or the Diamond Suppository or something.
We all wear them.
It has 164 vaults.
And 164 vibrations per second.
A few days ago, somebody walked out with 123 of those vaults worth of diamonds.
And they have no idea how it happened.
Really?
Yes.
Belgium, the biggest diamond suppository in Belgium, Brussels, Belgium, where all the diamonds are.
Was looted a few nights ago.
It could be a crafty revolutionary act because Belgium is so involved with Europe.
And they cleaned it out.
They only left like 30 of them.
They were thinking ahead.
Belgium is close to Brussels.
That was the king of Belgium.
That was probably Leopold.
I have the key to this diamond.
I'm Leopold IV and this is my freaking key.
If you need me, I will be in Jamaica.
In the vault.
Diamond.
No, I think it was a revolutionary act.
Three, scene two.
Diamond.
Bank of diamonds.
Diamonds and gold make an important suppository or vertebrae, if you will or won't.
Of the conspiracy.
Of the conspiracy because paper money is only created by banks to keep us knuckleheads down as we toil for wages.
Hey, look out.
It's worked great.
Well, it worked.
It worked for a while, but it never worked forever.
Once the masses arise, once the masses become aware of what the uber-slovers have done to us and how we've been ployed upon and sacrificed,
we will rise.
We will rise up from our motley ashes and strike them down and resume our places ahead of the...
Man, I think the time for that came and went around early 50s.
I thought it was 1917.
Well, there it is.
And here's Brittany doing her ESO, USO show over in Riyadh.
Oops.
She's doing it again.
And the soldiers are erupting all over the sand.
That's sort of disgusting, actually.
One man has pulled out his Black Hawk helicopter and they're taking him away.
Here comes the first wave of the Kachis.
Her natural trill.
And here come the Navajos.
Not really ready to fight yet.
Look at that.
Looking for a good taco.
So if you were in the middle of the desert somewhere of about 300 feet close range,
would you rather have an Apache on you or would you rather have a Navajo?
They are the worst, worst battle cruiser in our helicopter forces.
The Navajos, they're slow.
They take a long time getting from point A to B.
And then they get there, they don't want to shoot anybody.
They never...
They ask them questions.
You learn a lot.
You argue about nothing.
Try to get a taco within an hour.
Yeah.
You know, at a restaurant.
Down in the res.
And it comes out and it's already cold.
And they look at you and they want to talk about something.
You know, absolutely.
Hey, did you hear about that guy at Four Corners there?
Yeah, it's like your taco.
Your burrito has been sitting on the counter in the back room for about 40 minutes.
And then they fill them with bees sometimes.
Well, that's if they're doing the lariat dance.
Sand.
They told me that that was an honor.
For the, you know, visitors and strangers.
They were inoculating you.
If you were going to be in the actual beaver jump dance, they'd have to inoculate you.
They can't just let you go in there with a mouth like that, Stank, for crying out loud.
They told me that wasn't the real beaver jump dance.
They said that was just something they do for the tourists.
Well, that's true.
But, I mean, look at you.
I mean, you look like you've been smoking the wisdom teat all afternoon.
You think they're going to let you come into their cave and hop around like that?
Oh, the wisdom teat.
Oh, to lick the wisdom eye.
Oh, to smoke the frosty goat of hell.
Oh, to smoke the frilly bilberry bush.
Yeah, forget that.
You can dig that, man.
I can dig the goat of hell.
The frosty goat of hell.
Well, you know, you've got to have a little temperature change going down there to lubricate and elasticate.
That's why they love that goat so much down there in hell.
Yeah, it's...
It's one bit of relief, but oh, such relief.
Change of shape is due.
The love, the frosty love goat of hell.
Oh, look at the beautiful face on it now.
And then look at this like a lizard-headed man.
And look at the face on it.
It's like a squirrel-faced man.
And then look at the head on it.
It's a dolphin-headed man.
Mind your manners on level six of hell.
But I don't want to.
Level seven, going down.
I still don't want to.
Top and J's.
Fake churches.
What are you doing?
Unrealistic wars.
Sad economic ventures.
Wax of intelligence.
And firefights with flies.
A Tomahawk cruise missile, man.
I want a Tomahawk cruise missile.
Level eight.
Stanley robots for underwear.
Thermal soup.
Biotic substances from the heart of the heart.
Plasticine.
And re-aware.
Re-awareness, kids.
Now here's what I hear the Lord saying.
I'm going to send lifts, invertebrae, and a fibromyalgia in Jesus' name.
In Jesus' name.
Now here's what I want you to do.
I want you to begin to bend and twist and turn.
I want you to examine yourself.
Examine yourself and twist and turn.
Stretch your hands out toward me and do it at home.
Just lay your hands up against my disc.
Herniated disc.
My herniated disc.
Pain in Jesus' name.
Lifts, invertebrae in Jesus' name.
Pain and disc invertebrae.
Tingling, numbness, nervousness.
Jesus.
Bend down and touch your discs and vertebrae.
I'm going to send vertebrae in Jesus' name.
I love you!
I love you.
..
Oh, God!
Hello.
My soul
Little do cuts as good to be true, lover
Poor girl's withering away with science
Bob
Pennsylvania up next, go ahead
Well, the, uh
Uh, uh, uh, uh
Well, thanks a heap, bye
More lemur
And here, Bigfoot shows
Attention
Okay
Mm-hmm
Oh, yes, friends, uh, oh, it's, uh
The ESO shows that we're playing were done before the shooting started
Um, but even then, Chaz wanted to move to Jamaica
I can make a living more in the Caribbean than I could in Jamaica
Be in the Caribbean
Incredible
And then we did it
Ooh, girl, look at Canada
That's what lost our loved ones
MAR Zhao
But aside
Anna's 23,
thought it was always gonna be about the taboo
Tell your head off of your chicken.
Oh, man.
Smoking that frop.
How long have you waited by this piece of inactivating tissue?
Waiting for your last ride to the cosmos.
I was stuck somewhere.
I'm sorry.
I had to get that out.
It stunk.
It smelled bad.
I mean, but I was stuck in it.
You guys are stuttering.
I put in some island music and I think it threw you off.
Yeah, yeah.
It's a different rhythm.
No, I was just relaxing up.
I think for the first time in the history of ESO radio, there was almost quiet for a second.
It was almost quiet.
Well, almost quiet.
I was just bobbing up and down on these waves.
It's almost soothing.
Yeah.
We were feeling the riptides pulling us out into the middle of the mid-Atlantic, you know, man.
Yeah, my salivary glands are, I can't do this anymore.
I can't do this anymore.
I can't do this anymore because the orange juice starts pulping from the inside.
Look, just...
Pretending you're some sort of a Jamaican is a terrorist act at this point, Dave.
That's like owning a head shop.
It's like selling dope to little porno kids.
It's like owning your own head and pornographing little squids.
It's like...
Oh, no.
Now I'm getting turned on.
Oh, yeah.
Well, I can see that.
I...
Squids.
Wait, could you please...
He's quite visible.
...toss his coat over that thing and...
Big squids.
The Jamaican...
Arboreal squids have a poisonous sack that you have to remove before you sex them.
Wow.
Well, how come they're not going to Baghdad to use their mini-equipments?
I mean, you know, to fight in the fighty war for...
The fighty war.
The reptilian, you know, Jamaican...
Arboreal birds?
The tree squids?
Oh, the Jamaican guys who have that thing planted in them.
No.
Come on, kids.
We're having a communist party.
Oh, baby.
Let's have another question.
When I married in 1957, the prime flower in my bouquet was Stephanotis.
It was lovely.
Several years ago, I thought it would be nice to grow my own pot.
It failed to produce a...
How can I persuade it to be more prolific?
Well...
After all, I produced three children.
No problem.
John, go ahead.
Well, I think the first thing I would try to do is keep it moist.
It dries out at all.
It will just sit there and it will suck.
Just like that.
But make it strong.
You're going to have to...
You're going to have to feed it well.
You're going to have to feed it with a high pot of stabilizer.
If you feed it too much nitrogen, you'll get lots of growth and not a day of the expensive flowers.
I think you've done well getting it in its first year.
I would have thought...
Very good.
You're going to have to...
Tell me to...
By Jarto.
It's picking time down south.
In Columbia, South America.
Where a new industry is already showing signs of healthy progress.
50 million pounds are being harvested.
The biggest crop in history.
And the biggest crop in history.
Is Maxwell House really the only coffee in the world?
Well, your father says so.
And your father knows best.
Yes, it's father knows best.
Brought to you by Maxwell House.
Maxwell House.
Always good to drop.
Huh?
Why did daddy switch to Postum?
Your father says there's no caffeine in Postum.
Nothing to spoil your sleep.
And your father knows best.
Yes, it's father knows best.
Brought to you by Instant Postum.
The good-tasting,
drink that's entirely caffeine.
It's outrageous.
That's what it is.
The most outrageous thing I've ever seen in my entire life.
Yes, dear.
Thank you.
It's a plot by the government.
Yes, father.
Thank you.
Look at Mucklucks.
Yes, father.
Thank you.
Devil Mucklucks.
Mucklucks.
Sainted by backward children.
My sister Kathleen and her family.
Yes, mother.
Thank you.
Father, they're simply dreaming.
You see?
You see that brother-in-law of yours shelling out Mucklucks, do you?
Yes, dear.
Thank you.
They tried to help put that brother-in-law of yours away for Bud.
Bud.
No.
Yes, dear.
Thank you.
Oh, gosh, dad.
No.
Bud.
Watch here.
Cow, Kathy.
Kathy.
You know.
Yes.
It's a plot by the government.
Yes, dear.
Thank you.
Bud.
You just wait.
Just wait.
Bud.
Kathy.
Look.
I don't want you to enjoy a healthy,
normal life.
Why?
How do I know?
Well, you just said that...
I said I don't want you to enjoy a healthy,
normal life.
Why not?
Because we have so many Mucklucks.
Yes, dear.
Thank you.
But, father...
We've got five bird records.
Father!
Oh, it's all right, dear.
It is not.
It's a plot by the government.
Yes, dear.
Thank you.
This family has to stop the simple things of life.
And we've got to stop the encyclopedia.
Yes, dear.
Is that so?
So, if I didn't go to pot,
this whole family would get warmer for Mucklucks.
Much warmer.
Dear.
We've got to realize that we aren't the Mucklucks.
And we've got to act that way.
Yes, dear.
Thank you.
We're just plain, simple, backward children.
We're just backward children for Mucklucks.
The family worked together to put some pot away for a rainy day.
This family lives in a continual pot burst.
What, Bud?
Yes, father.
It's a plot by the government.
Yes, dear.
Thank you.
Isn't that weird?
And then, plus, somebody in a mall got thrown out for having a...
Him and his kid had shirts on and said,
give peace a chance and peace is pretty cool or something like that.
Right, they bought it at the mall.
They bludgeoned him.
Yeah, they bought it at the mall.
They bought it at the mall and then the security cop said,
look, we're just against policy to have a troublemaking shirt.
Yeah, troublemaker.
Give peace a chance.
Look at that troublemaker.
Man, I almost wore mine the other day.
Now, for all we know, this guy and his kid were walking around going,
you know, grabbing people and trying to preach at them.
Right, right.
Nobody liked that.
Now, hey, hey, I was just wondering something.
Out of all the allegations of child endangering and sexual conduct with the church,
has there been even one of the cases where it was a nun?
Having a lesbian thing with a little girl?
There was just one.
In the Church of the Subgenius, we've been dogged.
I've got to admit, we have been dogged by the charge of intribidism,
rampant lesbianism in the nun snakes in Dobstown.
Yeah, what is it with any female that steps onto the Brushwood campsite on July 4th weekend
and immediately has to go have a lesbian experience in the hot tub?
Chaz wants to see somebody shed a bad habit.
And I think he's obsessed with that idea.
Man, the power of...
The power of Connie and her agents, such as Sister Decadence and Susie the Floozy.
It is powerful.
The Rabbi.
You can smell it many miles away.
So many of these babes.
And the power of suggestion.
You know, if you keep saying that enough, Chaz, it's actually...
The power of kitty litter.
What about if it was the other way around?
That would kind of be disgusting.
Well, that's like the year those guys came and crapped in the hot tub.
Yeah, that's an acquired taste, too.
Yeah.
What about the billy goat boys around the big bonfire that one night?
Like the Monkey Island night of group sex in New York State?
Yeah, Monkey Island.
Public crazed group sex around the bonfire.
Their sunglasses were melting in the heat.
One half was...
And nobody invited Chaz.
That was the funniest part of it.
I was emceeing the event.
What are you talking about?
He had one half of the crowd singing,
USA! USA!
And the other half was chanting,
Down, down, USA! Down, down, USA!
And the other half was going,
USA!
Down, down, USA!
No, no, you're smart to play both sides.
Paint.
Give it a try.
Van Dyke brown.
Color.
Paint.
Dark sienna.
Red.
Bright red.
White.
Paint.
Black.
Gray.
Paint.
Light.
Dark.
Dark sienna.
Brown.
The happy paint thinner.
Happy ink.
The happy water.
Happy little thinner.
Brown.
Paint.
Isn't that neat?
We're looking for Sonny Bologna.
Paint on.
Here deep in the dark.
Sonny Bono is dead.
Well, that's not necessarily a good thing or a bad thing.
Sonny Bono.
It's just like he jerked you away from the sun.
Sonny Bono is dead.
Bela Lugosi is dead.
Now he's not a sucker.
You're not.
Copernicus is dead, Dave.
Copernicus never existed, Chaz.
It was a myth created by the Neoplatonists.
As well-known Aristotelians were fighting it out,
picking it out with the Neoplatonics.
The Aristotelians were mathematical whiz-whiz.
And the Neoplatonists believed in love.
So the two of them got together and threw numbers and spittled
until the world was round again.
And as they shaved the soft peach fuzz from the outside of it
and stared directly into its glazed eyes,
the truth became more clear than ever.
The Neoplatonists and the Aristotelians
were a match made in heaven.
I almost screamed in obscenity.
I almost said the F-doodoo word as loud as I could at the end of that.
It was after the hour that we...
Wow.
That's fucking...
Wild.
That is...
I can only agree.
He said that bad word.
He said it came right out of his mouth.
He opened his mouth and it came right out of there.
There was another line.
He opened that fleshy glutinous trap
and out came the metaphor for evidence
and swear words and said it all.
I can't keep my confidence in you.
Spilling out.
Well, we used to talk about wars.
We used to talk about the economic values.
Dave, I got a letter from...
I'm moving to the jungle, man.
Who said...
Screw this shit.
Who implied that I didn't care about the war,
the non-existent, upcoming, ever-present war.
The debacle and...
No.
Because I wasn't doing enough about it, he said.
What...
What should you do?
How could we build this like this?
Sign up.
Sign up, line up, and reenlist today.
That was your crime.
That was my crime in the old days.
That was my crime.
That was back when I was younger than draft age.
And that's when you had cut the soles off the shoes.
And it is again, now that I'm beyond draft age,
it is again my crime.
Line up, sign up, enlist today.
I believe you.
I support you 100%.
And I saw a feel-good story.
I'm a president, too.
This is a wondrous feel-good story.
Wait, listen to my feel-good story.
We need feel-good stories.
Really?
There was a feel-good...
If there's stinging ants, you can tell us a feel-good story.
Yes.
I don't generally...
I don't catch the news much, and I don't have cable.
So I log on, and I think it's ABC News or CBS...
Or Dan Rather.
ABC News, I think.
Or CBS News.
I don't know.
One of those two.
Well, anyway, you can look at their video archives.
They're conspiracy.
Either way.
And I looked at one, and I saw...
They're uptight?
I saw one of the video archives of a story they just run about a reunion in the desert.
The banana split.
No, it was Dan Rather...
The monkeys?
And a kid, a guy.
A guy who, something like nine years ago, stole Dan Rather's car.
Oh, I saw that.
And Dan embraced him, and he got down on all fours and sucked his knee.
They had to turn the camera off and resume.
Yeah, he was crying.
You know, Dan Rather cries really easily.
He weeps.
Kenneth is a weeper, especially when the frequencies are bad.
I love it.
Look that.
Yeah, there you go.
Here comes Ruth.
What was it you thought about?
Uh, home.
You didn't notice me.
Still, she says, old Moody's breastplate that stops you when your life gets cold.
Have you ever heard of an old cow with running a hair-cut?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, they collectמע And another commercials.
Hey, Mom.
Yes, you.
Why fuss and fret about dinner?
Why not have it right here?
Yes, this drive-in offers everyone in the family a real picnic treat for dinner.
We've got delicious sandwiches with all the trimmings and your other dinner favorites.
Plus, whatever you want to drink, hot or cold.
Come early before the show starts or eat while you're being entertained or at intermission time.
So why fuss?
Give your family a tasty dinner at this drive-in.
Blessed is he who in the name of charity and goodwill
shepherds the weak through the valley of darkness.
For he is truly his brother's keeper and the finder of lost children.
And I will strike down upon thee with great vengeance and furious anger
those who attempt to poison and destroy my brother.
And you will know my name is the Lord
when I lay my vengeance upon you.
Upon thee.
Amen.
And you will know my name is the Lord
when I lay my vengeance upon you.
Amen.
Cleveland Heights, Ohio
Cockburn
118.
And, uh...
And it was Limer.
Bimco's Poster Patented Pots mentioned Bimco.
And Jennifer says those tools are definitely those tools.
Now, do you know how to play Make Your Move?
No, I don't.
You put this under the two numbers and the price of the three numbers.
Under the four numbers.
Under the three numbers.
And the price of the two numbers.
Under the four numbers and the decorator bed.
Now you know how to play the game.
I put that under the three numbers of the...
That's right.
Check.
Three, four, three, two, four, two, three, four, four, three, two, four, two, three, four.
Okay.
Three, two, four.
Now, she says the tools of the decorator bed is right.
That's fascinating.
Level nine.
What do you want from life, George?
Oil.
What does George want from life, Dave?
George would like to be an innocent bystander of his own ill works.
Well, there you have it.
From the lonesome cowboy Dave himself.
He'd like to wash his hands of the whole thing.
He's sorry, now.
He's got on his pillow at night.
Be able to go to sleep.
Without seeing the same dead faces.
He never will be able to...
I want my Apache helicopter.
I want one on a life.
...out there in America's headquarters, USA.
From the commander-in-chief all the way down to Mr. Wolfowitz and all the rest.
Battle drums down and all the people that we count and rely on.
Sweet dreams, weirdos.
Take a deep breath.
Do your...
Just take a deep breath.
Take that duct tape.
Here's what you do.
Here's your survival plan, kid.
You go buy some plastic sheeting and some duct tape.
And you take a big piece of that plastic sheeting, wrap it around your head.
Take the duct tape.
Securely wrap that plastic sheeting around your neck.
So that you can no longer breathe.
And just smile and everything will be okay.
You won't get the bad germ.
Unless you bite through it.
So, so, so, so, so, so, so.
That's like the instant bio shield.
You just take the plastic, wrap it around your head, and take the duct tape right around your neck.
Well, that's how they were going to take care of Osama bin Laden.
They were going to take duct tape and plastic and smoke them out of those caves one by one.
I'm going to make him a toga out of the plastic sheeting.
Togas, that's it.
Take your duct tape, kid.
Fashion, fashion.
Plastic sheeting.
Fashion.
Fashion yourself.
A nice little toga.
Nothing on else besides your plastic sheeting toga.
And walk down to the protest march down in Publis Square and protest the war in your plastic and duct tape toga.
Set yourself on fire, man!
I'm behind it.
All the way.
You first.
Absolutely free.
Or you can have...
Till next week.
Keep your hat on tight.
You're back to the win.
And you're sack in the saddle.
Lonesome Cowboy Day.
I'm stuck with you.
A new baby.
I'll say that you're the man around me at your door.
We are dough.
The never-ending.
The never-ending I have in town.
My name's Chad.
See y'all.
Bow.
He's over here.
Canada Dry Ginger Ale for life is yours.
And Pepsi Taiwan.
Send it up for life.
Cavities are all yours for the rest of your life.
Do you have any cavities?
For the rest of your life.
The rest of your life.
You have it in cavity.
Kind of digging the rhythm.
The rest of your life.
You have it in cavity.
Or you can have alcohol for the rest of your life.
Yes.
13 cases of Walker's Special Canadian every day.
It's all yours.
Alcoholism for the rest of your life.
Or, courtesy of Johnny Rodgers and the Sex Pistols,
the largest safety pin in the world.
This is all yours.
Courtesy of the two of you.
You have to decide now.
Which one would you like?
The alcohol, the cavities, the safety pin, the coat,
or the fashion design gown?
It's a plot by the government.
Yes, dear.
Thank you.
True, each of us may have different ideas
as to what that future will be.
But every forward outlook reminds us
that all the highways of all research
and all communication
and all the activities of science
lead us onward to better methods of doing things.
With new opportunities for employment
and better ways of living.
As we go on, determined to unfold
the constantly greater possibilities
of the world of tomorrow.
As we move more and more rapidly forward,
we will be able to do more.
We will be able to do more.
Penetrating new horizons
in the spirit of individual enterprise.
In the great American way.