Favorite color?
Mmm, electric blue.
You?
Black, definitely black.
Oh, but also pink.
Oh, oh, and sunlight.
You're a vampire.
Don't you burn in sunlight?
Not silly.
That's only in the movies.
Favorite song?
That's a no-brainer.
Flawless.
It's Tash's new hit single.
Who's Tash?
Have you been hiding under a rock your whole life?
Tash is the most coolest, most awesome, amazing, beautiful, amazing rocker.
I have all of her albums, and I've seen all of her videos,
even the super obscure one that she shot secretly in Tokyo.
Oh, she's a normie.
What's that?
Normie.
Normal.
A human.
Okay, big deal.
So she's a normie.
Don't you think it's a bit unfair that humans are the only ones who get to be normal?
I mean, who decided that turning into a bat and sleeping in a coffin was weird?
Tell me about it.
Just because I need a few steps.
Stitches to stay together.
I'm still a person.
Do you ever wonder what it would be like to be normal?
I don't know.
Being normal never really vibed with me.
But it would be nice to do some normal things.
Like have friends.
Oh, and throw parties.
And hang at a coffee shop and order elaborate-sounding drinks.
It could be a coffin shop.
I love it.
And it could be right in the center of our little monster village.
Where?
Where monsters of all kinds could come to live together.
And go to school together.
A real school.
Oh, we could call it...
The Subgenius Hour of Swag.
Subgenius Hour of Swag
Oh, that's not true!
Yeah, no, bad idea.
What about...
School for the scary, strange, and... and...
Generally unwelcome.
Or...
Or we could just call it...
Monster High!
So simple and yet...
So perfect!
If only we could...
But...
It's impossible.
Nothing possible, just...
Challenging.
Subgenius Hour of Swag
I think I know most of it anyway.
My wife, Ivana, is a brilliant manager.
I will pay her one dollar a year and all the dresses she can buy.
I think the only difference between me and the other candidates is...
I'm more honest and my women are more beautiful.
I build the best buildings.
And I'm the biggest developer in New York by far.
While that's real estate and this is politics...
Are they really so different?
Usually, if I fire someone who's bad, I tell them how great they are.
Because I don't want to hurt people's feelings.
My fingers are long and beautiful.
That's been well documented.
Along with other various parts of my body.
My Twitter has become so powerful that I can actually make my enemies tell the truth.
The concept of global warming was created by the Chinese.
Sorry losers and haters.
But my IQ is one of the highest.
And you all know it.
Please don't feel stupid or insecure.
It's not your fault.
And it's not a wig.
It's my hair.
Do you want to touch it?
McCain.
He's not a war hero.
He's a war hero because he was captured.
I like people that weren't captured.
Okay?
What I say is what I say.
Well, I do whine because I want to win.
And I'm not happy about not winning.
I fully think apologizing is a great thing.
But you have to be wrong.
I will absolutely apologize if I'm ever wrong.
The best taco bowls are made in Trump Tower Grill.
I love Hispanics.
That was Billy West as Zap Brannigan speaking the actual words of that orange guy.
The Monster High clips and songs used in this show are all from the talk show.
The 2016 kids movie, Welcome to Monster High, which appears to be something of a franchise reboot.
And now, Reverend Draculaura.
For those of you tuning in for the first time, I'm Draculaura.
I'm not like other people.
But then again, who is?
And it was conceived, gestated and decanted.
And born on X day.
ZAP BRANNIGA
Today, the moon reached full perigee.
227,411 miles from Earth.
and the planets are achieving their formation for X-Day.
The Earth will be exactly at Aphelion, 94.5 million miles from the Sun,
while Mercury moves to a superior conjunction.
The X-est armada will manifest itself precisely at 7 a.m. Central Standard Time.
And now the opening ceremony begins for this session of the endless hour of slack
as I,
Ivan Stang, moves to ring the ceremonial bell, always heard on these occasions.
The bell is heard over land and sea as the ceremony begins.
The invocation to the four quarters and elements having been made,
which today we would call states of matter.
Ivan Stang sounds the gong.
Ivan Stang plays the gong.
Oh, come ye who are heavy laden, or just come in here,
if you're not doing anything in particular,
and prepare yourself for the awesome revelations
of the eternal hour of slack.
I can hear the bell.
Hear it, Ivan, for it is a knell that summons thee to heaven or to hell.
Don't blame me. I voted for Bob.
Yeah, what about that, Mr. and Mrs. America and all the ships at sea?
What are your priorities?
Don't you know this planet's had it?
Time to line up and get ready.
Line up. Sign up.
Line up and enlist today.
Pipes for industry.
Pipes for defense.
Pipe down, pikers.
Yes, friends, X Day has begun.
19 X Day, the last of the X Days.
You are privileged to be here for the final time,
to be on Earth itself for the final, yes, the final time.
Oh, yes.
And what do you do when you know it's the end?
Well, that's up to you, my friends, because this is the church of the subgenius,
and only you know what slack is for you.
Yes, that's between you and your innermost voice.
You have to make these arrangements.
We can't do it for you.
After all, we're not running this church to coddle people who are members.
Well, I thought this was the victim's church of the kid globe.
We don't tuck him into bed and give him a bubble bath.
That's not what this is about.
No, we give Bob a bubble bath.
And then he goes out and gives a bum a haircut.
Yes, we've heard about that.
Always the same bum, I understand.
Well, we don't have to get that detailed about it.
Well, anyway, it is true.
Bob is known to go out and give a bum a haircut.
But so far, this has been...
a wonderful ex-day.
We've already had the thunderstorm and rain.
Which is described in your literature there,
and was written beforehand with foreknowledge of these as of other things.
That's right. That's how we know this is actually day four in the schedule.
And, friends, we got off to a great start last night
once we finally found the key to the sound booth,
which happened to be the owner's.
The owner of the sound booth was the key.
We got...
I watched the most wonderful show.
And perhaps we'll be cutting away to parts of that show
in this and future Hours of Slack.
But I don't know what you'd call that band last night.
It was a doctor band.
It was...
Fid Chooley, Reverend Anna Maul, lots of new people.
Dr. Shoggoth, and also many oldsters,
such as Walter Kosmack.
And, friends, that was a really inspiring show,
because it was so obvious that these young folks had been listening
to the Puzzling Evidence Show,
the Hour of Slack,
and Susie the Flusie's Bob's Slacktime Funhouse.
And other fountains of truth.
And they had taken the ball
and run with it,
and then kicked it out of the park,
over both goalposts.
It's so nice to see somebody step up.
You gotta watch that forward lateral.
They took it a little further.
They're younger, faster, and drunker.
And it was really, really an inspiring thing for me to see.
I was so proud that we had
had something to do with such
horrible noises,
but wonderful concepts.
It was really good and funny,
and the performers will be glad to know that
the recordings sound pretty good.
And you don't have to be parachuted into sweet-sounding
You have to get up to speed
and you have to find où to go.
So, and they put out some fun shows
for me.
Thank you.
Are you ready to rock?
Are you being a mountain friend?
Upset with my possibilities and my future and my days?
Are you having problems with how my life is going?
Now I just give up and have a good old spoonful of scrum, a big old bucket of scrum, a nice
quart just to get another scrum.
Everything is fine now.
Where's Scott?
There's Doug.
Yes, pretty good.
Is that where I cut to a selection?
You cut to an incredible special effect.
Yes, that.
That's a selection.
There it is.
Good God, look at that special effect.
Incredible.
Ah!
It's so expensive, it hurts to look at.
Yes.
The more expensive the special effect, the better it must be.
Now that guy who smokes through his eyes, that's no special effect.
He actually squirts the smoke stream through his tear ducts.
But we all have our individual Bob-given talents.
Some of the Bob-given talents are unexplainable.
They may be useful in ways we don't know yet.
I'm thinking actually of Mr. Sister's son who can't talk, but I know that there's something
that guy can do better than anyone.
It's just up to the church to find out what it is.
Maybe if we put him in front of a hundred monkeys, we might be able to find out what it is.
Now that's how rich we are with typewriters.
We'll end up with a book of the subgenius too.
This music is wonderful.
This is the end of our journey of exploration and discovery over foaming seas of possibility.
The unfroppened voyage of J.R. Bob-dobbs.
I'm just wondering if yawn background music is actually loud enough for anyone in the
audience to hear it.
So, we're here rhapsodizing about something.
about music that they can't hear as well as...
They can hear it.
Look at them.
They have their thumbs.
They're putting their thumbs up.
Okay, well then...
And covering their ears and putting plugs in there.
Yeah, no, it's plenty loud.
Your headphones are weak.
Mine are very, very strong, though.
And they need to be.
So...
Very well.
Ah, yes.
Now, perhaps we could momentarily mention
the schedule of events.
Yes.
People are quite anxious to know
when the Bulldada auction will take place
or other important ceremonies.
Well, this is just the first day.
According to the schedule,
a bunch of stuff happens in the cafe,
and then later, a bunch of stuff happens on the main stage.
That's the schedule.
And it's accurate.
It mentioned the rain, and then...
The rain is done with for now.
Yes.
That's...
We can check off.
That's a...
We can check off now?
We can check off the rain.
Well, that's actually how...
I've been checking off this whole time.
That's why we put this tablecloth on the picnic table
that our studio is on,
so people can't see below the waist.
I don't know why you didn't put the new, more...
Look at that.
Impenetrable cloth.
Check that out.
Barbara Eden.
Well, that's nice.
Yeah.
Price St. Martin.
We were just looking at a topless picture of Barbara Eden.
Let her show her navel on TV.
But we subgeniuses get to see things like that.
Mm-hmm.
Interposed with grotesque sights of horror and...
Well, it's the contrast that makes it so wonderful.
Mm-hmm.
That's why we love monster movies.
There's always a cool, hideous monster
and a beautiful girl
who falls down, usually.
But I like things that...
As Princess Wee says...
...take me out of it.
...of my ordinary life.
Girls fall down.
Every now and then, you'll get a movie
where the guy falls down and the girl helps him.
Those are fun.
Well, as long as somebody helps someone,
that's the important thing.
In the subgenius movie,
lonesome cowboy Dave falls down
and Susie helps him up.
Well, that's art imitating life.
Right.
And speaking of that,
Susie is here now,
just arriving at Caffeina's.
We...
Oh.
There she be.
Here she comes.
What?
She's got eggs in her pants.
She's got eggs.
She pulled an egg out of her pant.
Perhaps we're going to have eggs Birmingham.
That wonderful delicacy.
Oh.
Yes, the egg.
Symbol of beginnings.
And, of course, the Bavarian albuminati.
Those egg...
Worshippers.
Is that a reptile or bird egg?
That's a bird egg.
Oh, wait.
Her mic was not on.
Let's get mic on Susie.
Does this turn?
You know, the reptile eggs are more oblong and leather.
I believe an Amish farm woman laid this egg.
You know, it was a little starch cap.
What will hatch out of it?
A little Amish boy or girl?
I don't know,
but I hope I'm going to eat the hell out of them.
Oh.
I hope they haven't got none of those pilgrim buckles on their shoes.
The eggs require occasional turning, but not too much turning.
Yeah.
While, on the other hand, if you turn a dinosaur egg, you kill the embryo inside it.
Really?
You don't turn those eggs.
Yes, you leave the eggs.
I'll remember that next time I come upon a dinosaur nest.
Oh, they'd be sore, man.
Hey, we can come upon dinosaur nests.
They'll be a little more fun.
It's just a few days.
Yeah, he's got them on his property.
No, no, I mean on Planet X, or whatever.
Oh, that, yes, of course.
Oh, I wouldn't do that to them.
You know, nobody ever asks what happens when we get to Planet X, or where it is or what
it is, or why it's called Planet X.
I advise to open that.
Ixnay on the Ana-X play.
I still think they should know about it.
Anyway.
Yeah, it's too late anyway, right?
Yeah.
They paid their dues to Bob.
They're going to be ruptured whether they want to be or not.
Yes, that is so.
One-way ticket.
One.
It's always best to prevent an eventuality as a possibility, or even a choice.
No one has been smart enough to buy the round-trip ticket.
The what?
Wait a minute.
The round-trip ticket?
Well, that's just...
That's another 35 bucks.
That's just kind of smart if you're going somewhere you've never been before.
Wow.
But this is the smart.
Where does that enter into?
Well, that's why I never bought one.
Yeah.
Duh.
La gringa estupida.
Never a duh moment at Ixnay.
I use that line two shows ago.
I really shouldn't do it again.
Yes, yes, yes, Ixnay.
The promise of Ixnay.
Some people spend their time thinking about all the destruction and revenge they're going
to...
What's a present tense of wrong?
Well, you know, we never claim...
Anyway, but...
...to be a particularly well-adjusted group.
No, of course not.
We're better just because we're different.
Isn't that what you wanted to hear?
Isn't that what you most wanted to hear?
Aren't we good at telling people what they most wanted to hear?
Until recently.
Yeah, well, some of that.
Well, that's a problem.
Yes, that's one for the recording angel.
All over and done with.
Oh, here's my show and tell thing.
Susie the Fruisy brought this while we're on the subject.
Does it ever end?
Barney Bear Comics.
Barney Bear Wakes Up.
It's Kitty's Christian Comics.
Right.
And you know when Barney Bear wakes up,
he's just going to start acting like everybody else.
That's their idea.
Well, he acts like anyone else in the morning would.
Morning would.
Someone's been sleeping in my baby bear.
He's a healthy bear.
But these pernicious comics are Christian comics
from Spire Publications,
created by Adler.
Al Hartley, who wrote such classics as
Hansi, the Girl Who Loved the Swastika.
That's advertised on the back.
Oh, yeah, that's one of these comics.
So it should be taken cum grano.
Okay, here's the climactic part of this comic book.
If God can do this for a caterpillar,
just imagine what he can do for us.
Mom, Dad, I found the better part.
The better part of life.
Let's go, Dad.
I'm ready for my father's business.
And now their business is
telling tourists at Yellowstone about Jesus.
Keep your hands inside the cart.
God loves you.
He sent his son Jesus to give you a better life.
Jesus will be your friend if you ask him.
He wants to be with you for seven years.
Years.
The end.
That's the side of bear rape that doesn't sound good to me.
The seven-year part?
No, the Christian part.
Oh, well, we didn't...
I mean, now it's an unsavory concept.
Before, I was all down with it.
I was rubbing myself with bear attractant.
Sorry, ursine species.
Only humans get saved,
and the bears shall burn in an eternal frying pan.
That's it, Dad!
Yes, only humans have souls,
according to Jehovah One's scribes.
Bears are going to have to look after themselves.
No exceptions.
What about subgeniuses?
Where do we fall into that?
According to them, do we have souls?
We're below the bears.
That's the way the bears like it.
We're removing ourselves,
as surely you among all,
Elfman.
You should know from that arena
to avoid the penalties of the Jesus crowd
and their apocalypse.
Yes, ours is one which contains an evasive maneuver, primarily,
but with the deal that Bob brokered with the exists,
we're sure to come out clean.
Duh, of everything.
Bob will clear you out, friends.
Are you clear?
Is your wallet clear?
We can make it clear.
We can audit your wallet.
If you ain't clear now, you'll be clear soon.
We're clear, we're here, get used to it.
Clear.
Right.
Alrighty.
Hey, look, Dr. Hell.
Look, a cassette tape.
When was the last time you saw one of those?
Boy, a quaint old time.
You can buy me a cassette tape.
But wait, there's more.
It's not really a cassette tape.
It's really a USB thumb drive disguised as a cassette tape.
Well, there you go.
You can take your cassette mix tape and put it on this thumb drive and still...
I would never find that in all my hundreds and hundreds of cassettes.
And you can buy these from Future Logic Development.
They're called the Future Logic Development Corps.
Corp.
Corpse.
Which happens to also be St. Andrew.
St. An-Juh.
Not to be confused with Andrew the Impaled, who is a different St. Andrew.
We have two St. Andrews here.
One of them, who sews your lips shut with surgical needles and thread.
The Infibulator, we call him.
And one who sells LP records.
And this interesting little Paola tape.
The Infibulator, we call him.
a plug thing, plug subject
which I'm presenting. That's damnable technology.
Well, you can't stop
progress.
Oh, I don't know about that. We're settlers.
We settle for cable. I'll settle for
stopping Congress. There goes Bob.
Oh, yeah.
Reverend Baby Bear is
placing the Bob effigy.
That's not Bob.
I thought it was some guy with a box on his head.
I really thought it was a
living organism. What happened to his
hat that was
on the top?
This year's Bob effigy has
a more or less human-like
body, but his
head is square
and he has four faces round
about. Wow, it's like that
mythological thing, Pandildo's box.
Well, like the aliens seen
by the prophet Ezekiel
in the middle of their flying
wheel in the Old Testament.
They also were
multi-faced, facing
in different directions.
And you know, that was what
Ezekiel saw was not the
greys, but an advanced
Certainly. Actually, it was
a runaway exorcist. Far more
advanced than those diddlers,
certainly. Yeah, but
we got a four-headed, I mean a
one-headed, four-faced
Bob effigy with
strangely spindly
legs. And what a hat.
I can't wait to see him
bang. All of the victims
can't be chunky. It'll be a burnament.
He's a sporting fellow.
The burnament is
Saturday night.
That's the only thing on the schedule.
On the top, underneath the hat, there's a face.
Okay, so he's got
five. I bet there's a face on the next stump.
I bet he's a six-faced Bob.
A six-faced Bob.
We need to make dice like that
for the subgenius game.
It's just a dog's head on either
face. Faces inside and out.
Oh my, that's too much.
That's a concept.
Always better than not enough.
He can see you from any direction.
I hope he burns
long enough to cook a hot dog on.
The last one did.
A mighty hot dog is our Bob.
Yeah, who was it?
Was it Reverend Fox cooked a hot dog
off of Bob's
dogs? His feet.
Wow.
Reverend Fox, I have a present for you
by the way.
Yeah. It's in his pants.
If you find it,
you can keep it.
Now it's staying. Really.
It's like, it's in the mystery
pants.
The mystery of the leaping
pants. Actually, what it is, is
I was going
through old trash. This is a page
from the last
of the hundred page stark
fist magazines that I published
and lost my ass
on each time.
And it has an article about a hypercube.
Now, if a 3D
cube can cast a 2D
shadow, then a 4D
hypercube can cast a 3D
shadow. And here's a picture
of the hypercube shadow.
We'll project that later
for our listening audience.
In 2D.
But I thought that
Reverend Fox
could use that in his hypercube
graphics.
If he hasn't already.
Here's another
interesting bit of plugola
or payola. This is something
I didn't know we sold.
It's a
puzzle.
That's your Bob crossword.
Jigsaw puzzle.
It's a jigsaw puzzle of the famous
45 Dobbshead graphics done by
Reverend Hartignition.
Guaranteed to give you a whacking
great headache.
I found
this in our cafe press catalog
and I don't remember.
I don't remember putting it there.
So you just went ahead and ordered one.
I bought one so I'd see what we were selling.
And I was so glad it's only 30 pieces.
So it's like it's a real subgenius puzzle.
A subgen... Most puzzles are like
a thousand, fifteen hundred pieces.
Yes, but since each piece
is almost identical,
it's not as easy as it seems.
Look at these huge pieces.
Wow.
Yeah.
That gives you a huge field
when you're through and can proudly
display it in your den or rumpus room.
Oh, did we also...
We also have the 45 Dobbsheads on a mouse pad.
Only one. This is the last one.
Everything Must Go by 1998, friends.
Everything Must Go by July 5th, 1998.
It's swag-tastic.
Yeah.
Hey, that's a new one.
Swag-tastic.
We'll have to play that back someday.
Yes?
Swag-tasm.
The motion picture.
Hmm.
What music is that?
What is this? Cut 21?
For the new Bob action figure toy line.
Invasion of the Body Snatchers.
Oh, yes.
1978.
That one.
This is the 1978 version.
You know, I never really saw that one.
I'm...
The Donald Sutherland Body Snatchers?
Yes. I saw the one that was made after that.
And of course I saw the first one.
But that middle one, I guess I was too busy
to go to the movies when that came out.
Oh, that's...
It's actually not bad.
So I understand, and I would recognize
some of the locations and some of the people in it.
I understand.
I remember one line from it.
It has nothing to do with the monsters.
You're charging way too much at this restaurant
to have rat turds in the kitchen.
But, monsieur, that is not a rat turd.
It is a caper.
Well, if it's a caper, then eat it.
Wah, wah, wah. Busted.
That was a fun movie.
That was the first time we saw...
What's-His-Name.
Yeah, and What's-His-Name.
And What's-Her-Name.
And What's-His-Face was in that, too.
Yeah.
And then...
Well, it was hard to tell them apart
because they were just pod people.
Kind of blanks.
But Leonard Nimoy was in that.
And he was such a cold character
that you couldn't tell the difference.
Before or after.
Was he some sort of cult leader?
No, he was a psychiatrist.
Oh, okay.
And had noticed that there'd been an outbreak of people
saying, my husband's not my husband.
Well, now, sure, you may think you saw a husband.
It's not...
Not too reassuring somehow.
Hey, watch it.
We're starting to talk about old monster movies again.
It always becomes that, apparently.
Yeah, you start...
How does that happen?
You start off on lofty, ascended subjects like J.R. Bob Dobbs, Slack, X-Day, Jehovah One,
and all that.
The important things.
And then you end up talking about invasion of the colossal faceless men.
But that's what brought us here.
That's what brought us to the church.
That is true.
That is.
It was my childhood religion, monsters.
That's one of our great commonalities.
They're a language in which one may speak freely,
unless you're a Christian.
And we are determined to rescue the monsters of the world,
the freaky, the beastly, and the downright weird.
Only, how do we find you?
Come on, isn't anybody listening?
Well, you're not going to reach any monsters like that.
No wonder your vlog doesn't have any listeners.
You're using normal internet.
Uh, yeah, that's how it's done.
Uh, yeah.
If you're normal.
You gotta use the monster web.
There's a monster web?
Your TCP IP RIP ports are all glitchy.
Let me just take care of this for you.
Behold, the monster web.
Available anytime, anywhere.
Mind blown.
I think it's time to say to yourself
That I'm happy being me and nobody else
No, no, turn off the shadows
Let's feast the light
Don't have to be afraid, nobody's gonna fight
Come out, little ghouls, wherever you are
Don't have to hide from one another
We need each other, so come out, little ghouls
Together we're strong
Don't have to hide from one another
So won't you come along now?
Now, now, now, now, now
Everyone, come out to death
Be who you are
We're awesome monsters
Let's celebrate
We're better together
Forever and ever and ever in monster high
Hey, little ghouls
Where are you, little ghouls?
Come one, come all
We all have so much in common
Hey, little ghouls
Where are you, all my ghouls?
Let's have a ball
Come on now, it will be awesome
Everyone, come out to death
Be who you are
We're awesome monsters
Let's celebrate
We're better together
Forever and ever and ever in monster high
Everyone, come out to death
Be who you are
We're awesome monsters
Let's celebrate
We're better together
Forever and ever and ever in monster high
If you identify with the hero killing the monster, you're not the material we're looking for.
Yeah, the hero is the cardboard cutout moved into place at the appropriate time.
Go join the army or something.
Villains are the ones that make things happen.
Heroes only react to...
It's the villain who really causes us anything interesting to happen.
But the monsters, the monsters are the subgeniuses.
Yeah.
And Bob is the greatest monster of them all.
King Bob versus Godzilla.
Abbott and Costello meet Bob.
House of Bob-ula.
I noticed in that art montage that the bear one somehow didn't make it into that one.
Into that one.
What in that one?
Yes, the one that just passed of all the ones that were...
The ads and so on.
You like those Doc Savage covers converted into subgenius things?
Yes.
Onan did that.
Yes. How appropriate.
I love James Balmer stuff.
Yeah.
See, did I just pause it?
I don't know. You brightened it up.
Superior mutant.
Doc Savage.
Doc Sewage.
Or kill me, Doc Savage.
Are we doing that again? We're looking at pictures that the audience can't see.
Careful, kids.
Well, it's radio. They can come up with their own bloody mental pictures.
Yes, the people here can actually see the pictures. So really there's very little to complain about.
I guess the Hidalgo Corporation was like the Captain Company.
Well, at least you got your stuff from there. Not from the Captain Company.
But back to monsters.
Are not the first stories monster hunt tales?
Of course they are.
The epics? The first known English...
It took humanity years to clear out those monsters.
Gilgamesh is a monster hunt story. Beowulf...
Grendel's attacks upon Heorot and his tussle with Beowulf when his arm was ripped out by the roots.
Me arm.
As every student of English literature does.
And then of course there are more modern day creatures like the Jabberwock and so forth.
Moby Dick is a monster hunt story.
Originally Mocha Dick.
Mocha Dick?
Yes. You know, changed for the book.
That's in bad taste.
Sorry, that's the way it is.
The actual whale that the story was based on.
Known as Mocha Dick.
Oh really?
Yeah.
I didn't know that.
Super huge whale. Well, you saw the recent movie.
In the Heart of the Sea.
Yes.
I sought that movie out.
In the 20th century, sperm whales were only known to grow about 40 feet long.
But it takes a couple hundred years for them to get as large as that whale was that sank the whaling ship Essex.
When they started whaling and sticking members of the pod, this giant monster came and stove the front end into the back end.
And then, if the movie is accurate, he continued to torment the survivors in the boats.
Yeah, he followed them across the seas.
Following them for miles.
Yeah.
Doing things to them.
Dogging them. Whaling them.
Yeah.
At the very end of the movie, spoiler alert.
Thor, God of Thunder, is standing there with a harpoon ready.
And the whale just swims right up to their little raft.
They're barely surviving it.
And he somehow can't bring himself to harpoon this thing looking at him with its huge eyes.
Yeah, the whale rolls over and just eyes him as if to say, look, if you guys quit, I'll quit.
And so Thor puts his harpoon down and the mighty whale swims away.
And everybody else says, what are you doing?
He was right there.
That's a fun movie.
It's a great monster movie, actually.
Not a lot of people would, I don't think it was.
A whale of a good movie.
Yes, the problem was that it came out at the same time as Star Wars and was forced off the screen by Wookiees and jittering robots.
Yeah, I rushed to sea in the heart of the sea, but I waited for the bootleg.
The Star Wars movie.
I've got my own copy of In the Heart of the Sea.
I saw the Star Wars movie at the new Alamo Drafthouse in San Francisco.
But you know about those, don't you?
No.
These are movie theaters where you order a dinner while you're sitting there.
But they insist that you don't damage the viewing experience.
And if you make a cell phone call, you're thrown out.
But the most interesting thing about it is to see the waiters coming duck walking between the seats so they won't get in anybody's way with the tray with your stuff on it.
And you order silently by checking off things in a little card at your miniaturized table which swings out by your seat.
And the movie costs about as much as a movie anywhere.
If you're elderly, attenuated, and blasted with antiquity,
you get a senior discount like me.
But once you start ordering this expensive gourmet food,
you're going to spend, you could get a $19 milkshake,
which is supposedly the best milkshake made anywhere.
But then again, what a dent in the wallet.
And other treats are available.
It's not just popcorn.
They make the money off the popcorn.
That's why they make the money.
The popcorn and the soda drinks.
The gevox of lamb in plum jelly or whatever they're...
Or in the dark, it's kind of hard to see what it actually is.
What? What? What? What? What? What was that?
Get in the pipe.
All right, we got our marching orders, kids.
That was a close one, yeah.
That was a big, it's a big pipe.
That's true.
There's a ladder.
A ladder goes up into the bowl.
It all started with that Bob Kane cover for DC Comics.
Where a giant Joker was going to smoke Robin and Batman in a huge pipe.
And they were feebly holding up their gloved hands to remonstrate with the Joker.
Who looked dementedly insistent with a giant flaming match on turning Gotham's crime fighters to ash.
It's hard to turn down that coffee.
I'm surprised I haven't seen a doctored version of that.
Well, I...
It's...
Somewhere I've seen that item repeatedly recently.
It's in my mind.
I must have seen it somewhere.
I built a giant pipe that you can live in.
It's four stories high.
The stem is a 50, 60 foot hallway.
I can move in there, you say?
If you're in the Minecraft universe, you can.
Oh, I see.
I built it in the virtual reality.
You really showed that old broad down the street.
He was living in the chute with all those kids.
That's right.
I got a pipe, honey.
I got a damn four-story pipe.
It's...
You'll have to visit someday.
My old family smells like feet.
You smell like fine shag and froth.
Rich rum-soaked shag.
I had not thought about that.
The old lady who lives in the chute.
Yeah.
It's not a new chute.
The athlete's foot is a problem.
I've got some cream for that if you need it.
It's like a boot.
Oh, I should mention, by the way, folks, I actually have...
We have a first aid kit and...
I got Bag Bomb.
And pills.
That's a first aid kit.
Yeah, she's got Bag Bomb.
I've got a magical cream that'll get rid of almost any kind of rash and it really helps with poison.
Oh, I fell for that too.
This isn't a joke.
I'm saying this for real because we are at a campground and some of you are absolute idiots.
And we'll bathe in...
Hey.
Or screw in the poison ivy.
It's been known to happen.
It happened to Sister Mary Squared one time.
Nature boy said, hey, let's go into this lovely little grotto here and do it.
She went to the hospital for that.
So you've got Bag Bomb, you've got analgesic cream, which you will apply with your own hands.
We've got analgesic cream.
Right.
We've got them kind pills.
We've got the Jesus J-E-E-Z exclamation point.
We've got those kind.
We've got every kind.
The kind pills, you might say.
Ibuprofen.
Them kind pills.
Wasp attractant.
In an emergency, you never know when you need that.
You brought that?
Sure.
I always bring it to X Day.
I thought...
Why do you think they stay on you instead of me?
There was one X Day where I seem to remember that somebody took the wasp attractant out of the car.
Wasp attractant?
Yeah.
But then somebody else put it back, I guess.
But I think it was even you who said, we don't need this at X Day.
And now there you are flogging it.
Yeah.
Wasp attractant.
You never know when you're going to need something like that.
Attract yellow jackets also.
Well, they are wasps.
Oh, I had a great...
I had a field day with those big red wasps at our Texas house.
They must have a nest in there somewhere.
They get born and then they can't escape.
They bang their heads against the windows over and over again until they finally drop to the floor where, damn it, the hound dog eats them.
Without getting stung?
Oh, they're dead.
But he loves them.
He loves them.
They're big.
They could still get stuck.
These are like this big.
They're crunchy.
They're very tough.
They're difficult to kill.
They are.
I have happened to...
Surprisingly difficult to kill.
I had leather...
Really thick leather gloves on.
It just came in.
There was a wasp bothering Wee Ma Ma.
How awful.
And I stunned it with a fly swatter and then I just decided, well, I'll just smush it with this glove.
And I couldn't.
Like his head was too hard to crush.
I finally...
I guess I...
I think I threw him down the disposal.
Now, I'm the kind of person who carries insects out of the house, honestly.
A regular Buddha over here.
Yeah.
I'm a Jainist.
That's what Ed Kemper had to do with his mother's bitching vocal cords, putting down the garbage disposal.
Venomous snakes and wasps, if they wander into the wrong place, my job is to hunt the monster.
Sorry.
That's just the way it goes.
It's them or us.
And you don't let...
You don't...
Oh, our music is gone.
If music be the food of love, play on.
But really, you know, it's like a moral decision.
Every time you deal with a bug in the house...
But you were so polite to Elroy yesterday.
Him being a locust and all.
Well, I don't...
Both he and Stang are visitors.
I'm not...
I don't have bug fear.
I have bug love.
I love bugs.
Including that cute Volkswagen that can talk.
I was afraid you were gonna mention that.
You put eyelashes on the headlights so you don't feel so inverted.
I love all life.
I'm gonna rupture up all earth animals onto my escape vessel.
On the Lovecraft.
Including the thousands, untold thousands of tons of microorganisms that live underground.
That far outweigh all...
They weigh all surface life.
Yes, outweigh all life on the surface of the earth.
They are the weight of the earth.
And they don't need sunlight to do their stuff.
I work well at night.
I must be microbial.
Based on Spirochete.
Stang ranch ambient sounds.
We're at a campground.
We don't need that.
We're going to wallow in nostalgia now?
No, no, no, no, no.
Is that the farting of the earth sound on there?
They're like the mudas noises that have been reported.
Strange creakings, rumblings, and sounds that the earth makes.
Restive...
Low frequency noise.
For all of creation is awake and complaining.
I'm totally awake.
vesomar Also awake.
All?
Get a job out with degrees you should learn from.
Like me?
B PLAYER AT A CLUB.
Thank you.
This is my very first
All Monsters show.
I'm so excited to be here
just for you.
Just for this occasion.
Let me hear it, Monsters!
We are the Monstars, Monstars, we are the Monstars
Slippin' on the sea and I'm feelin' real good
I'm just bein' me just like a monster should
Let's have a good time, live your life out loud
Visionary, legendary, bring that monster out
We're gonna dance, dance, dance the Friday way
We are, we are, we are, we're the Monstars, Monstars
It's time to celebrate!
Well, monsters, ghouls, creeps, and geeks, you heard it here first.
Monster High is here to stay.
And while we monsters haven't quite learned to live with humans just yet,
I'm certain the day will still come.
In the meantime, we have a pretty sweet monster ambassador for us out in the human world.
Mom?
For the first time in ages, monsters were truly coming out of hiding.
One monster step at a time.
Because, as you know, it's not impossible, just challenging.
Hey, I'm trying to impart words of wisdom here.
Can't you see?
Don't be afraid of your glow.
No more.
No more hiding in the dark.
You're alive, be who you are.
And I'm gonna shine so that everyone knows.
I'm on top of the world, gotta let you know.
Feeling so amazing, just the way I am.
Nothing is ever impossible.
Feeling so amazing.
Yeah.
Just the way I am.
Just me and me.
I want everyone to see.
I'm on top of the world, gotta let you know.
Feeling so amazing, just the way I am.
Just the way I am.
Mom?
We're the best.
Alright.
Nevermak Pull agasps of karate
I would to how like the moon for a mommy mocha.
Dad you are not even talking
You have better sized rien