It's been a busy month, so this hour of Slack number 1,243 is a rerun of excellent hour of Slack number 506 from August 1995.
Yeah, it was a great show, wasn't it?
Is that it?
You're like a crazy person.
Sound effects.
There we go, with sound effects.
They've been injected.
You are about to experience the awe and mystery which reaches from the inner mind to the subgenius hour of Slack.
Well, Paul, keep listening.
Yes, sir, and thank you, brother, and you keep preaching.
Thank you so much.
God bless.
Bye.
Thanks.
Boy, oh, boy, oh, boy.
Melba.
Oh, hello, Steve.
Hi, Melba.
God bless you.
Well, thank you.
You were at the meeting tonight.
I was.
I just got home about three minutes ago from North Church.
Yeah.
And I received such a blessing.
I was just telling the producer.
It was wonderful.
Really?
Yes.
I just have been so heavy, heavy laden with cares and worries.
Really?
And you just, the Lord used you tonight to just lift a burden.
I just, I've never laughed.
Like that.
Just laughed my cares away.
The ghost.
Oh, it was wonderful.
It was wonderful.
Oh.
And I enjoyed your singing, praising.
Frank and I haven't had a time like that since we saw Tony Bennett back in the late 60s.
We were swinging.
Oh, I don't know.
Oh.
We just, our only, you know, the only problem, we were sitting kind of close to that, that,
you know, crazy coon that kept laughing all night.
Driving us nuts.
Well, Tony Bennett, huh?
My friend, Lucius Tate, was there.
I think she was laughing because she'd seen him outside in the lobby and he shook his
dick or something.
What?
What is she, what is this?
One, two, three.
I don't know what, what is that?
I don't know.
Tony Bennett.
That's crazy.
Hi, who is it?
Do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do.
This guy's calling.
You calling from Tulsa?
No, no, no, no.
You're here in Dallas?
I live in Tulsa.
This is Rowdy Redding.
How you doing?
Oh, good, good.
I'm getting blessed tonight.
I really am.
Great.
Here, near Boston.
I'm in a little area called Chelmsford.
And we picked you up out here.
And, uh, you know, I'm a little bit of a, you know, a little bit of a, you know, a little
thing.
And I, it's great.
I wanted to tell you about a fellowship we started just for Christian truckers.
Uh-huh.
I'm a long-haul trucker.
Right.
And, uh, man, it's tough.
It's tough.
Uh-huh.
The lifestyle a lot of these guys lead.
And we started a Christian ministry and outreach for, for truckers.
And I've, I'll tell you what, listening to your show on the radio, I mean, an area's
where I can get it.
It's been a real blessing to me because I'm, I'm learning how to deal with people, you
know.
Wow.
And telling, you know, telling some of these.
There's a lot of guys that, uh, you know, that are, that are, that are, uh, you know,
They were Christians at one time, you know, but...
Backslidden.
Yeah, and they slid into this thing of feeling sorry for themselves.
Hey, you know, listen, you know...
Yep.
The brother Steve.
On the road again.
Cross.
Right.
Hallelujah.
And it's, you know, it's what they need to hear a lot of times.
Thank you, Jesus.
You know, and...
Because these guys, you wouldn't believe it.
These are guys that don't make a great deal of money.
They make okay money, but all these guys buy more...
More cocaine in a week than Robert Tilton Ministries.
I mean...
I don't know about that.
I've never heard about that, but it's okay.
Yeah, I...
Well, you know, it's incredible what these guys do.
We don't...
When we talk to them, we've learned a lot from listening to Praise in the Nights.
You know, we don't let them tell these stories, you know, these hard luck stories.
It's like, get to the point.
Tell them what your problem is.
Shit, let's talk about salvation, you know?
And quit moping and meandering around the cross.
You sorry ass, you know, feeling sorry for yourself, Chris.
Hey, wait, wait, wait.
You need to watch your language.
What did you just say?
What?
What did you sorry what?
Oh, I said taking the sorry path of feeling...
Oh, sorry path.
Yeah.
Oh, good, okay.
Because, you know, they're moping and meandering around the cross.
Right.
And, you know, feeling sorry for themselves.
Amen.
I say, you know, wake up, Christians.
The time is short.
Amen.
Preach it.
Get your thumbs out of your ass.
Get...
Is that what he said?
Get that guy off.
There it was.
Man, I'll tell you.
Hey, it's radio.
You know, good spirit, huh?
What is it tonight?
Is it a full moon or something?
Come on, man.
If you're going to be on radio, use your head.
You can't be full of the Holy Ghost and talk like that.
On radio or off radio.
Give me a break.
Use some common sense.
That's right, friends.
Sorry about those awkward cuts there.
But, you know, that guy let a bunch of real bad language slip by.
And didn't even notice until the guy got to the stuff that everybody else doesn't worry about playing anymore.
God, what a world.
Well, that tape was given to us from Brother Russell Ministries.
And, you know, to tell the truth, I probably shouldn't give their address.
Um...
He told me to feel free to write for more info or goodies.
It's in that tape trading world.
It's a limbo nightmare world, friends, where a lot of this stuff comes from.
It's the traders of, shall we say, tape recordings of sociological experiments,
often using the telephone as a medium of experimentation upon the minds of those who listen in.
Well, those who are out there would be preaching, and they ain't preaching good enough, friends.
You're going to hear some good preaching tonight.
I don't know which, but there's always some kind of good preaching on this thing.
In the meantime, let's follow what that fellow suggested.
And, you know, if you're going to be on the radio, make some sense, okay?
Susie, Susie, Susie, I want you to croak a last few words to the listeners.
The listeners generally are used to hearing your sparkling laughter and clear, clear, soothing voice.
And instead they get this.
Ah!
Beauty is only skin deep, but slack goes all the way to the bone.
You...
I second that.
Me and my comic books, my comic books will testify to that fact.
And now, back to the...
The Betty Boop Scandals.
Professor Nuts and Bolts is one of the foremost scientists in this country, you screwball.
Oh!
What you hit me for, Moe?
Just trying to knock some sense into your head.
Oh!
What a soup of noise!
Yes.
There, praise Bob, dear friends.
This...
I don't know what to call it in the background.
This is by the good Reverend Toe Fropphauser.
I love to say his name.
That's Toe Fropphauser.
Frauhauser.
To, Reverend
To Frauhauser.
He sent us this tape
full of noise.
But it's kind of cool noise.
It's so over-modulated
artistically. Listen to that.
Well, actually, let's,
it does kind of hurt.
Um,
enclosed, you will find
a copy of my stupid tape,
Frutenfiener.
I have sent it to you in the hopes that you will find
it entertaining and or useful. Please feel
free to give copies of this tape to anyone you
think would enjoy it. Although I prefer
you send email to
at FrappeeBrewichCom
or on FrappeeLand
BBS
at 713
3203 and blah blah blah blah blah.
Well, see? Now, Franta, if you
were on the internet, you'd already have memorized
those ridiculous numbers.
And, well,
friends, let's get religious now. Let's go
to a
live subgenius
devival as it happens
months ago in Cleveland
with live
on stage in the tent
at a big tent show that
Brother Steve Bevilacqua
produced, the most recent one.
Oh, this is really distracting
sound effect music in the background.
This particular sermon was broadcast
about four shows ago, but this
is different. This is the live,
live version. We broadcast a
studio version, I believe,
back about show 502.
This one here is 505.
I mistakenly called 502,
503. See? Now, you just
gotta remember to do
http://sunsight.unc.edu
slash subgenius
and everything will be fine.
It's got the western saliva in it.
Yes, it's got your own rich, moist
Texas saliva in it. Friends, I have
a confession to make.
I
well there aren't many sins
in the church of the subgenius
but I committed one
the stupidest sin of all
a couple of months ago
I worked too hard
on slack
oh I thought Bob
was going to be so proud of me
let me tell you
what happened
it was in 1875
I'd been preaching in a saloon
in Kansas City
Kansas City wasn't a very big town then
I was
crawled out of the saloon
crawled underneath the saloon
I'd been preaching in the saloon
and I'd had a bit too much to drink
and I was crawling
through the muddy streets of Kansas City
it was a thunderstorm
going on
there were literally rivers
of shit washing through the streets
they weren't paved
back then
I crawled out of that saloon
and who should I see
riding by on a great big white horse
but J.R. Bob Dobbs himself
wearing a great big old cowboy hat
and thick cowboy boots
and I'm a subgenius preacher
and I saw my personal savior
ride by
so of course
I had to lick
his boots
yes I saw Bob
and I had to lick his boots
I'm a preacher
in fact I had to kiss him on the cheek
I had to kiss his boots
I just ran alongside the horse
licking away on Bob's boots
I didn't care if he'd been walking
through the prairie
stepping on buffalo chips
and pasture pastries
and meadow muffins
I didn't care if he'd been walking
through the horse awful
filled streets
I didn't care what was on Bob's boot
but I licked it
oh I worked hard licking Bob's boots
I didn't care what was on Bob's boot
I licked and kissed and licked and kissed
it was disgusting
didn't taste real good
but you know
when you see Bob's boot cheeks
you gotta kiss them
and I was thinking
oh won't Bob be proud of me
oh Bob's gonna be so damn proud
cause I worked so hard
for slack
and friends my lips
got chapped
from licking Bob's boots
they got more chapped
than my chaps
they were like
creaking leather beaks
I couldn't preach
I couldn't even smile
to eat a hamburger
I had to flatten it down
and feed it in through the slit
I had to take saddle soap
and rub it all over my mouth
in order to loosen up those leathery
saddle like lips
from kissing Bob's damn boots
for too long
my lips were cold and I was like
crackin' and bleedin'
and gettin' that lemon oil
and saddle soap out
I was sick friends
I made myself sick
working too hard
for Bob
and you know what Bob did
he said thanks for cleaning my boots
dumbass
and he left me with the virus
and the yeast
but friends
I then
learned my lesson
I knew what to do
I knew it was time to do it
I knew it was time finally
to truly slack off
I pulled out my six gun
and I shot Bob Dobbs in the back
must have been the right Bob
cause you know he just kept riding on
but I slacked off
and that crust on my lips
sloughed off
and that's why I'm here to preach to you tonight
and this is where
here I started talking about the bats
and it got a little bit too
well just a bit too raunchy but
I had truly learned my lesson
no more would I work too hard for slack
in fact I'm tired of doing this right now
maybe I ought to just quit
I think I'm done
no more wrapped up
in white linen
wrapped in white linen
as cold as the grave
so beat the drums slowly
and play the fight
with the bat
And thefood marches
you'll hear me yell
Take me
And even though
I'veéŸ³ed out many a song
Be sure to wait
before I
break down
Calhoun's pee
and get a good roll
It's just about time
to get back
and show you
that I'm not alone
I got to do this
and of course Eddie Arnold did it better
but
can't get away
It still makes me cry, my dear.
It's so sad.
We've only got half an hour left.
We've got to have Circus Apocalypse.
We've got to have the head launch.
The head launch.
And we've got to have...
I've got to get this news around my neck.
And the testimonials.
And the loading shop.
String him up!
God damn it, idiot.
Can't even tie a hangman's knot.
Take another pill.
Well, they're going to do this song about pills.
This has got to be the most pill-savvy...
...the Bible ever.
It's like people are going to leave this revival going,
well, I thought they were going to be preaching about how evil the conspiracy is,
but all they did was talk about pills.
Take another pill.
How many words can you think of that rhyme with pill?
It'll cure every ill.
Take another pill.
Your brain will become nil.
It will make you want to kill.
Take another pill.
Leave it on the windowsill.
Put your mind through rototill.
Take another pill.
Just throw it on the grill.
Fall down like Jack and Jill.
Take another pill.
The vomit will start to spill.
Hey, bungalow bill.
Just take another pill.
Brew it up in your still.
Take another pill.
This is not a drill.
It will make you feel evil.
Take another pill.
You won't be happy until.
And come back for a refill.
Take another pill.
To do otherwise is unacceptable.
To do otherwise would be impossible.
Take another pill.
Pickled like a dill.
You'll feel like roadkill.
Take another pill.
Yo, yo, chill.
Walk through the daffodils.
Take another pill.
You'll be sprouting gills.
It's such a thrill.
Take another pill.
If you've been through the mill.
You'll end up on boot hill.
Take another pill.
Whales take them with their krill.
And I can't think of any more.
Take another pill.
That's the end of it. I'm on D.
I took so many pills.
Take another pill.
This nun suit is tight.
It's creeping me.
Take another pill.
All these panties don't fit.
Wait a minute. I shouldn't even wear.
Slack can only be sold.
It cannot be bought.
Take another pill.
Hey, can you guys do golfing music?
Yes.
Cause we got us a head to launch.
Take another pill.
Are you ready?
There's many golfer heads out there.
There's people that like to launch
the lips of Lee Trevino.
The lips of Lee Trevino.
Oh yeah.
There's those out there who would put
a rocket up and launch into outer space.
The feet of Sam Snead.
Oh yeah.
Jack Nicklaus tongues
have been launched in our public school system.
Damn it.
Thanks to the Trevinas.
But when was the last time
you gazed, bare eyeballed upon
the bleeding head
of Arnold Pond?
The bleeding head
of Arnold Pond.
Oh no.
Ahhhh.
The head.
Why?
The head asked why.
Notice.
Notice this neck stub.
Notice this wound on the forehead.
They didn't just cut his head off, man.
They didn't just cut his head off.
Where is the sacred
key? Where is the holy nine
iron?
There is no sacred key.
There is no holy nine iron.
God damn it. We're just gonna
have to launch it without.
We're gonna have to boot the damn head.
Yep,
we're gonna have to launch the head by foot.
Alright.
It's a beautiful ceremony,
friend.
Alright.
In the name
of J.R. Bob Dobbs.
of Arnold Palmer himself,
the true bleeding head.
In the name
of Floatats.
In the name of Brandon Stimpy.
In the name of
Jimmy Hendrix.
I can't do
it.
Watch that head, friend.
launch it back this way.
Launch that head back this way,
friend.
That's a five hundred dollar head.
Oh, it bounced.
And his eyes
are still intact.
Oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Excuse me, friends.
I've seen so many
head launchings. That was a
nice head launching and
we did get the, you know, of course,
when you hear me doing a head launching,
friends, we're probably
using the replica
head. It's pretty realistic
and a lot of people probably don't know the difference.
And, you know, it's like faith healing.
It still works.
Now, on the other hand,
when you see Pope Sternodoc's
keycaver or Saint Jane or
hyperclites launching that head,
you better not let any of that blood
drip on you, my man,
my sir ma'am, my woman.
The universe would have
ended instantly
because it's just not, the time is
not yet nigh for their
arisal. But I'm gonna preach.
What we're really doing here, friends,
is fighting a war.
This is
a war. Believe it or not,
not very good soldiers, but
you know, the conspiracy
has something like
50,000 nuclear weapons.
The Church of the
Subgenius only has three.
And yet we dare to fight them
anyway!
Because it's always been,
it's always been the
crazy people, the maniacs
who are the only ones dumb enough
to fight City Hall.
And one of these days we're gonna win.
But it is a war,
friends, it's a war of
the humans versus the subgeniuses.
It's us versus
them. Don't you just hate
them?
And the great thing about this church is
them is anybody
you don't like! Praise Bob!
The subgeniuses versus the humans.
And you know the ironic thing
is, we're the ones who
designed the humans
80,000 years ago in Mutantis.
Our worst mistake,
dear friends,
a dreadful mistake.
Because
you gaze out,
go outside, go to your job,
go look around this room, you'll see
the humans,
the normals, the mediocritons,
the pink boys,
the Barbies and Kens,
the cage dwellers. We've got more
nasty words for them than they even have
for us.
Because the problem is, pinkness
equals boredom. The pink
is afraid of that
which is different. They are what
you might call xenophobes.
The subgenius
is what you would call a xenophile.
We get off on things
that are different. We don't necessarily
like them, but when we first
see them, we go,
weird as hell, that's disgusting.
Tell me more!
The pink will say,
string them up.
We wait and then say,
But friends, it's a,
it is a religion.
Among other things, sure,
it's a big stupid
art project,
an excuse for
disgusting no good, good for nothings
like these guys to get up and jam.
But it is a religion.
Friends, it's a living,
bleeding religion for today.
It's not one of these old fashioned religions
for some guy who's been dead for
and hasn't answered his message machine
in 2000 years.
And when we talk about the
conspiracy, oh yeah, that's a
big joke, they're thinking, yeah,
they're making fun of those conspiracy
coops. We're talking about the conspiracy
that is so
dumb that it doesn't
even know that it is a conspiracy.
They do not even
know how bad they
are.
over themselves and much worse us.
Pinks, friends.
The conspiracy is a lot bigger
than Republicans versus Democrats
or Communists versus
Capitalists.
The conspiracy is nothing but an attitude
of distrust.
They distrust anything they don't
understand. And they don't
understand much at all.
Yeah, the conspiracy, it's a real big
joke. About as funny as the
headlines in today's paper, don't
you think?
Yep, it's not a clever conspiracy.
It doesn't even know it's a damn
conspiracy. It's a confederacy
of dunces.
The pinks are
literally stereotypes of
themselves. Mindless
bovine stereotypes like a herd
of cows and yet
they could destroy the world.
In fact, they may already have.
We're gonna destroy
the world too, but we want to make sure
the end of the world happens properly.
False
prophets, dear friends.
False prophets
surround us.
And the worst thing about them is
they call us wolves in sheep's
clothing. I'd sure rather
be a wolf in sheep's clothing
than sheep in wolves clothing.
Which is what we're dealing
with.
Now you may notice
that things seem to be getting a little worse
these days. Everybody's got
cancer. You get a new disease
every time you screw somebody.
There's poisons in the air.
The weather's kind of funny
lately. And the
world is horribly overpopulated
and so forth and so on.
You think about how bad it is
now. Think about what they're
not telling you about.
Well they've got all kinds
of tricks up their sleeves.
And they call the church of the subgenius
some kind of a cult.
Oh yeah, a cult.
I don't know, it seems like
if the United
States can get millions
of people to bury toxic waste
in their own backyards, how
is that any different from Jim Jones
getting 900 people to commit suicide?
America
is a cult these days.
Praise Rush Limbaugh.
The ATF is a cult
for that matter.
They barbecued all those nuts
just because they thought
some idiot
that thought he was Jesus had a bunch
of guns.
But you know the worst thing, the worst
thing about the conspiracy is
they make you think it's natural that
they make you want to work
for a living, dear friends.
They talk on and on and on about
family values, but they've got it
set up to where mom has to work,
dad has to work,
and the kids come home to an empty house.
Bob never said,
Bob's no communist.
He doesn't want everybody equally poor.
Bob Dobbs wants everybody
equally rich,
but without working.
Without working, dear friend.
Oh, but you say,
oh I don't work, but that's all,
I don't work for the conspiracy.
I'm a freelancer, I sell art,
I'm in a band,
the conspiracy can't get me.
Oh no, I don't work for the conspiracy.
You are, everybody works for the conspiracy.
They've got you by the balls
or the ovaries.
All the time, and all the, right now
they're probably just kind of tickling.
They've got you on a leash,
and they'll let you run pretty far
on that leash.
But when they decide you've run far enough,
when you've got a real good head of steam up,
and you're taunting along going,
man, I guess I'm free of the conspiracy.
Wow! They yank that leash back,
and you never forget.
Never forget again.
Dear friend, you may forget
the conspiracy for a minute,
but they'll never forget you.
They hate you worse than
you hate them, and they don't even know you.
As Bob Dobbs said,
Act like a dumb sh**.
And they will treat you
as an equal.
Truer and sadder words
were never spoken, dear friend.
Wow.
Man.
What a devival.
Well, that left me feeling
pretty devived, I'll tell you, friends.
But actually,
it is such a joy to work
with Einstein's Secret Orchestra.
I don't know what it is.
I just love
doing stuff with those guys.
They're in Cleveland.
And they're on
WCSB there in Cleveland
every Thursday, what is it,
Thursday nights until like 10 o'clock
or 11. I never can remember
I know we go from about
11.30 to 1, and it
always supplies me with
an hour of slack
material that I just
it's just such a joy
to not have to do it
by myself
sometimes, you know.
Uh,
and now
as we come down near the end
of side one of this hideous
radio show,
we wonder what will be next.
Well, I'm wondering what's going to be next.
As I've said before, by the time
actually, by the time you hear this, I may be
back from the GWAR tour.
Let's flip this show over and
see what I'm going to have to listen to
nine nights in a row.
Uh,
starting next week for me, but in
the past for you because of time control,
don't you see? The cheap,
cheap, cheap form of time
control.
Who dies?
Her chance
to sin.
Ha ha ha ha!
There's the rub.
For in that
sleep of sin
what
kingdom may come?
What
of the limitless
sex and violence
in the wake
of Ragnarok?
What
of the
slaughter?
What are you going to do?
What will be your epitaph
when we get done
with you? Are you going to
cry for your mama?
Are you going to have a good time?
Are you going to be a bohama
when it's your turn to die?
The target's
crazy.
Ragnarok all around!
Karakia, Thea, Rura,
Street, Ragnarok, Party Town,
You're painting it to turn
in your brain. It isn't burning
in your sanitation. The white eyes.
The final hour's here. Now grab your
bubble litter. You're out of the gate for one time.
I don't only get to jump.
I'm gonna have some fun.
Coming out of the blue. Cranking all the dirt.
The only beauty's winning that fight.
You're all sitting. Sitting feels so fine.
You're running from the tide!
Ashes to ashes.
Stop it. Stop.
It's always one hell of a party when Ragnarok rolls around
Ragnarok and roll, Ragnarok and roll
It's time to trash the planet, Ragnarok and man the crowd
Welcome to Valhalla, do not be afraid
Now you are a zombie, and all your friends are dead
It all gets rather nasty when you get backstage
Everybody takes a closer, I hope you're undirected
And they're joking, joking and they're joking
Laughing and they're loaning, loaning a lot of bombs
And we know you're running out of time
Dust to dust
It's always one hell of a party when Ragnarok rolls around
Ragnarok and roll, Ragnarok and roll
It's time to trash the planet, Ragnarok and man the crowd
Dust to dust
It's always one hell of a party when Ragnarok rolls around
Go out and check your city, if Ragnarok battles brown
Ragnarok and roll, Ragnarok and roll
And she's buying diamonds
stairway to
heaven.
Oh, man.
I'm going to be spending
nine or ten, no, something like
eleven days in a
bus with those guys.
And do you know
what those guys look like? Do you know what that group
GWAR looks like?
The lead singer, Odorous
Urungus, looks like he's got maggots
crawling out of his
face, which isn't even much
of a face at all. It's like a
destroyed skull.
Maggot.
Demon.
Bottle of rum. CD.
Real dead
purple
skull cow.
Oh, man.
I've been hanging around with Doctors for Bob
for all these years now.
It's the GWAR universe.
We will destroy you humans!
You all humans must
crawl beneath
great might of GWAR
and Bob as he comes to rip
your face off.
Actually, I think this show may feature such
scenes as Slymenstra
Hymen gets
impregnated by some, well,
these aliens, these aliens
abduct Odorous,
I think, and
they
extract some sperm
from Odorous Urungus
and it accidentally gets
Slymenstra Hymen
pregnant.
They crucify her
and give her an abortion
while she's being
crucified, but the baby
escapes and falls in
with the aliens, and then God
arrives, but it turns out God's
nothing but a big robot. Oh, I don't want to
give away the whole plot. Anyway,
the way they put it to me
over the phone, they go,
the way our shows work
is every
three songs, no,
we said, uh, every two songs
we kill or rape somebody.
Yeah, man,
those guys, they have their own
special version of slack, but you know
their message is the same. It's a message
of hate. It's just like
the message of this church, a message of
hate and, uh, and
agony for our enemies
and pure
degeneracy and wallowing
in slack for ourselves.
Praise Bob. And
I was gonna shut up and make this be,
uh, a music show, because y'all have already heard
me ranting enough. And what
do we have coming up next here?
Um,
music by your fellow subgeniuses.
Let's pull this little wellman
head through here. This is, uh,
Dr. Bizarro
and the Disgustos.
And here we go. This ought to be
pertinent.
This don't get us famous.
Nothing will.
Ha ha!
Now people don't even
know me. Cause I'm nobody
now, you see.
But what if people are gonna
know me? Because my musical
set ain't free.
I'm gonna have a big house and
two cars. I'll have more money
than I can spend.
Because I'm gonna be rich
and famous, yes sir.
And then I can buy some friends.
Being famous really
knocks me out. It's not so
fun, you know.
And rock, babe, we'll make it
to the top. If we ever
do the rock and roll.
Yeah, baby,
that's the way.
You've got to make
the rock and roll.
You've got to make the rock and roll.
That's right.
That's so cool.
I think I'm gonna choke on
the old vomit.
I'll be so famous.
I'll have so much cash.
Famous.
I can buy me some stash.
Famous. I can buy me a car.
I'll be so famous.
It'll be so bizarre.
I'll make America
I'll be so famous.
And play it for myself
And no one else
No more freebies
And if I can't pay my bills
I'll know it was the will of the people
It's not that I haven't tried
But there's a limit to my patience
Bet your ass
You'll spend your money on bullshit
Reward the media for years
Who are just in it for the bucks
A pack of opportunists
Who get stronger as they make you weak
They lie to you when you believe it
Just like they calculate you to
Their music is all the same
They can barely write their own name
By supporting them
What does that make you?
By giving money to the strangers
While neglecting the needs of your own
People who are just in it for the bucks
Harvest what you can and what remains
Because tomorrow you'll be empty and alone
I feel like I'm doing this for nothing
Don't have a house, can't pay the rent
While you go to shows by those who didn't give a shit
The whole affair's an embarrassment
You'll spend your money on bullshit
Reward the media for years
Who are just in it for the bucks
A pack of opportunists
Who get stronger as they make you weak
They lie to you when you believe it
Just like they calculate you to
Their music is all the same
They can barely write their own name
By supporting them
What does that make you?
What doesn't matter who they are
Why did those people him?
They see that they saw fire
And note when they know
How to turn their minds
About the ones they have
Of
The
Big
Canal
.por
Whoa.
Oh, friends.
Zug's Rift.
The brilliant musician, composer Zug's Rift.
Off of a special tape.
It's promo pack tape.
And, oh, man.
I'm going to have written down on my table here.
I've written down four numbers.
They're footage numbers.
Where I'm going to have to go back through that tape.
Hold it.
I'm not going to distort Zug's thing here.
I have to go back through these four footage notations here on the tape.
And put a blank spot where there were curse words.
Curse words that you can tell by the rhyme what they are.
And I know perfectly well how irritating it is to hear those blanks.
Right in the middle of so many subgenius rants and songs and so forth.
And, well.
We want to draw attention to the fact that there seem to be these superstitious people who control the entire country.
Who feel like words.
Words, friends.
Are somehow.
You know.
They're going to mess somebody up.
They're going to do some terrible damage.
Now, primetime TV.
They're not worried about that at all.
There's big money there.
But, and you know the thing is.
On a normal rock and roll station.
They say all sorts of bad words.
Some say.
You know.
My kids say.
Well the cool stations.
You know.
Leave the words in.
And the uncool stations cut them out.
Well.
All of those stations have lawyers on retainer.
The stations that play this show.
Don't.
And the conspiracy can give them a small fine.
That can shut them down for good.
So.
Rather than just avoid those confrontational songs.
That have a lot of cussing in them.
Because they're honest songs.
We go ahead and play them.
But we hurt them.
We make it very plain that we've had to do that.
And that's just the.
That's sort of the policy around here.
That way we can hand this subversive stuff out to anybody.
And it's brother.
And say.
Oh no.
This is perfectly alright.
Because.
It doesn't have those.
Four letter words in it.
So you're safe now.
You know.
Jesus won't be mad at you for having this in the house.
For your kid having this in the house.
Because you know.
It doesn't have those bad words.
Oh.
And bad ideas.
Bad.
Bad ideas friends.
Are so.
So much more subversive aren't they.
Anyway.
Zug's Rift.
As you can tell by.
The level of intensity in that song.
You won't be surprised to know that he just recently retired from the music business.
Gave up.
He's sick and tired of dubbing tapes for six bucks each.
I know exactly how he feels.
He's gone off to join that community hidden in Colorado in the mountains.
Where all the geniuses go when they feel like it's time to just tell the normals.
Man.
I'm gone.
And it serves you right.
And I've.
I've.
I've thought about that friends.
But I'm a sub genius.
They won't let me in.
My plane would probably crash trying to find that thing.
But I can give you the number for Dr. Bizarro and the Disgustos.
Which I did last week I think.
They're at IBOB Digital.
And that's P.O.
Box 3405.
IBOB.
P.O.
Box 3405.
Skokie, Illinois.
610.
6-0-0-7-6.
Box 3405.
Skokie.
6-00-7-6 friends.
And so they're, well they're, they're a habit.
Now I'm going to have to go through and cut all that stuff out.
And you've already heard how it sounds.
It's awful ain't it.
Praise in the Night will return following station identification.
Mmm goodnight.
Pete.
Hey.
Back, back injury.
Back injury.
Yes sir.
How long you been suffering with that?
About a week.
Had about a week ago on the job.
I work in a warehouse.
Mmm hmm.
But I'm believing God.
I'm believing God.
Tonight.
I just like that, that woman before the last one.
Yeah.
I have a testimony, I have a praise report a lot like hers.
I, I tell you I was, I made an idol out of them psychiatrists.
Like that you know.
Mmm hmm.
And I had folks telling me, you know, you gotta keep going.
And I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I
was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was,
I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I
I was making practices and I was.
You should never tick coding, orã¿prior gather up.
And take an identifencia.
Myself, I didn't give a shit, I was working for somebody else.
I had been working and I was better than, and just working.
me a lot of money, too. I'm telling you, stand
up. Your back's gonna get ready to get healed right now. You ready?
You standing? Uh,
yeah. Watch it. Shake!
I believe something's happening.
Hey, hey.
I am waiting for you.
Oh, Lord.
I am waiting
for you.
I can't touch my toes.
I can't.
I don't know if you can hear this, but I'm
leaning over, touching my toes.
Ow!
Ow! Hey!
I think you bugged me up, Steve.
This guy's at the church.
I'll tell you something.
Thank you, Lord,
for your time.
Thank you, Lord.
It's a serious thing to
be involved in. This is not a game.
It's not a show.
This is kingdom of God business.
Well, I used to be
a sinner because I truly
did believe that
the Virgin married Jesus
and me were thick as thieves.
And I used to give my dough to televangelistic snobs
Then the light had shone upon me and I found J.R. Bob Dobbs
Now my wallet belongs to Bob
Yes, my wallet belongs to Bob
Well, my heart is for my honey and my brain is for my job
But my wallet belongs to Bob
Well, Bobby goes a-fropping every chance that he can get
He can outperform the biggest without even breaking sweat
So I gave him all my money, Reverend Stang said it was right
And for only $20 he did save my soul tonight
And so my wallet belongs to Bob
Yes, my wallet belongs to Bob
No more can the conspiracy my lowly wages rob
Cause my wallet belongs to Bob
Well, Bobby's got a sweetie and Connie is her name
And her ways could put the sake of it all on the table
And she's the secret whore of Babylon to shame
She reaches in Bob's pocket, feels around for something hard
And pulls her hand out holding on to his mighty credit card
So my wallet belongs to Bob
Yes, my wallet belongs to Bob
And I never have to fear cause I know Connie's on the job
Cause my wallet belongs to Bob
Yes, my wallet belongs to Bob
Well, you may have your lady and your horny green man too
Their existential energy may be what's right for you
But someday you'll grow weary of those paganistic cults
And give away your money to the one that gets results
And then your wallet will be gone
Cause your wallet will be for Bob
Yes, your wallet will be for Bob
And you will be subgenius, not another stupid slob
Cause your wallet will be for Bob
Well, I believe I am much calmer
Got the bleeding head of Arnold
And the power of Palmer
Sitting on the dashboard of my car
Praise Bob!