This is a provocative, sour, highly controversial topic that we tackle over the next 60 minutes.
We ask you to suspend your disbelief, those of you who are skeptical, those who are believers in this particular phenomenon.
We ask you not to overreact to the stories, the horror stories that you are about to hear.
For those doing the view of the United States, the major concern for American people is still the economy, not necessarily the elites.
And today the government released news statistics that seem to indicate that everything is under control.
Everything is under control.
What he is like.
But I'm only hoping that the spirit will act with him.
But I'm only hoping that we all believe C will be sold at all because
Keelbell today blamed our kill bit.
Keelbell today.
Working feverishly on the atomic bomb.
Working feverishly on an Apple satellite that can count the stars.
Seeds in an Apple satellite that can count the seeds on the atomic bomb.
Working feverishly on the atomic bomb.
Working feverishly on the atomic apple.
No one on the block.
I don't know anybody.
No one on the...
Strips of flesh had hung down his back.
And through lips that were caked with blood, strips of flesh had hung down his block.
This is mankind's first marvelous glimpse of a living human.
No one on the block.
No anybody.
Anybody.
No one on the block.
No anybody.
Anybody.
Hatch out of its shell and reach the wound cavity.
Lips that were caked with blood.
Strips.
We all believe.
All believe.
C will be sold at all because we all believe.
Of course the fish is dead but I'm like.
Of course.
C will be sold at all.
Our kill bit.
Keelbell today blamed our kill bit.
Keelbell.
Out of the oven.
Even after shaving.
I got out of the oven.
Until she gets export longer.
Roll it out.
Until she gets text longer.
Until she gets out of shaving.
I got even after shaving.
I got rolling.
She'll keep the little presses rolling.
She'll keep the little presses.
Girls.
Yet it never stings most girls.
The plane was placed.
And they blame placed by theounders of most planes.
And they blame placed by the retrouve.
without a physician.
He comes in the box
giving herself an abortion
without abuse and control.
Had had his first
with control.
with abuse and control.
Telephone.
Look out.
There you know
that there's something
burning over there.
And this I do know.
The tender age
of 60 hours
shall keep the little
gymnasium
proud of me.
Ballparks.
Where's the stuff
coming from?
From the gut.
And it's deadly.
It helps a lot.
Roll it out.
It's dangerous.
Has a good arm.
That doesn't mean
anything, Steve.
It's dangerous.
Has a good arm.
That doesn't mean
anything, Steve.
It's dangerous.
Has a good arm.
That doesn't mean
anything, Steve.
So when you've got
a headache...
Joker!
Ah!
This is not a toy.
Properly used,
it can provide
many hours
of dimensional
entertainment.
Both interesting
and fun-filled
as well as
completely adult
in every way.
Remember,
follow directions
and hump only
when ready.
A.
Debug
packaging materials.
B. Insert your unit
coupling into slot A.
C. Remove plastic
nut holder.
D. Plug in.
Remember, energy is power
and power is everybody's
business.
So we suggest that you
turn off any device
not appropriate
to your lifestyle.
If you have followed
these simple steps,
you are now in full
control of your
subgenius hour of slack.
So,
have a good time.
We have assumed control.
Yes.
We always assume control.
And we have it.
May we assume control of you?
Ah, but what about this man?
The video clearly shows Mr. Howard resisting arrest.
Trying to injure the officers with using his body.
Yes, L.A. where we treat the public like a king.
Thanks to David Lynch for that.
And so much else.
.
My mind has deteriorated.
Deteriorated in its implementation.
This led to my failure.
Much has been said about my management style.
I can tell you, I've put in long hours for the nation's benefit.
Creating troubles or tragedies.
Catchy reports.
Erroneous statements.
Thousands of documents.
Secret bank accounts and diverted funds.
So that those can be available to me on a continuing basis.
That's so pretty.
Welcome to another installment.
Wow.
A dangerous, perhaps, installment of your subgenius.
Hour of Slack.
An especially musical hour of Slack tonight, I believe.
I believe that's how it's going to turn out.
But it's that hour you come to dread and pray for every week.
And we seldom let you down.
At least as far as showing up, anyway.
What can I say?
It's that Bob show.
That Bob...
We got a piece of mail this week from a young listener in another city who wanted...
I just heard the end of your show last week.
So I didn't really get everything but the address.
But send me information about that Bob Dog religion.
And we couldn't do that.
Because I don't have any information about the Bob Dog religion.
But if you have any information about the Bob Dog...
You know...
Send it in to the address that I'll be giving to you at the end of tonight's program.
And, uh...
Slack.
This is the...
You know, it's the Slack show.
Some nights more Slack than others.
So here's a song to begin with.
Here's a song all about Slack.
Slack.
You Slack for sure.
Slack me on your wildest dreams.
Right now it's Slack.
You have the power to find Slack.
Good something for nothing.
Credit cards are taken.
Slack.
Shit cares.
I want more Slack.
Send your money now.
Conspiracy denied me again.
Send your money.
I will have my Slack.
Your Slack show is here.
Slack.
Buy more Slack.
You Slack.
Let it go.
You're very old.
All sorts of Slack.
You Slack.
Every kind of Slack imaginable.
Slack.
Slack from heaven to hell.
Slack from the very inside of the world.
Slack.
Slack from right next door.
Here you go.
Here's your Slack show, my dear.
Slack show, my lady.
Your Slack.
My dear.
My now.
You Slack.
We have you.
I don't know who you are.
I don't know.
I want my slack
You slack
Slack off
If you have a gas you can have your slack
Money is slack
Something for nothing
Slack is great
Slack
Slack is government control for your protection
I want more slack
Slack is not for everyone
You cannot take my slack away
Slack can be taken by prescription
Slack is not for everyone
Slack is for everyone
Well that was the, or were, OBE, OutBanned Experience, actually Kings of Feedback slash OBE
And I think OBE would like you to know that their phone number is not what it once was
You remember it was 1-800-OB, you know, OutBanned, 1-800-OUTBANNED
It's not that anymore
If you want to join their audio shenanigans, and you do, believe me
Don't call that number I said a minute ago
Call 1-617-LICKOBE
L-I-C-K-O-B-E
Those of you who have called their number in the past know how much fun it is
Fun waiting for those of you
And speaking of fun, here's something
Well I like it and I hope you will too
I think that's what you get from watching this
If you want to get in touch with me in the future, just call me
I'll make sure to come back
Okay, thanks
See you next time
Hey
La la
La la la la la
Boiling out in euphemism
Slowly becoming part of the water
Like a frog who never knows
That you could be dead and hotter
La la
La la la la la
Hey, how you know I'm looking at you
If you weren't looking at me
Yeah
La la
I can't seem to differentiate
Between the yellow love you give and the white sex I take
I just want to fertilize you
Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah
The tracks will appear
From the instrument of death
The bright lights will change over time
The light of sun will shine in the ground
So when the skies of coolness rise
They'll all be on its way
And I got my thoughts in order
I see hell out this year
All I see is a full space
Oh, I got the time to get on now
Oh, the tick is out of an eight
Oh, one make comes out of a chicken
Oh, I take a side of an eight
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
guitar solo
a nice long tune called Egg
by one of my new favorite bands called Mr. Bungle
and these, with any luck, are the Android Sisters
money means
security no money means terror oh oh this is angel this is angel we are the android sisters
today's topic is money money is important everyone needs money
have you been deprived of money do you stop from money withdrawal do you need a money fix
if your money is not big enough what if you lost your job the job you can't stand the job
a machine could do and do it better what if you lost that then what oh no money means terror
oh oh
oh
are you happy do you wonder why you are not happy do you live in a constant state of fear
have they made you into a money junkie do you hate your job do you have a job to hate
are you looking for a job are you looking for a job you will hate the job that could be done
by robots is this not a stupid way to live your life you need money
money me
security no money terror
oh oh
don't you think it's odd to thin in because it's painful sometimes phones do you stop
it at a constant rate and then think about it this all day long how many hours a day
can you think about it
only
unrestkan
about so much you think about money aren't you sick of thinking about money
money
but money means security no money means terror oh oh
oh
the pharaoh with satisfaction
but then to his immense surprise his empire fell before his eyes a hundred thousand busy slaves
down the
tools
stood like the canyon
the pharaoh pulled up in his wagon
and saw within those walls of glass i heard of whales go racing past a hundred thousand fishy
tails crossed his mind about the day
the
the broken tablets had been mended
the golden calf had been up and dead
and old folks said
the fire would talk of voices from the sky babies sailing down the nile the recipe for locust pie
a hundred thousand frogs per mile we'd always ask them to describe
the
child
the child
the child the child
Bushes that refuse to burn Steamy sandals hardly worn
Raining blood, raining bread The night we painted Egypt red
Now shut that covet, shut that lie Now shut that bonk, you neighbour's wife
The recipe for egg-tripe lice A hundred ways to kill a fly
Love your daddy, love your mummy Put your bread and milk and honey
He cut his fish, he did, he did Never beat the wife and kids
Sloughed through deserts, sloughed through sand Until we reached the promised land
Now shan't not kill, now shan't not steal Shan't not plough in a jottery
Jottery size of fifty-pea White camel, camel shoe, camel shoe, camel shoe
Gold, gold, gold yiителей
Stop
Music
Okay, following the Android Sisters, talking on the subject,
although I think we are all the subject of money,
following that was either a song called Charlton Heston
by a band called Stump,
or the song may have well just been called Stump Charlton Heston,
which isn't hard if you've ever seen him.
I'm not sure about that, but I know this.
This is The Clash.
Of course. Of course.
Raymond?
The Clash.
Don't leave.
Well, I have actually, so far.
Rajwa, Rajwa.
The poor and the rich, the young and the old be smeared with guiltless gore.
I mustn't panic.
No time for regrets.
The Congress wants more.
Rebellion, the awful realization of it assails us.
Who is to command us all?
My name does not matter.
I have my misgivings, little experience.
There's no sleep for us. All is chaos.
But it's better than we dared hope.
The slaves to buy their freedom with army pay.
Our insubordinate, undisciplined New Englanders are beginning to obey orders.
We're true rebels now.
All of us here and in Congress walk daily in the shadow of the hangman.
But whenever any form of government becomes destructive of those ends,
it is the right of the people to alter or abolish it
and to institute new government.
We can expect the utter destruction,
invasion of all our homes.
Savage is turned loose on our frontiers.
But we have more than our lives or our property.
The nosso trabalho vai ser semana,
결혼
um município
cabal heart
cabal trão
Thank you.
Several times in fact, I'm able to transport myself there and back.
Zero gravity on an interstellar slide, breaking through to the other side.
Sex, food, sex, food.
TV preachers and creature preachers all night long.
Hey! Hey!
Sex, food, sex, food.
I've been to the Twilight Zone several times in fact.
I'm able to transport myself there and back.
Zero gravity on an interstellar slide, breaking through to the other side.
Sex, food, sex, food.
TV preachers and creature preachers all night long.
Life and love.
Sex, food, sex, food.
Well, I'll be darned.
That was a CD that just happened to be here at the station tonight.
It's a group called Alien Sex Fiend.
It's a song called Alien Sex Fiend.
And last week we got a call, or I got a call, from a listener with a request.
And since this was not only a paid up pleasure to this program, but a member of our beloved church,
we hear those requests.
Bob and his chosen, they do not hear the prayers of those who do not pledge or join the Church of the Subgenius.
So, this is an old favorite, although we haven't played this in a long, long time.
We only played it once.
This is Hubert Goetz.
This Sunday, stay tuned right after tapeworm baseball for...
Abedin Costello, Meek.
The Antichrist.
But Abed is the Animus.
Lou Costello is the Anima.
Spring Byington is the Magna Mater.
And John Ireland is the Beast.
In Abed and Costello Meet the Antichrist.
Check, check, check, check, check, check, check, check, check, check, check, check, check, check, check, check, check.
What is it now, Costello?
Look, look, look at that throne.
Which throne?
That throne, the Holy of Holies.
You mean the seat of the throne of Jerusalem?
I mean the throne of Jehovah.
I saw him sitting there.
What's the big deal? There's nobody there.
Will you stop fooling around and shut up and pass me the Kabbalah.
Check, I saw him there.
Who?
David Rockefeller.
But if I see you hitting the Holy Sacrament one more time.
See our two G.I. jerks say,
Nuts to the Nazis like this.
Now Homer, listen to me.
It's simple.
The forces of dark and the forces of light will fight for the last time.
You mean like Joe Louis?
No, no, Homer, the apocalypse.
Oh yeah, apocalypse. Oh, I like that Jamaican music.
No, no.
Don't you understand? It's Armageddon.
Armageddon what?
No, not Eurogeddon, Armageddon.
I don't understand.
You're telling me there's a final fight between dark and light?
But it's not a title book.
That's right.
You tell me it's Apocalypseo, but it's not Jamaican Gant.
You tell me it's Armageddon, but the only thing I know is I'm getting tired of trying to figure out this book of revelations.
See Lou go gaga over curvaceous Hilary Brooke, but bite off more hosts than he can chew when he winds up up to his stripes in hot holy water.
Homer, it's kind of hot in here.
How about if we step outside to the veranda?
That's okay by me, lady.
Why, you adorable little finger. Shy, aren't you?
Ah, shucks, yes, ma'am.
Call me Hilary.
Okay, Hilary.
Well, if you're ever lonely, Homer, you can give me a call. You won't regret it.
You're a nice lady. What's your number?
Here, it's 666-6666.
666-6666.
That's right.
Abb and Gastello meet the Antichrist this Sunday right after tapeworm baseball.
Subtitles by the Amara.org community
And thank you, Hubert Goetz.
Here again is Mr. Bungle.
.
Thank you.
Wake up. Time to die.
I'm just going to back you up.
Oh my God. Oh my God.
Oh my God.