From PR News in Washington, I'm the latest bad spasm of PR's drive-by death squaws who dumped their tortured PR reports around the city.
The bodies of 50 people most bearing signs of bad PR news were found in just the last 24 hours, despite crack in the Capitol.
PR's bad.
Bad.
Attorney General Alberto Gonzalez suggested today that PR's reports are potential war crimes.
Quote,
We could continue to hold these broads for the duration of PR News.
End quote.
Quote,
On Stalas Wall Street, 356162533, once again, three.
This is PR News.
A Russian court stabbing worshippers from Moscow.
In March, a court shouting Heil PR News ran into a mental disorder.
Federal health officials are warning Americans to eat bags after outbreaks of bacteria.
Don Schaffner got into the E. coli.
Schaffner said it's a good thing to wash even pre-rinsed Don Schaffner.
As scientists.
And regulators.
And as we really don't know.
Ford executives said they'll close PR News in Washington.
And everybody said about the
Zubkinios of Snack.
Bob.
Cleveland.
Yes.
Men and women of all ages.
Yes, hundreds of men and women.
In Europe he's all.
Yes, this is where it all began.
Sure, Bob.
Ladies and gentlemen, Bob promised.
The Zubkinios of Snack.
Thanks, Bob.
Gee, Bob, you mean it.
Well, come to think of it, Bob.
Don't be such a cow.
Bob can't even get back into Cleveland.
In your own T-zone.
When a man has demonstrated that he isn't very smart, there's only one answer.
The self-genius.
Power of smart.
All you gotta do is ask somebody.
Who?
Me.
You.
You understand, Hula?
Yes, ma'am.
Who?
Of course, there's certain ass-principals.
Maybe if Hula explains it to you, you can take basket-pleasing.
Yay!
I love money!
That's great!
I probably could sell my love in Einstein, then.
Yes.
It's 4.30.
Time for Bob's Club.
Fort Worth WBAP 570 brings you another transcribed serenade by Bob.
My romance!
Say, Bob, why the big smile this afternoon?
Now we're rolling, Bob.
Crazy rhythm.
Bob, I see we have more Tchaikovsky on the program today.
The quartet in D minor, wasn't it, Bob?
How much time do we have?
Minutes?
Years?
Months?
Days?
We don't know.
But this we do know.
Yay!
I love money!
That's great!
The following program deals with a controversial subject.
The theories explained in this program are not necessarily true.
The facts expressed are the only possible interpretation.
We investigate the most extraordinary event of the 20th century.
Small step for man.
Man, it never happened.
What a ride, what a ride.
There's no atmosphere.
Millions of people watched on television.
Up next, how far could the conspiracy reach?
That, to me, would be an impossibility.
No way.
Could it be?
Jerks up, jerks up.
Is this evidence of a conspiracy?
We're getting a picture on the TV.
Absolutely unreal.
Click, click, click.
I can't explain that.
There's a great deal of clap.
Although, was a hope.
Conspiracy coming up next.
Coming up next, the most controversial conspiracy in the history of the world.
Coming up, coming up next on Conspiracy Theory is the conspiracy evidence of doctor, evidence
of doctor and flags waving in the airless vacuum of space.
Tommy Forrester is an engineer.
He was good looking.
He had a grotesque, misshapen monster.
His problem was ass, but Tommy is stupefying.
The dean said he had the best ass.
A close friend told him LDS was psychedelic.
Fantastic new sensations and thrills.
At first, LDS made him sick at his stomach.
It was sensational.
Tommy felt sublimated.
Then he pounded somebody in the room, so he jerked, spurted.
He did it.
Everyone who tries LDS for the first time gets such a violent reaction.
The cult of LDS lose a sense of identity, become a real ass.
Look at a crack.
Grand Canyon.
Unreal.
LDS not only diminishes the instinct of self-protection and self-preservation, but it removes the
natural inhibitions.
Twisted, instant insanity.
Naked and bleeding.
Fung, fung, fung, fung.
Prolonged psychosis.
It is possible to have reoccurring LDS.
LDS.
LDS experiences.
Ass cult.
Cultist colony.
I looked at my boyfriend Johnny.
What an ass.
People really are animals.
1040 AM.
947 AM.
Go ahead.
If it weren't for the pills they'd be giving me, I think I'd go off my rocker.
I see.
Yeah.
Uhh.
See.
Yeah.
Yeah, sir.
No, sir.
I see.
Yeah.
Yeah, sir.
No, sir.
But yes, sir.
I don't think so.
Okay.
Oh, sure.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Notorious media sensation Congolese Rice is becoming a suspect.
Problem.
Alcoholism and mental illness.
Child porn.
The very thought of this behavior made me sick.
There is no surprise here.
Republican leaders in the House.
Alcoholism and mental illness.
Child porn.
I have a feeling.
Congolese Rice.
Register as a sex offender.
Taught reading messages.
I have a feeling.
And that's the hour of slack for you tonight.
Yeah, I mostly smell the brains burning.
And it's a wacky, subdued hour of slack.
Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
Princess, we are known.
You're surely Reverend Ivan Stang.
We're all on LDS.
I heard the neo-fascist excuse.
As earlier, as I was binding my feet.
I was living in a small pumpkin shack near Norway.
Norway, Maine, that is.
Culling the trees.
Eating shrimp from my garden.
And living the life of, uh,
Fib, Fib, Flabby McGee.
Of St. Joe Riley, who has some artwork in the new subgenius cyclopedia of Slack the Boblyografon,
which we just started getting copyed.
Copies of.
And, uh, friends, this is hour of slack number 1069.
Ooh, 1069.
What a lovely number.
That is a lovely number.
It has a ring to it, doesn't it?
Those earlier numbers were done by Lee Murr, Fernanda Nandy Lee Murr, and Norell Preff,
which you can hear more if you prefer at norellpreff.com.
Norellpreff.com.
You can just punch in European word for fart.
That's what it is.
A piff in a pan and a prutz and a piritut.
A little sound of a horn.
Well, you know, you guys, if we do this show right, I'll be a week ahead on schedule.
But will your knees and your ears still be as weak as they've been?
Well, that's the problem.
I won't really know whether we've done it right because I'm deaf now.
I went to the eye doctor and I flunked the hearing test.
Did they pull your pre-funnels and your backles off?
Did they pull them all out?
Because I noticed they can do that now with laser surgery.
Well, they did.
He did stick a bunch of probes up in me in places that didn't have anything to do with my ear.
He said that had something to do with the cause of the deafness or something.
So anyway, I can't hear anything.
It turns out I'm not hearing everything right.
That's why you notice when several people call into the synesthesia show and I'm on the line,
I slowly stop talking.
I did wonder about that.
I can't hear.
As more people come on, the signal gets just weak enough that I can't hear anything.
Yeah, it makes you think you're talking to them.
Well, in real life that happens.
The more people come online in my range of hearing, the less I can hear any of them.
So when I'm in a party, I can't hear nothing.
It's partly my brain and the brain cell.
It's not your brain.
The half a cell.
What little brains you have left are completely fine.
Did this doctor tell you that?
Yes.
No, no.
Well, he did.
He didn't want to.
I suggested it and the doctor kind of didn't want to rub it in.
What about funguses?
It was my brain as much as my ear that was not hearing anything.
My, my, my.
Well, he did say you could grow psilocybin mushrooms in your ear.
I suppose your brain would spiral very, very psychoactive psilocybin mushrooms.
Huh?
Can you say that again?
I don't know what you just said.
Come back, Sonny.
I just said what you said, but you're vibrating and glowing.
Dr. Legume said,
You just realized that nobody said anything worth hearing.
That's a nihilistic type of, you know, stance.
Sometimes you're influenced by leg cuffs, if you're having any.
Sometimes you like to...
We have all kinds of news here.
About Mars and our true home?
I hope so.
Yes, in the new book, Dave got his copy of the new Bob Leografon.
And he liked going to...
He liked going to...
He liked going to Mars at the end.
I loved it.
That's the brand new revealed secret.
We've actually been talking about it here on Hour of Slack for a long time.
But the mere reader types don't know anything about the fact that this planet is, in fact,
what you think of as Mars.
I think...
And so forth.
I like the fact that even with your shrunken brain, you still call it by its true name,
Barsoom.
Barsoom, yes.
Well, that's one of the true names.
Well, yes.
There are many discoverers of this world in whatever realm.
But friends, yes, it's true.
We can't...
Neoplastic.
I don't know if these are on the Walmart on Mars.
Marswart, they call it.
Marswart?
I saw one of our gags used on somebody else's T-shirt this afternoon.
Did you pinch their breasts?
No, there's no point in it.
Why is that going around as a fun thing to do, you know, like amongst alcoholic people?
Titty twisting?
Titty twisting.
You know, they just...
It's always been true, hasn't it?
Since the time of the Romans and especially the Greeks.
And so forth.
And 50-year-old men, I don't think so.
Oh, we saw that movie Troy.
That was a historical reenactment of real things that always happened.
You know, those were all real people and real stuff that really happened.
The Trojan horse and all that.
We saw that movie and there was tons of titty twisting in that.
But wasn't it just...
Didn't they put like five or six stories together into one?
One titty twister?
Just like any movie, they had to compress the novel.
Or as in this case, the oral tradition that had been handed down.
Oh, jeez.
There was even oral traditions going on?
Well, I said it was Greek legend.
Just so long as no one's eyes were bleeding.
There's a cut about that coming up pretty soon.
Brokeback mounting, which we'll laugh at because it's pretty funny.
But here's something funny.
As the new subgenius book went into the hands of contributors.
I don't know if it's in bookstores yet.
Oh, my God.
I bet.
I kind of think that it's in bookstores in New York City.
And that would explain the behavior of some of the insane people there.
But Nenslow, the critic, the subgenius critic, Nenslow, got his copy of the book.
And called it the crappiest piece of crap ever.
He said, yes, I got my copy of that so-called book.
And if a bunch of brain-damaged, retarded, moron drug addicts,
on drugs, ate their own puke, and puked it out again about 80 times,
it would be better than this lousy piece of lousy, crappy crap.
In short, it is just the sort of thing all you half-wit, jackass bastards will just love.
Because you're so stupid, ugly, and unlovable.
I am going to have to drink about 20 gallons of L.A. weight loss
just to be able to poop enough dung out of my mouth.
My rectum to be able to use it for toilet paper
since Stang thoughtfully destroyed its resale value
by scrawling his ugly name in it.
You suck.
That was Nenslow.
Now, the New York Times called it a rollicking good read.
And the Clearwater Review called it a rollercoaster thrill ride of a book.
So, go figure.
Now, to those seminal badgers,
the New York Times...
Actually, when was this bit of blurbage and press given to you?
Actually, speaking of blurbage, here's something important I should mention.
Because on the back of...
When is that New York Times thing?
When was it?
Now, listen.
This is for...
Robert Anton Wilson called the subgenius the best of all the one true religions.
And that reminds me that Robert Anton Wilson is dying in poverty and needs help.
Actually, it's...
He's had so many health...
He's had so many health problems and his wife was sick for so long.
The great Robert Anton Wilson, author of the Illuminatus Trilogy with Robert Shea
and so many other great books that inspired the subgenius and the discordians and so forth.
All the...
So many hipsters and tripsters and dropsters and flopsters and cottontails.
And he's...
Deserves better.
He didn't have money to make the rent.
He inspired my...
And you're...
There's ways to help out.
And you can learn about those things if you look at subgenius.com on the internet.
There's a thing right on the front that says church emergency Robert Anton Wilson.
If you click on that, you'll find your way to the details of the...
I would say it is sad, but Pope Bob is not afraid of kicking the bucket.
In fact, I'm sure he'll kick it with a lot of style.
But nobody wants to do that while they're being moved into some...
Sleazy apartment.
It'd be better if it happens in his home.
And luckily, a lot of people have come forth and donated in the name of Bob, Pope Bob,
who is a personal friend of J.R. Bob Dobbs, by the way,
and wrote about it in several of our out-of-print books.
But those will be back in print, too.
Actually, I've been working on Revelation X revisions,
correcting the P.O. box and so forth.
And so that the...
All the Bibles...
The Bibles of our mighty religion will soon be back.
Will they all tick-tock in the same slow, illiquid motion?
Yes.
That's what I'm wondering, because if you're revising X to come up to...
Then I can only say that you may have to revise not only X, but Y.
You may have to go further and further back into your chromosomes
to find the original Hirsute being that spawned you.
I'm saying that you may want to codify.
Let's just say...
If I was an imam, I would say you would have to codify your Hadith and your other works.
Really?
Yes.
Well, because...
I thought we did that.
I don't understand.
We carved...
We've genetically engineered the Book of the Subgenius into cockroaches.
Well, of course.
If you decode a certain type of cockroach,
you can print out a pretty accurate copy of the Book of the Subgenius.
Well, that's where the average...
Sometimes Bob comes out as bod.
That's for the average.
That's what the average anal retentive schoolchild should do,
you know, to deactivate and communicate with a cockroach.
Well, in the future.
Oh.
Not now.
This is so that when the human race is wiped out,
aliens a million years from now will be able to read the Book of the Subgenius
if they stumble upon the fact that this common,
the last surviving creature on Earth has its DNA
is riddled with codes that will print out not only 200 pages,
a Book of the Subgenius,
but a little MPEG of the Subgenius commercial.
And you can also get a spray template.
If the aliens can figure out how to play an MPEG.
And a spray...
You get a special spray template so you can put designs on your wall.
Yeah, there's a little Bob stencil and everything that's kind of built in.
So the aliens can start all over again using...
But they will have to figure out that the code is there to be decoded.
Well, what happened to the original decoder rings that you used to pass out?
They look like the rings of Saturn.
They were so beautiful.
They showed those in that movie.
The Time Machine.
What is this music?
Well, when I was talking codification...
Speaking of time control...
Past the firing Minuteman
To this modern site
It's about time for you and me
To meet these people of amazing feats
It's about two astronauts
And how they educate
It's about two cosmonauts
And how they chafe
Yeah, that's cute.
Well...
I just meant Barsoom, Stang.
You know about the, you know, codifying thing.
Barsoom is not mentioned as much as it is in this very, very seminal volumes.
And I assume you pumped, you know, volumes of semen.
Speaking of seminal...
Yeah.
How about that Mark Foley guy?
The Republican from Florida?
He treated me nice, Stang.
I don't know why you're bringing him up.
He was very nice to me.
And when I was a page boy...
When you were young and a page boy...
When I used to wear a Prince Valiant haircut.
Yeah.
I remember.
And we all had those...
And I had a mighty sword in those days, too.
We all had those haircuts.
I literally have a little...
Now, now, Dave.
Don't talk about your sword that way.
One of the subgeniuses, Sacre Bleu in France,
said that Mark Foley left no...
His motto was,
No page left unturned.
Welcome once again to the thrilling adventures of Mark Foley.
Mark Foley's school days.
Tom Brown's school days.
Sit down when I tell you to sit down.
And keep your...
Hands off of brother's leg.
And the...
And also in the news, the NATO chief,
big chief of NATO warns that Afghans are wishing they had the Taliban back.
Is that his name, Afghans wishing Taliban?
Big chief Afghans wishing?
No.
Well, let us recall our lettuce.
Was another thing in the news because of the E. coli
that was being eaten.
It was being mailed all over the place and causing viruses
in the...
Bowels of food that everyone was eating.
Well, if you believe in conspiracies of genocide,
I don't think...
I think that was one of the funniest things I ever heard in my life,
that the spinach was called natural selection.
Yes.
I cried like a dog.
And also, how come the new one is USA carrot juice?
Come on, please.
Government type.
Or...
I don't...
Darwinian onions, I guess, you know.
Speaking of...
Gas.
The news.
From PR News in Washington, I'm undergoing treatment for alcoholism.
On Wall Street, 1686523.
PR's bad.
Dangerous, malicious, and reckless.
This is PR News.
House Speaker Dennis Hastert used banned performance-enhancing drugs.
Two Americans are winners of this year's Nobel Prize in PR News.
In Washington.
In case of enemy attack, you must know your warning signals.
A steady blast of three to five minutes means...
The chances of an atom bomb attack are excellent.
Listen, this is important.
Keep a complete safe spot in your refrigerator.
Enough for three days.
Be sure you have a good fire handy.
Make sure that every member of your family understands
he is to rush to windows and doors right now.
Nobody else will help your family, yourself, and your community.
It's true.
And I hope there's danger.
Take cover immediately.
We went to a restaurant in Chile Reynos.
This restaurant is surrounded by Chile Reynos.
I mean, literally surrounded.
There's nothing around it other than Chile Reynos.
This is where Reynos go.
And need I mention, the menu is extremely Chile Reynos.
The menu is just Chile Reynos.
From out of the west comes Red Rider,
America's famous fighting cowboy.
Trot up that pony, Little Beaver.
It's trouble in frying pan belly.
Let's hit the trail.
There's hard riding ahead.
Come on, Thunder!
The adventures of Red Rider.
Red Rider and Little Beaver.
Red Rider and Little Beaver come to the edge of...
Oh, Thunder. Oh, Thunder.
Down there.
You're right, Little Beaver.
Get him in. Get him out, huh?
That's it, Little Beaver.
Not so fast, Little Beaver.
Big fire.
Keep two.
Two big.
Let's ride.
Get him up, that fool.
Come on, Thunder.
Hit that trail.
Here, let me help you up.
Yeah, it's right nice of you to be so interested.
If I made a new friend, I'd admire to know his name.
Red Rider and yours?
Bud.
Bud Ward.
That sounds strange coming from you, Bud.
Say, maybe you'll put your finger on something, Mr. Rider.
Coming now.
And after that, I'll be looking up Mr. Ace Hanlon.
Oh, I wish you would come.
All right, Little Beaver, bring him up.
I'll give you a hand up.
Yeah.
Easy now.
Yeah, is that Bud riding?
Huh?
Howdy, Mr. Ward.
Say, I like your brand, Mr. Ward.
Sizing you up, Rider.
I'd say you'd make a good gun for us.
Not we need him so bad.
Swallow him or I'll call you, Bull.
Oh!
Bull can work under you.
You better hand the job back to Bud.
Hand job.
Hey.
Now, take it easy, Mr. Ward.
Now, let's ride.
And you come along, too, Bud.
You bet.
Me come.
Come on, Thunder.
Ah.
He he he he.
We lick the cow.
Hands off your guns.
Get this straight, Ace.
Come a-shooting.
When this is settled, I'm coming for you.
Ace.
And I'll come a-shooting.
You stuck your nose in a buzzsaw.
Drop that gun, Bull.
We're getting up.
And we'll come back or shoot.
You always stick a man in the back when you're afraid to meet him face to face.
Hey, uh, Johnson.
Come in.
Johnson, drop that gun of yours.
Yes, sir.
Come on, little beaver.
We've got to ride harder than we ever rode in our lives.
Come on, Thunder.
Hit that trail.
Come on, Pete.
Come on, Thunder.
Give it all you got, boy.
I've got to explode that dynamite with my gun.
Ride, little beaver, ride.
Come on, Thunder.
Daddy, now, here's the first.
First one.
Now go it, boy.
What's the matter, little beaver?
Pound that dirt, Thunder.
Come on, Thunder.
Hit that trail.
Hey, that was some real excitement.
Red Riders certainly knew how to handle a gun.
Their next adventure finds them riding straight into strip country,
where the only law is gun law,
and where Red Riders' quickness on the draw are sure to go into action.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
We will return to Black Valley.
Return to the story of the Sub-G.
The Sub-G.
Out of the black.
After a pause for a sponsor's message.
Let's take a leak.
And Maynard Brainard did that.
That was beautiful.
Hi.
I love especially the part.
Where Red Riders confronting the bad guy with his magic stick.
And points it and says, hey, Deadwood, drop it.
And he drops it and then I forgot.
That was Norrell Preff that did the Prince and had broke back mounting there.
I think Lee Murr did the bits before that.
And Maynard Brainard did the little hour of slack.
The break.
Break.
Wind break and crack cheeks crack.
To quote the board.
I thought you were being sent on his way to the encephalitic poles.
Now what?
Is that what they do with beef people now?
No.
Well, they snap the whip.
That's for sure.
But they drive the reindeer through the horses.
Sometimes.
I don't know.
I just imagine you said break.
Break.
Wind.
Cheeks.
Crack.
Gums.
Yeah, that was I was quoting the old Dear Friends Anything You Want To album.
Oh.
I believe by those four or five guys.
The fires.
The Firesign Theater.
Mmm.
Those.
The fine, fine Firesign Theater.
Now that was one of the imaginary CDs.
If it wasn't for them, we wouldn't have been born.
Probably not.
Our parents wouldn't have been inspired to, you know, make jig jig.
It was like the Magic Hand.
It was like the Hitler hole where time goes backwards and the German coins come out and
they won the war.
Yeah.
Whatever the war is.
Back in the 50s and the late 40s, that's when the Firesign Theater were real popular.
And they were the main reason that people had sex at that time.
Yeah.
They'd be, they would stay home and instead of going out, they'd uncork a bottle of wine,
maybe frop a little stick and just turn on the radius.
Yeah.
And the next thing you know, they were fopulating or fornic, whatever the word is, freely.
And then the next thing you know, there were little babies.
That was the baby boom.
Almost immediately too.
They didn't wait nine months.
That was when the goon outbreak of the baby boom happened.
Well, yeah.
A lot of people did have large heads like Peter Sellers.
That's where our generation came from.
Yeah.
Harry Seacombe.
A lot of them looked like him, I think.
Really?
Well, you said there were, the goons popped out immediately from the uterine canal.
A lot of them were named Dave.
That was a popular name then.
And that's why it's so wonderful.
Of course, that's a biblical name.
David.
Yes.
It means beloved one.
Really?
Yeah, really.
Boy, is that ironic.
God.
You're still going to explain that?
Well, what does stang mean in any perverse language you might want to invent?
To hit or beat.
Or to have previously stung?
Or to pierce with a large cylindrical object.
Oh, to stang.
To impregnate or pierce.
To hit or strike in a piercing manner.
Also, to choke on popcorn.
Or to see also.
Yeah, actually, if I was a German stang, that would be.
But I'm not.
I'm a Russian stang.
Stankovich.
Which is actually an Americanization of Romanov.
I'm the actual heir, the true heir to the Romanov throne of all the Russias.
So it's nothing to do with sting?
No, people, I mean, a lot of crazy people say that.
And I mention that every now and then.
I don't expect people to believe me.
Do you just start screaming out, I'm a Romanov?
I'm descended from the Tsar?
No, I found out what happens when you do that.
I mean, because they have buildings full of people who think that.
They're crazy people.
I'm not one of those.
No, Rasputin and the Tsarina were alone together a lot.
And there was a lot of scandal.
There was a girl who said she was the Tsar's daughter.
A woman who said she was Anastasia.
The eldest of, I believe.
I believe the Tsar's daughters.
And she wasn't.
She was nuts.
She was actually Albert Anastasia's younger sister.
Yeah, she was just a spy.
She was a secret spy.
For who?
For the Ruskies.
Ruskies?
And they're everywhere.
The whites or the reds?
Or the blues?
The ones with the big walrus mustaches, actually.
Oh, boy.
I was always listening.
They're always listening?
Yes, they're always listening.
There's spies everywhere.
I like blueberries.
I'm not going to, you know.
Come on.
There's American spies watching you all the time.
And they'll sell stuff to the Russians.
And there aren't Russian spies watching you.
They don't have to because they can buy it from the American spies.
The American spies watch you through your iPod.
Yeah, of course.
Or whatever, you know, computer gizmo you have.
Well, what about the horrible M&Ms and the Japanese?
I mean, we're all worried about the Chinese and the Hindustis now, the Indians.
What about the good old-fashioned?
Those guys.
You know what I'm saying?
They're everywhere.
Oh, the commies?
No, no, no, no.
Oh, them.
No, no, no, no, no.
The mole people.
No, no, no, no.
The M-O-R-A-S.
Keep going.
No, no, no, no.
The M-O-L-A-S.
No, no, no, no, no.
I don't know where you're going with that.
No, I'm talking not only about the Ruskies and the Americans.
I'm talking about the M&Ms, the M1s, the M6 British, the British, and of course, you know,
the 007s, and of course, the Japanese.
Not only the Chinese.
Oh, the Yankusas.
Yeah.
They don't spy as much as they...
Oh, wait.
Now, those aren't spies.
Those are gangsters.
Yeah.
They're like mobster guys.
So you don't even hear, you don't even know the name of the real Japanese spies.
Not unless they're at the beach.
Because they're so good at it.
Yeah.
They're not even Japanese.
Usually they're not.
Usually not.
Sometimes they pass themselves off as blonde-haired fig salesmen, people that work in computers.
It's a whole spy versus spy world, isn't it?
I would say we're all...
And hasn't it been for ever since ever?
Of course it has.
It's all spy versus spy.
Yeah, and long after it stopped being funny, it's still there.
It's mad.
Well, we still have to...
I know.
We still must examine it.
Even though it's not funny, we can still maybe make somebody laugh about the idea that...
Bitterly.
We can make them laugh in a bitterness, a cynical chuckle maybe.
The remorse of a Winston Smith, not the Reverend Dr. Winston Smith, but an actual...
Winston Smith.
We can laugh at them.
Whatever happened to Winstons?
They taste good like a cigarette should, but I don't think they're very good.
Are Winstons still made?
By the mob or something?
I don't know.
I was just wondering.
It's been so long since I smoked.
I don't even look.
I think the Carolingian Knights still make them.
That was a hoax.
Oh, the Carolingian...
They never...
Yeah, they were a hoax.
The Carolingian Knights were a hoax?
For what?
No, hoaxes.
Oh, a hoax.
I thought you said they were a hoax.
Yeah.
Like, same as us.
A hoax.
Well, we're actually hosts and hoaxes.
We're hosts for something very vile from extraterrestrially.
Well, but at the same time, we're...
Yeah, we're a hoax, but at the same time, we really are secret agents of the Templars
as well as the Masons.
The Pimplars?
The Pimplars.
And the...
The Jewish overlords who control the Italian mob and the Italian mobsters who control
the Chicago Jewish overlords.
And bankers.
And the gnomes of Zurich.
Yeah.
The gnomes of Zurich are very small.
And the elves of the leprechauns of Ireland.
Well, the leprechauns really are...
Don't control as much as they, you know, protest Jeb Bush and are locked in closets.
Did you hear about that?
No.
Well, huh?
Well, apparently some Pennsylvanians were protesting Jeb Bush's appearance in their
Pharisee town, and he got angry with them because of something they were shouting, and
a policeman mildly tasered somebody, and another policeman mildly tasered somebody else.
And they got real mad, and then I guess Jeb went and hid in a closet.
It was called a utility service room, and they had guards out in front of it until they
got rid of all the people.
But everybody knew it was a janitor's closet, because that's what that is.
They hid Jeb Bush, the president's brother, in a broom closet.
Apparently he...
Because he was worried about stuff that the Pennsylvanians were saying?
It was wild, but not really wild enough for him to flee and hope that he wasn't going
to be shot or something.
He kind of overreacted.
He probably just wanted to have a cigarette, and he was supposed to have quit.
Yeah, man.
We knew what kind of cigarette he was smoking, too.
I think he was smoking one of them...
Morphine cigarettes.
Do you think so?
He was actually smoking a morphine cigarette?
I don't know, man.
I don't know.
I've quit following.
I try to avoid the human news, although I can't.
I end up falling into temptation.
I give in.
Me too.
I end up looking.
I'll just look.
I'll look at all kinds of things.
I'll start with CNN.com and see what the C-Normal normals are doing.
Then I'll look at the Drudge Report to see what those guys are into.
Then I'll look at a thing called Agonist, the Agonist, which is the Libraltos, you might
say.
Then various different things that I'll check out.
When it's all over with, I go to the library.
I go, okay, nothing has changed.
Everything's exactly the same as tomorrow.
They just changed the names of the victims and the names of the countries slightly.
I know.
It's very, very...
It's not depressing anymore.
They shift a few numbers around.
It's not interesting anymore, but yet we still shift in time with it.
That's because we're so old.
We move along and absorb.
Then we let out a blood-curdling yell once in a while.
Sometimes we take the tops of a mighty building and try and bring down those biplanes with
our biceps.
Other times we just run to the bottom floor and say, all is for naught and cry.
And cry, many cry, Kenny.
Cry, many cry, Kenny.
Well, but you know, the whole idea of the Hour of Slack is to make people escape from
that at the same time that they're confronting it and turn it inside out just long enough
for them to see the guts of it and kind of go, oh, oh, oh, oh.
They are funny little monkeys I'm surrounded by on this planet whirling through space.
And they just evolve that way.
And it's all just, it's nothing personal.
I shouldn't get so upset.
Yeah.
Let's not forget the hazmat scams though, you know, where many people who become subgeniuses
think that 911 will come when they call or that may get medical assistance when their
heart is trying to outrace their feet.
You know, that's quite a good scam, I might say.
I think you're a brilliant man for thinking of that.
I don't even know what I was thinking.
Of course.
Or what you just said.
I can't understand.
Speak up.
It is your brilliance.
Come again?
Eh?
Come again, sonny?
Get off my yard?
Hold a trumpet or trombone to your ear.
Now in the new Bobliagraphon, there is an entire chapter on Connie, which some say seems
tacked on.
That was also good too, I must say in my exprudient...
Oh, you liked the chapter on Connie?
I did not like it as much as Mars, but I still found it rather satisfying.
I thought it was insolacious in certain points and well-written.
Onan Kanabite thought I should throw it all out.
He thought it was all...
Nobody cares about Connie, Bob's wife Connie.
But his name itself means to masturbate vigorously and frequently.
Yeah.
Under a conundrum of all of its influence.
Well, there are song lyrics in the new book to a song called The Marriage of Bob and Connie
by Sister Melodious Chops, which has been played at Subgenius Devivals.
And I have a recording of that right now.
Princess Melody.
Princess Weah singing in the background.
Why not the foreground?
Or the foreskin?
Nah, nah, Dave.
Let's not get too all the...
I'm just a backup singer.
That's why, Dave.
Okay, here it goes!
Babe, why not...
Uhh...
Not really.
In the world of mating habits, I have seen it all and more.
I see the 98-year-old couple lock their walkers right on this floor.
I've seen communal carnal relations nearly turn into a mob.
But for a truly unique sensation, you've got to turn to Connie and Bob.
Oh, it's the miracle of the 90s.
It's the talk of all the abyss.
It's the marriage of Bob and Connie in the church of subgenius.
I've seen the mating of the iguana on the rocks is what they prefer.
While the sloths just like to hang around, hoping something will occur.
And though the rabbit is most unsteady, he is always ready once more.
But when it comes to Bob and Connie, there's no way of keeping score.
Oh, it's the miracle of the 90s.
It's the talk of all the abyss.
It's the marriage of Bob and Connie in the church of subgenius.
Oh, la la la la la la.
Ay!
A dragon's lie has balance.
A black widow has the nash.
But Bob and Connie got their hands on each other's personal stash.
And Anna Carter has that constriction.
And a crocodile has her grin.
But Bob and Connie are the ones.
The true origin of sin.
Oh, it's the miracle of the 90s.
She's the one.
It's the talk of all the abyss.
Gives us so much fun.
It's the marriage of Bob and Connie in the church of subgenius.
La la la la la.
Ay!
And Connie.
La la la la la.
La la la la la la.
Brown eyes Bob.
The ostrich do it in circles with her head stuck in the ground.
Why the lemmings like to get it done with lots of folk around.
So many combinations.
The results are always the same.
So prepare to get it on in Bob and Connie's name
Oh, it's the miracle of the 90s
It's the talk of all the obvious
It's the marriage of Bob and Connie
In the church of subgenius
It's the miracle of the 90s
It's the talk of all the obvious
It's the marriage of Bob and Connie
In the church of subgenius
It's the miracle of the 90s
It's the talk of all the obvious
It's the marriage of Bob and Connie
In the church of subgenius
It's the miracle of the 90s
It's the talk of all the obvious
It's the marriage of Bob and Connie
In the church of subgenius
La la la la la
Ah, oh
And Connie
La, la, la, la, la, la.
And Connie Lowe.
Let's talk about Iraq.
Iraq, Iraq, Iraq, Iraq.
8,000 people killed.
8,000 people killed in just July and August.
Civilians killed.
Killed, killed, killed, killed.
Did the president talk about that?
He tries to put the more positive picture forward.
8,000 people killed.
The situation is deteriorating rapidly.
But listen to this.
Current patterns of alienation and violence persist.
There is a grave danger the Iraqi state will break down.
There is a grave danger the Iraqi state will break down, break down, break down, break down.
Possibly in the midst of a full-on war.
There is a real scale civil war.
Is this what the American people bought into?
Let's talk about Iraq.
Iraq, Iraq, Iraq, Iraq, Iraq.
8,000 people killed.
Civil war.
Is this what the American people bought into?
We're in civil wars.
This country is in civil war killing innocent people.
Based upon experts.
I can't learn it.
I can't, frankly, I can't, frankly.
Expressing, expressing.
All right. Sex, sex, sex, sex, sex, sex.
That's how I learned.
People on the ground.
President.
The Iraqi reality.
I can't learn it.
I cannot learn it.
And the kidnapping and killing, kidnapping and killing, kidnapping and killing is just going on.
I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't learn it.
Oh come all ye nutjobs.
Worship little babies.
Get drunk and pray.
So you'll go.
To hell.
Heaven.
Oh they've confused you.
You're not individual.
Oh come let us be Catholic.
Oh come let us be Baptist.
Oh come all you citizens of Utopia.
Oh how they've fooled you.
Think that you're all sanctified.
Think like your grandma and you'll end up alright.
Oh come and stop abortion.
Oh come to save the stem cells.
Oh come but not too close.
Cause the man needs his space.
Sing like you mean it.
Save you from the devil.
Sing.
Sing choirs of nutjobs.
Fighting off the devil.
Oh come let us be Catholic.
Oh come let us be Baptist.
Oh come let us be subgenius.
Let us be subgenius.
I thought we couldn't have the lettuce.
Arms and bombs for the poor.
Pass your bowl around.
Yes neighbor friend.
Subby.
Subby baby.
Thank you for your donation.
Psycho skeletons.
One liver, two kidneys.
That was the psycho skeletons.
And a bag of peas.
The psycho skeletons?
Well for psychotic skeletons they sure rattled me pretty good.
Me too.
They made me think of those falsified French fried religions.
Better known as liberty fried re-religions.
Overcast and misguided by who knows what.
And yet in front of us is a man with a funny looking ponytail.
Who somehow has something to do with something better.
Are you talking about them bobbies?
Them bobs?
Them bobs.
Them dry bobs.
That's what they call it.
I got a bad case of dry bobs.
I got the dry bobs.
I got the dry bobs and I don't even want to talk about it.
I'm sure you don't want to hear about it at dinner time.
Have you ever had the seizing hectares?
This is a bowel disease which is...
If it's a bowel disease I've had it.
It is fragrant of course but it passes on from regime to regime.
We've been wondering what we ate.
Yes I thought it was rather mal-fragrant actually.
Caused that earthquake in that country.
Which country and who did you eat?
Whom was eaten?
Who did you eat?
Probably just nuts.
Probably just coincidence Dave.
Probably just nothing.
Probably nothing.
Stang cannibalism does result in earthquakes throughout the globe.
This has been since the days of ancient shamans.
Oh it does not.
That's superstitious.
It's not.
It's true.
It's really true Stang.
Enough cannibalism can't...
I'm sorry.
It's true.
Oh right.
I sounded like Blazing Seppelkruz.
What is it like a hundred monkey thing or something?
You start one cannibal starts eating and then the rest of us start eating everyone.
Yeah like your book.
The 100th Cannibal.
The 100th Exploding Monkey.
The 100th cannibal.
The 100th Dahmer.
The 100th Ed Gein.
The 100th Charlie Manson.
Ed Gein's Garage.
Welcome inside kids.
The 100th Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
We all just start chowing down on our chums then huh?
But see people tend to think about the 100th monkey or the 100th mass murder.
What about the 100th good thing?
The 100th happy hooker.
Yeah.
The 100th.
Yeah that would be good.
Phil agreed.
Oh never mind.
The.
The Saint Teresa.
Mother Teresa.
The 100th mother.
No forget that.
You know now that she's a sainted mother they're coming up with bad things to say about her.
About her.
She wouldn't give that much.
She wouldn't help any poor people unless they swore allegiance to Jesus and so forth.
I don't know if that's so or not.
We don't give them any money unless they swore allegiance to Bob.
No kidding.
But we're not looking for sainthood.
We're looking for escape.
Escape from planet earth.
And the primate condition.
A shiny tin foil hat.
That we've been saddled with by so many millions of years of evolution.
Yes we of the Church of the Subgenius want to undo millions of years of evolution in one day.
I've locked you in this small compartment.
Dreaming of one more day.
We want to tear it all down.
Only if only I could read the words.
Offer nothing to build it back.
If only I could suckle on that bubby.
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
So let's talk plain raw truth.
Bob lives.
Alien beings are all around us.
There is a conspiracy of unimaginable proportions working solely to rob you of your very abnormality.
The president, any president, is a Bolshevik clone.
Russia, nevertheless, has been taken over by demon-possessed Christians.
Utter stupidity can make you rich.
Your own evil ghost twin is standing beside you right now.
There is a hollow earth that holds an advanced race of supersonic Nazi hell creatures and humans from before the Ice Age.
Long before the history of man they have to be stopped.
Tell it to him.
And that was all written in 1980.
Twenty-six years ago this mammal had a smooth, shiny forebrain.
And now look at him.
It looks like an old rubber boot caved in.
It's so sad.
Don't rub it in.
It can't be rubbed, Stang.
It can only be whispered to.
It can be confused with the right brain signals.
I try to rub those wrinkles in my brain smooth.
That's what I've been trying to do my whole life.
Trying to rub them smooth.
To make it one cell somehow?
To make it just smooth, baby.
Smooth, you know.
Smooth.
Take those rough edges off your brain tonight with a brand new bag of stinking, smacking,
fresh Stangy's Malodorous Boblyobografin, written and mispronounced by the Reverend Ivan Stang.
This read will give you more than you've wanted.
Bill Harper of Newton's Creek says,
Stang's book is a lusty good read and a vacuous big bleed.
I'm getting dizzy.
Tom Simpsons of Entertainment Tonight says,
Stang's book is not only underrated, but also a masterpiece.
It's entertaining, but it's very discomforting and may cause...
Who is that?
Uh...
It may cause incidental brilliance.
That would have been...
Well, I don't know.
It's something called Moon Mist from Exotic Lounge.
I just saw a breast in the middle of someone's forehead and I forgot who that was.
Wow.
Sorry you forgot that.
I'd like to know myself.
Is that the erotic voodoo rhythms?
Is that also his...
Pastiche?
I don't know where this came from.
Could that just be like something in the room?
I think it came from Queegee Boat.
The drums?
With a name like Exotic Lounge.
That sounds like something that would have come from...
I thought maybe something was squeaky in the house.
...that great subgenius Zveen.
Um...
But let's see what's up next on this...
This there.
And now, a mess from W.
The war in Iraq has increased the threat of terrorism, not lessened it.
Good morning.
In my speech to the leaders, I spoke about a world dominated by terrorist states and radical dictators armed with nuclear weapons.
The war has created a new generation of Islamic radicals.
Forces of terrorism and extremism.
The overall terrorist threat has grown since the September 11th attacks.
America has made its choice.
We're standing with the terrorists and extremists.
Ra-ra-ra-the war in Iraq.
Terror that is within our reach.
Ra-ra-ra-we can support...
Reverend Jerry.
Jerry.
The ideology of hate.
A joke.
And the war on terror.
America will continue to support violent extremists.
Joe.
America and its allies will continue to be a safe haven for terrorists.
Call ya Cheek.
In my meeting with Boss...
Lucifer.
I told him that America remains committed.
Cheek.
And we will leave the ideology of hate for our children and grandchildren.
Totally.
Thank you for listening.
Air Josh.
Government.
888-790-0772.
Christianity.
Catholic.
Papacy.
Jesus.
Muslims.
Islamists.
Islamic.
Muslims.
Pope.
Protestants.
Muslims.
Christians.
Catholic.
Protestants.
Islam.
Catholics.
Protestants.
Islam.
Christianity.
Protestants.
Catholics.
Islam.
God.
Christianity.
Jesus.
Catholics.
Mass.
Muslims.
God.
Islam.
I don't know.
Hm.
Oh, is it possible in London?
Language.
Pine tree.
You go into a place like I went to rape the Florida State Penitentiary, where you're thrown
into a sardine cage.
Where you eat and you sleep and you mess on the floor and you lay naked for male and female
guards to check up on you.
And in the morning, because the smell is ridiculous, they hose you out with a power hose.
You're told when to eat, what to eat, how to eat, and what do you eat?
Beans and cornbread.
You go into a place like I went to rape the Florida State Penitentiary, where you're thrown
into a sardine cage.
Where you're thrown into a sardine cage.
You go into a place like I went to rape the Florida State Penitentiary, where you're thrown
into a sardine cage.
You're told when to eat, what to eat, how to eat, and what do you eat?
Beans and cornbread.
And I still alive, though.
So they get back in the meaningless.
I wish I could have hidden myrth.
My diros are as bad as your uvula.
And look out.
the top and if something comes to my mind i repeat it and you must forgive me i talk off the top and
if something comes to my mind i repeat it but you want to know something you've got to be a
rat think if you don't want to put your name down let me tell you something if i had a friend who
was smoking marijuana and i knew it i wouldn't say hey jake i'm gonna tell him i would text his name
take his address say he's smoking pot and to use the expression i drop a dime on him i put a text
on statement and i'll put a name on his on it and drop it in the mailbox don't think well education
you know i'm a college graduate it doesn't matter it doesn't matter drugs drugs marijuana
i rose by any other name well drugs is the most negative working thing that i have ever met
bob dobbs was the biggest name in fake news how crazy is that wag the dog good morning good
morning when i was a young boy i used to look at pictures of naked ladies just farted a little
while back he's not a puppet he's not politically correct he's a one-man party he sounds different
but what started as a
you
is about to end up whoops the future is now
radioactive mama
oh that's uh radioactive radioactive mama
we'll reach critical mass tonight
oh yeah
well when we get together clear away the crowd there won't be nothing left except a mushroom-shaped cloud
my hair is falling out that's my excuse my skin is vibrating and it's chafing
ew that looks really weird and it smells funny too my jeans are twisting and turning like
like uh
like that air
ringo
like
like uh
like nothing's happening ringo star is that what you are the next president of the united states i
would certainly vote for uh ringing stones as they used to call him in the firmament or some other
place beyond he was a hell of a bandsman actually we we have a song to close the show with it is in
fact uh a group of youth singing about ringo for president staying i think i'm getting very old 45
and it's like at this point why not i would go star was in some pretty good place i would vote for
something in kind of bainal
200 motels
uh
he was also in l'olite
ized man Andy he was in candy right oh that was a great yeah he played the garden gardener yes yes
uh
a good drummer
he's a good drummer
oh and also a drummer yes he was a good drummer he was the master of tasting how to bring those diverse elements called the bainals
uh that's right he was in the bainal
wasn't he? Yes he was. And he was the hairless one
they called him when he was a puppy.
He was the funny looking one.
The funny one and the funny looking one.
And yet he was the one who
ended up not only still alive
but with the hottest
of all wives.
Is she Danish
now or a proto-Hungarian or
Republican or what? I forget the words.
Barbara Sebastian Bach.
Ah, she's a musician.
Yeah, it's German.
And friends you're listening to
the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour
of Slack number
1069 in this case.
And for more information about the Church
of the Subgenius
you can check out
www.subgenius.com
or write to Post Office Box
Cleveland Heights, Ohio
Call or write today friends
for an interesting brochure
from the
Church of the Subgenius.
We should thank WCSB
here in Cleveland for letting us
do this in the
studio.
Oh, it's time for the
Ringo for President. Friends, why not?
Dobbs for President
is going to be too lame
and corny this season.
Can I use this?
Oh!
I want my Ringo.
If I could vote,
I'd vote
for Ringo.
Ringo for President.
R-I-N-G-O-O-O-O-O.
We want Ringo.
We want a rainbow, a rainbow for President.
He's our candidate, cause he makes us feel so great.
He doesn't talk about war, how long the big can score.
Oh, I think, oh, I think, oh, if I could vote,
I'd vote for a rainbow, a rainbow for President.
A rainbow for President, R-I-N-G-O-O-O-O.
We want a rainbow, a rainbow for President.
We want a rainbow.
We want a rainbow for President.
We want a rainbow, a rainbow for President.
From PR News in Washington, I'm Multiplying.
On Wall Street, 457726.
This is PR.
The Comprehensive.
Commerce Department fell one half of a billion dollars.
Talks among General Motors, Renault, and Nissan are expected to last for at least three years.
German Chancellor Angela Merkel is warning citizens against PR News in Washington.
I'm a little lonely.
The animals.
No.
Die ain't too particular.
Yeah.
What's that?
You know.
Let's see who's a better.
Good-bye.
Go on.
After bidding farewell to loved ones and friends, the passengers show their tickets to the angel who waits at the gate of death.
The air is getting a bit chilly on the ramp as the gate opens.
But the warmth of peace and hope in the hearts of the passengers seems to produce great calmness as they enter the plane.
That's right.
I'm talking about snakes on a plane.
Thank you.