Greetings, my friend. We are all interested in the future, for that is where you and I are going to spend the rest of our lives.
And remember, my friend, future events such as these will affect you in the future.
You are interested in the unknown, the mysterious, the unexplainable.
That is why you are here. And now, for the first time, we are bringing to you the full story of what happened.
On that fateful day, we are giving you all the evidence based only on the secret testimony of the miserable souls who survived this terrifying ordeal.
The incidents, the places. My friend, we cannot keep this a secret any longer.
Let us punish the guilty. Let us reward the innocent.
My friend, can your heart stand the shocking facts about...
The Subgenius Hour of Swag.
Power. We have vast power.
Power. At least 120 volts of pure electrical power.
And now all we need is 100 million volts of pure, unadulterated pleasure.
Another one?
I have appetite.
Hungers.
Needs like anyone else.
I must perforce indulge my...
May the pleasures hang.
As best I can.
Did not Bob say,
Do what keepeth thou from wilting shall be the loophole in the law?
Am I to let myself wilt, Bob?
Can I open if my idea of slack is against all laws of God, man, and nature?
Let it be so.
Well, um, there is no question that a cosmic interloper will hit the earth,
and we won't have to wait for millions of years for it to happen.
In 1908, a 200-foot-wide comet fragment slammed into the atmosphere
and exploded over the Taunguska region in Siberia, Russia,
with nearly a thousand times the energy of the atomic bomb dropped on Hiroshima.
Astronomers estimate similar sized events occur every one to three centuries
So hang out folks for another century
And you too can join George Bush looking up at the skies
And yelling and screaming about things that he can't change
Raging impotently in impotent rage
Yes, impacts of large objects from space hitting us
Have repeatedly disrupted human civilization
One killed 10,000 people in the Chinese city of Qingyang in 1490
Many scientists request to repeat these interpretations
Impacts are most likely to occur over the ocean
And small ones that happen over land are most likely to affect unpopulated areas
But with big asteroids it doesn't matter much where they land
Objects more than half a mile wide
Which strike Earth every 250,000 years
Or so
Touch off fire storms
Followed by global cooling
From the prior dust
Humans would likely survive
But civilization might not
An asteroid five miles wide would cause major extinctions
Like the one that may have marked the end of the age of the dinosaurs
Look at all that coffee
For a real chill
Just look to the Kuiper Belt
A zone just beyond Neptune
George Bush is swimming
And contains roughly 100,000 giant ice blocks
More than 50 miles in diameter each
The Kuiper Belt sends a steady rain
Small comets earthward
If one of the big ones headed right for us
That would be it for pretty much all higher forms of life
And the local team who wanted to go to Burning Man
Will never get there because a meteorite's gonna wreck everything
But it doesn't require a meteorite
For example, there could be a massive gamma ray bursting
That would be a huge amount of energy
And sufficiently extinguish all life on Earth
If you could watch the sky with gamma ray vision
You might think you are being stalked by cosmic paparazzi
Once a day or so, you'd see a bright flash appear
Briefly outshine everything else, then vanish
These are gamma ray bursts
Astrophysicists recently learned about these babies
They originate in distant places
Galaxies
And are unfathomably powerful
As much as 10 quadrillion
That's a one followed by 16 zeros
Times as energetic as our sun
Sol
Head of the heating system
Look, here's the big head
Did you hear the theory about how
If aliens come here
That they're probably already here
In a microbial form
And that they're going to
In intelligent form too
And that they're gonna take over
Through the internet
The world wide web
That they're just
Not microbial
I mean they're
What do you mean?
Nano
They're like nano
Nano virals
Aliens
Oh man, how could you be
In digital life form though
It's required to form the physical body
That we know as Bill Gates
God, just think of all the
How many microbes
And how they hold themselves together
Into a semblance of a
Of a human-like thing
That breathes and talks
Probably even eats
Peanut butter cup, Dave?
No, no thanks
I was gonna have some
Swarthy tumor juice over there
And then also a piece of
Hemlock pie
And I see the reverend
Brought his Slim Fast with him
You gotta drink coffee
You have to drink
Three or four of those every day
Now why would a man of your
Of your small
Not your girth
Wanna have a Slim Fast
For lunch or breakfast?
Because
Not as a commercial message
I can't suck down
The blood of a newborn kitten
Every hour like I would like to
So I have to suck down
One of these damn
Humanoid drinks
Well that
It's for the protein
I have to have protein
To balance the sugar and caffeine
Well I think
So I
So therefore I have to
Eat nuts or
Frop or some
Some other form of protein
Nuts and frops
And other colloquialistic terms
For human bodies
When you crunch off the tops
Of their heads
And dig right in
Into that
Fleshy medulla
Froplop
Zips of tops
Have you ever
Sliced a brain
So what do you think about that?
Aliens and nano-aliens
Well I was trying to ask you
A question
How could they make
My biotic form
Become digital
From a digital form
Actually boys
What's that mean?
The nano-aliens
That you're talking about Chaz
Are in fact
The WOM supercomputer
Predicted by J.R. Bob Dobbs
Described in
Not very much detail
In either of the
Bobbles
So to speak
This WOM supercomputer
Is actually
Like a zillion
Billion
Nano-alien creatures
Which
What is?
Or creature
Nano-creatures
They're artificial
But
You know
They're as alive
As any virus
Or bacterium
And these
These
This supercomputer
Of the
Exist aliens
Because of the
Nature of it
Is able to
Exist as a
Permanent
As a
Paint upon the
Walls
As the carpet
Underneath
As a
Very slim
Fast in that
Cannon as the
Can itself
Those are all
Part of the
Exist computer
That is how
The exist
Supercomputer
Is able to
Instantly grant
The wishes
Of all those
Who paid
Their thirty
Dollars
And simultaneously
Denied the
Heartfelt
Desires of
Those that
Wishes to
Crush and
Conquer
Following the
Rupture
Or predicted
We like to
Call it
Coming up
This July
5th
For skin
Day
One
For skin
Day
As Bob
Predicted
Yes
Holly
Hot
For skin
Day
When our
Mother
Lay down
Flare
The skinners
Of
That would
Create a
Moon
And mean
Here on
This
Consecrated
Ground
And we
Just
Decided
Actually
There was
A
Show
And we
Demand
That everybody
In the
Church
Be circumcised
Or circumvented
By
You got
Mixed
Up with
A certain
Heaven's
Gate
Or a
Certain
Judaism
Or some
Such
Thing
Or a
Certain
Medical
American
Conspiracy
But no
Trefonation
Was
I think
Everyone in
The church
Should have
A sex
Change
And then
Have a
Sex
Change
Back
Well you've
Already
Had
That's
Been
Done
That's already
Happened in
This church
Of
Expressions
And
I can't
Even keep
Up with
The names
Of some
Of our
Ministers
Whether
They're
Mrs.
This
Or
Mr.
That
Stinky
In between
Man
Woman
Lephargic
Thing
Purple
Hand
You know
These
Yeah
Pope
Popester
This
And
Mary
Popester
This
And that
But
All of
These
Predictions
Shall
Come
True
As the
End
Times
Unfold
I
Can
Do
The
Whole
Song
And dance
I'm
Sure
You've
Heard
It
In
A
Million
Times
How
Can
We
Expect
Trees
To
Communicate
When
We
Cannot
Even
Talk
With
Our
Own
Urine
And
Other
Bodily
Fluids
It's
Just
Too
Much
Back
To
Bodily
Fluids
And
Genitalia
That's
Little
Baby
Talk
You
And
I
Would
Prefer
To
Keep
The
Conversation
On
A
Lofty
Rationalist
Talk
Humanist
Level
And
Eschew
This
Metaphysical
Claptrap
Nonsense
Random
Errancy
Genu-Oriented
And
Poo-Poo
Oriented
Individual
But
Of
Course
That's
What
The
Audience
Wants
That's
What
Keeps
The
Advertisers
Coming
In
Here
At
WCSB
Dave's
Poo-Poo
Talk
Okay
Now
To
Close
World
Yes
You
Missed
Spot
Over
There
By
The
Airport
For
Your
Quick
In
His
Now
All
That's
Left
Are
The
Dixie
Chicks
Jeez
And
There's
Some
Salsa
Here
You
Could
Have
With
Those
Dixie
Chips
Well
Now
You
May
Laugh
But
It
Is
Possible
A
Massive
Gamma
Ray
Burst
Might
Extinguish
All
Life
On
Earth
And
Sooner
Than
We
Think
Yeah
Now
You're
Probably
Asking
Yourself
What
Causes
A
Gamma
Ray
Burst
And
You're
Right
Well
It's
Not
Entirely
Sponch
It
May
Result
In
The
Merging
Of
Two
Collapsed
Stars
Before
The
Cataclysmical
Event
The
Presence
Of
The
Foundering
Giants
Might
Be
Impossible
Understand
Here
On
The
Planet
Earth
Yes
Alright
So
Anyway
Let's
Go Back
To
The
Innocent
Explanation
Of
How
Life
Really
Happens
But
Once
The
Burst
Begins
There
Will
Be
No
Missing
Its
Fury
At
A
Distance
Of
One
Thous
Light
Years
Far
Than
Most
Of
The
Stars
You
Can
See
In
Clear
Light
It
Would
Appear
About
As
Bright
The
Sun
Earth's
Atmosphere
Would
At
First
Protect
Us
But
At
A
Cost
The
Potent
Radiation
Would
Cook
The
Atmosphere
Creating
Nitrogen
Oxides
Would
Destroy
The
Ozone
Layer
And
Without
The
Guardian
Ozone
Layer
Ultraviolet
Rays
From
The
Sun
Would
Reach
The
Surface
At
Nearly
Full
Force
Causing
Skin
Cancer
And
More
Seriously
Killing
Off
The
Tiny
Photosynthetic
Plankton
In
The
Ocean
That
Provide
Oxygen
To
The
Atmosphere
And
Bolster
The
Bottom
Of
The
Fulgur
Of
Course
All
The
Gamma
Rain
Bursts
Observed
By
Scientists
Up
Now
Have
Been
Rather
Distant
Which
Implies
The
Events
Are
Rare
But
Scientists
Understand
So
Little
About
These
Explosions
That
It's
Difficult
To
Estimate
The
Likelihood
Of
One
Detonating
Any
Minute
Whoa
Is
That
Right
You
What
Is
It's
About
Every
Know
On
Oops
A
e
the female alone. Caution to the wind. The eyes glaze. The glands swell and the brain freezes.
Breeding is an ugly thing. I didn't bring you down here so they could use you. I brought you
down here so I could use you. I am gone. I need your body as a dwelling place while I am here
on your earth. Your feeling of helplessness is your best friend, Savage. When I am occupying
your body or in my present transitory form, I am without substance and indestructible. You can
help me save the earth from a terrible experience. Yes, the whole earth. There is absolutely no doubt
of your power to destroy. I saw it. I saw an American colonel killed, burned to a crisp by
radiation with one look from this man. Feels like you got a real monster in there. You fool!
You fool!
You're feeding him human brains. You're making him strong. All I remember is feeling something
sticky in my pants. Yeah, but when it comes to blood in my underwear, I want to know how it got
there. You sucked out her brains? Yeah, right through her mouth. Is she dead? Of course she's
dead. What, are you kidding? Laugh for while you can, monkey boy. I don't know if anybody read the
Kurt Vonnegut book, Cat's Cradle. Sorry, gotta talk like this. He popularized the idea of Ice Nine,
which is a movie about a man who is a monster. He's a monster. He's a monster. He's a monster.
He's a monster. He's a monster. He's a monster. He's a monster. He's a monster. He's a monster. He's a monster.
A form of water that is more stable than the ordinary kind of water, and so it's solid at
room temperature. If you unleash a bit of it, then suddenly all water on earth transforms to Ice Nine
and freezes solid. Well, Ice Nine was a satirical invention, but an abrupt, disastrous phase
transition is a possibility. He's not the phase transition again? Very early in the history of
the universe, according to a leading cosmological model, empty space was full of energy.
This state of affairs called a false vacuum was completely precarious.
Thank you, DigiLady.
A more stable type of vacuum appeared, and like Ice Nine, it quickly took over.
You've got more show than most, Michael.
This transition unleashed a tremendous amount of energy.
Disengage.
A runaway explosion and expansion of the cosmos.
It is possible that another, even more stable kind of vacuum exists.
As the universe expands and cools tiny bubbles.
Messages.
Of this new kind of vacuum might appear.
Bye, DigiLady.
They would spread at nearly the speed of light.
So the funeral of the DigiLady at the bottom of the elevator shaft was hell.
And a blast of energy would dash everything to bits.
And her body was transported to the roof garden for a wake.
However, this is considered somewhat theoretical and not as dangerous as the menace of rogue black holes
passing near our solar system.
Yes, it's possible.
It's possible that these rogue black holes could deform our orbital path around our star
and even send the Earth itself into freezing outer space and darkness.
That'd be okay. It'd be new.
And isn't everything new, like new experience, a good thing?
Well, black holes have been around since the beginning of the formation of the cosmos.
What about Rodney McDowell?
The whole galaxy has held black holes.
He's been around since the beginning of time and space.
Like a piece of Swiss cheese.
He was playing the TVs before the negatives were wooden.
They are...
A collapsed stellar...
Oh, jeez, not again.
Just a dozen miles...
Every time you talk about that, it happens.
How full of tough questions...
There it goes.
Whole societies going down the drain just because hell had to bring up collapsed systems.
They're called black holes for a reason.
They call them black holes...
Well, I guess it's kind of...
You know, whatever's fair.
If 100,000 civilizations had to die so you could hear us do this show, I guess that's okay.
You see, their gravity is so strong that they swallow everything.
While their comedy is so negative...
That they are unobserved by science.
Yeah, never mind.
It's just a black hole.
Never mind.
Even the light that might betray their presence is routinely sucked into a black hole.
Anybody here?
No.
No societies are dying here.
You can go now.
I like my coffee like I like my black holes.
Don't worry.
Everything's just fine.
Well, there are about 10 million black holes in the Milky Way.
I don't want to hear any snickers.
Hershey observed.
The observatory confirmed this.
And the Clark Observatory also.
God, the collar hung up.
The creamy nougat surrounding the caramel coating.
So, you see, the black hole could distort the orbital mechanics of the entire solar system very easily by being a powerful attractor.
Only because you keep bringing it up.
But even that seems a more complicated mechanism.
And we should always look for a simpler...
...way for us to be annihilated.
And that is probably from a giant solar flare.
I think you're talking about pizza by the slice.
They get huge, you know.
They get bigger than ever seen.
It smothers out all life.
Of course, these solar flares, probably known as coronal mass ejections...
I think it could happen.
...are enormous magnetic outbursts on the sun that bombard Earth with a torrent of high-speed subatomic particles.
What if the Captain Crunch peanut butter one factory went crazy and started making too much?
Earth's atmosphere.
And it smothered the Earth...
...negate the potentially lethal effects of ordinary flares.
But while looking through old astronomical records...
Not the fruity one, but the peanut butter one.
...worried scientists found evidence that some perfectly normal-looking sunlight stars can brighten up briefly by up to a factor of 20.
These stellar flickers are caused by superflare.
Millions of times more powerful than their common cousins.
Within a few hours, a superflare on the sun could fry Earth.
Ow.
And begin to...
...again disintegrating the ozone layer.
Not again.
Although there is persuasive evidence that our sun doesn't engage in such antics,
scientists don't know why superflares happen at all.
Or whether our sun could exhibit milder...
Could.
...but still disruptive autistic behavior.
And while too much solar activity could be deadly, too little of it is problematic as well.
And so, the sun could become not brighter, but nearly 1% dimmer.
It might not sound like much, but a similar downturn in the sun could send us into another ice age.
We'd freeze to death.
There is evidence that decreased solar activity contributed to 17 of the 19 major cold episodes on Earth in the last 10,000 years,
as freezing night descends on the lunar surface of the playa.
...
Did you hear about the sun activity, too?
The sun is like going through like a total peak time right now.
Yeah, George Jr. is really...
He's as popular as the father was.
But it is.
There's like a website.
It flares up a lot, I've heard.
There's like a...
God, what's this?
There's a website.
Flare, that's just...
They're more like little pubescent rockets than flares.
It's a really cool website, too.
...
That's all about it.
You can get a real-time sun screensaver now.
I would love one of those.
You used to put up four or five different pictures of the sun.
I should have sent it here.
We quit doing that because it was so disturbing.
It appeared that huge, gigantic shotguns were blasting away at the sun about half the time.
I think those were Masonic subliminals from the Masonics
who are running the NASA corporations.
The engine that creates all warmth for the whole solar system
is having a little trouble right now, did you say?
Supposedly.
It's more than a little trouble.
Now, could this possibly be the coming of prophecy,
of all the prophecies of every primitive form of humanoid?
When your mom and dad and everyone who you don't even know
is going to want to crash firmly onto,
as it's so loose,
in the sky,
like a burning lantern?
That all things, that the great carpet of reality
would be rolled up,
taken outside, hung over a tree limb,
and batted by a gigantic old hag
with a broom standing on the back of an infinite number of turtles.
And that she would spray it with an anti-lice sort of lotion potion?
Right, and then it would be rolled,
laid back down,
and all things would begin anew
in the new,
the new age.
Or the new,
um,
I forget the...
Well, how about...
The new Navajo Trail.
The new Navajo Trail?
In the Church of the Subgeniuses...
That leads off into the cosmos.
These silly primitive superstitions are understood in a scientific way
as the time intersection,
which will happen when the great Mobius strip
or infinity sign that is the road of time...
It has to cross in the middle, right?
Well, we're nearing that cross.
That's the number point.
Yeah.
See, I can repeat that.
I wanna set up a little deli right there at that crossroad.
Chad Spankengold.
People are gonna say,
well, what are you gonna do if them X's don't come on X Day?
A little general story.
It's like, well, I think the X's are kinda wondering what the hell's gonna happen when
the time intersection occurs.
Listener!
So what are you doing about it?
Are you ready?
Go last year.
You was ready for Y2K.
Hey, hey, stop playing with the machine.
All their liquor's stored up, their froth was stored up for Y2K.
Now, they're not worried about nothing.
They ain't worried about X Day.
They ain't worried about time intersection, about the fine rupture.
They don't care about nothing.
About time.
They're gonna get drunk and party.
Time doesn't exist.
Why should it?
And how can it?
They're just gonna get drunk.
Softly.
RG's about radio.
You think we're gonna go out there and keep drunk?
I know you.
I see you up from up here.
You know CHS will come on top of your brain now.
Well, buddy, you know.
They don't cut no ice with me.
Speaking of ice cutters.
I don't hear them in the front dress.
Hey, you remember, you remember the time intersection?
Remember the time Jack and I were out and we were so far, damn far out there that when
we dug the hole, you know, and stuck the-
Squid gigging?
We were squid gigging and we stuck the little shack over the top of the little hole in the
ice, you know, and we're sitting there popping back a few beer, you know, and I guess one
guy, this guy, you know, he's talking about Mario Lemieux and all this hockey crap all
night.
And I says, I don't like hockey, you know, so I pull this little like harpoon device
I got.
You know, it's about four and a half inches long.
You get it from the top.
You can order away for it.
And I shove it right into his thigh and rip those, you know, those real thick muscles
near the top of his knee, you know.
You're a prankster, Dave.
I tell you, we had a good laugh after that.
We had years and years of stories about that.
And I guess, well, it got him a little railed up, you know.
So did he kill you then now, Dave?
I think I know where the nano aliens live.
What do you think of me?
Why, they're the leprechauns.
Who's that guy?
Celtic legend.
They're the wee folk?
Pink penises, red hearts and purple...
Dave brains.
Brains.
Frolicking over the hillsides of Emery, Emerald Isle, Emerald Palace, Emerald City.
Emerald mushrooms.
That dirty, perky, sharka-packed, black, bunka-murtin, we wantin' Philip Bunka-Murtin,
perkaluma-burton, bunka-murtin, don't you watch tonight.
Well, then, of course, there's the
The Big Bang Theory.
The possibility of the sudden and unexpected reversal of Earth's magnetic field.
It could happen.
Yes, indeed.
The North and South Poles could flip and then flop.
The last Dutch reversal was 780,000 years ago in early October.
So we may be overdue for another one.
Worse, the strength of our magnetic field has decreased about 5% in the past century.
It's a whole lot.
It's a monster name.
Why worry in an age when GPS has made compasses obsolete?
Well, the magnetic field deflects particle storms and cosmic rays from sun, as well as
even more energetic subatomic particles from deep space.
He keeps talking, but look, monster.
Without our typical magnetic shield, these particles would ping into us and strike
Earth's atmosphere, eroding the already beleaguered beagle of the ozone layer.
Well, there's always a guy that keeps talking, and then there's the monster.
It gets a negativefy, but then says, monster, wallop, and then you're dead.
Well, what is he expected to do?
Gronk!
That stamp.
That snort?
Yeah, that comes then, after he keeps talking, then MONSTER DESTROY CITY!
We had evidence of such a monster before.
It happened many thousand of years ago.
Hmmm
That little Mimico.
Here is Mimico's original burial
Many creatures navigate by magnetic reckoning.
A magnetic reversal might cause these giant monsters to be confused, and why should I
wander about aimlessly, bumping into each other.
Oh, excuse me.
There are no identifiable fossil effects from previous flops and flips.
This is most curious.
But still, a disaster that kills a quarter of the population like the Black Plague in Europe
would hardly register as little old blip in the fossil record.
Teeny-weeny.
What a fright!
I can smell it back!
I figured, you know, I just needed some help.
I ordered my body.
Within 11 days, I had lost my waist and my hips.
Today, I'm wearing those pants about a year and a half now.
My kids aren't hurting me anymore.
My knees at my face and definitely in my stomach and my legs.
It's incredible.
So what are you waiting for?
622-1800-622-NOW and receive $25 supplies.
You'll also receive the book, Lose Sleep While You Sleep, free with your 622-46.
2-6-8-4-2-4-6.
And now...
Hi, I'm looking mighty good there.
Ooh, yeah.
I injured my rotator gears ago.
What happened?
Finally, it's not bothering me anymore.
Well, thanks.
I used to struggle on my knees.
On my knees.
Low.
Well, thanks.
You're fine.
In 1783, the Lakey Volcano in Iceland erupted, spitting out three cubic miles of lava.
Floods, ash, and fumes wiped out 9,000 people and 80% of the livestock.
The ensuing starvation killed a quarter of Iceland's population.
Atmospheric dust caused winter temperatures.
The
lakey eruption caused a quarter-cubic million miles of lava.
That's the Lakey eruption.
The lakey eruption, 100,000 times as large.
Some scientists still say that this, not an asteroid, killed the dinosaurs.
An earlier, even larger event in Siberia occurred just about the time of the Permian Triassic
extinction, the most thorough extermination known to paleontology.
At that time, 95% of all species were wiped out.
Sulfurous, stinking volcanic gases produce acid rain.
In 2016, an entire carrier of hydroxychloriance capable of leaving for Earth was affected
by an annuallyctrinated plant.
This eventdaily war has began to lack and make way for a priority in the environment.
While the AC's
with large CO2umeres
and ofte
I think that is the only thing I want to know.
The last big pulse of flood basalt volcanism built the Columbia River Plateau about 17 million years ago.
We're ripe.
Look at the size of it.
Yes, friends, we are ripe indeed.
Ripe to throw that loaf of this planet overboard.
And we've been listening to, well, it's been kind of an unusual hour of slack in that a couple of things fell into my lap
and it suddenly turned into an end-of-the-world show starring the KPFA subgenius show from around 9-2000
with Dr. Howell Robbins going on and on about the end and the various ways we can meet it
and puzzling evidence filling in the blanks.
And, of course, friends, as always, a lot of Einstein's Secret Orchestra swamp radio
from TV.
WCSB in Cleveland with Professor Chaz Smith dances with rockets.
A lonesome Cowboy Dave and yours truly, Reverend Ivan Stang.
And the clips and little media barrage bits that we've been hearing in between are by our friend New Monet,
Saint New Monet, who posted those on all binary slack.
Friends, we'll see you at www.subgenius.com.
But hurry, because it's all coming to a close so very, very quickly.
How are you?
Well, we could be killed by global epidemics because if the Earth doesn't do us in,
our fellow organisms might be up to the task.
Germs and people have always coexisted, but occasionally the balance gets out of whack.
Like when they had the Black Plague killing one European in four during the 14th century.
Influenza took at least 20 million lives between 1918 and 1919.
Now we got the AIDS epidemic producing a similar death toll and still going strong.
From 1990 to 1992, reports the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention,
mortality from infectious disease in the United States rose like a balloon, 58%.
And meanwhile, old diseases like cholera and measles are coming back.
They've developed resistance to all the high-tech drugs we've been throwing their way.
Intensive agriculture and land development is bringing humans closer to animal pathogens
and stinky germs that rest in huge mounds of animal feces cast off from factory farms
where giant chickens meet a hideous fate.
There was nice giant chickens too.
They was the ones in the commercials.
The grimest possibility would be the emergence of a strain that spreads so fast we are caught off guard.
That resists all chemical means of control.
Perhaps as a result of our stirring the ecological pot.
Damn it. It's our fault again.
Thank you.
It's the Our Fault Show.
Join us, won't you, on ourfault.org.
It's like a saloon in the Dave brain.
It's like an old western saloon in there.
It's always 2001.
Except for 2001.
Right.
But it's 1888 and, you know, like, it's like an old...
It's 1888 and 2001.
At the same time.
And the year 2328.
There's them like Lily, you know, type prostitute dancer girls around and cowboys...
The year 5449 is in there.
Well, of course.
That's the saloon at the end of time.
The saloon at the time intersection.
Where Dave meets every archetype of Dave.
From throughout history.
The transvestite hooker with a heart of gold.
Dave Visa.
Or Dave Vess.
The crooked mayor Dave.
The rich developer Dave.
All in the saloon at the end of the universe.
The starship captain handsome Dave.
The saddled cryptid.
The abyssal lawyer in a wheelchair.
Dave.
Recently developed.
The best man in the saloon of life.
What do you have partner?
What do you have?
You there.
Partner with the one eye pointed down.
The other one pointed.
What do you have?
I'll have a thyme, I'll have a thyme...
I mean a sarsaparilla, sir.
Hey, we don't serve no sarsaparilla in the old...
St. Louis sissies around here.
You can drink a man's drink
or you walk out there in the street
and get shot down by him.
And at the moment that they...
The inhabitants of the
cosmic saloon did not even notice
the passage of the time intersection.
But everything
had changed.
And when they walked outside, the circus
of Dr. Lowe was just
arriving.
Now our fans and tankers
may instead
laugh, laugh, laugh
laughing clowns.
And Sheriff Grumley was...
The Yeti jumped,
the sideshow Yeti
broke free from its chains, ran
into the crowd and carried off the
spinster repressed
Bridget Librarian.
He and Pan, having a three-way
with her, turned her on.
And then the stupid,
ignorant, racist rednecks
while getting
the local town
survived.
The Indian to dance
accidentally knocked over the
fishbowl containing the infant
Loch Ness monster, which
grew to gigantic size,
chased the man into a giant flaming
cathedral where they
threw spears at him until
they traded to James Franciscus and it
died.
And so we learn that
nature, in its infinite
wisdom, mocks man
with his puny pride.
Nature, which holds us in its
tender grip, its mercies, its gentle
cradle until we've approached the
moment of wisdom.
At which time it turns its hand down
and its cold, icy stare
out of it.
And so we know that Godzilla will be back
again
to teach man a lesson.
Only this time
he will
he will come to man
in the form of a friendly little
puppy named Joy Boy.
We have already seen these things.
Dr. Panaram and Dr. Patel and I have
spent hours and hours in mystic dreaming.
And this is our prediction.
That not only will the white buffalo return,
but the cute little puppy will be the messiah of mankind.
Oh man.
That's a lousy prediction.
Then there's global warming.
Forget what the Republicans say.
The Earth is getting warmer.
And scientists are saying
that scientists mostly agree that the humans
are directly responsible.
Damn humies.
It's easy to see how global warming
could flood cities, ruin harvests,
and more recently
researchers have raised the alarm
that a balmy planet
could also assist the spread of
infectious disease
by providing a more suitable climate
for hideous parasites
that bore into your skin
and tune their way right to your heart.
Arrrr.
Heart.
At present, atmospheric gases
trap enough local heat
close to the surface
to keep things comfy,
but increase the global temperature a bit
and there could be a bad feedback effect
with water evaporating faster
right in your face.
Freezing water vapor,
a potent greenhouse gas
which traps more heat
which drives carbon dioxide from the rocks
which drives temperatures still higher.
Earth could end up much like
Venus,
where the high on a typical day
is a sizzling 900 degrees Fahrenheit.
Again?
It would probably take a lot of warming
to initiate such a runaway greenhouse effect,
but scientists have no clue
where exactly the tipping point lies.
I'm into that panorama.
What do you mean they have no clue?
They're smart guys.
They are smart, but they don't know
because this is a situation
which has never been experienced before.
Earlier today,
Chaz was giving a sort of a trance lecture
about the range from
the protoplasmic beginnings
of all life
to space exploration.
And this lovely dome here
is certainly a good place
to think about that
because if we're not lucky
and we're not able to do it,
all of our descendants will live inside
little buffer domes like this
because there won't be
the right kind of air outside.
And if we are lucky...
Ah, yes!
Oh, baby!
Do that again!
I say!
Oh, I say!
Oh, hit me one more time, please, darling.
Oh, oh, oh.
You know,
if you increase the oxygen
in here too much,
a spark like that
can cause an explosion.
We don't be fried like those poor brave astronauts
on one of those ill-fated missions.
Turn up the oxygen, man!
On the other hand,
if you turn the oxygen up,
you get kind of high.
Well, let it sleep first!
Aww.
We'll box on those.
Anybody's gonna know.
Now, I'm not saying
that you should be afraid
the air outside
is not exactly the same as inside.
So you might want to go through
that decompression chamber first!
Oh, man!
Jeez!
These kids just go right in and out
from Earth atmosphere
to outside atmosphere.
Doesn't even bother!
I have to wear a mask
to go out there.
It's hard to keep up with evolution, man.
It was hard enough just to crawl out of that pond
and use the lungs.
That hurt!
You kids don't know nothing!
You never did have to crawl out of that ocean
and use them lungs
the first time.
And that first time
we had to invent murder,
that was hell, baby!
But, man's gotta eat.
Man's gotta eat.
You gotta get that,
you gotta build that spaceship somehow.
If you have to start by
chipping flimped rocks together,
well, that's a start.
Better than sitting on your butt
and scratching your butt.
Or is it, friends?
Wouldn't it have been better
for early man to have merely
sat upon its butt,
scratching that butt,
and picking its nose
and flees off into each other
and grunting like happy little monkeys
instead of all this progress?
Which, while it has brought us
these apps and things,
they're still not working right.
We have to breathe
this processed atmosphere
or else end up like those
new breed of kids
with the giant lungs and stuff.
Come on.
Sometimes I get mixed up
and can't even remember
what century I'm in.
I remember that one
time when we invented
legs.
That was out of necessity,
believe me.
No, but, you know,
I mean, there's some people think that
that, uh,
well, I used to think, Chaz,
we've been exhorting people
to build their own ships just in case
the aliens don't save our butts,
but I used to say to people,
well, hell, we got a whole other planet
right here on this one that's a lot closer
than Mars or the Moon and a lot more
hospitable, that being the ocean.
Oh, we got a whole other
two planets worth left to pollute
if that's what we wanted to do.
No!
He's a maniac!
Out to rule the world!
What can I do to make you understand him?
I love you!
A similar biological
disaster would be a complete ecosystem
collapse. Maybe this skin cream
will help me out. Images of
slaughtered elephants and burning rain forest
uh, well, they get your attention,
but the big problem, the overall
loss of biodiversity,
is a lot less visible and a lot
more serious. Billions
of years of evolution have produced
a world in which every organism's
welfare is intricately
intertwined with that of countless other
species.
A recent study of Isle Royale
National Park in Lake Superior
offers an example.
Snowy winters
encourage wolves to
hunt in larger paths.
So they kill more moose.
The decline in moose population
allows more balsam fir saplings
to live since they're not nibbled
and chewed by the marauding mooses
or meese. The fir
trees pull carbon dioxide
out of the atmosphere, which
in turn influences the climate
as the CO2 is sucked
from the air, replacing
diverse wild plants
with just a few varieties of
crops, transporting plants and animals
and introducing new and dangerous
chemicals into the environment.
At least 30,000 species
vanish every year from
humi activity, which means we are
living in the midst of one of the greatest mass
extinctions in Earth's history.
And it's all the fault of the
Republican Party.
Now while we are extinguishing
natural species, we're
also creating new species
through genetic tamperings
in weird secret labs.
Genetically modified crops,
they can be hardier, tastier, and more
nutritious, and they can be intensely
radioactive. Engineered
microbes might ease
our health problems.
And gene therapy offers
an elusive promise of
fixing fundamental defects in our
DNA. Then,
there are the possible downsides.
Although there is
no evidence indicating genetically
modified poos are unsafe,
there still are signs
that the genes from modified plants
can leak out somehow
and get on you, and
find their way into other
species.
Engineered crops might also
foster insecticide resistance.
The resulting superweeds
and supergiant insects
could further destabilize
the stressed global ecosystem.
Altered microbes
might grow to a large
size and prove to be unexpected
and incredibly difficult to control.
Scariest of all
is the possibility of the deliberate
misuse of biotechnology
to create a robobab.
A terrorist group or rogue nation
might decide that
anthrax isn't nasty enough,
and then try to put together
an airborne version of the
robobab's virus.
Now there's a showstopper for you.
Yeah, well, those are all
very large-scale causes
of mass death.
The holocaustic
xenotaph of the human race.
All that show just
thrown away.
I have been told you are planning
a child sacrifice.
They would be like a beast.
I am a slave.
But you have me too.
Well, there's one thing I have to get myself.
Something that will tell me when I've succeeded.
What's that?
A live giant grasshopper.
This beast isn't only electric.
It's intensely radioactive.
We have just received a report from America
that mountains of dead fish are washing ashore
along the coast from Maine to Florida.
Does everything in Texas spit toxic cud?
When you ask for something as special as a brain,
even Buddha is going to give you the runaround.
She's dead, master.
You've been a very bad boy
today.
Are you ready to accept my domination?
How's the fillet?
Tender?
You're eating one of my trainees
that didn't quite work out.
She wants to be in a freak show.
It's a freak country.
What about a particle accelerator mishap?
It could happen.
You know,
Ted Kaczynski,
the notorious Unabomber,
raved, they said,
that a particle accelerator experiment
would have a brain reaction
that would destroy the world.
Surprisingly, many sober-minded scientists
have had the same thought.
Normally, their anxieties
come up during private meetings
with corporate bosses.
It's much more on the backs of used envelopes.
Recently, the questions went public
when London Sunday Times reported
that the relativistic heavy ion collider
they call it RIC
on Long Island, New York
might create
a micro-world
with a subatomic black hole
that would slowly nibble away
our precious freedoms and our planet.
Alternately, it might create
exotic bits of altered matter
that would shoot right through you.
They're called strangelets,
and they would obliterate
whatever ordinary matter they met
to assuage RIC's jittery neighbors.
The lab's director convened
a panel that rejected both scenarios
as pretty much impossible.
Just for goodness' sake,
to good measure,
the passenger also complained
when they dismissed the possibility
that RIC would trigger
a phase transition in the cosmic
vacuum energy.
That's what I spoke of before,
that the vacuum would collapse
and become celestial ice nine,
and we'd all be frozen forever
in eternal amber.
What about the sponge?
Well, the sponge machine
is not nearly powerful enough
to make a black hole or destabilize
the entire atmosphere.
But we can always build
a bigger accelerator.
No!
Oh, Fernando!
Your mother ate my dog!
Not all of it.
Oh, I hate Fernando!
But it might not be big things
that bring us down,
because we could also have
a nanotechnology disaster.
You see, right now,
scientists are working
on developing what they call nanobots.
Millions of teensy-teensy robots
that get into your bloodstream.
Nano-nano.
Nanobots.
I didn't read that.
Well, they're nano...
I saw it.
Was it a favorable article?
Fairly favorable.
A punk called Chicken John.
Yeah, well...
So you see,
these tiny nanobots
could be designed
by artificial intelligences,
which could continue to refine
the nanobot design
until the human body
would be considered obsolete
and would be instantly chewed to flinders
by millions of jittering nanobots.
Not again.
I hate it when that happens.
Or, conversely,
environmental toxins
could squirt into the atmosphere.
As in Bhopal, India.
You know,
the world is ending pollution
in the snows of Antarctica.
The Earth is hopelessly contaminated.
When giant monsters are waking up
with anger in their hearts.
Yes, indeed.
Of course, there's also global war.
A nuclear war would be harmful.
Let's admit that.
And it would probably be very harmful
for the human species.
Together, the US and Russia
still have 19,000 active nuclear wars.
They don't say that's doctrinal to me.
Look at his feet.
He hasn't got real feet.
He's got those weird, like, pod things.
I can't believe a guy like that.
Look at his ears.
They've got, like, the weird radio materials
hanging right out.
But seriously, you know,
if we look at prophecy,
like as many do the weekly world news
there at the checkout line,
as we thumb through
Revelation X and the Book of the Subgenius,
we're entering a glorious new age.
Using our second or third foreskin thumb.
A new era of diseases,
of volcanic eruptions
Praise diseases.
that decimate entire states.
Earthquakes,
incredible man-made disasters
of gigantic stockpiles
of nerve gases
released into the atmosphere.
And confused,
all flapping amongst the small
Union children.
As they gathered by the gates
to sing songs.
The madness of the middle ages
will pale in comparison
to the marvelous, futuristic
new age that's coming.
We know that you,
the listener, are interested
in the future, or you wouldn't
be listening to this show.
You who are hearing my voice now,
those of you
who live into
the new age, will see
such wonders as
rubber cities.
Gigantic
dominoes
the size of skyscrapers.
All set to go off
and fall at once
on July 5th,
at Brushwood Campground
in Sherman, New York.
Such wonders as
glass,
lipstick,
growth books,
we like the glass lipstick,
sin pills,
I have taken
many, Master.
What shall I do now?
other miracles of science,
such as the robotic
butt puffler.
The eye condenser,
the amazing eye condenser,
takes what you see or what you have seen
and procreates into a small, proclivitous
package.
The package can be owned by a member of your family unit
now for a limited time,
but not in the neutral space.
These are completely designed for a modern you today
in the neutral space.
If you care, or if you dare,
just step into the box,
reach your hand out,
the influence will go on and on.
Are you ready for this future?
Is this really the future that you want?
This is food for thought, ladies and gentlemen.
And until next week,
the box is done.
Don't you dare.
Don't dare.
You're about to win.
And you're sagging the saddle.
Think about it.
Well, Mom,
I didn't want to go, but I didn't want to go.
Well, the first thing you said,
if I didn't go,
then I wouldn't be...
I didn't want to go.
You forced me to go.
Well, the first thing you said...
It's right where I want to go.
I didn't mean it.
You're about to get in the box.
It's the box.
I'm ready.
I'm ready to go.
Ready to be in control?
We now return control
of your television set.
I'm so sorry.
That I broke your heart
Please don't leave my side
Take me home, you silly boy
Cause I'm still in love with you
I'm still in love with you
Got your pencil ready?
Bob, Post Office Box 140306, Dallas, Texas 75214
That's Bob, P.O. Box 140306, Dallas, Texas 75214
Stay tuned and praise Bob!
And the blood came down to the grasses of the street
And the water poured down to the trees
And the rice that they had to trade
And the numbers that came through the fire and the flood
For all the new trees were made to survive the flood
Laughter
Oh, my God.
Maybe I should give them one more chance.
What?
No!
Get her out of here.
Jesus, sir, it's her party, too.
Get her out of here!
It's God and Bob.
Hey, Mike,
pitch me a rivet.
Ow!
Everybody out!
Rick Hardy, we're out of here.
Yeah, we're out of here.