We interrupt this program to activate the emergency subgenius power of SWAT.
Yes, friends.
Well, you know, according to subgenius prophecy,
the space monster Jehovah One told mystic salesman J.R. Bob Dobbs
that the world would end,
for everybody except subgenius cult members,
at 7 a.m. on July 5th.
Well, my friends,
we still aren't really home yet from the New York celebrations of X-Day.
Our minds aren't home yet.
So you might as well consider this a live X-Day show.
Even though the event itself, July 5th, was weeks ago.
Friends, we're always behind after X-Day
because we blow everything off,
assuming that our guru, J.R. Bob Dobbs, is going to be right this time.
We weren't harvested, but yet we harvested lots of recordings,
such as this of Acid Corpse performing at Brushwood.
And we harvested many subgenius.
We harvested many subgenius' radio shows,
such as the KPFA Berkeley show,
the WREK show in Atlanta,
Bob's Lifetime Funhouse,
and the WCSB show in Cleveland,
Dr. Sinister's.
And we'll start with the KPFA Puzzling Evidence show, friends,
with Dr. Howell at Puzzling Evidence and Philodruman's X-Day Report.
Yes, everyone's somewhat world-weary here.
Because you know what?
These fine young folks have just returned from X-Day,
and they're coming back in their triumphant post-X-Day parade now.
They're somewhat bedraggled and debauched,
and that's to be expected.
But good Lord, how clean they are.
Absolutely sparkling clean.
Their skins shine with a peculiar iridescence.
And, uh, well, I, uh...
It almost seems to steam with the heat given by warmth and moisture.
Oh, you're not there. Jingle your, uh...
What marvelous sights one sees at X-Day.
Uh, but, um...
One thing we did see, of course,
was when we assembled at 7 o'clock...
No, I see you doing that, but nothing's happening.
...a.m.
We're trying to talk to Philodruman down on the field.
Yeah.
He is there, and we will be connecting with Philodruman momentarily.
You may have to move to the room in the short term or something, too.
It was at X-Day that we gathered at, uh, 7...
I just heard that, I hope.
...a.m. on July 5th of 2004.
You can yell and scream, but nothing's coming through.
And as we waited in the shade of the main pavilion,
a band played, and then all eyes...
The house is working, and no one is not.
...went to the zenith of the sky.
Where a huge, round, glittering shape rapidly lowered down, expanding in size...
The mic is working.
...and blotting out the light.
With an enormous metallic humming...
Now.
...like the ringing of a glass...
Now. The mic.
...or the buzzing of innumerable bees.
Long, telescoping legs extended and, uh...
There goes those bees again.
Hear that bee in the background? He was just buzzing, buzzing, buzzing.
Well, you know...
Yes, he's a busy little dog.
The main theme now is, for the whole of the audience, is they want to know what happened on X-Day.
Well, I'm telling you.
And so then the ramp came down, and, uh...
We all moved up and down the ramp...
Want to know what happened on X-Day? They keep asking that question.
Now, next up, on Monday, July 5th, at 7 a.m. Eastern Daylight Time,
our Earth will be at aphelion, which means that it will be at its farthest point away from our sun for the entire year.
Almost 3 million miles farther away than it was when it was at perihelion, its closest, last January 4th.
And then, get ready for a super goodie.
All right, Atlanta.
Perhaps we have something for you here.
Yes, perhaps. Who knows? It's one of those things that...
Like this church, it's wild and unpredictable.
We are going to attempt to...
We are going to attempt to get a live update from X-Day.
From Brushwood, from Ground Zero, 7 a.m., July 5th.
That's where the smokin's gonna start. It'll spread outward from there.
All right, well, let's... let's try to punch him in.
Let's see if this thing's working.
Hello, do we have Brushwood?
Atlanta to Brushwood, over.
I think we're being jammed at the source.
Uh-oh.
Oh, my God, you don't think they did it, Jonestown, already?
There's something.
Suzie, I don't know if you can hear me, but here at X-Day number 7,
it is a complete catastrophe.
I am watching the fire eat away at the very heavens right now.
It was a terrible tragedy.
The pipe of Bob that we had in the fire circle whenever the burning cross finally fell...
Oh, what the fuck?
Well, it disgorged a little gift for all of humanity,
and it's currently burning down everything that we ever loved.
I knew it was gonna be good.
And yet we somehow feel much more cleansed for it.
And now, with more details,
is the Reverend Ivan Singh on site.
Oh, no, that crummy...
It's a perfect success if death and destruction is...
Suzie, are you there?
Yes, yes, I'm here, but you can't hear me.
It's a nightmare, and yet it's like heaven.
It's like a Jack Chick comic come to life.
It's what every X-Day is supposed to be.
Surely the saucers will be here.
Oh, damn it, damn it.
What? What? Oh, my God, there's silence.
The police are coming.
We're gonna have to...
We may not be able to be on for long.
Hold it.
Hold on.
I'm gonna...
What?
Stand up.
Suzie, hold on just one second.
We're just kind of...
No, don't get away from me, you goddamn...
No, no, no.
You're a victim.
You can't...
You can't stop.
Ow!
Oh, shucks!
Oh my...
Oh, shit!
I gave them 32plea rand.
Okay, who are you?
I just sticks a blowjob a 30 this weekend.
Come in.
I was gonna say, if you don't block guys, we'll fuck...
I missed that time out.
That's an accessory.
Call that мест.
We will.
We will beat the fuck up.
He throws me a blowjob and does one side first.
I go.
And man, I really need that sort of stuff to bathe in.
I can't find virgins anymore.
Oh no, you can't find a good virgin these days.
Well, virgin on the ridiculous, but they don't go for the technical virgins.
Ah, it's starting.
The floppy boot.
Okay, now we started in the X-Day Parade.
This is inspirational.
To be here at the X-Day Parade.
At the 2004 X-Day Celebration.
While we wait for the saucers to descend.
It's a beautiful parade day.
On our...
Clear sky.
No sign of a saucer yet, but we're all hoping and waiting.
Except, of course, for Philo Drummond who decided to stay at home in his bed.
Reading the National Review.
But the rest of us are...
Wait a minute, is that something that we see up there in the sky?
A glittering round?
It is.
It's the saucer.
It's coming down.
Oh, this is just great.
The crowd is really reacting.
Look at their enthusiasm.
And the saucer now makes its way through the float.
Parade.
Look at those great little cutout characters of space aliens on top of the saucer.
Those aren't cutouts.
I believe they're made out of roses.
Actually, razor thin aliens.
Razor thin and razor sharp, I might add.
You wouldn't want them to make a...
You don't want to stroke those aliens on the edge or cut your hand.
I don't want to stroke those aliens at all, Philo.
But it may be that I'll have to.
It may be that we'll all have to.
You'll have to.
Since it's going to be a new day and a new world since we've been visited by our visitors
You have to stroke the alien sometime.
You can depend on me, darling.
Well, I better the aliens have a stroke.
I do depend on you to help me stroke the alien.
All right.
I think we've stroked this alien thing for all it's worth.
Isn't that a dance like Shock the Monkey that somebody did?
Stroke the alien.
Okay, if you say so.
Wasn't it Cha-Cha-Cha?
Nice hitting.
No, it wasn't.
Yeah, well, they do have nice cities.
It's hard enough to do these dance moves.
They're half underground, half above ground.
Yeah, this is when the saucers show up over you, these guys' heads.
I was strolling through the park one night and oh, I felt so blue
When I heard a little voice say, I'm so lonely too
Then I turned around to look and to my surprise
A little space girl said they're crying right before my eyes
Stepping up a little closer to see what I could see
She said, Mr. Earthman, will you please marry me?
I said, why no, I couldn't do that
Well, that just wouldn't be right
Cause you and me and me and you
We don't even know each other anymore
What do we look alike?
Cause you've got four arms
The better to hold you
Three lips
The better to kiss you
Three eyes
All the better to see
I can really rock and swing
Cause I've got more of everything
Oh, Mr. Earthman, will you marry me?
Then I said, what will people think
When we go strolling by?
Why?
They not only laugh at us
They lay right down and die
Then they'd put you and me in jail
There we would be
And the people, they'd come from miles around
Just to look at you and me
Cause you've got four arms
The better to hold you
Three lips
The better to kiss you
Three eyes
All the better to see
I can really rock and swing
Cause I've got more of everything
Oh, Mr. Earthman, will you marry me?
I said, this ain't gone far enough
I've had enough of it
She said, please, Mr. Earthman
Just one little kiss
I said, okay, okay, okay
But then you go away
But when I finish kissing her
I had this
Then I said, what will people think
When I've got four arms
The better to hold you
Three lips
The better to kiss you
Three eyes
Oh, the better to see
I can really rock and swing
Cause I've got more of everything
Oh, Mr. Earthman, will you marry me?
Why, sure!
A thanks to Artemia Savina,
for sending that one in.
And now, Reverend Carter LeBlanc,
live at Brushwood.
So, it's X Day.
It's almost X Day.
It's, uh, let's see, how far are we?
Anybody got a countdown calendar going?
How many more minutes till the end of the world?
No, I didn't think so.
Nobody really even seems to be paying attention.
I think everybody is kind of suspecting
the same things that I'm kind of expecting,
which is, uh, we got sold out, you know?
I mean, we really, we really kind of got screwed.
You know, we were told saucers 1998.
They make up all these excuses
that seem to justify
you know, the absence of saucers.
But the simple truth is
the saucers seem to have passed us by.
There were some people after 1998
that came to Stang
and they were, I think, really upset about that.
And a lot of those people,
a lot of people didn't come back, actually.
Which is fine
because really maybe those are the people
that got ruptured.
They got, uh, you know, they got taken away
because if there's one thing
that we really don't need here
in the Church of the Subgenius,
it's a true believer.
I mean, you know, we don't really need any, uh,
I mean, we don't really need any true unbelievers either
because, I mean, belief and disbelief
both mean pretty much the same thing.
You no longer are accepting new ideas
about a certain issue.
And, uh, so, so what I'm seeing here
is that something special has been given
to those people that lost faith.
You know, those people have been given a gift.
A gift called suspicion and disbelief.
You know, anytime any of those people
that have walked away from the Church of the Subgenius,
anytime they go to another religion
or another spirituality or another faith,
they're going to be receiving a form of self-indulgent,
uh, you know, self-gratification
that we like to think of as religion,
but it's just really justification for our actions.
Anytime somebody goes somewhere else
to find something else somewhere inside their mind,
they're going to be thinking,
is this just another scam?
Is this just somebody else making money off of me?
Is somebody else getting rich off of me?
Just like, just like when I gave all that money
to the Church of the Subgenius?
Those people have been given a gift.
It's called disbelief.
You know, the conspiracy pays you well, probably.
I mean, compared to how well
the Church of the Subgenius pays you.
Uh, I've, I have worked for both,
and I can tell you that the conspiracy pays you real well
to do work that is not,
is guaranteed to be forgettable.
That's what it's all about.
And so you, you're faced with the problem of,
do you want the pay,
or do you want to do the work that is useful
and will be remembered?
And, uh, uh, friends,
what we'd really like to do is,
you know, neither one.
Why, why, why do we have to do either one?
Bob said we should be rich without,
equally rich, without working.
Boy, that would be fair, wouldn't it?
Wouldn't it be so fair
if everybody was equally rich without working?
Well, friends, you have to make that choice.
Are you enough of a subgenius
to, to, to declare July 5th, Monday,
normally a working day,
as your religious holiday,
earned by the blood of Bob on that stage
as he bled for it?
Well, he didn't bleed for you, actually.
He bled for the insurance money.
We must get off of Earth.
Oh, Bob.
Oh, please.
Gotta get off Bob.
Bob, Bob, Bob.
Oh, oh man.
Holiday next day yet, but,
oh, looks like I'm just ahead of the clock radio.
Okay, this is it, this is it.
Okay.
Ten, nine, seven, eight,
five, three, four, three, two,
Monday, July 5th at 7 a.m. Eastern Daylight Time.
Oh, man, Bob.
Not again.
Oh!
.
Oh, hell.
Oh, at least I'm getting used to it by now.
.
Okay.
Well, I guess the next step is the inevitable vicious taunting
at the hands of evil Susie.
.
Yeah, that's the way it always plays out.
Ah, jeez Louise.
.
I can actually hear that heartless bitch warming up
. . .
. . . .the abrasive cacklers.
.
You're in my pill stash!
You're right, Blues.
Why'd you have to stash them under the toilet?
They're all tangy.
Spit them out!
Come on!
Some of that's for an actual emergency.
Let me go.
I don't want to live anymore.
Ah, help!
Get your head out of my damn mouth!
Oh, no!
Get out!
Oh, man.
What gives?
Does Freaky Friday fall on a Monday this year?
This post-X-Day Suicide Blues thing is my shit, dude.
Bite me!
What fools we were to think that we would get to go on some divine killing spree
and crush all the pink boys
with a single blow.
With our alien powers.
Well, we believed, uh, we believed Stang.
We did believe Stang.
Guess what he said.
I bought into it.
I sent in my money.
Well, so you really bought into it.
Like, literally.
The only kind of bot that counts, baby.
All right, baby.
Not to Bob.
We were, uh, young, dumb, and full of, uh...
Fun.
Yeah.
That's what we were.
We were bright-eyed, and, um, I can't spoil the end.
You all know what happened.
How do you think?
But about, just listen in.
In about ten minutes before X-Day, we actually started alibi-ing.
All right, fine.
Yes, I'm a little bitter.
Yes, I understand that the conspiracy made the calendar.
And it's not 2003.
Who knows what year it is?
It could be 1005.
Well, how do we know they got July 5th right?
And X-Day could be at any second.
I'm aware of that.
Does Ted Man make an appearance on the telephone during the show?
Of course he does.
Oh, that's wonderful.
I don't think you people have enough Ted Man in your lives.
He has a...
He's calling us from the Observer.
Right.
Oh, he sees the alien who wants to be his friend, and I think they have sex.
I believe they do.
Well, that's wonderful.
And, uh, there's some people who got some science guys, but hey, you're gonna hear it.
This show has been Stalinized for quality.
WCSB, you're on the air.
I got lost on the way to the station.
You got lost on the way to the station?
Oh, no, that's right, we already did that show.
Yeah, you already did that show, man.
Only we didn't get to do that show, but we did that other show.
He was patient there.
We need help on the next airport, because I'm stumbling.
We got lost in the station.
We got lost on the way to Planet X, man.
Yeah.
Tables say we'll turn around.
Planet X will soon be found.
How could you get in a place...
How could you get lost in a place so plainly and so clearly formatted?
Right in front of you, the holograms are everywhere.
If you get lost, all you have to do is wave your fingers in front of your eyes.
Bobbies know they're yeti pests.
I think basically we meant that right.
Pink boys, they're all guests.
Yeah.
He's the slack man.
That's why their armpits are so hot.
It's so sad that when you...
You...
You expect...
You expect to be ruptured and evaporated up into the escape vessels, but it doesn't
happen for another year, so you go home and in spite, you start up your lawnmower and rupture
your grass.
Yeah.
If I had a million little grass souls that my excess pleasure saucer played by my lawnmower,
I'd spend all morning sucking those little souls up so that they're...
Hold for a second.
Well, now they're on their way to the city dump, which will double as Planet X for them.
Pink boys, listen, we gotta take a break here.
I hope you guys hold the line for just a moment.
The wind break.
All right.
This isn't over the edge.
No, but it's over the line.
You crossed that line.
Oh, man, can't we just go back to have things like they used to be?
Can't we all just get along?
Now it's cool back down here.
No, we can't, man, because the world ended, man.
Like I heard last week, the world ended, man.
And you died, man.
Yeah.
Well, it didn't actually end.
We thought it was going to.
The big UFOs came.
We thought it would, but something happened and prevented it from ending.
No, it actually did.
We all received a mental block later, a piece of forced conditioning, which was...
Whenever you see this picture...
Ah, yes.
You see this particular picture, it brings one out of the trance of oblivion.
What picture is that?
I can't see the monitor from over here.
Show it.
Is that the X-Day picture?
It's a stereoscopic picture of what happened.
I already made a CD that made a million bucks off what you guys were doing last week.
Wow, invasion.
Invasion of Earth.
But it's really too late to do anything about it, so I don't even really want to get in trouble by talking about it.
Now, what was the other highlight of your experience at X-Day, Dr. Howell?
The other highlight?
Other than, you know, the beautiful naked women.
Come on, man, don't step on the Rice Krispies.
That was just one of the many highlights, of course.
Don't step on the Rice Krispies thing!
Here it comes.
Actually, I enjoyed the easy camaraderie of my comrades in arms in the barracks.
Blah, blah, blah.
The man must know that he hath broken his code.
And he shall soil thy loincloth with the fear of Jehovah.
For Jehovah is the God of wrath.
Step away from the bowling ball.
I think I saw the staying person light the fuse for the end of the world.
Light the fuse.
I think I saw it.
A mulberry stalk.
That's what you say you saw.
Well, he bent over and something came out of him.
And then...
Ew!
And then everything started shaking and he was running past me away from this area.
That was just his psyche that came out of him.
Why would anyone want to leave beautiful...
Uh-oh, he's releasing foul gases.
Yeah, something like that. And then we were running.
Apparently, Bob came and did something to all of us.
There's Reverend Stang.
Something did come out of him.
He changed us somehow.
Reverend Stang.
Ew!
What are you doing up so early, Reverend Stang?
Oh, the...
We...
Somebody burned the whole campground down.
Oh, no.
Yeah, I tried to...
Jesus!
But we were already gone, so what difference does it make?
Well, I was trying to go back there for the love and peace that happens at Brushwood.
And the whole campground had been burned down by the subgeniuses of the Black Flash.
All the trees were denuded and black and ash.
Once again, the subgenius Bobbies have ruined everything else.
Well, you know what that was? You guys, you didn't listen to me years ago.
That's what we would have called prop wash from the UFOs.
Those landing brakes they have just scorch everything, including the little non-normals.
Right, and they don't care. They're just aliens, you know.
They don't even see them.
I'm not wearing any pants.
Well, why would you have to?
Exactly.
In these modern times, no one needs to call themselves a zipper in strange ideas.
Especially not on the radio.
Oh, tell that to my sunburn, Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
Yeah, I got a little sunburned the next day, too, actually.
I don't think it was the sunburn. I think it was the...
It wasn't the sun. It was the saucers hovering overhead.
And when you get in the path of that afterburner of theirs, which is a special...
It's a special graviton emission...
There's protons.
Well, it's got a couple different...
A couple different principles working in the saucer...
The things that keep the saucers aloft.
One, of course, is the graviton emission.
Right.
You can get a sunburn.
You can get a lot of pain in the buttocks.
The other one, of course, is the...
You also got a multiple contusion going on in your skin.
Pastor Pressure was showing off a sunburn in the shape of Jesus.
It was an anti-sunburn.
It was like that Jesus was formed by little spots that weren't burned.
It was a reverse Jesus sunburn.
In the middle of a burned chest.
I think it had gone to a body cursing at a parlor, a biker place, before he attended the festivities.
And that's about it, Stang.
I think you're kind of ruminating over what might have been.
There were a lot of people who had actual saucer burn on the buttocks.
I mean, not in America.
Maybe 700. That's a lot, right?
Well, we had a little bucket of hell and a little bucket of heaven.
So you could put your feet in either one at the same time.
Get a bucket of heaven.
But yes, after the drag...
What did we do after the drag king, queen...
The drag queen and king balls.
Weren't there a million psycho-freaker rock and roll rock out rock bands?
That's right. We had a great...
It was the Acid Corpse played...
I guess that was the first night of band nights.
But what about the Swinging Luv Corpse?
Well, that's their name. That was their name.
We had the Swinging Luv Corpses.
Three members of the Swinging Luv Corpses.
Melded with four members of the Amino Acids.
So the Amino Acids provided the bass and the drums and the tenor.
I don't forget what kind of...
It wasn't a tenor, but it was maybe a baritone guitar that that one guy had.
And then we played sax and guitar and trumpet and violin things.
And violins.
We played Kandinsky Protesthera and Paul Jay for over and over again.
包括 большую доску музыю Someday that Joyeuse.
And then we played Stinewindbrderes
And we played a hit by Beeume
And it felt like the best challenge of our years."
Well, we played the Shimoy Baş channel...
And from the bottom of the house we played the singer殴
Ready?
Dude you got it.
His voice is so beautiful.
She said, oh, baby.
Oh, baby.
And then I said, oh, baby.
And then ever so gently, ever so nicely.
With so many sexual overtones, you looked over at me
and you said, baby.
And I knew right there, that's when I knew.
This is the way you said baby.
Not so much a B part, but a baby part.
Bye-bye.
You couldn't just say baby.
You had to say bye-bye.
What is that?
What's that?
Bye-bye.
That's a little number we've been working on called Bay Bay.
We was on drugs.
It felt good.
So then after the Acid Corpse played, and we played for an hour and 45 minutes, which
only seemed like 20 minutes to me.
It was just like being in heaven.
It was such great anti-music and wonderful mystery jazz and great sort of like space
bug surf jam stuff.
Space bug surf jam.
Yeah.
So after that, let's see, I guess after that we just partied until like it was 1999 until
about 2 or 3.30 in the morning, 4.30 maybe, and then we'd go to bed.
And then we would toss and turn fitfully as the three most thunderous snorers.
Suicide man wants to know something.
Oh, I just wanted to know.
No, we're not on the air anymore.
Hey, what happened to you, suicide man?
Are you on drugs or something?
I feel a little strange.
You feel a little slowed down to me.
Concentrate on the reality we're throwing out to you.
Look out.
Hey man, get out of the way.
You got to get out of the way.
The reality will run you down.
It's like a tank.
Let me dash.
Get out of the way.
It's like a fast tank.
It's a fast tank with wheels instead of tracks.
I'm just going to tell you what.
Straighten up or fly around.
You can lead a horse to water.
You can't make him drink.
So what's your point, dude?
You're sitting on your point, right?
You're sitting on it right now.
Admit it.
We were just discussing a strange fellow who claimed to have died, but is still alive to
plague us today.
You're right.
You have never seen such sights.
Your heart has never felt such emotion, such sorrow, such joy.
You will be uplifted and never have you seen such freaks of nature.
One look at them will tell you more than a thousand words of mine.
I'm sorry.
Come and see.
See little Theodore and .
I just sit here watching squirrels.
They have much more fun than me.
Sometimes they run around.
They run around all day in circles.
They fight and squabble.
Then they lick their wounds.
At least they seem to have a purpose.
My mind's always clogged with leads.
Like silly, stupid advertising jingles and themes on TV shows I do not like.
I must not go out the front door.
I could get hit by a car.
Just like the squirrels when a dog is growling.
There's perfect safety high up in the tree.
I'm not afraid of the squirrels.
I know I'm bad to just sit here.
I should not be so afraid.
But once outside I'd have to choose a direction.
It might be the wrong one so I'll stay here.
They tell me of self-improvement.
And someday could even have a job.
Then I would have become just like the squirrels.
I don't see how I could accomplish that.
First I'd have to choose a direction.
Like which tree I should start to climb.
видوING depiction
and it's all on to the Yu-Gi-Oh!
CAPTIONING PROVIDED BY Hageliendos Dr.
Subtitles took from Goodbye 사 booth by Zymena
Anchored by Cyndwha Therkovif
și
just watching squirrels.
Though the soundtrack could be much improved.
Those silly, stupid advertising jingles.
And themes on TV shows I do not like.
Wah, wah, wah, wah, wah, wah, wah.
Wah, wah, wah, wah, wah, wah.
Wah, wah, wah, wah, wah, wah, wah, wah, wah.
Wah, wah, wah, wah, wah, wah, wah, wah, бavian!
Wah, wah, wah,就是說 !
demonstrate .
Looks I'm between
wah, wah!
Dah!
Tl lassos chita!
R judicial bang!
I lil pekoeka.
You know, I like him.
He's silly.
The audience doesn't think that's very funny.
I mean, they do think that's very funny.
They're laughing their heads off.
Look, they love it.
Old rape a man.
See, I know people that say it's impossible
and completely antithetical to the concept
to think that a man could be raped.
That he wouldn't do it willingly and enjoyingly.
Joyfully celebrating the...
This is the effect of X-Day, folks.
This is what happens to the mind once it's brainwashed.
Yes, thank you, thank you.
We'll run to you.
We'll spin you.
Our entire time in the bachelor's cabin
with a crude, raucous joke.
We did manage to spend some time at the Frop...
at Dr. Frop's...
What do you call it?
Oh, so yeah, what was the entertainment like?
We just called it Frop's Place.
What about all the bands that played?
All the bands were excellent.
There was the amino...
the amino...
amino acids.
The music was literally pyrocyclic.
BEHIND THE EVERYTING
BEYOND THE FONE
OOF
You better touch this.
Yes sir, you better.
YA統ons
NO
He is the one doorway to financial heaven.
He is the one real shortcut to slack.
But the amino acids were actually almost shut, you know, not shut down.
And there was Little Theodore.
The first act.
Really? Oh, great.
Yeah, Little Theodore was there.
So why were they almost shut down?
Why were they pretend shut down?
Oh, I was just saying they were almost blown away by the band the previous night.
They were blown away.
The jam band kicked, literally kicked the posteriors of all the individual subs.
Boy, were they sore.
Was it with a big leather boot?
With a big leather boot with red straps.
Big leather hobnail boot with red straps.
Well, now, would you like to say for our listening audience just who were some of the famous subgeniuses present at this earth-shaking event?
Well, let's see.
We did have, well, we had you.
You were there.
Well, you're right.
I was there.
And not only that, I think I saw Reverend Two Beans there.
Yeah, Two Beans was there.
Let's see.
Who else was there?
There was Doc Frop and Sister Decadence.
And Dr. Piss Off.
Doc Piss Off.
Yes, Sister Decadence.
Magdalene and Jesus, of course.
Yes, and thousands and thousands of other famous and semi-famous.
Where did all these bobbies come from?
I think he was saying, I don't know.
They're not even yet to be famous.
That's what he's talking about.
I think all the grapes.
Bob Toberfest.
What they do is they cut their hair and then dye their heads purple.
It's having something to do with attracting the sun for Bob.
Hey, I think that's a good idea, Reverend Howell.
Maybe we should have a Bob Toberfest.
Yeah.
I get it.
Bob Toberfest.
That'd be awesome.
Can we have some beer there?
Would you come, caller?
We could find...
Could you bring some women?
Yeah.
Okay, good.
Sounds like you have a lot there.
You know, they're like smaller versions of us.
Okay, what notes do we play on this song?
Okay, this is Betty Blows.
Betty Blows, part one.
This is a little symphony we've been working on for a while.
Let's hear it with Lenny.
Music.
Sheddy blows, Sheddy blows, Sheddy blows, Sheddy blows, Sheddy blows, Sheddy blows,
He's gonna blow
Sheddy blows chumps
A bendy howls
Sheddy blows, Sheddy blows, Sheddy blows, Sheddy blows,
guitar solo
Blah blah blah
And they bringeth the light stone
Blahm, the whore
Virgin brain, the guilt finder
And smiter
The very mark of the covenant
And she is the eye of the Father
She shall rule thee
And overcome the mark of the beast
And shall give thee fornication
And the true sons of Israel
Shall be snatched up
Behold, my servant shall prosper
He shall be exalted
And lifted up
And shall be very high
He who knoweth the fools
Who prophesy for me
Shall be made over men
Many will be astonished at him
For his appearance is so marred
Nond human semblance
And his form beyond that
Of the sons of man
Those who are over men
Who have followed my almighty word
Shall be the minister
Of the angelic host
They shall speak for them
And my prophet who smiles
Shall be among them
And shall advise them
Well, I'm sorry to have to call you on a normal phone
From somewhere else on earth
And I'm sorry to have to call you on a normal phone
I'm sorry Bob let us down
I'm sorry, okay, I'm sorry
Yeah, but you get to be on the ship
You don't have to be sorry
We're gonna do it again next year
Hey, by the way, were you number one in line
Like your ticket says every year at the gate
Um, no, actually
I'm number one in line
We use a double because I'm the one
Filming the line
Ah, there's always a sacred filmer
And they always think that the sacred filmer
Is not really an artist
That's right, they don't recognize it
It's both a blessing and a liability
Have you looked at any of the footage yet?
Yes, yes and the
The bashing of the Christ
Not to be confused with the
Mashing of the Christ by Negative Plan
But our
Our competition for their short
Subject should be
Should really look good
We got plenty of footage, we really hurt Jesus bad
Did you kill him like Holy George?
He's still alive
Being a Merovingian
And we
So basically everything that way is great
For next year we'll have another Jesus
The campground will grow back
The pagans will
Recuperate, and the subgeniuses
Will return everything they've stolen
Once again
Wow, is the little fake Bob okay?
Yeah, that's the funny thing, this was the
Ex-day when the thieves
Returned what they had stolen
And
And asked me to thank them, expecting me to
You go, oh, thank you for doing that for three years.
That is a strange phenomenon.
But the thing is, back where you are on that planet, they return them.
Here they just keep them forever and gloat in their living rooms with their two friends.
Yes, yes.
We all know about that.
Ghosts and ghouls and wearing black.
The cross on no one there to come back.
Eternal, blissful, pristine black.
I've looked at death this way.
But now it's just a boring pain.
You get all stiff.
You blow.
You lost the game.
And I think it's your best chance for fame.
When it does you no damn good.
I've looked at death from both sides now.
From cool and blue.
And still somehow.
It's death's illusion time.
I really don't know death.
Oh, yes.
Little Theodore.
And I'll be giving you contact information for him presently.
Friends, we've heard all kinds of things.
Such as prescripture readings from Doc Ellis.
From the Book of the Subgenius.
By Gobs.
Friends, and lots of stuff from Doc Ellis.
And Susie the Flusie.
On Bob's Slack Time Funhouse.
On WREK in Atlanta.
The greatest college station in the world.
We heard Dr. Philodrum and Hal Robbins.
Doug Wellman on Puzzling Evidence.
On KPFA.
And we heard Little Theodore.
And Babushka.
And you can get more information from Little Theodore.
At www.littletheodore.com.
That's Theodore.
F-Y-O-D-O-R.
Lymph Node Institute.
Is where Doc Ellis is working from.
That's at lymphnodeinstitute.com.
And the swinging love corpses.
Philodrum and Sphinx Drumming and Ray Hay.
Can be found at quiveringbrain.com.
The amino acids are at theaminoacids.com.
And lonesome cowboy Dave and St. Bucky and I.
Have been calling in to Dr. Sinister's radio synesthesia.
On WCSB in Cleveland.
At St. Bucky and I.
At 7 o'clock.
No, 10 o'clock p.m. on Sundays.
Friends, that Bob Slacked on Funhouse.
Is on WREK.org at midnight.
Puzzling Evidence is on at Friday at 5 a.m.
On KPFA.org.
And Sinister's show is on at WCSB.org.
Friends, this is Acid Corpse in the background.
And this is Hour of Slack.
At number 951.
Oh, I should mention.
You can download copies of the Puzzling Evidence show from this address.
Get that pencil tape recorder ready.
That's matrix.c-s-u-s-t-a-n.edu.
Slash negative.
Negative.
Without the E.
Again, friends, this is the Hour of Slack.
Radio Ministry.
Church of the Subgenius.
Episode number 951.
Yeah.
This show has been done more to educate the denizens of Northern California.
And the one and only.
World on dozens of myths that have pervaded Masonic lore.
It's about saying what's got to be said.
Fascinating.
Horrible.
But fascinating.
Sit down.
Relax.
So, are you glad to be home now, Reverend Stagg?
Well, I'd rather be on my, you know, my home in outer space.
My own escape vessel planet.
In your special space ranch.
In your special yacht with L. Ron.
The yacht catisma.
Ha, ha, ha.
Actually, I was more looking forward to seeing Herf Applewhite, previously known as Doe.
Oh, yeah.
And David Koresh.
Yes, they'll be there in the afterlife, waiting with open eyes.
And all those young eunuchs.
All the great famous Texas evangelists are waiting for me aboard the escape vessel.
Yeah.
And what about the Nike-wearing eunuchs?
The Nike-wearing eunuchs.
That was first brought up in the artist press.
The Dobbshead shirt.
The Bob's
Yeah, that's what happened, is the people who did the first Dobbs shooting parody also
talked about the various heavens that famous people would go to.
And there they are.
And each person gets to go to his kind of famous person heaven.
But then you're stuck there with people like your own Jeaner.
There's Lon Chaney Jayner.
There's Lon Chaney Senior.
Lon Chaney Jayner.
There's Della Lugosi.
Lon Chaney.
Ha, ha, ha.
All the great celebrities.
Ed Wood.
I got a telephone voice.
They're all there on board the escape vessel.
Which is what we cover with this radio program, Coastal Damn.
I'm Art Bells.
All right.
The saucer last weekend.
The saucer.
Remember that?
Too good to be true.
I said so at the time.
Well, sure enough.
The good news is it's there.
It really is.
It is exactly where the photograph said it was.
The bad news?
It seems to be an elaborate construction by a member of the Church of the Subgenius.
A gag mail order classy religion that worships a clip art face named J.R. Bob Dobbs.
For lack of a better explanation.
The old abandoned saucer home also known as a pleasure saucer.
Where many a subgenius devour.
The Bible has no doubt been held.
Can be seen in detail.
And it gives a fine, you know, URL.
But it's the same photograph we have.
So it really is there.
I knew it.
They'll pay to know what they really think.
Well, Mr. Zhang, it was an almost foolproof plan.
Because I love Bob and I'm happy.
You're a fool.
Why don't you Dugs go over to Pirate Cat Radio and do your show over there?
We're zero listeners.
Too many Dugs.
Yeah, man.
Uh-oh, I didn't realize what time it was.
Uh-oh.
I did.
I could tell, but the show was getting so foggy and hard to hear, I figured it must be ending.
It's murky.
We'd like to add the murkiness at the end.
Sure.
Help murkify it a little bit.
It seemed like it has about a fog of fog.
It said at about six and the murk is moving up.
It's weird.
Ten.
Well, the murk is moving in.
And as you know, it's getting closer to that time in the schedule when puzzling evidence has to shut the special cap on Fox.
How does America handle a headache?
I'm proud to be on a murkin.
Well, that's true.
And so are we all.
Well, as we stand on that spotty flag after our long history and our climb up from the primordial ooze to our present eminence as prominent American subgeniuses.
Yeah, I'm going back to the ooze, man.
You should go back to bed.
You're going to go up to your special chamber.
My oozing bag.
I'm going to climb back in my oozing bag and go back to sleep.
Good night, Dr. Stang.
Kill them all.
Let Bob sort them out.
For in his sorting is not the high epaulet.
That's the most arbitrary of judges.
Oh, my.
So here are the engines of the oncoming ships.
Finally, they're landing.
Oh, no.
That was another drill.
Damn.
Well, we'll certainly have one.
You know the drill.
Oh, my God.
Christ, Bob.
Hello.
Is Bob Dobbs there?
I'm the little guy who lives in the corner.
Bob Dobbs, you there?
Hello?
Oh, you bastard.
I'm going to kill you one day.
Beep.
.
¶¶