And now you are ready for the final 200,000 mile voyage to the moon.
We subjected it to careful editing to eliminate elements which we might consider in questionable taste for late night viewing.
As it will be shown, it is well within the restrictions of the television code,
which is even more restrictive and stringent in many areas than the industry code.
So, we are sensitive to the concerns which prompted your letter.
We're sorry.
And assure you that this network will continue to adhere to the high standards we have maintained throughout the years.
We won't do it again.
Thank you.
You are about to participate in a great adventure.
You are about to experience the awe and mystery which reaches from the inner mind to...
To the...
Subgenius Hour of Slack.
Welcome, potential initiates.
And remain with us for the next 30 minutes.
Yes, friends, it's so good to hear Reverend Bleepo Abernathy doing that show intro with his voice
because, friends, we're going to be listening to Reverend Bleepo Abernathy a whole lot tonight.
Yes.
Because, friends, I'm in a big hurry to get the artwork out for the Steve Jackson Games subgenius game.
Yes, we're doing one.
It's a hundred cards of sort of a...
Not exactly a role...
I guess you'd call it a role-playing game.
It's part of Steve Jackson's popular and famous...
Illuminati game.
It stands alone.
You can just play it with only the subgenius cards
or you can work them into the greater Illuminati conspiracy.
In this fantasy world that Steve Jackson has helped create,
the Illuminati sort of controls the church of the subgenius
rather than the way it is in real life, the other way around.
So, friends, the artwork...
It's going to be reduced down real tiny,
but it is so fine.
It is so fine.
The greatest artistes of subgeniusdom,
most of whom you've never heard of,
are all represented,
including yours truly.
And I'm on a deadline.
I'm building Dobbs Town right now inside my computer
and really have to get back to it
and spend as little time on this show as possible.
And luckily, dear friends,
there was a...
There was a...
There was a wonderful subgenius live radio show
produced at Starwood this year in New York.
I wasn't there because I had to be here.
But Reverend Bleepo Abernathy and the Lord Jesus
and Lonesome Cowboy Dave and Chaz Smith,
Einstein's secret orchestra,
were all together and Regis recorded it
with his mobile sound truck so well.
And Ace drew such a wonderful crowd of weirdos.
This is at the same place that the X-Day drills are held at
in Sherman, New York, Brushwood Campout.
Only this was like a pagan event with a thousand people there.
And I'm glad I wasn't there this time
because Einstein's secret orchestra
and Reverend Bleepo did such a great job.
And Jesus and his...
Oh, by the way, I should mention that
during this entire DeVival recording,
there's a naked, a beautiful, young, naked woman
dancing professionally,
particularly when Bleepo starts talking about sex hurt.
That's Mary Magdalene, Jesus' new consort,
I guess you'd say.
She was all body painted up,
and it was beautiful anyway.
All right, friends,
let's go to that DeVival recording in progress.
Ah, yes.
Praise God.
I'm scared.
You're too reckless.
Slow down.
Bleepo Abernathy calling Bleepo Abernathy.
You don't know what you're doing.
We got to wait for Reverend Bleepo Abernathy.
He's a big star, so...
Does it too?
No, you don't.
Why did you do that?
Oh, hi, officer.
All right.
Praise Bob.
Welcome, welcome, welcome.
Subgenius Club Swank.
Kick back, relax, and feel the beautiful vibes of hate.
We've got a lot of great things for you tonight.
As always, we are recording live, an hour of slack.
Unfortunately, Reverend Ivan Stank is not here with us tonight.
But we have Reverend Bleepo Abernathy, the great,
who will be explaining to you many things
and telling you amongst other things why Reverend Stank couldn't make it tonight.
We have some holy sacrament.
We have go-go dancers.
And we have slack.
We're waiting for our notes right now, so they'll be here any minute.
Oh, who am I?
I'm Jesus.
Christ.
Hi.
Thank you.
I'm back.
Somebody asked me, one of my kids, amongst other things, amongst being the Savior,
I do the team programming here.
And they said, well, you know, if you're Jesus, why are you here?
This is like the absolutely worst place you could be.
And I'm like, no, no, no.
See, I must be amongst the sinners.
That's the way it's always been.
So.
Well.
Cut to the chase.
I'm not going to tell you all about the Church of the Subgenius
because Reverend Bleepo Abernathy is going to be getting into all that.
But the advantage of listening to heart sounds and blunders
is that of using words to describe them.
Yes.
It's somewhat like eating an apple and trying to describe how it tastes.
Recordings lend themselves well to repetition.
And it is on this basis that one can train himself
to more accurately distinguish different abnormalities.
Much of the difficulty arises,
from hearing too many things at once.
And it is suggested that you practice listening for just one thing at a time.
So I'd like just to clear up one quick thing.
And that is, people believe that the Church of the Subgenius is a church of hate.
A lot of people believe that.
And that's not true.
I'm here to tell you, we are a church of love.
We just happen to love to hate.
We love to hate the conspiracy.
We love to hate the pigs.
We love to hate the normals.
So with that in mind, I'm going to now introduce you to a God amongst men,
and one of our greatest preachers of all time,
who's going to be giving you a nice introduction on the Church of the Subgenius,
the kind of Subgenius 101.
So ladies and gentlemen, please welcome,
Reverend Blipo Abernathy, with Reverend Blipo Abernathy's Neighborhood.
Thank you.
.
Hello, how are you today?
Can you say, slap?
.
Very good, you're so responsive.
I like that.
Did you know that you're very special here at Starwood?
.
Who here has never heard of the Church of the Subgenius?
Anyone here never hear of it before?
.
Alright, who here is this their first subgenius type of introduction to anything subgenius?
Do I see any?
I see, yes, there's a few in the back there.
Well, just to give you the simple, basic explanation of what the Church of the Subgenius is.
The Church of the Subgenius was started in 1953 by Bob.
.
Now, Bob's full name, of course, is J.R. Bob Dobbs.
And he was an ordinary vacuum cleaner salesman who went door to door helping people pick out the right vacuum cleaner.
Helping to guide them to the sort of appliances that could help benefit their lives.
He saw himself as a humanitarian.
Even then, even though he knew he was making money off these people, he saw it as an ethical thing.
.
Can you down the music just a little bit? It's just a little loud for me.
The music is a little softer.
.
It's hard to concentrate.
Would you like two more thingies? That's good. Thank you.
Anyway, so what happened to Bob was he was, he had what I guess what is referred to now as a close encounter with people from the Planet X.
.
And as you may or may not know, the people from the Planet X are the people who are going to come and enslave the normals on July 5th, 1998.
When their pleasure ships will come down and zap everybody who wasn't, you know, a fully fledged member of the Church of the Subgenius.
.
And when that happens, the Subgeniuses will rise in the pleasure ships. They will be taken into the pleasure ships.
And they will have all the candy and sex and everything that they could possibly desire that they could ever need forever.
.
And it'll be a wonderful thing. They will have eternal slack.
But Bob was just an ordinary man like you or me.
.
I'm trying to tell the story though. I sort of should flash back here. Basically Bob was also a model. You may recognize Bob's face. He was, of course, a male model between the 1930s and the 1930s. .
And he was the handsome smiling dad with the pipe who would, you know, come up and say hello to Junior and hello to Sister and sit down and, you know, smoke the pipe while they were watching TV.
.
And it was a wonderful, normal thing. And he did that too as well as selling the vacuum cleaners and stuff.
Once he got immunized, immunitized by the echelons from Planet X, he became illuminated and he could no longer be photographed by ordinary means.
.
So they had to issue drawings of him for his modeling assignments.
The only way you can take a picture of Bob now is through Curlie and Photography.
.
because the entire zeitgeist of the Church of the Subgenius is slack.
And slack is what you all have here at Starwood.
That's what helps make you special.
And I think it's important to remember the specialness of Bob
and the specialness of you.
And if anyone has any more beginner questions
about the Church of the Subgenius,
I'll be pleased to answer them after today's program.
But as it is right now,
it's time for us to invoke something
that we've been trying to invoke for a while now,
and that is Club Swank.
If you'll excuse me just one moment
while our DJ puts on the appropriate Club Swank music
will effect this transformation.
Please stand by.
Hey, what's happening everybody?
Hey, Swanky Cats.
And people all around the place,
welcome to Club Swank.
Yes, this is your Starwood event, Club Swank,
where everything is swanky
and you're always a member as long as you pay your dues.
Hey.
But you know, Bob isn't just about paying your dues.
Bob is about having you pay the dues of the people
who don't pay their dues.
Because there's a lot of people out there
who haven't been giving their money to the church, you know.
And because of that,
unfortunately, it's just,
this is, we are in the final year,
as you know,
because July 5th, 1998 is coming up.
We have less than 300,
what is it?
I don't even know what it is, Jesus.
It's only a few more months, really,
until it's the end of the world.
So basically now is the time
when the most money has to flow into the church.
This is the final year.
This is the final moment.
So please buy our church membership cards and pamphlets, etc.
Jesus has all of them.
He has all of these wonderful things, the pamphlets, etc.
And please support your church at the sub-G's
because after all, we are the only church
that admits that we're in it for the money, basically.
That's why Stang's not here, as a matter of fact.
Stang was not offered enough money to come here.
And so he left basically Jesus and me holding the bag.
And we're going to use this, Jesus and I,
and wherever he went there,
Mr. Musician there,
we're going to have a musician,
Segway up here eventually, I think.
Anyway, I forget his name.
Einstein's Secret Orchestra guy.
Hey, Einstein's Secret Orchestra guy, what's your name?
Chaz Smith.
Right, Chaz Smith is going to give us a hand here in a minute or two.
But anyway, what we wish to invoke here today,
many of you may be familiar with the Reverend Ivan Stang.
Reverend Ivan Stang has been to several Starwoods in the past.
And he's an interesting fellow.
He's kind of gone from short hair to long hair, back and forth.
There's times when you'll meet Reverend Ivan Stang,
and you'll think he's the most ordinary guy in the world.
He's Joe Average.
He's Mr. Regular.
There's other times you'll meet him and he'll have long hair,
and you'll think, wow, what a freaked out geek acid head this is.
And, but he's been, you know,
fronting this church of the subgenius for many, many years.
And he's quite successful at it.
In fact, it's made him millions and millions of dollars.
So that's why he doesn't feel it necessary to come around here.
And he sends his lackeys like Jesus in his stead.
I myself come from New York City and don't live in Dallas, Texas,
as does Jesus with the Reverend Ivan Stang.
But this is the moment in which I'd like you people who are in touch
with your knowledge of Reverend Stang and the fact that he does this
X-Day thing here that's separate from Starwood, you know,
even though his whole introduction to Brushwood was through Starwood.
He's basically, let's face it, folks,
Reverend Ivan Stang has left us, his flock, in the dust.
He doesn't give a shit about us.
Let's face it.
I'm sorry.
I know you're going to have to believe that, Stang, when you play the show.
But I want to try to invoke some hate here.
Because in the church of the subgenius, we've learned to take our hate and channel it.
You see, a lot of people around here in this New Age kind of thing, in fact, I like to
rhyme those two words the way my friend Penn Jillette of Penn & Teller often does.
He calls it New Age.
He calls it sewage, see.
In this New Age, we're going to be talking about the New Age.
And this is kind of New Age philosophy that you hear a lot of.
But there's a lot of talk of peace and love and never ever having angry feelings.
And anger is bad and all that sort of thing.
So right now, I'd say that Jesus and I are beginning, you know, we've been feeling certain
first, I had to explain that when we first came here, Jesus and I felt this sort of like,
oh, gee, Stang's not going to be here.
We felt this sort of sadness.
And then the sadness sort of segued into regret.
Gee.
You know, the show really would be better if Reverend Stang was here.
And the regret kind of segued, as it were, into sort of an annoyance, I would say, with
Reverend Stang and his whole sort of uptight, hey, you've got to pay me lots of money attitude.
Because, of course, Jesus and I are doing this for free.
As is Reverend Mary Magdalene as well.
And, you know, it started, we were sitting over a cup of coffee this morning, and it
segued, really, we decided, you know, I'm going to do this.
And, you know, we hated it.
We hated Ivan Stang.
So, and so what we want to do now is we want, Stang is playing this right now on the air,
even though it's on tape, he's playing this on the air on his Dallas radio show that's
syndicated all over the universe.
So, Stang, we want you to know that everybody here really resents your uptight, hypocritical
attitude.
And even though we love you.
We love you.
Thank you.
We hate you too.
Praise Bob.
I hear you.
I hear you, man.
Okay, we're going to spell it out here.
Give me an I.
I.
Give me an H.
H.
Give me an A.
A.
Give me a T.
T.
Give me an E.
E.
Give me an S.
S.
Give me a T.
Give me an A.
Bleepo knew perfectly well that this was just the way to get my goat.
What's the spell, everybody?
I.
Okay, stake.
Is that good enough for you?
What are you.
Yes.
Let's hope so.
Very good.
Thank you.
Thank you ever, ever so much.
Sarcastic bastard.
You know, the whole theme of the church, the church is about a theme and the theme
was written down on my piece of paper which I had ... Where is that piece of paper?
I can't even remember the theme of the church.
God, it's Bob, man.
Anyway, as I was coming here to Starwood this time, I found myself sort of meditating
meditating on the lack of slack and how hard it is in today's world to be a subgenius.
No matter where you go, subgeniuses are subject to all sorts of oppressive activities and repressive, you know.
In other words, if you're a subgenius and you're in a job, you probably hate your boss.
Because you were one of those people in the back of the classroom saying, you know, ha ha ha, giggling at the teacher.
And then the teacher would say to you, hey, young man or woman, what's so funny?
Anyway, would you care to share it with the class? Wipe that smile off your face.
If that happened to you, you know that you are indeed a subgenius.
And the thing that's happened to me over the years, I used to have a big conspiracy radio job with a huge conspiracy radio corporation.
It's now run by, it's run by the guy, it was run by the guy who now runs like the entire CBS television network actually.
He used to run the radio network I worked for.
And they slowly started to sell it.
And they started to suck the soul out of me, even though I didn't realize that.
And over the years, I worked for them for like 20 years, over the years they actually sucked my soul out of my body.
At least partly. They didn't get the whole thing.
But it wasn't until I was able to get out of that job, and they actually corporately downsized me, that I realized, you know, just how evil the entire corporate communication system is.
And I could not help but to feel this hate, even as I sought other jobs.
So I was hired by another huge corporation, known by Disney, I can't tell you what the broadcasting arm of that is called at this time.
But they hired me for exactly three weeks to work at their radio station with Rush Limbaugh and those people.
And they just couldn't take it. They couldn't take a subgenius working there.
Because no matter what I did, my hatred of Rush Limbaugh would always show up, even though I never ever expressed this to them.
It would come out in little subtle ways, like during the Marines commercials.
I had to like dub the Marine Corps commercials onto the little cards.
And during them, I would like turn the volume on my mic up just a teeny weeny bit, and I'd say,
They're lying. Don't believe them.
You know, way, way, way in the background.
Mixed down so hard that you could never even tell it was there.
And somehow, this didn't meet with their approval.
These uptight cats.
So they got rid of me, and then the Mormons hired me, and I worked for the Mormons for about three weeks.
Also, and the Mormons own a radio station in New York City called 105.1 FM, The Buzz.
If anybody knows what that is.
It's a big commercial station.
No one knows it's owned by the Mormons.
It used to be Mix 105.
And they told me that they wanted me to create promotional announcements for them, jingles and so forth.
But they wanted attitude without swagger.
And they wanted irreverence without insult.
Now, my friends, you can't have irreverence without insulting somebody.
And you can't have attitude without wiggling your butt just a little bit.
Okay? There's just no way around it.
So, no matter what I did, I was like,
I'm gonna do my job, I'm gonna do my job, I'm gonna do my job.
And then my subgenious self kept on showing through until around Christmas time,
I was making a Christmas promotional announcement,
and it was supposed to be a Santa Claus announcement.
There would be, you know, more six-song-in-a-row sets of six wrong songs in a row right after this commercial message.
So I said, so I had Santa Claus say,
Ho ho ho, keep your pants on!
There's another six-in-a-row coming up right after this!
And at this point in time, the program director still trusted me to just make these little tapes,
and give them to the DJs, and the DJs just threw them on the air.
Of course, this one ran around December 22nd.
And he called me up and he was like,
What? How can Santa Claus say, Keep your pants on?
You can't have Santa Claus saying, Keep your pants on.
That's suggestive.
So, can't him say, Keep your shirt on?
Of course, if Santa Claus is saying, Keep your shirt on,
that has no attitude whatsoever.
So, I realized something.
The main reason why I was working there
was to work with the incredible, fantastic equipment there
and do all my little subgenius radio things on the side.
And that's really what I was trying to do.
I was trying to get something for free
by working for the conspiracy.
And friends, you can't do that.
It does not work.
As, uh, where did he go?
Well, this morning, I basically came up with
what we call the paradox of procurement.
And this is something that all subgeniuses must remember, okay?
And follow this paradox carefully, folks.
If you can't buy it,
repeat after me, please.
get it for free.
If you can't get it for free,
borrow it.
If you can't borrow it,
steal it.
And if you can't steal it,
buy it.
So, in other words, if you can't buy it, get it for free.
If you can't get it for free, borrow it.
If you can't buy it,
get it for free.
steal it, and if you can't steal it, buy it. That's the paradox of procurement. Whatever
it is you're looking for, your answer will be found there. Okay, now, folks, I've been
kind of dissing Ivan Stang now, and I realize that really we haven't officially, this whole
thing has just sort of been an introductory pre-ramble to the actual event itself, be
honest to myself or anyone else. And so at this moment, please, I'd like to cut all the
background noise. Could I please cut the instruments just one second, please? Can we cut the background
music just for a moment here? We'll bring it up in a second here. And Stang, I just
want to say, this is for you. I would like all of you subgeniuses now to bow your heads,
clear your mind, and I want us all just to enjoy a moment of sacred.
No!
Yes! Yes! Praise Bob! This is a revival, a devival! This is a club swank! This is a club
where you women can have as many orgasms as you want, and you men can have all the squirts
you want, and we can just get all the stuff we want! And- and- and- and- and- so there!
So there, conspiracy!
Here we are! Yeah!
Okay, so, uh...
Okay, so, uh, did we, uh...
Did we do it? Yeah.
Okay, at this point, at this point in time,
how many of you people would call yourselves
faithful subgeniuses?
Uh, okay, all right.
How many of you trust us?
Well, how many of you are foolish enough
to just let go of that distrust
and try something really wacky anyway?
I mean, this has happened before historically.
You know, a lot of people, when the media sees us
hanging around and trying to be our bachelor pad
kind of selves, our kind of subgenius star
with pagan selves, bachelor or bachelorette,
you know, I'm sort of trying to invoke
an early 60s kind of cocktail kind of mode here.
Well, how many of you,
uh, folks out there, uh,
enjoy a cocktail once in a while?
And how many of you enjoy cocktails
that are unnatural colors?
Okay.
Well, you know, when the media sees us
and they might portray us,
it's like CBS TV were to come here and look at us.
They would say, oh, it's one of those coats.
What?
I mean, after all, we got the symbol
blinking over our faces.
We got the symbol blinking over the hot tub
with a little star twirling around.
So if we sort of close our eyes
while we're lying back in the hot tub,
we get indoctrinated with the thought of the star.
You know, no matter where we go,
we see that little star, right?
So this cult here, the cult of the subgenius,
is the only cult that is fanatically opposed
to fanaticism.
So as you see here, our very own dear, sweet Jesus
and the incredibly beautiful and provocative
Mary Magdalene
are pouring out our electric blue subgenius
Kool-Aid cocktail.
Drink it.
So if you, if you dare, try it again.
It won't hurt you.
Drink.
You'll probably find yourself with
most of your mind in the morning.
Probably.
We can't guarantee it.
We hope you're drinking it of your own
energy.
You know, delicious.
But rest assured, there's nothing in there
that would harm normalcy.
Okay?
So if you dare, you know, accept the sacrament of Bob.
And in Bob's name, it has to be.
I dig that swinging, swinging sound.
Smoothie.
Yeah.
Oh, it's in Bob's name, brother.
So you can't drink it all at once.
All right.
Do we have more to go around or?
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
So we're going to take our time and pass this out.
Now, I was wondering if anybody out here
has been hurt recently by the conspiracy.
Anybody out here been hurt recently by the conspiracy?
Can I see some hands?
Who here has been hurt recently by the conspiracy?
All right.
In.
In 25 words or less, I'd like to invite you one at a time
to come up here and testify how the conspiracy has recently
hurt you.
Any of you who want to come up and just give us
a little testifying.
I just want to hear a personal life experience.
Any of you who have been hurt by the conspiracy recently?
Please.
Come on.
Somebody.
Somebody come on up.
Tell us.
What has the conspiracy done for you or against you?
I work for the federal government.
Oh.
Oh, my God.
We're the weirdest weirdos in the whole federal government.
And they just put us on charge during reengineering.
So.
Business process reengineering.
They took the weirdest and the most free-mindest people,
and they put us in charge.
Think about it.
I sit on the board of directors at the hospital now.
Oh.
That's intense.
There's an example right there.
That just shows you how important it
is to get in touch with your original slack.
Because the conspiracy has been trying
to take your slack away from you ever since the day you're born.
They tell you when you're in fourth grade, they say, hey,
wipe that smile off your face.
What's so damn funny anyway?
And then they say, oh, no, we're going
to track you because of your academic record, because
of the certain knowledge.
Because of the numbers.
Because of the things you decided to pay attention to.
The things that they care about more than you,
they're going to judge you.
And it will all go down in your permanent record
and following around for years.
This takes away your slack.
When you go to a job and they say, oh, yeah, sit at this desk,
but please don't think creatively.
And please, pay no attention to that boss
who's sexually harassing you.
Pay no attention to that.
Pay no attention.
Pay no attention to that guy next to you
who's the other boss's nephew who's
making $40,000 a year more than you do
and does 10 times less while you cover his pathetic ass.
It's so true.
Well, Bob will help us get in touch with our slack.
If you give your money to Jesus right now,
or later, or send a dollar, just send a dollar to P.O. Box 140306,
Dallas, Texas 75214, then you will receive some of that slack.
Of course, if you get a full membership,
you'll get even more of that original slack back
until you'll find the subgenius church will give you the ability
to do whatever you want.
Wow.
And you can do anything you like.
Yes.
Yes, Jesus.
I'm ready to make the toast.
I already drank some of this.
Don't drink it yet.
We're going to do it together.
I think we passed out about 300 cups, so this should look pretty good on nightly news tonight.
If you're not sitting down, sit down when you drink this.
Yes, please make sure you're seated.
We don't want you to fall down on top of anybody.
If you have small children, I know there's a small child there,
you might want to just force it down his throat.
Okay.
Fuck them if they can't take a joke.
Down that Jesus.
All right.
Praise Bob.
And he's still standing.
Now, that shows you how powerful the church of the subgenius is
because if he were a normal, that would have just killed him.
Anyone?
Everyone's still standing.
I think it's amazing.
It's a miracle.
Praise Bob.
I think there is sugar in that, right?
Oh, yeah.
Yes.
Cyanide.
Thank you.
All that good stuff.
I did have a visual aid for you tonight.
She's passing out juice still, though.
Tell Mary Magdalene to come up here real quick.
Come here.
I hear the mystery.
The visual aid.
I know a lot of you are familiar with the church of the subgenius and our doctrines,
and Reverend Blebo did a great, great job of filling us in.
But here's something that I want you to remember.
So I figured this would be the best way for everyone to remember it.
Oh, T-shirts is one thing.
T-shirts only $12.
Don't forget that.
Come here.
So here's my...
Turn around.
July 5th, 1998, 7 a.m.
Stare at it.
It grated in your face.
It's a great day.
I believe that the Lord was displaying this phrase written on the side of his girlfriend.
The naked Mary Magdalene body painted up.
Oh, yes.
All right.
Thank you very much, our lovely assistant.
Now, Jesus is here tonight also to give us his healing power.
The Bhagwan.
The other Bhagwan.
He helped heal you tonight with the power of hate because I am a Christian.
I am a Christian.
I believe a lot of you have been sickened by the conspiracy.
Yeah.
I would like everybody once again who said before they had been hurt by the conspiracy
lately.
No kidding.
Raise their hands once again.
I'm with you, man.
Okay.
Come.
Form a line, please.
Form a line.
Get in line.
Come all up here, please.
I'm a waiter.
Here it goes.
Here it works.
Praise Bob.
He's been sickened, friends.
He's been sickened.
He's been sickened at.
I'm a man who can handle conspiracy and all the people work.
The conspiracy wants me to pay the cost.
Wait a minute.
He's been sickened.
Friends.
What?
Hallelujah.
Look at that.
Look at that, friends.
How could we lie to you?
Are you employed?
Yes.
I free you of your job.
Oh, thank Jesus.
It's a miracle.
What's wrong with you, brother?
I work at McDonald's.
Oh, God.
My God.
Good Lord.
Sicken this man.
Oh, my God.
for the feeling of Bob.
Do you reject the conspiracy at all?
Do you reject the conspiracy?
Oh, praise Bob.
Yes, it works.
The power works, friends.
And you, friend, come up.
Come up, please.
Don't be scared, children.
I have friends in jail for marijuana.
Oh, the worst of all problems.
Okay, well,
do you believe in Bob?
I believe in Bob.
Praise Bob.
Oh, it just warms the cockles of my heart.
Miracles.
Friend, step up, little friend.
If there's anyone who doesn't have any problems,
come on up.
We'll give you some problems.
Please.
Ask my ex-wife.
I'm not allowed to drink on the job.
Oh, my God.
Oh.
I just want you people to know something.
All right?
I don't abuse drugs.
Wait, just one moment, Jesus.
Okay, you can keep healing.
Keep healing.
I don't abuse drugs.
I'm a sober individual.
However, I managed to get myself a job
with High Times Magazine.
Anybody know High Times Magazine?
All right.
It was because I held on to my slack
and I didn't let go that I finally got this dream job
of my life by doing this radio show
for the High Times Magazine.
It's the people who have all the great weed on their cover
and all the fun and stuff
and the really weird music and stuff.
And just so you know,
come on up, children.
Come on up, children.
Bob, this is the power that Bob will give you.
I now...
He just said that the other fellow said
that he wasn't allowed to drink on the job.
I am forced to smoke the best pot in the world
in my job.
That's what Bob forced me to do.
I'm going to help you, brother.
Whether I like it or not,
I'm going to help you.
He's kicked out.
He's kicked out of his apartment.
Oh, my God.
Did you pay your landlord?
Your landlady?
Your landlady did what?
Kicked me out.
I'll free you of all your rent.
All right.
Come on, come on up, children.
Come on up.
I have more slack in my life
than should be allowed by law.
Hate Bob, then.
Yes!
Bob!
We can give you...
We can give you the hate,
and we can give you the love.
All right.
Jesus, are you all right?
Good, see?
It's okay.
It's because of Bob.
It's because of Bob, friend.
Come on up, children.
Yes, sir.
Can I help you with...
Oh, my job robs me of my slack.
You reject the conspiracy,
and all the people work.
Oh, hallelujah, friends!
Come on up here, Mary Magdalene.
Come over here.
Come on.
Be by your husband's side.
For we all know
that the secret doctrines of Jesus
are that he and Mary Magdalene
knew each other.
And indeed they do, friend.
I have to do the fucking budget
for the VA medical center,
and it's driving me insane!
Praise Bob!
Oh!
Look at that!
Hallelujah!
Come on up, children.
Come on up.
My father is an apostolic Pentecostal minister.
Oh!
Whoo!
Everyone's gonna have to help me with this one.
Everyone, hands in the air.
Hands in the air.
A lot of hands.
She's been sickened by the church, friend.
Hallelujah!
Great job, Bob!
Um, my mom works for the government
and my dad's a lawyer,
and I can't find any hallucinogenics.
I think I'm blowing out of my mind.
Oh!
Oh, hell!
But you have nice teeth.
Check out those teeth.
Ah, a true Yeti.
Praise fucking Bob!
Whoo!
Bob, we'll give you more slack
than you could ever dream of, friends!
Come on!
I'm the school chief, you know I'm responsible
for educating the youth of America.
Oh, my God.
She's a school teacher responsible for teaching the youth of America.
Yes! Yes!
What did you do to that one? I missed that.
Reject the conspiracy and all it's evil works.
We'll heal everyone here.
Okay, good. Just check. I just want to make sure this is fine.
Yeah, okay.
Yes, sir.
I thought this was the line for the floor flushers.
Thank you.
No problem. We can direct you anywhere you want to go.
You can go there.
From the Church of the Subgenius Friends, no matter where it is.
The woman I'm falling in love with has been trained me to be a psychoanalyst.
Faith and vigour. It worked.
Okay, everyone put your hands one more time in the air.
Anyone who needs healed, we're going to do a mass sickening.
Do you reject the conspiracy and all it's evil works?
Praise fucking God!
Hey!
But you know, friends, the Church of the Subgenius is more of a church than those Pentecostal sort of crazy wild Jimmy Swaggart, Faith and Vigour, Fire and Brimstone, Snake Oil healings.
The Church of the Subgenius is an intimate church.
The Church of the Subgenius, friends, is a church much like mist on a fog-shrouded marsh.
Gorillas in a nest.
Yeah, there's times when the Church of the Subgenius is a serene feather floating to the ground in a zen-like fashion.
And you can feel...
You can feel...
You can feel the funk of Bob.
And you can smell his psychic stench as the feather floats down and touches the ground with a loud boing.
But the thing is, this is Bob's way of showing you the subtlety of the sex hurt.
The sex hurt isn't always an obvious thing, friends.
No.
The sex hurt is...
Is the essence of doing something not because it hurts, but doing something so pleasurable,
so incredibly, ecstatically, maddeningly, joyously, beautifically, blissful, that it hurts, friends.
Yes, yes, you get to the point where you're experiencing so much pleasure.
You say,
Stop!
No, Bob!
No!
Bob, I've had enough!
Oh, God, you're the best!
You are the best!
But no, no, no, hold off for a moment.
No, no, Bob, no more.
Hold off, please.
Please, Bob, because too much of it is flowing in my direction.
Like that man said, he was having...
He was having too much.
And you tell Bob,
No, no, stop, Bob!
I came already.
You don't have to do it.
You don't have to massage the gland anymore, Bob.
Please.
After you're satisfied,
you kind of go,
Oh, come on.
Quit it.
It's like when you were wrestling with your big brother,
that kid in school,
and he'd like hold you down,
and he'd say,
Have you had enough?
And you'd say,
Yes.
And then he'd say,
Well, here's some more.
No other church,
no,
no other church
will offer you this kind of complete,
Money back, guaranteed satisfaction.
Yes, friends, if on X day, is this still true?
Is this offer still in effect?
Okay, yeah, pretty much.
I'm assured this offer is pretty much still in effect.
Okay, if it all goes down as Bob has predicted,
and when it all goes down as Bob has predicted,
and the people from Planet X come,
and you've paid, what is it, $40 now?
$30.
You've paid your $30 membership to the church of the subgenius,
PO Box 140306, Dallas, Texas 75214,
email address subgenius at AOL, no.
Yeah, Jesus, you can write to him at jesusatsubgenius.com, yeah.
Email address.
And also, Stang is also at stangatsubgenius.com.
Just, yeah.
If you got the, yeah.
Praise Stang.
Hate Stang.
Can I hear hate Stang?
Yeah.
All right, thank you.
Friends, where was I?
I completely spaced out.
Oh, yes, yes, yes, yes.
As you do this, you will see that it,
basically what happens is the luck plane from the day you're born,
the day you're born, the luck plane is at an even angle to you.
You are standing, you know, as an infant, you could stand.
You could stand.
You'd be basically standing at a 90-degree angle to the luck plane.
It would be stretching out before you as a promising vista of golden horizons.
As the conspiracy works against you all throughout your life,
the luck plane, for most normals, tends to tip further and further away from you
so that the luck actually starts to flow out of you
and down the luck plane to other people at the other end of it.
It flows basically into the subgeniuses.
And, uh...
What the wonderful thing is about the church and subgeniuses,
you learn how to be on the...
Either one of two things happens to you when you join the church.
Either the luck plane tilts up towards you
and starts pouring the luck in your direction,
or they give you the instructions, they give you like a map
how to walk to that part of the luck plane that's tilted down
so that it flows onto you.
Either way, you get it.
Yeah, yeah.
But, no, we admit we're in it for the money, sir.
All right.
Are you accusing us...
...of being a rip-off?
We wouldn't lie to you, friend.
We guarantee you.
Yes.
Oh, yes.
So what I was saying is the guarantee.
That's where I was.
The guarantee.
If on July 5th, 1998, X Day comes,
when it comes, of course,
if you, a dues-paying subgenius member,
are not taken up into the pleasure ships
and are instead just wiped out by the exes from Planet X,
like you'd kill a dog that's been injured on the side of a road,
if that happens to you, you will get your $30 back.
We guarantee...
Because Bob has sold the rights.
Bob has sold the rights to the human race to the exes.
And the only way to get your share of it back
is to give him your money, just so you know.
But, yeah.
Back to the sex.
Back to the...
Bob is a mighty sex god.
That's why I love him.
He's given me, if not a bigger...
You know...
Yeah.
If not that, then at least the illusion that I have that.
And isn't that what counts, friends?
I mean, let's face it.
The conspiracy's always telling you bigger is better.
And Bob isn't gonna necessarily just make you happier with what you got.
He'll make you so convinced
that you have more than you can afford.
More than you already do.
That you'll believe it.
And it won't matter.
That's the miracle of Bob.
That's one of the many miracles of Bob.
And so, with this thought in mind,
I know there are many people, animals,
inanimate objects and stuff,
at this event that sort of hook up with each other.
There's sort of a...
All those drums going on all the time
kind of causes a love vibe.
And...
And as is happening,
you know, people get together.
And of course, only safe sex occurs.
Right, friends?
And...
And what happens is, you know,
we may be polyamorous and stuff,
and we're all like,
hey, everybody can do whatever they want or whatever.
But people kind of tend to couple up.
And also inanimate objects.
People with inanimate objects,
people and animals, whatever.
So if you find friends
that during this event
or even just during this ceremony,
there's somebody that you feel close to
that you feel it would be beneficial
to the two of you
to be married
under the auspices of the church.
A short-duration marriage.
These are short-duration, 24-hour marriages
that we perform here.
That's true.
And today...
We at the church...
Yeah, we at the church feel...
Is this on?
All right.
Yeah, we at the church do perform
short-duration personal marriages.
They last for...
Tonight we'll be doing them for 24 hours.
They could last for an hour, a year.
Yeah.
It doesn't...
It goes away with the messy divorces.
They just...
They end.
You know, because it is a hectic pace.
We also have short-duration personal saviors.
Right, right.
Such as Bob himself.
We're going to perform this...
We're going to perform this marriage...
Yeah, a mass marriage ceremony.
Beautiful mass marriage ceremony.
So what we'd like to do
is we'd like all of you couples,
any, you know, men and women, please.
Men and men.
We can't marry you to your wallet.
Women and dogs.
We can't marry you to yourself.
Men and women.
Farm animals.
We can't marry you to
really much anything
that you want to be married to.
Rabbits and fish.
Frogs and leopards.
Whatever.
Come on.
What?
Let's...
Oh, anyone.
Anyone.
Come on up.
Come on, friends.
Oh, there has to be someone
who's filled with love.
If you want to declare your love for each other...
Come forward.
...through your love for Bob.
All right.
That's it, friends.
It's as meaningful or meaningless
as you want it to be.
It's a...
It means exactly what you want to mean.
This will allow you to consummate the marriage
completely legally.
Oh, praise Bob.
He's going to do it again, folks.
This is going to work, friends.
It's guaranteed to work.
And this is something we're giving you today
for free.
Neither Jesus or I
or any of the people here right now
are being paid
for this promotional announcement.
These six people are going to marry each other.
He's going to marry his master.
Yes.
You are marrying your wallet.
Marry your entire wallet.
Praise Bob.
This family of four...
This is a...
This is a subgenius family.
Right here.
Three...
One man and three women.
Oh.
It's so...
It's beautiful.
I love this.
Come forward.
You can just stand up in your seats
where you are
if you'd like to take place in a marriage.
Do you know...
Raise your person in marriage?
I don't know.
Do you?
No.
Oh, gosh.
All right.
We're not doing the authentic marriage.
We're doing the version, folks, tonight.
We're not doing the Stang-approved version.
But we're doing...
We're going to have to wing it.
We're going to make it up.
This is the Dobbs trance-induced version
of the short-duration marriage right now
as improvised by myself
and Jesus and Mary Magdalene.
Dearly beloved...
So repeat after...
Yes, repeat after Jesus, please.
Well, actually, repeat after Jesus.
Dearly beloved, we gather here today
to unite these people, things, objects, and each other
in united...
United...
In holy matrimony.
Do...
Now you can repeat after me.
Do you...
Person A...
B and C...
B and C.
Take person and object and or wallet
D, E, F, and G...
And or any others not mentioned in the above list
to have and to hold until time that you grow tired of each other...
And or sometime later or before that moment...
For at least a 24-hour period...
With or without any further stipulations
that may or may not be mentioned at this time.
In the name of J.R. Bob Dobbs and...
Either legally or illegally...
Fill in the blank.
And fill in the blank.
Say, I do.
I do.
Shake on it and say, it's a deal.
It's a deal.
I now pronounce you man and wife and wallets and...
And everything. Praise Bob.
Yes.
Thank you.
It worked.
Look at that, Jesus.
It's a miracle.
Friends, I've seen so many miracles here today.
You may now kiss each other.
Oh, this is exhausting.
I can't believe...
We have one...
We have another ceremony.
The last ceremony.
We...
Uh, Bleepo had said earlier today,
you can't always believe what a subgenius preacher tells you.
Uh...
Oh.
Oh, wow.
Yes.
Whoo!
I didn't know it was going to happen that quickly.
All right.
True love.
Uh, Stan is really not a millionaire,
although we are trying very hard to become millionaires,
because we believe at the Church of the Subgenius
that to destroy the concept of money,
it's going to take a lot of money.
A lot of money.
Exactly.
This is why...
So once again, friends, if you can't buy it, get it for free.
If you can't get it for free, borrow it.
If you can't borrow it, steal it.
If you can't steal it, buy it.
Yes.
I have in my hand an authentic American one-dollar bill,
which somebody gave me, thank you very much,
and in one of our greatest subgenius ceremonies...
It's a windproof...
As the smoke from this dollar bill rises up above...
This is a windproof cheap...
This is made by one of the last free objects made in free British Hong Kong.
This cheap ripoff that actually works very well of a windproof lighter.
Oh.
This cheap, along with cheap and cheap EKn's can be drunk...
It would be cheap to sell...
...and eventually to have a stamp home and,
Unlike the west side of the vendetta,
which just, actually,breached the sampling rules of anych...
bleibt...
It is that kind of bomb blasted here.
You know, folks...
Obvious ests bien estuviendo aqu y tengiendo...
Dicha bomb stripspathe de Sleeping
look at her friends.
yes friends
and now
as a final final act
of tonight's
subgenius
club swank extravaganza
I would like to offer
to destroy time
yes friends
any of you
who has a watch
that you would like us to smash
and not be able to restore
that you would be entirely responsible for
when you wake up the next morning and say
holy my god
that man smashed my watch
and you won't kill me or Jesus
even if you want to
any of you people that has a watch
that you would want to smash
have smashed
by me and Jesus
under these circumstances
with all of these disclaimers
he's got the brick
now remember
the church of the subgenius
will give you control over time
but only if you let us
smash
and destroy
there's got to be one of you
take off the shackles of the conspiracy
take off satan's handcuff
bring it up here son
bring it up here
yeah okay you want to do it yourself
alright I'm going to take it out in front
wow that's a nice watch
are you sure
praise fucking bob
take off the shackles of the conspiracy
this watch will be
healed only on the astral plane
and only
in the subgenius dream time
which is the only real time
there is friends
this time is an illusion
the time of bob is the true stone
it's the stalwart stone
that will free us
yes friends
kill it
kill the
yes
kill the watch
kill the time
praise bob
oh hallelujah
kill off the shackles of the conspiracy
oh
what
woo
friends friends
I want to thank you all for coming to club swank tonight
we need to thank the great
the great loathsome cowboy
day
woo
and the mites
and the mitestine secret orchestra
who will be playing tonight
right in the puffer dome
chaz smith
woo
and they'll be playing here at 9 30 as well
our great dj
craig
also serves us food here at starwood
in the back at the holy sales table
pastor craig
pastor craig who helped me come up with the paradox of uh
who brought the kool aid
of uh
procurement
let us not forget the beautiful
mary magdalene
without without whom none of this would have been possible
and jesus praise jesus without whom none of this or that would be possible
and the great the one the only the king of swank
lippo abernathy
no no please
the sales table will be open for the rest of uh about ten minutes
this will be the only time to get your subvenus goods
praise the lord
bless you
we're signing off
thank you so much