Praise God.
Oh yes, dear friends.
This is Li Li Jing, a Chinese subgenius.
And you are listening to the Hour of Flag on KNON in Dallas, Texas.
Praise God!
Somebody help!
Somebody help me!
Please!
Please help me!
Help!
Where are we, Wang?
You are nowhere.
You just stop rubbing your body up against mine because I can't concentrate when you do that.
I don't want to be hated.
Just a minute!
Well, the wolf was a man.
There once was a man.
Well, it's great to say he was mad.
I say it, he was mad.
And he had ten thousand fans.
And he had ten thousand fans. I'm not looking mad.
I'm not looking mad.
He Colombia перед ciudad, he teche yникинfishunk Pomimiin drink us up.
It's anesser a se points.
This is Li Li Jing, someone from Le Indigo Pacificaf Sheila raporter.
Who knew he was theığın, you saw it just cats and dogs.
factorial.
No, born, but knew that the cat likes dogs in Toolbox 시청a H FREE arms.
Youoner scarves the actual enriching coat maine.
You have a nice coat, so let me check it on.
I'm going to wear several sandals.
And I was one of the best in the country, Lear Doc.
There goes another shot.
Yes, he's hurt.
He's full of sweat.
All this love.
And it's coming again.
Oh, yeah, we're back on the air now, I guess.
But it's pledge drive.
I don't know what difference it makes, though, for most of y'all.
You don't care.
Shoot.
Well, I'll tell you, I have a story to tell.
This is Reverend Ivan Stang.
I'm talking to you tonight.
But this is, I mean, it's pledge drive.
It's supposed to be big whoop-dee-doo.
But, friends, I'm afraid to have to.
Oh, shut that music off.
I don't want to hear that stuff.
Oh, shoot.
Bob came to me.
The other day in a vision.
Yes.
Oh, you go ahead and laugh.
You out there.
You can laugh all you want.
But Bob, I'm Reverend Stang.
I'm the one of the first apostles, friends.
And I'll tell you what.
Bob Dobbs came to me and he said, Reverend Stang, I'm going to take you home.
I'm going to take you home.
If you don't raise $8,000.
By midnight.
The night of your show.
That's it.
I've had enough of this stuff.
I'm going to take you away.
You ain't going to.
Friends, you know what?
I mean, that.
Shoot.
I don't care.
I don't care what you say.
I'm ready to go with Bob.
Go off to heaven or hell or wherever.
Hell or fire.
I don't care what he wants.
You know?
You don't care.
I can tell.
Y'all don't care.
Because you ain't calling 828-9500.
You don't.
828-9500 or 823-7490.
But you ain't.
You don't got your pencils up.
You ain't writing those numbers down.
You think the hour of slack is going to be free forever.
Oh, yeah.
I'll be taken by Bob by midnight tonight if we don't raise that $8,000.
We didn't do so good last time.
Oh, you think.
Yeah.
You think.
You know everything, don't you?
Well, that's 828-9500, 823-7490.
You can talk to the Will of Dobbs.
You can talk to Reverend Zaphon.
You can talk to Reverend Shimon.
You can talk to the mighty Pope of Sicilia.
You can even talk to the nameless Harvey, the invisible one.
Now, you think I'm crazy, don't you?
Well, who's shoot?
Right in stewing and stabbing and jiving and jabbing.
Having a good time.
Petting and poking Bob.
Here, help me.
Somebody.
Okay, here we go.
The demons you may see during the initial hallucination sequence are not real.
If you do not panic, this phase will end after a few minutes.
Always resurface from the hypnosis slowly.
Coming out of the tape has been likened to a total rebirth process.
Yes.
Managed successfully.
He knows that a creative sale is one in which the idea that leads to a purchase
generates in the mind of the salesman before it does in the prospect's mind.
Right.
Sales, that's all it's about here, friends.
Sales.
The code is broken.
Trouble?
Big.
Oh, over here.
We've got the slackless children who've been cast out of the home for slackless children
because you didn't send in your donations to the station, friend.
Look at these poor little children.
What do you have to say to the people, children?
My truth is loose.
Like my sister's truth is.
I got an ant box.
Right.
A big old bug.
See, friends, these are truly slackless children.
And these kids, these ant bites and these little bumps and bruises.
Now, friend, you're not going to let these poor kids, these are American kids.
You're not going to sit by and let these kids be in pain and slacklessness, are you?
See, they all call me daddy.
Isn't that sweet?
These are only two of over 5,000.
5,000.
No.
Because we have this amazing electronic babysitter here, this handsome robot.
You can hear it talking.
He's going to make a million dollars.
That's right, friend.
He's going to make a million bucks.
Inside the brain cavity of Doug Smith.
My legs are on fire.
They smell pray sauce.
2-8-9-5-100 is the number to call if you want to save your soul, friends.
Not just this station, but your soul.
Your eternal soul.
So, open your heart.
Close your mind.
Unzip your lips and bend over to pull out that wallet, friends.
Because you're going to receive the word of Bob.
Because this is the last hour of the last pledge drive of the last hour of slack.
If you don't.
Call 828-9500 and make that pledge.
And dear friends, that some already have, even before we got on the air.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, that's easy.
That's just a tape.
See, I'm not feeling so hot about this stuff tonight.
No.
Because I know that I'm ready to meet my maker or whatever.
Whatever he is.
I don't even care.
Shoot.
Bob, he said he's going to take me away.
And I know I've said that before.
I've said that in that last pledge.
I said that in 1986.
Well, Bob, we raised that money that time.
I was sick.
But I'm a lot sicker this time, friends.
Yeah, I was sick last week.
And this time, I still ain't over it.
And it's getting worse and worse.
Worse.
Oh, yeah.
But I, you know.
Yeesh.
If you ain't going to call 823-7490, I'm going to die by midnight.
That's all there is to it.
Severe pharyngitis.
That's the thing.
It's sick.
I know.
I'm sick.
God, no.
I'm going to lay the truth down on you.
I'm going to strap it on.
I'm going to put it on with big red straps, dear friends.
I ain't going to spare you the truth.
That's right.
I'm going to preach on.
I'm going to tell.
I'm going to tell it like it is, as they say.
But you got to call and pledge that money.
And you know what?
You can't just.
I know you ain't going to do it.
You don't care.
Don't make any difference to you.
Oh, slack.
Big joke.
You ain't going to write that check to Box 710909.
You got that pencil out again.
You slow, full, unthinking, unfeeling.
You might as well be animals.
Most of it's box.
710909.
Dallas, Texas 75371.
Or call 8237-4900 or 828-9500.
But you don't care at all.
.
Daddy, what's going to happen if I don't get any money?
I can't tell you what's going to happen.
Mommy, what's wrong with Daddy?
What are we going to do without Daddy around?
Yeah, he seemed awful sick when he left for the station.
I think he's really worried about the money.
I don't believe that people listen to gain and win
and they don't give any money to it.
People really don't listen
without pain, do they?
They must be bad people.
Poor Daddy.
Give me some money, man.
Hey, mister, listen.
If you don't pay any money, I'm going to take it out of your pocket.
I'm going to walk up and take it like this.
So you better give it to me.
Me too.
I'm going to call the cops on you, man.
I'm going to call the police.
Maybe I'll call the rock and roll dogs.
I might call the pincher dogs.
I might call my friend Raymond.
He lives across the street.
He has a mohawk and a duck tail
and walks around with a knife in his pocket
because they're not paying any money.
I can see what's going on here now.
You're all waiting for the other guy to call in.
Yeah, that's what it is.
You're just waiting to see what will happen.
You want to see Reverend Stang die, don't you?
That's fine with me.
That's just all right.
Yeah, yeah.
That's just perfectly all right.
Well, we've had a few.
There's a few that care.
Alan Walker, yeah.
I've seen Alan.
I know what Alan Walker was doing.
I've seen him.
His car pulled up in front of Eileen Hobbs' place.
Yeah, yeah.
And look, what did he put in the offering plate?
25 cents, a quarter in the offering plate.
But...
But go ahead, blow it off.
Don't call 8237-490.
Don't call 828-9500.
Mandy Macademia.
Yeah, I've seen what Mandy Macademia's been up to.
Oh, a woman.
A woman, she says.
Yeah, I want to see some of these phone lines lighten up.
We got a bunch of mighty sexy preachers here ready to talk to you.
And they're bored.
They're bored.
They're about to go home.
We're all going to quit.
Oh, now quiet down now, y'all.
You're getting too noisy.
Hold it down.
I can hear you.
I know what's going on out there.
I'm going to preach on.
I'm going to...
I'm tired of this stuff.
I'm going to have to unload on you.
You think I don't know what's going on with y'all?
You think I don't know if Will Frazier's been up there to see Wanda?
I see everything.
I see every bit of it.
Oh, sure I know.
I know it.
Don't you?
She told me.
She came into the dang altar, back behind the altar.
Where have you been that you don't know this stuff?
You don't know no phone numbers.
You don't know about 828-95-183-7490.
Oh, sure.
Yeah, once or twice a year you'll come in and make your pledge.
Well, I'm sorry.
That don't cut no ice here.
Hell, fire.
I'm going to get down on some of these butts today.
It's part of our job, fortunately, being the Subgenius Foundation,
it is part of our job to scare people.
It's also part of our job to exercise slack and to serve as role models
of abnormal behavior for people who have not yet been freed from the restrictions.
I'm going to get this.
Don't get mixed up anymore, you act like a douche.
pallete s.
I like that educación.
Most of my people are based in Mexico City.
Yes, and you've moved to Los Angeles and you've lived there about a year before.
I'm a friend of yours so long.
We met a little while ago, we longer ninth and an eighth hours on earth.
No moral.
And if you joke around, you too.
I don't have any excuse. You're fake.
Friends, you better call in this time.
I mean, we aren't kidding.
We didn't do so well that last pledge drive.
It's going to be the last hour of slack if you don't get it together.
We're only talking about $10, $15.
Not everybody can give that much.
You know, Dr. Drummond and I once talked about, you know, who means the most to Bob?
Is it the little old lady who can, who, you know, doesn't have anything at all to her name,
but she donates a quarter, her last quarter?
Or is Bob more impressed with the rich man who could give a million dollars but only gives $10,000?
We prayed on that, friends, and we realized that in Bob's eyes,
that rich man is the only one that's going to get to heaven because he paid more money.
So I want you to call 828-9500.
I mean, 828-9500.
You have to, not just that number, but 823-2490.
That's 7490.
You know, when you pledge, when you pledge,
you're showing that there is a listenership out there for the hour of slack.
And believe you me, we need proof every minute.
This show causes this nice station more headaches than probably just about any other show.
And, you know, we've probably got more enemies than most shows.
So we need to prove that we have the friends.
The dear, dear.
To fill their minds with questions.
Questions that only Bob can answer through his chosen apostles, his fishes of wallets.
And what is money?
Nearly another tool of the conspiracy.
Except when it gains power by passing from your pocket to Bob's.
I would like to testify to the power of Bob and what it has done for me.
And before I'd like to do that,
I'd like to bring you a message.
A public service message from the subgenius foundation.
And friends, I'm talking about, about your cash flow.
Have you thought about your cash flow recently?
Yeah.
And where's it flowing?
It's flowing out, isn't it?
Is there one person who says they got cash flow flowing in?
Not one.
Let me tell you something, brothers and sisters.
Let me tell you, cash is flowing into me.
Oh, I'm not telling you.
But I'm going to tell you.
I'm going to tell you right now because you asked.
I believe in Bob.
And if you have a problem with your cash flow,
it's because your cash is not flowing towards Bob.
This is the first industrial church.
We're not a tax write-off scam.
We are an incorporated profit-making foundation.
If there is such a thing.
We're profits and we want profits.
So you've got to come back.
To the old American way.
Yes.
You've got to come back to quality goods.
For your dollar.
A right to purchase.
Let me ask you a simple joke.
How many of you have been tithing up to Bob?
That, which is truly Bob's.
Tell me that joke.
How many of you have been giving 10% of your worth of goods to Bob?
I don't care who you are or where you come from.
If you haven't sent your $20 into Bob, you're going to burn.
And can I win?
Mother Teresa.
I don't care how many people she's helped.
If she hadn't sent her $20 into jail, Bob Dodge is going to burn in hell.
Friends, I want you to reach deep into that holiest aura piece in your body.
And have your back pocket pull out that wallet.
And we don't just want the money out of the wallet.
We don't just want the credit cards.
We want your library card.
Your social security card.
We want the wallet itself.
Because it ain't the money, friends.
It ain't the money.
It's the black.
Bob's got lots of money, friends.
Bob has lots of money, dear friends.
The money, you know, it don't buy you happiness.
But it allows you the choice of what kind of misery you want to endure.
And if you can't have real slack, then I guess false slack is better than no slack.
But remember, the conspiracy set it up to where you can never make enough money.
So, and this is something my young son just spouted the other day.
He spouted the word of Bob.
He said, don't take money, take Bob.
And you can't get Bob without sending money to K-N-O-N via calling 828-9500.
This logic is self-evidently inescapable.
It's, you know, obvious.
It's obviously true.
But, you know, there's so many of you.
You've been out here taping this show.
And guilt is that feeling that you've been feeling.
It's like, it's as if the most hideous henchman of the tiny demon, Iheg-Ihin,
was gnawing and tickling incessantly at your very guts.
Like, the same feeling you get when you call a pledge into 828-9500
and then don't make good on it.
And it isn't from being afraid of the punishment.
It's from knowing that, you know,
from that time on, you won't be allowed to forget what you didn't do.
And guilt is the way you're gonna feel when I finish this sentence,
which is actually that you did pledge to K-N-O-N last pledge drive,
but you never sent your money.
You're getting free on this radio station what other sub-genii outside of Dallas
have to pay eight, up to eight bucks for, for one hour's worth.
And on top of that, you've been taping them, sending them around.
Maybe you haven't.
Maybe you've been sinless by omission.
But, friends, Jesus, though Jesus Christ relieves you from, from guilt,
Bob, he, he, he, he don't forgive your trespasses.
He, he may show you some new ways to sin,
and he may give you a divine excuse by which to rationalize your sins.
Oh, yeah, but when it comes to sins against Bob,
against Slack, and against K-N-O-N,
which is a pillar of Bob's temple,
oh, no.
He ain't gonna, he, he's gonna be whooping on your butt for your trespasses,
and he's gonna do it in an hour that ye know not.
I lay upon ye jokers the curse that,
now, here it is,
may the curse of the head that has, hath never bled be upon you,
that you may live, listening to the other stations, in quiet desperation,
and, and not, not one new mind-breaking experience would you have
to give you that eternal,
eternal satisfaction, because,
because it would have taught you how to appreciate the Slack you already have.
But no, you're just gonna keep getting that slow poison.
You're gonna keep getting that slow, from not calling 828-9500 or 823-7490,
you're gonna get the drug of normality seeping further into your brain tissues.
Listen to it, listen to it seeping in there.
Ugly sound, ain't it?
That's the, that's the, it's real brain damage that comes from the stations
that play just what you want to hear.
Because if you had any brains at all,
you'd know that you don't really want to hear what you think you want to hear.
You pay to know what you really think,
and you want to hear surprises,
things that are new to your brain,
and they may be scary,
but it's like giving your brain a good rinse,
like through the car wash.
You know, you can't think about your own brain, friends,
but you can dial this number,
and, and pledge that money to, to KNON,
to help keep us all on the air.
And may, you too, for instance, at some point.
So, it's your choice.
It's your choice.
Go ahead and launch whatever spirits you hold.
Oh shoot, I've had enough of that.
I'm gonna shut off these tapes.
I'm just not in that kind of a mood.
We've got, we've got five preachers sitting here.
Some of the, some of the mightiest preachers in town.
They're, they're just, they ain't, they ain't doing nothing.
They're just, they ain't, they ain't doing nothing.
They're sucking on their thumbs.
They're just, they're, huh?
Playing Switch.
They're, they're, that's all they're doing.
They're playing pocket pool in here.
I've had, I've, I've never seen such a thing.
Oh, you quit laughing down there.
You, oh, you laughing.
Do you think it's funny?
We ain't getting no calls.
That's all there is to it.
That's, and you, ingrates is what they are.
I've had enough.
I'm just gonna get off.
Bob's gonna take me home.
He's just gonna, we're gonna get out of here.
This is gonna be the last hour of slack.
I'm, I'm, I just can't take any, I'm, I mean business.
I ain't hearing no praise, Bob's, and I ain't wanting any.
Hell no.
Hellfire.
All right.
Now, I noticed last Sunday one of you all out there put a, a nickel in the offering plate.
Yeah, phyllo drumming, a nickel.
There you tight son of a.
I see all, I see everything that goes on out there.
You think I don't know nothing?
You're the one that don't know nothing.
Dog like creatures.
Thanks.
I can't stand it.
I just can't stand it.
Y'all are going to fry like free toes in the skillet of Hades unless you cough up.
This is poor.
All right.
That's right, Al.
I'm maybe, let's just go to another church, Pope S. Cecilia.
Whimps, whimps.
Let's just go on to another radio station.
Maybe we'll go to one that pays.
Maybe we'll go to one of those stations people like to.
No.
They don't mind that commercial.
They'll give us gold Cadillacs.
Of course, we'll have to quit talking about Bob, but they don't care about Bob.
They don't want to hear about Bob.
We'll have to quit playing.
We can't play.
We wouldn't be able to play this unreleased Devo tape.
Oh, God.
No.
We're not going to be able to get around to that unreleased song that you ain't heard yet,
because you ain't calling in.
Old Will of Dog's, Will Frazier, he's just sitting there.
I see you out there.
Zaphod is totally idle.
This is pathetic.
You know what these boys are going to start doing if you don't get their hands busy on
that telephone?
I'm going to be seeing ugly stuff here right in front of me.
I don't like it.
I haven't had enough.
I'm bored.
It's the end of the road for me.
I've lost patience with you people.
What does it matter with you people?
You're sitting on your butts.
You get calling 823-7490.
I'm bored.
823-7490.
4-8-2-8-9-5-100.
Now pick it up.
Oh, there's one call.
One call.
One call coming in.
Well, great.
That's going to make the Hour of Slack look real good.
How about the rest of you, huh?
How about the rest of you Slack thieves?
You're stealing this.
You're not paying for it.
Everybody else is paying for what they want to hear.
You know how we turned out on that last pledge drive?
They told me this was going to be the last Hour of Slack season if we didn't start raking
something in for the next hour.
The station is going, why do we need to have the Hour of Slack on there?
It's a big headache, big trouble.
All the Christians call up and complain.
All the demon worshipers call up and complain because they hate Bob, too.
What are they going to do when they lose Bob?
What are they going to do?
Oh, they don't care.
They don't want Bob.
Shoot.
Hell.
Fire.
They don't care about the church.
They don't care about their mental lives.
They'll say praise Bob as long as I'm saying something they like.
But when we start talking about money, then, oh, then they want to go up on the mountaintop
and get drunk with the other cavemen or sit there watching that tube.
Bob doesn't care about anything else.
Bob wants what's most important to you, and that's your cash, is it not?
That's right.
That's all they care about.
That ain't going to get it.
That ain't going to get it, hoss and hosses.
I mean, this is going to determine whether there's going to be an Hour of Slack.
I'm sick.
I'm just as soon.
Not just a hour.
I'm going to die.
A K-N-O-N period.
Where the heck else are you going to hear anything like you hear here?
You don't.
Nobody plays the things that K-N-O-N plays.
Nobody.
I just don't want to be a pastor to a bunch of lazy damn, I don't know.
My sermon is done.
Y'all don't pick.
I've had enough.
If y'all don't pick up those phones, I'm going to excommunicate y'all, every one of you.
You'll never get another drop of slack from me.
You're going to be false or otherwise in your entire lives.
I've had it.
Brother Woodrow, why don't you just lead us in the closing prayer?
Well, are you going to do it or not?
Oh, God.
Dismissed.
I've had enough.
Praise God.
Yeah, I, I, I.
And you can call in and you can talk to the, there's some sexy ministers on the, on the
line tonight.
Your prayer partners are here, ready to receive.
Your promise.
Your covenant with Bob, friends.
Friend, this is, I, I cast ye out.
It was Bob, that banished you to the pit.
It was he who flung you, from the depths of heaven to the pits of hell.
It was he who cast you out.
One clean spirit.
He has dominion over you.
I order you in the name of Bob to come out.
I'm telling you, this is, you have to do, these are not just some, you know, there's
been a few, a few different things that have happened in your life.
We don't guarantee
Anywhere caused by
Or anything out of the
Space here or beyond
It's a comply with the
Instruction
Or recommendation
We don't guarantee
Anywhere caused by
The space here or the water supply
Any damage resulting
From a fire at the sky
We gotta sell you friends
We're not just gonna sit here
And talk
Bob said we had to party
Didn't he?
He said we had to party
He didn't say we could
He said we had to
And so we must also sell
Christ, Bob and Tink
I think this is in the mail
Tink
Hey, okay, okay, okay.
You're very impetuous.
Now get on your knees on the floor and start.
Just like we said.
Now you can have Reverend Ann.
Now you can have something to sell.
We all know we're in the art of selling.
We create a mental and an emotional climate of unconscious selling.
Right in your own home.
When everybody sells.
We're all selling.
We all have something to sell.
Yes, everyone selling together.
Mighty symphony of prosperity.
For we all have something to sell.
Well, dear friend, J.R. Bob Dobbs and some outmoded, overused deity from ancient fairy tales.
The living bleat.
The child Bob experienced a traumatic, close encounter with a UFO.
What?
Yeah.
Age of three.
Soon thereafter, he began to exhibit strange powers of persuasion.
By age six, he had made his first million almost by accident.
You have to love Bob.
He loves you, Bob.
You love Bob.
You have to.
Or else what happens if you don't love Bob?
He'll kill you.
So Bob, you have to.
Bob.
Bob, you have to.
You heard it here first.
You heard it.
You don't love Bob.
Bob, you have to.
Maybe it's your friends.
Oh, yes.
Well, you know, if you don't pledge, there's going to be more than one.
You're going to have to listen to it forever.
Or at least until the money.
Dear friends, we need that money.
Oh, my gosh.
Let's get us.
Come on.
Let's get something happening here.
All right.
We're finally getting a couple of phone lines.
We've raised $200 so far.
Great.
Can you imagine a world without slack?
A world without the hour of slack?
And even almost as bad, a world without can-win at all?
Because if you don't send some money by midnight tonight, you're going to be wishing to God you had or Bob.
Oh, the world's going crazy.
Enough with the movie.
He doesn't deserve the credit.
Enjoying your...
He deserves it.
He deserves it?
Hospital
He deserves it.
was the infant Jesus, either man or God?
Or merely one of the countless aliens
that visit the Earth each and every day?
The answer, yes, definitely.
Take that and shove it up the two-part certainty
in the fuzzy place called the Twilight Zone.
Yeah, yeah, that's right.
Yeah, and if y'all don't call in
some of that pledge money to keep this station going,
then you might as well forget it.
We ain't gonna be live for long.
We're gonna be off.
You're gonna get the hour of slack
at four o'clock in the morning,
and I ain't gonna be doing it.
No, it'll just be a bunch of tapes,
but that's okay.
That's all you care about, ain't it?
All you care about is these unreleased albums
I'm never gonna be able to play again.
We're having a pathetic turnout.
We need your money, folks.
My baby doll
Baby, baby, baby doll
Light of my life, she turns it on.
Toot, toot, toot, toot.
Over my head, not closing up.
Toot, toot.
My baby doll.
Doll baby.
Baby, baby, baby doll.
My baby doll.
Baby doll.
You look so good.
You feel so big.
Baby doll.
You let me have it.
Why don't you do it, baby doll?
Baby doll.
We've2 done it.
Yeah, died. That's right. That song's going to stay dead and you're not going to hear the rest of any of this cool, groovy, unreleased stuff until we start getting some calls in.
I mean, it's 1139 at KNO in here and we ain't getting nothing.
Come on, you slugs.
Listen, I'm serious. This is, this is, it's really, really looking bad at this point, friends.
Uh, we've got, this is my one hour to raise some money for this show.
The only time we're not going to be able to do it next week.
Uh, you know, I'm not going to be able to do it again for another, uh, three months.
Yeah, well, that's, that's it. That's a good, that's a, we may not be here.
We died. My baby died. My baby died. Who cares?
Um.
I mean, friends, there's a big thermometer on the wall here and it, and unfortunately it's only up to about 10% of what it's supposed to be.
Now, last time, most of you called in in the last 10, 15 minutes and I'm assuming that may be what it is.
I sure hope that's what it is.
So we ain't got half what we did last time and last time didn't do us a whole lot of good.
And I'm, I'm sorry. This, uh, this is getting a little bit frightening to me because, uh, you think, I mean, I get on, I try to be entertaining and funny.
But.
Uh, frankly, it's true.
I went into the spirit and Bob Dobbs came and said he was going to take me off to that place where, where subgeniuses go.
Asgard, the home of those slain by overwork for Bob.
And that, I mean, listen, you know, they live, they let us have this show on this station only, uh, as long as we can prove there's a listening audience.
And so far we just aren't doing it.
So I want you to.
To seriously call.
You don't have to pledge a hundred dollars.
You don't even have to pledge $50 pledge, $10 pledged, you know, five, 20, something like that.
And the numbers to call are 8, 2, 3, 7, 4, 9 0, or 8, 2, 8, 9, 500.
And the place to send those checks is a PO box 7 1 0 9 0 9.
But, uh, you can, you don't even have to send a check.
You can call us in with a bank draft.
Uh, give us the information.
On your, uh, your bank account.
It'll be taken out automatically every month or so, painlessly.
You all, they don't care.
Well.
They don't care.
Yeah.
And.
When he's there.
When he's there, when he's there, when he's there.
When he's there, when he's there.
When he is there.
When he's there, when he is there.
And that's your symphony.
That's right, friends.
Now you can have
this amazing new symphony
generates in the mind of the salesman
before it does in the prospect.
Oh, something to sell.
He used to be my savior.
He used to be a friend.
But he didn't have just enough money
to lend some.
We don't think about
money.
dollars anymore.
We don't think about
Give me that again, will you?
Who's gonna get them?
The helots.
Who are they?
Listen, Sucky, you ever been broke?
Sure, mostly often.
All right, you're walking along.
Not a nickel in your jeans, you're free as the wind.
Nobody bothers you. Hundreds of people pass you by
in every line of business.
Shoes, hats, automobiles, radios, furniture,
everything.
They're all nice, lovable people.
They let you along.
Was that right?
Then you get a hold of some dough and what happens?
All those nice, sweet, lovable people become helots.
A lot of heels.
They begin creeping up on you.
Trying to sell you something.
They get long claws.
And they get a stranglehold on you.
And you squirm and you duck and you holler
and you try to push them away,
but you haven't got a chance.
They gut you.
First thing you do, you get a hold of them.
You know your own things.
A car, for instance.
Now your whole life is messed up with a lot more stuff.
You get license fees
and number plates
and gas and oil
and taxes and insurance
and identification cards and letters
and bills and flat tires and dents
and traffic tickets and motorcycle pops
and courtrooms and lawyers and fines
and a million and one other things.
And what happens?
You're not the free and happy guy you used to be.
You got to have money to pay for all those things.
So you go after what the other fellas got.
And there you are.
You're a helot yourself.
You win, Colonel.
Here, take the 50.
Go ahead and get rid of it.
You bet I will, just as fast as I can.
I'm going to get some canned goods,
a fish and rot, and the rest I'm going to give away.
Give away?
Hey, get me a pitcher's glove.
I've got to get some practice.
Say, he's giving it away.
I'm going to get me some of that.
Hey, come back here, you helot.
Well, you said
if anybody should ask you what the average John Doe is like,
you couldn't tell him
because he's a million and one thing.
He's Mr. Big.
With Connie's encouragement,
the young Dobbs became a salesman
of legendary and almost frantic
and frightening abilities,
known to his peers as the man who could sell anything.
He worked his way up to the very top
of the conspiracy ladder and might have saved him.
But...
But, dear friends, but...
What?
Oh, folks, I want you to get back on those phones
and call in another pledge.
And don't just pledge money, pledge everything.
You can pledge...
You can pledge credit cards.
That's right.
We'll take Visa or Master Charge here.
Most of you feel the spirit of giving, friends.
This is that wonderful time of year.
And if you can just call 828-9500,
folks, and keep us on the air.
Not just the Hour of Slack,
but KNON and all the other shows that you like
and that I like.
But don't...
You know, we got a lot of subgeniuses out there
that call in with their phones.
With their church names.
Their...
Their church names.
And see, the problem with that is
if you don't give your real name also,
or rather your human name,
if you don't give your human name,
the mail won't get to you.
Your subgenius church application form
won't get to you.
Your KNON t-shirt,
if you had that large of a pledge,
your KNON newsletter,
that won't get to you.
The post office,
we have found out the hard way,
is have many subgeni out there
that if you don't tell the conspiracy your real name,
they use that as an excuse
not to give you your due slack.
Just one of many, many excuses.
So watch out with fake names,
but do call in with that Visa and MasterCard number.
Call in with that promise of a check or cash.
And look at these names.
Look at these souls lining up for the harvest, friends.
Oh, look at these...
I just wanted to be positive.
Look at these souls.
Look at these souls lining up for the harvest.
Yes, we got a couple of them.
And we finally got a couple of pledges.
We got $100 from the High Council.
Yeah.
I want to see that $100 cash before I'm leaving.
I've got 13 minutes to live, dear friends.
13 minutes to live, according to the word of Bob.
And I don't know about you, but I trust the word of Bob.
In fact, it's about the only dang thing
in the world.
And this university can trust.
And he's a hell of a liar.
So I don't know.
I just don't know.
Call in those numbers.
823-95...
No, it's 823-7490
or 828-9500.
Are we getting any in there?
Oh, they're just sitting there.
They're trickling in.
We got two or three, I guess.
That's going to be a great ending for my life.
Great.
12 minutes to live.
I guess I'll go out in a real bang, huh?
It's going to be great.
I'll be going out in a poof.
More like it.
More like what it is.
They don't care about their souls.
Mom, I don't know where my soul's going in 11 minutes.
Well, I hope I know where it's going anyway.
I don't know.
My friends post that they can keep...
Can I tell you?
No.
Uh, look where Positive Thinking has gotten most of the world so far.
People say that Reverend Stange is a pessimistic booger,
but frankly, I'm worried that my most pessimistic predictions
might turn out to have been, in the long run, idiotically optimistic.
And our fear tonight is that you out there taping this show
will think...
will think, oh, well, well, they'll stay on the air or not.
Whether I give or not.
But folks, if you don't pledge, the world will literally come to an end at the end of this hour.
If you, and I don't mean just some of you, I mean you, the one listening right now.
Oh, you're laughing. You're laughing.
It's going to collapse around your pathetic ears, but you nihilistic teenagers out there,
oh, no future, man, no future.
You know, that's why if the rival cult that wants these airwaves had this hour,
they'd have raised $10,000 by now.
And you know what they'd do with it?
They'd build concentration camps for the likes of you.
You abnormal.
You punk.
You old hippie.
You humanist.
So genius.
So friends, you know, the money isn't just for the hour of slack.
It's for the totality that is K-N-O-N.
It isn't just for us mutants.
It's for your very mind, your very soul.
And you wouldn't believe how close your soul is to being sold out.
Dear brother or sister, between your job and the drugs and the lies,
listen, you need every bit of slack you can hang on to.
And we have a special form of slack in store for you tonight.
Not stored in souls anywhere.
And the type of slack you're going to be getting,
is guilt.
Guilt.
Tonight we're going to whip us up some guilt.
Some of you are saying,
oh, what's pledge time,
Reverend Stang's going to rant all night about money.
And you better be afraid that that's true,
little Bobby, little gimme Bob out there,
because if you don't send that pledge by midnight,
by midnight tonight,
you're going to be wishing to Bob that you had,
or whatever god you worship,
the stark fist of a beautiful nose,
whether you did or didn't.
Do you think I'm crazy?
That's what they say about me.
We'll call 828-9500.
Call that number, 828-9500,
or 823-7490,
and receive the word of Bob.
And first, you will want to turn away from him.
Then, you may find him a silent, unresisting target for your ridicule.
Stand up.
Stand up!
Turn around!
Mister, why's your head so big, mister?
But if you come to know him,
Have you always been the way you are now?
you will begin to see beyond the perversion of his form.
Are you in any pain?
Are your parents still alive?
and discover the beauty in the beast.
At no time have I met with such a perverted or degraded version of a human being as this man.
I am not an animal.
I am a human being.
At this level, our salesman can see the top of the ladder and is well on his way to it.
Well, I wish, I wish.
Funny, you think it's real funny, don't you?
I've about given up.
I've got eight minutes to live, friends.
Now, the hell is growing. The money ain't.
The calls, Pope S. Cecilia's sitting there twiddling her thumbs.
All six of them.
But what can you, a humble servant of Bob, do?
Bob, my friend, is begun.
But you are the boy to go.
The showdown is fast approaching.
Though the church is still unknown to most pigs,
its infectious, ever-changing doctrines are spreading across the continent.
Church headquarters, the first megafist of the lodge,
is housed in this Dallas skyscraper,
from which Dob's secret mandates are issued to his agents in the dreaded Brotherhood of Bob.
But this mighty edifice represents but the tip of a wandering rogue iceberg.
The words, hymns, and sound effects of Dob's are disseminated on a weekly basis.
The
First Bob, my name is Billy Jing.
I will tell you some funny story.
We know that humor is through exaggeration.
Now a high school student came in and said that Bob is going to get arrestedプ där
credits
Well, that's the joke it's just the writing.
people got a piece of a right
that people were normal
well and I was not
aram
cannonball
separated Belt
I don't even care.
Ivan, no.
Wait a minute, is that clock right?
Oh, my heart!
Ivan!
No!
Oh, no!
Ivan!
Ivan, no!
Please, help!
Oh!
Ivan, he's...
No!
He's dead!
You dogs!
You animals!
You killed him!
You scum!
You did it!
No, you couldn't believe it, K.O.
We had to send you your money, and now he's dead!
He's dead!
Oh, no!
And you think you'll hear the hours like on any other station?
Ha!
Dream on, it's over!
There's no staying!
Let me slap you around a little, see if you can't take it!
Yeah!
Stay funny!
Come on, Stank!
Get up!
I tried again!
Hope you're happy!
Come on, Stank!
Yeah, killed him!
No!
Deader than hell!
He's not moving!
Oh, my God!
It's all over, and it's your fault!
Faithless!
Hell!
I've never seen anything like this!
Anybody got a 220 wire, I'll stick it up next to his heart, if we can find where it is.
That won't do any good.
I've got a cab!
His net life is gone!
All right!
He's been deserted!
Get it going!
Where are those phone calls?
That's the only thing that can bring him...
up is phone calls!
Why aren't those lines being lit?
No, they don't care.
Couldn't believe that there even was a Bob.
I believe that varies.
Oh, 823-7490-828-9500.
Please call.
Call now!
Hurry up!
Any sec...
Here's Ron Lindsey.
Oh, my God!
Here's Ron...
Come!
Come on, now!
Hurry up!
Ouch!
I'm so confused!
Okay, poor Ron Lindsey's walked in on his horrible tragedy!
What's wrong with you people?
Okay!
Okay, we've got the high power line.
We're gonna apply it to Ivan's heart now.
Only you can help save the Reverend Stanning.
Only you can save him.
Come on.
I know you're...
I know you want to.
It's in your heart.
You've got to save Ivan.
How can you live without Ivan?
We've got the power line.
Ready switch.
Hit it!
Ah!
Look!
I've been to the mountain top.
I've seen the possibilities.
I've seen what awaits us.
All right.
Wait a minute.
I'm getting a transmission.
Friends!
Bob said I can tell the truth now.
I can go ahead and tell you what's been going on here.
What?
Friends, I lied.
I lied.
Lied, lied, dear friends.
Actually, the last pledge drive.
This is the first time we've announced this.
We've known for about a month.
During the last pledge drive, the hour of slack raised.
Actually.
The hour of slack raised.
The hour of slack raised more money per hour than any other show on KNON.
Can you believe it?
This, the weirdest show in the Southwest, if not the universe,
managed to raise more per hour and just about more, period, than any other show.
More than the, I mean, it's unbelievable.
And this was paid money, dear friends.
Paid, paid up pledges.
Now, what we got this time?
I've got a giant chance.
We've been faking you out, you fools, suckers.
We got your...
No, we actually, actually, don't speak too soon.
We just got the, we just got the pledges.
We don't have the money yet.
It don't count.
That's right.
It doesn't count until we, until we actually get that green in the station's pockets.
And if you don't get it, Zaphod comes looking for you.
That's right.
The station's got big, big pockets.
And Zaphod's got a mighty...
He's got big...
Big feet.
Being a son of the Yeti, he's ready to stomp you, friends.
So, stay tuned.
You've got two minutes for...
Keep, you keep on calling in.
You've got two more minutes to go ahead and top us off if we possibly can.
I don't think we did as well as the last pledge drive.
But, but it's, you know, we could.
We could, we could make it.
823-7490, 828-9500.
You know, I mean...
Let's, let's, let's not...
Hell, hell fire.
Hell.
I've had it.
I've had enough of this stuff.
I'm ready to get out of here.
I'm sure something's going on here.
I'll see you in over a week.
Hey!
Bye-bye.
See you next time.
We'll see you next time.
Bye-bye.
But, get in the Jaybirds.
What? What? What?
No, we don't. We're getting out of here.
No, you can't. Not anymore. It's over with. That's it.
I'm sorry, friends, that we had to pull these gimmicks on you to try, but I swear y'all were sluggish tonight.
Sluggish. I think I will just go home and die every night.
But Ron Lindsey is here.
And, friends, you better get ready to pay up again.
Do it again. Call in another pledge.
This is the stateside. That's all it is, friend.
Money. What is money but merely a medium of exchange? Who cares?
We're going to go back to the home for slackless children.
Tell the poor kids we just got enough for...
Hey, we don't have enough money for modeling clay this time around.
I've had enough.
No free lunches this time.
Thanks a lot, suckers.
You're listening to KNON 90.9 FM. Praise Bob.
We'll be right back.
Money, money, money, money, money.
Money.
Some people got to have it.
Some people.
Really need it.
Listen to me, y'all.
Do things, do things, do things, bad things with it.
Well, you're going to do things, do things, do things, good things with it.
Yeah, yeah.
Uh-huh.
Talk about cash, money, money.
Yeah.
Talk about cash, money.
Dollar bills, y'all.
Come on now.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
All the love and money
People will steal from their mother
People will ride their own brother
All the love and money
People can't even walk the street
Because they'll never know
In the world they're going to meet
For that deed, oh, deed
Make great
Almighty dollar
That's money
Drink
All the love and money
People will laugh, laugh, they will cheat
People don't care who they turn up to be
All the love and money
omina
All the girls andatrias
Will tear theiracher's clothes and proper clothes off
Those altar seats all that make one look so happy
He touched theester chocolate on the back of my head
Guevara,yeog,hrina and organizza
That remember to call me, そら,yeog,hrina
品でぜひぉつきを曲がっちゃって