Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
This is Timothy Larry reminding you that just as you need slack, Bob needs your help.
Send in those pledges and praise Bob.
Sound impossible?
Yes, you rub it between the forefinger and the thumb.
Say what?
You take a pinch of salt, you rub it between the forefinger and the thumb,
walk with a shim around a turning decapitated child's head,
and then jump into the grave and say,
hop on my thumb, hop on my thumb, this is a problem I must overcome.
Throw in a dead cat, or a live cat that's not feeling well.
Then cover with the sod, and when the birds chirp on the third Saturday after mickle mass,
take a large dill pickle and insert it in the tumulus.
Insert it in the tumulus, the heap, the shambling mound over the grave.
And this time you will experience a divine regurgitation,
somewhat like under the immaculation of J.R. Bob Dobbs,
the slain and martyred hip-hop in the Church of the Seventh-Decade.
I believe it's something God puts in us.
It's something somebody put in us.
Fusion, may I help? Hydrogen fusion?
Hydrogen fusion?
Hmm, well, if I don't have my fusion,
I'm going to church at a service.
Yes, hydrogen fusion.
Hybrid fusion.
This material contains information affecting the national defense of the United States
within the meaning of the espionage laws, Title 18, U.S.C., Sections 7098 and 74,
a transmission or revelation of which in any manner to an unauthorized person
is inevitably prohibited by law.
Ah!
The beginning is a very delicate time.
Shut up!
Look out, guys!
Ah!
Well, we're tuning in on you right now.
And there, we're centered on...
Oh, okay, we're on lockup.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
You are interested in the unknown, the mysterious, the unexplainable.
That is why you are here.
We are controlling transmission.
Control, control, control.
No trouble.
Just get set and get going.
Hey, man.
Recording.
Everything's going fine.
No trouble.
Wait a minute.
Wait.
That's this switch here.
Okay, I think we're ready to go.
Let's go.
Welcome, dear friends,
to the...
The subgenius hour of...
What?
Every time you say, see, hear, or think...
Bob?
That's your key phrase.
It will trigger the entire message without your being aware of it.
We are controlling transmission.
This is Doug Smith, radio operator.
Ah, it's been nice out here in the little...
The Learning Studio.
Oh, yes, dear friends.
As you may have guessed, this is another rerun show.
Technically, this is hour of slack number 1071.
But in truth, it's a rerun of an old taped show, number 66,
which would make it from probably around November or December of 1986.
20 years ago, this particular show was marked by me.
Headphones, sound effects, and then it says,
end is amazing, but that doesn't necessarily mean anything.
I'll have to go through and clean up some of the Dallas station
and Dallas address references on these old shows.
But, friends, we're doing reruns,
partly because we're working really hard on a subgenius history project
that takes the form of an online course,
which you can learn more about at maybelogic.com
or maybelogic.org.
Maybelogic is one word that sounds like those two words.
Praise Bob.
Anyway, let us go back in time now to the olden hour of slack number 66.
Perfect concentration.
No distractions.
No anxiety.
No fear.
Brazil
We stood beneath an amber moon
And softly murmured
Someday soon
We kiss
We do the work, you do the pleasure
Hi there.
I want to talk to you about ducts.
Do your ducts seem old-fashioned?
Out of date?
Central Services' new duct designs
are now available in hundreds of different colours
to suit your individual taste.
Hurry now, while stocks last,
your nearest Central Services showroom.
Designer colours to suit your demanding taste.
The rumour became reality.
Another satanic cult.
Yes, just another evil cult
that was supposed to be a good one.
This is how the war gets on the radio.
I think a lot of subgeniuses
originally believed they were doing something good
by joining the church.
That wheel and chain set up
makes the sound of moving artillery.
Sounds like a real battle.
Well, it's nothing compared to what it takes
to move this show.
Don't be alarmed.
It's a lot more work than saving souls, believe me.
That punch didn't connect.
The sound was fake.
Although, Stang suffered a real blow
from an infuriated Gabofran.
That was a great blow.
Yes, the mallet on a grapefruit
gave the sound of that blow.
Oh.
Curiously refreshing.
It was a lot of fun, too.
But here they come.
The guard is forming to march the guilty offender away.
Yes, those who believed
the wrong lies in the book of the subgenius
taken into the stadium
near Dobstown
and all the Malaysians
pour into the little wooden seats.
For the clumsy child with the hard-to-fit shoe size,
Cap Bigfoot, our 31st season.
Boys and girls, 6 to 18,
10D to 15, EEEEEE.
Our patient understanding staff
has had outstanding success
with the clumsy, uncoordinated child.
Our unique, patented method
starts your child from scratch,
from crawling to early walking,
to full walking, trotting, and running,
until he is actually strutting, dancing,
and doing gymnastics.
Many of our graduates are now prominent
in ballet and jazz tag.
Write to George Trefeld, Camp Bigfoot,
Peppermill, Oregon, 65201.
We like you.
And should ignore you.
But instead, we are...
Agh!
Yeah!
And!
Why?
Bob
Here and there
Closet, gallery, knock, empty, where
Bob
Oh, yes, dear sir
This is the beast
The Chinese subgenius
And you are listening to the hour of slack
Remember, Bob is the comrade of all people
He is a Chinese
Just like in America
And people need slack
In Chinese, we call slack
What's a butterfly?
It must be true slack
Not the bad slack
Boy, will you look at that guy's slack
Help me somebody
Thank you, Lili Jing
Yes, my friend
We have the great Ivan Stang here tonight
Ivan Stang himself
The grand auditor
And chief inquisitor of the subgenius faith
Who has every subgenius' name
On his special basement computer
And he's here tonight
To make the hour and a half of slack
Seem like, well, like forever
Ivan Stang
That's Stang of Stang's
Slack
Sibling stouter of rang
Of Cerno's claws and Jinger's fangs
When the peaks are upon us
When it is finally on us
The peaks will broil
But not in song
Nature and men will stand aside
The jaws of doom shall open wide
While Ivan Stang shall perch in song
Where fromlessness and fear will be gone
And in the swells
False prophets from their citadels
He topples down
To nether hells
He judges kings and guinea-pods
And renders into visit laws
Those who prove the name of gods
He rules the masts of King Yorhost
Evens his knights on the coast
A pledge from his name
As from a ghost
Where can we go? Where can we hide? No place in all this world so wide shall escape the dire subjection of life.
The dangers howl, the sternows plead, Oh, harmless rises from the sea, no hiding place for you and me.
What future does our doom procure us? Heavenly earth indeed endure us, let the damn wound outend nor us.
A man nor us, and a wretch, the gangster of the yale gang, let us now welcome Ivan Stang.
Ah, yes, dear friend, so good to be here.
Say it, Ivan, say it.
Feeling the power here in this hideous, hideous place.
Bob lives, friend.
Bob lives.
Don't let him tell you otherwise.
He ain't dead.
Oh, what is this, anyway?
I should know.
I'm the, I'm the guy that has to read sooner or later all the mail that comes to that P.O. box that you probably thought was just made up.
The opinions expressed by Ivan Stang do not necessarily reflect the opinions of the staff and management of this radio station, the other staff, the relations and spouses of the staff and management, or the staff of this staff and staff.
That's really good.
That's really true, Hal, but he doesn't know that it's all over the place these days.
A Bob body dragged out of the Victoria Theatre with these eyes, these dead lights looked on Bob and the light was trilling from them forever.
There's, there's saint of sale corpses dotting the landscape all the way from Little Rock to Berkeley here.
I don't know what the big deal is.
I mean, that's just because, just because there's a, a Dobbs corpse there doesn't necessarily
get me.
I mean, can you really tell me what the big thing is here?
Can Bob really die?
Oh, my God.
When it blows its snacks,
when it blows its snacks,
when it blows its
snacks,
stacks, there ain't nowhere
to be found.
When the wolf's close
While we're down
We'll watch out
Till the town is around
Hide all the women in town
Hide
When it blows
All you girls
Make no mistakes
Here's a golden snake
Snake's in the snow
He takes them out
Out on the nice mud
Town of the nonsense
They all see around
When he's straightened up
They all bend down
He don't bow to bad water
He don't push it all around
When it blows
Stacks
parliament
It blows
Stacks
Blows
That alone
BS
Nope, nope, nope.
A second.
Okay, you gals out there.
We haven't gotten any more entries in the win a date with Cleve Duncan contest.
I mean, I'm not even going to go into...
If you don't know who Cleve Duncan is, then you probably don't deserve the date.
But if you do, go ahead and try.
Go ahead and try.
It's important.
Very important.
All right.
How do you across?
Go for lever.
There you go.
Đây là các bạn.
If you want to know the truth, then that's a fact.
Somebody scream, give me more slack.
Give me more slack.
Do you like slack?
I like it.
I love slack.
I love it.
Do you want slack?
I want it.
Do you need slack?
I need it.
You like me?
Yeah.
Come on.
But I need me.
Go get it.
What about a moon moon?
No.
The moon is a dismal.
Get down the program.
No.
Right out the hobo booth.
You like naturalist.
No.
Got the balls in the show.
You and I, baby.
No.
That's a real cool book.
Out of the world with a proper book.
Yeah, he'll be hopping to the barbershop with more slack.
I got to have my slack.
Give it to me.
Yeah.
Praise Bob.
Hey.
Boy, I mean, slack is better than red beans and rice.
I'm top of a smoky.
All covered with sand.
I shot my poor teacher with a red rubber band.
I shot her with pleasure.
I shot her with please.
Please.
I couldn't have missed her.
She was 40 feet wide.
I went to her funeral.
I went to her grave.
Everybody threw flowers.
I threw a grenade.
The police came and got me.
And put me in jail.
I brought a bazooka.
And shot into a T-L-L.
Oh, thank you, Tevis.
That was a beautiful rendition of a classic, classic childhood song.
And there'll be more from the tiniest subgenius prophet coming up.
But friends, you know, we've been griping about those who didn't pay their pledge.
But we haven't really thanked those who had.
And, well, the Will of Dobbs and I got together.
And we got to looking at this board in here.
This poster that they've put up that keeps track of what shows are ahead and what shows are behind on the pledge drive.
And, friends, I could scarcely believe it.
But the Hour of Slack is number five among all KNON shows as far as paid pledges go.
And the other, the four shows out of 80, what, 81 shows, I think.
Yeah, 81 shows.
Out of 81 shows, the four shows that made more money during that pledge drive than the Hour of Slack were all on for like 10 hours a day.
They're on every day.
We did better than Pajama Party, better than anybody.
Now, the gospel shows, they got as much pledges as the subgenius show.
But, strangely, only 8% paid.
I wonder what that means.
Well, anyway, 50% of you subgeniuses have paid, I think.
By now, probably 50%.
And those who haven't, if you haven't gotten the calls already, you will.
You'll get that call.
And it's all being recorded, not only on magnetic media here in this century, but on the Akashic Records.
The records of all things that have ever occurred, even inside your brain.
That's all recorded.
And we have access to those through our guru, J.R. Bob Dobbs.
And, friends, we're going to continue with the show.
I hope you're, once again, I hope you're in headphones.
This is a real headphone.
This is a real headphone show.
How do we know you're not being a top?
How do we know?
Good God.
Just have to tell him we don't see anything.
What is this world coming to?
Don't listen to him.
Yes, you can find help.
You can be deprogrammed.
You can find out the truth.
What?
Beat me every day.
It's a hell of a day.
I know you're a dumbass.
They force you to sleep on boards.
What a device.
No, he's not.
He's a piece of shit.
What a device.
What's going on?
He's a release device.
I don't—
He's not a piece of the en currteo,
no, you son of a biop.
Sometimes I haven't heard these things,
You know what I mean.
That's what it's about.
The most strange thing that a stripper does
is pick a piece of paper,
baw incoming,
No, no, no, no, no.
Let's shut the fuck manage.
Don't touch it.
Don't touch it anyway.
What a piece of shit.
the upper teeth. Be sure to keep it down until the fingers are in position. At each corner of the
mouth, insert a thumb under the upper lip. Now slide the thumbs along the inside of the upper
lip until they are positioned just below and to the side of each nostril. The results are thrilling.
Everywhere these messages are heard, souls are being saved and sick bodies are being healed.
Don't send them your money. They've got me locked up in there.
I too refused to send money to the church of the subgenius and I too fell under the power of Iggy.
What?
And I don't think they must know. They're trying to shut us up, but there are subgenius
dissidents.
Stop right there. Sorry for keeping you in, doctors. Go on.
Don't leave me here.
They make me sick.
I understand.
I'm sick.
Don't let them kill me.
Torture me.
I understand.
They torture me.
I don't want to see you.
Torture me.
Is that what I want to be saying, miss?
Don't let them kill me.
It's been the subgenius, parrot and parakeet training tank...
They tortured me.
...to go in there and kill me.
I hate the budget.
...subgenius, parrot and parakeet training tank...
I hate this.
...to go in there and kill me.
This has been the subgenius, parrot and parakeet...
...training tank...
I'm proud of my language, but...
Yee-haw!
Let the sons of God and man be a witness.
Even in the belly of the Thunderbird,
I've been casting out the false prophets.
I'm busted. I got him blowing my O-ring.
Hey!
No!
Hey-ya!
Yeah!
Wow!
We have with us from the Ministry of Information,
Deputy Minister Eugene Heltman.
Good evening, David.
What do you believe is behind this recent increase
in terrorist bombings?
Bad sportsmanship.
A ruthless minority of people
seems to have forgotten certain
coolness.
Good old-fashioned virtue.
They just can't stand seeing the other fellow win.
If these people had just
played a game,
they'd get a lot more out of life.
Nevertheless, Mr. Heltman,
there are those who maintain that the Ministry of Information
has become too large and unwieldy.
David, in a free society,
information's the name of a game.
You can't win the game if you're a man short.
And the cost of it all,
Deputy Minister,
7% of the gross national product.
I understand this.
I understand the concern on behalf of the taxpayer.
People want value for money.
And that's why we always insist on the principle
of information retrieval charges.
It's absolutely right and fair
that those found guilty should pay for their periods of detention
and for the information retrieval procedures used in their interrogation.
Do you believe that the government is winning the battle against terrorists?
Oh, yes.
Arm around, my child.
Yes.
We're fielding all their strokes,
running a lot of them out,
and pretty consistently knocking them for six.
I'd say they're nearly out of the game.
One law-abiding citizen
has to subsidize criminals.
But Mr. Heltman,
the bombing campaign is now in its 13th year.
Beginners like me.
I'm a little bit of a rock.
Thank you very much, Deputy Minister.
Thank you, David.
And a very Merry Christmas to you all.
Know then that it is the year 10,191.
There have always been Bobs.
There has never been a world without a Bob.
Just as there's never been a Bob without a Dick,
his corresponding evil twin brother, Dick Dobbs.
After a mental mutation.
Bob's waiting to come home.
The demons you may see during the initial hallucinations
Get him away from me!
are not real.
Erotic carnality.
If you do not panic,
this phase will end after a few months.
Jabber.
So always resurface from the hypgnosis slowly, dear friends.
E-I-I-I-I-
Hoo-hoo!
Oh, yeah, I want to...
I want to...
That's not right, Gary.
That should be a...
Hoo-hoo!
Well, yes, I was going to make serious funny noises.
Because we all know that Bob is the man that makes all the ladies go...
Hoo-hoo!
He's the man that makes all the men go...
Well, let's take a little rest.
It ain't an own-chattin' laid-back universe, dear friends.
It's a...
Let's take a little rest and...
...universe.
Shh!
An action-packed universe.
Hello, what's in here?
Yeah, a boring and...
A burulating and...
...biodiversity.
...biologically active...
...a universe where everyone has a...
...orange globe coming from...
...events coming from holes between their shoelaces...
...oranges, bluefish...
...oranges, lobsters...
...enormous bioplasm that stretches throughout...
Hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
Oh, did you get some of that, too?
Yes, it was delicious.
That he'd force him to eat this big, ugly piece of meat.
Hoo-hoo!
He was a little short, chubby guy, and that's where Bob got the idea.
They say he came in with checkered pants on, but I just don't remember.
He was allowed to eat all he wanted.
Anything he wanted.
Bob's big boy was a real person.
That's true, but there was a real Bob,
and this parable goes to show that there is indeed always a real Bob.
There has to be a Bob, dear friend.
Even the things which you cannot possibly believe in, Bob's big boy indeed,
turn out to be an actual historic person,
and as it is with Bob's big boy,
surely it is with the far more impressive and major deity we know as the Avatar of All Slack.
That's how we know him.
Others call him Pimp or Mongrel.
Others call him a demon or your mama.
Indeed.
And the children of Bob are everywhere.
Bob lives on in his millions and millions, literally millions of illegitimate children,
all of them pressing lawsuits against me personally.
Well, Doctor, I'm sure you're used to it by now.
When I took on the job as sacred scribe at the church,
I had no idea what I was going to be getting into.
We had 500 employees in 1980.
Now it's just me and someone else.
Well, that's just the Reagan-esque spirit.
That's it.
Bob's boy is stabbed up in a corner.
And yet they say that Bob doesn't even exist.
There are some who say that there is no Bob.
If there's no Bob, then where did all of those dead bodies come from?
What about all those ads in the 50s that he posed for?
Well, it says right here, the body store.
Dead Bob's for any occasion.
Oh, put that away.
No Bob too small, no Bob too big.
No, really, guys, all kidding aside, I must admit,
Rob's a rough one.
At least the official father church, the subgenius foundation,
which we don't expect any of you except the stinking Bobbies to cling to.
Nevertheless, we have the only true word of Bob, the original apostles.
And as far as I'm concerned, this whole thing about Bob being dead is a ruse.
Bob staged that whole thing himself.
It was fashionable in the 60s.
Bob, Bob, Rob, Rob.
It's the same frontwards and back, friends.
There's a reason there's an O in the middle.
A hole in the middle between those two Bs.
It's symbolic, friends.
You can look through the center of that O in Bob's name and see the future and the past.
But the spice must flow.
Oh.
A woman age 93 was killed on a merry-go-round when she and her wheelchair were thrown from the thing in Sherman's amusement park.
Yankee Doodle went to town riding on a baby
In the corner just in time to see the naked lady
Yankee Doodle went to town riding on a turtle
In the corner just in time to see the lady turtle
Yankee Doodle went to town with a bag of peaches
He rode so fast he was coming back
He smashed some healthy peaches
Yankee Doodle went to town riding on a pony
Riding on a rocket
Bumped into the Alamo and peed on Davy Crockett
You have reached the correct number
However, your call has already been analyzed and rejected
This matter is out of our hands
As soon as we are able to transcend the time problems
Inherent in life on Earth
And gain control of the situation
We will return you to your previously scheduled conversation
If this had been an actual phone call
You would have been instructed to leave your name, number, time, and message
When you hear the tone
Thank you
Uh, reference time, praise Bob
This is Robin Anton Wilson
And about my appearance for the Church of the Subgenius
Jeff Rosenbaum, who arranges
The tours will be calling you about that
Because he has
He's the one who has all the flight plans
And the airline tickets and his controls
He will be the one who will arrange the dates
If you win, I'll be there
And I better shut up because I'm running out of time
Praise Bob
Well, yeah, that's right
That was Robin Anton Wilson
And about ten of you listeners probably know who he is
We have the chance of setting up a lecture
And or show or whatever
With Robin Anton Wilson
He's going to be coming through Texas
To do shows at least in Austin
At the Book People's Bookstore
I know about that one
But we could set one up here in Dallas
But we need like about $450 or $500 front money, see
To get him in
And that's just the cost of the show, basically
So we also need a place to do it
And if anybody is wild and crazy about Robin Anton Wilson
And wants to get real involved in the show
And bringing him to Dallas
Then let us know
For those of you who don't know
He's the author of Illuminatus and Schrodinger's Cat
And several other cosmic science fiction books
That, well, you just have to check them out
But write us here at the station
Or write to Bob
Or call us right now
You can speak to the Will of Dobbs
So we're going to continue here
Oh, right, you're negatively in the background
We have a swimming pool in the background
Well, as a matter of fact, we're going to do a show
So you can hear Dr. Hal Robbins
And Gary Gabroke from the studio
Them and several movie soundtracks
That's what we're doing, is movie soundtracks
You're hearing the soundtrack of Brazil
In stereo
That's why I insist on the headphones
Brazil, Big Trouble in Little China, and Dune
Our favorite sound effects horrors for tonight
So, yeah
Yeah, this is Steve
I'm going to be in town all the time
What are you talking about, man?
But hurry, but hurry, but hurry, but hurry
All right, it's Mike at Jimmy Carr
Oh, too bad we missed you
This is Mike and Pam in Chicago
We didn't know if you had caught Pee Wee's Playhouse this morning
But Bob was prominently displayed on the bulletin board
If you didn't get it, let me know
And I'll send you off a copy
Have a good one, bye
How long have you been in the U.S. of A?
Three months
Where from?
Hong Kong
What happens?
You stay here a while?
Old girls leave, new girls come in?
Maybe
Take your tie off, please
Yeah, I know what you mean
My wife gave it to me for Christmas
Oh, my God
Green explosions
People flying in and out
That was not real
I want to talk to the cops
I want my truck back
Now, where the hell am I?
I want my water
Is this a gas cellar?
No, I still don't
You called after me
I know you miss me
I got a gift from some stick
Cool
What's in my pocket, then?
Well, I hope they'll pay 부 clue
Have as long as you wish
Ow!
Chris...
You injured my eyes and toppled the Louvre.
I think you guys are afraid of J.R. Bob Bob.
You've been doing this show for almost five years now, disrespectfully, making fun of your high E-pop, the man who brought you slack.
I ain't afraid of no pop.
Bob died for your sins.
Nobody knows how many times.
The only thing that ever brought me slack was leaving Paul in St. Louis.
I'm not kidding, Bob.
I was the only slack I ever got out of this damn church, and it cost me $3,000 to have him shipped back.
Well, most people don't fear Bob.
Don't fear him a bit.
Oh, they think Bob's always going to be their buddy.
And then as soon as they think Bob's dead, they turn around.
They think he ain't looking anymore.
They turn around and go.
Go to the pinks.
Go into the pinks, every one of them.
Oh, friends, he's just testing you.
He's been testing you for two years.
He knows if you've been bad or good.
Oh, yeah.
But more people are frightened of Gary than frightened of Bob.
Anybody want to go to an E-pop?
Why does this situation persist?
Well, it's because of the general loss of faith in the companies of modern people.
And the feeling that one can no longer support the fragility, superstition, and fanaticism of an earlier time.
When one might well have believed in the smiling, pipe-smoking, benevolent figure known from the book of the subdues.
That's right.
That was really beautiful.
Very touching.
It was just beautiful.
Could you repeat that?
Everybody welcome.
Now I'm here to talk about the conspiracy again.
As usual.
But I'm talking about a different conspiracy.
This time.
The conspiracy within the church of the subdues.
I was right.
I'm afraid it's true.
There is an answer.
The conspiracy has a way of outweighing the end.
And I think most of you know what I mean by the conspiracy.
I knew God's name.
But he goes back.
He will be on the road.
With no slack.
On the phone.
Oh, Lord.
And he's coming on.
Again.
On the road.
And he's coming again.
If we don't want the answers upon us.
Then we need more to be honest.
On the road.
And he's coming on.
He's coming on.
On the road.
I'm the purple flower of hell.
Give me wide berth.
When I drop my drawers.
Mother Nature swoots.
A six million year cycle will end in 1998.
1998, Bob sees the world entering a new aeon, which, in a few years, will bring more wondrous and miraculous change and carnage, insanity, and destruction than all of mankind's history and prehistory before it.
Bob brings a new destiny for America, a time of cataclysmic economic change that will offer untold riches and power to those in the know, while billions of deserving conspiracy dupes fry in hell on Earth.
Uncontrolled thinking, controlled by Bob, will usher in a spiritual rebreath and a cascade of astounding mysteries.
Supernatural bridges and a restoration of lost psychic abilities will totally transform the lives of those who dare to seek them and pay for them.
That's right, you're lucky to live in the end time.
Here's more money, Bob!
Lies up! They're out to get you!
Moving podium!
Rods!
And having once thought it moves on, I'm not moving.
You know, the subgenius is not just below a genius, whatever that may be.
The subgenius does not pretend to superknowledge, but to subknowledge.
Knowledge of the underthings, the underwear lurking beneath the clothing of existence.
The foundation garment, if you will, underlying reality.
You see, the subgenius is a subgenius.
A strange beast indeed.
Give me a can of sound effects while you're at it, would you?
Oh, yeah, and some show stretchers.
And listen to him.
I need some show stretchers back.
Yes, ma'am.
How about something to eat?
Little did many of you know, but...
Who wants peanuts?
This isn't the only subgenius.
This is the only subgenius show.
In fact, there's six weekly subgenius shows now in New York, Beijing, New Jersey, Richmond, Virginia, St. Louis, Dallas.
Come on, hurry now.
We have to catch the last one.
I gave the anti-virgin a hot protein tassel wash.
I'm a bacteriological weapon.
I'm armed and I'm loaded.
I'm a fission reactor.
I fight plutonium.
Power plants are fueled by the sweat from my brow.
When they plug me in, the lights go out.
In Hong Kong, I weigh 666 pounds and zero gravity.
Come and get me.
Soon, they'll begin to fold space.
Far off in the control rooms of Spice Gas.
Traveling without moving.
Ivan Stang, 15, shows scars after being attacked by an alligator near West Palm Beach, Florida.
On Monday, Ivan and a friend were swimming in a lake when suddenly he was grabbed by the head and pulled underwater by a giant sharp-toothed saurian.
I couldn't see anything but teeth and didn't know what had hold of me until the gator let loose and swam away, said Ivan, who suffered wounds requiring 41 stitches.
This is supposed to be a religious show.
Now, what is the interpretation of this parable, my friends?
The alligator is the worldly mob, the rabble.
The rabble is the world's most powerful.
We seek to devour and assimilate the holy men of the Church of the Subgenius.
The lone swimmer, buoyed up by the fluid element, represents, upon the other hand, the striving outward force of the Church of the Subgenius,
which requires 41 stitches, the same number as the number of bullet holes in Bob's bullet-reddled body.
Praise Bob. Praise Bob. Praise Bob. Praise Bob.
What are we going to do?
Wouldn't you like revenge on these mediocrities?
I wouldn't go that far.
These pink boys, these box-dwelling Barbies and Kens, these normals who have made normality the norm?
Well, no, I wouldn't like revenge on those people.
I'd like revenge on you, Ivan, because you've taken one too many $20 check from me.
I've never done it.
I want my slack.
Let's see your Subgenius membership card, hmm?
Now, let's not get into it.
I mean, say the end times came a little bit soon, Gary.
Do you think you'd make it on the escape saucers of the sex goddesses without your little...
Subgenius membership card?
I'd sure try.
Ah, this is a great example you're setting for the people out here.
I've got my Bob America card here.
It says that I paid up to 1997?
You see, Gary is the Rasputin of the Church of the Subgenius, often thought for, but rarely encountered.
And it is this self-same learning for slack which separates us from them.
At the hip.
The human may live out his entire life in a grinding cycle.
In slacklessness.
Yet he never feels cheated.
He thinks it's natural.
He thinks it's fine.
Who?
Big deal.
Who cares?
Well, dear friends, this is Reverend Ivan Sang.
And we've been getting some calls tonight from people who apparently never heard of the Church of the Subgenius before,
don't know anything about it, don't know that there's acres and acres of reading material available,
which is up at least to the level of the incredible mixing you're hearing on this show.
And you can...
You can write for information.
That's all we can tell you on this station.
For very good reason.
Because you need to send your money to the station.
But you can send your letters of your questions.
Send your questions to Bob.
That's J.R. Bob Dobbs.
And friends, that address is coming up as you stay tuned for Ron Lindsay's Sold Oldies.
Have that pencil ready by now?
Well, you need to write to Bob at P.O. Box.
181.
417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
www.subgenius.com
So friends, your hour of slack is coming to an end.
But be ready for more slack.
More slack dripping and leaking all over you.
Oh, yeah.
I suppose we could get in, but...
They're nothing but half-footed cattle.
Racing each other to be first to the slaughterhouse
and stampeding you along with them.
But what do you care?
Oh, you've got slack.
Slack.
Yeah.
Anybody want to go down the slide?
Oh, get along, little bobbies.
Go head on down to Dobbstown now.
Get on in that Dobbstown corral, you little bobbies.
Bob.
Oh, there's a nice fat one.
Yes, you'll be a good trading commodity
come the bargaining session with the exes.
First up, I noticed y'all don't talk about religion much.
I guess it's real hip out here in California.
It's a more humanistic approach to life.
No, we believe in just letting the holy benediction of Bob
flow out like pus from a bus job.
We just don't understand the true power of religion.
We're looking the wrong way.
It's really up in here right now.
We're not going to think you to even be arias Program today
Now he was a prophet.
I don't hear.
Chaines to say.
I love this principle.
There are a bunch of good things in the world,
and it can be hidden quiet,
but you get
shot every time you make a mistake.
in reverential resignation.
No wish to strive,
no thought expressed,
only a sense of suffocation.
With the groove I only got,
we shall all be moved.
Ready or not,
here we come,
getting down on
the one which we believe in.
Can I get it on my foot?
But thank the God.
I'll come again soon.
One night you will be moved.
I think it's up or down.
He don't tell me now.
Friends, if you're interested in more history
of the Church of the Subgenius,
there will be an online course taught in that.
That's why we're doing these rerun-type shows.
And if you want information about that,
you can check out
maybelogic.org
or even maybelogic.com.
It's MaybeLogic Academy that is doing this.
For information on the Church of the Subgenius,
please look into subgenius.com.
I love you.
Speaking of ancient fossilized subgenius tapes,
I'm going to close with some cuts
from Media Barrage No. 4,
which predates Hour of Slack.
This was put together in late 1980.
And it'll be okay because
remember where Bob is?
Bob is at EO Box 1403-06.
Bob can help you.
That's right.
Thanks, Bob.
Thank you for bringing that joy
and sunshine and blood into my veins
and bringing those pills into my briefcase
where I can get them out and take them
whenever I want.
Yeah, pumping through me.
And I like the pills that Bob sends
because Bob sends pills that make my heart wise.
I have wise blood and family.
It's just one of the wonderful things.
I love to feel the blood that Bob makes me
pump through my brain
because the drugs and, oh, Bob.
I like it.
What if somebody isn't really good with throat noises?
Will you still take their money?
We do not require proof of subgeniusness at all.
We often find that we're able to,
once they join up,
we're able to get them off to one of our subgenius retreats,
change their diet,
start feeding them.
We're able to get them off to one of our subgenius retreats,
and start propaganda,
repeating the same thing over and over again
until they forget who they are
and start responding only to our dogma.
But it's all real.
It's really real.
It was really, really real at the time we were there.
The communications are wide open.
We can hear everything coming down that pike,
coming our way.
And we like to be on the radio
and talk to all the boys and girls
that are all out there.
We're letters.
And keep them cards and letters coming, girls.
And send pictures.
And send pictures of yourselves,
if you know what I mean.
Because we need more girls at the church.
And bring your rich fathers.
And we'll convince them that we're not really that weird.
And we can get some money
and really make him a lot more money.
Because we're a modern mystical business, man.
Marvelous.
The smell of success is never too sweet.
We can help you out.
I think we're being sold a bill.
A big bill of goods.
You can fly to Malaysia and Dobstown.
And you can fly to the special mountaintops
where Bob learns from great holy men
that have helped him along when he was younger.
And now he's teaching them.
And you can be with Bob
and be listening to the teachings
teachings that come through. And I tell you, friends, if you can just get that, if you
can just pull out that wallet, pull it out of your pocket, pull it out of your purse,
pull it out of wherever you got it. You can put one hand on the radio and with the other
one you pull out that dollar bill. And I tell you, if you don't feel that power coursing
from that dollar bill to that radio or that tape recorder or that, whatever you may have.
I mean, some people tell me they hear the voices and they don't have no machine running
at all. The only experiment people can do if they're listening on the radio or on their
tape machine is they can take that dollar bill out of their pocket and hold it by one
end above the machine that they're listening on, whether it be the radio or the tape recorder.
Hold it there on one end with two hands, right? One grasp on each corner and hold it above
the machine and you'll notice that it bends down and points towards the radio. It will
point. It will point. It will point. It will point. It will point. It will point. It will
point down towards that, down toward the center of that machine, right where the real
power is meeting the wires and it's all coming together. It's coming out of the reality of
the physical world and turning into the spirit world. And there's a bridge there and Bob
can help you make that bridge to where the physical world don't no longer mean nothing
to you and that dollar bill won't mean nothing to you. And friend, I'm telling you that in
five years that dollar bill ain't going to mean nothing in the spirit world, the physical
world.
The physical world on a mental world to anybody doesn't mean anything. Now it, it, it means
very little. It can mean a bottle of beer for some lost individual. It can mean a cigarette
or two. It can mean enough gas to get you back home from the gas station. Sure. But
I tell you what, when that tribulation money starts coming down, you're going to find out
that those little green pieces of paper made by made by the clones in Washington, the people
that there aren't people there, they're making that stuff and it ain't going to be worth
nothing.
You can't, you can't, you can't, you can't, you can't, you can't, you can't, you can't
sleep on it. You can't burn fires with it. You can't stay warm with that. You have to
have too much of it. But I tell you what you don't need too much of. And that's, that's
the word of Bob.