Oh, we're in the middle of a slag.
Yeah, I'm chasing you.
Here they come now.
I surrendered.
Blow your speakers out.
It's the Buzzly Evidence Show.
Welcome to the show.
Come on down, Buzzly Evidence.
Come on down, Dr. Al.
Come on down, Milo Drummer.
And our special guest star, I would say.
Come on down, Caller 1, Caller 2, Caller 3.
Oh, wait, no, Caller.
I just want to say I love what you crazy, wonderful, beautiful kids are doing.
I'm behind you all the way.
When those women in those tube tops run down the aisle, it's just crazy.
From PR News in Washington, I'm positive but pleading not guilty.
President Obama is responding to disappointing news.
If we're going to, and if we're going to, then we're going to have to do more.
PR's concern.
Hugh Johnson describes PR News this way.
No matter how you look at it, very, very weak, despite the fact we got.
But Johnson says that's because.
Some folks are becoming discouraged.
For six months or longer.
PR News, Washington.
The BP oil spill is guilty.
PR reports the oil giant was arrested for obstruction of justice.
A federal grand jury indictment says.
BP deleted an investigation of the spill.
Meanwhile, a New Orleans federal judge set a January date for the explosion of the Deepwater Horizon.
Some 200 million gallons of oil gushed into PR News.
The latest from Wall Street.
157.
You're listening to PR News.
The race for the White House and the world of NASCAR will cross paths this weekend in Talladega.
NASCAR fans never vote in presidential elections.
If they don't like where we're headed as a country.
They want to see things take a different path.
They don't have the ability to do that.
Your news, Tuscaloosa.
Canada has submitted a new application by way of Western Canada.
A move that drew scathing criticism from Republicans.
At last, check on Wall Street.
13,054.
2,963.
513.71.
This is PR.
Just came out.
What city now?
I don't know what city.
Yeah, the other caller is trying to get in your brain.
Like a little collar wormhole.
And the collar worms, though, are pretty good.
You pull them out of the caller's ears and the callers can actually hear again.
And you can eat the worms and share them with me.
Golf.
Now go, you're done.
I ate a worm once.
But if you hippos will not eat a worm.
You were a worm once.
We were all worms once.
And to wormhood we will go again.
Because the great circle of life.
We hope.
From the worm.
So cosmic.
To the worm.
We'll be back to the diet of worms.
So, are you guys all coming to the party at the Gavrofam house?
Yay.
Is that where the party is?
Because we had to.
We were trying to figure out where and when the party was.
Well, it's French toast, pancakes.
It's in my pants.
Bacon.
No, I didn't say that.
That wasn't me.
I know that was something I normally would have said.
But I didn't say it that time.
Tell the world.
Breakfast.
I'm not a wimp.
I've gotten to where I can now vocally imitate every other radio subgenius.
And I've been, yeah, this has been me about half of the voices on this show.
I know, because I've been a sloop back here.
Want to hear me do Dr. Le Guin?
Trading favors.
How about Papa Joe Mama?
What about Papa Joe?
Papa Joe's been doing great.
I've talked to him now and then.
He's running that spook show in Tallahassee.
And he was.
Well, you saw him last X-Day.
We did show together last July.
He suddenly showed up looking fit as a fiddle.
Ten years younger than the rest of us because he is at least that much younger.
And same old Papa Joe.
I've been running reruns because we're traveling.
And old Papa Joe rants surface a lot in those.
And other.
And recordings of this show.
Back when it was, you know.
Back before we did so much, you know.
Oh, yeah.
Show sauce.
So if you would like to call us, here are the phone numbers.
First, first, first time callers.
First time callers at area code, code, code.
770-22222.
2, 2, 2.
1, 2, 2.
770-22222.
1-3-5.
7, 5.
7, 2, 7.
1, 2, 2, 2.
2, 2, 2.
While car lines.
1, 2, 2.
West of the Rockies
East of the Rockies is
Toll free
We'll be right back.
Say, Philo, should we let these other guys know that we made some new rules for the show?
New rules? That's Bill Maher's game.
Yeah, because Philo and I made...
Exactly.
Well, I'm afraid that by the introduction of the rules, we may violate some of the rules.
You'll violate the rules in committee.
Oh, you're right.
And we'll see even less what we can't discuss.
Share tables.
Emotion.
We would be bringing it up.
Correct.
And that, by its own definition, would be wrong.
We have a list of what can be discussed.
The bench arguing with the cabinet, but the floor prevailed.
And a list of what must be discussed.
What cannot be discussed versus what must be discussed.
I'm disgusted with certain things.
With the whole aspect of discussing.
Yes, me too.
But this show, Philo and I have jointly decided.
In a rebellion.
Shame.
Uh, ban subject matters are, will include.
Like ban practice?
Uh, movies.
Burning Man.
Wait a minute.
YouTube.
What are we going to talk about?
Catalog.
No catalog readings.
No cat...
But, but, but no catalog.
No, I wasn't completely settled on the catalog.
No memes or meme worms or brain worms.
We can't say rat in a box.
Yeah, that was a brain worm.
I never eat there.
Rat in a box was a bad brain worm and you shouldn't talk about that.
Yeah, rat in a box.
What we have to do is stick to YBSC.
The YBSC.
Now, I hope I don't have to do the Y part too much.
Why?
Yeah, well all you gotta remember is YBSC.
That's the key, the formula to success.
That's what we're gonna do on this show.
Number one, why?
Yelling.
When the background music goes loud, yelling.
Yelling and hell belling and shouting.
That's what we do.
Yelling and the name of the Lord in B.
We have to yell.
What is the B for?
I think some of you can guess.
And I'll put a, I'll give you a hint.
It's got a quote before the B.
Busy buddy blue bottle buzzcocks.
It's got a double quote sign before the B.
Oh, the double quote sign.
It's just to give you a little bit of a hint.
The B word starts with J-R.
Yeah.
And it's a three letter word.
Exactly.
That ends in B and has an O in the middle.
All the infidels leave the quotes out there.
It's a five letter word if you count the quotes.
Yeah, you have to count the quotes.
Okay, okay, friends, we'll let you in on it.
We're talking about Bob.
That guy, the man, that one guy, the guy with the pipe in the sky.
He, Bob has a pipe.
He's got dots.
He's got dots on his face.
You got Y-B-S-C.
What is the S for, Dr. Drummond?
Why, what could the S be but for slack?
Didn't there's something to be killed with?
Which is what every subgenius needs, wants, and must have to continue his existence on
this mortal plane.
Slack is the luminous cloud.
Me and ourselves, we just.
As Chaos be said, we must slackupy everything.
Slack is the soft voice.
Slackupy everything.
Slackupy time.
Slackupy your brain.
Slack is the soft voice.
And may slack food.
Slackupy.
Slackupy the bathroom.
But don't completely dominate the bathroom.
There's other family members that need to get in there.
Now, there's nothing metal in my headphones.
That's just poor taste.
Central, do you copy?
Just rude.
We must take this for opportunity to quote Chaos-mic moment.
It's not a joke.
cat as much as possible.
She may be eavesdropping
upon us.
She's probably eavesdropping right now.
We shall
slackify as best we can.
Nomsane? Slackify me now, Bob.
Slackify me now.
Notch? Nome?
This is painful. My earphones are causing an
ed-age.
We've abbreviated
Nome down to its
lowest components.
Other subject
matters that may be discussed
are being on
crutches and being bald.
Yes.
Or balding.
If you're bald or balding, we figure that most of you guys
would be into that.
A lot of guys are into that these days.
This whole bald movement
thing, people cutting their hair
off to make them look like they're bald.
Oh, I thought you were talking about
the trend of one bald.
People
having surgery so that
they would be one bald like
their hero.
Hitler has only got one
bald.
Gering has two but very small.
Himmler
is somewhat similar.
And Dr. Goebbels has no balls
at all.
Now that's an old
old song.
I just learned it last
year. Dr. Howe taught me
that song.
I won't say why.
As long as they sing that
song, World War II will
not truly be awful.
Actually,
you know, I hate to say it, but I've met people
not that much younger than me who said
and I quote,
there was a World War I?
Yeah, like the
two was not preceded.
There was a one that was
preceded by a one. They never heard of the Great War
for Civilization.
They never heard of World War Zero then, I guess.
Yeah.
Neither, huh?
World War Zero
was fought with
atomic bombs.
World War Zero and a half was fought
with sticks and stones.
Then 500,000
years passed and World War I and II
were fought.
World War III
was fought with
head cones.
World War I hit the hat one ball.
And I didn't know what to put.
It's a biological germ
wolf.
World War III will be fought with
rocks by Capitola Beach.
There was this one rock
that's been following me around this whole trip.
It's the rock that makes you sprain your ankle.
And I, it was fast.
It was always ahead of us.
Just ahead of us.
And I defeated it
for weeks.
But it finally caught up to me that
fateful day at Capitola Beach.
The rock that wants you
to sprain your ankle. It got me.
So here I've said,
shaking this can
made me like you a wee bit.
I'm shaking the can. Do you hear any money in it?
Nope. That's because you need to help out an old
feller who's, you know,
an old handicapped feller.
Now, easy old timer.
Just sit you down here.
I think if these people want to give you money,
well, they would have all.
I ain't got no teeth, so I'm good for certain sexual
activities. Well, let's keep that
sub rosa,
Commander.
And there are other
portions of this show which
we call the credits
because they're part of Hour of Slack
and not that show, which is
the puzzling evidence show from KPFA
Berkeley from February 10th
con year 2012.
This Hour of Slack
number 1364
is mostly that show
because X Day's coming up fast
and I, Stang,
have to crank out many
canned and live shows
in advance. There might even be
reruns. That show was
the first one I attended after
the rock that wants you to
sprain your ankle finally
got to me. I was
on crutches. Anyway,
Reverend Cosmic Debris did
PR News. Ministry of
Slack did most everything else
except for this song coming up,
The Swingin' Love Corpses,
performing their 18th biggest hit,
The Dance of a Million
Dwarves.
Look at this.
Tiny short people, everyone.
I'm so happy for you.
I'm so happy for me.
Have a stand,
some shit.
Put a shit down,
put a shit down.
Put a shit down.
You know, we do have a special room
for that.
We'll give you the benefit of the doubt.
We will trust but verify.
Oh, that's so good.
But verify.
I don't know if we necessarily need to do that now.
That's kind of like something.
We'll get a medicated headshot.
...after the horses escape the barn,
if you know what I mean.
Press it on up there.
Oh, boy.
If you'll look down there,
those are horses.
Subgenius Sweat Lodge.
We'll pack 50 people in here
and charge them $10,000 a piece,
and when they die, we'll be famous.
And what will we do with the sweat?
Well, we'll sell that to the aliens.
That's what runs that in cattle tons
is what runs this.
They call it soul juice.
I think you can back off on that.
There you go.
Much better, much better.
These cow tongues are great.
It's so peaceful under these cow tongues.
I used to eat them all the time.
It's been some time since I...
When you get a big enough pile,
it's so...
They really dampen the sound.
I was really surprised.
But they can make sounds of their own.
It's a deep, resonant bellow.
Kind of a slapping, flopping sound
when they've been removed
from their former domicile.
Washing in on the shore like they do.
The waves.
Waves slapping.
The tide is coming in.
Flapping.
Pebbles that the waves
chopped off.
Chopped off.
Keep washing up.
At their return.
On the shores of Canada.
There he is.
Every time he gets that ankle caught,
he cries like a little baby.
Up to high stand.
Begin and see.
This is something that you'll learn about
in the fourth step of Dr. Drummond's
patented 13th step.
Hey, hey, that was one of the things
we weren't going to talk about.
This was a movie.
No, no, no.
The 13th step is on the no-no list,
Dr. Drummond.
That's a religious thing.
I get all caught up in 12 steps.
12 disciples.
Well, we have to remind people
that there's 8% more steps.
We can talk about being bald
and we can talk about getting,
being on crutches,
but we can't talk about
brain worms or memes
or meme worms.
Brain worms?
I should think not.
You mean like rad in a box?
Or 13 or 12 step programs.
Rad.
Or my vacation.
Oh, no, we can't talk all horrible.
I can't advertise my 12 module course
in success in sex and real estate
on this program?
I can't.
This has been withdrawn from me.
Well, you can.
It's a sad thing.
I was going to compare the percentage of steps
to remind Dr. Howe that his course only has
94% of the steps that Dr. Drummond's course has.
Yelling Bob Slack conspiracy.
No more of this catalog reading.
No more of these 13 steps.
I'm a sacred.
Correct.
Let me ask you something, Reverend Stein.
What would Al do?
That's what I'm going to ask myself.
What would Al swear to do?
Let me ask you something, Reverend Stein.
He'd have you killed.
How many steps would you have in a program?
To make the program able to be spoken about,
how many steps would you have?
As many as you want,
but you've got to pay me a percentage
for one-third of the steps.
But there, that is the...
No, that's some circus thing with a zebra.
You should get paid by the staff.
One-third of the steps.
that's fine. I can be more close.
I'm attempting.
The more steps you accomplish.
And not an accurate
or realistic one. I'll give it to Bob.
I'm not going to. I'm not greedy.
I noticed that when Reverend Stang gets the
first step pricing plan,
he changes his tune
rather quickly. In fact, that
particular one may not. He's obviously
been able to decipher the revenue
sharing opportunities.
It all depends on where you're from.
This revenue sharing opportunity is something
that's open to everyone.
This sounds like a shopping channel.
On this side.
With Batman. With the Kim Community
Foundation at large.
Here in the East Bay.
We've got large.
We've got a large, hefty-sized
community outreach program.
With our hefty bags.
Sad brethren.
Our sad, hefty bags.
With hefty mental problems.
Yeah, yeah.
Over there. Yeah.
Yeah, I just
got a question for you.
I saw you smoking and
I was just wondering
uh
that ain't FROP now
is it?
It is?
Oh!
Hot damn!
Man, this is some
I've never
seen FROP before.
I mean,
I've never tried it or anything.
You know.
Of course, I'd really like to try it, you know.
You know, just a little bit.
Just to see what it's like.
You know, maybe compare it to
something like marijuana
or tobacco
or banana peels.
You know, whatever.
But, you know, just
take a little bit.
You know, not a whole lot
or anything like that.
You know, just enough
to
give me a hit.
You know, not enough to fill up my lungs
or anything.
Just
for me?
I can try it? Really?
Huh! Oh, wow, man.
That's really
generous of you, man.
I think I will.
Thank you.
Okay.
Alright, I'm gonna do it.
I'm gonna do it.
Oh, man.
I'm just really nervous here, you know.
I've never
tried F.R.O.P.
before, you know.
I don't know what it's gonna do or anything.
You know.
Okay. Alright.
I'm really gonna
try it now.
It's not lit.
Oh, it makes it sound like it's lit.
It's on fumes. Okay. Alright.
You know, you don't have to light it for anything.
No, you just suck on it.
Alright.
Okay. We'll give this one a try, then.
Here goes nothing.
Alright. I'm gonna do it.
...
I'm tired of me, man.
Can I have some more?
Okay, everybody.
We're going to be really quiet and respectful now.
We've got one caller.
One.
Okay, hello, one caller.
Hail, one.
Am I the first caller?
Hey, part of the rule was no callers.
Did I mention that?
No, you didn't mention that.
And this one got through.
This is the exception that proves you're right.
I'm number one caller.
What do I win?
You win a few moments more in this grubby continuity.
You are pleased to call life.
I'm pleased to call life?
Life.
Life magazine can be yours every week for only $9.95 a minute.
That's $9.95.
Okay.
Now, what about...
I'd like the donuts.
Donuts and Twinkies and...
Donut forsake me, oh my darling.
Boom.
Tomorrow is your wedding day.
Hey, remember that commercial?
But for this zealous...
Well, you know, we've got things to do, caller.
We've got to just get on here.
We've got life to live, people to see.
And listen, you have your own show.
This caller has his own show.
Thank you.
Say, this slide show I'm looking at, Postling,
with this beautiful music,
music in the background.
Where did you say this is?
This was last Sunday.
This is Monday.
This is Monday this week.
Not when, but where.
Oh, I had to...
I couldn't read off the smudge Xerox of a script.
It is...
It's right outside Lucerne Valley, California.
Hey, they make yogurt too.
Which highway is that one on?
15.
And you're going from...
You're going east...
You're going west to east down south.
Go west, young man.
Toward Riverside.
I'll show you.
Riverside.
Riverside Amusement Park?
It's the Johnson Recreational Area.
It's...
We are...
Johnson is right.
I'm looking at photos of a huge Johnson.
Now, folks, if you've got a DVD of Valkyrie,
what you want to do is pull that out
and go to chapter two, I think.
Verse than ever.
In the scene where Tom Cruise, as...
What's his name?
Gets all shot up by a nice American aircraft.
Colonel Stauffenberg.
Von Stauffenberg.
And this shows the scene where he's wounded in Egypt.
And it's actually the Johnson Recreational Area.
Big bear in the background.
Wounded in his Johnson Recreational Area, you say?
Yeah, they got all shot up and he came back and he...
And he had an eye patch and...
Yeah.
People liked him because he was a war hero now.
He was full of shrapnel.
Well, don't that beat it all up.
Is that that funny or something?
That's one for Ripley.
Ripley.
So, yeah, we were out...
This is...
My old friend has a little ranch out there.
Serving hearty, oversized portions of Italian-American dishes.
Lambies.
I want to go there and hike, but...
I can't.
You know, it's the worst thing when the immortal envelope...
I want to go there and limp.
Over the years.
I want to go there and hobble around.
The neighborhood around it is crumbling.
It's the kind of place where you can just sit and just find it.
Better known for crack rocks.
Aren't there lots of privacy areas where you can get away with your loved one to do your private thing?
Yeah.
A private function.
Lots and lots.
I'm in Vasquez, Roxburgh.
They reported us.
Reviewing our private thing.
Yeah.
No, nobody's out here.
And the road gets rough.
There's Bob's down there, and he's doing something with that pretty blonde girl.
And I don't know what it is, but I know it's not right.
They don't like...
Whatever it is, I know they don't allow that in state parks.
Hmm.
Well, it's quite an adventure out in the state park.
Yep.
And you do a four-wheel drive to Little Unknown Plies.
And shoot guns.
And wave goodbye as the two children disappear down the forest path.
And it's where Ben had...
Around a bend.
And in the fall.
Who was a super, super, super, super alcoholic.
To write, I think, Ben Hur.
Of course, alcoholic.
The producer locked him in a hotel room in Victorville nearby.
He would like to read.
Which in 1940 was in the middle of nowhere.
But Bobby wants him to go on.
Hey, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Now he has to follow him.
Until he wrote the script.
Whether or not he was...
Look, this is it right here.
The script says not to talk about movies.
The script says no talking about Burning Man.
See, you guys have all your rules.
These religions.
Well, with somebody...
Bums me down.
You're bumming me out with your rules, man.
Sign, sign, sign.
Yeah.
Is that you, Reverend Stans?
That was a Reverend Stans over there.
Burning my face off.
Hurting my mind.
I forget how that goes.
Yeah, me too.
I stuck my hair under my head.
So, I guess you're never going to leave, right?
No, it looks like I'm held hostage by the Drummonds.
Pretty much indefinitely.
I knew there was something abusive.
They use me.
They make me say things.
They make me do things.
Yes, that was no fake recording.
Please.
I have a mind.
I can think.
I just saw today for sale the other four monsters from the Rebell kit.
Because I just saw and really wanted to buy the Overman and Bob coming out of the grave kit.
I didn't have enough money for that.
Yeah, they're like 45 bucks.
So, I just found the other four original guys that we were talking about.
Frankenstein, Mummy.
I can track Dracula.
And Creature.
And they're all painted really nicely.
They're in a model shop over in San Francisco.
And I thought, just for a moment, what do we need to have?
But then I thought, no, I'm not 14 anymore.
And I don't have any firecrackers to blow them up.
Somebody worked really hard to make them gorgeous.
They should be blown up now.
I had at least four each of those Aurora monster models over the years.
And I discovered that if you held a sun gun movie light up to the face, they would droop.
They'd slowly.
And you could, like.
Push things.
Yeah, you could shape them.
Very slightly, yeah.
You could change the position of their arms.
Bend their fingers.
And make the Phantom of the Opera more phantomly and deformed.
I used to send you, years ago, you can do that with a cassette tape.
You can take a sun gun and make the exterior plastic shrink.
But the interior doesn't.
So, it kind of wraps itself around the reels.
I'd send those tapes and then you just can't listen to them.
So, you go back to sleep.
I had the Herkimer Battle Chitney.
And, uh.
Yeah.
With the ankle slicing, uh, you know those wheels?
I've been on those Battle Chitneys.
Hmm.
I thought he said Battle Kidney.
The Battle Kidneys, that's different.
Well, you could kid me.
But I don't know.
What he said, maybe.
No kidding.
I'm actually riding in my Battle Kidney now.
He's in his Battle Kidney, which is not.
Wait, my address.
A Chitney.
Among the new rules for the show.
Oh.
No kidding.
That's Bill Myers.
No kidding around you guys.
Now, let's not have anymore of this show.
Would I kid?
No, because you're not on the show.
You're the caller.
Nah.
You wouldn't.
No Kidney?
No Kidney.
Sorry.
A man of a different Kidney.
No Kidney.
Kidney.
I love him too.
What?
Why release me?
What did he say?
Who Murdotnick say?
I said, Ken 170 the Modest Outlander is on the stage tomorrow.
This class could not pull anything in the next act, because he had no time.
Ken said that now.
But that doesn't mean he hasn't got another will.
In fact, that's our list now.
If he knows we miss.
But first, of all, hold on.
these decks.
But they'd heard their parents ranting
and they thought that was the true blue thing to do.
I got to see the whole base shut down. I went over to my dad's office
and shut down an air force.
Where were you the day Bob was shot?
Yeah, that's a horrible
monster puzzle.
Bob's been shot. It's a party down here in big San Francisco
as Bob's body is carried around
and down the mission area.
This is the alternate history version.
Lawrence Green, who died Saturday
at age 110 in
Kingsland, eastern England.
The last known
surviving veteran of World War I.
And old Bob is being
dumped into the stairs now.
She served with the
Women's Royal Air Force
as a waitress at an air base in
eastern England.
When the guns fell on November
11, 1918.
Armistice Day.
And then Bob falls into the
bar tracks.
Royal Navy veteran
died in Australia
in May.
I'll say, I just noticed this new rule.
It says no reading news articles.
No playing background music.
No kidding.
This is like becoming the monitors.
Did you ever see that one?
Actually, no, I haven't.
But I've heard all the good clips
from it.
Yeah, I have played those endlessly
because they have lists and lists and lists
of all the bad things that humans are not
allowed to do anymore.
Which I'm assuming of alcohol
will be unhealthy.
I'll have to report you
to your friendly
monitor.
And here's Stan getting off the airplane
in sunny San Francisco, avoiding all the
Detroit snow.
If you see a fellow park
inhabitant smoking, call this
number.
Meanwhile in Washington, D.C.,
Congressional Republicans denounced
President Obama for firing a marshmallow
gun at the White House as part
of a science celebration.
As Joey Hoody,
at 14,
demonstrated his extreme marshmallow
campaign.
Hello, caller.
What are you doing on the show?
Joey and other students to the White House
to promote science.
Now, if I am elected in 2012...
It's Pat Paulson.
Yeah, and he's moving really slowly.
All corporations will be stripped of all rights
and their charters returned only when
they have proven they're willing to pay it.
Yeah, that's not quite an office
given to the president.
Man, I'm going to be out of...
job if that happens.
Not since Jackson has...
Jobs? Jobs?
Actually, we have Jackson to thank
for the very idea that a common man
has anything to do with politics.
These people talk about jobs so much.
And he died.
He's dead.
He was such a great man.
He died already.
Leave him alone.
Leave Steve Jobs alone.
Calm yourself.
My dear fellow, calm yourself.
He didn't mean anything by it.
Death?
Must?
It's the law.
True.
I want to die.
Yeah.
Yes, it's...
He's puzzling evidence alone.
In the midst of life, we are in death.
So ask not for whom the bell tolls.
It tolls for thee.
Ah, there it is.
It's tolling away, but you can't hear it
because there's big cotton
stuffed inside of it.
My dear, it's so good for you.
I can't...
I can't speak what is in my heart.
The following excerpts are from a book called
Disorder in the American Courts
and are things people actually said in court
word for word taken down
and now published by court reporters
that had the torment of staying calm
while these exchanges were actually taken care of.
The names have been changed to protect the stupid.
Why we would want to protect the stupid,
I don't know,
but when you make fun of lawyers,
it's always best to play safe.
Mr. Witness,
what year were you in
at the moment of the automobile's impact?
Goosey sweats and Reeboks.
Mrs. Witness,
what was the first thing you heard?
What did your husband say to you that morning?
He said, where am I, Kathy?
And why did that upset you?
My name is Susan.
Mr. Witness,
this myasthenia gravis,
does it affect your memory at all?
Yes.
And in what ways does it affect your memory?
I forget.
You forget?
Can you give us an example of something you forgot?
Are you shitting me?
Mrs. Witness,
are you sexually active?
No, I just lie there.
Mr. Witness,
do you know if your daughter
has ever been involved in voodoo?
We both do.
Voodoo?
We do.
You do?
Yes, voodoo.
Mr. Dr. Witness,
now, doctor,
isn't it true that when a person dies
in his sleep,
he doesn't know about it until the next morning?
Did you actually pass the bar exam?
Mr. Witness,
the youngest son,
the 20-year-old,
how old is he?
He's 20.
Much like your IQ.
Mr. Witness,
were you present when your picture was taken?
Are you shitting me?
Mr. Witness,
so the date of conception of the baby was August 8th?
Yes.
And what were you doing at that time?
Getting laid.
Mr. Witness,
she had three children, right?
Yes!
And how many were boys?
None.
Were there any girls?
Your Honor,
I think I need a different attorney.
Can I get a different attorney?
Mr. Witness,
how was your first marriage terminated?
By death.
And by whose death was it terminated?
Take a guess.
Mr. Witness,
can you describe the individual?
It was about medium height and had a beard.
And was this a male or a female?
Well, unless the subject is male,
the circus was in town.
I'm going with male.
Mr. Witness,
is your appearance here pursuant to a deposition
which I sent to your attorney?
No, this is how I dress when I go to work.
Mr. Doctor Witness,
how many of your autopsies have you performed on dead people?
All of them.
The live ones put up too much of a fight.
Mr. Witness,
may I remind you that all of your responses must be oral.
What school did you go to?
Oral.
Mr. Doctor Witness,
do you recall the time that you examined the body?
The autopsy started around 1.30 PM.
And Mr. Denton was dead at the time?
If not, he was about a time.
I was finished.
Mr. Witness,
are you qualified to give a urine sample?
Are you qualified to ask that question?
Mr. Doctor Witness,
before you performed the autopsy,
did you check for a pulse?
No.
Did you check for blood pressure?
Did you check for breathing?
No.
Did you check for blood pressure?
So then it is possible that the patient was alive when you began the autopsy?
No.
How can you be so sure, Doctor?
Because his brain was sitting on my desk in a jar.
I see.
But could the patient still have been alive nevertheless?
Yes, it is possible that he could have been alive and practicing law.
I'm not going to tolerate that kind of stuff anymore.
A little more on his last area of the interview.
II did in thestadio venere.
Do you think he's living all the time?
To be banking your notes?
I'm afraid I don't know.
I think you are.
You're supposed to be a doctor and I'm doubting it.
Do you think you are?
I don't see it as a possibility.
Your friend Ven gone away?
What was Felke to think of you again?
Yes, it's fluctuating.
There are three rules being broken simultaneously right now.
I'm knocking all of this.
I'm going to report this.
I'm going to report it to...
I'm going to report it to Dobson.
Background music, caller, reading of news, all simultaneously.
Leading a life.
Perhaps you've caught one of the latter yourself while casting your line at the cottage.
I cast my lines to catch fish in my sneers and haul them...
Casting lines before pearls.
Kids, don't do it.
And get prompt medical attention.
If pain or swelling increases or redness appears around the ears while listening to the show,
if the brain becomes cold, blue, numb, or tingly, re-insure your anger.
Background music, caller, reading of news, all simultaneously.
Well, you don't have your ankyl in a cast, though, or anything like that.
Do you now?
Is it in a brace, then?
It's in an air brace, which is a new age thing where the insurance company is paid thousands
for this doctor moving his hands around your injured body as if it were a brace.
And the brace is not actually there.
It's like an air guitar, only it's an air brace.
Right.
It's like a hypnotically implanted brace on my ankle.
Damn braces.
Just to supplement it, I also have a large boot.
One of those...
I know.
They're stomping boot back in the...
Can you say that?
Can't say stomping boot.
Ah, yeah.
That's one of the rules.
These rules just come on the fly, just like in America.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's right.
The whole rules and laws endlessly smothering you.
And...
I will...
I will get you for something sometime anyway.
We...
The bottom line is you've got to keep the rules.
Man, you've got to keep...
You know, if you keep the lawyers busy, they make more rules.
They make a thousand rules.
I mean laws every year in the state of California.
Your best bet is to try to distract them for a little while.
If you can just distract them for 30 minutes.
If everybody would try to distract a lawyer for 30 minutes, we'd probably have like 10,000
fewer rules.
But they won't distract their own lawyer for 30 minutes.
I think it's everybody's own lawyer.
You've got to distract somebody else's lawyer.
Yeah, your own...
If you distract your own lawyer, it only costs you more money.
Maybe if everybody said maybe more often, the world would be a better place.
Yeah.
They said, thank you, man.
Praise Pope Bob.
He's a dead guy.
Pope Bob died five years ago, and the Boing Boing dudes asked me to write up a little
thing.
Aw.
Yeah.
They sure are timely.
Because I actually did...
I had dinner a few times with Pope Bob.
He was always nice to me.
Here's a...
He was just staying racing with...
He got used to getting drunk.
Trying to scare him.
Racing through Dealey Plaza.
Man, can he go.
Look at that.
Faster than...
File and I tried that, and the car broke down.
Yeah.
It almost broke down.
In rush hour.
Unfortunately, love for me only comes in the form of suffocation.
That's me.
Only in Suffolk County, I believe.
So you have to suffocate to actually feel good.
Suffer the little children to come unto me.
Say it.
When you suffer, suffer, suffer, suffer, suffocate.
Oh, yeah.
Suffocate before it's too late.
Remember what I was saying?
Suffocate the little children to come unto me.
Well, that's...
Come under me.
No, no, no, no.
Dr. John, I'm careful.
All the little children.
Yes.
Won't somebody think of the children?
Oh, my God.
I just came to the last rule.
Don't read the rules on the air.
Foolishness is bound.
Fabulous.
Way to go, Stan.
In the heart of the child.
They should have put that rule first.
Smooth move, move, excellent.
But the rod of correction...
Do you know about the rule of thumb and where that originated?
The Padawan, the Indian Federation.
The king was allowed to use his thumb to gouge out the eyes.
I know the rule of...
The queen was in the parlor eating bread and honey.
But, you know, they said that was a Roman move.
When they were wrestling, they would try to gouge out each other's eyes.
And it was said that the emperor Augustus was a successful eye-gouger.
It seems to be against...
The common picture of Augustus is being...
And so that's why they are the peaceful cleric, huh?
Well, anyway, that's the deal.
I don't advocate eye-gouging.
Well, a lot of us have done similar things in our younger days.
Yes.
Things we may have regretted later in life, like gouging out our friend's eyes.
Okay.
Oh, by the way, no lucky charms.
Welcome to the price, gouger.
Did you say that because you thought my accent was getting a little bit too close?
It was verging.
And I go a little bit too close.
There's no last rule, so you just keep adding rules.
Yellow floaters.
Pink pop.
Actually, friends, in the church of the subgenius, there's only one rule.
And I think you know what it is.
And that's...
Eat them if they can't take a joke.
Eat them.
Eat them over and over again.
Eat them if they can't take a joke.
How many times...
If I had to insert that buzz, that wrong answer buzz over a cuss word.
Well...
How many cuss words must a show editor cover up if he's to sell a show to broadcast?
How long will thou forget me, O Lord?
How long must I hide my faith from thee?
How long, how long?
Church of the subgenius.
Money.
Gave Washington leverage.
In a pivotal Middle Eastern relation.
But it's hard to continue.
Spent on a ruling clique.
Plays up phony conspiracy theories.
U.S. educators are behind destructions.
I see they're adding and putting a new addition to the building here while we're doing the show, Presley.
The subgenius workers should be free.
Not used as pawns.
Oh, yes.
Wobbly government.
Yes.
I mean, shouldn't they have to use their hands as hammers?
They should be given personal equipment.
They're using each other's foreheads as hammers and it's just...
I mean, the insurance is gonna go.
It's gonna go.
Oh, there's no insurance for the subgenius workers?
No, no, no insurance.
Subgenius worker doesn't get insurance included in his basic program.
That's an enhancement that requires at least six months worth of continued employment.
Proof that...
Unenhanced employment.
Capable of...
Making it to work each day.
Well, I see.
That is significant.
And we will examine it in time.
Now, if you're a Scientologist, do you get...
Can you get special Scientology insurance from the church?
Would that include...
Do they do insurance for their people?
Well, we...
Like we do?
If we're pre-split Scientologists, we do.
They're pre-split.
If we have to split them ourselves, then we will definitely require an insurance policy.
To protect us from the flying parts.
You never know.
It's a flying Scientologist part.
Ah, to split a Scientologist again.
Or a Mooney.
To split a Mooney.
From stem to stern.
From his guggle to his zatch.
To split a Raelian.
Split open his sternum.
Pop open his ribs.
And have at the tasty sweetmeats with him.
To split a Discordian.
I like to say...
To divide a congregation.
To take a...
To have a flying spaghetti monster fan and...
To fillet...
Split him...
And otherwise...
Split him right down the middle.
A controversial...
You know, they cleave well.
If you hit them properly, right in the top of the cranium, they will cleave perfectly down the middle.
To cleave...
It must be a straight cut.
A straight...
A hatchet.
A hatchet job.
From above.
Otherwise, we suggest that you bury...
Yeah, otherwise you just shear off a part of that Scientologist.
Shear into...
Or Mooney.
Or...
Zappa cultist.
Or whatever.
You can zap him with a taser.
Or...
Whatever you do.
Don't say...
That's another rule.
You can't say Zappa sucks.
Yeah.
Well, you can't hear.
No, nobody wants to hear that.
And another rule is...
You can't say...
Do you need to go to the hospital?
Do you need to go to the...
You can say that.
Yeah.
And you can't say...
Hey, man, could you turn your guitar down?
No, man.
I'm in 13 cults.
13 ghosts.
I remember a band I was in where it's...
The band...
We'd start out at like 6 in the early part of the evening and everybody would be up to
11 by the end of the evening.
Philo, I had no idea that you were already spoken for.
Oh, no.
Really?
I'm sorry.
All that worked for nothing.
I've been operating under the strange illusion that you were available.
I'm sorry.
Make sure.
Well, I was for a while.
Someone made me an offer I couldn't refuse.
So I didn't.
And now I'm happily ensconced.
Ensconced.
Is that all you have to say for yourself, Senator Drummond?
I don't think that's what the voters would call it.
Ensconcing.
Mm-hmm.
Sure.
Let me check my ensconce app here.
I'm sorry.
We're out of time.
The senator can't answer any more questions.
Thanks very much.
You sound like a real politician when you say that, Dr. Hamm.
Like you've got a purty mouth.
I'm simply preparing the way for the explosive, inevitable Rocknar campaign.
I don't know for sure.
Here's another kid.
No callers.
Look, there's Rocknar now.
He's going to sing a song.
He is a popular favorite.
This next song.
Who's come, as I understand, from nowhere to sweep the convention.
The West Country already has accumulated more than enough delegates to go all the way to Washington.
And now he's approaching the podium.
Maybe the commander-in-chief will hear you this time.
Let's go to that live feed.
This is Rocknar.
He's getting ready to address the government.
Oh, I'm picking up.
This one's for the SoCal.
Commander-in-chief.
Yeah.
Wherever you are.
Wherever your heart is.
Go.
I'm picking out a guitar part with my lead thing.
Dear Mr. President, I want you to know I am deeper than you.
I'm deeper than you.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Oh, you said president.
Yeah, no, he said deeper.
So he's been buried by an enormous.
Hey, if you say president and have jet airplanes, sound effects at the same time are going to take you.
Okay, bad.
Bad.
Thanks.
That's right.
See, that guy was singing about Mr. President.
Then he said, bury.
So the computer said, okay, and sent an Air Force wing toward him to bury him under the radio dirt.
Now we don't want to bother the good folks out there with some of this sordid lowlife.
Let me hold you, little man, as the parade marches by.
Let me hold you, little man, and we'll pretend you can fly.
No.
Flying with a jet plane overhead.
That was Rocknard's protest song.
Little man, you're crying.
All the elevator buttons.
I know why you're blue.
Someone stole your TV.
I stand today for the midget.
Half the size of a regular guy.
You talking about Bob there?
Let me hold you, little man.
What does that mean?
Everyone passes by.
The enemy has run.
Little big man.
Is that low?
Talking about holding the movie?
Cradled in his arms.
No, I don't think it's that part.
He's talking about a body part.
Oh, your God.
Little man.
It's like a little elf.
I'm banging the drum.
Your big day will come when they re-
Make the wizard of Oz.
So let me hold you, midget man.
You pretend that you're lying in space.
You let me in.
So let me talk.
Because you're supposed to call him the little piece.
What if he's just singing about the president?
Oh, he's getting close.
Reverend Sting, did you hear that?
Yes, Mr. President.
Did you hear him?
Yes, I did.
He already played that part.
Yeah.
You're after me, lucky charm.
Little man.
All right.
I thought we weren't going to do the lucky charms.
Put your hands off my little man.
Very impressive.
I mean, the honorable voice.
Please take your hands off my little man.
That's crazy, Tom.
Or sexual harassment outside.
This is what I think of your little man.
He shot him dead.
Take your hands off my little man.
And now we will credit the large.
Thanks to the large for contributing with the hour of slack.
The large is Cleopatra's bar.
Chunks of your money.
The Buzzling Evidence Show.
Yeah.
Ah, Chase.
Here they come now.
I surrendered.
Blow your speakers out.
It's the Buzzling Evidence Show.
Welcome to the show.
Come on down, Buzzling Evidence.
Come on down, Dr. Howe.
Come on down, Milo Drummer.
And our special guest star, I would say.
Come on down, Caller One, Caller Two, Caller Three.
Oh, wait.
Don't call her.
I just want to say I love what you crazy, wonderful,
beautiful kids are doing.
I'm behind you all the way.
When those women in those tube tops run down the aisle,
it's just crazy.
And so the ending recapitulates the beginning.
Thanks to the Buzzling Evidence Show with Dr. Drummond and Dr. Howe,
who, like Dr. G. Gordon Gordon,
will be together again at 50 next day this July,
along with the amino acids, Fat Man D, Andrew the Impaled,
the Evolution Control Committee, Reverend Sam Singleton,
the Atheist Evangelist, the Duke of Ute, DJ Shaver,
the Mutant Mountain Boys, Dr. Legume, Priestess Pisces,
Suds, Tommy Amoeba, the Drive-Ins, the Burnings,
Old Sequa, and we hope Papa Joe Mama.
I should also mention that Dr. Howe, Reverend John Shirley,
and I, all three, now have a regular blog called
Culture Clutch at rawstory.com.
Read all about it at subgenius.com.
And now, accept.
For that URL, your mind will be erased.
Thank you.